Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz, only available
at Bed MDM Casino.
Spin on Spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM in game sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia only, games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal -durable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry. Gambling problem? Call 1 -800 -Gamber.
Firestone Complete Auto Care's epic savings advantage is the sign you need to stop putting off your car's maintenance.
And you can save up to $100 on tires and services while you're at it.
Don't wait, call Firestone Complete Auto Care for an appointment.
This is a headgun podcast.
Hey folks, guess what?
It's Will See You In Hell, your favorite podcast that commentates, discusses and reviews
horror sci -fi and fantasy films. This is Joe de Rosa coming to you live from the
thick uncut dick house and that's Patty Walsh and it's time to get on with the
show and what else Pat? Well I just want to be clear that while I do have a
dick and it is thick it is very much cut. I don't want to let anybody down if my
Nudes get out there and that and by that you mean ripped
My dick is like rip like a very muscular dick
It's gonna six there's veins in it
But I am cut. Let's just be real you Joe
Yeah, I'm snipped snipped
Not in a vasectomy way in a in a in a Jewish way in a Lorraine a Bob it way
Hi, oh, is that a timely joke folks? I bet a
a lot of people listening to the show don't even know who Lorraine and Bob it is.
Who was in more jokes from 1992 to 1999?
Michael Jackson is the only one that could give Lorraine and Bob it a run for her money.
It was Lorraine and Bob it was it was Michael Jackson.
It was Monica Lewinsky.
Sure.
That dress.
Anyway, I'm sitting here sipping a nice little whiskey.
Pat also has a little whiskey.
no, we're not drunk. Get off our backs. We work hard for this. Maybe you're a fucking drunk.
Yeah. You ever think of that? Yeah. Maybe you're throwing out the fucking accusations.
You know what? Maybe I wouldn't drink so much if I didn't have to listen to your god damn nagging
every day. Yeah. Do you know how great is it being off Twitter? Do you ever miss it? Not in not even a
little bit. Right as I was about to follow you off, I realized I got to promote my fucking program
and I can't get off, but I want to be off. I still promote, I just promote through Instagram
and then send it over to Twitter from Instagram. Yeah, but how many people are really clicking on
Instagram on Twitter? I've never done it once in my life. But it goes out as a tweet. Or get a second,
if somebody's tweeting and I see it's like an Instagram link, there's then get a second, not
a million years. They get a second party app that lets you promote. And then you can tweet without
going on to your actual Twitter. I'm going to go ahead and promise you I'm not getting a second
party app. Why? In order to get on to Twitter. I'm jealous. I wish I was off of it. It's a
shit show filled with in our lives. I am way more off of it than I used to be. I do an occasional
check in. I'm horrified and I get off. But it's a good way to kind of get get news. You
know, and I'm not talking about that. It's a terrible way to get news, folks. It's a terrible
way to get news. It's a good way to get one sided alarmist news from either side of the
argument. That's true. It's terrible. It's it's it's a horrid harming. I mean, let's let's be
real. Shuts alarming. Well, but I'm saying like everything delivered to you, whether it's pro
Trump, whether it's anti -Trump, whether it's pro -hillary, whether it's anti -hillary, whether
it's the state of the economy, whether it's the state of investment banking, whether
it's the media, whether everything is turned to an 11 and it's just, it's just not a good
way to get news.
It doesn't make you feel good.
It's people screaming at one another and it's not healthy.
It's not healthy.
It's a sick, sick fucking world.
That's why Joe goes to Breitbart .com
Breitbart .com
For fair and balanced reporting in all fairness in my defense. I stopped reading Breitbart when Steve Bannon left
He was sort of your Walter Cronkite
Steve Bannon I could always call him more of a Katie Kirk, but yeah, I I admire Steve Bannon for
Or, you know, pushing past what we initially thought of him, which is, let's be honest,
this guy got here because of his looks.
And he revealed himself to be deeper and more knowledgeable at every turn.
And not just the sort of sex pot we initially thought he was.
Right, right.
And people said, this man is defending a potential racist.
And he said, no, I'm leaving to go defend a potential pedophile.
Yes.
Exactly.
it's a good time. It's a good time. Hey, folks, you know, as they say in true detective
season two, we get the world we deserve. As I said, whilst watching true detective
season two, when is this over? Folks, folks. Is it time we get on with something, Pat? Yeah,
No, Pat, you failed miserably at your promise to do 90s hit songs.
You don't give me any buildup time.
It's like, do it.
And then I do it like a fucking train monkey.
Here's what I did it like a tugboat and I think people probably enjoyed it.
Here's what I would have done.
Ready?
Give me, let me do it one time.
Please do.
Get on with the show and in fact, we should also get on with the
Jolo, Jolo, Jolo, Jolo, Jolo, Jolo, Jolo, Jolo, Jolo, Jolo, Jolo, Jolo, Jolo.
I am still dreaming of your tits.
What's that song?
It's ever clear.
It's every, ever clear song, gong, gong, gong, gong, gong, gong.
There are nine songs that have that riff.
He was the one, there was that song and there was the one where he's like, me and my black
girl friend.
Yeah.
That was a weird one.
Uh, there is Monica's a great song.
I love Santa Monica.
Um, a great and a terrible city.
I once said to a buddy of mine, I held up the Everclear
greatest hits.
And I said, why don't they just call this gown, gown,
chicken, gown, gown, gown, gown, gown, gown, gown.
It's all they got.
And I often, I often, Santa Monica for me often bleeds into
backwater by the totes.
Those two songs, you could make it make it.
I'm so glad you brought this up again because you brought it up
in the last podcast.
And I just let you go.
I didn't want to interrupt.
In the last pot.
Last time we discussed 90s music, okay, but I knew you're wrong. I just let it go because we were already getting tense
But many people pointed out on Facebook and I present it to you now backwater is a song by the meat puppets
With backwater, sir, and there is something
Oh, yeah, you're right. Cody song is I come from the water
Gail Gail I come from the water. I come from the water. It's called I come from the water song. It's called I come from the water
That's the name of the song it is that's a great song and it's the follow up to Possum Kingdom, which is no I'm talking about the Possum Kingdom song. That is
Gang out that's similar riff. That's the one I'm talking make up your mind. That's the one. I'm talking about this side to walk with me. Yeah,
I always bleed tonight. I always bleed that into Santa Monica if I ever clear. I guess well that it upsets me because the totes are so great and you're
I love it. I'm not shitting on either band. I love calling the wrong toady song backwater.
And you were actually talking about not I come from the water, but possum kingdom.
Yes. And most people know that song as my sweet angel. Yeah. Like the one that I worked karaoke
at this bar in New York, this guy kept requesting sweet angel. And I was like, what are you talking about?
And he meant possum kingdom which is should not be the name of the song. That's song about vampires
It'd be a good song for Joe scary stuff. It is a vampire show because I was gonna say it's just talking about like a
Murt is he's like murdering a body or dumping the vampire. It's a very cool song very cool song
And a great band and I've also recently started to listen to a lot of the meat puppets
But backwater was there a big hit, but it was a big hit because Cobain started
Referencing them all the time my dear friend Dan Weinstein and I
We'll often play a game called, well, never really had a name, but we basically, it's
basically Arosmith Megamix, and it's that you can, every Arosmith ballad is interchangeable
with another Arosmith ballad, and you can just do a mega mix of all of them.
So we would go outside of sweet emotion and dream on.
I prefer, at least in the later years of Arosmith, I prefer the ballads to the rock song.
we would go we would go jaded love that song yeah we would go I'm crying because I
left you you're amazing angel baby yeah they can say way into another pretty easily yeah
jaded is it's definitely the last great aerosmith song but it's a really really
strong melody for people that made in their career what jaded is which one was
right? Now pat, you've often said, that's a great song. You've often said in musical
arguments, not just arrowsmith debates, musical debates in general, that I don't want to
miss a thing is not only the best Irishman song, but the greatest song ever recorded.
You've said that many times. I've never said that Joe, but I do love the song and I
remember the summer I started dating my high school girl friend your sweetheart
old sweetie piece she's married with like nine children now but she wanted our
song if I remember correctly to be what it became I'll be by Edwin McCain
Yeah, it's a terrible song by Edward McCain, a huge hit at the time.
And the other huge hit, but it had just become a hit, was I don't want to miss a thing
from the Armageddon soundtrack.
That song is terrible.
You like that song?
It's terrible, but they were the two big love songs that summer that we started dating.
And she kind of was like, I want it to be this one or this one.
And I was like, they're both so bad.
And we went with Albi, which was good because it didn't get so overplayed, because obviously
that movie was huge that year.
And in fact, I used to work at the West all of 16 cinema as an usher.
And when people were getting out of Armageddon that summer, I would wave to them as they left
and say, hurry up guys, my Armageddon tired.
Oh God and I tell you Joe these people laughed like you wouldn't believe I don't believe you my
Armageddon tired. I don't believe you anyway
Had a had a lovely relationship with that young woman and our song became I'll be
Joe do you have you ever been with anyone long enough to have a song?
No, but I did I did once request
that that girl is dating that our song be on bended knee by boys to men
oh god give me a reason she said no and then i said well how about motown
philly and she said yes motown philly back no i never had a song with me i've
never dated anybody more than i don't know maybe six seven weeks
uh how do you how do you do it no i know i went nine months with somebody once but
we didn't have a song uh we had more of uh
A daily fight.
No, we didn't.
I remember she loved that song by God.
Now I'm going to play.
I can't remember.
So I'm shit fucking song.
She always liked.
I was like, I don't like that song.
And she'd get upset with me.
And I'd go listen to bad religion.
Slam the door.
Just want to be your last girlfriend, right?
No, not my last.
I'm kidding. I wouldn't slam the door or go listen to bad religion. What was the song? Oh, Silver Sun pickups
That's what songs you loved
Silver Sun that band Silver Sun pickups. Oh, you mean that the one that was like a smash and pumpkins rip off that
Yeah, it kind of sounded like yeah that 1979
Yeah, but I don't remember what the chorus was. I just remember the verse was like
The chorus was the was the was the most questionable part the chorus just went come come come come come
all over the room. No, it just shoot your come on the lamp and the walls. That can't be right.
Why is this? Why are these the lyrics folks to this silver sun pickup song?
It's a wild wild bit. Anyway, Pat, it's good to see you. I hope you're doing well. I'm doing fine.
It's the holiday season. Of course, you probably noticed that since it's 87 degrees outside
and sunny. So why wouldn't it be the holiday season? It's a real shit. LA during the holidays,
real shit time. I found myself going over to the Grove just to get some sort of semblance
of like lights and music. Yeah. Yeah. It's a fucking Grove, the most empty, empty place in perhaps
all of Los Angeles. I never go to the Grove. I just go to the America. Outside of some of these
Zachary's head's folks.
I only go to the Americana.
I don't, the grove is too far.
And it's the same thing.
Yeah, you know what I mean?
The, the, the Armenian grove is the, uh, the Americana.
But you find that empty, you mean emotionally or physically?
I find it just to be like a big mall, you know, but like they,
they manage to somehow get a little more spirit than other parts of LA.
This big like consumer dump.
They make it snow every night. They make it snow. They have the lights and you know, it feels colder when you're there for some reason.
Nothing. Look, a mall feels like Christmas time. That's right. A mall always feels like Christmas time. That's right.
Which I like, you know, we used to do a mall crawl every December 22nd, me and my buddies,
through the King of Pressure Mall in Pennsylvania. We'd hit every bar in the mall, which you'd be
be fucking surprised at how many there were, right?
Corn dog on a stick bar, the steak escape bar.
It was the best.
It was, it was, it was so pretzels.
It was a really, you know, we would always say, you know,
the mall Christmas time is just,
it's there's something that you get you in the spirit.
Orange juice can bar, you know.
All right, Pat, you know, do you ever think I've had enough?
Everything I've put up with enough, do you ever think?
Maybe it's time to give Joe a break. Let him fucking have a breath for once.
Does that ever occur to you? No.
So let's head over to Pat's movie corner. I need to get some ice. So you started off.
go for it. Folks, I watched an old sitcom that I had bought years ago and just started
tearing through it. And I watched seasons one and two. I had a real nice time. I like
watching a sitcom from the beginning. You can watch it evolve and grow in the character's
shape and et cetera. And the show was called Norm. At first, the Norm show, and then it became
Norm and season two, Norma McDonald's short -lived sitcom.
And I watched it when I was in high school, I hadn't seen it since.
My dear friend Ian Gomez, who was on my show, was in it.
The great Laurie Metcalfe justly discussed in the possible best supporting actress race
this year for Lady Bird is also in it.
And Max Wright, the dad from Alf, who was caught in a meth den with male prostitutes near
the end of his career and rear end at a cop car while drunk on champagne. This was the
dad on Alph. Anyway, he's in it as the boss. And I got to tell you folks, especially in
season two, this is a very funny show that was like playing by the rules of a sitcom
basically. But then they would say that you could tell they were like, we'll play the
game over here. But then we're going to slip in some of the weirdest, darkest jokes you've
ever seen on network television. And I thought that the show was extremely funny in spots
and that norm should obviously do more sick comes. He's a delight. He can make anything
funny. I urge you to check it out. It's also cheap on Amazon. I reference news radio.
It's nowhere near that good. How much is the enormous set on Amazon?
That's about 30 bucks. Wow, and for what two seasons three three. All right, my 10 bucks
of season. That's not bad. The second season's great. And they get good gas like Jack
Warden who was in dirty work and all, you know, like a lot of funny people. If I'm not mistaken,
then for Norm McDonald's lips to my ears. Oh, the one time I met him,
he was a delightful man. The, uh, that was the final appearance of Richard Pryor. That's
on anything barely speaks yeah yeah yeah so all right I gotta I gotta you know I watched it
when it was on but I don't really remember yeah it's it's no classic folks and especially the first
season you're gonna be like I don't know if I want to even stick this out but by two they're having
a lot of fun and a chose and I liked it and they bring it already lying season two oh nice oh
I've already I have I've got a couple rewatches for the movie corner this week I rewatched a film
called 976 Evil, which was Robert England's directorial debut. I think it might have been
the only thing he directed, and I can't remember. But anyway, they released a special edition
Blu -ray of it. I got it on Amazon for like $12 or something, and it's the original theatrical
cut and also the home video version. I'd only ever seen the home video version, so I watched
the, uh, Fox used to scare me at the video store. It's a creepy box. Now 976 evil. It is not,
I would not call it a good movie, but it is fun. It's enjoyable. It makes virtually no sense.
But the saving grace of the film is, and I'm blanking on his name, but the kid from heaven
helped us and he plays evil ad in the original Friday night. He's the star. That kid is fucking
incredible. Like it's, it's, I want to, I want to, William Ragsdale? No, it's, I'm gonna,
I'm blanking and I don't feel like. Bill Ragsdale. It's not Bill Ragsdale. Anyway, he's just great
in it. He's great at playing weird offbeat characters. He's really enjoyable. Also, the lady,
and again, I'm blanking on a name, the lady from who's afraid of Virginia Wolf places, like bible
thumping mom, she's great.
Elizabeth Taylor.
No, the young blonde who's afraid of Virginia Woolf.
Sandy Dennis.
Yes.
She plays the Bible thumping mom.
That bald guy from Nickelodeon shows up at one point.
Bald guy from Nickelodeon.
What is this?
He was like the older bald guy that was...
You have to mention it?
That was on like all the sketch shows.
I never knew the guys.
Now, I don't know the fucking guy's name.
He looks kind of like an older David Cross kind of a vibe.
No clue.
Anyway, it's a fun movie with it on square one.
Yeah, it was like, yeah, one of those fucking things.
Robert Piccardo?
Yes.
Are you aware of how good I am and how little respect I get?
I mean, I didn't even look that up in my phone.
Some call it good.
Some would say it's psychotic, Pat.
About a Piccardo.
Yeah, I used to read the Leonard Molten's movie guide.
Or like the cable guy.
You're like the cable guy.
That's literally the point that you're at.
where I stepped, I don't try to kill anybody.
Not that I've seen.
Not that you've seen.
I wouldn't be surprised though if I woke up
and you were standing over my bed one night.
I wouldn't be shocked.
Master bed.
I would hope so.
I mean, if you're gonna go through all that trouble,
at least give me something.
Let me get some out of it.
Sure, sure.
Anyway, it's a fun flick.
If you like it, it's campy old, you know, 80s horror.
It's, you know, it's funny because when I was watching it
And this never dawned on me till this last watch.
You know, these movies come out nowadays where it's like about like, I watch this horror
movie on Netflix and I can't remember the name of it.
I can't remember anything.
Wow.
But it's about a horror.
It's about an app that like makes your worst fears come to life and then it kills you
whenever.
Yeah.
It's okay.
But I just was like, oh, you know, this is like what people do now, like they find a thing
that's popular and they go, well, let's make a hard move about that. And it's funny when I was
watching 976 evil. I was like, oh, this was like the app hard movie for the 80s because the 976
numbers were big. It's a sex line that, no, it's a horror scope line. But it's fun. And there's
some good deaths. It's a great scene where he goes to a poker game that these bullies that
fuck with him all the time host and he's killed two of them and he goes up and he goes can
I enter the game with a pair of hearts and like pulls out the two hearts. That's a
cool scene. It's fun. It's goofy and fun and it doesn't make any fucking sense, but I
enjoyed it. So there you go. I watched a little picture called Adams Family Values. David
I remember seeing it the day before Thanksgiving,
when I was probably 13 years old, and loving it.
I loved the original, and I just kind of forgot
about the franchise, and I was like,
oh, I'll give it a minute, it's on Amazon.
I'd tell you, at least for the first half,
this thing's got some of the darkest, best jokes.
It was a fucking amazing comedy.
It loses its way in the last half, for sure.
or John Cusack takes over it.
I love John Cusack, but she's trying to marry Fester for his money.
Okay.
Well, that's weird.
You never see Cusack in like an underhanded role.
She's, she's always playing like a very sweet and real bitch.
Yeah, yeah, that's weird.
But especially for the first half, I mean, these jokes are so funny.
And they're, you couldn't do it today.
They're trying, they're actively trying Wednesday and Pugsley
to kill this baby for the entire movie.
They're putting knives above its bed. They're trying to decapitate the baby.
Well, Christopher Lloyd, who played Fester, has often said in interviews that the Adam
Sound of the Values was really a heightened commentary on the abortion argument.
Really?
I don't know if you knew that.
Yeah.
No, I didn't.
It's about abortion.
Lloyd is great in it. Julie is great in it. Houston's great in it.
Yes.
Um, and I love both both the pictures. Now the first one had the Adams groove. That's what made me think about watching it. The MC Hammer songs
We were singing on the last episode. Well, they do what they do want to do what they want to see. Yeah, yeah, so stupid that song. And then apparently on the second one
Michael Jackson
Was supposed he recorded a song called for called like it's spooky or something
Then he got in all that trouble and then they added a joke into the movie where crumb holds steps into this cabin
and screams, like, ah, do you think somebody's about to kill him?
And they look up and it's a poster of Michael Jackson.
Wow.
And he's playing like a nine year old boy.
Yeah, and Kremel's is like 10 years old in the movie.
Yeah, right.
He's playing a nine year old boy.
Yeah, he's not a nine year old boy.
So, well, but the way you said it, it sounded like he was 35,
portraying a nine year old.
It's like he actually is like nine or 10 or whatever.
Oh, there's all these jokes about murder and the baby dying.
At one point, they whip up a hair of the pup
like a hangover cure for the baby the baby sitting there in sunglasses like
he got wasted the night before and he's hung over like there's weird jokes dark
jokes what did he do the night before the the assumption is that he's hung
over there making him you know a hangover mix in the morning she to the baby
went on a bender for that's the implication why why though it's just a joke
joke you you wouldn't like this movie if you're gonna ask that I just don't get
whipped to the I don't get the bit but but at the end since they didn't have the
Michael Jackson song, here's what here's what happens the second the credits role of this
like very classy well done movie credits go like this, whoop, Adam's family, there it is,
whoop, oh boy, Adam's family, there it is, I couldn't believe my ears.
And is it whoop, it's the whoop, there it is guys, I assume it was text.
Speaking of which we reviewed justice week a little while, our justice league a little
a while back. Yeah. And you said we just weak a better name. Sorry about a week ago,
two weeks, whatever was weak. It was fine. Uh, you, we talked about Boo. Yeah. Yeah.
Cyborg. Right. And you said, you, you made the joke, he should have said, boom, there
it is. Yeah. I talked to a friend of mine who also is black. Okay. And I said, I thought
it was weirdly racially uncomfortable that they had cyborg say Boo. Yeah. And he said, no,
he says that in the comics. That's like his catchphrase. So I was like, all right, well,
I'm glad they just didn't throw that in. So that's still weird. Yeah. You know, I don't know.
But my point is is apparently it was a thing. I love to have some values. And the best part is
I remembered it very vividly from my childhood. There's supposed to be doing the the Thanksgiving
play for all the parents of like, you know, the first Thanksgiving and Wednesday and crumbles and
and Pugsley all flip it on them and they're like,
we're the Indians and then it's like,
you thought you could take our land, bitch.
And they burn this place to the ground and the Indians win.
And they're like, they go through this whole thing
of like our ancestors are forced to work in casinos
and drink too much alcohol while your ancestors
sit and get rich and play golf.
It was like very, very pointed shit.
They go, I imagine like Native Americans cheering this
because it was like really great.
Yeah, that's, that's pretty great.
Then they start shooting flaming arrows
at the camp counselors who are Christine Buransky
and Peter McNichol from Ghostbusters 2.
I love Peter McNichol.
Christine Buransky is, she was in, she's in men,
both finger, right?
That's right.
Yeah, I love her in both finger.
I do too.
They are turning those two over a flaming spit.
These two are playing camp counselors?
Camp counselors.
They're 40 years old at the time this film came out.
That's right.
They were a little younger, but yes, when the scene ends, they are roasting them on a
spit that they are tied to with flames licking their body and they're screaming while bound
and gagged.
The kids are turning them on a spit.
And then Wednesday walks over to the little blonde girl who was playing like the head pilgrim.
Now tied to a stake with rags all around her, soaked in kerosene, and Wednesday strikes
a match as the scene ends. Presumably killing Jesus Christ, her friend. And I loved it. I loved
it. I was very impressed by how dark it was. Dark sequel. That's like babe too. Pigg in the city
is very dark. It's very dark. Yeah. There's that whole plot with Mickey Rooney being the magician that
like has enslaved animals and like it's it's it's it's dark stuff. Yeah. I got I got a joke like
that in my show of Tony Rocks talking about how he likes church girls and things like they're not
so churchy at home. And then Jay goes, oh, I got you, babe in the streets, babe too pig in the city
and the sheets. And I put it in the table. I put it in at the table read because you get like five
chances to like see a script performed right. And at the table read, I was like, no, he's going to laugh
at this right and it kind of got this like weird rolling laugh where people like kept laughing for
the next minute so I kept it in but I was like I guarantee the room of writers I was like this
will never be on the show it's too stupid it's too strange and then sure enough went up on the
night of the show got a big laugh and then we gave Tony the the black guy there he goes what about me
makes you think that I I would understand that reference and then another huge laugh and I was like
This joke is gonna stay in the fucking show. That's very funny babe to pick. I can't believe that many people got that reference
I guess it was very big one an Oscar. I think it was no babe. Yeah, but if you just say babe in the sheet
No one no one's going to the pig movie
Sure, yeah, plus babe to pick in the city was a notorious flop
Yes lost millions and millions of it. It's not a bad film. I hate it. I saw it on the theater. Why'd you hate it?
Too dark. Yeah, I just
I wasn't willing to go on that journey with babe. I didn't love babe that much to go on this journey.
I never saw babe one. I've only seen babe two.
Well, babe one's delightful movie.
It's, it's, it's a little too childish for me, I think.
Okay.
But I don't know. Babe two is childish too. It was dark for.
Yeah, it wasn't, it wasn't returned to Oz dark.
No, you know, no.
All right.
I have one more for Pat's movie corner.
I saw again, it's a rewatch, but we've never talked about it on the podcast, but I watched.
Actually, you know what? I'm not going to do another rewatch. I'm going to do a new thing that I did see.
Trailer Park, boys. Finally, started watching the trailer.
Never seen it. I'm embarrassed to say I'd never really seen it either.
I've heard, forever, from a ton of people about how funny it is, how great it is.
I'd never really watched it. Finally, like sat down and started watching the new season.
and hilarious, it's great.
The new season is funny.
It's like season 18, literally season 11, I think.
Okay.
It's really funny.
They're really funny.
I want to go back now and experience the entire show.
I'm excited to have discovered a new thing
that I can now trudge through and get to see from front to back.
So that's going to be fun, man.
And, you know, all I say is this,
The Bubbles, who was the guy with the big, thick glasses, who's like sort of, I feel like
the poster boy for Trailer Park Boys.
They did an in -character interview on Kimmel to promote the new show.
And Kimmel says at the end of the interview he says, you've had a lot of celebrities in
this newest season.
That must be very exciting.
and bubbles puts his finger straight up into the air like this as index finger
strip of the air and he goes oh yeah it was exciting my bird was doing that which
destroyed me I was like that's so fucking funny and he just kept sticking his
finger up to the air gone my bird was doing that it was doing that my bird and I was
It's like, that's really fucking funny and stupid
and immature and I love it.
So they just like, sit around or are there stories
to the show?
Well, this season, I'm assuming they've done this before.
Again, I've never watched it.
But this season, it's sort of like a road rules kind of thing
where it's like, they're in America.
It's called out of the park.
And they're in America.
And they have to do, like, these tasks.
Like, they travel around and they have to do tasks.
and then they incorporate clearly like real people into the stuff a little bit it's scripted and
everything but like they will go into a bar and you can tell like they're actually talking to a
waitress or a waiter or whatever and that person's actually reacting you know so it's got a little
bit of a baradish feel but it's just a funny show man it's it's they're endearing characters the one
was an influence for Danny McBride
with Eastbound and Down.
There's the one guy like it is Kenny Powers.
Like in my opinion, like it's like, you know,
he wears the gold chain outside of the T -shirt,
the fucking like ridiculous white shirt,
crazy pointed sideburns, go T, loves weed.
Like, so I think it was probably like a little bit
of an inspiration for Danny McBride.
Which is cool, I love Danny McBride.
This is a Canadian program.
Yes.
But I enjoyed it, man.
I thought it was really funny,
and I look forward to seeing their very irreverent,
which I like.
You know, these three dudes is a crew.
They have a new show called like the,
the drunk and drugged up party hour or something,
where it's like a sketch show.
And it's like, I watched a thing about that,
and they were like, you guys have done,
And it's them playing black people, it's them playing Chinese people, it's them doing drug
humor, it's them doing sex humor, it's them cursing, it's them doing, it's like, I kind
of liked that they're like kind of a reverent and they seem like nice dudes and they're just
like, yeah, we just kind of do whatever we think is funny.
Reminds me of it's always sunny, it's quite frankly.
It's that kind of thing.
How are they playing people of other races?
with makeup. And they've got no flak. Well, they live in Canada. I don't know
maybe they have, but that's the kind of the point. Look, it's always
Saturday getting any flak when they were dressed up as Danny Glover doing
the, because I think if there's there is some weird thing that you can do where
if you do it right and it's funny enough, yeah, people are like, ah, they're
joke and they don't, they, they, they don't mean any harm.
Big ol' risk.
It is. Well, I mean, that's, it's always sunny to do that whole episode where they turned
black for the whole episode.
Yeah. That's true.
So, look, whether you...
Well, I myself know a black lady who really, really did not care for that episode.
Well, sure. But I mean, here's my point.
Whether you, whether you agree with that or not, or whether you approve of that or not.
Yeah.
Uh, and I mean that for any, any, somebody playing a Chinese guy,
at whatever the hell it is.
Well, I appreciate the time elephant in the room
to tell everyone I was just cast as Mulan
in Disney's live action.
And also you helped fund the trouble with the poo.
I did, yes.
Look, obviously, and I can tell you this
by the amount of people I know that don't agree
with blackface, but are also furiously annoyed
at the trouble with the poo documentary.
Okay. Uh, there are clearly right ways and wrong ways to do things. Uh, and there are
right ways and wrong ways to do humor. And I think humor always comes down to, is it funny
or is it not? People are mad now about the Simpson's portrayal of a poo. No, they're mad
about the documentary. Yeah. Like this is, this is the argument now. Like, you know, so it's,
um, look again, like I'm not taking anybody's side. I'm saying, I did see that documentary.
You did. I know you told me about it, Pat my point is that was so short. I felt like I hadn't seen the whole movie
But I did it was like 40 minutes long. I'm just saying
Whether you agree with the joke or not. I agree I like when humorous or taking risks
I appreciate that because you could say about a million and one people that have done things that weren't racial but perhaps of sexual
a comedic sexual nature, or a comedic drug nature, or drink, or whatever the hell it is,
like there are people that get offended and the people that don't.
And I like when people are taking some risks out there, and my favorite comics take some
really crazy fucking risks, so it's gonna be a lot less of that going forward.
Yeah, so I don't know, that's just how I feel.
I hear you. I hear you.
I hear you.
Talk through this pack because I think vintage our friend Vince just showed up
I got to let him in but just keep talking pet. I have a Friday the 13th Blu -ray set that I bought for like 40 bucks on the Warner
Brothers lot and it's all the movies including Freddie versus Jason
dogs barking
Hey Vince
Now I never opened this thing, but when we reviewed Freddie verse Jason on the show I opened it and Joe me opening that box set
cost me about $1 ,000 because I just found out that the set is out of print and going for
an outrageous amount of money.
I opened it to watch Freddie versus Jason for this podcast.
This is my problem with you.
It's your greed.
When is it ever enough?
Joe, when is the money ever enough?
Why do you feel the need?
Nine hundred and fifty dollars.
I would have fucking died.
Why do you feel the need?
Who would?
And I'll tell you folks, does you at home that don't know this about Pat?
And I'll tell you this about Pat.
I don't care.
I'll put it out there. He says things like I'm gonna gouge these poor fucks. That's he says stuff like that
He goes fuck him if they knew anything they wouldn't be poor. He says things like this
And then he who are the poor fucks? I'm claiming to be gouging. I don't know. It's just funny
No, but I opened it and I put it up online. I'm selling my used copy of it now for like $400
$400 and that's you I could have bought this goddamn thing for like 80 bucks. You should have bought it
I didn't know it went out of print and I hit a real sweet spot with it
But I was like maybe I'll try to watch all the Friday 13's before I sell it and I watch the first one and I said
Oh, no, here's why I've never seen any of the other ones from the jump
This is a ship franchise. It's a shitty movie. It's a shit and I'm glad you feel the same
Do you feel that any of them are even slightly above average?
Uh, I will say, uh, absolutely.
Friday the 13th, too, is where it kind of kicks in.
I will then I'll wash that tonight.
Uh, Friday the 13th, one is a really boring setup.
It's so boring.
Uh, what I liked what they did.
So for those of you that don't know, the first front of the 13th, Jason Voorhees,
the boy that was deformed and bullied died at Crystal Lake because the camp
counselors were being irresponsible 20 years later or whatever the hell it is
he's back for revenge he's killing camp counselors and whatnot and then at
the end of the movie you find out it's not Jason Voorhees it's not a super
natural zombie situation it's his mother killing camp counselors for revenge
to, you know, to, to bring a, to a vent, to a vent your son.
And then in the last moments, the only really cool part of the movie,
which is, well, aside from Kevin Bacon getting killed on the bed.
That's a great kill. But aside from that, the only other cool part in the movie
in my opinion is Jason's, you know, zombie body jumping out of the lake at the very end.
Very cool. But here's the thing. I always remember that as the final
seen in the movie and it is awesome. Yeah. But then there's the fucking, it was all a dream
and she's in the fucking hospital bed after that. Right. Now, they couldn't even get the ending
right. They get this great ending like the fury which we talked about on last week's show.
They understood that if two telekinesis having people square off and one causes the other one to
to explode using only her mind,
that that's the time to wrap up the picture.
Let me save you some time.
Front of the 13th gives us this tacked on shit prologue.
And does that woman come back even?
Why do we need it?
Is she some beloved plucky air?
She's in the second one.
But that's why, that's one of the things that Jamie Lee.
Curtis.
That's one of the things I liked about the front of the 13th remake.
was that in the cold open they do the they tell the entire story of the first
movie right and then show like oh the mom what it's what it's owed yeah the mom's
dead but now Jason actually is back that's a really really great way to open
the movie but it's yeah I agree with you dude I can't disagree I Friday the
13th is not a great film. I, in fact, own the top 100 horror movies book by Fantastic
Press. Now, Braggar, there's shit in this book that I absolutely do not agree with.
Mainly their number one choice and, quite frankly, their number one hundred choice. But I
will say, the one thing I do agree with in the book is, or one of the things I do agree
with them the list is that Friday the 13th is not on it.
Yeah.
And I think a lot of people would include it in their lists
out of obligation.
Say, oh, you got to include it.
No, I don't even get the mask in this first one.
I assume that's introduced in two.
Well, he does potato sack in two,
which is scarier than the hockey mask.
Okay.
Because it gives it like an elephant man vibe.
Sure.
Which makes it more disturbing for some reason.
All right.
Hockey mask comes in in three.
I'll try to watch them all.
I got a two, two is good.
Three's fine, four's fine, five sucks.
I love six.
Six is a fun, like romp.
Jason comes back from the dead, he gets struck by lightning, it's goofy, it's fun.
It was a five was supposed to be the end, well four was supposed to be the end, then
they did five, but it wasn't Jason and five, it was somebody pretending to be Jason.
And so then when they did six, it was called Jason lives and they actually brought Jason back.
And there's a scene, you know, it's very self -effacing. There's a scene where there's a grave digger
filling in Jason's empty grave and he goes, he goes digging up Jason Voorhees. Who the hell would want
to think that was a good idea? You know, like it's fun. It's very fun. Seven is great as well, which is
is direct continuation of six.
After that, they get pretty, aside from some fun kills,
I can't really go to bat for the quality of it.
Which one of those Jason takes Manhattan?
That's eight.
Okay.
It's got its moments, sure.
Jason goes to hell is, in my opinion, dog shit.
Jason X, which is the space one, not a good movie,
but fun, the coolest Jason kill I've ever seen
where he puts a woman's head in liquid nitrogen in her head freezes and then he smashes it on the
countertop and her and like a like head slurpy
splatters everywhere. That's pretty cool. But I mean that being said, it's not a good movie. It's
entertaining. Much like 976 evil. So Jason born. Now Pat, that's not related. And this is what I don't
like when you do this nonsense stuff, well, shit. I mean, the, how did this become one
of the classic horror franchises when there's not a, not a classic amongst them?
Well, I mean, it's look, it was, it was an early slasher film. It came out the first,
I think the first one came 80. First one's 80. The goal was to rip off Halloween, explicitly
stated in the documentary. Um, I don't know. I don't know. I mean, it's like, look, I've
never been that impressed with the saw movies. They're about to release soft or they did
release. Also, it's out 10 or whatever the fuck it was. Like, you know, some of these things
just catch on and people, whatever is at this point, the man so old, he's just making
jigsaw puzzles. Just 90 minutes of a man making a jigsaw puzzle, folks.
Aizen, gentlemen. Um, it's, I don't know, it's for some reason.
They can't look. There were, there were five final destination movies.
It's like, yeah, you know, I remember the first two being awesome.
They were okay. They were fine. They weren't like cool.
shit. Folks, you can find me on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh. You can find me
in the club with a body full of Bob Mama. I got what you need. Sure. As always. And my television
show Living Biblically premieres on Monday, February 26th after the Winter Olympics at 9 .30
p .m. check it out joderosa comedy on instagram and twitter
penhouse column you let me down check it out and we will talk to you soon folks