I'm here for Bet Rivers online casino and sportsbook with poker icon Phil Helmuth.
And now thanks to the excitement of Bet Rivers, I'm also a slots icon.
That's great! And a same game, Parley icon.
Cool, cool. A Blackjack icon, a Moneyline icon,
A Roulette icon. Take it from Phil Helmuth.
If you love games, Bet Rivers is the place to play in Bet.
Bet Rivers. Games on.
Must be 21 plus in present in West Virginia.
Void were prohibited. Terms in conditions apply.
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gambling.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October,
if your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 -plus gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberler, often not available in those days
terms apply, see Phenatic Sports Book App.
There's a new podcast app that delivers chilling true crime stories straight to your
mobile device every day.
They release a new episode that investigates the gruesome true acts of America's war
serial killers, and you can explore into the minds of psychopaths and murderers.
To get started, find and download Murder Minute from the App Store or visit murderminute .com.
That's M -U -R -D -E -R -M -I -N -U -T -E dot com to get your daily dose of true crime, creeping
is delivered straight to your mobile device.
It's a cool to show!
How do you, motherfuckers?
Welcome to We'll See You In Hell.
Woohoo!
It's time to rope a dope around some horror flicks and sci -fi films.
And afterwards, we'll get some colds ass burrela and wash it down with a slap -a -go -fuck -yourself.
And now on with the boys, along the ranch.
Smooth as silk.
I've never been smooth.
youth. Folks, let's get on with the show and at the same time on with the holiday
Joe ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho ho
back. So this is our second beer of the afternoon. Before we go to a bar with Vince Avril.
This is what people, this is when you know you and your friends might have an issue. Vince
is like, Hey guys, I see they're serving hamburgers at this part of the day. We should go
try them out. It's like, yeah, we can get burgers anywhere. But we're like, that sounds
fun Vince okay let's go try these burgers well I now am under so much extreme
duress during the week that the weekend comes and I have to kind of get out
of my head I do not allow myself to drink or indulge during the week I can't
work the schedule I'm working and also be hungover or whatever else so I'm you
know as a lover boy I believe used to sing everybody's working for the weekend
That's right. I myself I'm doing the same and as they said in the film lover boy
Patrick Dempsey I'm gonna go fuck this old lady for pizza money
I used to watch the movie all the time on channel 11 edited and I could even crank one out to it
Edited I'll tell you that it is it is it is my fantasy that was my fantasy growing up like like gorgeous older women
like paying this teen kid dev sex with them and like yeah I was like this is
amazing man those movies were a dime a dozen you can't even find a movie anymore
about paying a young boy to fucking old lady and I think it's a shame you can't
find a movie about pizza anymore either that's true yeah yeah the Ninja Turtles was
probably the last big franchise about pizza well what I wouldn't say that was
about pizza. To me, it was. You thought it was a metaphor for pizza? I thought I think
everything's a metaphor for pizza, folks. Today we're talking about tails from the hood.
I think an unjustly underrated film that we'll get to later on, but one of many tails from
places. Yes. People like when the tails come from a place. The dogs just like stand -alone tails.
Yeah, I know the porch. Yeah, the hood, the deep on American tail. Yeah, the tails have to come from a place. Yeah, where are you getting these tails? That's the big question.
I even know where the tails are coming from. I couldn't give answer tails about where these tails are. I lost it. I lost it. Um, I watched Seinfeld the other night on a cold bear. Okay.
boy it was making me laugh for it's he still makes me laugh really still makes me
laugh he doesn't give a fuck who doesn't make me laugh who did for years is
Colbert yeah I know it's too repetitive it's like I mean it's in a weird way I
bet Seinfeld is 20 years older than Colbert and he seems younger yeah
bear feels like one of your dad's friends now I guess it's probably this fucking
CBS that he's on but but Seinfeld did the hungry man bit yeah which I
I love, I love the hungry man.
He goes, he goes, every box says hungry man.
Yeah.
Because they were at the meeting going,
all right, we're not going to do anything
about the quality of the food.
We've established that.
Let's focus on marketing.
Yeah, very funny.
I, for a long time, my Instagram was basically
just like comments on advertising.
When Instagram started,
and I would always do it in a sign -filled voice in my head.
My favorite was that it was like got HIV and it was three chimps like covering their eyes, their ears, and their mouth, and neon background and said you probably got it from one of us.
No, I was just like, you know, like the marketing executive comes in the meeting and it's like guys, what billboard image do you think would really convey the horrors of the AIDS virus and then everyone around the table in unison goes neon chimps.
I love the man and I am a fan he's the kind of guy who like old people will occasionally
start to build up a little backlash for but the backlash is just because he has so much
money.
He's funny as fuck.
And I always say too, when somebody goes somebody goes, oh, that style is so dated where
I go, yeah.
So is Sinatra.
Yeah.
You're allowed to have comedy from different eras that echo of a different time.
It's good. They don't play jazz music on the radio anymore. Does it mean a new band playing jazz music or modern
Man playing jazz music sucks. Well, yes
Come on all you know all modern jazz sucks. That was a bad example. No, I'm saying if they're playing like this the the classic classic jazz
I'm not talking about like
Do -do -do -do -do -do -do -do -do -do -do I don't mean that kind of shit. Ken G. Let me ask you this. Do you think Kenny G would have been
successful. He had gone by Kenji. I think people would have gotten confused and thought that he was
some sort of Asian man or a brother of Benji, the beloved pooch. Yes, we're an Asian Benji.
Not even a reaction from Con when I said Benji, you should have parked right up. Let me just
clarify. Is Cona Benji? I think so. Yeah. I don't mean anything against the fine people of Asia.
Yeah, you're saying Kenji sounds like an Asian name.
I feel like there was a Asian animated film
years ago called Kenji.
Or what was that?
Kubo and the two strings.
That was Kamal Nanjiani.
That movie was called.
It was about a young, beautiful young woman
whose dream was to be on TV and had to dress as a man to do so.
Okay.
No, because that movie's about how she wants to,
I know the movie you're talking about, huh?
Kubo and the two strings is that what I'm thinking? No, you're talking with the Disney movie where the girl has to dress up as a guy so she can fight
That's Mulan. Isn't that what you're talking about? No. I was talking about Kubo and that's why I was making the joke that he had to dress up as a man
I got you to go on TV Mulan and by the way, why not move man? She's dressing up like a man
folks
Yeah, we're talking about tales from the hood before we get there
I'd love to take you over to path movie corner. If I may and I
You know, I'm doing all things from over the hiatus because I haven't watched anything in a while, but I
Watched on HBO the Tom Cruise Doug Lyman directed vehicle American made. I love that movie. I thought it was great
Very cool very fun very well done
I mean, Cruz doesn't have a lot of fucking misses.
Oh, he's very good.
You know, like it was, it's, I guess Lyman also did edge of tomorrow.
It's not that good, but it's a very entertaining movie.
And really a perfect like Sunday afternoon HBO goes if you have HBO check it out.
And when the hook of the movie becomes, he's done so much illegal shit.
He wants to go to jail because he's going to get killed if he's not in jail.
when the hook is fully realized you know he's in the court hearing in the last
like 20 minutes and they're like you're free to go and he's like I'm free to
get like yeah because he's just begging to be arrested yeah it's very funny it's
a very funny movie good moment yeah I enjoyed it I rewatched my two for this
week are rewatches I rewatched young guns I have not seen that movie since it was
new never seen either of the young guns pictures it made me realize
How awesome of an actor Emilio Estevez is always liked him. He's awesome. He's really really good. I'm like Gordon Bombay, baby
Huh Gordon Bombay who the hell is Gordon Bombay coach Bombay of the mighty ducks. Oh, I never saw the mighty ducks really
Yeah, I was like 15 when it came out. I'm gonna go watch a bunch of nine -year -olds play hockey
It's really good. I'm sure it is it opens with people forget this Emilio Estevez Gordon Bombay
getting a DWI. Oh really? And the cop comes up and he goes,
breath, blood, or urine, and estimates goes, no, thank you,
I just ate. It's funny. It's a very funny movie.
Young guns is a great, you know, it's a, it's a loose biopic
about Billy the Kid. They sit, some historians have said it's
actually the most accurate depiction of the events that
supposedly happened in his life. Now who are these historians?
I read it on Wikipedia because name was Jake something Jake and the fat man
But but it's a fun movie. It's an awesome fun movie. You know, Lou diamond Phillips Charlie Sheen
Are they all playing figures of the day real figures?
Well, one guy is actually Pat Garrett, but the other guys. I don't think we're actually like key for Southern place
This guy doc something, but it's not doc holiday. Okay
So I don't think so. I think it's sort of like this is just a gang of guys he was running with. Did Bon
Jovi do this music for Bolthor just for the second? Lays of Glory. Yeah. So it's a lot of fun.
In a blaze of jewelry. And a bonus. A Jonas. A bonus, Jonas. And you're really rooting for them in
the movie. Yeah. That was the most interesting part of the film to me was it and I didn't remember
the suspect of it. It doesn't, you know, hear about Billy the kid, all you think is
always the kid that killed all these people. To pick some way more as a guy sort of a
loose can and sure, but a guy rebelling against the very corrupt, yeah, Sheriff and whatnot.
So you're rooting for them through the movie to win. And you'll just have to watch to see
if they do. And look, I'll just do both of mine in a row. Who is the villain? Jack Palants.
Oh nice. Yeah, so he's always great. Yeah, and then I watched young guys do a my number one guy and die
It's from bad man. Yeah
I also watched young guns two which opens with an old Emilio Estevez as a man claiming he is the
He's Billy the kid and he wants to be turned over. He wants to be taken into custody old age make up and yeah
It's actually not bad makeup. Okay
And that's a real thing that happened like a guy in the 50s or 40s did it like a news reporter met with this guy that said
I'm Billy the kid. Yeah, and they couldn't prove it whether he was or wasn't, but
And then they go into the you know, the sort of the second phase of the Billy the kid story or whatever
Keeper Southern women returns
Christian Slater is now added to the mix in the second one. Okay, they recast Pat Garrett
I forget with who and Balthazar Gettie and what I believe is not his first role
But one of his earlier roles. Yeah, it happened to that guy
I would imagine drugs. I don't know. That was an age of drugs. Well
Anyway, the second one's fun. It's not as good as the first one
But it's you know, it's fun to check out
Balthazar Gettie was like in Lord of the Flies, right? That's was his first movie I believe
He looks good
But the producer half of rap duo the wow.
So I guess that's what he got into.
I guess.
All right.
You got one more?
I do.
I'm going to split the diff because I've seen half of two seasons of HBO shows, the first
half of Sharp Objects, which I briefly mentioned last week.
So far, it is Amy Adams driving around drinking vodka.
And I'm here for it.
I'm enjoying it. She's, she fills an heavy on bottle with vodka, gets behind the wheel.
How big is the bottle? It's a, it's bigger than the small, but she's bringing around like the leader bottle.
Drinks it, drinks warm vodka with no ice, no mixer, just no, no even wind center face.
Every time you see her, she's surrounded by vodka bottles. They do a scene where she walks into a
the liquor store buys a bottle of vodka and as she walks away, they cut to the salesman
looking at his watch. And it's like 8 a .m. It's fun to me. You know, I think Heather, my
wife was more disturbed by it. I kept laughing at all the drunk stuff. Who amongst us hasn't
been there? But it's, that's basically all it is. I think there's like some really disturbing
revelations coming. She's a cutter. There appears to be some
molestation in her past. Her mom is played by the great Patricia
Clarkson, who is very, very cold and like just basically tells
her daughter like, I don't love you. Other things that were making
me laugh that I think Heather was troubled by. But and it's the
young girl, the girl from it. Yeah, that's right. Is young
idiot. By the way, perfect cast. They look identical. Yeah, way
better than the Jessica Chastain casting as the older version of her in in the
it movie. They look identical. It's shot very well. It's the guy who did big
little lies, which I was just as into as anybody else. I thought that was a
fantastic program. And you know, it's slow. I guarantee it's gonna be too slow for
some, but I like depressing shit. I like watching people self -destruct. So I'm into
it. And the only issue I have is Chris Messina, an actor I've normally liked, is unbelievably
miscast, is like a hard drink and detective. That's her love and trust. He's really bad
in it, I think. He was in Vicki Victoria, Barcelona, Vicki Christina, Barcelona. Who do you
play in that? He was the fiance. Okay. Likeable actor. He's not right for this part. He has
has no edge to him at all and it's pretty awkward actually.
Adam's is great, it's a good show.
And then I'm also halfway through succession,
which everyone I know has been talking about.
They say it starts out slow, but gets great.
I'm halfway through, it's starting to get great.
I didn't think it was that bad.
The first few to be honest with you.
They're really good.
I mean, they're not, they don't slip into like
the classic sopranos, deadwood, six feet under HBO.
Pantheon, but succession is really entertaining.
And Brian Cox is awesome in it there's a awesome scene where Brian Cox is like he's been in a coma
And he's like brings his son closer and his son's like bragging about something he did
He's like I'm taking care of the family business pop, you know, like he waves him over like I say
He gets up and gets in close so we can talk and he goes you're
Fucking
eating idiot. I just loved it. I thought it was awesome. It's the guy, the guy who's
less famous, who writes like the thick of it and all those British shows with Armando
Ianucci and Adam McCay directed the pilot. I recommend it. You know, these are good
programs. All right. What do you think about doing a few deadlines from the screaming
and news psycho I'd love to hear some well we got two here that that that
connect and and I think warrant some discussion because they are movies that
fall into our our pantheon Texas chainsaw massacre and Charlie's angels have
both been given reboots again Texas chainsaw massacre the franchise signed a new
deal for a TV series and a reboot movie. Charlie's Angels, the reboot is already in motion and it's
going to start Kristen Stewart. And my question to Hollywood is sort of so not that it's why can you not
let these miserable franchises die. Texas chainsaw massacre had its moment. They have tried now three
times to get it going again. They have failed every time. The best of the efforts was the Jessica,
what's your name? Bill. Bill remake of the original.
The prequel to that at the beginning was not very good. The Texas Chainsaw 3D was an
abomination and I didn't even see leather face because I heard it was so fucking bad.
right uh let it go yeah let it go we got three good movies out of them one two and three
four sucked never saw three three with McConaughey no that's four okay terrible um I mean
the the thing is like they're like well there's money to be made from the name or whatever but is
there? They released one last year that to my knowledge never even made a dime. They keep
bombing over and over. So what is the rationale? And who on God's earth by the way is still,
that's what I mean. These are franchises that began in the 70s. Right. What young woman
out there is going, I'm just gunning for a Charlie's Angels movie. They want to see new shit,
Give them new shit. Yeah, also young women don't like Kristen Stewart. I like her. I think
She's a fairly solid actress, but young women don't like her. They think she's boring
She's painfully boring. Are they gonna be in like bikinis and stuff? Or is it a modern feminist?
Look at it. I have then why are you doing Charlie's Angels? Which was a show about women jiggling in bikinis?
I have no idea. I have no idea. There's no way they're doing it that way
like even like they did the ones in the 2000s, which I thought were kind of fun.
Um, I mean, the first one had some merit. The second one was, you know, that's what I mean. It's like
Crispin Glover was fun. There's a reason there wasn't a third one. Yeah. You know, they did that
full throttle one that fucking did Mick G direct that one too. He did the worst name in history. Yeah.
It's like, look, there would have been more clearly. It was time to stop. Like why do you have to keep
doing this every 10 years. Stop it. Let these things go away. None of the Texas
Transome Asker movies, other than one in 1973, has made any money.
I think they made money. They made a, you know, a million or something. I think
the second one probably did because they did do a third one. The third one
flops, I know, but it's actually pretty good. But again, it's just,
just, this is just stupid.
It's just so stupid at this point.
You're not talking about Marvel comics
or DC comics or Star Wars,
or you're not talking about these timeless brands
that can conceivably be reworked or not,
not saying they don't fail.
But you know, this is like,
we're gonna reboot the A team.
What, why?
Wait, they're rebooting it again?
No, I'm just saying like that this these two to me are like if they were going to do that
It's like leave it alone. Yeah Texas Shane's look. I'm sorry. I love Texas Shane. So massacre the original is to me is one of the best
Top 10 horror films ever made. Yeah
This is not nightmare in Elm Street guys. I'm sorry
It's not Friday the 13th either. It's not even hell razor. Let's be honest
This is not as iconic as those movies. Why do they keep beating this fucking thing into a ground? Especially
Especially when it's a premise that relies on the mystery of the family.
Once you know too much about the family, it's not fucking scary anymore.
The mystery of who are these people, why do they live like this, what are they doing
in this house, how do they control this town, what is going on, is there any way to escape?
That's what makes it scary.
You know, you guys are trying to do like a fucking matrix thing with this, where you're going
to explain every aspect of the fucking blue pill world or whatever.
It's like no now it sucks. Yeah, it's boring. Who cares? I don't care anymore than like when the matrix did it either
Yeah, I'm watching a guy out here
Supervised and he's a strong -looking guy supervising his girlfriend putting a giant chest of drawers into a truck
Is she a strapping lady or she looks like she's handling it. Okay, but he's literally watching and like giving performance notes instead of grabbing the other end of the
Yeah.
Anyway, be nice to your partner.
Help them out.
Maybe she wanted to do it.
Maybe she...
I got it.
I'm strong too.
Maybe that's a girl, I don't know.
I don't know, maybe that's happening.
I'd love to date somebody like that.
I never had to lift any self -sufficient.
The, I don't like lifting.
I want things lifted for me once in a while, you know?
Sure.
That's so bad.
I, you know, I used to be a friend of me
Like, hey, can you help me move or whatever stuff like that?
I love that I am now at an age where everyone knows
not to ask me help them move.
I'd rather throw you a hundred dollars
and say, go buy a mover.
Yeah, I have no problem saying no.
Leave me alone.
There's no way.
But I'll give you pizza and beer if you do, no.
Take that money, buy a mover, and don't call me again.
You know what I say?
I say, take that money and shove it up your ass.
Sure.
What do I look like?
I say, hey, do you see the word sucker
written across my forehead right there's a reason all those guys have back braces
you know they're they're setting themselves up for for a life of pain. Anyway
fuck moving, fuck moving, fuck reboots, most reboots, most reboots, yes.
And let's talk Joe about the film and hand tales from the hood.
Well, you know what?
We're a little ahead of schedule.
Could I squeeze a scary stuff in?
I know.
Would you have another scream line?
No, it was those two reboots together.
Those two were two stories, but a quick scary stuff for, you know, guys, you know how much
I shit on Marvel comics and Marvel movies on this podcast?
Yes, you are well aware that I have no Marvel fanboy, which is going to make what I'm about to say all the more worthwhile.
If you got yourself a PlayStation 3 and you haven't played this game, you need to go out and get yourself Wolverine, the Uncaged Edition, X -Men Origins, Wolverine, the Uncaged Edition.
Now, correct me if I'm wrong, I've never seen Wolverine in a cage.
Am I I'm not making a joke why it why uncaged he's not cage gonna tell you why okay?
The original version of this game
Was just a Wolverine action game and you ran through was Wolverine kidding people through claws and stuff
Then long before the film Logan was it was even a glimmer and in its daddy's eye right
They made they released a version of this game called
called The Uncaged Edition, where they added dismemberment and blood.
So it's a video game where you play Wolverine in the storyline of the first Wolverine movie,
and you run through absolutely tearing people to shreds, literally, more like in Logan.
Yes.
Decapitations, arms and legs coming off, throwing people into walls and getting impaled with spikes.
it is a fucking bloodbath and it's a hell of a lot of fun the Wolverine
skills are really fun you could do these lunges where you pound down like
50 feet onto a man and stab him in the neck with your claws it's just a really
wild fun game if you like Wolverine at all you'll enjoy this game trust me just
trust me get it I think it'll run you maybe I think it's like 15 or 20 bucks
used for the PS3. There's a reason that price point is still that high because the game is very good.
A little long, a little tedious after a while, but a lot of fun in spurts.
And it's right up here, action, bloody video game alley if you like that sort of thing.
I'd like to recommend Wolverine Walmart edition. And this is where he goes through slashing prices.
Yeah, folks, and they say this guy's crazy. Yeah. Have you seen these prices? Yeah. Yeah.
Um, all right. Well, as always, I probably won't check that out, but I hope our video game listeners do.
Oh, by the way, you know what, you know what a young fan of ours asked me the other night at a show? No.
Hey, did Pat ever give you the PSVR thing? I didn't know.
I'll give it to you have you used it no once no I'd like it. I don't know how to set it up
but I will you will give it to me yes give it to me and then we call that birthday dinner off the
books no I like that you've been telling me you want to take me to the tab for birthday dinner
belated I was gonna do it today and you didn't want to do it so no no no we we're gonna do it today
we're gonna do a brunch and then record and you texted me at nine thirty a .m. and said can we do
this earlier. It was past 10. So I said, yeah, let's go get breakfast and then do this. I was just
like, I don't want to do it at one. We got to go to the 10 at 11. They're open at 11. So that's
your first meal of the day. Prime rib. You're just going to choke that down. First, first meal of the day.
Prime rib. I have a full menu. Sorry. Prime rib burger. Horned beef. I mean, it would be what I
actually ate. And as I said to Pat at the meal, I thought he was going to pull a fucking banyah
Yeah, on me and make my pancake meal count as the big meal. Maybe I already have
You give me baby you give me that I want that PSV are so badly. I'll give it to
We are square my friend. All right, you know, just let me play it once
You come over here. You play it and then you play with my balls
Would you like that? No, that's not guaranteed reality. That's reality
Now I know Joe was a fan of anthology horror. I know Joe likes a movie with a a
social conscience. I'm watching Tales from the Hood for the first time this
week and I was like, Joe, you must love this movie. Joe's like it sucks. But you
did change your mind on this latest viewing. I watched it again last night because I
said you know too many people who like horror movies tell me this is a really
good movie yeah and for some reason I've always reacted very poorly to it I
always thought it was a little too hokey and I rewatched it last night through
the lens of this is supposed to be a little tongue and cheek it's supposed to be
fun because look imagine watching that movie seriously and you got
Clarence Williams, the third being like, oh yes, the shit, I mean, it's it's like you're
like, what is happening right now? He's filling in for the crypt keeper and the stories
themselves, I thought were very serious. The stories are very serious, but it was, it was
that, that threw me off. Look, I was wrong. It was shortsighted of me. I was wrong. I really
enjoyed the watching love it last night. It's four stories. A lot of fun. All, all, somewhat
related to the black experience in America in some way.
Yeah, I think the reason I had brought it up for the show is I've been reading about it
a lot tied to get out, which I think it is sort of a precursor to that.
It's horror but it's treating the black experience in America as horrific, which by all accounts,
it is, or it can be.
and I thought each one was about a really cool issue I thought each one was
done well and I liked all the performances in them I thought they were great
I think it's a lot of fun this movie my one criticism is it's a little it's a
little two on the nose of course get out kind of skews the concept enough to the
side this thing get out no but it's you know so you know it's like I don't
I don't need the police officer, excuse me,
I don't need the guy that's the activist in the hood
yelling at the police officer going,
and as long as cops are dealing drugs,
I'm gonna keep out in them.
Just say that you're exposing corrupt cops.
It doesn't need to be that specific,
but let's go piece by piece.
The stories are, but I did really enjoy the film.
Yeah.
The stories are some gang bangers
are trying to break into Clarence Williams' funeral home.
Not even break in.
They just get a message from him that he's found a bunch of drugs in an alleyway, so they're
going there to make a deal, a deal.
And he winds up, you know, basically, but they're in hell by the end of it, you find out,
which I thought was an ice little twist.
But he's basically playing Cripkeeper to introduce his stories.
One is...
And the stories are introduced out of the launch point is the cough, they go into a room,
there's a guy in a coffin.
He says, yeah, let me tell you a tale about this man right on then it goes into the
thing.
The movie is produced by Spike Lee, and directed by Rusty Kunda, who directed a bulk of the
Chappelle show, and also fear of a black hat, which is a great documentary about the rap
world.
And the movie is very well directed. He plays the suspense really well. Yeah.
So the first one is, uh, you know, white cops beating up on a black guy. And, you know, basically,
they wind up kind of coming back. He comes back as a zombie of sorts to torment them. They piss on his
grave. Uh, and then he comes up and that's an intense scene. Yeah. And then in a final twist,
just the black cop who didn't stop it is also implicated.
That I didn't agree with.
Yeah.
Cause he does try to stop it.
Not, not, not.
There are three men that are threatening to kill him.
I get it.
No, it's just a tricky situation.
And he's like,
we're gonna take him to the hospital.
Let us do that or else.
And he's like, all right, fine.
Just please take him to the house.
I kind of felt bad for that guy.
I was like, this guy didn't do anything wrong.
He just did your bidding for you.
He led the dirty white cops back to your graves,
you could kill them.
He quit the force and became an alcoholic
because he's like,
I don't wanna be part of this corruption.
I didn't think that guy deserved to be killed.
No, yeah, there's like a beheading ending, et cetera.
Two, I believe is the stepfather story
where David Allen Greer, my now co -worker
and to me one of the funniest community performers ever is in a very serious role.
He's like a, he has a Shakespearean trained actor after all, but he's playing a very threatening menacing stepfather
that the boy keeps describing at school as a monster that gives him bruises and etc.
And that one I think was probably my favorite and the most effective.
It when he's tearing the papers up, it had some really cool effects
He but basically it's like voodoo whatever he does is done to the stepfather. It did every does to the paper. Yeah
Yeah, it kind of begged the question. Why he had this not been working in the past
Unless I miss something because he he says he just learned it
Just learned it. Okay, the kid says that he goes so and so told me that if I do this. Yeah, I can get rid of my if I draw
all my fear on a picture on a piece of paper,
I can burn it or crumble it and it goes away.
And then the teacher of course is like,
well I don't know if that's gonna work buddy,
but hey, whatever you're gonna do,
and then he crumbles the paper of the bully,
and then it cuts to the bully kid in like a full body cast
being pulled off of the playground, right?
It's one of my favorite scenes.
The teacher walks up, she's a kid,
a nine year old kid on a stretcher, dying.
Every bone in his body is broken.
that you just go, well, what happened here?
Yeah.
All right.
Well, yeah.
Well, he was an asshole.
I liked that one a lot.
And I liked, they give it at the end, you know,
a line that's clearly designed to like make the theater crack up
at the end of an intense story.
But David Younger is basically a face lying on a pile of clothes.
Right.
And he goes, this ain't over yet, bitch.
And it was very funny.
Right.
but kind of, you know, throws the rest of the, you know, pretty intense episode under the bus.
Um, the third is my favorite, the Corbin Bernson one.
Corbin Bern, that was a heavy one, man.
It was.
It was heavy, and so that is Corbin Bernson is basically, uh,
winds up being attacked by these dolls that contain the spirit of slaves.
Uh, I'm always a sucker for a doll getting revenge on somebody.
Yeah, I like killer dolls. Not great effects. I liked it. I like the stop motion effects. I like the stop motion when they'd went to the CGI of them all like advancing on him. It looked like you know, like when they'd go driving in a Hitchcock movie and you see the screen flipping behind.
Yeah, I like this one. I thought it was.
is, I thought it served, they all serve a certain amount of justice to the bad guys, but
I just really liked the idea, especially after just seeing black clansmen.
And this, again, a little on the nose, that Gordon Burns in place of politician named
Duke, who used to be in the clan, you know, you didn't have to call him Duke, we got what
you were saying.
Right.
But anyway, it was just it just was a very satisfying come up in at the end of this thing and I love the I love the device. This is this is like totally my kind of hard device.
There's a painting in his office of because he lives he moved into this plantation as sort of an extra fuck you to the black community.
while these slaves were killed and in his office there's a mural of this old
woman who carved these wooden dolls and supposedly transported the
souls of the dead slaves into these dolls and throughout the movie as he
returns to the room there's more of the missing from the painting which means
right they're in they're now in real life right and I just love the last shot
where he goes in and it's just the woman and there's all the spaces where the dolls were
were empty and he turns and they're all standing there. That's a really, really great.
Yeah, great shot. I like the puppets for sure. Corbin Burnson was good in it, but I watched they
with all these screen factory things they did a really great documentary on it, modern day,
interviewed everybody. And Corbin Burnson is interviewed and he talks about how he gets
recognize for it more than anything else. But him and the director keep talking about how funny
it was and he kept improvising stuff. So like, when he said, when he called them, N -I -G -Lets,
right, that was a Corbin Burntson improv and he's like, we'd all be behind the camera cracking up.
I was like, if I had that part, I can assure you there would be no improvisation. I couldn't believe
it. So they talk to Bernson and he goes, I get a kick out of people, you know, come
not to me and call me Duke and call me this character's name because it's not me. Then
he pauses and he goes, well, I wrote down the quote. He goes, you know what? It is me.
That character is me. He's like a white supremacist. Then he goes, well, it's not me, but it's definitely
in there. And as long as I can just not act on it, then he stops himself again. I couldn't
believe he let them put this thing on the documentary. He's basically saying like, yeah, at my
core, I'm an extreme racist, but and it's a battle to keep it in check. Wild stuff.
Bernson's got a dark side. Did you ever see Bernson's the dentist or a movie? No, I heard it's actually
pretty great though. Really? I have. Okay. It's, it was on, well, it was on
a, I watched a show 50, 50 scariest horror movies you've never heard of or
whatever and that was on there. Okay. Then again, pumpkin head was at like
number two or one and I'm like, guys, not only have we all heard of it, it's not
scary. I ain't seen pumpkin. It's not scary. It's got its moments but whatever.
and the fourth one was refresh my memory? The fourth one I thought was unnecessarily elaborate
for what it was. I mean the fourth one is essentially a device to set up and show that the
three guys that are in the funeral home actually murdered another gang member earlier that
Yeah, that's the that's basically why it's there, but the story itself is
literally just
It's just a ripoff of
Clockwork Orange. Yeah, so they're gonna take this really violent gang member
They increase gets incarcerated. They go you can be
Rejuvenated and then and then we'll set you free and then the the the the therapy for for him
and becoming a clean solar, whatever you want to call it,
is like, you know, his eyes are pinned open
and he watches all this horrific footage of stuff.
And it's literally a clockwork, aren't you?
Yeah, and you know that they're basically
he's being punished for, which I thought was interesting,
killing other black people.
And the point of it was,
you're black, you're already a minority,
why are you killing your own time?
Yeah, and they make them watch
like all that like clan footage and stuff like that, right?
Yeah, some really graphic stuff it played to me sort of like well, I can't you know what now
You know
It okay, now I take back what I said that that that that's a very fitting
Lead into them being in hell at the end. Yeah
All right, it played it sort of like I don't think part of this was just the budget
But it played kind of like a play you'd see on Santa Monica Boulevard or something like a kind of a bit a bit too preachy a bit too
But the doctor in it little fun fact
you know, she was? No. She was, uh, she's the lady on the episode of The Golden Girls,
when Dorothy's son, uh, comes in and says he's marrying, he's getting married, and then he's,
turns out he's marrying an older black woman. Okay. And Dorothy's mad that she's like, you can't
marry someone that's much older than you. Yeah. It's not right. I won't allow it. And then the black
family is like I can't believe she's marrying this skinny little white boy
right and then somehow they all put their hate together and bond over being
hateful about the union all right that's that's that's how it all ends up in
the end probably a more realistic portrayal of how they go down I was I was very
very impressed by tales from the hood I thought especially just even looking at
the cover of it. I thought I knew what I was going to get with it. I thought it was
going to be like that Snoop Dogg horror movie, which I have not seen by my own hood of horror.
Hood of horror. What's bones then? Bones is the one where Snoop Dogg comes back and
is like a Jason or something. Okay. Snoop Dogg's hood of horror is a hood horror movie.
Yeah. An anthology hood horror movie. How's that? It's fun. I mean, you know, it's enjoyable.
It does not have the weight or commentary that Tales of the Hood does.
It also features Jason Alexander playing a record executive and for some reason he's
doing an Australian accent and you can tell that he was just like, I'd like to do this
accent.
But it's not a bad film.
It's a fun watch.
I thought it tells from the hood, especially paired with the great documentary on the new
Blu -ray, it was really great.
When they talked to the writer and Rusty Cundiff together, their intentions for this thing
were like, you know, the intentions of all the great horror movies.
They really had some stuff to say, and if they hit it a little too on the head at times,
which they probably do, it didn't bother me.
I thought it was really, really something deeper and
meteor than it had to be, and I think that's the reason
that people still talk about it to this day.
We're also going to do tales from the hood too, which I think
they have even more to talk about now.
I can't wait to see that.
Yeah, we'll probably do that next week, but I agree with you.
I, regardless of things being directly on the nose at
times, it, it, it does not harm the film in any way.
no. And I was very wrong about it. I and I could admit when I'm wrong. By the way I thought Clarence
Williams was hilarious. I thought he was too. Yeah but I first watched this thing when I was in
college and I thought I didn't get it. I mean there's no other way to put it. I just didn't get it. I
thought it was supposed to be serious. And then Clarence Williams threw me off and then from there on out
I was just kind of off the track and I didn't understand it admittedly.
Upon rewatch last night, I truly, truly enjoyed it.
It's actually a film that I do want to own now.
I would like, so maybe I'll buy that screen factory and I'm excited to see tales from the
hood too, which, like I said, we'll review that next week.
Yeah, and it's available on demand.
You can get it on Amazon or on your local on demand, direct TV, whatever.
by the way. We almost forgot to talk about the coolest part of the movie. It's Wings
Houser by the way is the name of the like main asshole cop like the biggest
one. It was like the meanest. That guys are real prick in this movie. That's a
great name though. He has been. It's been in so many fucking movies. That guy has
has the the racist in prison. I've seen him in a million things too. Wait, would
Did you say the racist in the prison scene at the end?
I've seen him in a million things too.
Oh, okay.
They're actually similar actors, similar faces.
Dwayne Whitaker popped up in here
who is Zed in Pulp Fiction.
That's right.
That's what was interesting.
Roger Gwenevier -Smith was in this
who is an excellent actor.
He's in deep -cover, he plays the crack head.
I love deep -cover.
I love deep -cover too.
He's in Malcolm X.
He plays the guy that like heads up the gang
with Malcolm. He's awesome. And almost everything he's in. Well, and everything he's in.
Well, he's the guy from Do the Right Thing, too, the handicap guy, right? Yes. Yeah.
That's a, uh, a ballsy and very great performance.
Rosalind Cash is the woman from the Golden Girls, and she plays the doctor. Yeah.
Jotory was, was great. Baseball manager, Jotory. He was really funny. He's a comic, of course he was.
David Allen Greer, as you said, was great. Everybody was great. It was a really, really well done film.
I look forward to seeing the sequel and before we wrap it up, I want to mention what I thought was the coolest part in the movie
When Clarence Williams says to them at the end
This isn't a funeral home. You're in hell as they stand next to their own coffins
You know, of course the funeral room transforms into hell
Mm -hmm, and that's fine
But Clarence Williams turns into the devil and I got to say legitimately a very scary -looking devil
It was a very frightening devil.
Yeah, it's weird to hinge that much on special effects when you clearly don't have a budget,
but they really made it work and it was very cool.
I like the kind of home spun quality that certain horror has and this one felt cheap,
but not shitty, you know, like everything felt like it was done with a lot of care and
love.
Well, they had something to say and they had a lot to say.
And that's the, and that to me, therein lies the beauty of horror for me versus sci -fi or fantasy or we're, you know, I love all the genres, but I feel like horror you can make a home spun horror movie and it's, it's great.
Yeah.
And it doesn't matter that people don't take, it's like just like with comedy, people don't take the genre seriously for some reason.
Yeah, every once in a while they will, right, but not do something like get out of the exorcist, but
These are these are movies that are in my opinion clearly passion projects
And I think it's cool that they're off the beaten path and a little under the radar
And that they have this quality to them. So
It's a fun flick
Check it out
That's our show
Yeah, so I am on Twitter and Instagram at the patch wall sh cool kids from here September 28th on the Fox Network
Our live show is October 20th at 7 30 and then again at 9 30 two different shows
These shows will be available as podcasts, but you're gonna want to be there live
They are both sold out. There may be a stand -by -line keep watching for that
See you in hell pod on Instagram has a lot of great fan art and news that we'll see you in hell Facebook page is always a delight
Thank you to Emily and to Ken for running that so well. Yeah, I got the merch
The hoghouse page on Etsy just search the hoghouse on Etsy and Joe. What do you got?
Well, I'll be in China and Japan
From like I guess it's like the 18th of September through the 28th or something
then I go down to Atlanta for the Red Clay Festival and I will be doing Shanghai in Tokyo
by the way. Those are the cities I'm doing in China, Japan. Red Clay Festival, last Sunday
of September, I will be doing two shows seven and nine thirty at the Earl to record my
latest hour. Just going to do this one as an album again and possibly, well, I'll get
into the other possible stuff later. But anyway, this is exciting. I look forward to
doing the record and recording it exclusively for serious XM radio. That's the only place
it will be released. And it's going to be a fun project. I haven't done anything like
this before. So that's it. Jotaro's a comedy on Instagram. And we'll talk to you soon.
and we'll talk to you in L.
It's a good show!