I'll see you at L. I'll see you at L.
They brings us out on a yos bring us back arms, I think I'm a dreams in them.
I say hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey I'll see you at L.
You know I'll see you at L. You know I'll see you at L.
YOU KNOW I WANT MUST GO!
Hello everybody welcome to another edition of We'll See You in Hell the podcast.
about horror movie commentaries, not about them where we do them. And then you can watch
the movie along with it if you want. How shitty would that be? A podcast about commentaries.
We review commentaries on horror movies. I'm Joe DeRosa. I'm Patrick Walsh. And we're
pleased to be here doing this podcast. Now part of the Fangoria Podcast Network for more
information about the network, including other programs, how to follow this show, other
shows find episodes of the show or of other shows or past episodes or whatever the hell it
is. Visit Fangoria .com. Let's get down to it. Today's movie is Hellraiser. Just a technical
note. I am on one side of your head right now. Pat is on the other. We do that so we're
in separate years. So in case you do want to watch the movie along with this commentary.
The movie sort of goes up the middle with us on either side of you.
Stereo Sound. I'm on your right. Joe's on your left. We are aware the past couple weeks.
I have been mixed too low. That'll be corrected this week. They're already saying it's
corrected. Terrific. It's already corrected. Also we are now available on iTunes, which was
a question a lot of people had. You can download it, subscribe, review the show, give it a nice
review. It would be great. We're starting out. Be very helpful. If you have questions or
movie suggestions or recommendations or things you'd like us to discuss on the show, you can
tweet me at the Patrick Walsh or Joe at Joderosa Comedy. That's right. Now in this little preliminary
bullshit talkie period before we start the movie Hellraiser, which is what we're watching
today. Now's the time for you to get on your device, get on your eye, your Netflix thing,
and find Hellraiser as we talk here, and hit play and then pause it as soon as the picture
comes up so we can start it all together in a few minutes here. Pat, can I tell you what
I did this week? Please do. Master baited into a cup. Okay. Explain. Went to the urologist
had a prostate issue. Nothing serious. Relax, Pat. I know how you worry about me. What I didn't
really care at all. What was it? What was the issue? I mean, we don't have to get into all
the details. I take a step forward. You take a step away. That's the dance. Prostatitis, which
is a very mild prostate issue, but my doctor was like, look, it's probably prostitized. We're
just going to make sure you got to go do a urinalysis and a semen culture. Okay. I'm not crazy
about them calling it a semen culture, by the way. We're living in a semen culture. That's
what I'm saying. I hear you. So I'm like, okay, I got to go to one of these places and you
go into the room and you master bait. Sure. I even asked a friend. I go, what do they
do? Can you bring somebody? And she goes, you can bring people in if you need to. Anything
to get that nut into the cup. This is woman with the speaking kind of with the language
of the street. Yeah. Well, she's from the street. Okay. As am I. But anyway, I go to this
place, this clinic, it's a suite inside a building filled with different suites, all kinds
of offices and different businesses in this place. I go into the, I go into the clinic.
The lady puts two cups on the counter. She goes the bathrooms down the hall to the left,
meaning the public bathroom. She wants me to go whack off in the men's, the common men's
room. No. I thought that was a crime. First of all, that's what Peewee Herman went to
jail for. Yeah. It's no different being in a men's room. I guess if you were to blame it
on the clinic, you would be in the clear, but that's not cool. That's not legal. Let
me ask you this, even in a stall, it's not legal. Let me ask you this, who's able to whack
off in a men's room, no visual stimulant, no loob. If I try to whack off in my own bedroom
with no loob or no stimulant, 90 solid minutes easily. And your bedroom doesn't wreak of business
man shit, business man shit floor cleaner. Right. You know what I mean? Yeah. There's not
a hand dryer blowing just on repeat. It just doesn't stop. Somebody hacking a loogie into
the sink. Yeah, it was insane. So I brought it home. I brought the cup home and I I whacked
off into it at home, but I had to use lube. It's not worried. I'm going to my urologist is
going to call me in and be like, we got to talk. Yeah. Found a, there's a hello in your
gym. So you definitely, I don't think should have done that. Why didn't know what to do?
How do you do it? Can you whack off without the lubricant? I've never used it to be honest
with it. I can't do it. I don't love the direction this podcast is heading, but I don't use
it. Why? Never have? No, no, why don't you love the direction the podcast is heading? It's
just like, hey guys, and then we're talking about whacking off into a cup. Yeah. What's
it? But I did this week. No, I'm sorry. Is this too low brow for you? Maybe it is.
Is this too low brow for you? Maybe it is. I was going to talk about, you know, the work
of merchant ivory productions, room with a view, Howard's in. Okay. Nope. No cup, jizzin
in those films. The piano. I want to stay up to watch. They made the piano. Yeah. I don't
think they did, but I love the piano. They didn't. But Harvey Kitell's penis is in that
you call that art? No, definitely not. All right. Thank you. What was the, I guess it was a
room with a view. And I used to stay at my friends house and I would stay up even after he went to
bed to watch the nudity on cable because it was my only way to see nudity. And it said a room with
a view starting next, nudity, PG 13 for nudity. And I was like, oh, God, I watched two and a half
hours of this thing. And then I see Daniel Day Lewis running naked down a hill into into like a
river. Wait a second. A room with a view is that's a Titchcock film. No.
Why? A room with a view is a Daniel Day Lewis British merchant ivory production.
I'm thinking of a view to the kill. A view to a kill. A view to a kill is a James Bond movie.
Rear view window mirror. Rear window. Rear window is what I was thinking. Jesus Christ.
Yeah. Anyway, the point is I'm up at like five in the morning. Can barely open my eyes waiting
for this nudity. And then I see Daniel Day Lewis's bear ass flopping around in a swamp.
How long are you going to take you to finish to DD? It was like 10 minutes because I don't use
lube as we just done. All right, let's start hell, Razer. All right, you should be all paused up by
now. And I'll set to go. I'm going to count to three and then say play. And we all hit three.
We all hit play when I say play one, two, three, play. Now we're wrong. You're you're opening
graphics. Do you have any stories about masturbating into cups?
Sadly, I do. When I first moved to LA, I had no money. And I decided I was going to donate
semen. I got a trash can here full of liquid gold. So because you wanted to create a life with
your semen. Yeah, exactly. So this this jerk off is going to go jerk off to create another jerk off.
Exactly. So I drive out. I think it's funny. It's really a strong joke.
I said it to Pat before we started recording it, he didn't like it. And I think it's a funny joke.
I thought you were kind of trying it out to see if it was worthy. I gave you a firm no. And here
it comes. So I drove out to Westwood and I go to this kind of shady looking clinic. And they did
have rooms, almost like peep show booths that you'd go in and play a DVD to jerk off and like made
made very sure you didn't touch anything in there. And I go in. It's a very attractive Asian nurse.
And she ends me a cup and a DVD face down. And I'm thinking, well, it's probably going to be like
playboy, wet and wild. Yeah, Jenny McCarthy. Right. And I'm maybe going to live a you Newton
John. Right. Or like they'd give you a sports illustrated swimsuit edition or something.
And I get back in the room and the DVD is called jam it all the way up my ass part two. Okay.
Which I was shocked by that in a doctor's office. This was the material they give you.
And what if I'm not into that, by the way? It's anybody's into that in that situation. That is a high
pressure masturbation situation. They're giving you filth. Yeah, they're trying to get you right to it.
It was really rough stuff. And I'm in there and I'm thinking I don't want to take too long
and have her think I'm perving around. Well, that's why she gave you jam it all the way
at my ass part two. They don't want you slowly making love to a fucking end in a cold -smith video in
there with a with a soft focus. Right. I'm also thinking I don't want to come out too early and have
her be like, oh, this guy, in case her and I make love later, I guess is what I'm thinking. She
thinks I come to. Can I tell you the worst case scenario? Yeah. You're in there forever with the
jam it up the ass video. And this she's out there thinking, this guy can't this guy's real
demented. She must need something far darker. But I came out I handed to her and as I'm leaving,
she goes, Mr. Walsh, we need the DVD back and I had been so nervous that I was just carrying it with me.
I was ashamed. I brought it back to her. Can I make a joke here? Yeah. Were you carrying it or was
it stuck? That's good to your hand. No, I washed my hand. That's a gizzo. No, I got it. Now,
we're into the movie. It started or in Marra cash or something. Yeah. The Indiana Jones is sitting
behind these people at a table somewhere. Terrible dubbing. I watched this last night and especially
on that scene, it's like, I think the guy was speaking his native tongue and they dubbed in like,
maybe they didn't want to do subtitles or something. Throughout this movie, there's many
instances where the dubbing is way off. Yeah. It's a low budget film. You know, they did what they
could. But we've got, I would say, our main antagonist, Frank. Many people think the antagonist of
this film is Pinhead. It's not Pinhead. It's Frank. And he is toying with the box. This is actually
exciting for me to watch. This is the first time in movie history that you ever saw the box
happening on film. They went on made nine sequels to this movie, I believe it was. And this is the
first time you actually seeing the box. They all involved the box. Yeah. Yeah. The, uh,
what, how would they never make a hell razor porno about the box? Well, now I always thought too easy.
Maybe they did. We don't know. But we called a ball hell dick razor. It's something like that.
Bull trainer. Yeah. Bull drain. Yeah. I always thought that Pinhead's name was hell razor when I
see this at the video store. And saying, tell everybody how recently you thought that too.
About a year ago, I thought his name was like Jackie Hellraiser. That's embarrassing. The only
thing that worse that would be if you thought that the monster in Frankenstein was still named Frankenstein.
No, I've learned that. Uh, now Frank just got hooks in the skin. He opened the box, hooks came out
evidently hurt him. Uh, you know, as we're going to see in a moment here that he's been ripped to shreds.
Yeah. And this poses my one question about the hell razor franchise and the workings of the box.
These guys obtain the box to explore the heights or depths, if you will, of pleasure and pain.
I've never seen one person get pleasure in any one hell razor movie from the box. No. Every time they
open it, immediate hooks in the face and they die. Is it, is what we're supposed to believe that they've
chased the erotic eyes for so long. The only thing that can get them off is true pain.
I don't think it's that. I think it's that they're, they've, they've sunk to such a depraved,
immoralistic level. Yeah. That they are willing to, to play with this box. And then the,
the twist of fate is you die immediately. Okay. You know, like there, there is no winning. Like,
right. It's a trap. I know it's part where there's a skin all over the floor. And it's really gross.
They're kind of fingering through it as if it's crawfish. Yeah. Like they're fishermen that just
brought in a, like a load. Oh, so that's him. I didn't even put that together. God, I'm dumb.
The, so for those of you not watching pinhead just put a face back together on the floor. That's clearly
a clitoris cut type thing he's doing there, right? When he was supposed to believe that's like a fingering move.
It's how he's super sexual. All right. But let's just, let's just glaze over the dumb thing you just did.
Then we just watched him and get ripped apart by hooks. And then pinhead comes in and puts a face
back together on a floor riddled, littered and ripped up flesh. Pat didn't know that that was the same guy.
Well, I guess it's because you only see the hooks going into his hands and then he's just kind of
vanishes. I didn't really connect Jesus. Oh, literal wash we call him. I am too logical with things.
This, you have a poster on your wall of hell, right? So you must love it.
I love this movie. I love this movie. I love the second one. And I'm a big fan of the fourth one.
Outside of that there, I'm not too crazy about the other entries into the franchise. But that
poster up there that I'm in my wall is the original poster. It's not the original meaning it's an
original. It's, but that's the original poster before pinhead became the sort of mascot of the
franchise. Right. As you can see, there's a frightening clown on it. And there's not a clown on this
movie. No, there's no clown in the movie. And it's signed by Doug Bradley who is portrayed, portrayed
pinhead in all the movies except one of them. And I heard that the casting search for a guy with all
those pins in his head just went on and on and on because it's hard to find. I mean,
and this coming from the guy that knocked my jerk off, making the jerk off routine.
This, now when I got that poster signed, this, the cast, some of the cast was there. Doug Bradley was
there, but this lady was there that plays Julia, the stepmother, the wicked stepmother. And it was
weird meeting her because she's so mean and evil in this movie. And she was so charmingly lovely
in real life. She got to pick out of being the fans. These, like, this couple's not in the other ones.
No, I assume is another is one of the future ones like set in pinheads world.
Hellraiser two delves into it. And we should do hellraiser two at some point because hellraiser two is
the best entry in the whole really franchise. Hellraiser two is awesome. Okay. Hellraiser one is one is
great, but hellraiser two is really. I really wanted to be out of pinheads world when I was in
there. I didn't like watching it. I was watching it before bed. I didn't like it. Sturved me.
I had nightmares. He, to me, is one of the, I mean, to most people I would think is, you know, he's
definitely one of the great horror icons of all time. But he, to me, is the coolest of all the famous
movie monsters. And I'm a huge Kruger fan. Jason's awesome. Chuckie. Why not? You know, I like them all.
The alien, you know, everything's great. But to me, pinhead is the coolest because he's so elegant.
There's something he's very Darth Vader -esque. Yeah. Well, his sidekicks are the freakier ones in my
opinion. There's a fat one that I despise looking at. You know what his name is? No joke. Pudgekins.
Butterball. Butterball. Yeah. Okay. Look at that maggots. Real maggots. Really gross. I remember
have a maggot experience. Oh, yeah. You want to hear about it? I guess I had one myself. I mean,
it's not that much of a story. I flipped over a piece of meat and there was a ton of maggots on it
and I screamed for 25 minutes. I had a horrible apartment. Where was the meat? I came up from the grocery
store like set it on the counter. Went about my business not for a long period of time and I came
picked it up and had like maggots all over. Well, that was bad when you bought it. Yeah. Oh, absolutely.
Well, I used to go to the Vans at Melrose and Vine with my apartment which at night they enclosed
in giant black bars like a prison. Oh, good. So they always had the most high quality
meats. Welcome to Hollywood kid. Yeah. Close the bars that go jerk off in that cup for money.
It was a real nightmare. I had an experience in college. I lived with two guys. There you go. There's
my roommate Mark said I refused to clean anything until our other roommate Jim start doing dishes.
He just refused and it got so bad that finally Mark said, I'm just going to do the dishes.
Clean the dishes. Got to the bottom of the sink screamed and ran across the kitchen and I said,
what? He goes, look in there, man. And I looked in and there was a half eaten burrito with maggots in it.
Oh, it was disgusting. That's disgusting. Yeah, I started gagging immediately. Then we yelled it.
Who throws a half eaten burrito in the sink? Jim did. We yelled at him about it. This is Christ. We yelled at him.
Now, this is Kirstie coming in. She is our protagonist. Pat, you know the difference between an antagonist
and a protagonist. Yeah, Joe. I've sold two screenplays to major movie studios. Oh, look it. Look
at the big shot. Now, what is this? He's fully dressed having sex with him there. I didn't quite understand.
Yeah, we're looking at she's looking at pictures of Frank. She's clearly got a lust. She had an affair
with him. This man, yeah, why don't ruin it for the people that I haven't seen yet? I thought that had
already been. No. Well, nobody's watching us for the first time. How do you know? Maybe they are. But
they can't hear the dialogue. So why would they be watching? Maybe they turn the dialogue up loud.
All right. Maybe they're doing it. Let people do it the way they want to do it, Pat. It's not your
decision how they will enjoy this. Let them enjoy it their own way. They can, but I can also say that
she had an affair. She was just, yeah, Julia, the stepmother was just looking at pictures of Frank,
and he was weird because it was sex pictures, but he was clothed. That's why I say it's a sexual film,
but I wouldn't call it gratuitous. There is some butt and a near dick. Clive Barker just released a
book called The Scarlet Gospels, which was what he said to be his final installment of the Hellraiser
mythology. Okay. And there was a really gross part in it where a demon made a guy spit
into his hand so he could jerk off. I don't care for it. I didn't care for it. I didn't really like
the book. It was too, it was too, it was too like, it was too raw or something. I can't, I can't put
my finger on it. Now, here's an interesting piece of movie trivia. That guy right there, the mover
that's moving this mattress up the stairs. Yeah. The swarrow, the Italian looking guy. Swarrow,
these are where we don't really use in this house. That pin, but Doug Bradley was offered that part.
He said, he said, he said, you can either play this demon, and it's a cooler part. The problem is,
is nobody will see your face. Right. Or you'll be in full view. But it's just a move. Wow.
What a strong decision. Yeah, he goes, well, I guess I'll just play the demon. That seems more
interesting. Yeah, of course. Made his goddamn career. Well, has he ever done anything else?
Yeah, he's in other stuff. Okay. But once I was in a bar drinking and I looked over and he was
standing next to me. And I said, Hellraiser 2 is the greatest horror movie of all time. And he said,
no, it's not, no, it's not made. And I said, yes, it is. He goes, no, broad of Frankenstein is.
And you can ask Robert England. He'll agree with me. Okay. I took a swig of my beer and shouted
in his face. Take the compliment, Bradley. And he laughed hardily and took a swig of his beer.
All right. It was a good time. This poster you have is a quote from Stephen King. I have seen
the future of horror fiction and his name is Clive Barker. I read Ebert's review of this. Ebert hated
this movie. And he said, I guess Stephen King was thinking of a different Clive Barker. So why did
Ebert hate the movie? Hellraiser. He said he can't believe all these people worked on something so
empty and soulless and terrible. Like he really hated it. Really? Yeah. And it's weird too because he
likes really cool, like original visuals. So he loved dark city a lot more than I did, for example.
But I don't know. He couldn't see the craftsmanship that went into this. I think they did a really
great job with this movie. My favorite movie review of all time is his review of Kingdom of the Crystal
Skull. He said that before. I'm one of the podcasts. I said it on this one. Yeah. Well, then all right.
Sorry. I'm just, I'm just helping him. Jesus. I didn't always with a stenographer. Get off the weed.
Joe or the grass. That's Woody Allen. What's an international man? Yeah. Yeah. Oh, yeah. We
Yeah, we talked about that before, right? Yeah. We both saw a rational man this week. There's Woody Allen's
new movie. There's a scene where it's a good movie. It's one of his dramas. I really like that. I
liked it a lot. But he's writing for Emma Stone and Parker Posey and Joaquin Phoenix. And he's 80 years
old. So at one point, Parker Posey is like, you should come up to my room. I've got some terrific
grass. And the whole theater just like burst into laughter. And I can't believe that. And Woody Allen has
said in countless interviews, he goes, I'm not married to the words. Yeah. I just say get the
gist of it. I don't care. I can't believe Parker Posey didn't go. Can I say weed, please? She was
probably scared to be like, Hey, old timer. You know, I'm then another point Emma Stone goes,
let me get one of those jazz cigarettes. Oh, God, I made that out. Oh, oh, yeah.
Well, remember the part where Joaquin Phoenix had skittily bebop. Yeah. And I was he's
jazz is here to stay swung a pocket watch around. Yeah, yeah, yeah. This is he was doing that thing
where you wag your finger off the side. Yeah, yeah. This is now Frank is coming into the house here.
We're seeing flashbacks. This is where the affair for those of you that don't remember when Pat
forgot to say spoiler alert. Spoiler alert. If it's going to happen in 30 seconds. We're showing
the movie came out in 1987. We're showing the flashback here where they meet. And you can see in
Julia's eyes, she wants to bang brother Frank. Right. It's her husband's brother. Do you? Now,
do you? I don't go for this spoiler thing at all. I think if you're, if it's last night's episode
of Mad Men and it's Monday morning, you can't walk into the office and be like, Oh, my God. Can you
believe Don Draper kicked that guy in the throat or whatever. But if a movie came out in 1987,
we're past spoilers. You can't be upset about it. I mean, Pat, look, these are your rules.
I'm asking you, what do you think? It sounds like you're telling me what to think. No, this started by
me saying what do you think? I'm telling you what I think, which if we're not allowed to say what we
think, this podcast is going to really be boring. No, I think that I think at any time, if somebody
says, you know, don't spoil it for me, you got to respect that. You got to respect it. But come on.
I agree that if I'm, look, if I, you know, if I, if I, you know, if I've never seen the Empire
Strikes Back, okay, and then I'm reading a magazine article today about the Empire Strikes Back,
I'm going to expect that it's going to blow the lid off of some of the stuff for me. Sure.
That I get. But I hate in conversations because people do this all the time conversations. They'll go,
you know, top gun or whatever you go, I never saw it. Don't, don't, don't tell me the end. Yeah,
they'll go, you've had 30 years. Get over it. That, no, that you can't do absolutely. But you should
feel comfortable discussing top gun at lunch. Well, of course. But if somebody says something,
then you know, you know, we'll give them a minute to cover their ears and hum, you know,
so they don't hear it. Goosties. But this is the part of the movie. Goosties. I know Goosties.
I've never seen the film, but I know Goosties. It's pretty good. I like this move here. Now,
they're about to, they're about to consummate their affair. Uncle Frank and Julia and his,
his first decision is to take out a switchblade and cut her 90 off of her.
Sure. It's a bold first move. I mean, but you know if she stays with you, you're in. You got
a keeper, but it's a gamble because if she doesn't like the switchblade play, you might be in some trouble.
Well, she went for it, man. So I went for it. Look at this. He's banging her on her wedding dress.
By the way, what's strange to me is he's like, he's the kind of guy who's going to cut your dress
off with a switchblade, but then he's allowing her to just calmly lay down. It seems like he'd be more
of a thrower. Yeah, he's gently kissing her breasts. Yeah, pick a side. Oh, this is real gross
when he catches hand on this thing. Spoiler alert. Yeah. Well, I like the, I like the cross -cutting
between his wife getting fucked in the flashback and then try to move the mattress and the grunting
of the moving. That's very strange. The grunting of the sex. And there's the knife. Yeah. And he cuts
his hand with the ejaculation, I believe. Yeah, this would be the scene where my mom would walk in
if I was watching it as a kid. And I go, I'm just watching. This is a strange thing to admit.
I saw this movie when I was... Oh, God. I saw this movie when it came out of video, but near dick,
I was promised with my old tiny bit of dick shot there, just a faint dick shot. So this movie when
I was I think 12 with my parents. See, you have a very different relationship with your parents
than I did. My dad wanted to see it for some reason. He was like, I want to say I move with the guy with
all the nails in his head. That looks cool. All right. And we watched it. I remember this part
made me feel uncomfortable though. I couldn't see our moves low 17. And in the PG -13, if there was
a couple and they started making out, if it felt at all like there could be any sex in the future,
I went in and got a drink for maybe five minutes. I would like carefully place cubes in the cup.
I can't do it still. That's how repressed my family was. I
can't do it. I was watching movie with my mom and dad over Christmas and I said, Mom, I'm just
going to tell you now, never admit it to you, feel very uncomfortable when anything new or whatever
happens in your room. So I'm just going to, when you see me look away, it's because I feel weird.
It felt, it was such a release to just finally admit that. And the movie you were watching?
Bad shit. I'm it all the way up my ass part. It was bad, Santa. Oh, sure. See, that's too
blue for a family view. No, it was great. We had a great time watching it. I just had to look
away during the fuck me Santa parts. Sure. Sure you would. Gilmore, girls, that lady. Now,
I'm not criticizing the film when I asked this question. What is the rule that the blood? Now the guy
moves the couch he cuts his hand or the mattress he cuts his hand. He goes up into the room where Frank
was killed. His blood is dripping on the floor. And now his blood is going to reanimate Frank.
Yeah, what is the rule of that? They don't explain it. And to me, I thought that was kind of cool.
Like when the, when the guy just kind of shows up and you realize he's formed from blood, I was like,
I get it. I didn't need anymore. Oh, you know, well excuse me. Like what are they going to do?
Like have a piece of parchment float up and then like stick to the camera so you can read about
the legend or something. There's no one here to explain it to us. But why? But then he gets,
he gets to escape hell through somebody else's. I guess it's that it's the bartering of souls.
If someone else gives their blood on purpose or by accident, you get to return from hell.
Like, but that's what's weird too. I know I will think about it. It has to be in your in the home
that you, you know, like what made his blood bring this guy back? Because they're family.
Because his heart was under the floorboard. You just saw it. How did that happen? Why was his heart
under the floorboard? I don't know. But, you know, in horror movies, I'm always just kind of like,
what are we doing now? You know, I don't care. Clive Barker has a very different approach than
Stephen King, which is there are questions. There are more question marks with Clive Barker. Yeah.
And I like both for different reasons. Right. Stock footage of nature. It looks like. No, that's not
stock. That's reverse. That's reverse. Claimation. Just look really bad. This was a really awesome
effect, I thought. This is great when his body's coming out of the floor. Yeah. And I like,
this is really cool when his head forms. It didn't form yet. This reminds me of the fly. Yeah.
The gold bloom one or the thing. And the dog, the horrifying dog that is possessed by the thing. It's
one of the grossest things I've ever seen. It's horrible. It's horrible. Nothing to me is gross
in the fly. And it's one of my favorite movies ever. We should do that one next time. Yeah. Love it.
It's a tremendous piece of work. It's a tremendous piece of work. I like when his head comes on
here and forms and it cries like a baby because he's being reborn. Yes. And I'm trying not to talk
over it so we can hear it right now. But what hear the oozing? No, I want to hear when he cries like
the little baby. Look at this. Look at this. These are great effects. Look at this. The slime and the
right? Yeah. It's really great. Blood coming up off the. Look at this. See? Yeah.
It's pretty cool. He cries like a baby. I like it. Didn't anyone get when I said,
no, you crown him, bird? That there was a reference, a lyric from British hip hop artist,
The Streets. I would imagine zero of you. Not a fan. I actually love The Streets. I guess he's
done because he hasn't released an album in 10 years, but I love them. Don't care for techno beats,
the rhymes off time with. Well, you're a very traditional hip hopist and I embrace all kinds.
Hey, can you blame me? No. I blame all kinds. They run into this dinner party scene.
Here's the hard part for me to understand is you got the, they're in a dinner party now. Look at
these people they hang out with. They're like the dorkiest fucking Mayberry couple on play. That guy
looks like, you know, he's married to a woman who fucks with a switchblade. Yeah. Exactly.
It's odd. Well, but that's probably what happens out there. You know, I got a friend back home in
Missouri. I won't name any names who told me that two different married couples in their coldest sack
were having two separate affairs with each other. And not a not a planned wife swapping thing. The
wife of one and the husband of another started hooking up. The other two found out about
it privately discussed it and then said, hey, if they're going to do it, we're going to do it and
start having sex as well. So they both just carry on affairs that they kind of may know about,
but it's not officially wife swapping. It's not an open marriage. It's very dark. Very dark. Sounds
like a good deal. I guess marriage, man. Hey, some tough shit. Hey, you know what they say, Patty,
you can't live with them. You can't live without them. You know, wives, women,
wives, marriage. You know, it's about as big a cliché as you can get, but it is true. It is true.
I've never lived. And I'm sure women feel the same about men. I'm sure. We're terrible. Yeah,
well, what can I say? I'm never banged a man so I don't know what annoying things we do.
Well, I could tell you what you do that's annoying. I don't have to bang it. I don't see why you would have
to do that. Anyone listening to this podcast can probably name 10 already. That's, that's, I mean,
I don't even know why you do that sort of thing. How do you hurt? What do you feel the need to hurt?
Heard people hurt. You know, it's true. Jerkoffs make jerkoffs. Yeah, there you go. All true.
That's a great bumper sticker. Jerkoffs make jerkoffs. Make it make a million dollars. Million.
Julia now is about to find Frank in the room. And this part is really creepy the way he like
scurries up to her. Yeah. Oh yeah, he's just like a pile at this point.
He's it's it's tremendous makeup. And it always
made me sad that he's the guy that plays Frank is in the guy in the makeup. It's a different guy with
a double. Really? Yeah. Well, that's pretty clear. I mean, they don't look anything alike.
I know, but I I don't know. I want to. What is that? Rats eating puke? It looks like. Yeah. I mean,
what what? But here she here he is. Frank just grabbed her. And this is very creepy. Look at
it. Oh, look at that. Look at that. Oh, it's so creepy. It's not unlike the sloth guy in
seven. Oh, which is a terrifying movie. Oh, God. This is just rough stuff. Don't I love that line.
Don't look. Don't look at me. I just grabbed you and chased you from the room. But don't look at
me. You're a skeleton with a little bit of flesh in your face who just grabbed me.
What do you want me to read the newspaper? Yeah. Why don't you just stay in the corner in the shadow
and just say, just go. Excuse me. And then he says it's me Frank. And she believes him. Oh,
she just believes him. Sup, Frank. She just she just watch her. We used to get it on.
That's how quickly she accepts this. It's me. It's me, Frank.
Well, maybe she thinks he just got burned or something, you know. There's no way. No,
they don't look much alike. She already believes him. How long did that take? Yeah. Let's roleplay this.
Pat, it's me, Joe. Uh, pretend I look like him. Oh, no, I didn't answer because I'm I'm in my car
driving home. Oh, you think I'm hanging out with you after that? That's me, Joe.
I think we're going to go get a hotdog. No, seriously, it's me. That's literally what he just did.
Yeah, it's me. No, no, no, no. And then it goes by the blood on the floor, brought me back.
She's like, yeah, I bought by that. Yeah. All right. Well, I gotta get back to the dinner party. Yeah.
What else is on your mind, Frank? Very, very cool looking makeup here. I mean,
this is this is a harm movie done right? You got a you got a creepy zombie guy coming back to life
slowly regenerating slowly up in the attic. That's fucking creepy enough. Most harm movies that would end
there. But then you got the centipites coming. Yeah, they're coming. And that's great. I can't,
I can't imagine that hell rise or two would be better than us because hell raise or two is awesome.
They go into hell. Yeah, I don't want to go into hell. It's awesome. I had to live my whole life
trying to avoid hell. Hell raise or two has arguably the greatest harm movie quotes of all time.
All right. I'll watch it tonight. No, I'm not tonight. It'll be one third in the morning.
Want to hear a great quote from hell raise or two? Yeah. Pinhead goes, uh, but fooless again,
child. And your suffering will be legendary, even in hell. Oh, wow. It's a great quote.
It sounds like some tough suffering, Joe. Tough suffering. That was the name of my post hardcore band in
college. We are tough suffering. One, two, three, four. Yeah, this song is called meat. Did that fake
British accent like Billy Joe Armstrong? You a green day fan? I was, you know, I was like everybody
I was in the early days. Not even the early days. I stuck with them through all the way up through
Nimrod. Oh, well, that's still the early days. Nimrod's a really great album. And I liked warning
and I liked parts of American idiot to be honest with you. Nah, church on Sunday is a great late
green day song. I don't know it. Now you got this guy too. I forgot about this third monster guy in
this in the movie. This bearded man that's sort of early in it. But it's still it's a third monster
to fill in the gaps between the other monsters. I like it. This guy looks like like if you told me
that this was Clive O and 20 years ago, I'd completely believe you. Who her boyfriend? Yeah,
Kirsty's boyfriend. Because he looks like Clive O and like before he became cool.
I'm not getting a Clive O and I'm getting a young Matthew Modine vibe for Jim. What are you talking
about? I'm getting a... This man looks exactly like Clive O and nothing like Matthew Modine. I'm saying
the main guy. Okay Madeline is in beautiful, right? He is. I'm not saying he's not Pat. Timothy Hutton.
Timothy Hutton. I'm getting a young Timothy Hutton vibe from this guy. You know, especially when I was
an NBC page when I was 23, I used to get on a daily basis. You look like a young Timothy Hutton.
Look at this. Now Julia. No thoughts on that. Lying wide awake in bed. Taken so much by the fact that
this guy fucked her so good switchblade style before he died, that she actually wants to go up and
visit his goddamn slimy body in the category. Yeah, it's insane. It's nuts. No sex is this good.
It's nuts. Look, she goes up to Sam. Yeah. Now, oh yeah. See, really this is kind of a similar plot
to little shop of horrors, where there's this creepy thing in the basement that needs blood to
get bigger and better. You know what? I never put that together before until right now and you're
absolutely right. I would have liked to have seen Rick Moranis in the stepmother role here. Sure.
Sure. Rick Moranis being laid down on the bed in a silk nightgum. Oh, you can have sex with me.
All right, I guess that's cool. Are you a fan of little shop of horrors?
It's one of my favorite movies, especially when I was a kid. I would watch it constantly. I love the
music. I love Steve Martin. I think he's hilarious. I love John Candy in it. Everybody.
Who's John Candy playing in it? He's just the host of that weird radio show, Ellen Green.
Everybody in the movie's awesome. Suddenly, see more. What more do you want to have you ever seen
the original with Jack Nicholson? I have. It's not a great movie. Nicholson's great. It's not
Nicholson's great in it, but Bill Murray and that Nicholson were all as tremendous. It was incredible.
I think also completely improvised from what I heard. Really? Yeah. Now on Broadway,
Jill and Hall is playing Seymour. I'll buy it. I would see it if I lived there.
Who's in the Bill Murray role? That I don't know. Who's playing the dentist? Probably Lance Bass or
something. I don't know. They just did a scaring nightmare sequence. That was freaky.
So he's got a lot of good things to keep the freakyness rolling pretty steadily throughout.
For a movie where if you didn't know any better, you'd think that it was going to be all about pinhead.
Yeah. Being like a sort of Freddie guy. Pinhead's not really in this a lot. That's probably
total seven minutes, I would guess. They do a good job of keeping that freaky factor going.
Yeah. Going strong, which I like quite a bit. Pinhead scared me. His associates scared me
much more. Like pinhead, I'd seen him so many times. That was kind of like only bothered by the
others that I thought were really, really gross. Well, the the chatterer is the freakyest one.
Yeah. I didn't. And then in this, there's that big thing that runs toward her in that hallway.
That was really freaky as well. Yeah. We had another monster. Yeah.
He's lousy with monsters. So these are things that are in just in hell hanging out. Are there souls
or because I I didn't get an explanation. Well, that's what upset me about this book,
The Scarlet Gospels that just came out. You know, before came out, they were saying that they were
going to really explain the the centabytes are part of the order of the gash yet another sexual
Sunday. Yeah. But they said they were going to kind of or Clyde Barker said he was going to kind
of explain like what that was and how they, you know, what the history of the centabytes. Okay.
And it didn't at all. Oh, it's just a story about pinhead trying to take over hell. And he's kind
of an asshole in it. And it's not that fun. Right. All right. I kind of quit on it halfway through.
Feel bad saying that. But I just wasn't feeling it, man. Clive, I'm sorry, baby. I'm sticking with you,
but I just wasn't feeling it. How many so are none of the movies are at none of the yeah, none of the
movies are adaptations of the books, are they? This is the adaptation of the hellbent on heart,
which I have. If you want to read it, you can borrow it after sure. Is it faithful? Unlike this woman?
Pretty faithful. Yes. Yeah. Julie is now at a bar trying to find men to go bring home to get their
blood so she can rejuvenate Frank. Right. Because she needs that dick. Now I was thinking because I
watched this and actually laughed to myself. Now I put myself in her husband's position. Okay. So
you're a man. You think you're happily married. You got a wonderful life. You're moving into a new
home with your lovely wife. And you find out that she's cheated on you with your brother. A,
that's like step one, like the most bare bones thing that she's done. Sure. They had hot,
switchblade style sex together. Then he dies. She's so obsessed with him that she continues to go
upstairs and like basically carry on an emotional affair with his charred remains. Right. Then she
loves him so much that she starts bringing home other strange men from bars. She makes out with
him whatever it takes to get him upstairs. Then she kills them and feeds them to the corpse in the
hopes of bringing him back so he can fuck her some more. Right. Imagine finding those things out as
the husband. This is a dedicated woman. This is a dedicated woman. Well, how unsatisfying must
their love life be? I mean, that's the thing. Is this guy a chump? Or is she just that rotten? You
know, who knows? The movie, the way the movie plays it is that she's just pure evil. She really
is. But I don't get why she married the guy to begin with. I'm confused by it. Also, by the way,
security. She's lured this guy home from a hopping bar. It's three o 'clock in the afternoon. Did you see
that bar? Yeah. It was swinging. Yeah. It was swinging. What bar has happened like at 3 p .m.?
I don't. Maybe it's a Saturday, Joe. No, please. It's not. This guy's a businessman. That just
skipped work. That was the issue. You thought strand credibility and hill razor? I'm not saying credibility.
I'm just saying, you know, okay. This guy didn't go back to the office. He's like, I'm just going
to go bang this fucking broad at home. Well, she took him. She told me not who wouldn't go. Who am I
thinking? Would you go? Would you go? Look at this. She goes, we don't need a bed. He's standing
in a room where there were rat -seating vomit. He is. He is drunk. There's no way that room doesn't
smell horrible. Yeah, there's a slime man sitting in the corner that he can't see. But maybe that's a
little hidden theme is like guys will do anything for sex. I think that's part of it like the depths
you'll sink to for your pleasure. Yeah. Pleasure. Pleasure. What is your pleasure? Plus, I mean,
this guy must have thought, hey, I look like Phil Collins. He's probably getting late all the time.
You know, he's got that weird bald, anti -bulled spot in the middle of his head. This guy looks like
Phil Collins. This lady looks like she was on ab fab. Exactly. I've never seen an England look like
in the 80s and 90s. This was like, this was like England hot back then. You'd call them all handsome.
Yeah, handsome woman. I'd have sex with this lady. Look at those big star earrings she's got on. Yeah.
Now, big tall hairdo too. Real tall hairdo. That's kind of tidy whiteies. Oh, Christ. Now they cut
that so it looks like he's staring into this man's butthole. Well, I mean, kind of liking what it is.
The room is lit up. It's three o 'clock in the afternoon. You got some. How is he not seeing
the rotting man in the corner? He's you know, he's drawn to the flesh. I mean, it just doesn't
it doesn't seem likely to me. He's saying he's got to go pee now. Too much to drink.
Ten to the old bladder. The guys. Oh, this guy if he could just get out of the room. Oh, there you go.
Hammer in the head. Oh, she beats him to death with a hammer. Christ. See, they go to terrible way to
die. This movie I've noticed, they go a little further into grossing you out. Like any other movie
I just basically hit some of a couple of times with a hammer. You see his jaw bashed off. Give it to me. Disgusting.
Give it to me, baby. Now she's got this guy's blood on her face. He could have any kind of
blood -borne disease. Oh, it's in her eye for crying out loud.
Don't look at me. Frank says again, I just killed a man for you and still I can't look at you.
Do me a favor. Bring me a corpse. Beat him up with a hammer. But don't look at me. Yeah. Hey,
a couple of demands. And then once you've done them, I'd also going to continue demanding certain
things from you. The way she loves it. Whoever played the Frank in the suit, crawling around the floor
deserved an Oscar as far as I'm concerned. It is the most disturbing body movement I've ever seen. Sure.
What's that thing on the wall? It's just wondering. And dryer. It looks like the world's largest
private bathroom. And dry. Yeah, what is that thing? I have no idea. She's looking good. That looks good.
Well, that blood splattered on that black lace. Something sexy about it. That's a good shot.
Gone girl did a similar shot. Uh -oh. People ripping off barker. I don't think he was ripping it off.
Baby. Although I have mentioned two finchermembers. Maybe he's a hell -raiser fan. David Fincher.
That's my Dennis Miller. Yeah, I got. Yeah, Sarah Arifant talking over to David Fincher.
Look at it. Oh, now she's mortified. She comes back in and sees that his corpse has been dry
of the blood, and now she's freaked out. She's going, oh, Jesus Christ. They don't really show how he
sucks it out. I mean, is it through the neck vampire? In the second movie, they show it. Okay. They
don't show it in this one. Frank can stand now. Yeah, this was very cool. How this all progressed.
It gets a little more flush on them each time. Look at this. That's very good makeup. Yeah,
and I love that he's constantly dripping, right? Constantly dripping.
Now, do you think he's in pain? Uh, yeah, probably. With all those exposed nerves and everything.
You know what? Probably one best makeup this year was like the last emperor,
like some movie where they like put like a couple wrinkles on a guy to age him over 30 years,
you know, because why would anyone in the academy watch this?
He, uh, the, the, for those of you not watching, uh, Frank is, uh, he, he looks like the, you know,
the, the biology book guy. Yeah, like no skin. You see all the organs and he's demanding that Julia
come to him so he can touch her and she let him grab a tit. Yeah. She let him get a tit grab in
even though his skull is showing because there's no skin on it. And her husband just came home. How do
you suck dried corpse in the floor in a, in a biology tech. Yeah, now imagine he opens this door
and she's like, um, so a couple of things. It's not what it looks like. So I can explain the, uh, first,
she's carrying very strange, carrying the, the sucked, leave it in the room. Where was she taking it?
That I didn't get either. She's taking the corpse into another room, leave it in the gross room that
he goes in. Yeah. Oh, hey, could not be sunnier outside. All of this. I think she, yeah, she
like fakes diarrhea. Oh, does she? The husband, by the way, seems really nice to, seems like a great
very understanding. He's in something else. I can't, he's in another horror movie. I feel like it's
like returned to Salem's lot or something. Okay. And then she says she's feeling sick. That's,
for those of you at home, if you ever caught in the midst of a murder, a double bathroom, say,
you're feeling sick. Yeah, apparently, that just gets you right out of it. And then he's like, oh, I'll
get you a sprite babe. Like, okay, cool. Like, and, and what does she do? Go out and kill more men
for this demon upstairs. So she can fuck a skinless body. Yeah. Does she, she fucks him before he's
like regular, right? Um, yeah. Yeah. I mean, he's not all the way back. You got to imagine,
what does that dog look like? I'm just exposed. A big fucking bloody dog. A big bloody old swinging
dog. This guy must be hung like fucking man or man. But why, yeah, you think you could see it, though.
Oh boy. Look, look, I love it. So she goes into the room to find him, to, to reef, engage with
this fucking abomination. And he taps her in the shoulder. She screams, right. When are you going
to be done being startled, Julia? You're in, you're, you're, you're way steep into this. No, I would
always be startled by this man. Look at this shit dripping up his shit. How do they make him keep
dripping like that? Brothers right before each take, just dumps them onto the tub of his head, you
know? God, that had to be a miserable makeup process. Maybe that's why the guy didn't play the part.
I did commercial. The first acting gig I ever got was a commercial for sports in that New York,
where I played their mascot who was a guy that a TV for a head. Yeah. And they actually hollowed
out a real TV and bolted it around my head. How was that? It was excruciating. Yeah.
It was horrible. It was really heavy. It was really hard to move around. And it would burn
incessantly after like an hour. And I'd have to have it on for three hours at a clip. It was horrible.
But, you know, as bad as that was, I couldn't fucking hold the candle of this, you know.
Well, it's horrible. We had to do a shot where I had to walk down the street and I couldn't see
anything. And they were like a guy had to walk in front of me and just I'd to follow his voice.
What was this for? Sports net New York. Okay. But I was shocked that how many people knew it was
me. They were like, I heard that you was in the, they knew my voice. Were you handsomely compensated?
No, it was a buyout. It was fine. I mean, at the time, I felt like I made a fortune. But, you know,
right. What are you going to do? Now we're in a pet store and here's the guy again. I love this part.
He eats the crickets. He's standing over the, like, slizzard tank. That's, oh, yeah.
This is really gross. But then what is this guy that's never really addressed? Oh, yes it is.
It's absolutely addressed. Okay. Then maybe I wasn't paying close enough attention.
Oh, it's so gross. What are those crickets? Yeah, are those crickets?
They're not crickets. They're, and this guy's eating them. Oh, that's so great. I love it.
I love it. Does she work in this pet store? Yeah, I believe so. She's just being like a good social
person kicking the guy out. I don't think she was like shopping for a pet that'd been odd.
Well, I think it's odd that she works in the pet store. Yeah. People have to work in pet stores.
You need jobs. This is the guy, this is the sort of, he's the sort of curator of the box.
Oh, yeah, yeah. The instrument who's, I assume, is Satan? Has there ever been a movie with more
hand on the shoulder scares? They've done it now eight times. You're doing plenty of hand on the shoulder
scares tonight. Hey, would you do earlier today? I worked all day. Yeah. Some of us work for a living
job. Why do you ask? I make a living doing standard. I did an audition for the tonight show that was
so bad. Valon? Yeah. The crowd was so bad that halfway through my audition. I said,
fuck it. I'm not, I'm done. Oh, wow. I just started doing other jokes. Pulled a Larry David.
Oh, they were terrible, terrible audience. So you were, you were supposed to do like a five minute
audition set. Yeah. Just like, I don't need them. I mean, they were not laughing at a goddamn thing.
Yeah. It was terrible. Does that matter for the booker? I guess it does. My friend is the
booker and the tape will never, you know, they'll never show anybody. I'll just get them in
up a different tape another time. I'm probably if my friend were the booker, I wouldn't have taken
that liberty. Yeah. But I've known the guy for years. I'm sorry to hear that. Well, what are you
sorry about? I wish it had gone well for you. Pat, we live, we learn, you live, we breathe, we die,
we breathe, we converse, we seduce. You know what I mean? Yeah, I guess it's, it's another day.
That's true. Well, you're not usually that guy, Joe. You're usually very despairing. I'm not anymore.
I've been so positively with you. You've been stone drunk every time I've expressed a piece. You
don't seem to remember it. And I also, I haven't had a drink in 12 days. Oh, well, I also have an
food. I'm doing a cleanse. Get him a medal, everybody. I'm just simply responding to your
accusations. Right now. I'm kidding. Come on. But the, the, it is true though. Every time I tell you
I'm happy, it's when we're in a bar drunk. Okay. Well, you're usually, to be honest, saying you're unhappy.
Huh? You're always saying that you're unhappy. Never saying that. Why don't I say that?
Joe, we've had this conversation a lot lately. No, no, no, I told you I was mad at my friend and then
you said you sound like you're unhappy. That was your saying. Yeah. No, you do. All right, fine.
All right. Are you happy? I'm not going to scroll through the text. I'm happy. Yeah. Yeah. All
right. I mean, everybody goes in and out of it. But what tech, what are you talking about? What
tech? Well, I think we should talk about your happiness after the show. All right. Joe, you're always
like I'm having a rough time. I'm, I got a cancel tonight. I'm, I'm in a bad place. I'm not
dreaming these things. But you're, you say the same things? Not I'm in a bad place. I
occasionally, you know, you have, I know I can't like not hang out because I'm in a bad place.
I think I just admit to it more than you do. That's probably true. I think I'm more in touch with my
feelings. You're a callous Irishman. Yeah. I mean, that's all true. You shove it all deep down in
your soul. Right. You'd be good at, you should get your hands on one of these boxes from the hell
razor thing and, and go to hell. That's what you want from me. I, I could see you being a guy
that's like, ah, fuck it. I would, I want to see what the, the pain and the pleasure are the same.
Yeah. No, that's not going to happen. I feel like if we were in the hell razor movies, I'd be the
nice husband. You'd be frank. Wow. You really view us differently than I do. Somebody would be
bleeding you back to life. Now, I can only orgasm if a homeless man watches.
I don't know if that's weird, but so it's usually like if I pick somebody up, it's like then I
also have to pay a homeless person. That's a shame. And a lot of times the, the lady in question is
not up for that. You know, and I get that. That's, that's really a shame. I hate to hear it. I really
hate to hear it. He's what I was going to say last night. I saw the man from uncle. Oh, I heard it was
great. No, who should have told you it was great. The reviews. It got okay reviews. It's fine.
Well, what were you expecting? I kind of didn't expect it to be good, but like, Henry Cable,
the most boring actor alive, Army Hammer, the second most boring actor alive. I like both of those
guys and I enjoyed the lone ranger. I don't care what anybody says. I didn't see the lone ranger.
You like, you like Henry Cable, an Army Hammer. I said Cable first. That didn't feel right.
Cable also didn't feel right. You're thinking of, you're thinking of, you're thinking like,
the easel. No, I, no, I'm not thinking of Jesus. I don't think it's Henry Cable. I think he's a great,
I think he's a great Superman. I enjoy him and Superman. I enjoy him in whatever works. The Woody Allen
movie. Those are the only two things I've hated that man of steel. And what was he in, he was like a
Rachel, Evan Rachel would or whatever name is, you know, whatever works. The guy that's like,
that lives on the boat. All right. And he's quite, quite sure. He's quite charming. All right.
Sometimes you say somebody's somebody. It's not the somebody that you said that it was. Pat,
here's what I'd like out of you tonight. One compliment and not a criticism. Any other
criticisms? Joe, you're unhappy. You don't have your facts straight.
Uh, uh, you talk too much about it masturbation at the top of the podcast. What have I done?
What have they done to deserve this? Nothing. I made an error on on the previous podcast where I
said that the guy who molested the kid, who, uh, directed powder, Victor Solva, I said,
he made a movie called The Fun House, produced by Francis Ford Copeland. It's not true.
The movie I believe was called Clown House, because I looked it up and it was like Roman Copeland or
another Copeland. It is Clown House. And if I'm not mistaken, Sam Rockwell is in Clown House.
That might be a young Sam Rockwell. I've got to publish the clarifications now for previous
podcasts. I'm working on a Sam Rockwell impression forever. I can't get it down, man. He's not
that easy to do. I can't get it down. You want to try? You want to try? You easily slide into it into a
Giamatti. And he seems kind of like a very toned down Giamatti to me. I slide into a Giamatti.
Yeah, like your voice naturally without much doctrine works as a Giamatti impression.
A little bit. Yeah. There's a little. I have a Giamatti. I have a Giamatti look. Yeah, true.
I feel like I could maybe take the parts that Giamatti turns down soon. Sure. You know,
I mean, you look like, here's a compliment for you. Look like a more attractive version of a
attractive version. Pat, I've never said this to a person. I want you out of my house for the
love of Christ. You a fucking cock sucker. Now, Frank's about to kill this poor bastard. All he's
trying to do is fuck his wife. I honestly can't believe how terrible this woman is. And she does stop
the killer. She's trying to stop Frank from killing her husband, though. She's saying, please don't.
Her husband thinks. Look at this. That's a rat open over the bed. Why does he do that to be like,
to be like, I'm in control here. That's so gross. Now, also, husband thinks she's crying. Please,
no, don't fuck me. Yeah. Now, the guy keeps going. That's why I didn't understand too. The guy
keeps going and she's going, I can't bear it. I can't bear it. The first time I hear I can't bear it.
I'm wrapping up the love making. I don't think that he's ever heard his wife say, well, because
here's why because upstairs she starts jumping. When they first go upstairs before the scene, she's
she's all over seducing him because she's trying to save him from Frank. Yeah. And then they go down
stairs. And then Frank turns out to be in their bedroom. So now she has to switch gears.
See? Yes. It makes perfect. I honestly look. I don't know what it is with me. I honestly thought
that she brought him up to the room. I think she did bring him up to the room and then she had second
thoughts. Oh, but I just thought that went in there because he's in the room. I didn't know he could
get out of the room. Well, I couldn't get out of the room. I just assumed there were rules. You
only see him in the room. Has there been one rule so far in this movie? No. And the blood bringing
people back to life because I was just like the brings demons we haven't seen in an hour and a
hand. Yeah, that's true. You know what I mean? There's no rules. Because I was also kind of like,
since when is there a bed in this upstairs blood -drenched attic? But now I understand. I heard
Clive Barker on set. He would say to people, hey, when they would ask questions about the script,
he would go, you go, hey, Steve, when would it roll with it, baby? That didn't happen. I heard that's
what he would say to people. He just plays it on a boombox.
This Chinese restaurant therein makes me so hungry every time I see it. It looks -
I told you I haven't eaten in 11 days, right? So good. So anytime I see food, except in this movie,
I'm not feeling hungry. I mean Pat, listen, you live the life. It's a real healthy routine you have where
you destroy yourself for six months and then - That's extreme. Not eat anything and drink vegetable
juice for 18 days straight. Once a year? Yeah, it's works. I'm sure it's a healthy way to do the
thing to do to your body. I mean, actors do it. Yeah, well, you know actors, they're healthy people.
Hey, Pat, I'd like to introduce you to my friend. His name's moderation.
But you do the same job. I mean, you're a big, I'm not drinking. And then I just get drunk.
Now, we're those kind of people. It's a very Catholic thing. I don't think - I'll take a little
break from the booze sometimes, but like I never did this cleansing to not eat and to drop. Wait,
this is Mishugana. I don't know. It works for me. Nobody does their own shit.
Well, I'm just saying, when you drop dead, you'll know why. Yeah, I'll stand over you,
saying I told you so. I would hope your reaction was something different than that.
I feel like if I died right now in front of you, it would just still be the same stoic.
I, you know, I'm a little more emotional than people think. I haven't cried in a decade, but -
And when I did, it was at the movie about Schmidt. No, it's a 127 hours, the other movie I cried out.
See, that's the problem. The last time I cried, I think was when I saw 127 hours.
Our relationship started with great emotion. You mean just that we liked each other?
We were - it was fast friends, but then we had that Christmas text where you said,
Joe, you texted me Merry Christmas. You were the only person I was going to text that to today.
Yeah, it was very nice. I felt like we got off at a nice emotional start.
And now I feel like you take me for granted.
Well, this sounds a lot like other relationships I've been in. Would I have left town for a week
and a half? You've texted, Joe, do you even miss me? You've texted that to me? Yeah. Well, you know,
these are kind of jokes, Joe. I know, they're jokes, but the thrill is gone. It's my point.
The thrill is gone. Our IPBBK. We're sleeping in separate rooms at this point.
Yeah, exactly. I saw - we're both reading separate sections of the newspaper at breakfast.
It's that we're at that scene in singles where they're -
Yeah, yeah. Hey you. Hey, what is it when they read the paper?
She's dating with Kyra Sejik's dating. It's really awful like -
Oh, yeah, yeah. Hey you. Hi. So just dead. The whole relationship.
Second podcast. We talked about singles as well. Why wouldn't you talk about singles?
I don't know. We haven't worked into this one yet.
Child Mala Station. No, I did. I brought out the powder guy. Oh, there you go.
But the man from Uncle, so I'm thinking - I had a joke about this today, but like
a studio, you come to them and you say, hey, I got Army Hammer hot off the Lone Ranger,
one of the biggest flops of all time. I've got Henry Keveel.
Right. And I want to reboot a 60s TV show that no one knows
with the worst title ever, The Man from Uncle.
I think it's a great title. Why on earth was this movie made and it cost $100 million?
Actually, I looked it up because $75 million. It was a bomb.
I just - I don't get it. How these things get made? How they decide what to throw money at?
You could make not - not kidding here. $75 million, cool, interesting movies that would all probably -
Some would turn a profit. You know that's not their goal.
Yeah, of course, but what is - what is their goal? They're losing money on Man from Uncle.
Unless it makes money overseas or something. They're like, oh, Superman.
You know that's not their goal. I remember talking like you've been in this town for five minutes.
Like you're chewing on a piece of straw. I'm saying why couldn't they? Why wouldn't they?
Well, why couldn't they? It's not the question, Pat.
Like anyone would know. Like it's - it can't be a shock to them that some of these movies bomb.
It can't be a shock that The Man from Uncle bombs.
But it's how they've been doing it forever. They put all their chips on one number
and try to make a windfall of money. Right.
You know - Okay, fantastic for completely bombed six years ago.
So what should we do? Let's make it again.
Well, and let's make this one suck too.
But that's Sony - that's Sony, uh, you know, trying to, uh, you know, they're saying,
hey, they fucked it up once. Now Marvel's hot.
Right. We're going to try to reboot it and do it right this time.
But then that director fucked it all up apparently.
Who was a cool director?
Made the old Chronicle.
Yeah, Chronicle. You know, I thought that movie was overrated.
But visually it was cool.
Yeah, it was fine.
It did some new things.
It was fine.
Frank is now trying - by the way, Frank, uh, just exposed him - not exposed like genitals.
Exposed himself to Kirsty for the first time.
Right.
She also came to terms with this very quickly.
Well, now, why did he expose himself to her?
Because these are - he's a dad, right?
He looks nothing like herself.
No, he's not her dad.
He's - these are Uncle.
Okay, yeah, yeah.
But he -
What is that? Come to Danny.
I don't - I - I think he was just in the -
Oh, because she - because she saw, um, uh, she knew Julia killed somebody upstairs.
And then she went upstairs.
And then the half dead guy came out like helped me.
And then - so the jig was up.
She knew what was going on.
And then Frank came out like,
hey, come here and fuck me.
All right.
Take your blood or something.
You know, like one of those things.
He was also trying to bang her, correct?
Yeah.
He's a pervert.
He's a man.
And this woman is still interested in him.
The married woman.
Yeah.
Yeah, Julia is a terrible person.
Crazy.
Look at these three.
Yankees have.
Who put these three people together?
To - to - they were, uh -
They - they were a do -wop group on the corner that came out.
Like, literally the three people that run the food truck.
Just were used as extras in the film.
This is supposed to be set in London, right?
You know, I've never been able to figure it out.
Are they - I hope that you give that guy a Yankees cap.
So we believe this was New York City.
I don't think it's supposed to be set in London
because nobody is English accents except Julia.
That's true.
It feels very British to me.
It's clear that we'll look at this fucking hospital room.
She's in the Cry 6.
You know, you wouldn't see a hospital room like that in the States.
I don't think you'd see one like it in London either.
But I don't find -
Have you ever been to London?
Yeah, I have.
Maybe two years of talking about it.
I didn't go to the hospital while I was there.
Wasn't that kind of a trap?
Look at that guy.
That doctor has some kind of weird makeup on.
You know, I always wonder in both horror movies and in comedies.
Like, David Lynch always casts
completely freaky -looking people like you've never seen before.
Crazy faces.
Everybody looks interesting.
And it keeps you on your edge.
He doesn't even have to do any work, really.
He does, everything's amazing.
Then in comedies,
why wouldn't you cast like funny -looking people in these bit parts?
Get some extra laughs.
Look at this weirdo.
They're always casting people boring people.
No, I'm not talking deformities.
Jesus Christ.
I'm talking like interesting -looking people.
Get a big fat pig in there.
We all laugh at the fatsoes.
That way you want pet?
That the fuck is wrong with you.
No, not at all what I was saying.
Jesus.
I'm saying get people with some character in their face in these bit parts.
They always have like generic boring -looking people in movies.
This movie's doing a good job.
You got some weird -looking people.
Right.
I agree.
Interesting.
Let's say interesting -looking.
We did judge beauty.
Like under the skin.
There's a great example.
I love that movie.
Kind of a horror movie.
You won't watch it because of that guy.
I get it.
It upsets me.
And that's an actual deformity.
I know, I don't say that to be mean.
It looks like the elephant, man.
But somehow
I can't watch the elephant.
His real life face
is more unsettling than the elephant, man.
Well, I heard that if you go back and re -watch the elephant, man.
Now it just looks like bad makeup.
I don't know about that.
I don't know if that's true.
I can't watch it.
I can't watch mask.
I can't watch the elephant, man.
I can't, and it's not out of
meanness.
It's out of it.
I find it very upsetting.
All right.
Now you were saying last week on the podcast.
What?
Show me something.
You were like the director didn't want to have Freddie Krueger something
you had to look away from.
In horror.
But you were like, I want that.
Give me something I have to look away from and make it disturbing.
One horror.
Now you're saying the exact opposite.
No, in horror, it's
Kirstie just opened the box.
Here we go, Goy.
Here we go.
The wall just opened up.
That means pinheads coming.
No, it's, it's, see that corridor pet.
Yeah, this part in the wall.
Probably kind of bothered me also.
What did it bother you?
It's horrifying.
It's hell.
That's what that's the gateway.
Did they have to make hell so horrifying?
Sparkle a little heaven in for us pussies.
What did you want hell to look like, Pat?
I don't know.
I thought it would be red.
Maybe a pitch for it.
Maybe a more like a bam, bam bigelow scene
with a painted flames everywhere.
I mean, give me one guy with a fork tail kind of shaking his toes.
Sure.
You like more of a hot rod race kind of.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah, I understand.
Like the mascot of this very podcast.
I understand.
This thing that comes at her is disturbing.
And I also wondered if you can see the man's legs
who's running it.
I don't think you can.
I paused it and I was like, I think I see this guy's legs.
But maybe I didn't.
With horror, I like gruesome and gross and
disturbing and blah, blah, blah.
When it's a real person, it upsets me
because I feel terrible for that person.
Sure.
So it's hard for me to watch.
This guy seemed really at ease
and actually does full frontal nudity in under the skin.
God bless him.
Yeah, go for it if you're going to do it.
This part always reminds me of like a like this big
worm big adventure is kind of what the vibe is.
It makes me think a gym like a gym henson kind of thing.
Yeah, we're noises it's making are really what makes it unsettling.
It makes me think a labyrinth.
Yeah, sure.
You know, because this hallway looks like the labyrinth.
Labyrinth always scared the shit out of me.
Do you ever see the dark crystal?
Of course.
That one is to this day freaks me out.
Yeah, I love it.
It's one of my favorite movies of all time.
It scares the shit out of me still.
I don't feel she's running fast enough.
I would be running much faster.
I think the I don't think it's supposed to be like literally
look how fat she's you know she's running this fat.
I think it's just she's running.
Okay, she's running.
No pinhead.
I want it some pinhead there.
We didn't get any pinhead.
He's barely in it right now.
I've already said that.
Sorry.
Well, you I'm just pointing out.
I've said it.
There was a time when we used to listen to each other.
I went when I lived in New York.
I went down to I believe film forum on Halloween
because I had no friends.
I had lived there for two months and had not.
I don't think I'd said a word.
Do you have one uplifting story about you moving to a city?
No, you move here.
You're gated into a prison.
You're masturbating for money.
Well now it's like some kind of boogie nights climax.
Yeah, it wasn't like that.
You go to New York.
You have no friends.
You're going to movies alone.
For three months, I don't think I said one word.
But the stories have had beginnings
because I wound up with lots of friends
and having a good time.
But at first I didn't know anyone.
So Halloween night, I had nothing to do.
And I went to film forum and watched this all night horror festival.
And they showed Donnie Darko.
Buy yourself.
But buy myself.
Donnie Darko.
The saddest thing to remember.
They showed this movie called King of the Ants.
That was terrifying.
You ever see that movie?
It's with William Shatner.
Is it not?
No.
Okay, sorry Pat.
I don't know.
George went to it.
But it's really, really scary.
King of the...
What's about giant ants?
No.
What's it about?
It actually was more of like a very real life horror kind of thing.
It was Stuart Gordon who did reanimator.
Oh, all right.
I'm in.
I want to see.
Man, it was really freaky.
And then Hellraiser was like the 2am movie.
And I was like, I don't want to get out of Hellraiser at 4am
and then have to walk home through the streets of New York.
I couldn't stomach that idea.
Well, so I just went home.
It's a good thing you didn't because in that book,
the Scarlet Gospels I was told you about.
These centenabytes are popping up all over New York.
Yeah.
See, I wouldn't have been good with that.
I do get very scared of things when I watch them along.
That guy is really gross.
Who Butterball?
Yeah.
He just licked his lips.
Yeah, I saw that.
She's pretty scary.
Why is her throat propped open?
Do you have a problem with it?
It's awesome.
That's why.
All right.
Oh, listen or growling.
That's pretty cool.
Like just take the pins out and light your throat close up.
Let it heal naturally.
He's put a lotion on it.
That's such a great line when he says that.
Oh, no tears, please.
Such a waste of good suffering.
No time for argument.
He's so cool.
He sounds like Darth Vader.
I love him.
I love him so much.
Now she makes a deal with him here.
She makes a deal with him.
I tell you what, they're not going to take her.
Take that pin out of your nose.
I'm giving more advice to this girl.
Slide it out of your nose.
Then you don't have the pin in your nose anymore.
And sew up the neck hole that you have.
Then you'd be a nice looking gal.
You could get dates.
She doesn't want to sew up the neck hole.
The point is this is who they are.
All right.
The move is about being yourself.
That's what you're saying.
The whole movie is a metaphor for goth kids.
I mean, let's be honest.
Yeah, for sure.
You know, a lot of black leather and nobody understands me.
I live at a dark box.
I used to drink at this bar.
And Holly would call it board nurse.
And it was next to a club that had a -
Alone?
No, we were the sad part of the story.
And I had -
It was next to this bar that had a golf night every Saturday.
And we would go just so we could watch these people.
And there was a girl
yanking her boyfriend around on a chain,
a dog collar and chain.
And he was wearing a shirt that said,
I have a tiny penis.
And she kept like bringing her around.
I was like, I want you to meet my boyfriend.
He has a tiny penis.
And we were like, okay,
it was like some weird punishment they were doing.
And that boy was Jason Schwartzman.
Yeah, he later became Rushmore.
My -
My friend at work is reading the -
Are listening to the autobiography of the -
Of Jason Schwartzman?
No, of Rob Lowe.
And that's got tons of ass stories in it.
Well, they said every chapter ends with uh -
So I was hanging out with this girl.
And it was no big deal.
I mean, it wasn't like she was anybody famous or anything.
But in just one year's time,
she was Winona writer.
And every chapter ends like that.
He doesn't tell you who the person is that he's talking about.
And then he goes -
Does he bang all of them?
I think he bangs most.
He was in the first sex tape scale.
Oh, Poonhound.
I know, that was when people gave him about sex tapes.
Yeah.
He had a sex of the 16 year old girl
and now we all love him.
But he was 21.
But he didn't even get in trouble for bang in the 16th.
Nobody even cared about that part.
They were just like, can you believe it's on video?
Yeah.
He videotaped it, that degenerate -
I don't remember what he was doing about the 16 year old.
Yeah.
It was two girls, I believe.
It was.
Yeah, that girl there, that guy -
I'm sure Rob said of the police like,
hey, you know, fellas,
he was 16 going on 40.
And they high -fived him and sent him on his way.
That's probably how that went down.
Oh, I love it.
I love it.
Now, who's banging Julie?
Is this another flashback?
I believe so.
Oh, okay, she's having a flashback.
Okay, because this is the final,
we're in the final run now.
She's preparing to feed her husband to Frank.
How good must this sex have been?
The sacrifices she's willing to make
to get one more taste.
It must be Dick Almighty, man.
Plus, then he's proven he's not even going to be faithful
to her when it does happen.
He's trying to hit on her niece.
I know.
The guy's like,
yeah, I know this woman's murdered 10 men
to have another taste of my dong.
But I think I'm going to hit on her step -niece.
It's her stepdaughter first.
Stepdaughter.
It's his blood niece.
His step, his blood niece.
He's trying to fuck his blood niece.
Sorry, I wasn't following these family tree of hell -reson.
That'd be a good name for a harm movie.
Blood niece.
Wouldn't it?
Yeah, she's like your niece,
but bloody.
Now, this is frank in the dad's skin now.
If you can't tell by the boils in the bloody scene.
Now, how?
Outside of his head.
How does that work?
How does he slip on the skin?
It's the same thing that bothers me about mission impossible
when they put on the mask and they look exactly like the guy.
It's ridiculous.
You see the new mission impossible?
I loved it.
It was fucking awesome.
I said it was almost Mad Max good.
It was so good.
Yeah, when he was down in that like washing machine thing.
Yeah, I was.
That was amazing.
It was tremendous.
The whole plane sequence was out of this world.
Yeah, loved it.
His entrance into the movie,
him running over the hill and ducking.
Can you get me on the plane?
They're better than the bonds, I would say.
It was so fucking good.
But it does still bother me that they put on a mask
and then they're suddenly the other person.
Sure.
Well, two same body.
Two really overdid it.
But like same body.
Everything.
Same everything.
Two was like a dog walks up and then peels off a mask
and it's Tom Cruise.
Like two was ridiculous.
That's ridiculous.
That didn't happen.
It didn't happen.
Come on.
Then John Wu, you know, real hit or miss that.
He didn't do a movie since.
He was the biggest thing since sliced bread for a while there.
No, but he made.
You know how big sliced bread is.
He made it.
Can't eat a sandwich, man.
No, it's Ang Lee.
Wow.
Oh, I guess they all look alike to you, Joe.
Ang Lee and John Wu could not be more different, direct.
I thought Ang Lee actually made Mission Impossible too.
Because I'm thinking of mission.
I'm thinking of how he made the Hulk.
Yeah, that's true.
I mean, he also made Mission Impossible.
How bad was that Hulk when Nick multibytes into that electric wire?
It starts okay and then they start switching shit around
and then it's pretty stupid.
It could have been good.
Well, you know, why wouldn't Edward Norton play the Hulk?
I like the Edward Norton one.
That's the Ang Lee one.
No, it's not.
The only one is the Eric Banna one.
Oh, God, the Edward Norton one is good.
The Edward Norton one was Tim Roth
and he becomes a bombination.
I, they all run together to me.
But yeah, the Ang Lee, the Hulk move,
he's running the other way better.
Way worse.
The Ang Lee one is bad one.
The, the, the, the way worse.
That's why the Norton one's good.
It's like that's part of the official Marvel canon
in the Avengers and everything.
Well, that doesn't make it good.
It's a, I haven't enjoyed it.
I'm a bad person to talk to about this.
I don't like those movies.
Does she not know?
Does she not see the blood dripping out of her dad's hand?
She's clearly blinded by lust for this man.
How's she doing that?
Wait, who's blinded by lust?
We're talking about the daughter.
Oh, the daughter.
Yeah, I don't know.
I guess she just didn't look.
Oh, maybe she, I think we talked through it.
Maybe she does know it's not her dad.
Oh wait, wait, does she?
No.
That's for, is she, is anyone come back for a hell razor too?
Yeah, she comes back.
Jen, just, uh, I don't want to ruin anything
but she's back.
Curse he's back.
There they are.
I love the thought that someone listened to this movie
with us talking over it could have something spoiled for them.
Well, here's the thing.
Like, hey, he ruined this movie that I can't hear.
They broke.
They broke another rule that centabytes just appeared
and they, nobody opened the box.
Whatever, though.
Why is Curse fighting that?
I'm confused.
I got damn it.
This is bad for the podcast, Pat.
I don't know what's happening in the movie right now.
I got really lost.
She doesn't know that's her dad yet or she does.
Uh, she knows, I believe.
No, that's not her dad.
That's Frank.
Okay, she still thinks it's her dad.
She thinks it's her dad.
Why is she not noticing the blood then on the side of his heads?
She probably just like, hey, there's some weird shit going on in this house.
My dad's heads all bloody by the side of his hair.
She's been through pretty rough days.
She's just got chased by a whole demon.
By the way, how did she get out of the mental institution
and she was locked up?
Look, we've got a lot of questions.
I'm sure she has even more.
All right, now she knows.
Okay, she thought her dad killed.
Yeah, when her dad tries to bone her,
she's like, oh, okay, I get it.
She thought her dad killed Frank.
She thought that dead body upstairs was Frank.
It's not it's her dad.
That's why when Pinhead said we want the man who did this,
she thought she was had to turn her dad over and she said no.
Right.
I mean, and this Julia lady is willing to fuck this guy
with skin hanging off of his face,
which is grosser than when he just had like his shoes.
She just doesn't care.
Oh, there's the switchblade that he used to bang his...
Yeah.
Why?
I like...
Why doesn't he have Frank's voice anymore, by the way?
Do you notice that?
I thought he was getting a more normal voice
because he's becoming more normal.
Now.
No, he's got...
It's just the actor that plays the dad.
It's his voice.
Yeah.
Yeah, they could...
They've dubbed everything else.
Why not dubbed them?
Yeah.
Oh, God.
Oh, and he takes...
He takes Julia's flesh here.
That's the line.
Nothing personal, baby,
as he sucks her life out of her.
But that's good makeup.
Man, I'm so surprised that this guy proved not to be trustworthy.
After all she did for him.
His face doesn't look any better
after sucking out Julia's essence.
Right?
Why didn't it heal as wounds up?
Yeah, it should've...
Breaking...
Clive break the rules, Barker.
Clive break her.
Of repeat rules.
Oh, no, no.
No, no, no.
There you go.
Still love the movie.
I'm not shitting on it.
But...
No, I mean...
The unexplained is what...
The horror's all about, you know?
That'd be a good name for a horror movie.
The unexplained.
What's going on?
I don't know the unexplained.
And that's the whole trailer.
Cheech Marin is the unexplained.
Why Cheech Marin?
I don't know, he needs work.
No, he doesn't.
I haven't seen him in a long time.
They've been doing those Cheech and Chog tours.
They're mopping up, man.
Oh, all right, great.
Yeah, they're killing us.
Well, then let's cast somebody else.
Yeah, and I kept them
if you thought Cheech needed work over Tommy.
Yeah, well, I don't like Tommy.
Wow.
I think Cheech carried Tommy for 50 years now.
I think Tommy's very funny.
All right.
They're both very funny.
Do you know Tommy?
Not at all.
Did you work with him or something?
No, neither one of them.
Okay.
Hey, you used to work with...
You worked with Roddy Roddy Piper,
were you sad when he died?
Of course I was.
I um...
I mean, to tell kind of a strange story about it,
I was doing the extras for the always sunny DVD.
And Rob McElhenney called and was like,
you guys got to come down here right now.
Roddy Roddy Piper's on fire.
He's been telling stories for like four hours.
You got to get him on tape.
And we're going to do a DVD extra
like Roddy Roddy Piper tails.
And he's telling like some of his best stories.
And by the time I got to set,
we were interviewing him,
and he was just like very much not making sense.
Like his brain had been banged around so much
that maybe he had a good hour or two of stories,
but then eventually it just stopped.
That's really disgusting.
But he couldn't have been more charming,
it couldn't have been more nice.
He was funny.
But the story's disgusting.
The story's didn't make sense.
Because it sounds like you're saying
Roddy's brain damage was disgusting.
No, he was a sweet, delightful man.
He was very funny in the show.
I was saying that head full of maggots was disgusting.
Yeah, well, you got to describe it to the people
that aren't seeing this right now.
A head came out of the darkness
and maggots fell out of it.
Yeah, that was really gross.
Roderoy Piper, a great man.
It is gross.
I'm gonna see if there's a way next Halloween
that I can do that to you somehow.
Fill a fake head with maggots and throw it at me.
Like a prank.
Well, let's come into your house and do it.
Let me tell you how that ends.
We never hang out again.
Ever.
And I don't answer your texts or calls.
So if that's worth it, do you?
Great.
You would never hang out with me again over that.
That's a guarantee.
If you throw a maggot filled head at me.
No, I didn't say throw it at you.
I would just dip it next to you and freak you out with it.
You'd never talk to me.
Do you do it in your home?
Like you're spilling maggots on the floor of your home?
That's where it's really scary.
Yeah, so now my floor is covered in maggots
and we're not friends anymore.
The maggots.
I wake up November 1st
and I delete your number from my phone.
Really?
Yeah.
Jesus.
Sorry.
You're a real fucking thing.
I don't need friends that I can't trust
not to throw maggot filled heads at me.
One time my friend Chip got mad at me
because we went down to the Jersey Shore.
We went down to Atlantic City.
It was me, my friend Chip,
and my friend Scott who you've met.
And I went into the bathroom, man.
Did you fix your hair up nice?
Stress yourself up pretty?
Yeah, for the tables.
For the table guests.
We went to Atlantic City
and like to reference things.
Scott was in the shower
and Chip was in the bedroom part of the room.
And while he was in there,
I went into the bathroom
and I shit onto the soap dish.
Oh god.
And then put it on the sink.
So it doesn't matter with you.
It was one of the funniest things I ever done in my life.
I was uncontrollably laughing.
I couldn't get my shit together.
It was laughing, sorry.
Couldn't get your shit together
because it was sitting on a soap dish.
Chip was so offended
that he didn't speak to me the rest of the day.
And it was my birthday.
Chip, you and I are kindred spirits
because I think I would probably be like,
yeah, you're on your own this week.
Well, you're an animal.
It was my birthday.
I've never liked pranks.
I had for Christ's sakes, Pat.
Would you get over it?
I don't like them.
I think they're made.
You're a TV comedy writer.
You don't like pranks.
Yeah, you can be both.
The hell are you talking about?
That's really gross.
The centabytes are here for Frank.
This is the big climax now.
Oh, look at her hair.
I never noticed that the weird
centabyte lady has like strands of hair.
Frank.
They're going to take her.
Here we go.
I see.
Now, this is what they lost
with the centabytes.
Okay.
Here we just said to Kirstie.
Pinnet just said,
Bench.
No, no, no.
What Pinnet said.
Oh yeah.
Just said to Kirstie.
This isn't for your eyes.
He's telling her leave.
This has nothing to do with you.
He's a rational man.
Yeah, he's a rational man.
He's a judge.
He's like, you seem like
you could probably
have a nice time going
with a fella to a movie and holding hands.
You don't need to be exposed
to this underground world
of torture to have sex.
But, you know, and that's the thing
I didn't like about the new book is
that they make him,
he's just like a raging asshole in it.
You're like, this isn't what Pinnet,
this isn't how he rolls.
People change, you know.
Maybe Pinnet had some
misfortunes in his turn.
Eternal demons change.
I didn't know that.
I thought, kind of,
if you could count on somebody
it'd be a centipede.
Jesus Christ.
This is really gross.
And then this is the part.
Yeah, I looked away for this
when I watched where he goes.
Terrible.
I love this line at the end.
Jesus wept.
Yeah, that's funny.
Why does he say that?
Like, I suffered as he did or something?
I think Jesus, I mean,
Jesus wept means like
this is fucked up basically, right?
I'm not a big Bible head.
I don't think so. I think it's just,
I think he's saying like,
this is my crucifixion.
Oh, all right.
Well, it thinks a little highly of himself.
Well, yeah, Frank does think highly of himself.
Yeah, and that's a good little thing.
He fucks women with a scratch plate.
That's true.
Not with us, which,
yeah, there's another rule broken.
Centipede scraping the wall,
blood's coming out of it.
Why are they coming after Kirsty now?
They just tried to save her.
Ugh.
They just said,
this is not for your eyes,
get out of here,
and now they're coming after her.
Why is that happening?
Maybe because she didn't get the hell out of there
when they told her to.
She left, didn't she?
No, she's, I don't know.
She watched the guy say as Jesus wept on.
Is that what it is?
Yeah, I see a book one go into my
guy dressed in the skin of my dad.
I leave.
Sears Pint, he's telling you,
okay, so this is the penalty now.
You got to come with us.
You saw all the other stuff.
Okay, I get it.
Now,
has there ever been a more warranted, oh shit,
than that one?
Yeah.
And she's, now,
Kirsty closes the box in order to,
I guess, trap the centibites again,
which they can get out of the box anyway we've seen.
And I like the Pint head just goes,
don't do that.
Yeah.
Hey, yeah.
Well, they establish in part three that he can't take the box from you.
It has to be given to him.
Okay.
Well, that's how this works.
This is part one, so.
But why didn't he fly his chains at her?
A lot of questions here.
Clive, I got a lot of questions.
I'd like to get you on the phone.
I'd like to discuss this with you, please.
I got a lot of questions for Clive.
Break the rules, Barker.
And Chrissy is played by Chrissy,
the same actress and everything.
And the second one?
Yeah.
That looked out for her, getting that part.
She's in two.
She has a tiny cameo in three.
Con.
She turns up again in like five or six.
I have six, it is actually.
Boy, I can't believe I remember that, but I do.
What?
How lucky are you as like kind of an okay generic actor to get like the lead in one of these eight
part things, you know?
What a dream.
I love to do movies like this.
Yeah.
Wouldn't this be a fucking ball?
I mean, like, saw their swapping out people every time.
But like that, anything where you can like, carry it out.
Except the one chick was in a few of them.
That's you, whatever.
Oh, who's the broad?
Who's the broad that was in a few of the saws?
She was a victim in one, and then she's in part two.
And she falls into like the needle pit.
And then she becomes like his apprentice.
I, Tandy, Tandy, she's got like a interesting name.
She was on Becker.
She played the dumb girl on Becker.
I don't know.
Yeah, well, what are you going to do?
I interviewed all of them.
I used to work for Cinematical, which was a great movie website for AOL.
I got to interview all these people from saw.
This thing's back now.
Now this big, this dog thing is back.
And she grabs the box at electrocute, sir.
Why did that happen?
I mean, I hate to, I just hate to ask so many god damn questions, Pat.
But I'm sorry I am.
Yeah, I mean, I think honestly, because in writing stuff,
all you have to do is ask yourself these questions and try to make things work.
And it's so exhausting that when I sit down to watch a movie,
I tend to not ask questions.
And the people who are like, well, why did this?
Why did this?
You know, I get it.
I have fun having those conversations,
but I'm never doing it myself.
I just let things happen.
Well, you know, that's the world you want to live in.
It is.
I question everything else in my life.
I don't need to question the movies.
You know, I spend so much time being like, well, I don't know if this is right.
I don't know if it's good.
I don't need to do that when I watch a movie.
Hey, welcome to Obama's America.
That's what I say.
I don't know what that means here.
That's a joke.
I was making like a political joke that you don't get involved.
No, I don't get involved.
I have nothing against Obama.
I take that back.
It was just, he's a great man.
I thought it was a funny thing to say.
Who do you think's running our country coming up here?
It's Trump.
The question could be Trump.
It's, it could be.
It's insanity.
It could be time for the pendulum to swing again.
This is how it goes every eight years.
It goes back the other way.
I don't think even Republicans
trust Trump run on the country.
They don't, but he's leading the polls.
Yeah.
He's leading the polls.
All right.
I can't go much further with political talk.
I don't know what I'm talking about.
Neither do I.
Okay.
Look at that shirt.
I'm going to make sure I know what leading the polls mean.
But that's, I read it today or something.
That shirt is the stupidest choice to end a horror movie.
Unless it's like,
well, it was the year that it, you know,
I mean, Joe, it's of the time.
I don't know that that was of the time.
That's like something that kid or play would wear
in house party three.
The pajama jam.
Well, the funny thing is is every time he looks at that
cross -colors ray on shirt that he's wearing,
he's going to go,
I fought demons in this shirt.
Oh, I'd be done with that shirt.
There's my demon shirt.
Yeah.
Every time he get it out of the closet,
do you ever wear it again?
Or is that it?
I probably wouldn't.
I also wouldn't wear it because I would have to beat the shit
out of myself if I saw me in that shirt.
All right, here comes the answer to your question
about the, you know,
who's the bearded man or whatever.
Yeah.
He's coming back in in a second here.
Give it a second, Pat.
Be patient.
Oh, there he is, see.
I might have been peeing during this part or something.
What are these piles of fire, by the way?
Is this the house?
It's just a field of like homeless people fires.
I guess that.
Yeah.
Very strange.
I think, you know, and I agree with this.
I think somebody like Clyde Barker,
even though I don't think I've seen any of his other movies,
I think he just wanted to create a mood.
I agree.
And I dig that, especially in horror.
I'm not knocking it.
I'm just asking questions.
What's Clyde Barker's like second most successful?
Like he did like Lord of Illusions.
I don't think I've ever seen any of his movies.
Night, nightbreed probably.
Yes, I think I've been tend to watch nightbreed.
It's in the queue.
I am not a fan of nightbreed.
Okay.
Have you seen the director's thing?
The director's cut?
Yes.
Okay, I'm not a fan.
All right, I'm going to watch it.
I'm not a fan.
It seems to me to be a very creative dude.
He is very creative and I think he's great.
I just, you know,
but he never had another big like franchise.
Canon movie other than that's right.
Ah, this was the biggest, yeah.
But I mean, this is to me.
Despite all my questions,
it's, it's masterful.
Right back to the beginning.
A new man gets the box.
Great ending.
Can't argue that.
I love anything that starts.
Ends where it started.
Frank the monster.
Okay, so we weren't clear on Frank the monster.
Oliver Smith.
Oh, now why would you do that?
Do you think Sean Chapman was like,
I'm not sitting for all that makeup.
Now, I just think they probably want it to somebody.
Look at this in the credits.
I love this lead cinema by Doug Bradley.
Before they had an end.
Wow.
Yeah.
For the end of Jackie Hellrazer.
That's another cheesy part in the,
in the book that he just put out.
There's this whole thing where if you call pinhead pinhead,
he gets furious.
Really?
Because it's like, don't call him that.
He hates that nickname.
Yeah.
Do they, when do they refer to him as pinheads in the movies?
Or that's just what society called him?
It's just kind of what the name he got from the fans,
I guess, caught on or whatever.
Gotcha.
But they put this thing in the book where it's like,
you better not call him pinhead to his face.
He'll get real hot.
Well, they took that from back of the future.
Well, whatever.
Ladies and gentlemen, that was Hellrazer.
Yeah, it was a wild ride.
That's makes two nights in a row,
where the last thing I do before I go to bed
is watch Hellrazer.
Well, horrific visuals and then go to sleep.
And count the minutes till Halloween, Pat,
because a handful of maggots is coming at you.
And you need to treasure
these last few months of our friendship, Joe.
I haven't treasured the first few months of the friendship.
I'm not going to treasure the last few.
Right, fair enough.
This has been, we'll see you in Hell.
Again, you can follow us on Twitter,
or send us any questions or comments or requests.
Yeah, I'm at the Patrick Walsh,
P -A -T -R -I -C -K -W -A -L -S -H.
Joe DeRosa is Joe DeRosa Comedy.
And tweet us questions, thoughts, movie suggestions,
stuff you want us to talk about,
thoughts, criticisms.
Look us up on iTunes, review the show,
give us that five stars, we'd love it.
Thanks for listening.
We'll be at the mile high horror fest in Colorado.
Littleton, Colorado.
First week in of October,
we don't know yet which day we're performing.
It'll be Saturday or Sunday,
or not performing, but we'll be doing a live podcast there.
Details to come, but please come out for that.
It's going to be a lot of fun.
You've been listening to, we'll see you in Hell,
a presentation of the Fangoria podcast,
Network Produced by Thomas DeFail,
an executive produced by Ken Hanley of Fangoria Entertainment
for press opportunities,
advertising inquiries,
and information about we'll see you in Hell.
Contact Ken at Fangoria .com.
Thanks everybody.
Thanks guys.