Summer is here, and Bet MGM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bet MGM Casino.
Spin on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Waiter, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only, games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal, durable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
Gambling problem, call 1 -800 -Gambleer.
Hello, everybody. And welcome to we'll see you in hell. This is we've been we've been keeping
I'm coming to you week after week, but Joe and I haven't seen each other in about a month.
A little peek behind the curtain.
We had to stockpile a bunch due to holiday travel, but we're reunited and Joe, it feels so good.
It does actually.
I'm happy to see you, man.
It's been a while.
Staying.
Remember staying.
It's, look, if we could tie one more shitty to mediocre song into this reunion.
I was, my old, this girl used to hang out with, we were in high school.
She was a pot head before I even understood where she got pot.
We were in like early college.
And I was straight laced at the time.
And what kept me off pot for probably 10 additional years after this was one night we're watching
some show on television, Friday night videos or something, it might have been like a tonight show type
here. And stained that Aaron Lewis is sitting in a chair, he sits in a stool with his head in
his hands is how he performs because he's so serious, you know, and he sings, it's been a while
and I'm getting ready to like laugh and turn and make fun of it with her and I look and she's like
leaning into the television mouth slightly open hypnotized by this stained song
And it ends and I was like, well, I'm not gonna make fun of her. She's enjoying the song and it ends and
She turns to me very slowly and was like holy shit
That is a deal breaker if I've ever heard one
Well, we were never romantically involved. My god
Woof woof woof woof woof there it is I remember
Excuse me. I remember when the
the, uh, not the last tool album, the one, the, what was the one that had been down, down,
down, down, down, down, down, I think there was the last tool album.
You mean, I know the pieces that second to last one.
Yeah.
I don't know the last one.
They had a lot, the, uh, slightly more watery version of that sound on the next
album.
Anyway, when that song got released, I remember a friend of mine heard it first and he
He's here in the new tool song, and I go, no, no, no, and he goes, fucking sucks.
And I was like, oh, really?
That's a bummer.
Yeah.
It sucks.
And he's like, yeah.
And then I was listening to the rate, the alternative station in my town.
And they go, uh, up next, the new tool song coming up soon.
And then after the, they went to a break and then after the break, they played it's been
a while.
And I thought that was the new tool song.
Wow.
He sounds enough, enough like him that if the, I'm sure he was influenced by.
Yeah.
And I was like, what the fuck this blows never after that? I was like,
didn't even do it. I was like, oh, this new tool song is pretty good.
I thought, didn't anyone, and it was a cool song. Yeah. And I never liked
tool. I like that song. I actually, well, I mean, that was not my kind of music
at that time as we've discussed. But I, I preferred perfect circle to tool.
I never liked the perfect circle. I like that first album a lot. I mean,
I'll dislike, I might just don't care. It's very melodic. It's like,
pusifer, pusifer, I remember pusifer. It's a, you know, the, the, the, the, I just got
that. Is that pussy fur? Oh, wow. Well, holy shit. All right. Well, I always thought it
was a play on Lucifer, but pussy, like pusifer. But I think you're right. I think it's both.
I think it's my super and pussy fur. And the lady from resident evils in that band, isn't
I don't care enough to even look at my phone.
Speaking of, by the way, I know, I really, I had a lot of time off, and I got to really
peruse through the Facebook page, and I engage with y 'all every couple days.
And it's a lot of fun for me.
But you guys were giving us a lot of shit on one of these posts.
about being on our phone at the movie theater.
And it was going back to the Justice League.
And folks, last Jedi, we weren't bringing the phones out.
This is Justice League four weeks into its release.
My second viewing of it.
His second, six people,
well, they're bothered by the lights from the phones.
There's six people in the theater.
No one like behind us who would be bothered by it.
And I don't do that.
I don't bust my phone out for movies.
That's kind of like a holy time.
You got to watch that shit. I just want you to know we're not those annoying people although in terms of things
That you could do that piss people off at a movie theater for me that almost doesn't register if someone in the row in front of me
Has their phone out it honestly doesn't bother me. It's not too bad if it's constant
It's the modern day version of talking during the movie people don't talk as much during movies anymore. That's not true at all
All right, I saw a shushing go down the other night where I thought these guys were gonna kick the shit out of the shushar
to the point where I was genuinely scared.
I shush.
I've shushed.
Yeah, I mean, we know the bad Santa story, of course.
Yeah, but yeah, I've shushed grown men.
Yeah.
But I mean, it's, I can't stand people talking
during a movie.
I can't fucking stand it.
I've yelled it, I've yelled at middle -aged women.
Wow.
So then sitting next to me, two women in their 60s.
You were dating them.
I was.
You were in a heart of a Zac Morris
where you were dating them both.
It was a hot three -way.
It was open.
and we lived in a cabin and did that.
We wrote books together.
You met at a hometown buffet, if I'm not mistaken.
She was at the chocolate fountain.
I've always wanted to, how was hometown buffet?
I always wanted to go.
Is hometown buffet old country buffet?
No, I don't think so.
Old country buffet was an East Coast,
well, I knew it as an East Coast thing.
I've never seen one on the West.
I don't think they've ever seen one.
But they might be out of business even.
My big once a month out to a restaurant with my family, sadly, was told comfortable.
That was a spot for us too.
Yeah.
It was great.
I loved it.
That's why I want to know how hometown buffet.
Why don't we just go to hometown buffet one day?
I'll do it.
There's one up in Burbank.
Actually, everything you want that you think doesn't exist here is all up in Burbank.
I'm going to toss this out to the fans.
I haven't even run this by you.
the idea just popped into my head.
Glad I'm sitting down.
I want to give us feedback on the Facebook group
about this.
How would you guys feel about a tear on the Patreon?
Where?
You give us certain amount of money
and Pat and I take you to hometown buffet in Burbank.
You'd have to be local.
I would actually not allow somebody to fly out here
just to do that.
I love that idea.
I'm serious.
You know I would do it.
All right, so we'll do it
If you guys want it, and you let us know if you want it.
So now let's get on with the show, and at the same time, on with the Joe, Joe Sheila,
let me love you till the morning comes, right?
Very good.
Now, the audience might not know that, although weirdly today I was, well, Joe, all the fans
were wishing me a happy birthday.
Happy birthday.
Thanks.
I wish you had a birthday.
My birthday didn't happen.
I said it yesterday and I forgot to say it again today.
Sorry.
I'm breaking your balls.
You said it yesterday.
But I realized our fans are around our age.
For some reason I always think of them as being these young kids who don't,
who wouldn't know a song like Oh Sheila.
But there were a lot of them who are our age or older.
So I think of them as much younger than I just find myself to,
I look at myself as a crappy dying piece of shit.
God same. I mean, I, I put on a face mask last night. And it's because like for whatever
reason, one to 36 birthdays had no effect. I was never like, boy, you're getting old.
I never do that shit because I don't, I don't feel much different than I did 10 years ago,
aside from a wildly depressed streak. But 37, for some, maybe it's the seventh, the additional
syllable or something. It feel that today felt old. She got, I think 37's a juicy one. I enjoyed
37. I was like, oh, I got three hot years left before 40 years. Yeah. I mean, 40 have actually enjoyed.
What if you and I pitch a buddy comedy? Well, I'm not going to cast it just yet. I want to tell
you a little bit about it first called three hot years. Uh huh. And you and I have been lifelong
friends. Wake up. It's our 37th birthday. The one guy's like, I feel old. A lot. The other guy's
what are you talking about? We got three hot years and we see maybe in real time those three hot
years unfold in real time. Yeah. Well, your three acts are your three years, I would think.
So your movies structured are are excuse me are movies structured. Who now, who do you see in it?
who I think Vaughan is too expected,
and Vaughan is also in his late 60s.
Oh, I am, there's no bigger Vince Vaughan fan
on planet Earth than me.
But yeah, he is not pulling off 37 on camera these days.
I saw, I watched this movie called Brad Status,
which I actually really enjoyed with Ben Stiller.
Oh, is that the one with Dustin Hoffman in him?
No, that's my, my, my, my, which chronicles.
Wait, what's Brad's status again?
It's a Mike White movie.
It's like another Greenberg type thing, isn't it?
Yeah, but it was, yeah, just a very depressing comedy,
kind of, and he's a guy who obsessively compares himself
to all of his friends' life, and it's kind of,
really just kind of almost like a nice little
fable almost about how you, you know,
we actually see what is going on in the lives
of these people that he thinks are having such a better time
than him and et cetera.
Oh, that's cool.
It was really, really good.
and kind of funny, and the kid who played his kid was awesome, and stiller was awesome.
Stiller's always talking about it. I loved it more than I even realized. It was very good.
Stiller is always great.
Hey, before we get to run us over to pass movie corner before it's time.
And we haven't even cast this project, but, but move on.
Well, let's cast it.
I'm going to say I think in Prince Jr.
In a comeback role, but then we'll need a more established star.
Right off the top of my head, Channing Tatum, I'm going to toss him right in.
And he's the right age.
That's good.
And then I'm going to put next to Channing Tatum a crisp pine or, you know, you're making
a classic Hollywood mistake.
Two handsome no comedian.
Well, you got to go one comedian, one handsome.
I'm going to go versatile here and also fresh faces and also get your show a little more
attention.
Okay.
I'm going to throw Tony Rock in there.
I think Tony Rock.
Tony Rock.
would be spectacular in three -hot years. Tony Rock would be perfect for three -hot
years. My show would have to be a massive hit for him to jump into the lead in a
feature film. Well, you guys are going to love Tony Rock. Tony Rock, maybe, well,
I shouldn't, I was about to say his age, but he's older than you think and the fact
that that man hasn't popped is crazy. He's so fun. Had I say it to myself in the
mirror every morning. Yeah. About Tony Ruck. All right. Well, I do want to get away before
we go to Pat's movie corner. Yeah. Shout out to do or dive in bed style Brooklyn. Oh,
one of the greatest bars in all of New York City. One of the bars I plan on spending quite
a bit of time at, uh, in my upcoming stints in New York, uh, and, uh, I've always loved
the place.
I've been back a few times.
I have a fucking blast every time I'm there.
And one of the bartenders whose name is escaping me and I'm so sorry, but he's a tattooed
man.
If I remember correctly, he was bald with a mustache.
I do have a video.
That's a good look somewhere on my phone.
It was a very, I think he had a, like a Bronson look, like Tom Hardy in that Bronson movie.
Sure.
Anyway, I was thinking Bronson Pinshow.
Yeah.
So same difference.
I had been drinking at this bar for hours with my friends Heiss and Michelle, and we had
it.
We were having a blast.
Heiss?
Heiss.
He's from Holland.
All right.
Great guy.
Michelle is my favorite lady in all of New York City, and we just, we just had a blast.
Not Lady Liberty?
right behind Lady Liberty and Lady Luck it's hard to compete with Lady Liberty
but we were just having a blast and just time went on and hours into this
hang the bartender goes huh I fucking know I knew I know I knew you from
somewhere man and I was like yeah what's up where it goes we'll see you with
No, I knew I knew your voice.
I listened to your podcast, man.
I was like, oh, that's so cool.
So I did a video of him screaming
that he loved the podcast and the phone.
And I said, give us an on with the Joe.
And he did it.
And that's how he knew he was a real fan
because he'd went on with the Joe.
Like he, he did, and then I sent it to Pat.
And it nearly crashed my phone,
downloading a four second video.
But it was just a wonderful, nice little surprise
at an awesome, awesome bar.
So if you're ever out in bedstie Brooklyn, if you're ever in Brooklyn period, if you're
in New York period, make your way out to bedstie, go to do or dive.
It's a fucking great bar, great drink, specials, cheap beer.
It's awesome.
Just go.
Can I tell you about a quick fan encounter?
That maybe that'll be a new segment where our adoring public close encounters with the
fan kind.
We could call it.
It never really never happens to me.
It did briefly in my vine days, but it doesn't anymore.
I was in Sacramento with Heather and for Christmas, yeah, so, you know, Heather's about five
years younger than me and her sister's about five years younger than her.
So it's a very different age group, but we're going to meet her friends at a karaoke
bar.
And it was a real kind of red neck type joint.
We walk in and it's like ten of her friends who are like 25 years old and I just felt
old and I don't know anyone there already swits a little awkward, I don't know from Sacramento,
but we're trying to hang out and the kids are kind of giving me the cold shoulder if I'm being
honest. Then from across the bar, here a booming voice go, bad whoosh! Turn around, never seen this
kid before on my life. I'm thinking that I knock his wife up or something, what's going on?
and comes over. Huge handshake. Couldn't have been a nicer guy. Just a fan. He listens
to the podcast. He seemed to be very knowledgeable about myself than myself. He was like my
favorite thing of yours is that I'm like, I don't recall saying that, but all right.
It was a nice thing. It was great. It was very cool. And got you bang this guy after we
fucked. Yes. All right. But Heather watched. That's something we like to do. Yeah. That's
what that's I heard that's the only way she can get it off these days is watching me Roger
another gentleman. Yeah. I like to watch. She says she tells me that whenever we get too
too drunk. You see I look over and in the darkness you just see a cigarette get lit the the flame
appears in the darkness and it's Heather's face watching her eyes wide open as I sadly try to force
My penis into an adoring fan folds it in half so it feels erect in some way
Anyway, let's go to the movie corner now that we've sucked around Dix, let's go
I got a bunch for this one. I have so many. I have been watching three to four and in some cases five movies a day
Because I I worked so much and now I'm off for a long time and it feels great
Well, that's a lot so no, I know. I'm not gonna go through all I won't go through all all right there
You most important to me. I want to get out this movie folks
Haven't seen it on a single top ten list all the top ten lists are the same the same shitty pieces are
shit that we'll be discussing. Maybe one of them on this show. Everybody raised about the same
movies. I mean, it disgusts me because they're scared to venture out on their own. They're
scared to like us to me. Oh, well, you know, when I was, when I was a critic, half ass critic, whatever,
I was just screening of memoirs of a gaysha. And this guy fell asleep and was a, I'm gonna
I told the story I'm here before, but this critic,
well -known critic from the New York Post or whatever,
fellow sleep, half hour in, it was a very boring movie,
wakes up because someone woke him up
when the credits were done,
and the man raved about memoirs of a gaysia
and the next day's paper.
Jesus Christ.
I mean, I know this shit goes on.
It's disgusting, it's yeah.
So I have, now, you do yours first, but I'm trying it.
On that note, I'm gonna do my first one
after your first.
All right, great.
Maybe we'll shine a spotlight on some lost gems.
Is that what you'll be doing?
No, what I'm gonna do is talk about the same old shit.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
Well, that's in our new segment, SOS.
Right before PSI.
Look.
This movie is called The Work, which is honestly a bad title.
It's not memorable, but once you see it,
it makes a lot of sense.
Never been heard of it.
But it's the kind of title that somebody tells you,
you gotta see the work and then three hours later,
you're like, did they say the job, the, you know, like, it's a bad title.
The help. So yeah, the room. So please write it down. The help. And it
is now 99 cents on Amazon. And I just said the help. Did I?
Yeah. Holy shit. Folks, it's called the work erase the help and
write the work 99 cents on Amazon 99 cents on iTunes. It is a
documentary about at Folsom Prison? Is that in Sacramento? Up by Sacramento?
I think we saw Folsom Prison was like in the South. That's why Johnny Cash did that album there.
I don't know. Sure. Well, I mean, there's a city called Folsom up there. Anyway,
Folsom Prison, once a year, people from Folsom are invited, if they want, to go in and
And fraternize and have a sort of group therapy session with the prisoners.
Oh, that's cool.
So already you're like, oh, great.
And I imagine I'll make this into some schmaltzi piece of shit movie with Sandy Bullock or
something.
But I mean, this thing for 90 minutes, and I am a man who was, as we have discussed, very
dead inside.
Yeah.
I'm just an emotional void.
Nothing.
And I'm now, because of this movie,
happy to share this with you and not ashamed.
I sobbed like a small bitch
from two minutes in till the end of this thing.
I was making noises like,
I will say sobbing perhaps.
Yeah.
And I don't wanna tell you too much about it,
but it's essentially guys,
guys, it's all dudes. And these guys go in and they're all just kind of like, I can't
imagine myself breaking in here. They're judging these hardened criminals who are trying
to force themselves to open up and access their past damage. And it's really hard for all
of them. And then finally one guy I'll make a little break through and then there's a guy
who's such a fucking asshole who comes in from the outside. And he's like, can I just make
make it quick, like judgment here.
He goes, I mean, you had a little break through there,
that's fine, but like, you know,
one should be right back in the same place tomorrow.
Are you kidding me?
Like this guy's been in there an hour
and then this, the hard and criminals at certain points
get real angry with the people from off the streets.
Sure, of course.
There's screaming masses and everything else,
but what the movie is really is every 10 minutes,
a man who looks like he's killed hundreds of people.
We'll have like a deep dark, dark emotional breakdown brought on by this group of like loving,
supportive men who are who have to make an announcement at the beginning when we step in this room,
we put aside our crimp and blood differences that exist out there are scripts and bloods in each
of these groups. All right, then I'm assuming it must be California. I think it is. Yeah.
But I tell you what, but the thing blew my mind.
And then I also started thinking, should this movie
be released?
These people are bearing their fucking souls
and having like these really personal,
but I think the reason they all agreed
and consented to have their faces in it, I would imagine,
is because it would help people.
It like, I would say that it changed my life.
I would recommend watching it very, very highly.
You sold me on it, I'm gonna see it.
Not a full movie.
You sold me on it, a movie.
I don't mean, I don't mean that in a shitty way, I just mean, you know, you'll rave about things and I'll say, I'll check it out if I see it, you know, this I'm gonna go hunt down and watch.
Well, it's a dollar.
Yeah. Well, my dad.
Beautiful movie.
My dad is a deacon in the Catholic church.
He used to go and talk to the prisoners.
Yeah.
Greater for prison where we used to live.
And I was thought that was a pretty cool thing, you know, so I'm interested in this.
I'm gonna switch it up.
I'm gonna save the one I was gonna bitch about for later.
Okay.
you got me on an emotional track here. I finally saw Lady Bird. Yeah. 10 minutes
into the film I was texting Pat saying, I'm just dead inside. Nothing. I don't
feel anything anymore. Yeah. I hate this goddamn movie. I was supposed to love it.
I hate it. This main character is awful. Yeah. Pat was like stick with it, stick
with it. I was like, oh fuck it. I'm more interested in the friend who she's
Treating like garbage and the parents are trying to keep the damn family afloat.
And this kid's just running around being an asshole demanding.
She be called this ridiculous name.
Well, Joe was saying why why it isn't the movie about the fat friend?
Why isn't it about the parents?
I'm like, Joe, it's all of those things and more.
And then as I continued to watch the film, I saw that Pat was right.
I was jumping to conclusions.
I realized that my reactions to this character at the beginning of the film were my own
hatreds and criticisms about myself from that age. The shift in this movie is impeccably written
that you see a daughter in the sort of domineering, spiteful position for the first half and then
it almost seamlessly transitions to where the mom is doing it. You realize these are two people that
love each other very much and don't know how to express it properly and get frustrated.
And then doing say things they don't really want to do or say, it's beautiful when she
reunites with the friend that she disregards loved it.
I mean, the end of the song, it was a perfect choice of song.
I was like, I don't even care that it's Dave Matthews.
It's really great moment.
When it cuts to them singing that on the hood of the car, it was one of the funniest things
they've ever seen.
The play auditions were one of the funniest things they've ever seen.
Yeah.
That's what people are kind of forgetting, I think.
I never even see it mentioned in reviews is that it's really really funny. It's hilarious. The kids are
lots of pranks like kid from me mentions it as a comedy right kid from Manchester by the sea hits
a fucking homerick just devastating scene when he's frying. He's like I'm just so ashamed. Please
don't tell anybody that guy is and it was last name is hedges. He's the son of Peter hedges who wrote
my favorite book of all time. What's eating Gilbert great. Okay. Not the novelization of the film. It was
a book first. Right. The novelization of the film was written by J. K. Rowling's.
He did some cash. But it's just a, it's just a beautiful movie. It's, it's so true to life.
My hat's off to Greta Gerwig. She did a really, really phenomenal job. And the fact that it took me
through the emotional rolecoaster, it did where I was furious at the top of this thing. Right. And then
and laughing and then sobbing at the end
when she calls the mom and thanks her and yeah.
And I did that, the thing she does at college,
I remember going to college and it was very,
it echoed a lot of the relationship with my mom
that I have, you know, there were a lot of similarities there.
But the one thing I really related to the most was
the being brought up Catholic school,
very much denouncing it to people,
going to college and feeling so isolated and so alone
thinking all my problems are gonna be fixed. And then going to church in college when I first got
there because I just didn't know where to turn. And you're just trying to find anything that feels
like a tie to home that you can relate to where you're not being judged. And that also is saying
fuck these assholes that you're in school with that think they're too cool for anything or whatever.
Right. Um, it was just a beautiful, beautiful movie. Uh, I loved it.
Matt calf. She deserves an Oscar for it. I think it's going to come down to her and Janie.
She and, uh, Tracy Lutz, who I never liked. I loved as the dead.
What was his line of the car? What was his, he, I laughed so hard on one of his lines in the car.
And you just saw it. I forgot it. He's like driving her to school.
He had a sense of great joke. I remember really enjoying.
I mean, Metcalfe is, I mean, it's, it's a half -quirt swish.
Yeah, she's awesome.
And the main girl is good too.
I can't remember her name.
Ciorci Ronan.
Yeah.
It's a star of Brooklyn.
Yes.
One of my favorites from a few years back.
But that thing where Metcalfe is just like, why don't you just go to city college and then
go to jail and then get out of jail and go back to city college.
Right, right.
It was just so funny, man, it was, it was really great.
Yeah.
Anyway.
I loved her the adoptive brother sister characters like they were great. There's just a lot of great shit in it
I would say like you know anyone reading that script would be like cut the
Brother and sister care now you need them because just when you when you start to question the mom
You realize she's taking these two kids right and it's fucking beautiful and I'm not saying it was the right no Joe
That's the note you would get now. I feel like you wanted like a suit these days. I do I can't help it
Um, which means I'm wrong 100 % of the time, I like to think I think like a like a G string
bikini, but that's just me.
What is that man?
I don't know.
I said, do you think like a suit?
I think like I have a wild, I think wild, I don't know, it was a joke, I got it, I got it.
Um, Harry, what else you got?
I mean, I've seen every big movie, uh, so I don't want to do them all, I'll say I saw
the post Tom Hanks, Meryl Streep. This thing is raved about on every top ten list as well.
Folks, I got three words for this movie. ZZZ.
Snoozeville. It's boring. And Spielberg is lazy in it. Hanks is lazy in it. Streep is lazy in it.
I don't know.
all the hype. You got to see these movies kind of earlier else you can't escape the hype
in your mind. But yeah, the post, I was just like, this, they're like, the movie we need
now more than ever and all this shit. I'm like, come on. I look forward to watching
and I do have a screener here. Look, I'll say the same. It's fun. I, another film I saw
that, well, you know what? Let's hold it. Let's keep it to two each because we're already
get the 30 minute mark here.
All right, I have about 40 more, honestly.
All right, well, let's do, I'll do one more,
you do one more, I'll do one more, all right?
I saw, I'm saving the third one for third.
I also saw itanya, you know you've seen it.
Again, I was sort of up and down through this thing.
Ultimately, I liked it.
Ultimately, I did feel bad for Tanya Harding.
And ultimately, and again, it's a movie that pushed my buttons, and I like that.
There were times in the movie where I felt sorry for her, there were times in the movie
where I was almost yelling, oh fuck you lady at the TV, right.
And it's nice to see movies that are doing that again.
That's not what movies are supposed to do, but what movies can do.
And when they're well done, they can do that.
Yeah, and I'm speaking specifically now to James Gunn's response to Jody Foster
Jody Foster's right. She's like going on the movies anymore
It's like going to a goddamn amusement park, right and then James Gunn is like
I love Jody Foster, but she seems to think that a blockbuster film can't be thought provoking
I'm sorry mr. Gunn. Are you trying to insinuate that guardians of the galaxy is thought provoking?
Stop it
Anyway, this movie was thought provoking.
You didn't know how to feel, you were laughing
and then you were kind of cringing
and then you were laughing at shit.
You didn't even know if you should be laughing at it.
Oh, so you liked it.
I liked, ultimately I liked it.
The text I received from you was quite negative.
I said, I'm 20 minutes into ithanya.
I'm not that impressed.
But again, what I realized was, I haven't seen,
and this is the same thing I realized with Lady Bird.
I haven't seen a movie come out of this sort of and these are
Indies but they're still they're still Hollywood fair. I haven't seen a movie in a long time come out of the sort of Hollywood market
That made me feel that way right?
You know and not and I wasn't mad at it
I just wasn't I was looking at it as a Hollywood film and so when you start to not like something my first reaction is
Oh, I'm supposed to like this person.
These fucking executives are telling me this is who I'm supposed to.
And then you realize, no, because honestly, quite frankly,
it's like a Lena Dunham girls thing for me.
I really liked girls in the beginning.
But when the other shoe never dropped and there was never a reckoning
for all these characters acting very selfishly
and stuff never comes there, I watched the whole thing.
I was like, well, fuck you then.
Like, this is what this was, you know, like,
So I I kind of have that in my head and I need to get that out of my head that that's what this thing is going to be
And I did like it tiny a lot and I like the part where I'm paraphrasing it
But she's where she's kind of says the thing like you're all no better
Right been the guy that beat me whatever, you know, I like it
I like that she's like yeah, you're all blood thirsty. Yeah fuck yourselves
I love that the last shot is a pool of blood on the mat, right, right?
You know almost saying like come lick this up. You fucking animals. You know like I liked it
I thought it was a cool flick at that line when she's like, you're all as bad as the,
I watched it with my mom, uh, she said, you're all just as bad as the guy who, uh,
you know, did this, my mom goes, well, I don't know if that's true.
It's not, yeah, when I wouldn't say we're quiet, we're not as bad.
But yeah. Uh, and Janie, Janie's fantastic in it.
Janie is real fun. Uh, but I would put the award nod to Margot Robby.
Robby over Janie. Okay. Janie was great. Robby. Robby. Robby. Yeah. Janie was fantastic.
I'm not taking anything away from Janie, but I've seen Janie, yeah, in sort of similar roles
to that before. Not saying it's not great. It's just I've seen her in similar roles.
Margot Robbie to me. I was like, I was like, that's fucking, she's tying your heart. I didn't,
You know, at one point, I was like,
this is the same girl,
I played like fucking Harley Quinn in the Suicide Squad movie.
Right.
And, uh, uh,
Careers sent some real lows and some real highs.
Exactly.
And the wife in, uh,
Wolf of Wall Street.
So I, I just thought you, it was the first time I'd seen her
go to that kind of emotional depth
that I really liked it.
And I thought she was great.
Should I tweet this right now?
What?
Airbud colon.
Wolf of Wall Street.
like you're pitching that as a movie.
Yeah.
Okay. Now let's cast this film.
All right.
Who's going to be right this down?
By the way, because that's, that's good.
All we need are a dad and a kid.
My pitch for the dad is Rick Moranis in his comeback role.
Actually, he's probably the grandfather.
You're not going to get him.
Okay.
My pitch for the dad.
I'm going to say Billy Gardell, a buddy of mine,
from stand -up comedy of Mike and Molly.
Yes.
Yeah.
I could see him being the air bud dad.
Oh, okay.
We're doing like a directive video.
These movies aren't theatrical anymore.
It could be Billy Gardell.
Well, we don't need to knock Billy and Tony down.
Well, not knocking Billy or Tony.
I'm saying they're not at the level
where they're opening a feature studio film.
I don't think air bud woof of Wall Street.
I'm saying we're going directive video with it.
I think even if it hit theaters,
a Billy Gardell could start it.
Yeah, I think you're right.
So they get French steward.
I'm gonna put him in the in the dad role
and then I'm gonna put the kid,
I'm gonna put the black kid from stranger things
in the kid role as an adopted son of Billy Gardell.
Wow.
And I think this is we got the makings
of something really good here.
But why?
Like you've always thought those two would be good together?
I just think they're both got a lot of charisma
and I could see it working.
All right, fair enough.
And then I'm gonna put in a Brad Garrett
as maybe the bad guy coach or the other team.
I mean, I don't wanna see this movie.
Do you wanna see any air bud movie?
Is there an air bud movie you wanna see?
No, that's true.
It's new and I'm gonna tell Vince 1215.
Another step behind the curtain folks, 1220.
I tell him 1220. Listen to that. Yeah, you're just when I 12, 1230.
1230. This is Pat planning as I'm casting a brilliant film here.
He's planning lunch plans with their fight. It's my birthday lunch.
You know, the last time we, uh, people did a,
people did a big discussion about what was their favorite fight of ours on the show.
Right. Boy, it was taking me back to some funny, funny memories.
But the only one that I went back and listened to was everybody was talking about
Rogue One, which was one year ago today probably, but it had just been my birthday and remember
we had the big thing about it.
I invited you guys over to my house and you'd rather go to a bar.
That was when I started out.
Well, because there's not enough fuck there, so we, I listened to this entire episode again.
I was laughing so hard because it starts like there's barely an intro and you and I are just so
really arguing with each other. And it goes on and on and on for like a half hour.
It's all very funny. We're laughing. Right. But, uh, yeah, that we've really lost the
argument element. It was so intense to listen to. Pat, this world has beaten me down to
a place where I can't, I can't turn on my loved ones anymore. I don't have the, I can't, I
don't have the time, I don't have the energy, I don't have the balls. I completely agree.
Okay, look, we're at the 37 minute mark.
Let's, why don't we move out of the movie corner?
We've got plenty for future episodes.
We're getting the Joe's scary stuff.
Yeah, and I got a real quick one.
I don't know if you have one or not,
but full moon, pictures.
I don't know if they're still doing it.
Folks, they had a great sale going on over the holidays.
A lot of their classic films restored and on Blu -ray.
and they look like they've done a very nice job with these.
I like the packaging, I like the cover art,
and they are actual restorations,
according to the website.
So go over to full moon features,
fullmoondirect .com, excuse me.
These movies are just like trash, right?
Well, some of them, they have trashy elements,
but they're very fun horror movies.
So I got the creeps deformed monsters.
I got hideous deformed freaks.
I got a rituals of the occult three -pack that has totem voodoo academy in another world
on it voodoo academy and I also got head of the family now let me throw this out you
speaking to JK Rowling do you think perhaps some elements of Harry Potter came from voodoo
academy I've always thought that she's lifted the best voodoo academy I've always felt that
She lifted the best parts of those stories
from most of the full moon features, production.
Anyway, so they had these things for like 11 bucks.
Like I've had the creeps on my Amazon wish list
for a long time and it was fairly priced on Amazon.
It was like 15 bucks or something
but getting it directly from the company that made it
and only having to pay 12 bucks
and then they get the bigger profit
was obviously the best scenario for all parties.
So go check that out. I got a quick one. It's not and I'm going to say it's scary stuff because
adolescence is a scary time, John. I want to recommend the new criteria in addition of the breakfast
club. Okay. John Hughes is my number one. I love him. His movies were my, you know, Star Wars and
I was growing up. And there's there's very little information about you rarely get to see him talking
or directing or hear interviews with him because he was a very private man.
So the special features on this thing are fantastic.
If you're a fan of Hughes, Breakfast Club would be one of my least favorite John Hughes
movies.
But what?
One of my least favorite of his movies.
Really?
What the hell are you putting above Breakfast Club?
Of his classics, I mean.
Well, no, no, I know, but I'm saying what do you eat?
Here's what I put above Breakfast Club, 16 candles.
If I don't agree.
If I'm being honest, weird science.
Okay, I'll give you weird science and I'll give you Ferris Bueller.
Ferris Bueller's day off was next.
Uncle Buck.
No fucking way.
100 % way.
Playing the strands on on bills, obviously.
I'll give you a plain strange.
Your way off on 16 candles and Uncle Buck.
Come on man.
Without question.
I'm sorry.
And I really love the breakfast club.
All right.
But that's how much I love John Hughes.
I think he's got better stuff.
Honestly.
Home alone.
Even though he didn't direct it.
the fuck up. I'll remember home alone moments after I said I can't argue with my friends anymore.
You're enraging me. Yeah. Home alone. If we're going movies, he wrote over the breakfast
club. Home alone, national ampune's vacation. Okay, I'll give you that. By the way, just listen
to these credits. I know. The guy is, he's the Scorsese of TIT comedy. Well, he's the TIT comedy.
I know. I'm just, it's just a funny phrase. And you'll learn that when you watch the special features
on the breakfast. Anyway, it's a, the, the restoration has with all criteria and shit. It looks
unbelievable. And the special features, there's an hour of deleted scenes on the thing. And what
has me rock hard, Joe, not the way you're sitting right now in a pair of shorts. What has me rock hard
right now is that there is a three plus hour cut of plans trans automobiles that Hughes showed to
his friends and recorded the laughter.
We talked about it, you've told me about it.
Are they going to release it finally?
Once they start with one director criteria,
they tend to kind of stick with them.
If they love this and it's a big seller,
I could see it happening.
Well, I'm excited.
Nothing would make me happier in the world.
And he recorded a commentary for the DVD
that he pulled from the DVD.
He was like, I don't want people to hear this much
about the movie, I'm pulling it.
So the commentary exists.
They could put that on this thing.
I'm going to buy it. I'm going to buy the breakfast club
Criterion. I also want to get the new the night of the living dead criterion. Oh, sure. Of course, you know
I love how they waited till George Romero was dead for him to finally get the profit off of this fucking classic movie
You made right anyway
You know I'm pick I'm splitting hairs here. It's great that they put that out and I look forward to getting a copy of that
Alright, our film in the week, we are reviewing a little piece called the Shape of Water,
Guillermo del Toa de Rojo.
His latest feat, it's a movie, if case you're unaware about, it's sort of a throwback
I would say to the universal monster movies of the 40s and 50s, not in a
sensational over -the -top sense as they eventually became, but the true early
ones like the original Dracula and the Frankenstein, so on, where you know it's
a monster movie in a sense but it's really a movie about the characters and
And it's got a soul to it, and it's a human story and blah, blah, blah, blah.
And the horror elements are there, but they take a backseat to that.
So this woman who was mute, she can hear, but she can't speak, works in a top -seeker government
facility as a janitor.
And she falls in love with a top -seeker government project that turns out to, it's a fishman.
man. It's a fish man, folks. Yeah. So anyway, that's what you're
waiting for the big reveal. So anyway, that's the gist of the
film. It's about lonely people finding one another her
per -only friend is played by what's his face from the bongo
movie Richard Jenkins who plays a gay man in like the 50s. So he is
He's very lonely because he's, he's very closeted and she's his only friend and obviously
the fish man's lonely.
He's living in a goddamn government facility tank and then Michael Shannon plays the bad
guy and he's clearly really kind of a new type of performance for Mike Shannon.
I've turned on that guy.
It took me a long time because I loved him so much, but now I'm like, come on, dude, mix it
up. Um, he, he does, yeah, he likes playing those bad guys. Now I'll say weird sex scene
with Mike Shannon in this movie. It wasn't necessary. Absolutely not. It wasn't necessary.
There's a sex scene in the movie where he's fucking his wife and she's talking like, you
know, she's given him a little dirty talk 1950 style. So it's just like, oh, yeah, mama,
You know, it's that shitty dirty talk baked me up a couple of them apple pies. Yeah. Yeah, yeah leave it to beaver
uh, then he
He covers her mouth and he goes just just just don't say anything don't talk
And then you can see that that's like what turns him on and as far as I could tell
That's only in there so there can be an unnecessary scene later
Where he tries to sexually assault the mute girl and it's like
I already hated this guy.
Yeah, I didn't even put that together.
It's me, I just thought it was like...
So you get that he's a bad guy.
I'm like, I get it from him whipping his dick out
at the janitor ladies and then slapping everyone on the face.
Yeah, and it was one of those moments
like when he comes on to the mute character
and then like, he doesn't force himself on her
but he grabs her inappropriately by the arm.
and with, with certain force and, and you can see that he's got it in him to potentially assault or rape or something.
It's one of those moments in the movie where you're like, I don't need the bad guy to do that. Right.
This guy is already unlikable enough. Instead of that, I'd rather you give me a scene where I see a little humanity in the guy so I can understand his motivations.
Instead of him every scene him being this guy that's like fuck you me me me me. I am awful. It's like
Okay, he's awful. Why though, you know, right? Well to that
Maybe you could have used that five 10 minutes. They spend on him
to give me
10 seconds
of the love
of forming between the mute woman Sally Hawkins
and the fish man.
I felt nothing.
These people talk about them sobbing
at the fucking shape of water.
What emotions are you feeling watching this thing?
You're rooting for her to fuck the fish man?
She's a beautiful woman.
You see her naked 10 seconds in.
And I'll tell you something, that body don't quit.
Didn't quit.
And she's mute.
Yeah.
I mean, what a dream woman.
and she can cook.
Yes, it's like go outside, can't find a man.
Have you left your house in five years?
That's why you're settling for a fish man.
Go to the market, me introduce yourself.
It shows that her early activities
are making sandwiches for Richard Jenkins as he paints.
Who's gay?
And then accompanying Richard Jenkins
to hit on what it turns out to be a straight man
who sells pies.
Yeah, she has no other social like and then her friend who I love this lady
What's the actor's name Octavia Spencer? She's fucking wonderful. Yeah, Kent Hollywood
Can you let her play anything but like the sassy lady from the first half of the century?
She's literally like so okay, so when you think of like the sassy black friend stereotype if you're thinking of them
Like a romantic comedy then it'd be like oh like honey. How was his dick? Yeah, let me tell you what Octavia Spencer says
in the Academy of War front runner for best picture of the shape of water so he's got a fish dick
it's the same thing just just because it looks beautiful doesn't mean you're making fucking art
and it does look beautiful she's such a tremendous actress or actress about the fish man's dance
I know and it's like pleased every movie they make her be the lady that's like well honey listen to
like they they just stop it yeah she's good she's great in it she's kind of
playing that same part again obviously it's what I'm saying it but everybody's
very good in it let's look obviously folks we didn't like the movie very much
it doesn't it I will say especially like the first half it looks beautiful yeah
let's start with the positive as all del Toro shit does it looks fantastic
That's a dreamy, well -directed, extremely well -acted.
I will say Del Toro does stuff with the camera that excited me and it's things I haven't
seen since early Spielberg, like Raiders of the Lost Ark.
There were moments in this, like when Michael Shannon's entrance, the way he has him dressed,
The camera move he does the music playing you're immediate it's literally like when the black coded Nazi with the glasses walks into the bar and
Raiders of the Lost Ark and immediately you're like this man is awful, right and I was like God that the guy speaks so much with a camera like he just he he he gets so much across with these shots, I
I guess I wish he did other people's scripts.
So I feel about Shyamalan though.
They're really talented directors
who need to stop doing their own material.
I agree.
I think Del Toro is best when he's adapting.
Except for Pan's, I love Pan's laughter, right?
Pan's laughing with his true masterpiece.
And his earlier stuff.
But I mean, just, I mean, Crimson Peak was a,
I would say it was a bad movie.
It was, but I will say, you know, visually that one,
even more than shape of water,
it held my interest for that reason alone.
I thought I loved the look of it.
I liked the look of this, and that's kind of where,
and I liked the first half.
I was really enjoying the first half,
and then just as this point where I was like,
oh Christ, man, I'm tired of this.
Like I'm bored.
Like it's just dragging on and on.
There's no really excitement to any of it.
And I'm gonna tell you, Shannon with the gun out in the rain,
that all that stuff at the end,
I mean, I almost turned it off.
I was like, that's enough.
I done the stories over.
Yeah, and I'll tell you a real fuck you moment for me to the main character the mute lady. Yeah
That fucking scene where
So she lives above a movie theater. They live in this like kind of low -ranked apartment above a movie theater and
These people are obviously not rolling in dough
But they they have what they have
There's a scene where she takes the fish guy into the bathroom and
and plugs the door up with with towels under it.
So water can't get out and she turns on all the water
so the bathroom can fill up and be a tank
that they can like be in together while they fish fuck.
And it's like, and then it's leaking down
and ruining literally the man's business downstairs.
And I'm like, oh, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Your thirst for bestiality is so strong
that the fucking movie theater now has to pay a debt for it.
That bothered me.
I was like, that's just selfish.
Yeah, you're an asshole.
And since none of those scenes had any passion to them,
you didn't even buy that like,
I gotta fuck this, fish man.
Like that's the only way you sell something
that insane and selfish is if it's like,
I really gotta fuck this guy.
They had no heat between them, no chemistry,
but folks, how could you have chemistry between a woman
and a fish man. And folks, here's the peers what it is at the end of the day. I get it. It's art.
It's art. Story he want to tell fine. But just remember this, for all of you writing blogs
about whether or not you found Dave Chappelle's humor concerning Louis CK appropriate or not.
Oh boy. There is a movie that is a front runner for the Oscars
is that glorifies beastieality.
That's true.
Just remember that.
Just when you say, is that joke inappropriate?
There is a movie that is gonna get nominated for Oscars.
Best picture.
That glorifies fish fucking.
Yeah.
So everybody calm down a little bit.
That's all I gotta say.
I can't go any farther than that.
folks. I am at the Patrick Walsh on Twitter and Instagram. My show featuring
Joe DeRosa living Biblically premieres on Monday, February 26th at 93830 Central.
Take it away, Joe. Joe DeRosa, comedy, Twitter, Instagram, Penn
Housecombe. Let me down every month in Penn House magazine. And that's it for now.
We'll see you next time. We'll see you in hell.
That was a headgun podcast.