Summer is here and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer, or check out
our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz, only available at Bed
MDM Casino.
Spin on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia only, games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal -durable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided in applicable terms.
Reward subject to expiry, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamber.
The football season is full of guarantees.
And here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if your
football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fancash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fancash,
guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
winning hits different here must be 21 plus gambling problem called winning 100
gambler offer not available in all states terms apply see Fanatic's fourth book
It's a good show.
Howdy folks.
Welcome to we'll see you and how it's a Sunday morning. We're here Pat Walsh to myself. We've got a couple of mimosas. I
Didn't realize you were starting over completely
Well, you wanted to we didn't have that much material
We we got on the mics and immediately started shitting on everyone and everything
Felt bad about it. I thought we'd go back a couple minutes. You didn't you didn't miss much that was the whole thing
It was it was literally after the hello
We started shitting on it was basically. Yeah, hello right into shit. I'm doing mimosas
Yeah, we got a couple mimosas here like gentlemen do late morning. I am
As I said on the previous recording that we cut I am approaching a Dennis Hopper level of
God knows what you know
I think I'm two ticks away from living like on a farm where I shoot watermelons with a machine gun
You know like I'm wouldn't you have a better time? I know I would I'd have a much better time
Yeah, I'd have a much better time
So I got rather shoot like a can and enjoy the delicious watermelon
Especially if you're on a farm. You're you're away from the grocery store
Well, the fun of shooting the watermelon explodes like a body
Right I think is the whole thing kind of looks like guts flying out sure. That's why it's fun sure
But I mean I never shot one
Have you ever seen my VR yet?
I see it up there.
I did.
How is it?
Well, it's my VR because you gave it to me.
Right, right.
But it's amazing.
Okay.
It is an incredibly, incredibly, it surpassed anything, you know, we all know what VR is and
we all know what it's supposed to do and you have an idea of it.
But when I actually did it finally, it blew past anything.
I set it up just because I was having friends
over one night to play games.
And I was like, I should set this up.
So I was like, all right, I popped in the demo disk.
And I was sitting on the couch by myself,
giggling like incessantly, it was so cool.
It's amazing.
I played it for about six minutes before I felt like
I was gonna vomit everywhere.
But I do plan on playing it again, but it was it's incredible. I may have Batman, but I hear that's the game to get Batman's supposed to be great. I got a
PlayStation 4 and I've yet to play a single game. I played that giant thing looking monster game for five months. What game?
Something too quick to or okay, it's like it looks like thing from the fantastic for jumps around. It might be a child's game.
If I'm being honest, it might be a house of pain based game out of jumping, but it was fun.
And can you do VR porn with it?
You apparently can, well you got to do that, I, it's one of those things, man, it's like
heroin.
You're like, do we want to open this door, you know, like, I mean, it's a lot less, you know,
Risk a lot less emotional damage a lot less. I I would argue the emotional damage part of it
It's just it's a big it's a big door to walk through
I'm not against it. Yeah, I just I'm you know, you have to it's not just like you pop that set on and you have VR
Portland like there you have to take several steps to
Get it onto the PlayStation. So I I'm just a porn disc, right?
Or you just do that. I guess yeah
I didn't even think of that.
I mean, you got to try it or leave the room
and let me try it.
I will eventually, I just, right now I don't, you know,
I'm like, all right, maybe we just do it
the old fashioned way for now.
Do you like the POV pornography?
Yeah, that's not really my thing.
Why?
You like to see a man's face?
Well, it's just, it's like, am I really supposed to forget
That this isn't my penis that you're
I'm supposed to believe this is my giant black cock. I don't think so, fucks. It's just okay. I just don't I mean
I guess VR would help but I'm just kind of
The whole thing where they're supposed to be talking to you
I'm like I'm not falling for it. I'm sorry. It's nothing to do with the the dick. I'm just
I don't know. I don't I don't see how it's anymore
or believable than just watching two people bone.
Either way, you're watching two people bone.
But it's got this fake quality to it
that I don't like.
I wonder if the guy's realistic is all that other porn.
It's not realistic, that's right.
Pat makes a gonzo style porn.
Something that feels like it's really happening in the moment.
You mean like a muppet porn.
Yeah, a big blue bent thing.
Well nobody can 69 like gonzo, that much I know.
No, he really gets in there both ends those noses shaped like both the six and a nine
That's right. So that's why right try both ends you oh, yeah, yeah
That it would curve right down into it. That's right. It's a good point. Thank you. Maybe you maybe we could make one of those
hilarious dirty puppet movies that they keep making you ever see that happy time murder's fucked out
Yeah, I mean I didn't think it was funny when fucking Peter Jackson didn't meet the feebles
But at least it was original at that point like my least favorite movies made the
field made me sick to my stomach. He did one the guy that directed Spider -Man
did one like like where they're caught, which was also where there were cops. No
no the guy that directed the news the guy that directed cop car. He did a dirty puppet
movie. Yeah like one of his first movies was like a dirty puppet cop movie. It's
been done. No I've seen a trailer for it. It's so fucking bad. It's like the
The whole joke is, look, a puppet said fuck.
Right.
We're like, look, a puppet gizzed everywhere.
Like, okay.
And that's how fucking immature this country is, by the way.
That, you know, if you put an actual person gizzing into something,
they're immediately like, it's porn, it's this, it's that.
But then you have a puppet do it and it's doubly disgusting and weird.
And then people go, it's cute and it's funny.
This fucking place sucks.
I don't know how many people are saying the happy time murders was cute or funny, but they use silly string
I assume I would guess so, you know, and I think this is the first thing I thought of that's probably what they did in that movie and it's the whistle
They do the one of those woo woo woo woo woo woo woo woo yeah whistles. I bet when it when he jizzes right
But I mean, it's it's a country of children. I see this story about
Amy Schumer got hospitalized because she, you know, she's having a, you know, just not
a complication, but she's sick from being pregnant or something. Yeah. And the stories
about her post telling her fans, like, sorry, I have to cancel my show because I'm sick.
And she goes, I'm very, I feel very lucky to be pregnant, but this is some bullshit. All
stories about this post. They quote, that's a news story. Yeah. Well, that's the first
problem, but they put the post in the story so you can read it for yourself, unedited.
Then in the body of the story, they quote what she says and they put asterisks into bullshit.
What the fuck is wrong with everybody?
What are we dealing with here?
I don't understand because it's a tweet culture.
Are you the only way to get attention
is to have a headline like that?
Everyone clicks on it, gets shared around.
Everyone makes the same 20 jokes about that headline.
But you're missing my point, not my point.
I mean, that's part of my point.
My point is though, they put the actual bullshit,
they put the post in the fucking thing
where it says bullshit and they don't edit it.
Then in the story that they write about
the post that they're showing you, they quote it.
And then when they write bullshit, they put asterisk
It's like, it's right there.
You already put it there.
Right.
Oh, this bullshit of like, well, I didn't do it.
I didn't do it.
That was that.
I'm just, the world we are living in,
we're post, we're post what,
when people can care about cussing, you know?
I don't even understand.
At the end times, we should all be cussing.
Post 1958.
Yeah.
The fact that cursing is, it's just for Christ's sakes.
Speaking of which, I saw the trailer for uh, not speaking of which, I guess speaking of
cursing.
I saw the trailer for crashing season three today.
Have you seen it?
I have.
Yes.
Our front page show.
Uh, 90 second trailer.
Yes.
Featured every comedian in comedy except me.
I'm officially the only comedian that has never been on the show.
Even though I worked on the show.
would you would you ever ask me no okay let me answer that question before you
even finish it well he doesn't listen to this so he's he's not gonna know no I
would not I don't I don't you know is it New York and LA comedians or maybe
they're just getting people who are local it does seem all right in all fairness
it does seem to be mostly New York got it and now so maybe that is what it is
Maybe it's just New York comics.
Still, I've been in New York when they were shooting.
Sure.
I mean, hell of a business were in.
When I was working there, there was talk of two roles going to you that I don't think
were ever offered.
Oh, I auditioned for them.
One of them was to play myself.
That didn't get it.
Paul was later changed into a woman and given to somebody else.
I told him I would have played it as a woman.
I would have done a Milton Burl thing in a wig and a dress, I'm not above it.
You're not above much.
I'm not above much, except this guy's balls, I was doing a bloody job joke, like I was hovering
over.
Gotcha.
What are we talking about today?
Oh, planes, trains and automobiles.
Yeah, first ever this is a real risk. This is our first ever night. This doesn't fit anywhere into the genre
Well, I tell you
You know
Getting getting home for Thanksgiving can often seem like a horror movie
I don't know I went and saw this picture at the Vista theater here in Los Angeles on Friday night midnight
So technically Saturday morning
good turnout almost sold out I told Joe this story they asked a trivia question I
was the only one on the theater that knew name two of the three movies that John
Hughes wrote under his pseudonym Edmund Dante raised my hand I knew all three
Beethoven which I don't know why you'd ever be ashamed of writing Beethoven it's
very funny movie made Manhattan get it understood and drill bit Taylor which is
also fine. I think it was Seth Rogan's writing debut. But the guy goes as this real nerd guy
no offense to the gentleman. He's wearing like a suit and glasses. Wait, Drillbit Taylor
was written by Seth Rogan or John Hughes. John Hughes and then the first two were written
by John Hughes. Drillbit Taylor was story by and I think they took his screenplay and modernized
Okay, see what I'd rather watch the movie about an actual drill bit. Yes
So I win the thing I'm in the back row of the Vista and I walk all the way up to the front doing like a celebration
I just taken in an edible
Marijuana edible to watch my favorite comedy
So I go down I'm like yes
Walked down to pick my poster the guy doesn't even acknowledge me
He's got a poster sitting right there next to him. Mm -hmm. He just keeps talking trivia facts about the movie
rattling on. I'm standing there, the audience is kind of nervously laughing. It's so uncomfortable,
and I'm starting to freak out on the edit. Yeah, so that'll do it. I mean, you're in a
fucking room full of John Hughes freaks. You know, at any second, Motley Ringwald might swing in
and start chastising all of you. It felt like a bad dream. I felt very exposed at the front of the
auditorium. Sure. My also, my cock was out. But I'm standing there. Eventually, I sit down because I
couldn't face the awkwardness anymore. I sit in the front row, and the guy just keeps talking,
talking, talking. And he's like, all right, that's my time. Uh, enjoy playing.
And so all the bills starts walking up the aisle. I hear my friends in the back row start laughing
because they've been watching me sit there uncomfortably for 15 minutes.
I ran a midnight show. The guy talks for about 25 minutes before it starts. So I go, hey, man,
I didn't get the poster because I'll give it to you after a lot of attitude and then walks out.
sounds like a real asshole right then I stand up and walk all the way to the
back row again feeling just shamed mortified did you get the poster got the
poster it's very nice and they they do good work they always do a midnight
movie up at the Vista they were on Saturday night they were gonna show the
directors cut of return of the king starting at midnight you get out of there
at five in the morning.
Oh, good.
Rather die.
The great line in clerk clerks too.
There's only one return and it's of the Jedi.
That's a good line.
Is it?
Yeah, it is.
What's when they're arguing, which is better?
Star Wars or?
Yeah, or the right.
That's a great line.
It's a great line.
Yeah, it's in the context of that argument.
That's great.
Lord of the Rings, look, look, you fucking nerd.
There's only one return and it's of the Jedi.
That's a good line.
in that argument.
All right.
You know, give Randall a little slack.
You know, he didn't write the line.
Yeah, but he delivers it with a subtle perfection, if I may say so.
Do you have any scream and end news, psycho pieces from that?
I think the Schumer thing was that.
Let me see.
Hold on.
What's cooking this week?
let's go over to a old movie web .com where we we hack our news from them. Bill
Marr viciously bashed for insulting Stanley and comic book fans. I rarely
rarely agree with Bill Marr and I 100 % agree with him. I didn't even see what
the hell he said. Just basically like enough of people acting like this is some great
literature. Get over yourselves. It's dumb down America. All movies are comic book movies.
Oh, here's the quote. I don't think it's a huge stretch to suggest that Donald Trump could only
get elected in a country that thinks comic books are important. I actually agree with that.
Look, I've been saying it for the last two fucking years. People are going, how was he president?
I'm going, how is it he president? Yeah. It was a fucking idiot box we're living in. Yeah.
What do you think was it makes perfect sense everybody worshiped reality TV for the last 20 years
Everybody thinks that the only fucking goal in life is to be rich everybody thinks they can just be you know
Arrogate and shut you down if they if they don't like what you're saying
This is people on all sides of the right and the left do they all do this and they go can you believe this?
Billionaire guy who shuts people down and was on reality TV is pretty yes. I can't believe it took this long
I'm sorry, I'm not trying to get all political, it's all right, you know, look at this.
Somebody said, well, I feel sorry for you, Bill.
Also your show isn't exactly sophisticated television compared to breaking bad or
a sopranos.
I mean, what's the comparison you fucking idiot?
I hate Bill Mar and his stupid show, but what kind of argument is that?
Those are scripted dramas.
I know. It doesn't make any sense.
This is an interview show.
Look, I'm part of the Breaking Bad family.
I don't get it.
You know, well, you've also never seen Breaking Bad.
But, you know, when I came clean about that recently
to the creators, I mean, there's no one I hate more
than Bill Maher.
He doesn't even care about laughter.
He cares about you clapping with each line that he says.
He shuts down anyone, the minute they open their mouth.
It's like just do a monologue show.
If you're not going to talk to anyone, I can't stand him.
Well, look, here's the thing, you know, I like, you know, I like comic books, I'm a fan.
I also don't take offense at somebody making that statement.
I don't give a shit.
Yeah.
Who cares?
And I love these stories, man, where it's, these are, these are new stories now, where they
go, Bill Marr bashed, and it's like, by who, at Ashley, Dot Ashley, the lady from Toronto
I mean, it's like, you know what I mean?
Greg Kapulo, they make it sound like press
and celebrities are going after him.
Or people of note I should say.
This is a guy who routinely says,
horrifically racist and offensive things.
No one cares about his views on comic books.
Folks, let's get on with the show.
And at the same time, on,
what the hell song is that little shop of horrors grow for me sung by Seymour himself
The only song I remember is...
Suddenly Seymour...
Great movie, great songs.
I used to mow lawns to the soundtrack.
You don't know uh...
Mean Green Mother from Outer Space?
I'm in it for an Oscar.
I don't remember it.
I mean I remember the idea of the song.
I don't remember how it goes.
The only one I could remember was suddenly Seymour.
How about Steve Martin's dentist song?
Pat, I'll say it again.
The only one I could remember is suddenly Seymour.
When I was younger, just a bad little kid.
You don't remember that one?
I remember it existing.
I don't know how it goes.
Very funny performance by Steve.
When I was a kid it upset me.
I didn't like seeing him play a bad guy.
Yeah, it's rare with him, but yeah.
Similar vibe, but not rare.
Not medium rare, yeah.
Yeah, Joe and I went and had a little dinner last night
and Joe's like, oh, that place is too expensive.
It's crazy.
I'm like, ah, you're out of your mind.
Check comes like $70.
It's a rip off.
It is a rip off.
I got damn prime rib dinner.
Shouldn't be $48.
That shouldn't be the base price for the prime rib dinner.
No.
Prime rib is not that expensive of a meat.
I think it's just the word prime,
I think they can throw things around.
Oh, I'm gonna open a Transformers themed steakhouse.
Do you see where this is going?
I do. Optimus Primera. Yeah, I didn't need to finish it.
Let me take you over to Pat's movie corner and I'll start with a picture I watched when I woke up in the middle of the night as I do every night in a hot panic.
The movie is the new film from the Cohen Brothers, The Ballad of Buster Scruggs.
I've heard it's very funny. Some of the stories are very funny. I've heard Joe. It isn't funny at all
That's how I'll start this off
Now I heard the first stories really funny
No, all right. It's got a couple laughs and it's got Dave Crumbholz in it old Davey Kay a much heavier Dave Crumbholz shot a while ago
Yeah, it is, I mean, I truly, truly love the Cohen brothers almost without fail.
They've had a few in recent years and they had kind of a dark period around the Lady
Killer's days where they took a dip for me.
But this, for me, ranks right at the bottom of the pack.
Worse than impeccable beauty or whatever the fuck that one was called was a tolerable cruelty
Yeah, I like intolerable cruelty some some big laughs in that movie. I'm not a fan. I hate the way it's shot
Okay, I don't like that film that whatever that film filter they use to the whole movie is which was kind of popular at that time
I don't care for it. All right, looks like it's supposed to be like a bad like action movie or something
I hear what you're saying that was not their greatest time
And I think the past few years have not been the greatest time serious man is kind of their unsung masterpiece
Everything after that has left me a little cold
But what came after that the one about the Bob Dylan guy walking around the East Village for two hours
Which I thought was fine Louis and Davis, but I didn't love I didn't see it cone brothers movies always
Reward repeat viewings
But this is the first one where I was like not
Super engaged with that first viewing. I kept having to kind of
It's re -psych myself, I felt like if I'd pause it to get a drink of water, I'd be like,
I really want to go back, maybe I'll watch it tomorrow or something.
And part of it is that it's six stories.
It was announced three months ago as being a series, a Western anthology series, then it
just kind of drops as a two and a half hour movie with no explanation.
It is six stories, nothing really ties them together except it's like pages of a book.
The first one is Tim Blake Nelson, who is a very strange actor, who I've always liked.
So it was like the poor man's Tim Roth, or the rich man Steve in Baldwin.
Yes.
Exactly.
Yeah.
He plays like a singing cowboy, like a Hank Williams, and he is kind of walking through the
countryside on his horse.
It's unbelievably shot.
It looks incredible.
Sing's a catchy little song.
Then he goes in and the gimmick of this one is he's a singing cowboy who's like a cold -blooded killer
It's probably the most entertaining of them. It's brief. It's nice to see Chrome Holt's. There's some extreme violence in it
And it kind of plays like a looney tune short, really. I liked it. Okay
Second one is James Franco
Like forget forget phoning it in like he's having a friend phoned it in
And it's the, you're working with the Cohen brothers.
Just a lazy fucking performer.
Franco is not a good actor.
He's just good at being Franco.
Yeah, he's really bad in this mode.
Yeah, like when you put him in the role of,
you know, like in the interview or whatever,
where he's the party guy that went,
he's great, he's super funny.
When you put him in anything where he has to bounce out of that,
except for the, except for the fucking room movie
that he did which I thought he's pretty good at the it's it's he's not good like it doesn't you know
They kind of been planted in the apes as a scientist. It's like what yeah, there's a lot of Jim Belushi in there as a
fucking scientist. I think the box office might have suffered
It's him and then Stephen Root like tap dancing acting circles around him, but
Stephen Root playing like an old crazy dude
That one is fine, but kind of a weak story
There's a really good one with Tom Wates as an old prospector I love that. I don't like Tom Wates his music, but he's really good as an old prospector. He's a great actor.
That one is insanely well shot. He clearly it's like one of the better parts he's ever had.
It was kind of interesting. There's a real long one with Zoe Kazan the girl from the big sick.
And that one is like 45 minutes and just not an interesting story at all and then at the end there's one where like five people one of them being time daily are like sitting in a stage coach talking time daily and it made these sitting in a stage coach talking scenes in hateful eight that were like 45 minutes seem briskly paced so at this point I'm doing a lot of like pausing on the Apple TV and I'm like real
We still have 45 minutes. It's almost 2 .30 and I have never, whether I love them or hate them
or they grow on me or I love them in first viewing, never on a Cone Bros movie have I been bored and I felt bored.
It's worth your time. I would watch it as originally intended in six parts and watch a little story
in night because frankly it just gets a little tiring. I think I even forgot to mention one because I
I, excuse me, I have been watching the new season of It's Always Sunny.
Yes.
I'm enjoying it tremendously.
I haven't seen all of it, but the ones I have seen I like very much.
I don't want to spoil too much for anybody.
If you're a fan of the show, you should see it.
I think you'll enjoy it.
particularly the Me Too episode was very ballsy and very funny and they once
again took a sort of social commentary issue head on and made jokes and somehow
pulled it off and it worked it's it's it's very impressive to me that they
pulled that off at this point but I've been enjoying the new season I mean it's
over it's already played all the way through yes I saw them all giant swings
highs, lows, a couple episodes that really didn't work, a couple episodes that were all
time classics. And that's the nature of doing a show like that. If you're going to take
those big swings, you're not going to land everyone. I admire what they do. I thought
the finale much talked about the ending of the finale was kind of spectacular. I don't
know that it is always sunny. I don't know that it necessarily counts as the show, but it
It was interesting, and I respected the chance that they took.
My take on that was they had to do something heartfelt to make up for all the low -brow
jokes they made at the beginning of the episode.
Sure.
I thought the episode was really funny, but you know, in this day and age, obviously it's
dicey to make those types of jokes, and I think that was their way of saying to the audience
like, look guys, we're joking, we get it, we understand what this is.
Yeah, but that being said what you know it was a spectacularly choreographed dance sequence. It was not it's always sunny. No, and what I really
Disliked about it was well, this is going to be spoiler, but whatever damn divino starts crying
his character starts crying Frank starts crying who's the biggest scumbag character of all of them yeah
and he's crying because he's he finally understands like Max struggle as a gay man and that's very
nice in everything in real life but yeah this is a show where it hinges on these people never fully
respecting one another. Like I thought they were even pushing it when they did the episode,
which was funny, where they did like the Charlie day and they made all the gifts for them and stuff.
Yeah. Like that was just, you can't go any further. These people are constant. The beauty of the show
is that it's almost like a married with children thing. Like they'll band together against a common
enemy, but they are never, you're never going to see, you never saw an episode of married with children
where buds like, Kelly, I love you and I appreciate you as my sister and I don't say it. It's like
Like it's just not what it is.
So that's the only thing I didn't like about it.
And also I like my comedy's funny, as I've often said, and, you know, especially with
a show that are reverent, I don't, you know, it was an impressive sequence, but I wasn't
thrilled that the season ended on this, like, suddenly, very serious note.
Then again, it could have just been a setup, because when Dennis left at the end of last season,
and they played it pretty straight,
but then they put a button on it as a joke, right?
Where they blow up his range Rover.
This, I kinda think they were just maybe taking that
a step farther, making people think like,
oh wow, the show's taking a turn,
and then next season it'll just be the show again.
I mean, I don't know.
Yeah.
They had several sweet moments.
They gave D the steak and the premiere,
or the escape room one.
Yeah, which yeah, that was yeah, but it was also like they still had the thing in there where they
were like telling the escape room lady to fuck off. Yeah, correct. You know what I mean? Yeah, like
I would have liked a little I don't know something like that. I don't know.
I remembered the other story which actually was kind of a cool story about going back to the
Buster Scruggs.
Let's Liam Neeson.
He's any, he totes around this armless, legless kid
who recites all the great speeches of history.
And then little by little, the audience
to start slipping and Liam Neeson sees that there's a chicken
who can add and like pecs the right answer to math questions.
So he decides to like dump the stump kid
and move forward with his chicken.
And you think that they're like dear friends
and they've made this relationship,
but he's all about just making money,
which seemed a real commentary on the entertainment industry.
However, this is the time of the end of it.
Segment took 25 minutes.
That's what I'm saying.
What I just told you is the story,
and I got the point in and everything.
Of course, so far I want to see this film.
I'm even the time daily segment.
But it's all right, and it's interesting,
but it's one I don't think I'll revisit.
I thought that way about,
Oh brother were arced out the first time I saw it because I was growing me growing me and it grew on me
But I was riding such a high from Big Lebowski sure nothing they did could have followed it for me
And then when I saw oh brother right out there
I was disappointed and then the more I watched it the more I was like oh I get it right it's just I had to get a little distance
I watch the love me when I'm dead.
Yes.
Just a new Netflix documentary about Orson Wells's kind of final film that is now released
on Netflix as well.
I have not watched the film.
I wanted to see the making of prior.
I've heard the film is mocking self -indulgent directors of its day
But that it mocks them so well that it just feels like you're watching a self -indulgent director make a 70s drug movie
But the documentary was pretty interesting
Orson Wells is always a fascinating character just a drunken mess. I love I saw half of it
And then I shut it off because I didn't want to I was afraid they were gonna spoil the movie. I don't think the movie can be spoiled
Well, I think it's just like a head trip movie, um, but I loved it.
Yeah, the documentary is great.
Peter Bogdanovich, one of history's greatest, uh,
smarmy douchebags.
Yeah.
It's a great effect as, uh,
Dr. Malfi's therapist on the sopranos where he would have an
Ascot and a thermos.
We always pour water out of this thermos that crack me up every time.
But he is, I mean, you can find him on almost every DVD of a classic film
Stick in his nose and there with some big anecdote. He is such a windbag, but I do love him. He, uh, they show in the documentary
They show a clip of him in the other side of the wind, which is what the documentary is about that. That's the movie
And it's Peter by the way, I'm just talking about like being in the movie. Yeah, and it cuts to his part and he's like
He's like, oh
Oh, sir, he plays a reporter.
He's like, what did you think about it?
And you're sitting there going, what the fuck is he doing?
And then it cuts back to him and he goes,
for some reason Orson told me to play it like Jerry Lewis.
Yeah.
Well, Orson, around the time this movie came out
like last picture show and stuff dropped.
And then Orson Wall started getting insanely jealous
of Peter Bogdanovich, who he was dear friends with
and had him in this movie.
So he started turning against him.
But it's a good story if you like old Hollywood shit.
but it's very entertaining.
I also, my favorite part of the film
was seeing the interviews with the footage of Orson Welles
doing interviews with the press and stuff
where he was not a nebriator or anything
because Orson Welles now, a lot of him has been reduced
to these like clips that leak out of him doing
like these wine commercials and shit
where he's wasted.
It was nice seeing him at the end of his life
like talking to people and being collected and cognizant
and being charming and funny
And you're like, okay, this is like why this guy was good at what he did.
I can't believe it though.
They're like, they talk about how he couldn't, they're like, he never could have matched
citizen Kane.
They just, he's made so many brilliant movies.
Like, I'm just like, who looks at these movies and goes?
Yeah.
Touch of Evil, Lady from Shanghai, Magnificent Ambersons.
And he couldn't recover from Touch of Evil.
Consider one of the greatest films ever now.
Yeah.
These are all great movies.
But it's, it's an interesting documentary.
I don't have a comment on the film itself because I haven't watched it. That's a that's a great scene in Edward when he meets Wres and Wells. Yes
The studio wants me to cast Charlton Heston as a Mexican
Well that that counts as my number two as well. Okay, then folks. I'm gonna because last time I recommended it after the fact
I'm gonna recommend it while it's on because
Because for whatever reason, even though no one ever talks about it, nobody has the channel.
I tend to like the offerings of the Cinemax Network.
They are reduced to the joke of Skinemax, but they're much more.
They did an amazing show called Quarry that lasted one season that no one in the world saw.
I urge you to check it out.
It was great.
It started Logan Marshall Green, who was also the star of Upgrade.
And what they have going now is season two of Tales from the Tour bus.
season one about the outlaw
country guys was a real treat for me every week.
This is no different.
Yeah, the first one is about George Clinton
and Parliament, Funkadelic.
The second one is a two -parter
about Rick James bitch.
And they're great.
I told Joe the funniest story
in the George Clinton one
as they talk about being on acid.
They go in, they're performing
in this like hotel ballroom.
They're like we're all tripping our balls off at one point
Clinton lifts his like he's got like a
Blouse type thing on he lifts it up and is whipping his dick around shaking his dick around
They're like oh fuck we're gonna get in trouble. It's Bootsie Collins telling this story
He goes anyway, we played for two hours
Maybe the tightest we'd ever performed the best show we'd ever done. We were high out of our minds
Then the lights come up
There's not a single person in the motherfucking auditory, and we realized we were at the wrong place.
Nobody had seen us play for two hours.
I was laughing so hard and they cut over to George Clinton in the present day and he goes,
and I'll tell you what else.
That was neither the first nor the last time that that happened.
Just a perfectly told story.
Just the thought of like playing the best show of your life and no one is there, but you think people is there. It's pretty amazing.
Here's my question. You got to go through a sound check. Who's like, I am helping them set up.
I mean, I assume they just kind of like were like, this must be it. Everybody was like, okay, just going along with it.
I guess the tour, everybody was just fucked up.
I think they were at the right hotel, but in the wrong ballroom or something.
I'd have to watch it again to get the details funny, man.
It's a great store.
Tales from the tour bus, it's on cinemas.
They've only aired two.
I think the third one airs tonight.
Check it out.
Or last night, if you're listening to us on Monday.
Joe, did you have a pop tart?
How are pop tarts these days?
Are they the same rest of the thing?
I don't want one, but...
I got them for us.
I know.
You want some of that mix that I got?
Whatever that guardette hose?
Yeah.
No, I'm fine. I'm fine. I don't want this shit. I don't eat this crap
Why'd you buy it? Because I thought we would need it to snack on something instead of just drinking blindly on an empty stomach
Who stop and do it alone
So bonding experience I'm getting the nutrients from this five calorie orange juice
I'm gonna make us two fresh ones, but first let me hit you with some scary stuff. Please
You didn't make name your third your third picture
I don't have one because I'm saving my three. I have three left. I'm going to save them for the next episode. All right.
Because we're going back to back today. But I will hit you with a scary stuff real quick.
For Nintendo fans out there, a pretty cool reissue of a game that was only originally released in Japan.
The game is called Holy Diver.
Quincidentally, also the name of the best deo record and the best deo song.
Holy Diver is a Castlevania -esque type of video game.
Haven't you talked about Holy Diver because I think I sang Hold Me Close or Holy Diver?
I don't think I talked about this yet.
All right.
Why else would I have sang Hold Me Close or Holy Diver?
Well, maybe you just sang it to me when we were hanging out.
Okay.
Anyway, this game was originally only released in Japan.
It was, it is a Castlevania style game, but much darker, much, you know, much more horror -themed.
Well, not much, I shouldn't say much more, but it's sort of like a darker Castlevania, but the same solid game.
Anyway, it was only released in Japan until very, very recently a company picked up the rights and has re -issued it
and you can now put retro bit as the company.
You can now get reissues of it, not only in Japan,
but in the States as well.
I actually got mine in Japan,
so I have the Japanese reissue with this thing,
because I didn't know they released an American version,
but they did, and you can get that if you prefer.
But the Japanese version is plenty playable.
You know, it's not really a role -playing game,
so when the text comes up and you can't read it,
it doesn't really matter.
or you can piece the story together, people.
But great horror video game for horror fans out there.
I highly recommend you seek out this beautiful reissue
they did in a nice new box with,
I think there's a deluxe edition
that has all kinds of weird goodies in it and stuff.
But check it out if you have yourself unintended.
All right, now Pat, take the wheel
because I'm going to make us two more goof juices. Sure. I will take that wheel.
I'd like oh Joe wants me to make a joke about how cars have wheels and
plan strands automobiles. So anyway, make your own joke out of there. I'm sure it'll
be great. Um, plan strands automobiles. My history with the film, I was not allowed
to see our rated movies. It's been well covered on this show. My dad, whenever I'd catch
a little wind like he, once in a while, he'd be like, well, I can't remember why that would
be rated R. Then I knew that I could really work on him. Perhaps convince him to watch it
again and decide if it met his strict criteria.
So he watched plane strains,
the only R -rated content in it
because it definitely shouldn't be rated R.
Is the Steve Martin says,
fuck, 45 times,
talking to the lady at the car rental counter.
Edie McClureg,
character actress extraordinaire,
also played the secretary grace and Ferris Bueller's day.
I love Edie McClureg and she's somebody where I'm like,
how was she not in more stuff
And how is she not won awards? I know. Well, she was on the fucking Hogan family, which was like the most you got of her
She was the annoying next door neighbor. I mean she's she's really good, man
She's great. I tried to get her on my show and they were like she's kind of out of the game. So I
Think she might have had some health issues. I was supposed to do a podcast with her once
Oh, okay in Austin, Texas and and
The reason I said yes was because they said eating McClurger's appearing on right and I got there and they go she had to cancel
She was sick. Yeah, which it might have just been a lie to get a name like me down there
They'd just use her as bait eating McClure
That is an amazing amazing scene in the movie. It's a great scene
I remember the excitement that washed over me when my dad
Rewashed it and said it was okay for me to see it. He did not even make me leave the room for the fuck scene
But my favorite comedic actors at the time and really
I mean essentially right up to the present were John Candy and Steve Martin my favorite writer director was Mr
John Hughes and the fact that this movie existed and I was unable to see it tore me apart inside
Probably watch it when I was 12 13
It's a tamer of the John Hughes film. I agree. It's it's when he's when he starts clearly moving towards more family -oriented stuff
Yeah, you know, it's pre it's it's not too long before home alone
right you know Dutch all that stuff you know where he kind of gets out of kids
fucking yeah and into adults yeah 16 canals is PG way racier than
plans trains which came out years later and his rated R 16 canals is PG are
you sure about that came out just before the PG 13 rating there's Titson it
there's a joint there's a fuck and there's a you know what some people argue now
was a date rate. Yes. Yes. The opening line of the Steve Martin thing is, I mean it's
just, you know, you can start by wiping that stupid fucking smile off your rosy fucking
face. Yeah. It's a great scene. Watching it the other night and maybe it was just being
high. All of my laughs came from candy. I think that is one of the best performances,
not just comedic performances, one of the best performances of all time, is John
Candy and playing strans. Steve Martin, who was a master, especially at this kind
of straight man role, he's the perfect straight man, but he's kind of playing catch -up
to candy. Candy is... I don't think he's playing catch -up. I think he's
playing his part. He knows where he knows where to do it. Yes. He knows how to do it.
But anybody else that's...
Martin could not have played the John Candy part.
That's for damn sure.
Well, I don't think anybody but John Candy could have played the candy.
But my point is, is a less skilled actor than Steve Martin would have been in there trying
to chew up the scenery.
But Steve Martin knew.
He's like, no, you let you lay back, and it's all about my reaction to this guy, and not
about me being funny.
Yeah.
I think a similar performance to that is Nicholas Cage and Honeymoon and Vegas, which is
a very underrated movie as well.
that kind of great slow build frustration that has moments where it gets a
little big but nothing crazy. My only issues with the film seeing it as you
know a 37 -year -old man and no longer a child is stuff like when he's walking off
the runway Steve Martin and St. Louis Lambert Airport when he walks into the
place, he's got his tie wrapped around his head. And I was like, well, so the wind blew his
tie from his neck up to his head, like in a movie that is so character -based and so realistic,
they make a few choices where you're like, what are you doing? And I'm not talking about
when they turn to skeletons and when you see John Candy as the devil, because that fucking
and made me howl in it.
That, for seeing it with an audience,
that thing played huge.
Candy in the devil suit is pretty magnificent.
I have that as a frame picture in my home.
It's pretty magnificent and he's doing that candy laugh.
Yes, it's pretty great.
There's just a few of those little moments
and then the biggest issue
and it's pretty egregious on a big screen
when you have the sound system pumping,
is it has one of the worst musical scores in the history of film right it
almost derails the movie in spots the worst offender is of course they go
back to it again and again this shitty hip -hop beat like turn tables and then
Steve Martin's voice from earlier in the film going you're messing with the wrong
guy. So you're looking at Steve Martin doing something and hearing his own voice say lines
that you've already heard over a rap beat and it's so fucking bad. Last night there was
at an event and I met Mark Boone Jr. who's an actor that I'm a fan of. He's in Sons of
VanArkey plays Bobby Munson and he was in Momento.
He was in Batman Begins is what I know him from mostly.
He plays Bullock in Batman Begins and he's great.
He plays a great dirty cop.
Anyway, he's at this event that I performed at
and I noticed in the audience while I was on stage,
he was laughing.
I thought, oh, great, I can go meet this guy.
And I walked up to him and I was like,
hey man, I just want to say I'm a big fan of your work.
And he was like, hey man, that was really funny.
I really liked it. I was shit faced at this point. This is hours later. And I go,
I love what you do, man. Batman begins delirious. Yeah. You're in delirious, right?
And with John Candy, and he goes, yeah, he goes, yeah, man. And I go like this. I go, you've
been playing with this, haven't you? And he goes, I'm sorry, excuse me. And I go, you've
been playing with this avenue and he goes,
what are you talking about?
And I go, that's your line in Delirious.
You're the cable guy and you go,
and he goes, oh, I can't fucking remember him.
And I was like, all right, well, I'll let you go.
You think even if he didn't remember stuff,
he wouldn't remember Delirious.
I felt really stupid.
I know who this guy is.
He looks like, who does he look like?
Got a wild look.
Yeah, he looks like a troll almost.
All right, well you know to cut the guy down, but he he was on Suns of Anarchy. Yes, that's correct. I mean
He was born to be on Suns of Anarchy. He looks like a biker. Yeah, there's no more perfect role for him
But then when you see him all shaved down, he's barely recognizable like in Delirious. It's I didn't even realize it was him. Yeah
Do you have his IMDb up while you were talking to him and go through each film? I did also say I own a perfect place on DVD and he went a
a perfect place and I went it's a short film you did where you'd got to hide
the dead body I bought it because Mike Patton my favorite musician he like he
did the soundtrack so I bought it and it came with the DVD it's pretty good
little short he's like oh yeah oh yeah okay cool thanks seem as if he didn't
remember most of what he had been it I mean that's a guy who's in three things
a year and doesn't think anything of it probably done a lot of drugs he died
well he looks like he might like to have a good time yeah you know but I can't I
I can't speak for that.
Anyway, I just brought that up
because it was a candy thing.
Sorry, back to the trains, plane trains.
Quite a right.
Yeah, this score, I mean, it helped me out.
I bought on Amazon the soundtrack
to plane trains for like a penny.
Why?
Because I loved the movie so much,
I was like, I'd like to have it.
This was years ago.
Does it have that rap beat on it?
It does.
I got it, I played it.
I was like, this soundtrack is terrible.
Especially for John Hughes,
Who like was a connoisseur of good music? So well it seems like that was probably around the time where it got a lot more
Expensive to put songs in movies. Yeah, and he was like we need an original. He did score, you know
We were talking about it last night that the that fucking awful sentimental
Yeah, and like the scene where John Candy's sitting in his car, where he's like, you did it again. You can't shut up, Candy. It's like a very sad scene. The whole time, it's like,
Like the same volume as his beautiful monologue and it's annoying.
The end every time you go away is like, you know, that works.
That's a pop song.
But they got this shitty version of it.
Like even the Hall and Oates version would have been better.
It's a terrible version of the song.
Yeah, it's like the version you get on like the CD you buy it at the checkout in the supermarket.
Yeah.
Where it's like all covers of songs.
I'm surprised that he had hues let it all slide the end of my little anecdote on the soundtrack is that
This movie while always well -liked
Became sort of a Thanksgiving staple. I think when Ebert included in his great movies column
Which usually was reserved for a citizen cane and stuff like that and he put it in that company
He didn't use a Chicago man. So it makes sense
But he was like this is one of the best character comedies ever made and he's right. Mm -hmm
I noticed at that point the movie developed like a big following, it became a yearly Thanksgiving tradition for people.
I popped back on Amazon and I sold that soundtrack for $145. I still remember the price.
A shitty, used CD copy of the Planestrand soundtrack.
Now, I scrolled down. I was on Google Search Mark Boone, Jr.
yeah first video things get awkward in a hurry with sons of anarchy star mark
book junior they there there's a paparazzi videotaping him coming out of the
supermarket uh -huh Joe apparently thinks we're doing a Mark Boone junior
podcast I'm trying to talk about one of my favorite films over here alone the the
actor looks at the cameraman and says what are you doing man what are you doing
like, what are you doing? That, that makes sense. I understand that. And then when the
guy asks him about it, if there's going to be a son of Ion Eric, he spit off. Boone
says, you know, man, it's the mine thing, whatever. Good luck today. I should have spent more
time with this guy last night. Yeah. I can't believe Papa Routzi is stopping this guy.
But okay. Sounds like Ion Eric. He was a huge show. It was. He was not even like a huge key
role in it. I um back to playing strains. Yeah. I was going to say I met some I know somebody
who is famous who told and I'm not going to name names because I don't I don't roll
like that Pat. Sure. I don't roll like that. We already said Pete Holmes once. That's as deep
as I go. Um but a famous person just talking about how I don't roll like that either with my
a good friend Fred Savage yesterday on set.
We were both not those kind of guys.
Speaking of which, I was at the Rainbow Barn
Grill the other night.
I thought I could have sworn Ben Savage was in there.
He might have been.
It wasn't.
I kept staring for a real long time,
and then finally, after 20 minutes realized,
that's not Ben Savage.
Yeah.
Anyway, it was there.
Though Ron Jeremy, just looking like he crawled out
of the deep fryer in the fucking cage lived there,
I've seen him like an outside of the hustler bar and grill.
It's got to be a dark life, right? Oh, yeah. Anyway, I a person
I know that had lunch with Steve Martin. He said he also said
playing strings and automobiles was his favorite movie. And he
said he asked Steve Martin about the scene. You know, you want
to hurt me? Yeah, I'm going to use a target that whole scene. And
Steve Martin said it was the fight of the century. The studio
desperately tried to remove the scene really because they thought it was too
heavy and too sad yeah I mean these people don't know what the fuck I mean I've
never heard worse decisions being made it's literally what makes the fucking
movie this is the topic I can't get into today or I'll be out on the 10 free
way drunk screaming at passing cars, studio and network interference, but he, it's one,
one of the best scenes in movie history.
And I had never seen it at a theater.
So to see it, you feel the audience like laugh, laugh, laugh, laugh at the Steve Martin
line, cut over to John Candy's face, everyone's like, like the air goes out of the room.
Then he'll build them back up laughing again, because what he's saying is so funny
Yeah, but then they cut to candy again and everybody's like
Oh, and it happens over and over. It's something credible
It's a brilliant brilliantly scripted and acted scene
It makes you think about all the times you've been in both positions. Yeah
You were a hundred percent with Steve Martin laughing your balls off because up until that points
It's tribute to how well written the script is. Yeah up until that point
I mean, candy's character is unbearable.
Yeah.
He's awful up into that point.
And that's the first time he realized,
oh, this is a person.
He's not like the cartoon character.
Right.
And that's when you start to like candy in that moment.
Yeah.
You know, because up until then, yeah,
he's the guy that steals his cab.
He takes his shoes off on the plane.
He does offer beer, slurpee, hot dog, coffee.
Yeah.
He's like the crass guy.
Diner bucks in my left nut says there's no way we land in Chicago whatever whatever the line is
You know so
But uh, but you know that scene is truly truly incredible
It's such an amazing turning point in the movie and it's and then it's also when you realize like oh Steve Martin
It doesn't have it all together. Yeah, he's a he's kind of a shitty upie who's on his own world
It needs to learn that there are other people out there that aren't like it's a fucking great movie man
Jesus Christ.
Yeah.
At that time, Steve Martin was always the hero of these things and he kind of is and in
these movies and in the millions of movies that have ripped this off, your due dates,
whatever it may be, your Dutch.
Your Dutch and I fucking love Dutch, but this one is so much more nuanced than that because
you are totally on Steve Martin's side and then it's like, oh, wait a minute.
Because generally they would treat that guy as a joke the whole time till the last two minutes
into the movie. And then it's like, oh, he's not a joke anymore. Now we care about him
because you need to for the movie. Yeah. But this is like, no, let's treat them both
as like real actual human beings throughout. They both learn from each other. And John
Candy learns like, yeah, you can't just flap your gums all the time either. Like they both
have a very valid lesson that they take away from this movie.
Well, also when you realize that the, you know, the candy's character is the way he is
because he's running from the pain of having lost his wife.
Yes.
And he can't go home and like, this is sort of the cocoon
he's created for himself.
It's fucking heartbreaking.
Also, and I don't say this to be crashed.
I root for real.
I'm really asking this.
That last scene where he meets the wife.
Yeah.
It seems a little flirty, doesn't it?
The way she's like, hello, Mr. Griffith.
Was that you saying this?
No.
Somebody brought it up at work and I was like,
shut your fucking mouth.
Like, don't you ruin this move.
Shut the fuck up.
Seems a little weirdly and then I watched it couldn't get it out of my head. She's not being I know that's not the intention
Yeah, but it's odd the way they they it almost seems like they're gonna bang or so ruining it for all these people
And I wish I'd never had that thought in my head to be honest fine now
Let me throw this at you this might this might floor you John candy when this movie was made
35 years old Jesus Christ man looks 53
three. Easily. 35. I mean, if he was 40, he Martin was 27. Yeah, I think he was born
in 1950. So he would have been, let me double check this because I realize we say a lot
of things wrong on this podcast week after week. Yeah, born in 1950. So he died when he was
44 so in wagons these two was only 44. And then this was 87. Yeah, by the way,
back to the Mark Boone junior video, 36, pushing a full shopping cart to his car.
It has a thing of toilet paper in it. That's it. Is that like Arrowhead? I don't know.
Looks like a place I go. Supermart. Look at that. Full shopping cart. All of a sudden,
is the toilet paper. The man. I mean, would you want to be stopped while you're taking out a 84
pack of toilet paper? I'm just saying, wouldn't you just carry the toilet paper to your car?
You would. You would. Um, anyway, so yeah, 37 when plans ran, we lost, we lost many, many
great years with John Candy. It's a terrible thing. We just aged differently now. I was watching
Sin fell the other day. Yeah, there's a scene where George is like, I'm 33. I deserve more and like
What the fuck? Well, it's because I think he was actually like 33
It's because people like that were allowed on television and in movies. That's the difference
Of course, you know a 33 year old who looks like a young George Stanza, but only beautiful people are were generally on TV and in movies
I don't know any 33 year old that is age that poorly.
I think also when you see somebody from when you're a kid,
they seem impossibly old, but they are not.
It's just an odd thing.
It's like to me, you're gonna tell me,
you don't notice a difference between a modern day
Jason Alexander and a 33 year old Jason Alexander?
Well, of course, he looks older now.
Yeah.
But I mean, it's just, it's a different aging process.
You watch that show there's no party you that goes Jerry Seinfeld as a man in his early 30s
You you ever true true. It's like it's just and part of it is because of lifestyle
You just grew up differently. Yes, you know, it's like though. They're those are friends all looked
They all felt yeah, but it's just interesting to me like the thing they do on
And Seinfeld a lot is like they get cake and coffee as younger people.
That's an old person thing to do, but it was just a different time I guess.
I feel like our Seinfeld would be like, you know, just were doubled over in a fucking
bar, you know, like, oh, Christ, you know, I have a crush on the blue sweatpants lady.
Hey, do you want to go get drunk?
You have a crush on a blue sweatpants lady at the bar.
That's why they have a box in Seinfeld.
Oh, oh yeah, that's right.
He goes, yeah, girl, of course, the girl in the blue, my bad.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Um, we were going to do a commentary on plans, trains.
It wasn't streaming anywhere, which is absurd.
We are planning a commentary for the near future.
We'll do one.
We hear you.
This one was widely requested.
So we felt OK, breaking the format.
And it's Thanksgiving week.
Enjoy your Thanksgiving.
Have a good one.
Watch this movie, if you can, because it's absolutely
fantastic. A great Michael McKean cameo also from the Better Call Saul family. I'm not
remembering that. The cop who pulls him over. Oh, that's right. Do you feel this vehicle
is safe for highway travel? Yes, I do. Yes, I really do. You couldn't, I was really cool
on a theater to hear it. Like lines were, you couldn't hear lines, which is really rare
in a movie that's like 30 years old. That's like when we saw smoking in the bandit, it was
Yeah, man. Uh, the, uh, oh, I got to mention my favorite line in the whole entire movie though. I'll do mine as well is
We were robbed you think so do you think so
Incredo it's so unexpected does that scene actually plays kind of slow and you're like all right get to the information
But it's all just building up for that
My favorite line is right after that where they're trying to see if they have any credit cards and Steve Martin's like
Yeah, you know mine are gonna work to what do you what do you have any credit cards and he goes
Cholmer's big and tall men shop
It's a seven -outlet chain in the Pacific Northwest great stuff
Unfortunately, it does us no good here
That response got like a two -minute laugh. I couldn't pull myself together and
That felt probably wrong because he was always wrote great lines like that
He never left the line unfunny
That's what I most admire about it, but candy also did a lot of improv and that that to me
Smells like a candy improv because I'm remembering that amazing home alone improv about getting trapped with a dead body
But uh, what is that? I don't remember it in home alone. He's telling Catherine O 'Hara
Every every line he says in home alone apparently is improvised. It was him in O 'Hara
And he had 24 hours between movies. He flew in shot it left
And completely improvise the scene where he talks about how he's like don't feel bad about leaving your son home alone.
I left my boy in the room at a funeral home with the dead body for hours and he does this big monologue about it.
That is in home alone and people forget about it, but it's an incredible scene.
It's the, that's up there with the, and we look, we've talked about it very recently,
but the, another great -used monologue is the, is the accharide, for sure.
My husband and a story my uncle would tell, about a bunch of army patients that were being
experimented on, escaped from the metal cages they were kept in, found a group of campers
slaughtered and ate them.
yeah man's a great great job the movie boy is incredible we lost John
candid too soon too soon uh we also like we lost his talent even before he was
dead he had four his last four years were just kind of embarrassing same deal
with Farley I think Canadian bacon is okay I mean bacon sucks I mean it's not
worse than wagons east. I saw wagons east opening day at the theater. It's not great.
It can't be worse than wagons east. Him and Richard Lewis on the western trail.
I mean, a fan of both of them, but I just let this picture. But right before wagons east
was, uh, wasn't it like only the lonely? The lonely is great. Yeah. I love only the really
good movie showing it a little different side. Delirious got a panda. I love it. Anyway,
by Jotaroza Comedy on Instagram, this weekend, shit, yeah, if you're in Philly, I will be
at the punchline and fill it off your Friday night and Saturday night, two shows each
night. Come on out, work off that turkey dinner with a few aerobic laughs. I'm at the Patrick
Walsh, sort of on Twitter, sort of on Instagram. We have a great Instagram page. We'll see
when hell? Is it see you when hell pod on Instagram? Yes, see you when hell pod. They as I didn't
even know our friend Vince pointed out that they do these dialogue exchanges that I often don't
even remember but are super funny on the Instagram. He was loving them. I didn't know they did
him either and we're drinking in a bar and he started reading them to me and I was laughing. I never
look at the Instagram stories. So, so now I am. So, yeah, thank you to Emily for all that.
The Hoghouse, Etsy page, check out the merch, check out our Patreon page. Thank you for all the
support. Thank you for the support and cool kids Friday nights, 8 .37 .37. See you next time. Happy
Thanks for having me and we'll see you in the next video.