Summer is here, and Bed MGM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer, or check out our
exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and the Wizard of Oz, only available at Bed MGM
Casino.
Spin on Spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Land, Raken
Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia
only, games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal, durable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Monthly 21 -plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberer, offer not available in all states
terms apply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
This is a headgun podcast.
Folks, welcome to we'll see you in hell
It's a show that delves into one horror sci -fi fantasy type movie or show each week
It's a spirited discussion that branches off and all kinds of different crazy wild wacky directions
Anyway, without further ado. I guess we'll get on with the show and in doing so on with the Joe
Yeah, I
That was a good one.
Very, uh, well, it started like one of those clown horns.
Yeah.
Like a, like a fail and then it went into like a vaudeville thing.
That's very good.
How are you?
Well, I'm good.
I was just talking with Joe here about our great new sponsor,
Me Undies.
They're sending me and Joe pairs of Undies, which is exciting.
But I had to say, the word Undies, so many times during this ad
And it was rough folks and I also had to say the phrase so soft and touchable the
You don't want to hear me say that. It's fine. I get it
I don't want to hear me say it either. You don't want to hear it. No, you don't want to hear it
But I had to do it hold on a second. It's a great product and I can't wait to get my balls into them
Never mind. I thought something was wrong. Nothing's wrong. That's good. All right. I thought something was wrong. Nothing's wrong. Everything's right
today. It's Sunday. It's Sunday. We're in my apartment. Very hot in LA. I like
to get things pop and conversation wise with a little weather talk. But it's
real hot. I mean we have a special episode for you today. We are doing a
commentary on a TV show which is a first and today's TV show is of course her
related and it's the Monsters Today, which was a reboot of the Monsters from 1989, it was
a reboot of the original Monsters that was released tonight, maybe not.
Yes.
Okay.
Yes, excuse me.
And in a bunch of episodes of the Monsters, but when I was very young, like I would say less
than 10, and I don't really remember it, but I've never seen this new version of the Monsters,
nor did I know it existed.
I remember when I was a kid, I really liked it.
it. And I saw that they released it on Hulu. Yeah. My assumption is because Seth Meyers
is rebooting the monsters again. Uh -huh. You said it's in hipster Williamsburg, Brooklyn.
Yeah, which I think I like Seth Meyers, but that that sounds like a bad idea to me, but
you know, I don't know. I did all those jokes on on the broke girls. It was a hipster as
a Williamsburg. We get it. Well, also, this never works. This is like when they did like
the caveman thing. Yeah. It's like it, it just doesn't work. And I guarantee you it's going to be like
a darker sexier monsters. You know, it's like the sexy Godzilla that we discussed on the show.
Yeah. Like nobody, like he's not going to look like Frankenstein. He's going to be Frankenstein.
He's not going to be your father's Frankenstein. Yeah. He's just, he's the stitches are going to be hidden
by his clothing and stuff for the name of the Frank probably for Frankie yeah so you know I don't
know I guess it'll be I don't know we'll see but anyway I think because of that announcement they
they put the monsters today reruns on Hulu right so I started rewatching them and I'm deep in at
this point I'm willing to season two well so then it doesn't look like we're about to watch the pilot
this is called vampire pie or is that the name of the pilot this is no the pilot
it was never aired as far as I know.
This is episode one, season one.
Okay, so folks, if you do want to get it,
we had a bit of talking to do before we started,
but if you want to search it,
it is called The Monsters Today,
season one, episode one, Vampire Pie,
you get a cute up if you want to watch along with us.
Yeah, and it's on Hulu.
And we also have the Hulu that's commercial free.
So yeah, right.
This is going to go 21 minutes straight on our end.
So keep that in mind on your end.
and just pause it, folks.
Yeah, we'll count it off when we're ready.
I've also heard they're inserting ads into our old episodes,
which is awesome, but they break up the commentary sometime.
So, you know, it's a little annoying, I know,
but the easiest solution is just to pause both at the same time
when you hear an ad fire up.
And hopefully they won't do that anymore.
We've requested that they not do this, so.
Okay, so let's get on with the other stuff
we gotta do before we get into it,
because we got a new segment today we're going to get to.
Yes.
But first off, Pat's movie corner.
What do you got?
Well, you know, I've been very busy, but I watched most
of the season of Glow and the Gorgeous Ladies
of Wrestling Show.
And while I'm not like yucking up, yucking it up at it,
laughing a lot, it's a very entertaining show.
It's shot great, great 80s music.
the ladies are gorgeous, it's called the Gorgeous Ladies of Wrestling, and it's just got a nice,
fun, funny vibe. My one grievance with Orange is a new black, is that I like it, but I think it
should have been a half hour. You know, I find that I'm struggling near the end of the season to get
through. Glow is basically your half hour Orange is a new black. A bunch of funny characters,
Mark Marin is great in it. Alison Brie is really great in it, and I love it.
Good, I love the show. I love Marin, and I'm happy to hear that he's on a cool
new show. I haven't watched it yet. Yeah, it's as good as he's been as an actor. He's a good actor. Yeah.
So you started watching Glow. I watched some classic stuff here. Kojak, Kojak, The Night Stalker,
which I'd never seen. It's a TV movie from the, I guess, late 70s starring, what's his face?
uh... that from the game in the game as uh... as cold check you know that role was
uh... written for and offered to an almost played by jack nicholson
the role of the dad and christmas story
oh i think the old man check
which but i don't see both
yeah now he was going to be the dad and christmas story which
would have been a much bigger movie obviously but maybe
maybe not as uh...
but nobody nobody nobody could have what mcgavin did with that role he was great
Right he was great.
He is the guy.
Nicholson also came very close to doing bad Santa, which I can see.
I don't know that he would have been better than Billy Bob.
I could see it a little more than the Christmas story.
And Bill Murray was very close to playing bad Santa.
Oh, that would have been interesting.
Very dark for Murray character.
That's a role that I think would have been very different regardless of who played it, but
they got the right guy in my opinion.
But I found the double feature of Colcheck the Nightstalker and the Night Strangler at
of Meeba Records for a cool $18 used, but then I checked online and it's selling for
like 40 bucks used online. So I got a deal. A honey of a deal.
Night Strangler is enjoyable, but okay, but I thoroughly enjoyed Night Stalker. I thought
it was cool. I really like the interpretation of the vampire. You know, the vampire like,
There's all these scenes like the blood banks keep getting robbed in addition to people showing up dead
Because he's just like I got to just get a lot of blood. Right. That's how I live
So there's like a scene where they catch the vampire robbing the blood bank
And all these cops are trying to stop him and he's just like
throwing cops through windows and shit, you know like he just cut I was like that's a cool take on this like that's how a normal guy
Yeah with vampire powers would would just rob a place. Yeah
Yeah.
So I enjoyed it, McGavin is charming as ever, and it's a funny film, and it's got some
creepy parts.
I liked it.
I liked it a bit, quite a bit.
So I want to get the TV show now, which I've never seen.
The movie came first, two movies, which they're essentially the same movie.
The Night Strangler is not a vampire, but it's a creature that needs blood to survive or
something.
Then why waste Strangler, like, why?
It's weird.
It's almost like creature and night Strangler. It sounds like
Jack the Ripper. It's almost like night. It's almost like this network thing
My assumption is it's some network thing where they're like well the first one was great
But we want you to prove yourself again remake the same thing right and then we'll give you a show
And then the show only went 20 episodes anyway, but yeah, but anyway
I would like to see the the entire show now and I enjoyed it
I still have not watched gross point blank. I'm sorry
It's christ. Uh, I've been away. I was thinking I like showing people my movie rack with this giant gaping hole in the jeez
Just calling out. I know you don't like that. No, I don't
The other of us have seen much. I think the only other thing to discuss for this segment
is Twin Peaks, am I right? Twin Peaks, yeah. I mean, I'd say spoiler alert, but if you're
not watching it, you're probably not going to watch it. Let's be real. It's been a
frustrating ride with some huge eyes. Yes. But essentially, I think we can say
this without saying it. They've kept a truly beloved character from the Twin
Peaks universe, kind of at an arm's length, the entire season. And now that he's
finally getting back to the character that you love, which happened end of
episode last week, I learned that tonight is the finale. So the entire run of
the show, except for the finale, they keep this guy not what you want them to be.
And I get that David Lynch is clearly into fucking with people, but this it
almost feels a little cruel looking back over the season with like what he made
people put up with. I don't think it had to be like that. But I've seen some
reviews of this thing that are making me think I should watch it again. They're
saying and there's tons of stuff you missed about, and I'm sure there is.
Well, I will say in the last two episodes so far this season, they started tying up
a lot of loose ends.
They started clearing up a lot of the air, and I had a lot of, oh, okay, moment.
So I was like, all right, maybe I need to re -watch this, and it's a different experience.
I also realized, too, that had everything just been the way I wanted it to be from the beginning.
probably would have gotten kind of stale or boring. I also realized that something
I thought was interesting. It's an exact reverse of the first season. The first
season starts very small and gets crazier and crazier. This one starts
insane and gets smaller and smaller until finally all roads lead back to Twin
peaks. Yeah. So I appreciate that. And I said to pet earlier, I have a hunch. This is
sort of a slow setup for another season. I think so. I might be wrong. I don't know. Now,
let me ask you, Joe. So when Grace the brisky, who is her mother, Joseph played Susan's mother
on Seinfeld, to like just classic TV roles for this moment, very intense actress. So yes,
There's an episode where mild spoiler alert, but not really, she essentially takes her
face off to reveal like the universe inside of her face.
This is revealed to not be a dream sequence and actually happens to other people throughout.
So this was not, Twin Peaks was always nuts.
I don't recall things like people opening their face to reveal a portal to another world.
Well, she's a plant, like Lauren's character.
They said in the last episode that Lauren's character,
they were like, you're not you, you're a plant, we grew you.
So apparently the black lodge is putting
like these doppelgangers out there.
Okay.
That's right.
So something's going to happen.
But the doppelgangers go out to enjoy a bloody Mary.
Are we to believe?
I think the doppelganger's job is to be a decoy, so it's like business as usual.
Go around town, be the crazy lady, everybody thinks you are drinking the bar, smoke your
cigarettes, and if anybody gets out of line, you take care of it, which she does, so that's
how I took it.
This helped me already.
I'm glad we discussed this because I was left pretty baffled and I haven't read any of
the fan theories and shit.
But I will say this I was giddy last week. Yeah, it was great when when things started coming together
I was giddy when Audrey Horn danced to the original Twin Peaks music and thank God because her story
But that's why I'm kind of thinking her story was the worst storyline in television history
It's Audrey Horn arguing with a dwarf husband about whether or not they're gonna go out or not and it goes on for like six weeks
One week felt like about half the episode. I did find it very twin -peaks though
right I hated it it was the worst they it was even worse than the installing
Venetian blind storyline that they did in the original TV show and I hated it
so much and then at the end when I was like I can't look at these two anymore
this is this is infuriating me then she breaks out the dance and starts dance then
just as I was getting tired of this other character not coming around he comes
around and the first thing that happens is the guy he's talking to says finally I
I think David Lynch is saying like he's toying with your expectations, but just spoiler alert.
What are you referring to?
What other character?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, the main, I mean we could we can we just say it for Christ's sake,
say it's Cooper.
I was and essentially a coma and he's not himself and then he comes around at the end of the
second to last up.
I was off the couch when he when he jumps out of the bed, pulls the tubes out and the guy
goes, you're awake, he goes 100 % like I was like, and then they start playing the twin
peaks theme.
I'm getting chills.
And he goes, should he call the FBI?
And he goes, I am the FBI.
He's like right back in his Cooper.
Right.
I also enjoyed that he understood everything that was going on when he was in that cantonic
state.
Yeah.
He wasn't another person.
He just knew he was trapped and he couldn't communicate, which explains why he was able
to like solve the insurance issues and all that stuff.
So I thought that was all really cool and I also like that at the end of the episode Audrey Horne seems to wake up in another place
Yeah, that was wild possibly a mental institution and I'm like, okay, so this this story with her and her husband is like in her head
Maybe yeah, by the way, Billy I think is the guy in the jail cell that has the blood constantly coming out of his mouth
Yeah, he was on the best show this week with Tom Sharpen. He was the guest
What is he's like in real life?
It was just super nice, you know.
David Lynch was just like, I want you to play this part.
It's a revolting character.
It is.
He said his wife can't watch it.
It's disgusting.
Yeah.
And it's not blood coming out of his mouth.
It's like it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's like, it's gross.
And the same thing that came out of that, in my favorite scene of this entire season, the
passenger in the car when that fat woman hits, re -rends them.
And then I think comes up and all that goop comes out of it.
Yeah.
That was my favorite scene of the whole thing and that woman was a genius, that actress.
The other weird thing that happened at the end of the last episode, which is curious,
is a gray -haired man attacks another guy and goes, that's my fucking wife.
It looks maybe like it's Bobby from the back.
And we do know that Bobby does have some envy about his, what's his girlfriend's name on
the show?
I can't remember her name, don't remember her name.
But you know, she's got that new guy and he's clearly not happy about it and their daughters
all fucked up.
So I think maybe that's Bobby attacking that guy.
Okay.
I don't know.
So I'm curious to see what happens tonight.
Yeah.
I mean, Heather, my finance and I have been watching it religiously and I, you know, she likes
it perhaps more than I and it was one of my favorite things.
She got super into it and the new season.
She's gone till Tuesday.
say, I can't, I can't wait.
I'm going to have to watch it on a y -cliff song.
Yeah.
So my decision is, do I say, hey, I haven't watched
Twin Peaks yet.
You want to watch it hit play and then just sit
through it a second time.
No one's the wiser.
I think that's, or do I come playing him, be honest?
No, I said, you just wait and you watch it with her.
It's too late.
I'm going to watch it tonight.
It's going to be ruined for me.
Runed.
Well, don't go on the internet, Pat.
But I like the internet.
I'm safe there.
We need a comfortable, you got a, it tells me
news and gives me validation.
I would wait to watch you with your lady, that would be a very special experience for
the two of you.
You're right.
But then sure of that cherry so to speak, God.
But then, you know, I check it on my Gmail and there's a pop up in the corner that says,
can you believe Dale Cooper was really John Goodman or whatever the fuck and then it's ruined?
That doesn't happen, that's not going to happen.
If you get on the internet at all after a big thing, you're going to find out about it.
You just have to avoid the side that's supposed to check my notification. It's not gonna. Oh, it's not gonna hurt you to stay off Twitter for a day
And then you know, all right, just just don't fuck around. Yeah, why don't you stay off Twitter for a day. Let's see if you can do it, Joe
On to Joe's scary stuff. Is that cool? I'm ready
Third week in a row. We got a creep show item creep show the graphic novel adaptation of the original film, which was a release in
1982 or three
my dear friend James Pinkstone, or we had a copy for when he was a kid that his dad had bought him,
and he has been the envy of me for our entire friendship, for having an original copy
of the Creepshow graphic novel. But much to my joy, they have re -released it. I got it on Amazon.
I think it was $13. Very, very nice job. Came in the mail today. Looks great. Looks exactly like the
comic book in the movie that the kids reading. And then it's, you know, full adaptations of all the
stories. So very, very cool. I suggest you get that if you're lover of film and comic books.
All right. Thank you. Anything for this? Well, Joe, I mean,
shall we discuss a brief scary personal thing? It's not part of it, but we can, yeah.
I never quite know what the theme is. Let me try to explain this. It's horror fantasy
sci -fi -related products. It's just not a movie or a show. No, but here's what it can be.
You can say, I got the box set of the Millennium TV show,
which I really love.
And my point was,
I think the Stone Edge one worked.
Sort of.
But you do a review of the box set.
You're not reviewing the show, saying,
here's what I like about the show is what I don't,
you're saying like, here's what they gave you in the box set.
Here's the bonus features.
This, they did a nice job.
I got it, it's just like how many horror box sets do you think
I'm gonna buy?
I gotta put shit on home for this week.
I got two video games in the bank. I got to talk about listen, you don't have to have something for this. It's okay
Well, no, I was gonna say but go ahead. We maybe this is a fourth segment now where it'll be called pets
Scary personal issues. Yeah, no. Yeah, I mean
It is it is a scary life. I have a lot more responsibility and pressure and so forth now running the show
Yes, and the worst part of this entire process has been folks
Joe was not continuing with the show.
Yes.
I walked off the set.
It was an ethical debate.
Artistic differences.
I'm not going to throw any one of the bus.
I know.
It was about 10 billion percent, not me.
I fought against it.
You can't really fight these sorts of things.
It was a network matter.
They wanted to go a different way.
That said, you will see Joe in the pilot of the show when it airs.
and he gives an incredible performance.
And he really does.
I've said it from day one.
And then you can go back and review that he's just gone.
You can go back and review the tapes.
But, you know, I've said on the show many times,
Joe was great in it.
He was really great in it.
He's funny at first.
And then he gives a great dramatic performance.
And I'm not gonna give you any more details on that.
But he's great in it.
If I was Joe, I'd submit him for an Emmy.
I'm gonna submit him for a guest star, Emmy.
I'm a very cute Patty.
You know, no promises obviously, but I he did a great job. It was a thing. They do a guest star
army Betty White usually wins for the for the ladies. Um, but, you know, you'll see what a crime
it was that Joe has been replaced. It was completely against my my wishes and uh, no, no struggle
between Joe and myself. I think he understood what it was. Uh, you watch me be torn apart by this
process in the past. I said to pet and I continued. I said to pet very early on and maybe I am petting
myself on the back. I'm not. I just, but I said, I said to Pat very early on, I was like,
look, dude, if the day ever comes, because I knew how tough it was for him through all
this stuff. And there's a real push and pull between network versus artistic versus the production
company versus the studio, real push and pull. So he was, you know, having an emotional ride,
bumpy ride, obviously, which was understandable. And I just said, look, dude, if the day ever
comes that they say, we don't want this guy in the picture anymore, just tell me, don't
carry any of it on yourself. I get it, dude. I know how this shit works. And that's exactly
what happened. And as I said to Pat today, I was bummed for about four hours. I went
to a bar with Vince Avril. We talked about quite frequently on this podcast. We had a few
drinks. He gave me a shoulder to cry on for a minute. I, after a few drinks, I was like,
you know what? I don't want to get drunk right now. That's not going to make this better.
I came home, I was feeling sad, I took a nap on the couch, I woke up, and that was it.
I was like, all right, up and at him.
And the next day, you know, I just got back to life and I actually said, this is going
to happen sooner or later, I'm glad that I got to experience it, and I'm glad that I'm
able to stomach it like this.
So that's all very true, and I cannot thank enough the support that I got from Pat, the
entire cast reached out
every single person reached out to me first and foremost was uh... sarah
gilbert
yes
uh... who's a lovely woman
rose and fame who i was all structures are working with
uh... and uh...
as soon as i got the news i got a text from sarah like an hour later
uh... which she didn't have to do and you know but but jay well you were loved by
the cast i mean what what shocked me was that uh...
Joe's firing wasn't an interpersonal issue,
because I assumed he would be in a fistfighter
or a screaming match or something, they want.
So I get the call that he's gone.
I was like, oh, Joe's sent a threatening text,
maybe a leering DM to someone in the cast.
But no, the whole cast love Joe
and we're all kind of baffled and you know.
It's a sad thing, but yeah, I made some great connections.
I made some great new friends.
I got paid to do a TV show.
Yeah, and you'll see him in the pilot of the show that'll hopefully be around a long time. Yeah, I had a blast
Yeah, I'll get that sweet residual money. You will pilot the
There was one other camera manheim just lovely Lindsey. Yeah, everybody everybody was really great, but there was one
Oh, I've got a Galecki and Andrew and you know, everybody was really great and supportive and wonderful and I am appreciative for it
Crumbholtz, of course. I said crumbholtz, but
But there was one other thing regarding this that I thought was funny, that I wanted
to tell you, and now I can't remember.
So that brings a close to Pat's scary personal issues.
And, you know, all words and upwards, we had our first table read Friday, it went great,
and I can't wait for you guys to see the show.
That means you'll also see the show.
Yes.
Last but not least, we've teased a new segment this week, you know, let's save this for
during the monsters because I don't think we're going to be glued to this fucking.
Oh, yeah, we can pop this off.
Let's get started.
We're going to do a new segment every week now where we just kind of discuss like some horror -related
news story or something.
This week we'll be talking about, well, I'll wait, I'll need to tease it.
in the meantime put it in here we go one two three play here we go one two three play
and we're into the monsters today holy shit now this is the theme song they're all dancing
on the couch. John Schuck, yeah who well we'll talk about who he is in a minute I want
to make sure that I don't talk over a very important part of this song because I want
to hear Patch genuine reaction okay all right here it comes it's coming up here hold on
I'm going to be quiet. All right. I'm listening.
Whoa.
They're singing. This is like for a kid's puppet show.
Yeah. Now what you can hear is they start singing.
Patricia Fass Palmer. She was a supervisor on my pilot.
Remember, she was the kind of older lady who kind of ran the production.
Oh, yeah.
I got to ask her about the monsters today.
and let's get into that. Get me back onto that set so I can ask some questions.
Um, for those of you that, because you can't hear what we're hearing, uh, they start
singing lyrics to the monster's theme song, where are the monsters as they're all dancing?
Uh, these jokes are, I mean, it's, you know, it's one of the jokes that you said, why bother
to dust the house? You just have to do it over again in another 50 years. And now, then
then you find out she's dusting the cobwebs off.
So the cobwebs shine.
Is the plot of this,
that Herman Munster Frankenstein is closeted?
Closeted game here?
Is that the plot of the show?
Because this man is clearly gay.
Well, this is, it's funny you mention that
because this guy's one of my favorite episodes
of the Golden Girls where he plays Frankenstein?
Yeah, he plays a,
He plays a politician that they're all like supporting, who's like a really good guy.
And then the newspaper breaks a story that says he fucked Blanche.
And it's not true, but nobody believes Blanche, that's not true.
Yeah.
Because he publicly lies and says that it was her.
And then she's like, this is skirting dangerously close each weekend.
Each week it's a little bit closer to just being a full on Golden Girls episode by episode
podcast.
So we're called the Golden Guys, which probably exists.
Let's be real.
She says to him, she's like, why did you lie?
And he's like, because it's the first time anybody thought I was like a bad guy and
that was good for my votes or whatever.
And then she's like, you better tell the public you're lying and he agrees to.
So then he goes to this press conference, he admits the lie to fucking blanche.
And then he says, I have another secret.
For the first 40 years of my life, my name was, I went by a common housewife, you know,
a Bernadette, a Robert Ducci, or something like that.
Sounds like a typically grounded ep of the Golden Girls.
And then the last joke is Sophia goes,
I told you, I told you, I knew he had a secret,
and Dorothy goes, mom, how could you have known that?
And he goes, look at his nose.
Of course he's Italian.
Freeze frame cut to credits.
Bam, bam, bam, bam.
Whoa, they're feeding a dragon?
Yeah, that's the dragon.
Now the pilot episode, you want to talk about networks?
I can't believe how fake this dragon looks even for sitcom standards. This thing looks like a school play
It looks bad and the dialogue appears to be a school play and the performances appear to be from a school plot the woman
Lily monsters being played by the actress that played
Catwoman in the Batman Adam West movie not the TV show. How could they not get a viral for this part? Joe?
Or did she pass on it? I don't think Elvira would fit in that top if you know what I'm saying
Yeah, she just, they could have gotten her bigger top job.
She just said, oh chicken fingers,
and had actual like chicken toes.
Well, I don't, could Elvira play the part,
well, like play it like that though,
or would she have to be like Elvira?
Well, I think this would have been more successful
if it was married with children with the monsters.
It went, it went three seasons, 66 episodes.
Holy shit.
It's on Ho -Hoo for Christ's sake.
It's in syndication.
Yeah.
Yeah, well, I guess it probably played for kids.
I remember NBC doing like a starting at 6 p .m.
sitcom block on Sundays.
And they would have like eerie Pennsylvania,
which I love, they had, I don't remember it.
You know, life goes on and all that shit.
Sequest, DSV.
The disacquaged HPV.
Was a sea, I sailed one fateful summer folks.
No, I don't know.
I might have HPV.
it would be dormant in me, but it would reveal itself in symptoms with us any sexual partners
that I would have.
Well, you'll know when your wife gets sick.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
I'm kidding.
Can't you joke?
Funny joke, Joe.
Would you say that to her face?
Yes.
Let's call her up.
She's a nurse.
She would get it.
Yeah, you're right.
You're right.
The guy that plays grandpa.
She's also not a nurse.
She's a physician's assistant.
All right.
She's a doctor, can I get this goddamn useless fact about grandpa?
Yeah, but I can't I couldn't let that pass if I hear this. Why didn't you tell him I'm not a nurse?
Not there's anything wrong with being a nurse folks
Now we're gonna get hate me. She's you know she's a physician's assistant. It's a it's between a nurse and a doctor
It's closer to a doctor. Yeah, no, I see patients by herself. I've been to I've been to physicians assistants. Yes
I mean quite frankly. I've been to assistant physicians. Okay, and
and that's a whole other thing.
I have, I remember watching this now
when I see the outside of this house.
Well, that footage of the exterior of the house,
I believe we're just stock, their footage they took
from the 1980s TV movie of the monsters.
Yeah.
That started the original cast.
They just took that and repurposed it for this.
Like you can tell like it's old footage.
Yeah.
The clip they use has credits from the actual opening
of the movie of the monster's movie.
Yeah, starring Fred Gwynet said.
This kid was on, I believe, boy meets world at some point, he was.
The guy that plays grandpa is actually an old Hollywood actor.
Like he was on like, I googled him.
He was on like password and or 10 ,000 dollar pyramid and shit like that.
So he's actually, you know, he's a, he's been around.
This lily lady, I find her very attractive.
I agree.
Even in the weird like vampire -esque costume she's wearing.
I say especially because of the weird vampire was constantly sure sure
The a body rate thing going air. I took her out for dinner. You want to talk about a blood sucker?
The
She had the steak
Oh
The so now the plot of this episode is that Herman is
serving food to the family. He's becoming a cook for some reason. And obviously he's
going to be really bad at it. This is this music. And I mean, this just is a disaster.
Now what makes you think that Herman is coming off as a as a latent gay man? Joe. What?
The performer. He's it's Fred Gwyn and a mask. Not Fred Gwyn. Who am I thinking of? No,
No, who's the guy to play?
The guy Alec Baldwin does.
Tony Bennett?
No.
The guy who wrote the Trump.
Paul Lind.
That's right, folks.
I mixed him up with Fred Gwynn because of the monsters.
I think he's trying to do a variation of Fred Gwynn.
They're all doing sort of impressions of the original game, I guess.
Well, and Fred Gwynn is sort of like, you know, he's very handsy and not like not
in appropriate with women hands. I just mean like he's like, you know, he's always like shaking
his hands around and being, you know, what's that called? What's that feminine? No, that's not what
I was going to say. I was going to say demonstrative. That's not the right term. When you're always
demonstrative. Yes, you're gesturing with your hands. Yeah, he's always gestating. Okay.
So I was trying to say so I mean look the brains the brains not been good late
No, that was hard to watch. What was that? Oh the gestating. Yeah, yeah
So now what is grandpa wearing a metal?
That's the original costume. That's like a Dracula amulet. He also just was doing
He was also just doing a godfather impression. I believe. Yeah, I think so
Pat let's get that poly walnuts hair. Let's uh wait hold on I want to hear this joke
Hold on
There you go there's a joke my wife was the greatest cook of her day anybody whoever tasted her transom any surprise never lived to regret it
These are jokes that I think they literally yanked out of like a spooky jokes for Halloween book
Like a lucky taffy for Halloween special edition, you know this audience is laughing like at gunpoint
They sound scared. This writing staff rated a Spencer's Gifts came out with a script. Oh,
This is what I was going to say. So this show you want to talk about network complicating things unnecessarily with notes.
They
The pilot of this which is not on here. Yeah. I read the synopsis of it online
They go into a sleep chamber that grandpa creates, right? Now keep this in mind
right. This show takes place literally 30 years after the original show, right? Okay.
He sets the timer in the thing for 30 minutes, right? It gets knocked. What do you think
happens? Somebody knocks? No. No. No. Timer gets knocked to forever. Okay. Then some real
estate agent 30 years later exactly comes in and bumps into it and wakes them up. Why? Why
I wouldn't it just be 30 years.
Right there, that was just my first instinct.
Yeah, so there you go.
They would have called me.
They would have had a show on their hands.
Anyway, I was nine, but I could have done it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's get into our new segment, Pat.
And we'll come back to the monsters.
All right.
Because this has got about a how to 11 minutes left,
which is gonna feel like a fucking eternity.
Yeah, this is right.
Our new segment is a, as I said, a news statement.
We're gonna just discuss a story or two about stuff going on in movie news fantasy sci -fi
horror.
And this is the story that jumped out of me that gave me the idea for this segment.
I was reading on movieweb .com, so that's where the story is coming from.
That the premiere of Jeepers Creepers 3 was shut down by the way folks, one of our best
episodes I would say for sure is is Jeepers creepers go back and give that a
lesson I agree uh it was shut down um it's not happening it was canceled
rather because there was so much protesting about Victor Selva the writer
directors passed the convicted pedophile who has been directing steadily for
about thirty years now look often funded by Francis Ford Copeland here's my
thing I obviously don't agree with the fact that he's a pedophile right I don't
to prove. He went to jail, he served his sentence, he has been in therapy since, he has worked
on himself supposedly, has not repeated offended, he has admitted that he had a problem and he
has apologized. So if we're going to be progressive people, which most progressives believe,
criminal activity of any sort comes from some sort of psychological off balance or your
environment putting you into a very unfair situation.
So if we're going to believe in either of those circumstances, which I don't think environment
applies to pedophilia.
So we'll take the psychological route here.
Why can't he go on with his life?
I mean, environment could, I assume.
Well, yeah.
But why can't he, well, for the offender, I mean, well, I guess growing up, yeah.
So I don't know.
Maybe he was molested and maybe he's fucked up.
But why can't he go on with his life at this point?
He paid his, he did his time.
What are you supposed to do?
Like you you're just supposed to be blackballed for the rest of your life because you made a hard mistake
Like if now if the argument is I choose a different word than blackballed first
Well because he is worth for this discussion no because we're talking about pedophilia
But and where we often are on the show
I mean the easy thing for me to say here is that is that Joe was taking a pro pedophilia stance
when he has clearly said that he is not
but
but I don't know.
Well, you know that I'm not, right?
Yes, oh, I know.
Oh, okay.
That's the kind of crime to me where it's like,
if it was in jail forever, I'd be fine with that.
Well, that's, and that's what I was getting at.
But he's not, he's out.
That's a different argument.
He served as time.
If the argument is a pedophile should serve a greater sentence,
okay, then fine, let's discuss that.
Sure.
But if the law says this is what the sentence is,
the guy does it, then he amicably goes into therapy
and tries to fix himself of this issue.
And doesn't offend again, then why like well, he's got to work like I don't understand, you know like and
Nobody's protested his other eight fucking movies he had since then. That's true. I think it's just we're we're in a protest
D .A. It's yeah, it's getting more it's he was he's been a convicted pedophile since powder since everything. Yeah, this happened in like the
80s or something so
So I don't know folks, you know if you're gonna do this then you know
Where's everybody protesting Rolling Stone's concerts because Mick Jagger fucked Mackenzie Phillips when she was like 16 and
John Mackenzie or whatever her dad's name is or John Phillips whatever to fuck was banging
I mean, there's a story. It's in the books. It's in like the
Autobiography's it was banging on the door saying can you not fuck my daughter please and Mick wouldn't open the door
It's like nobody's protesting that nobody's protesting the slew of fucking
half -naked, 16 - and 17 -year -old girls that they parade around on MTV, the music awards
every year, not every year, but many years, you know, it's like, come on, guys, like
either we're doing this or not. It's either, you know, and I just think that people pick
very easy targets. And again, I'm not defending what he did. I'm defending the fact that he served
his time, he has tried to fix himself, he has not done it again, and he's trying to move
on with his life. And I just think it sucks that people seem to pick out the easiest target
and go after it. Nobody gives a fuck about Jeepers Creepers 3. Nobody's going to get any backlash
from the big powers that be in Hollywood or the entertainment industry for shitting on Victor
Salva. You might get some backlash from going after a Mick Jagger for somebody like that.
And I'm not calling Mick Jagger a pedophile. I also understand it was a different day and age.
Okay, like not saying it was right, but it was a different time sure so and you know
It's a slippery slope here, too, but there is to me a difference between
Whatever this kid was seven
And 16
Neither is ideal neither is good neither is a provable
But yeah, it says he was I don't know how old the kid was a 1980 was searched with 11 counts of sexual abuse
found guilty of four of the lesser counts. Maybe that's what the anger is about, that he
should have been convicted on all counts. So, okay, that would be a different argument.
I think they didn't want to bring a ped - Well, no, they let him shoot there. I remember
that was an issue, too. They weren't going to let him use his locations that he had booked.
Well, here's my question. Is this the atrical release or what they're going to be doing?
Yeah, no, limited theatrical release. Okay. And folks, trust me, if anybody doesn't want
I see Jeepers, Creepers, three hit theaters.
It's me.
I think the franchise is a fucking travesty.
I hate it.
Right.
I'm the fan of the franchise.
But where do you draw the line with that, you know, like that's my bigger question.
Where do you draw the line?
Do you do it?
Do you then boycott any actor that's ever been in a Victor Salva movie because they worked
with a convicted pedophile?
Do you boycott the studios for funding it?
Do you boycott the investor?
Do you boycott the producer?
You know, where do you draw the line, you know, like, I'm not saying that as a challenge.
I'm really asking.
I was feeling a lot of people think quite rightly, there are probably probably in this apartment complex
10 aspiring great film directors
Why continuously award a pedophile?
That's a fair point a lot of people who would love the opportunity to direct a movie and this guy's I guess got a sense of style
But it's not like he's
Roman Polansky folks. That's a fair point who also that's a fair point
But I feel like that's not who's protesting this right now. I don't think like I don't think young directors. Yeah, our pros go out there going
I was up for Jeepers creepers three. No, they're not they're not I have a feeling it's it's it's a bunch of churchy types. Yeah, for sure
Although you don't have to be churchy to oppose pedophilia folks. No, but it seems to be the only reason I say churchy types
is because it always well actually hey hey folks last night check the church was pretty
cool with it.
Yeah.
Oh.
Uh, it's usually churchy people protesting movies, right, and I'm basically that entirely
on the people that were screaming at me when I went into the theater to see the Da Vinci
code, which I was able to get right in on on a Friday, opening Friday to see because people
are so angry.
Terrible movie.
I like Da Vinci code.
I thought the second one was okay the third one is terrible never saw the third of the second one was put me into a coma
Now back to them. Oh God back to the monsters
Wacking now they closed her to be a duck. No, she's having an anxiety attack and she cracks when she has an anxiety tag
Oh my god
This woman is not funny enough to pull this pedal off. No, I'm sorry. That's not what it is. I remember now the plot
But the side effect, if you forget an ingredient in the vamp
in the Transylvania surprise that he made,
if you forget one ingredient, it turns a person into a duck.
That's the plot.
So she ate it and she loved it.
Now she's turning into a duck.
Just by quacking, just by remaining to be an attractive woman
who's just going, quacking, quacking.
Like every third sentence she goes, quacking.
Well, yeah, yeah, he's also doing Paul Lindt.
Well, he's really doing a Paul Lindt thing,
but he's also kind of doing grandpa from the original show.
Now, here's what I don't get about this show.
Now, we're going to Adam's family or a monster's guy.
I was monsters.
Really? I think the Adam's family then and now is great.
Both those movies are hilarious.
I like the movies.
Great movies.
Like you could have done it any better, I don't think.
I just, I got, I got such a soft spot for Fred Gwynn.
You're not going to.
Sure.
Well, I love my cousin Vinnie, as, as you know,
we got the tag coming back.
This is a one last quick scene that,
that's sick on people call a tag.
Let's see what the joke is here.
Okay.
They're playing chess.
Herman's mad.
I got Lily out this dialogue is death.
Okay, here's the joke. Lily says, why do you, she goes, oh my God. Lily goes, why do you want to play
Chuck's with me? I've, I've won a hundred six, get jokes, games in a row. And then Herman goes 105. And then that gets a
laugh. That's a joke. He just got a laugh sitting down on the couch because it put some smoke up. I can't tell if
there's a real audience in the show. Well, there's not. Are these people are held there against their will? I was
positive in the first season there wasn't when I got into the second season I was like I think
there's a real audience there's real organic cheers for things and like I mean if it's not a real
audience God bless the sound designer he deserves an Oscar right he should be doing like you know but
no I know but I'm saying what I was getting at is like he should be the guy they get for like the
Revenant. Okay, you know, like that's how that's how good it sounded right
Long tag. Oh
Now Frank signs about the fucker
Yeah, they just did a dream date joke as she brought him up to the bedroom. That's a disturbing
I don't want to think about these two banging around the uh, now here's what kind of hog you think Frankenstein's sport and big cock
I'd imagine it's pretty ample
But I think I'm just going off of young Frankenstein where the joke was that Frankenstein had a huge cock
I think everybody would just assume he's got a big fat cock.
Yeah, is it green?
I would hope so.
Now I'm going to throw you for a loop here.
I feel like another giant green guy has a very small cock and I'm talking about Shrek.
Now why do you think it's small?
I think Shrek does not strike me as a guy with a big dick is all I can say.
I think he looks like he's got a hog.
All right, he's dating that hot princess.
How else does he keep her around?
Fiona just looks like him.
She didn't at first, she changes.
She just loves it like him, that's right.
Now here's my question.
And this is the last thing I'm gonna say about the monsters today.
All right, unless you have anything on it.
Unless we go hit that cheese store.
Why do normal people see them?
How are the monsters?
Why is it like so?
The show?
No.
That beautiful block down there in the corner
of the case. Well, no, this, this is how I would play. You go into the cheester, you go,
how are the monsters? And he goes, that, that, that, that, that cheese is quite tasty this
year. And you go cheese. And that's the cold open to my new monsters reboot. Yeah. And then
it goes to the monsters. Somebody get it to set fires. The executives are like, why are we
starting in a cheese store? Then that's actually a valid note. That's a valid note. You don't
start a monster's reboot in the cheese store.
Not for a joke.
No, that joke might be worth it.
No, I think there's a lot of opportunity.
That joke might be worthy of doing it.
You could have grandpa go,
Herman, that cheese is greener than you are.
I think you got a lot of ways to go in a cheese store.
Here's my question.
Why do some people see the monsters like in the show,
like normal people see them and freak out,
And then other people see them and just like don't even notice that they look crazy
It's a problem with all these shows that you get into a logic hole that you either take it or you don't
I think you're a guy who takes it. I tend to let it go. It's like when I'm watching
Liar liar
You know whatever it was at the beginning a genie curse or something
Whatever it is whatever stupid shit you have to do to justify the comedy just get there quick
There's that movie where Jason Bayman and Ryan Reynolds both pee in the same fountain
and swap bodies.
It's a terrible movie, but at least the movie starts with I'm like peeing in a fountain.
You know, like -
But I don't think they're -
Give me their quick.
You're not answering my question.
What was your question?
What I'm saying is -
I don't know what the hell that was a response to.
That had nothing to do with what I was saying.
I'm saying in the show, over the course of the Monster's TV shows, sometimes normal people
see them and they just treat them like normal people and then other times normal people see them and
they're like horrified. All right, well, I was branching off into kind of other things. I guess
yes. Yeah, there's no, there's no consistency. So I don't understand. I see what you're saying.
I just mean like the central gimmick of a ship, but there is no consistency. I see what you're saying.
That's all. Yeah, I got what you're saying. I think we both get what each other saying because we're
We're great at communicating.
Folks, that's our monster's episode.
And I don't want that.
That's not against revisiting a few more of these
over the course of this show.
I think that'll probably be it for me on the monsters.
But we'll be back.
Also, folks, we told you we'd be every other week.
We've been every week.
We've been killing it.
We've been killing ourselves for you.
Yes, don't forget that.
Yeah, don't forget that.
Show a little appreciation.
Happy to be back with you again this week. Thank you to everybody that was in San Francisco for the shows last weekend
I had a great time. Thank you for being there. I will be in Washington, D .C. at the D .C. Draft House
in September and then at the end of the month Kurt Branneler and I will be in Vegas for scoops fest to do emotional hangs live and let us know if you want to live
We'll see you in hell
Where you're at and we'll see if we can put it together
I am on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh, and if you want to come to a
taping of by the book, it's in Burbank at Warner Brothers. Check online, get
tickets. Those tapings are starting up very soon. Folks, that's all I got. I
guess we'll see you next time, and we'll see you in hell.