Summer is here and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer or check out
our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and the Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spin on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Bet MGM game sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM dot com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and
West Virginia only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal throwable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
Gamling problem called 1 -800 -Gambleer.
Comcast is committed to bringing access to the internet to all Americans, including rural
communities across the country, like Sussex County, Delaware.
We were being left behind.
Everybody around us seemed to have internet, but we did not.
High -speed internet is one of those good things that we needed to help us move our farming,
our small businesses, our recreation forward.
Learn more about how we're bringing our next generation network to more people across the
country.
at comcastcorporation .com slash investment in America.
Welcome to We'll See You In Hell.
Hopefully your favorite podcast about horror movie sci -fi films and fantasy pictures.
You know what we do here?
We talk about them.
We commentate on them.
We review them.
This week we're going to be getting into some 1922 by Mr. Stephen S. King.
And I don't know if that's his middle initial, but God damn it. It should be out of
Anyway, it's a review week 1922, and I'd like my friend Pat to get us started here
You mean you'd like me to get on with the show and also on
Wow
Wow, that sounded like rat, the band.
Yeah, it was kind of like an old witch.
I thought it was hair metal.
It sounded very stand up and shout to me.
Sure.
Shout out to the devil.
Uh, I think stand up and shout was a more accurate thing,
but sure.
I don't know, stand up and shout.
Stand up and shout is, you know,
it's probably quite right or somebody like.
Oh, okay.
Maybe it's by DO.
All right.
Anyway, who cares?
How do you get on other jobs?
I only know the hits.
It's good to see you.
How you doing? It's good to see you, Joe. I'm excited to talk about such a fun film as 1922.
How to pick me up. No. No. I was in... I would say now I met like a 1 .2 in terms of mood.
Last night I was in like a 0 .4 and I sit down and I'm gonna like catch up on my curb and my shows and I'm like,
No, I got to watch a man murder his wife and then be tormented by visions of rats.
But we'll get to that later dark, dark, dark stuff.
You're 1 .2 on a scale of what?
I mean, if you're it's a scale of 1 to 2, that's great.
10.
Oh, I've been, I've been bottoming out mood wise.
You know, it is what it is.
It's just an awful time.
there's no there's nowhere to look for a reprieve for a breather just a suffocating
it's a suffocating twirling typhoon of shit everybody is yelling nobody's
listening no it's getting very confusing yeah I don't know what to do no you
know I just I don't know what to do no there is there is no nuanced discussion
with anything anymore.
No.
It's just throw the bodies on the pile and burn them.
And if you're not gonna burn them with us,
then we'll burn you too.
Yeah.
So, you know, I'm sure we have some listeners in Alabama.
Are you voting for the pedophile?
Is that the side of history you wanna be on?
Is he now, is he definitely a pedophile or just accused?
I mean, there's a lot.
I'm not playing devil's ad because I'm just a lot of proof. There's a lot of proof and I think more all the time
They got a pale and shovel with more all the time seeming in it. Yeah, I did nothing on that
I thought that was funny. You said there's a lot of proof
I said they found a pale and shovel with some seam in it. Yes, exactly. Oh, I forgot folks were coming to you live
From the hog house
People did like they did you have to make pig noises just go
Dude, the Tim Allen.
I feel like it slides us into like a man show territory.
But that's the joke of it.
We're making fun of that.
I can't even do that ironically anymore.
All right, we need a good...
We have one.
We have several.
No, we need a good name for the studio.
What do we call this place?
The lion's den.
Coming to you live from the lion's den.
Lion's den, I like.
I think, yeah!
There you go.
I make a jaguar noise. Yeah, there you go. No, I said line and I'll say I did say line and then you'll say Joe
Nothing's ever good enough that I do and then I'll slap you in the face like I always do when you mouth off to me like that
Well, when you say all right like that it sounds like I really slap you in the face. I like it
He does me know why I do it
But it reminds me of the piece of shit that I am and that you're in charge.
Pat does like it and he'll say things like, tell me I'm a bad boy, you know, make me
dirty.
Yeah, I try to be good daddy, he says, things like that, it's real sick shit, pacifier in my
ass.
Oh, oh, yeah, well, you know, look, we can, we can traipse on over to Pat's movie corner
right away.
Look, it's a rough time, it's a real noisy world right now.
I can tell that neither of us want to really talk about any of it.
I did the great Craig Ferguson's radio show again the other day and he was like, we're just,
we're just having, let's just have fun, man.
Like it's I think everybody's a little
News out. Yeah except for the newsies who are they're shooting a sequel
I heard with the original cast with bail
I'm joking
But I do believe Max Casela is back and I actually they're calling it two Z's the number two and then Z's you're full of them tonight
That was remember earlier when you said oh wait, maybe they didn't play the commercial yet
There's a real good punny throws out on the toothbrush commercial today look
That's what I do, folks.
Folks, I can take you down to Pat's movie corner.
Because I get a long thing I want to talk about in this.
All right, great.
I watched a few more episodes of Mind Hunter,
which I am thoroughly enjoying, taking my time with it.
I watched...
The film at hand, 1922, that might actually be it.
Now I was watching Milff Hunter,
is that in any relation to Mind Hunter?
Is Milff Hunter in the van?
I've seen several, that's bang bros.
That's bang bros.
I gotta say, they make it very convincing.
They wear, they find in the Milffs.
They just, they're hired, they're porn ladies.
They're like, ladies that do porn.
And they wear, they pretend they find them.
They pretend that they just are driving on the street like,
oh, that goes a hot lady.
Yeah.
And they pretend like they're just like,
it's all happening in real time.
That would work, I'm sure.
But it's very, very convincing.
Yeah.
Milf Hunter is, I don't even know if he's still around,
but Milf Hunter was a guy that used to only have sex with Milf's.
Was he kind of a,
I can't almost Danny Bond a douchey look to him.
He was sort of short.
Now I got it.
Yes.
Yeah.
I mean I don't really know much about the guy, I don't know what he's up to these days.
And I've never seen pornography so I don't know what you're talking about.
Well pornography is interesting, because the people they'll have sex on camera,
but they'll show it, they'll show the insertion.
Okay.
That sounds like something I'd be interested in.
Yeah, you'll see the penis going into the, I call it the potato because I don't like to be dirty.
Potato is so much dirtier than what it actually is called.
You see the pepper going into the potato and and then sometimes the cheese comes out
Milton burl radio hour
The only the only other thing that I would have watched would have been
Actually David Crumholz told me about this show that he made two years ago for IFC
called Gigi does it where he portrays a like 70 -year -old Jewish lady in heavy
prosthetics kind of a jimmy glic type thing. I've seen stills from it folks I
watched four episodes the other night was laughing my ass off it's worth a
season pass 20 bucks really very very funny he's a funny man it got horrific
ratings and was immediately canceled I want to see it but it's a very funny show
Gigi does it yeah, and is it like he goes in public with this or a descriptive thing?
It's a mix. It's it's largely scripted with some I mean it's mostly it's all improv
But then there's also some Borat type like he goes to to do like sketch a naked man class
And that's all clearly
What is the voice that Gigi does?
It's very like oh well you know I'll tell you something it's you know
That's an old Jewish line.
Yeah.
You know, the stereotype.
It's, yeah, that's what you're gonna say.
It's pretty scary.
You're racist.
It's the pretty, yeah.
It's stereotypical.
But I think that David Cromholz is Jewish.
So it's okay.
I think he might be.
Yeah, there's a chance.
Folks, I've talked about it every week
on Pat's movie corner.
I'm not gonna stop here.
Even deeper into perfect strangers than I've been.
Wow.
So you're, they're all living together, I assume.
No, no, because I had to agree to go back to season five, but I'm just taking it all in.
And I realize some of you out there might be too young to even know what perfect strangers
is.
So if you missed it, perfect strangers was a sitcom from the late 80s, early 90s, about
a man named Balkybark Takamus from an island called Mipos. Balky is a man with, they never
address it, but he's apparently got some sort of regressive mental disorder. He's got the brain
of about an eight year old. And he's also, there's just something wrong with him. And then he comes
and moves in with this cousin Larry, who is the biggest piece of shit that ever lived.
That's extreme. And then just a divisive prick. So then the whole show is just
Larry taking just episode after episode of him manipulating this simple cousin of his.
And like literally doing things where he'll be like,
Like, today I was watching one and he needs to get a,
he wants to get a picture.
They gotta, he's gotta go interview this morning TV show guy.
Yeah.
This guy does a kid's morning show.
Wait, he plays a dog.
Okay.
Cause the character.
Like, man's beloved by children everywhere whatever.
What is Larry like a beat reporter?
I don't even remember.
Yeah, he started, well they started out working
in the antique store and then they get the job
in like the mail room and Larry starts to move up.
How many antiques break when they work on that antique store?
Well, hundreds.
Pat, in episode one,
Balky went left to run the antique store,
sells a man what he thinks is a set of speakers for $40.
And the boss is the boss who's a real skin -flint.
He's real excited because they really ripped the guy off.
Then he realizes that Balky didn't sound the speakers.
He sold him a speaker, the speakers plus the receiver,
plus the C, the record player,
like all that was attached.
Again, Balky's got some mental condition
where he doesn't understand anything.
So we don't start the pilot with him coming over from Meepo's.
Yeah, yeah, but then later, by the end of the pilot,
they're working on an antique shop.
Balky gets hired at the very end,
but Larry leaves him there to watch the store
because Larry's gonna go do something selfish.
Anyway, they play the stereo that Balky had hooked up,
and it's so loud it shatters everything in the store.
So then he hires Balky and he's like,
now you're gonna work for free to pay me back for all this stuff
you busted.
It's one of those things.
Right.
That only happens in movies.
Yeah, well, we're sitcoms.
You lost dishes.
So anyway, they gotta go get the interview with the dog man.
today for the kids. Larry's pissed. It's not a big story. He wants the big story.
This is a trivial story. Tells the guy, I'll see in the dressing room, I want to
take a picture and do the interview. The guy goes, you can't take my picture once
I'm out of my costume. That's my rule. No pictures out of the costume. You got to
promise me. Larry's like, no problem. Guy walks away immediately, he goes, gotta get
that picture, then proceeds to go to Balky and says, you know, Balky, it's a shame.
And this, this happens almost every other episode where he does something this underhanded,
to Balky, he'll be like, you know, Balky, it's a shame.
He just won't take a picture with a reporter.
If only we had somebody here who loved him, that could take his picture, and then Balky
with his eight -year -old brain was like,
oh, cousin, I want to take the picture, you know.
Which by the way, this is an old trick done by TV.
TV actress, these network people and everything.
It's like they're so progressive and open -minded
and everything like that, they're not.
This is all they do is they won't say anything racist
about an existing race, but what they'll do is they'll go,
we're gonna invent a fake place.
And then we'll just shit all over that, like, you know,
And just pretend it's like instead of saying the guy's like Russian or whatever, you know, so anyway
That's that's what they do and he tricks tricks Balky into taking the guy's picture the guy's right life gets ruined
You find out he has a prison record for writing bad checks. Okay gets fired
It's this is every episode Larry ruins everything in every episode out of just sheer
Just lustful greed. Well, you know the networks now are obsessive about every single character being
likable. And then even now that, you know, like I'm going to this testing, they want the
unlikeable characters to be likable. And if you think back to even this, this is like
a TGIF show we're talking about. Yeah. Larry Appleton was a monster. Yeah. I always preferred
Larry to balcony. I love Larry. He's a great character, but he, he is a spineless, lying,
cheating asshole. Yeah. And that's a TGIF shell. Like people will roll with it
because people are at their core shit. Spineless shit. Yeah. Spineless piles of
shit. And that really is the point of perfect strangers. Everybody's a
Spineless pile of shit. Yeah. Unless you're from a country that is so dumb you don't
know any better. And even then you're just going to be manipulated. And they'll
by one of the spineless pieces of shit.
Yeah, and by the way, the ongoing thing is Larry continually believes in Larry because
he's so naive he thinks Larry's gonna change.
Larry never changes.
At the end of every episode he goes, I don't know why I do this.
I'm so sorry.
I lose control.
And then the next episode he does it again.
He does it again.
But it's a funny show.
I really enjoy it.
All right.
Anyway, I watched that and I watched how deep bar you've watched a hundred episodes.
It's probably I'm I'm deep into season five. I was a hundred episodes
No, is it 22 a year 24 a year? Probably so
Well, because you're an idea where my life is at
folks
I also watched X X very good a horror anthology
The old ladies one. Yes, it's an all it's not an all female cast, but the the main character in each story is a female
And I think that each segment was written and directed by a different female.
Same Vincent to one of those?
Musical artist.
She was supposed to, but she bailed out or something.
All right.
I like her.
Yeah.
I like her too.
But you know what, St. Vincent?
Fuck off.
Whoa.
Look.
I like her too.
But in a business where women are struggling, women who are committed to their lives, this are
struggling to get a slot directing one 15 -minute story and a fucking anthology.
How about you go do something else, St. Vincent?
It's like when John Mayer would come down to the comedy clubs and do sets, it's like I'm sorry. I'm starving to death. Can I have the set?
Did I can I didn't tell you my John Mayer story what he's always been very nice to me, but I you know, I'm just
John Mayer so I
I'm gonna tell a story about a tweet folks always the most riveting of stories
Three years ago or something I tweet this I think I was high when I didn't know I don't remember coming up with it
But it was the tweet is people often ask me, Patrick, I don't like you, which to me is like funny and then you think about it for a minute and you're like, that's pretty clever and I know that it's kind of clever and good, but I don't think it's like the best of the best, but it lit a real fire under America.
It's at about 10 ,000 faves.
It's one of my most successful tweets.
Okay, so at some point when they said you could do your pin tweet
I'm like all right. That's the one people always like write to me and they like hey
Can I use this tweet in this article or whatever? I'll throw up this tweet. I pin that as my best tweet
so I
Actually, I do know it Pat Noswald retweeted. It got a lot of heat that way. Yeah, so
John Mayer about a
Month ago tops follows me
And when he does, so he likes the tweet, people often ask me, Patrick, I don't like you.
So I'm like, all right, I'm no fan of the man's music, but you know, whatever, I like
him enough.
I'm like, that's cool.
I follow him back, and he's pretty funny on Twitter.
Finally, one day I wake up, and I've got a direct message from John Mayer, very weird.
I'm assuming he's wanting me to come over and fuck him.
right but it says hey think we had a case of parallel thinking this week so I'm
thinking he's gonna accuse me of stealing a tweet of his like okay reading this
he goes uh but uh it seems uh I accidentally had the same thought as yours it's
this such and such a tweet what's the protocol here I go look at it and John
mayor has tweeted, people often ask me, John, you're not funny. It was basically that.
It was the exact same tweet. And he did the thing where he changed one word. And he liked
this tweet of mine not a month ago. And then was like, I think we accidentally had the
same thought my tweet was three years ago he followed me the same day he liked it
and then and then tweet the same thing so look folks don't please don't tweet ad
John mayor seems pretty clear I don't even know if he stole it but at least it
was in the back of his mind and he accidentally tweeted it so I'm like actually
I wrote him back and I said well I'd start by lawyering the fuck up John mayor right
and I gotta say this I'm surprised that's the tweet he stole from you yeah and
not when you tweeted Katie Perry been there, done that and not impressed. Yeah. I did.
I can't believe he didn't steal that word. I agree. I agree. Um, married to now.
Nobody. He just fucks along. He's not a player. He just, he likes to crush a lot.
Well, I had a John Mayer tweet that I was worried he had seen. I thought it was worried. That's
it was, uh, it was when I lived in my apartment and I had no air conditioning. It was my apartment
and it's so hot today, John Mayer just lazily figured it while yawning, but anyway, folks,
um, golden, anyway, he caught, and that's really a compliment to him that he gets a lot
of hot ladies, but the, the message comes and I'm like, lawyer up and I'm like, no, man,
don't worry about it.
But even a year ago, I would have been when I gave a shit, I'd be like, well, I would
I hope you'd retweet me or turn your 12 million followers
onto my account or something.
But the fact that he doesn't -
He knows what the goddamn fucking protocol is.
The protocol, John, is delete your tweet and retweet pets
or don't retweet pets, but delete your tweet.
I don't even need him to delete it.
I would have been thrilled with a,
hey, I think there was some parallel thinking with this guy.
He had the tweet three years before me.
At least then you get the attention.
But I'm just like -
Just like any of this?
It made me realize how little I care
about the shit anymore.
But I was just kind of like, to me, it was sad
that John Mayer felt he had to do this, you know?
And I believe that it was an accident.
I don't think that's for a second that he stole it.
But he was what I think.
I think the man is on such a pedestal.
Yeah.
He's got that Robin Williams thing
where he just like takes shit from people.
And you know, and then like, you know,
and this maybe this is the only case of it.
But my point is, and then like, he's like,
oh, sorry, he did it again, move here.
And it's like, yeah, dude, how about you just kind of
maybe take responsibility for it.
Yeah, I mean, in my mind, it was like,
if John Mayer said, I just stole this tweet from this guy,
he was, he's gonna lose zero of his 24 million followers.
So what's it gonna hurt you to not even say that?
Just delete the goddamn tweet.
To just toss me a damn bone.
That's all I'm saying.
Just delete the tweet.
Delete the tweet.
You're going a different way because I don't,
you know how many faves he had on this tweet?
Like 50 ,000?
Yeah.
in a day you know they say the cream rises to the top and by that folks I mean
the rotten milk cream and bastards rise a great song by an underrated band
called Harvey Danger they're more than just flagpole sit -off you know I got
first Harvey Danger album mainly because heep show used the big single from it as
their theme song. They had three great albums. I don't like the ones where they
start getting into all the piano. It gets a little bend -folds -y on that third
record. The third one's a little popier, sure. I don't mind the poppy. I don't
like that it's so piano driven. I like when it's like that really raw like
guitar. They had that song authenticity, which was on the trailer for disturbing
behavior. Remember that movie? Katie Holmes. It was a horror entry. Katie Holmes. Maybe
Josh Hart not disturbing behavior. What was it about? I think it was a Williamson or was it about?
I don't fucking remember. But I had the song Authenticity which is a great song.
Well Pat, back to double X or XX whatever it's called however you say it check it out. It's a great
anthology, it's worth seeing. I like the first story and the third story best, but it's a good one.
It's a goodie. Okay. So nice work to everybody on that one. I also saw Sauer. Oh, from my
uh...
cult cinema cult collection the Australian DVD company
i watched
uh...
oh wait did i talk about this last week
yeah you talked about it nevermind all right well that's it
let's get into some joe scary stuff do you have a fuck no it's okay
we've had to get these pretty close together because we're doing some
traveling coming up
uh... i got one quick thing
Some of you may know I am an old retro video game collector and I've quite a bit of fun if you have yourself a super Nintendo
System the SNES as it's called if you have yourself one of those. I'd like to highly recommend you a game called
Robocop versus the Terminator. It is a Mesh up versus a
Mesh up of these franchises and the plot line is how cool is this?
John Connor in the future
says, SkyNet was basically created or at least further perpetuated into the Armageddon
state that it caused by a man robot cyborg that goes by the name of a Robocop.
So he sent in some terminators back to destroy Robocop to fix the world and you start out
is RoboCop. That's as far as I've gotten. I'm sure or I'm assuming somewhere along the line,
RoboCop is going to be like, I'm not guilty, creep. He didn't do it and then he helps the terminators
or maybe he doesn't. Maybe that doesn't happen, but it's fucking fun, man. It's really fun and every
time you shoot somebody, side -scroll 2D platformer, action platformer, every time you shoot somebody,
they burst into flames and disappears. That never gets old. Music's great, graphics are great,
sound effects are great. It's just a real dream for anybody that enjoys a nice sci -fi,
darkly edged video game. Go and check that out, folks.
books. Great. Let's do this movie. Now, I've been playing
Oh, Predator versus Kevin McAllister from home alone. Yeah, I
know who Kevin McAllister is. And you think the Predator would
have the advantage, but I'll tell you what the Predator's not
expecting traps. Well, more each each more fiendishly clever
than the last. He's not expecting traps because I'll tell you, the
end of the first Predator film is very homologous. It is. It's
There's a lot of booby traps going off.
A lot of things involving big heavy things swinging down
and hitting in the fittings.
That's what Apocalypse is too, home alone at by the end.
Apocalypse is booby traps?
There's a lot of booby traps and quantum of solace
has a lot of booby traps as well.
Well that makes sense, it's bond.
Bond's not a big traps thing.
That makes sense to me.
You know I always wanted to set up a booby trap.
I never got to do that.
Anytime I do something like put a bucket of confetti
over the door to like fall on my dad,
like he'd pushed he'd pushed the door open angry from work the bucket would
fall and hit him on the head and he would be so furious and then beyond the
initial screaming he would be talking about it for like hours to come I never
got hit all right I you know what there were times I would have preferred a hit
But folks, we weren't a big prankhouse is what I'm getting at.
Uh, yeah, I pulled one prank on my mom once and got in a lot of trouble.
I put her ran rap over the toilet seat.
That people don't like that.
And I was at my friend, Billy Morgan, he was his house.
He was my best pal growing up.
And we were having the time of our lives and phone rang and his dad said,
that Joe, it's your mom and I got on the phone and wow.
She was screaming at me.
In a way that I could only imagine was caused by her having
to take a massive shit and then seeing plastic,
or maybe you shitting on the plastic,
I don't know.
Well probably the plastic.
But she was really mad.
I was immediately grounded and brought home,
even though it was April Fool's Day.
What does that prank do for you?
This is why I don't get about pranks.
You weren't even going to be home to hear the scream makes a mess makes a mess of your
mother's ass. That's what you want. That's what you need. I didn't see it that way. I
saw it as you pee and then the pee rolls off the sides. But there's also shit. Well, maybe
she wasn't shitting. I don't know. I was eight. I didn't mean I didn't think it through
all the way. I'm sorry. I don't know. I guess it just never seemed that fun to me to torture
my mom. Well, you know who else didn't think it was fun? The judge. I did three hard
years because of that prank. No. No, I mean, I don't know. Like it's a funny prank to me.
You put saran wrap down. You put so many peas on it and it all goes everywhere. Yeah.
Crumbs in the beds are good. What? Vaseline on the phones a good one. Why? Crumbs in the bed.
Because when you lay on it, there's crumbs on your sheets and you can't get them out. It's really annoying.
What why is that fun for anyone?
I covered the phone in Vasily, and then called the room, and my rooming answer didn't
you just heard, you heard the phobic cover, you just heard him go, motherfucker, and then
the phone dropped.
That was very funny.
All right, at least you got something out of it.
Yeah, that was very funny.
I like pranks.
I like shit pranks the best.
What's going to be the worst type of pranks?
What are your other ones?
I do weigh more with my own shit if I could get away with it, but in this in this climb in it's not safe to do shit
Yeah, well this climate has some pros
It means you're not throwing a turd at me as I walk in
Like a damn chimp
When I was a kid I would
But it's very funny to me, when I was a kid I'd go in the bathroom, take a shit, wipe
myself and come out with, wow, I can't get it out with soiled toilet paper and chase
my friend around the house with it, it's disgusting, it's disgusting.
I was a little shamed of yourself a few things brought me that level of to if I could do it now
I'd do it man. It makes me laugh had you caught him would you have wiped it on him? No, it was just fun to watch
I kind of it was one of the only times like I got serial killer behavior
Like you would grow up to be a serial killer. I was just gonna say it's one of the only times I got like how leather face must have felt
Yeah, chasing the people around
Yeah, you just see you just saw fear in the in the in the boys eyes
As they chased it as you should, but I never went to wipe it on him. I wouldn't have done that. That's nuts. That's sick. That's crazy
Yeah, anyway, I hope our listeners enjoyed that whole segment. I do too
Joe let's let's kick it over
Let's top in a time machine and take it back to 19 -22. I try to do
I'm starring Tommy Jane the Punisher who I've liked in one movie bookie nights.
He barely opens his mouth in this picture to speak.
Joe's left the mic.
It's all me now.
But the plot of 1922 is basically Thomas Jane wants to and this book is in which of Stephen
king's the short story. It's in night. I don't think it's a nightmare. I've read it. I know,
I've read it. It's in novella. I know that. And it's one of the more. I think it's in different
seasons. I thought it was in one of the more recent books. Maybe it is. I don't know unless he has
a couple about like a I think yeah, I think this was in the new one. But basically he wants her land,
he wants her money and he decides he has to enlist his son to help him in killing her.
well because she wants to leave the farm life behind right he says at the top
of the movie in 1922 a man has two things his son and his land yes and then
you realize that he's kind of a cuckold man because the land is not his like
he's got all this pride and a man must own his land and everything but then you
realize oh he doesn't even own the land right it was his wife's father's land and
And then she inherited it and then he married her because clearly he wasn't hitting that
achievement button as hard as he wanted to.
So the wife is saying, I want to move to the city and when I'm selling the farm, that's
all there is to it.
You can have half the money.
Which seems like a good god damn deal to me.
I don't know why he's so attached to this fucking land.
No clue.
The sun was in 1922, Joe.
All the man had.
Yeah, the sun wants to stay with the dad, but but the mom's like I'm gonna take our son and there's nothing you can do about it
And then he makes a plot to kill her now the interesting twist or not twist really, but an interesting development is when he decides to kill her
You you think
This is horrible obviously. Yeah Jesus Christ
They do an interesting thing where after he decides he's gonna kill her and convinces the kid
They go a good 15 -20 more minutes before it happens, and you see the wife acting
horrifically to them. Not that that justifies her being killed, but it's just an interesting way to portray it because they kind of
They kind of pulling in a couple different directions
But they end up killing her and it's a it's a very brutal scene. It's yeah, it's it's it's it's I mean this movie
like from a gruesome standpoint made Gerald's game look like a fucking like
Willy Wonka or something oh I disagree oh this was really gruesome I
thought I wasn't that bugged by anything but it's from full dark no stars
which I read I at least read this story it's like the first story in the book
actually 22 what's the story book called full dark no stars it's a short story
collection from 2010.
Oh, okay.
But there's a lot of rap material, much like Graveyard Shift,
which I've never seen.
I like the movie Graveyard Shift.
I like the story a lot, too.
The movie's not great, but it's fun to watch.
Okay.
I like this.
It had a good tone to it, a good vibe to it.
It was kind of like very dark and slow and depressing.
I was loving the music.
Look, actually looked up who did it, which I never do.
Mike Patton the faith no more yes who you saw with me at the will turn I did Mike Patton does a lot of
Score he did the place beyond the pines great moving
He's done a lot of scores. He's he's great. Yeah, he did a really nice job with this one
He did a really really nice job. Yeah, it was like his plans a saw or something like it was a lot of that
Like sort of Hans Zimmerman like building Zimmer. It's just Zimmer
It was like a lot of that crescendoing like single note that keeps building and growing
like that.
You know where you're just like, oh my god, you want to rip your hair out.
Yeah.
I dug it.
Do you like the picture?
I thought it was terrific.
Yeah.
I thought it was one of the better adept, Stephen King adaptations ever.
It got, of course, slammed.
And people said it was terrible and it's too dark and this and that but I thought the performances were tremendous
I thought the the mom was
Really fucking good. Yeah, she was great. That's seen where she's like drunk and she's basically calling her kid like a pussy because he won't have sex with the
girl that he likes like right that was very she she was great that scene
The guy that plays the neighbor that looks like he has silver eyes
he was in the walking tall remake,
played the bad guy in the walking tall remake.
I was like to see that guy and stuff.
Enjoy Thomas Jane thoroughly.
Yes.
Really dug like that, no open in the mouth thing.
Like I was like, how's he doing that man?
It was weird, but it was almost like a ventriloquist.
Yeah, the kid was great.
Yeah, excuse me.
Especially when the kid, like when she really dresses them down
the kid looks really angry there for men. That was a particularly effective shot.
And you know, it's a simple story. It's just a man. It's very Gerald's game in a way
in the sense that it doesn't take place in a million settings. There are a ton of characters
and it is really a story about being haunted by your past in the decisions you've made
and having visions that are clearly not happening. But those visions are quite creepy
and terrifying and I loved it. I thought the movie was great. I really, really thought it was
well done. And I hope that between that and Gerald's game and well look the success of it is
going to we're going to get them all again. All the ones we've already gotten. We're going to get
them again. We're getting pets, I'm a Terry again. So I'm not happy that I didn't like it but I am
happy that it did well because it means it will further open that door for more
Stephen King adaptations. And I think this is how it's going to go. I think Netflix
and these streaming services are probably going to do the smaller ones. And they'll
do bigger ones for the movies that probably won't be that great. But hopefully they
are. I mean, I know they're remaking pet cemetery now. I can't imagine a world in
which it scares me more than the original film did. No. But there's a ton of
shit in that book that the original film doesn't get to.
So maybe they're gonna go in a different direction with it.
I don't know.
But to the problem is,
I think we're gonna get a Melissa McCarthy misery
in five years.
Thanks so much.
Can almost guarantee it.
Really?
Yeah.
It'll be like McCarthy and Dick Jenkins, something like that.
Dick Jenkins will be too old at that point.
So I'm just throwing somebody out.
Costner.
Yeah, maybe a costner.
I think it's a thing for kids I don't know, but I was like this is it's not a drama.
It actually appears the plot when a when a guy's blind date goes missing, he enlists
his retired like CIA grandfather to help him find her. And then it's his action comedy.
I'm like, no, no.
It really doesn't sound that funny, like a woman missing, you know, but, you know, just
the title alone, you're like, this is, this is, this is sunny for Christchurch, but it's
not dirty grandpa.
That's true.
And that movie that cons in, I can't remember the name of it, it was on Netflix where he plays
the neighbor that the kids try to, they set up like a fake, they've set up all these devices
in his house to make it look like his house is haunted, digs town, digs town, yes, I believe
it was called digs town. It was, uh, it was, it was, it was, that was good. I like that.
I enjoyed that. What was that called? Digs town. You're right. Lou Gossett, Jr. plays the
kid next door. I only like Con really. Well, no, I've liked one of you, but like the Godfather,
Honeymoon and Vegas. And then California split back in the day, or the gambler, you know,
You know I never saw the gambler than that. I'm not a big fan. I like both versions of the gambler even the
Marky Mark John Goodman one. You didn't have nice things to say about the
Marky Mark one on this podcast. No, I liked it. I like Goodman on it. I bet if we go back to the tapes
I liked it. Okay. All right. I didn't love, but it's a solid entertainment. I thought the movie was okay
I don't think it was bad. I thought it was horrifically miscast with Mark Wahlberg as a college professor. Yeah. No
I agree. Yeah, we talked about that. Yeah, I like gambling movies.
What can I say? We do think about a Vegas vacation. That is, to me, the most accurate,
sort of gritty depiction of what gambling can really do to you.
I like that it had a very funny war scene where they're playing war except now you can actually play war in all Vegas casino
I remember not that long after it came out a guy I knew from Philly saying that he went to a casino and saw that
And he was like cause I thought it was like that fucking Chevy Chase movie. I was like what the fuck dude?
They haven't it ever casino. Yeah, it was I
Like Vegas vacation probably just as much as European you know
I think it sounds like an idiot right now it goes one three and then like two and four or both kind of shitty now
It goes one then two then three stupid then four that's stupid. You just said you Vegas vacation that starts that starts
That starts with an opening sequence of him
Driving his car mr. Magoo style around the neighborhood right that's on par with European vacation
I think Vegas is probably a scoosh worse than European vacation a scoosh a scoosh a scoosh
I
Think about a scoosh. Yes, that's insane. I like the Papa, Georgia stuff
The only part that made me laugh in Vegas vacation is when he goes
Is when the guy Toby husk? Yes is doing the Sinatra like casino blood and he and the kid walks up to when he goes
You're a man on the town
That really makes me laugh. There's some like funny fringe shit in Vegas vacation, but look European
Just always really let me down because one and three or two of my favorite comedies four. You're like, ah, they lost it
What order did you see him in I?
Would have seen them
Probably three one two. There's your problem. See I saw them in the order they came out. Yeah
I saw your pification as a sequel and I enjoyed it quite a bit and then the third one. I said, okay, here we go again
Yeah, I'll go for another ride. Here we go again
I
Think that was the I think that was the tagline for it here. We snow again. I really do. I don't think it was
Well, it was you'll have a great time was one of them because I had I had it on VHS and I think the back said
The other I really do here. We snow again, but uh oh my
Lord, that's Larry Appleton's catch fruit.
And also I have a plan.
Has that become a catch phrase yet?
I've not heard him say that repeatedly.
Then there must be one season
where he's just starts saying it all the time.
I mean, he says it here and there,
but oh, my Lord is like once in episode, he says it.
No, definitely then in the later season,
he'll go, I have and Belki goes, oh no.
Yeah, no, they plan.
They do that, they do that.
Okay, but it's more like the idea of him having a plan. Yeah, is the thing whereas oh my Lord like exact same inflection every Oh my Lord
Like that's like his that's his don't be ridiculous or his got any cheese
Got any cheese is it oracle is that Erkel? Oh
But look yeah, I when I worked for Cinematical a well as movie website
I did, they used to do like, what now on the onion calls run the series, and I used to
do this too.
You would review all the movies in a series or a franchise.
And I think I'd probably shook it out, one, three, two, Vegas.
But I also had to watch Christmas vacation, two, Uncle Eddie Hawaiian style, cousin Eddie
Hawaiian style.
Why would you watch that?
Because I had to watch all the movies in the series as I established at the beginning of it. I didn't hear that part, but it was
What you want to talk you want to up your opinion of Vegas vacation?
Holy shit. There's like a curse. They're on an island. I mean Chevy Chase isn't even in that one. Chase is in that
The end isn't in that one. That's correct. And where would you rank?
Maybe our most discussed movie ever on this podcast the remake of vacation
I put the remake way way above Vegas vacation the remake is better than Vegas
I think Vegas vacation is a terrible terrible movie that has a few funny
Parts and maybe the Bose die. It's the way I like like a tack of the clones
It's like I'm such a diehard Star Wars fan. I find the stuff in it
I like but I know that I can't compare to like the original movie
I remember being very depressed when I saw when I was like 15
I was like oh fuck I'm finally can go see one in the theater and this is what I get
However, your European is vastly overrated. I was about 18 when when Vegas came out. Yeah
Uh, and that I knew then it I said it doesn't say national lampoons on the top of it. Mm -hmm
It's gonna be different people. It's why the third naked gun isn't that good
It's because it's not the same guy. It's not the whole crew. It's one of the guys and you know
Anyway, folks hot shots one end do is better than naked gun three
Yeah
Yeah. I mean, look, there are days where I tell you that wrongfully accused might set
above naked gun 33, that we've talked about this over many drinks. Yeah. Oh, yeah.
1922. Overall, yes. I go watch it. It's a solidly entertaining movie. If you've got
Netflix, you could do a lot worse. You're not going to feel good afterwards, but you're
not going to feel good before it. That's a good point. If you feel good, I have nothing
in common with you. I don't know what you're watching in terms of society.
We'll keep the plug short. We'll say happy Thanksgiving. Bonus app drops next week
along with the final episode for November. Thank you to our Patreon contributors.
We can't thank you enough. It's been an overwhelming response. If you want to
check out the Patreon page, maybe give it contribution. It is patreon .com slash
WSYIHPOD that's patreon .com slash WSYIHPOD and I am on Instagram, Twitter, whatever
it is, Joe DeRose's comedy. I'm on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh
watch for promos of my show Living Biblically which comes to CBS probably in the early
new year. Thank you folks. We'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.
That was a hitgun podcast.