I'm here for Bet River's online casino and sportsbook with poker icon Phil Helmuth.
And now thanks to the excitement of Bet Rivers, I'm also a slots icon.
That's great. And a same game, Parley icon.
Cool, cool. A Blackjack icon, a money line icon,
A roulette. Take it from Phil Helmuth.
If you love games, Bet Rivers is the place to play in Bet.
Bet Rivers.
Games on.
Must be 21 plus in present at West Virginia.
Void were prohibited. Terms in conditions apply.
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gambling.
Firestone Complete Auto Care's epic savings advantage is the sign you need to stop
putting off your car's maintenance.
And you can save up to $100 on tires and services while you're at it.
Don't wait, call Firestone Complete Auto Care for an appointment.
Welcome to another episode of We'll see you in hell, your favorite podcast where we discuss
horror, sci -fi, fantasy, sometimes action, and occasionally now mob movies on one of your hosts,
Joe DeRosa.
I'm the other of your host, Patrick Walsh.
The rare AM recording of We'll see you in hell.
Top of the morning, do you?
Enjoying some morning, Joe, with my morning, Joe.
Joe DeRosa, we're your drive time crew, your drive time commute.
Yeah, we just talked on the Patreon about Gotti.
So if you're on the fence about signing up for the Patreon,
I recommend doing so.
Joe and I discuss our viewing of Gotti.
We discuss mob movies in general.
We discuss all the directorial efforts of Kevin Connelly, E from Antourage, my favorite director.
And we can do a lot of things.
We talk about Golden Girls Live, which was a live drag show.
Joe and I saw this weekend.
It's a fun one.
Check it out.
And you're a fun one.
You're a fun one, too, Joe.
Morning, we are talking about Army of Darkness, which has long been requested.
And we'll get to it eventually.
It was actually the first of the Evil Dead films that I saw.
And I had a poster up for Army of Darkness.
I'm looking at Joe's VHS copy of it right now.
I had this poster up in my room for most of my childhood.
It came out in 193.
13 to 16.
I had this poster up having never seen the movie.
It's a great poster.
Great poster.
You had it up because of the rippled mussely shirtless man on it, correct?
Him and also the heavily doctored female lead,
Mbeth Davids.
They didn't use her body or her face
for this poster.
I guess they thought that wasn't going to sell units.
So it isn't it?
It is odd.
But yeah, I definitely cranked it to that poster.
I'm not going to lie to you.
I was 13 people, right?
To pretty much anything that came into my field of vision.
But we'll get there.
We'll talk about it.
I don't know what Joe thinks of the movie.
He actually had a bit of a tone when I brought it up,
but yet he owns it, but he's a walking contradiction.
Well, when do I not have a tone?
First of all, we've always got a tone.
And if you're going to refer to me as a green day song,
I'd prefer a basket case over walking contradiction.
You are a basket case.
Although I love the song walking contradiction.
I love it too, but basket case is the green day's greatest song ever written.
It's unquestionably great.
It was beaten to death on the radio.
But I mean, the first time I heard that song,
I was like, you got to be kidding me.
Yeah, this is awesome.
You know, they are now treated in just a pile of
forgettable shit.
Like, you know, like they're always lumped together
with all those pop punk bands.
And, you know, they didn't invent the form,
but I really don't understand why they started getting shot on.
It makes no sense to me.
They were relevant for...
It's because they're music started to start.
Well, sure.
Did you, were you a fan up through American Idiot?
Or no.
I was long gone before Mary.
I believe Nimrod was the final thing of quality they put out.
Nimrod is great.
Almost a double album, really.
Yeah, after that, they did warning,
which was like the sort of like acoustic one.
I liked warning.
I like some songs on warning.
I prefer probably American Idiot to warning.
But that was, that was when I got out.
It got too broadway.
Yeah.
Which then eventually literally led to Broadway.
But like it just got too like,
and it was also kind of trite during that period.
Like that whole, like, yeah.
It was during the Bush era
and everybody was suddenly, was a political band.
And it was, it was just annoying.
And it was, it was just had been said so much it was.
I didn't even listen to those Uno Dose Trace albums
that came out.
I did.
They had their moments.
I mean, I'm not going to say they were without value,
but they were not great albums.
Right.
They just became to,
I don't know, but a lot of people thought that
when they put out Duki just because it was on a major label.
But Duki's a really good record.
Love Duki.
I mean, the ones that everyone says
are their true punk albums.
They're not, they're not great.
Guys, Kaplunk and the other one.
Kaplunk is much better than Slapy Hours.
Yeah.
I like Enema the State.
I mean, I'm not pretending I'm some hardcore punk.
I like Blink 182 for a couple albums there.
Really?
You never identified as a hardcore punk?
I know you might think that about me, but no.
Well, I just because of the nose ring
and the constant oi oi that you're always letting out.
But the Wallet Chain.
Yeah, I was more of a hot topic punk, you know.
Well, that would explain the Wallet Chain.
Yeah.
I, you know, look, sometimes I'll go into a public place
wearing that Nirvana shirt with the smiley face on it.
You know, so I do definitely represent
some more kind of obscure off the beaten path punk music.
But right.
That's what I always liked about you, you know.
Yeah.
You marched to the beat of your own drummer.
I've always said that about you.
That's true.
Look, I took a picture in front of CBGB's once.
I was there.
Joe, what's going on with you?
You're a mirror mess, I assume.
Place is not a mess.
Ladies, place is tidy.
I've gotten the new apartment to where I like it now.
Yeah, it took me a minute to get it all set up right.
But I've got it all set up right now and I like it.
And I actually think I'm going to be selling my Gallagher machine.
Okay, I was I was wondering about that.
I'm going to keep that beautiful Star Wars machine.
It's my prize possession.
I know you're keeping that.
But the Gallagher machine it's sort of, you know,
it's not really the machine.
It's an old cabinet but the artwork looks to be reproduced to me
and it's got a 60 and one game board in it.
So it's not like it's not like it's a classic thing.
It's a very modded up.
How much are you going to get for it?
I bet you get $1 ,500 for this.
All right, I bet you.
Would you sell it like to an individual or to a
sell it back to the store I bought it from?
Well, surely they'll not give you a great price for it, right?
Well, I paid more than that.
Okay.
I'm just thinking what I could get for it.
Yeah, but it would also just clear up some space over there and
right.
You know what I mean?
Sometimes you want to stand in the corner of your apartment.
Blair Witch style and stare into a corner, you know?
Is there anything wrong with that?
Yeah.
If there is, I don't want to be right.
Plus, I don't have room out here for my Vectrex machine,
which is a very cool little machine.
Okay.
And I don't know.
I work out machine.
No, it's a video game console.
But that is something that is very unique and very authentic.
And I can't put it out here because I know where to put it.
If I get rid of that
Gallagher machine, then I could have my Vectrex back out here again.
All right.
I mean, I don't think this is probably interesting to anybody,
but that's what's going on in my life.
Not me, but I mean, who knows?
I've started doing a meditation app.
How's that going?
I would say it's helped very, very slightly,
which is better than not helping at all.
But it, whether, you know, it does help to sit in the morning
and instead of slowly spiral out of control
to sit and take 10 minutes of deep breaths while a guy with a British accent
tells you you're doing great.
Okay.
Now, this is a guy you bring into the house.
I pay him, yes.
All right, it's $500 a sesh.
It does he have a British accent in real life,
or does he just put it or expect that it's fake,
which I tend to focus on taking me out of the meditation.
But no, it's helpful.
It's the headspace app.
I had wanted to do it.
When I was going to therapy,
it was recommended to me about a million times.
Since she's like, if you won't go on anodity presence
and you won't meditate,
like you're going to go insane.
The meditation helps.
I'm back running a show.
It's monumentally stressful every second of every day.
It helps you just sit, check out,
not look at my phone.
It's a good way to kind of start the day and center yourself.
And there's little things.
He gives you little tips throughout the day.
He's like, when you get out of a chair or get into a chair,
take the time to go,
I'm standing up or I'm sitting down.
He's like, I know it sounds stupid.
But it'll help remind you of who you are, where you are.
Right.
And it's called McCartney is doing the air.
Yeah, right.
Then the next morning, he's like,
you didn't remember to check it when you was standing or sitting down.
Did you?
And every morning, now for four weeks,
I have not remembered to do it one time.
How much is this app every month?
I might do it.
For a year,
they have, I'll send you, I'll forward you the next special,
because it's $99, but they drop it all the time to $40.
For the year?
For a year.
And they have all kinds.
They have creativity,
like they have special guided ones
like I do the anxiety one every morning.
I got to do this because I'm not going to therapy anymore.
I'm on the meds.
It's helpful.
I'm not going to therapy.
I don't give a shit.
It helps me out a little bit.
You know what doesn't help me is meditating
and then drinking a 64 ounce iced coffee on an empty stomach.
That's what I'm doing, folks.
I am hungry right now
in a way I can't even explain.
Famished.
And yet we're still bringing the heat.
And I'm drinking a big coffee too
and it's making me sick quite frankly.
Yeah, you get that kind of a little bit of nause,
a little bit of heartburn feeling.
I don't like it.
I puked this week for the first time
and ages just simply due to nerves.
Really?
So yeah, some, some's got to give.
And you know, we'll see what it is.
Yeah.
Joe, I'd love to take you if I could over to
Pat's movie corner.
Before you start the show.
Well, no, I guess I could start the show.
Get on with the show.
And at the same time, get on.
With the Joe.
That's a repeat.
It's not it was requested.
And I said, I didn't want to do it.
And then a guy said,
please do my request.
Send me a message.
And I'm doing it.
I thought you did that one already.
I think I might have said somebody requested it
and I don't do requests.
And then this guy wrote me and was like, please do it.
So look, even if I did do it,
I don't, I don't really care at this point.
All right, fair enough.
Somebody asked me for something
and I like to make the fans happy, you know?
So Pat's movie.
The.
Corner.
Mm -hmm.
I think today I'm going to focus on three television shows.
And I will start with Detroiters.
Detroiters is on Comedy Central.
It stars Sam Richardson, who you may know,
as the only black person ever to appear on Veep.
I think that might be pretty close to true,
although that show, for some reason,
never gets any flack for it.
And also a guy who you probably don't remember
from Saturday Night Live,
because he didn't really make an impression there.
But his name is Tim Robinson.
Didn't make an impression on me.
I didn't think he was very funny.
Okay.
On Detroiters, these two are fantastic.
It is a great reminder that sometimes SNL
is just not a good showcase for what people do well.
Ben Stiller did not thrive at Saturday Night Live.
You know, he did funny shit,
but he wasn't making an impact there.
Sometimes it's just not a good fit.
Detroiters is about two guys who are very low level ad execs,
who make commercials.
You get the feeling the show was pitched
as going to be a lot of commercial parodies,
but they really don't go to that well very often.
It is a very, very, very funny show.
It is very kind of surreal at times.
The first season is, I would say,
significantly better than the second funnier.
The second season just wrapped up.
I have now seen every episode of it.
It's all delightful.
It's got a delightful theme song.
The first season has a scene
where Tim Robinson has a realization that he can't sing
and he keeps trying to sing.
Like in this recording booth,
he goes in and just screams.
He keeps trying and each time you see in his face that he thinks,
maybe this will be the time a perfect voice comes out
and it causes him to start screaming at the end and he's like,
I can't sing.
I'm sure I'm describing it okay,
but this scene is one of the funniest television scenes I've ever seen in my life.
I think the show is great.
I recommend you watch it.
I hear great things.
I got to check it out.
Very funny.
I don't have comedy central
and I don't have a lot of willpower or drive is the better term.
Sure.
But I'll try to get to it.
There's a real charm to it.
I like the show a lot.
Well, if you want to talk TV things,
I saw, finally, Alan Partridge,
Sizzard Isle,
which is the latest Alan Partridge.
Wasn't that coming to the CISO?
It was on TV in England.
It was supposed to come up to Netflix, I think.
Anyway, it's an hour special.
You see it?
It's on YouTube.
I just watched it on YouTube.
Okay.
I got to see this thing.
Any good?
It's great.
It's Alan Partridge.
It's hilarious.
The plot of this one is he's doing an almost like,
almost like a Michael Moore style,
investigative report into the,
into the quote, lower classes,
and quote of England.
Yeah.
And then the gag is, you know,
he goes to Manchester and he's like,
I have never seen anything like it.
They have these stores that are the source of their economy,
that they're referred to as supermarkets.
Okay.
So he has, there's a really funny bit where he becomes a checker for the day,
just so he can live like the common man.
Yeah.
And this old lady comes with her gross reason.
She doesn't understand like to put,
he for some reason wants her to put the,
the groceries on at the end of the belt,
so he can move them.
And she keeps bringing them the front.
And he's like, no, no, no, to the end,
to the end, I bring them forward.
I bring them, you know, I have seen it.
And it's just like an abitant Castello like,
I have seen this.
Yes.
It was great.
I watched it grainy on YouTube or something.
It was really, really funny.
There's another really funny part where he goes after a guy
for like unfair wages at his company or something like that.
And he's like, you're bastard.
And he's screaming at him and everything.
And then the guy's like,
stick to radio mate.
This isn't your thing.
And now I'm part just like,
radio, what do you mean?
Do you know what I am?
And he's like, yeah, I listen to you every morning.
And then immediately he's like, all right.
Well, just try then if you could.
Yeah.
If I've never recommended it on here,
the Alan Partridge audio book fully read by Cougan
as Alan Partridge is one of my favorite pieces of comedy of all time.
It's great.
And I have not yet listened to Alan Partridge Nomad.
They follow up, but I'm very excited too.
I've listened to Parks and Nomad.
It's very funny.
There's a joke every other sentence in the Partridge book.
They really didn't phone it in.
Now, a audio book I'm listening to now
that did phone it in a bit sadly,
although it's not without its charms is toast on toast.
Because I got deeply into toast of London,
my next album show, which I know we discussed on here.
The pilot of it, I was kind of like,
okay, but episode two, I just really snapped
onto the wavelength.
I watched that entire three -season show
get to your bones.
You can't get enough.
You find yourself talking like the guy.
Yeah.
Toast of London on Netflix is a fantastic, fantastic British comedy.
I recommend it.
Wait, did you get the audio book of toast on toast?
Yeah.
Is it good?
I'm an hour in and I've yet to laugh out loud.
I was expecting a Partridge level thing
and this feels a little bit like it kind of rushed.
Okay.
But it's not bad by any means.
I can't tell you not to listen to it.
Okay.
But if you have not watched toast of London,
it is really something special.
It is the boss from the IT crowd, Matt Berry,
who is just a super funny dude.
I, at some point, locked into him doing a little bit
of Austin Powers, Mike Myers.
There's a hint of it.
And then I was, it was hard to separate that for me,
but Austin Powers is a hilarious character.
And Toast of London has some of the greatest bits.
The bits where he is recording,
it starts pretty much every show,
but the bits where he is trying to record
an audio book or voiceover or whatever
with those guys who are like winding him up.
Steven, this is Clem Fandango.
Can you hear me?
Yes, I can hear you, Clem Fandango.
We watched a collection of those in the writer's room at work.
No one had seen the show,
and they had a YouTube compilation.
People were just screaming, laughing.
It's, when you watch them back to back,
it's unbelievable.
And the rest of the show is,
it takes big swings,
it's spotty, it's hit and miss,
but the hits are really, really something.
I recommend it.
Yeah, it's a great show.
Yes.
That's, they're doing season four too,
so that's exciting.
Really?
Yeah, that's fantastic.
Was that your thing?
Was that your go?
Sure.
All right.
I saw black clansmen.
Can't wait to see it.
Spike Lee's finest film.
Since Malcolm X.
All right, I was hoping there was a disclaimer.
Well, since Malcolm X,
but I mean, it is up there in my opinion
with Malcolm X and do the right thing
and all of his best work.
That's, that's really big talk.
I don't give a shit.
All right.
I mean, I'm excited to see it,
but that's very big talk.
It's a phenomenal, phenomenal movie.
Okay.
Now, I put, I put,
my special category of films with Malcolm X,
I mean, excuse me, with Spike Lee,
are Malcolm X,
which is one of my 10 favorite films of all time.
Sure.
I would put, do the right thing in that category,
one of my 10 favorite films of all time.
I would put,
I don't know, I'm blanking on all Spike Lee movies.
25th hour.
No, I fucking love 25.
I love it too.
But I think there's,
I think he makes certain movies
that transcend just being movies.
They're riveting stories
and they're so socially relevant
at the time they come out.
It's, it's almost jaw -dropping
and do the right thing was one of those.
Malcolm X was one of those.
This is definitely one of those.
Like it, it, it is alarming
how many parallels there are
between the storyline of a, of a black,
of the first black cop in,
where does it take place?
Colorado Springs or whatever.
Yeah.
In the 70s, realizing that that was a thing,
they didn't have a black officer
yet in Colorado Springs until the 70s,
which is crazy.
Yeah.
We, we, it's just the whole movie is,
we realize how shallow,
how shallowly planted these,
these, these roots of racism truly are.
Like, that's the wrong way to put it.
They're deeply planted.
But, you know, we haven't grown past this.
Past the roots for very long now.
It's a fascinating film.
It's an amazing story.
Washington hits a grand slam.
Driver hits a grand slam.
The movie's perfectly cast.
It's beautifully directed.
House Toe for Grace.
He's phenomenal.
Everybody is great.
It is, it is a, it is a perfect film.
And then he does the,
well, I don't want to tell you what he does,
but, but I'm going to see it.
By the end of this thing, you're almost in tears
at how, and you'll see why
over the social relevance of it all,
I've heard from people who liked it a lot.
And the criticisms I've heard
just as much as the praise
were a, it's a mess.
It's not a mess.
Okay.
It's absolutely not a mess.
That's a ridiculous statement.
And B, it gets real heavy -handed by the end.
Yeah.
It's about the clan.
Sure.
I mean, I, I'm not coming down on either side.
I haven't seen it.
Trust me.
Tell me what I keep hearing from people.
It's, it's, it's, it's the best film he has done
in a long time.
Now, look, I loved Inside Man and 25th hour and all that stuff.
That's 15 years ago at this point.
I mean, he, he has, when, when they've called him out
for being in slumps before,
I don't think he has been.
He's been, he's been in a bit of a slump of late.
Like, it's, it was hard to get through that vampire one
and I did not get to it.
It was, she hate me, which is pretty old,
as a terrible movie.
Shytown.
What was it?
Shyraq.
They were, that's like they were rat,
like wrapping in Shakespearean style
or something I didn't, I, I didn't ever even start
at that one.
And that's, that's one of our best directors.
That's why I'm saying that this film is so special is because
did you close your legs, please?
Why?
Folks, Joe has legs spread wide open with me looking directly
into his nut sack.
Well, look, if I was wearing pants, it wouldn't bother you.
It would, but you're wearing shorts.
No, I actually can't look at you.
I meant that I was naked.
Oh, okay, I got you.
It was a joke.
You fucking idiot.
Well, I was answering it in a very reasonable manner.
You're wearing shorts.
I'm sorry.
I'm just trying to be comfortable.
Be comfortable.
When I talk about socially and racially relevant films,
I like to be comfortable.
You don't got to share in stone with your balls.
It's, it's a movie that hits the notes
that a movie like Jungle Fever, for instance, hits
in its commentary on a racial, in the sense
of a racial commentary.
But every once in a while, he does it at exactly the right time
and it's perfect.
And this was that.
Not to say that Chirac wasn't something
that should have been talked about.
I just felt the execution of the film wasn't as good as it could have been.
Yeah, did you see it?
I saw it, yeah.
I gotta see it.
My only complaint.
He also got a lot of shit for that movie.
He did.
But my biggest complaint about Spike Lee
has always been the blaring
trumpet heavy jazz scores.
That's the only issue I've had,
like even with his masterpieces of which there are several.
I'm always like, can we at least turn down the trumpet in the mix?
There's a really, really, really funny line
in Black Clansman when Ron Stallworth,
who's the, who's the character that basically sets up the meeting.
Yeah, he goes to his like superior at the police department
and he's like, and the guy's like, you want a what?
Yeah, that's how the scene starts.
You know, yeah.
He's like, sir, I want to infiltrate the Cluclux clan.
Now, I've already got a meeting to meet with one of them.
One of their recruiters, the guy just goes,
I wouldn't go to that meeting.
Like it, I like it.
Yeah, it's very funny.
Adam Driver is becoming, in my opinion, our finest,
newest young actor.
He's good.
I always like him.
And then also,
great Spike Lee, traditional Spike Lee stuff,
hits it from all angles.
Doesn't just hit it from the perspective of
how do Black people deal with racism in this time period?
Right.
Gets into it from different angles
and challenges you from different angles.
And it's really, really, really great.
It's a wonderful film.
Can't recommend it enough.
Can't wait to say it.
My only criticism
was the casting of Nick Titoro.
John Titoro's brother
as a
astute clansman.
Right.
Well, Spike Lee has a real allegiance to the Titoro's clearly.
He loves the Titoros.
I love the Titoros.
I've actually met Nick Titoro.
He's great.
He's hilarious.
Yeah.
He's like another, like a Joe Pesci type, right?
But, you know, so
it's, the Titoro brothers are so Italian.
They look like, they look like
Puerto Rican or something.
You know what I mean?
Like they are, they are the most
Italian men I've ever seen ever.
Like it's very Sicilian Italian.
Whatever.
So when he's running around a clan meeting,
being like,
shall we tell the grand wizard?
It's just a little weird.
And well, maybe that's historically accurate.
I don't know.
That's what I was wondering.
I was like, but then
my friend who I saw the film with, she said,
she said, you know, maybe she goes,
look, maybe that was the point.
Maybe Spike Lee's point was like,
these guys don't really care, right?
If you're
you know, Italian and whatever.
And by the way, when I say,
they're so Italian, look, Puerto Rican,
I don't mean that to be funny.
I'm saying like,
there is a level of Italian
that you would constitute as almost not Caucasian.
You know what I mean?
It's the same thing with certain
certain areas of Spain and stuff.
So it's like,
it's like, and she was like,
I think maybe that was the point
was which she was like, as long as you're not black.
Yeah.
But, but, but I don't know if that was the point or not.
Whatever happened to like two years ago,
they were making a
John Terturo starring
spin -off of the Big Lebowski.
It was made.
It was made and not released.
It maybe just hasn't been released yet.
That doesn't bode well.
It's an odd concept.
I can't wrap my head around it.
I mean, you're making a comedy about a pedophile.
That's it.
It's an odd concept.
Yeah.
And you love that character in the movie,
even though he is a pedophile.
But you love him because it's
John Terturo is very funny.
Very funny.
But he's also not the guy you're rooting for.
You want the dude
yes, to beat him in the bowling thing.
Of course.
Do you think the colon brothers will ever revisit those characters?
No, they don't do sequels.
I mean, it's such a cult following.
They don't and they won't.
I was, I couldn't believe they licensed it over to Terturo.
I mean, apparently Terturo was very responsible for like that character.
Like, you know, he really took it to another place.
You know, but I'm excited to see their new
the ballad of Briggsby Brogues or whatever it is.
There was going to be a TV show and now they're making it a movie.
What's it about?
It's a Netflix Western with starring Tim Blake Nelson.
Is it a comedy?
I'm sure it looks like their usual fair.
All right, it was going to be a six -part series and now it's a movie.
So that's also a little strange, but they said they didn't want people
watching them out of order or they didn't want people skipping ahead
to what they heard was the best episode or whatever.
And I get that.
So now it's just a six -hour movie.
Yeah, I don't know how long it is, but yes.
They might have also just realized they didn't have enough goods for sex.
Joe, have you yet watched
Who is America, the Sasha Barron Cohen vehicle?
I've seen some of it.
I don't have show time, but I've seen what I could and I enjoyed what I saw.
I watched the premiere and I was giddily texting Joe like
this is the most exciting thing to have in a comedy in a while.
I can't wait to see who he goes after.
This is what we need right now.
And it was very smart and political and exciting to me
to expose these people who just first strike against them.
They're stupid enough to not know that this is Sasha Barron Cohen
or clearly a guy in prosthetics because the prosthetics are ludicrous.
But that's how dumb these people are and he goes after some big names and that stuff is great.
But very quickly, it became and still remains a show that is obsessed with
sex jokes, calm jokes, shit jokes, piss jokes, etc.
And Sasha Barron Cohen has never been able to shake that.
He has such a love of
scatological comedy, like the the dictator
was almost overwhelmed by that stuff at a certain point,
even though it had really smart stuff to stay.
The Grimsby that I was one of the few people that saw
the brothers Grimsby.
The brothers Grimsby.
You saw that?
Saw it in theaters.
How was it?
It had a couple laughs, but it was very bad.
And there's a scene where he's like,
you know, like face down and precious, the actress who played precious, Gabrielle Cidabay.
He's going down on her and there's many jokes about that.
There's an elephant who sprays him with like a swimming pool amount of calm.
Okay, you know, like it's basically the age to see this thing.
It's basically the Ace Ventura joke where he's inside a
rhino or an elephant, you know, like inside his ass.
But then another elephant comes up and Fox and then sprays him with calm.
Okay.
And you're just like, how is this the same guy?
How are you this smart that you're able to infiltrate top government officials
and expose their hypocrisies and yet you'll also devote 20 minutes
to trying to get a woman to cut her pubes off, which was a very funny segment.
But it's, it's, you know, it's the same thing with Mike Myers.
Like he said that exactly right.
Inside the outdoor studio, he goes, look, there's a lot of high -brow stuff
and then I have him drink poop, which is my favorite scene.
That's my least favorite scene.
I mean, it's a different of taste, difference of taste.
All right, Michael York say it is shit Austin is very funny to me.
I mean, I like the lowbrow and the highbrow and I like it when it's mixed too.
But for me,
this is like, this was an important thing this show.
I go from the jump.
I was like, he's got access to these people that nobody has.
We can really see these people for who they really are.
But he, he gets too swept away from my taste
with the shit and the piss.
And this one, he plays a guy named like Bruce and DeGiocello,
who's like a super NPR loving there.
And even that, he starts taking kind of two easy shots right away.
But a big like Hillary guy and Peter guy and it's something.
Yeah, yeah.
And the first one where he's talking to this like clearly closeted man
in his Southern Baptist wife about how he is in love with a dolphin.
And he doesn't think that America should judge him on that.
And there, that was in the pilot episode.
And I was like, how laughing at these two?
Like it was a genius segment.
But by now, and last week's episode, he wants to experience childbirth.
So he puts a fake vagina onto his asshole.
This sounds great.
It's just this segment is 20 minutes of a show.
All right.
Then you have like this, here's where I start to bump on it.
You have an actual Hispanic barely speaks English nurse
who he is now forcing to completely fist his asshole on television
and he keeps clenching his ass, I guess, on her hand.
And she's like, I don't want to hurt you.
I need to get more lubricant.
I can't, but she's real.
So this, I don't know how this isn't sexual assault at some point.
And she's got her hand stuck in his asshole and is ganking it back and forth.
And at some point, you are laughing at this.
But you're just, I don't know how you couldn't be.
You're not alive if you're not laughing.
You're just like, how did it get here?
Like this show could have done so much because you only get one shot at it.
Part of it.
Look, look, look,
nobody's going to let him in their office again.
I don't agree with, I don't agree with this show is so important.
I don't think anything needs to be thought of that way in the realm of comedy.
I think comedy can help.
I wish there was a better balance is all of that.
Sure.
But, but anyway, I think comedy obviously can help
as a great way of commentating with everyone.
Yes, but you know, I think, look, part of what Sasha, part of what he's doing is
he's also mocking the character that he's,
the people that he's parroting as he, as these characters, he's also mocking them.
Yeah.
So some of this is just like a guy like this is so extreme.
I wouldn't be surprised if he did something this ridiculous.
For sure.
So there's a bit where he's talking to a guy who sells yachts to people.
And he's, and it's a great bit.
And he's clearly, clearly this guy like is, is a scumbag.
And he's like, what if I want to, you know, transport, you know, underage girls?
What a matter of what he says, the guy's like,
Jury yacht, man, you could do what you want.
And it keeps going and going and going and going.
Right.
And at some point, the guy's girlfriend, or, you know, it's a fake, like kind of
porn actress who's portraying his girlfriend, starts giving him a hand job under a towel,
while he's talking to the guy about yachts.
Then she goes head under the blanket and starts blowing him to completion.
I mean, it's faked, obviously.
And the guy sits there and is just still, let's talk yachts because he must deal with the absolute
scum of the earth.
That is using sexual, scatological humor to really prove a point.
The other ones just go off the rails to me.
But the show is nonetheless fascinating.
It's just, I thought, what it could have been, I guess.
But then again, we don't know.
I want to know how this show was made because it boggles the mind that these people let this
thing happen.
I have friends that worked on it, you know, and I didn't even know they were working on it.
I mean, it was utter secrecy.
That's, you got a little flag because it's like a 20, 20 dude zero woman writing room.
No, I know some women that were in their writing.
It's not, they're not credited.
Well, that's odd.
But I know, I mean, maybe they were, I think, I don't think, I think he only had two permanent
writers and then he had people coming.
I don't know.
Yeah, I can't explain, but I have a friend that worked on the show and she said it was a lot of fun.
But no, I can't speak to what the credit was for that.
But anyway, it's a fascinating program.
Don't get me wrong.
I just, you know, I think he, he takes his eye off the ball a little bit.
And even in simple ones where he's got like Dick Cheney, there are somebody where you're like,
oh, there's so much actual hypocrisy and stuff to latch on to.
He winds up like trying to get them to say testicles or something.
And you're like, no, man, like you could do that with anyone off the street.
You have Dick Cheney here.
Well, listen, you also don't know what's not being shown.
And maybe he tried for all this other stuff.
And it's like, look, if all else fails, do this.
That's true.
So I don't know.
But my hat's off to him for making a good show.
I would have seen him.
It was funny.
But yeah, it's, it's something else for sure.
I'll close us out with one you've already spoken about.
I saw three identical strangers.
What do you think?
I was on a plane.
I said, there's that documentary Pat was talking about.
Let me watch it.
Amazing.
It's really an all -time great documentary.
I would say.
Earth shattering.
Yeah, just amazing.
Something else.
And then it's, it's like a fascinating story
and a perfect, exact, perfect setup for a documentary.
But it goes to such like broader, bigger places by the end.
Yeah.
And you had said on here during your review,
it starts to take some dark turns.
Yeah.
So when I first started watching it,
and the brothers are sort of saying things,
it's upbeat, but the brothers are saying things like,
we were so happy.
Yeah.
And you're going, oh God, where's this going to go?
And then don't spoil it.
I'm not going to spoil it.
But you think this is a family movie.
Yeah.
You start to think about crimes of the family.
And that's kind of where my head went.
And that's not what it was at all.
Yeah.
It was so much bigger than what I thought it was going to be.
Yeah, it's got, I assume you were thinking of
molestation or something like that.
Something, yeah.
It, uh, yeah, it's got a really kind of more global
universal message by the end of it
that kind of shook me up.
It wound up getting me talking about my own family
and, uh, all sorts of things.
It was a great, great movie.
Great.
Let me take you to scary stuff.
I got one thing real quick.
I've been on a Star Wars kick lately.
Yes.
Folks, Star Wars fans, I implore you.
If you live near a video arcade, like an actual video arcade,
you need to call that arcade and ask them if they have a game called
Star Wars Battle Pod in the arcade.
If they say yes, you need to go there immediately.
And play this game.
Leave your baby in the car in the hot car and run inside.
That's how urgent it is to play this video game.
It's, it's a full pod that you climb into.
I haven't played it.
I'm, I'm adding to the hyperbole.
Full pod that you climb into.
There's 180 degrees screen in there.
You're surrounded essentially by screen.
It's a first person flight shooter.
You do all the missions of Star Wars.
The graphics are incredible.
Everywhere you look, you're peripheral.
You're, you, it's, you're in the game.
The, the goddamn thing blows wind at you and shit like that.
Like when you accelerate.
And apparently there's one that actually moves.
The whole pod actually moves.
I didn't get to play that one.
I played the, I played the one that's just you sit down and,
and look at a screen and play, which was really cool.
But then I actually played the one that you get inside and it was the pod.
And that was fucking amazing.
I mean, it is the closest you're ever going to come to being in Star Wars.
All right.
It's better than any of the, you know, I, I love all those Disney rides where, you know,
Star tours and all that shit.
This, this makes that shit look like fucking child's play.
It is awesome.
Now, you have referred to about 10 different games on this podcast as the closest
you can get to being in Star Wars.
No, no, I haven't.
This is the new one.
No, I haven't.
I said that for so long.
I've heard it for the closest you're going to come to be being a
Jedi.
Okay.
Because that when you have force powers.
All right.
I guess I, I missed the difference.
Well, I'll tell you what I miss.
You being a friend.
Let's get to our movie.
Well, don't you think I could maybe go to the fucking scary stuff quarter?
I know.
Let's, let's see what you're going to do this week.
You saw, you saw a box on the street that had a skull painted on.
A spooky box.
This week, I do have one and it couldn't be more fitting because I have to highly recommend
the shout factory edition of Army of Darkness.
Because it had tons of special features that I loved.
And I think that is what scary stuff can be.
Right, Sean?
Yes.
You finally did it right.
It's got like a 90 minute documentary on the making of Army of Darkness.
That's fantastic.
It's got everybody but Ramy.
It's got alternate endings.
It had a very bleak original ending.
It's got the original cut, the director's cut, the international cut,
and the TV cut, like for broadcast TV cut, which is pretty amazing.
I'm not going to watch all four of them.
You can watch some deleted scenes.
You can watch different cuts.
There's a documentary on the making of it.
How they made this Harryhausen -type deal on such a low budget.
It's great stuff.
My favorite thing, even with a movie I don't like, is to watch one of these documentaries that goes
from script to marketing and failure or success of the movie.
And there's two few of them on DVDs.
This has a great one.
I recommend it.
You know, it was originally titled Evil Dead 3.
Yes.
And then it was also going to be called Mid -Evil Dead.
And they set it as part for some reason.
Well, they decided that not enough people know the franchise.
They didn't want to be tied to it.
We want to be doing fine, but not a huge hit by any means.
Well, let's take it on into the review of the film.
Yes.
And it was marketed as a comedy, which I feel it kind of is.
It is.
They were talking about how they shouldn't have marketed as a comedy.
It's a comedy.
No, I absolutely do think it's a comedy.
When I was a kid, I was already in Evil Dead 2 fan when this film came out.
And I didn't realize it was part of the series until I saw I was in the video store.
And they had a section called Prequels and Sequels.
An army of darkness was on it.
And then they told you what franchise it was related to for each movie.
So I was like, oh my god, I didn't know that this was a sequel to Evil Dead.
I got to see this.
And that was when I first saw it.
As a kid, I really enjoyed the film quite a bit.
It takes place after Evil Dead 2, which ends with Ash getting sucked into this time vortex thing.
And he lands in like medieval times.
Right.
Not the restaurant.
Yes.
A parent, which apparently is where this
necronomicon comes from or whatever.
That causes all this trouble.
This book that causes all the problems.
So then the third movie, Army of Darkness, is him trying to figure out how to get the hell out of there and get home.
When I was a kid, I really, really enjoyed this film.
As an adult, I almost never ever want to watch it.
It's two.
The beauty of Evil Dead and Evil Dead 2 are the fact that there are humorous aspects
sprinkled over a traditional horror film.
An actual horror film.
Much more so in two than one.
Yeah.
One is pretty horror.
Those movies are legitimately scary.
And when they are funny, which Evil Dead 2, or Evil Dead 1, isn't really funny much.
Evil Dead 2, when it is funny, it is not funny because there's a gag or a joke.
It's funny because you see a man reacting to an insane situation.
And he doesn't know how to react to it.
He's freaking out.
And a lot of it is, a lot of why it's funny is that.
There's the occasional gag where like,
I mean, even when the hand grabs his head and it's slamming him, he's slamming his own head
into the floor.
Yeah.
It's like, that's funny for obvious reasons.
But it's also still believable.
Like, if your hand got possessed and your hand wanted to hurt you,
that's probably what it would do.
Right.
Army of darkness, on the other hand,
goes full on into self -aware comedy.
This is where Ash becomes the smart -ass,
quip, very full of himself.
Guy, and he's not that in part two.
And part two, Ash is a guy that's forced to figure out how to become a warrior
in an extreme circumstance.
I don't like that in part three.
Suddenly, he's, he's Rambo.
Suddenly, he's the guy that's like, I've been around this block before.
It's like, well, you sort of have for two hours last night
before you got sucked into this time thing.
Right.
But now that's sort of the same energy they brought into the TV show,
and you love the show.
I didn't love the show.
I loved the first season.
Okay.
I thought the second season was
the first season I was willing to go with it.
And I liked the comedy I was willing to roll with because I thought it,
I thought they at least got the show closer back to the evil dead roots,
which they did.
And there were twists and turns and it was interesting.
But like the pilot of evil dead,
or the pilot of the show,
Ash first evil dead, has that scene that had me dying
where he steps on all the light bulbs.
That's like how it starts.
It's a comedy right out the gate.
Well, the difference was this,
that the threats enabled in Ash versus evil dead were threats.
Yeah.
In this movie, you've got skeletons walking around,
talking like they're the groucho marks and shit like that.
You know what I mean?
It's just, it's too much.
I liked all that shit.
I think the reason I really wanted to see this so much when I was a kid
is I was really into which might surprise you that I wasn't more popular.
It was very into like that stuff,
like Harryhausen type stuff,
and I remember before Christmas type stuff.
Yeah, I like that stuff.
The stop motion.
I always like the claymation specials and all that.
Yeah, this, when I saw this,
it was the first evil dead I saw.
I was really worried because I saw it like a sleepover
that I was going to be too scared of it.
And then I was like, oh, this is like Beetlejuice.
This is really fun.
And they talk about wanting to do a different tone
for each of the evil deads.
I love a comedy horror when done well.
I wasn't dying laughing at army of darkness
until the the reshoot part at the end.
I thought that was really funny
with the in the store when he's like,
price check on aisle gun or like all those quips.
That part, so I like that part a lot.
Come get some.
I do too.
Bridget Fonda weirdly.
Yeah, it's his girlfriend for like 10 seconds in it.
They said she was just a fan of evil dead
and wanted to do it.
It's an hour 20 minutes.
The movie.
I mean, I had a good time with it.
You know, I like that aspect of it.
I thought that evil dead too when I saw it
was pretty damn funny.
This one goes more into like a three stooge's territory.
Like much more when the when the little ashes are like
stabbing him and stuff.
You know, like that's just like slapstick comedy.
Yeah, it's it becomes a little too much for me.
The you know, now and drag me to hell,
Remy gets back to a little more of the tone of evil dead too,
yeah, which is there are funny things in there.
Yeah, but he's not going for the gag every time it.
But that's the problem too with ash versus evil dead.
Or that's what happened.
Halfway, half of the second season was too goofy.
Yeah, it was too funny.
It was too joking.
The joke the whole time.
It was too.
I only saw the first.
The stakes became very diluted because even ash didn't seem
to be taking it all that seriously.
I never even saw the third season.
Yeah, because I was like, wait, you're bringing a daughter
into this now?
Like I'm done.
I love Sam Raimi.
I love Ted Raimi.
I love Bruce Campbell.
I'm a fan of the work that all the people on that show did,
the entire cast.
But but I just I don't like when it goes too hard
for the joke.
I just don't care for that.
Not when it's this.
If you're talking about, you know,
Jonah Hill made a horror comedy, fine.
Right.
I'm not expecting him and Danny McBride
to deliver something truly scary.
But you know, when it's something like this,
it's like, you know, keep it.
Keep this once it's once everything is a joke,
the stakes are gone.
This is always my gripe with the Marvel movies.
Once you're making a joke every 10 seconds,
there are no stakes because it seems now
that nobody's taking this series.
Sure.
Anyway, that's my take on Evil Dead
or an army of darkness.
I'm not I'm not without joy.
I'm not against watching the film.
Yeah, I just think compared to the other two,
it's it's lacking.
I agree that it's lacking.
I dug it.
I like that vibe.
You almost never get a movie like this anymore.
The fantasy Conan the Barbarian type.
That they don't make them.
And if they do, there's they star a wrestler
and they're in theaters for a week.
But I dug it.
I had a good time with it.
If you're a fan of the movie,
I mean, this Blu -ray is an absolute must -own.
I know there's eight million versions
of this movie on Blu -ray,
but this is the one to get.
And I dug it.
I may or may not return to the show.
I love Bruce Campbell.
He says the thing is the only time he was ever
the star of a studio release.
Army of darkness sat on the shelf for like two years
and he said it kind of really stalled out his career
and he has conflicted feelings about it himself
because he had done this big thing
but nobody knew about it.
He sat around having like trained
and gotten into the best shape of his life
for two years and nobody wanted to cast him
because they didn't know he's in this.
Anyway, you know,
Evil Dead has some big supporters.
I think people really love this movie.
I'm surprised to hear you say, yeah.
I don't hate it.
I just think it gets too funny.
And this is why I got mad when the
when the Evil Dead remake came out
which I thought was awesome.
It was.
And people were complaining going,
it's not funny.
It's like this was never supposed to be funny first.
Right.
That's what it evolved into.
This was supposed to be scary first.
Stop fucking complaining
that they're not enough jokes in the Evil Dead remake.
But I was surprised by that as well
because it is one of the few movies
that goes for that tone.
So when the reboot just went straight,
you know, like really extreme horror,
I was kind of thrown by that too.
Maybe because it was really traumatizing
in a few parts of that movie.
It's one thing to say.
Hey, I was thrown off.
I thought maybe it was going to be a little funny,
but it wasn't okay.
That being said, dot, dot, dot.
People were literally like using that as a strike against it.
Right.
Had this this movie misses all the humor and joy of the previous.
It's like, did you watch the previous fucking movies?
Yeah.
Anyway, all right folks,
that's our show plugs.
What is this first episode of September?
So I'll be in China and Japan performing
this month.
Have you ever performed there?
I've performed in China, but not Japan.
Okay.
Guys, I don't know the venues or anything yet,
but it's happening.
I've got my flights.
I'm coming out there.
And then I'll be at the Red Clay Comedy Festival in Atlanta,
the third weekend of September.
And then that'll launch me into a few gigs
around the southeast of the United States.
I know we're supposed to be doing Asheville, North Carolina,
and some other places.
Don't worry, the show will go on.
Pat and I are recording far in advance,
so we don't miss any episodes.
That's right.
And it's Jota Rosa Comedy on Instagram.
Yeah.
Well, we should definitely plug our live show.
October 20th here in Los Angeles at Omy Ribs.
There are two shows at 730 and 930.
You can buy one ticket or a ticket to both shows.
We'll be going out afterwards.
Go to the CU and HellPod Instagram to find the link.
I am on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh.
We have a Facebook page for we'll see you in hell,
run by Emily Florence, which is fantastic.
Her and Ken Hanley have really been taking care of the merch.
And the live show Merge is available at the Hoghouse page on Etsy.
Give it a Google.
Cool kids, premiere September 28th on Fox.
That's a show I'm running now.
That's all I got.
We'll be back next time.
I don't think we have a movie selected, but we'll get to it.
That's all I got.
We'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.
I'll see you next time.
It's a cool show.