Summer is here, and Bed MGM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MGM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Bet MGM Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal, durable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Monthly 21 -plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gampler, offer not available in all states
terms apply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
This is a head gum podcast.
Hey there, Helians, it's Joe de Rosa here.
announcing the start of your favorite horror and sci -fi and fantasy movie podcasts.
We'll see you when hell voices a little groggy smoked a few sigs last night drank
a few whiskeys and you know the person I did that with he's right here hello Patrick
I don't smoke. I want to make that clear. I think it's a disgusting habit, and it's terrible for your health.
Well, I'm having a hard time seeing Pat right now, because he's way up on his high horse.
I only spoke, I think, four, but four is enough, it's too much.
It is.
Anyway, since I forgot last time, I need to do this quickly here.
Let's get on with the show.
and also on with the Joe Dalin. Please believe me.
What song is that? I know you wouldn't know that. Joe doesn't know the Beatles. I don't like the Beatles.
We're talking about tomorrow, never knows, last night, and Joe's like, what's that?
I don't like the Beatles. What's that?
I'm allowed to not like the Beatles. No, it's fine. It's a Beatles song.
a wide album, O. Darling.
Oh, that's the one that made Manson murder people.
I think so.
Yeah, let's all celebrate that record.
Look, those people were gonna get murdered anyway.
Oh, Jesus, Pat.
I'm sorry.
They were, they were unlikable.
Tate's sister is, is really taking shots at everybody now.
Rightfully so, she's like, I think it's disgusting
that every producer in Hollywood is rushing to get out of Manson project this year for the 50th
anniversary of this horrible event. I agree. Hillary Duff is playing Sharon Tate and so that's the
one she went after the hardest. She chose not to go after the hardest, the Tarantino picture.
Sure. But she did, she said everybody. Now Joe, why did you tell Chuck Manson to do what he did?
Well, and see, and there's the problem, that was the mistake.
I meant to tell Chuck Vance, and there's another guy, and I ended up, I said, Charlie,
that's got to be short for Chuck, and all I said was, you got to go paint the walls, and
I didn't know I was speaking to a sociable person, and so there you go, that's, it was just
a big mix up.
All right.
You know?
Now after you brought to light the sex in the city three controversy going on. I went home
last night. I get into bed. I googled sex in the city three controversy. That's where I was at.
And there's some new tea as they say. Tea is now slang for gossip. I don't know why.
Okay
Controls brother died yesterday or two days ago. Okay, and
Sarah Jessica Parker
gets on
Instagram or what have you with a heartfelt message out to Kim control and I'm praying for you in this difficult time whatever it may be
Control swipes back
Claws out. I don't need your thoughts in prayer. It was one of the most savage things I've ever seen
Wow, and I'd love to to read it to you now because that's what this podcast has become. I want to hear it
Kimmy
Ketral, believe it or not, I don't follow her on on Instagram
Okay, I assume she's left this thing up, but it is shocking
My mom asked me today when will that Sarah Jessica Parker and she tagged her
My mom asked me today, when will that Sarah Jessica Parker, that hypocrite, leave you alone?
Whoo!
Sarah, your continuous reaching out is a painful reminder of how cruel you really were then and now.
Let me make this very clear, if I haven't already.
You are not my family. You are not my friend.
So I'm writing to tell you one last time to stop exploiting our tragedy
In order to restore your nice girl persona in quotes, Jesus Christ, and then she links to a New York post article called
Inside the Mean Girls culture that destroyed sex in the city. Wow
So S .J .P. is
Apparently a bit of a demon dog there. That's correct. That's correct. Look. I have
Yeah, well, you know what? I'm gonna leave that alone. I'm gonna leave that alone. I was about to drop some fucking team
I damn self about some folks involved with the production of sex in the city. Don't drop the way they fucking treat people
Don't drop no tea. All right. I'm not dropping. We don't need no tea dropped in this place
You get a nice hardwood floor. It'd clean up easy if I just drop the little tea
I'm gonna drop you know what I will drop if anyone knows why it's called
Spill the tea or drop the tea. I'd love to know. It's probably from RuPaul
I can tell you why because we live in a nation of fucking children. That's why
That's why because because we live in a country where grown people instead of saying I'm cognizant of social dilemmas that we need to fix
They go. I'm woke. These are people in their forties are using terms. That's true
We live in the stupidest fucking culture on planet earth. That's true
But also, one of the best because you can kind of do whatever you want, you know, by weed
for no problem and drink and tell it and make fun of the president openly or whatever
you want to do.
But at what cost?
You know?
Well, at that this cost.
Are we even meant anymore?
Do we even know where we stand in the great cosmic circle of things?
So I'm going to somebody about like veterans?
Yeah.
Like I respect the hell out of all veterans.
But just like the shift in the shit I guess the post is kind of what handles a bit of this
But like the the difference in the perspective of being a veteran pre Vietnam and post Vietnam
How different it was because I remember like meeting guys that were like in World War 2 that said like
When I used to work with elderly people and they were telling me they were like yeah, I was 15
I lied so I could fight. Yeah, I was like I can't that does not happen anymore. No, no
Well, you wouldn't be able to get away with it number one, but yeah, I know it's it's a different kind of vibe now
I'm not saying it's not
Honorable to join. I'm just saying it's a different vibe
Not our not our president. He had bone spurs
Yeah, has any of them fought has any president ever fought
Presidents used to fight. Yeah, but I mean like since Kennedy forward. I'm saying like
I don't think Nixon was out on the front lines.
I remember when Clinton was in office, like people would show up, but when Clinton spoke
at the Vietnam Memorial, there was a guy holding a sign that said slick Willie, the draft
dodger.
I think they all kind of, well, everybody was bitching the W didn't fight because he didn't
fight.
The amount of money you need to have to run for president, I think, is the kind of money
that gets you out of going to war, but you know, I was never in some sort of, is the
draft going to happen situation? Thankfully, I would be killed immediately in any sort
of combat.
M &M was one of many musicians that claimed the draft was going to come back.
I remember hearing that, you know, I remember hearing that, and it didn't, well, you know,
like let's, oh boy, let's say this were to go another four years after this or something.
God forbid, that would be the kind of situation where I could definitely see a Trump administration
being like, I feel like these millennials are getting a little too soft.
Just to punish people for like being young, I could definitely see that happen.
Well with the millennials it'd be hard for me to say, don't do that, but do we want them defending
our country?
No, no, no, no, that's going to be a problem.
And I'm not I'm not at all a guy who who shit some millennials. I think they're probably much better people than
Then a lot of what came before them. I don't blame. Well, that's that's I just don't know that they're necessarily fighters
And I think that that's a good thing. I and I know I know they're not people who want to fight for this country
I don't think millennials are better than the people that came before now
But I also think I'm not saying they're the greatest generation or something. I think they're saying they're no different
They're human beings. Yeah, they're not as bad as people paint them out to be
And by the way, millennials, I've been meaning to say this publicly for years, you guys get a lot of shit
And I thought at one point I was cross with you guys. I'm not cross with you guys. It's your fucking parents
I hate your parents are fucking assholes. That's really what it is
But I mean millennials, bro, it's mainly baby. Well
Generation X what are we generation? Why we're like generous. Oh fucking knows
That's what's gonna say millennials now is such a broad term. Yeah, like there are people that listen to this
podcast, I'm sure that are in their 20s, that would be technically considered millennials.
I don't consider them, when I think of millennial, I think of, when I go to the, when I go to
the woke cafe, and to get my non -gluten rice cakes or whatever, the girl in front of
me that's like, you can totally go if you know what you want.
I'm still thinking like that, that's to the millennialist to me, where the guy in there
with the man bun that's like, I just, I just, you know, I like to feel things instead of
think them.
You know, that, but that, I mean, that's clearly a stereotype, though.
But yes.
No, I'm saying when I think millennial, I think that person, only, I think, but I don't
think that's what most people think of it.
But I don't think all millennials are that person is my point.
Yes.
Well, they aren't, of course.
Right.
So that's what most people think of.
There are whole sitcoms devoted to just look at these millennials always on their phone
That way every joke is that. Hey, look at these adults always on their phone. Exactly. That's what I say. Exactly.
That's what I say. Hillary Clinton had two phones for God's sake. All right. All right. I'm not gonna go at a political thing.
I was just making a joke like we don't lead by example. No, well, of course not and the whole reason that everyone hates the
Up and Coming generations always as they get older is because they are young. They are hot.
They are going to have a lot of fun sex in the coming years and your life is over. That's why they're hated
So they lash out with anything they can find my problem is I don't feel my life is over
I don't feel John. I didn't mean you specifically. No, I know. I know you didn't mean me. So I'm just saying
I'm talking about you know the 60 -year -old guy
Choking down his fourth scotch and giant t -bone steak
But even talking about all these millennials only care about their phones
Well, that's a stereotype too. So you don't stereotype in the other direction.
Sure.
But my point is, is you're approaching 40. I am 40. I'm three years away.
Let's just say from a distance.
From a distance.
The world.
Remember how big Earth Day was when I was like nine, you were 25?
Yeah.
I bet Middler had a whole special about Earth Day that I remember being forced to watch at school.
Yeah, there was yeah, there were Earth Day specials and and then now when the world is in much more trouble
You hear nothing about Earth Day. It's weird. It's almost like causes just become bullshit trends that nobody takes seriously
Correct. Yeah, it's it's it's weird. I've never noticed that pattern before
Waaatch
But here's my point. I know I I'm 40 you're 39
Seven just turned 37
I don't, I don't, I'm like, why are people our age and older so mad?
It's like, hey, man, I'm still under having a great time.
We went to see Fu Manchu last night.
I had a couple weed gummies.
Yeah.
I had a bunch of drinks with you and the boys.
I had a fucking blast.
There was not one piece of me last night that felt like,
oh, you don't do this at this age.
I was like, no, this is exactly how I rolled when I was in my 20s.
I agree, but you know, this is also a time of life when the vast majority of people would
be settling down having kids or in a lot of cases I think married for 10 years or had
kids for 10 years.
Certainly the case with all my friends in Missouri, et cetera.
And sometimes I feel like, you know, it's time to pack this in, but I'm getting married.
So I'm doing it.
You're not packing anything.
But we're late.
You know we are late in the in terms I guarantee you when you get married
You're not gonna pack a damn thing in. I'm not gonna pack it in no, but you have kids you each each one requires a little more of packing in and I
Welcome it. I'm not the guy who's like oh my little social calendar's gonna die when I get my no a
Have a fun wife fiance who I can bring out to things hold on my alarm's going off hold on Joe's alarms going off
But I know tons of married couples, old married couples who have a lot of fun, you know,
it depends on who you choose as your partner, if you're miserable in your marriage, it's
on you.
You've chosen someone incompatible.
Or you're, you're a bastard.
All right, well, that's, and that's, this is a new segment called Hot Takes with Pac -Wall.
Something for the new generation of married people.
Yes.
I think, you know, people are much smarter, obviously, heading into marriage.
I'm not saying anything new.
That's I mean people wait a long time till they're a hundred percent sure I
Because the failed marriages of their other previous generation. I absolutely could conceive of getting married at this point
Yeah, I absolutely would have no problem with it. I absolutely would like many aspects of it
But I also think I would if I did get married
I'd marry somebody that was like let's go to the fucking show. Let's go have some fun tonight
I mean if that's what if that's the life you like as you do as I do you have to marry someone right
You can't, the problem these people run into is,
oh my wife's always fucking nagging at me.
Well, if you're partying five times a week
and you get married to someone you've obviously been dating
for a year at least, you didn't pick up any vibes
that she didn't want you going out five nights a week,
do you have to pay attention to your partner?
Well, no, people think that they literally think
they put the ring on in their life
and then it's like, now it's married time.
No, I can't do anything.
I think a lot of those people are also bullshitting
to their friends and really enjoy staying at home watching movies because I got to tell you
yeah I do yeah I like to go out now and then of course but as certainly as I get closer
and closer to 40 even though it's three fucking years away not that far away you know I like
staying home I don't need to go out all the time hey well you know let me rush us over to
Pat's movie I'm sorry yeah right corner and I was holding us up over here you're not holding
this up. This is why you're not going to get married. I thought we were going to talk
a little bit about the Fuman shoe show. Oh, well, all right. Well, I know you got a
hard out to go to the doctor, so yeah, yeah, I do. All right. That's not everybody's business.
I didn't say that it was the prick doctor. It is the prick doctor, meaning he's a prick.
Folks no last night we we saw a fume and chew. It was fun. Um I will say more than any other band
you go see a fume and chew show your nose is assaulted with smells of stale old gas
coming from large bearded men uh assaulted. I didn't smell any gas but oh my god I was getting hit
from all sides. Do you have a good time? I had a great time. I had a great time. I love
Fu Manchu. It was very fun. And I talked a little bit about this. You know, they're
not metal or something, but they're like kind of a stoner rock band. Pretty hard rockin.
Man, it is whole family up on stage. He brings his little girl up to sing like the hook
of one of the songs. A weird beard. And I'm sure a lot of people were like, look, this.
That's not rock and roll but again getting older folks. I thought it was kind of sweet. I thought it was sweet too
Yeah, I wife's up there cheering them on as is you know
His daughter comes up and hit and takes the mic. It was awesome. Yeah, it was very lovely
Yeah, it was also nice that his daughter had those like ear protector headphones on you have to do those kids
I've seen people with their babies and kids at concerts. I'm like what are you fucking doing right now? Yeah, so I like that
But he's also a responsible parent.
I had a great time, I loved seeing them setting up their own stuff, their real grassroots
band.
Yes.
They put all their records out on their own label.
The set list was killer.
It was an awesome show.
I had a great time.
It was.
And then me, Joe, our buddy Vince Averill and a couple other friends went out in what's known
as Boys Town, WeHo, West Hollywood.
would. And never felt more welcomed. I had a good time. I was catching a little bit of a weird vibe
from the bartender when I was buying drinks only because I think he knew we were four straight
guys. And I think he might have thought we were there to smack heads or something. I don't blame
I don't blame a guy in a gay bar thinking sure are these four straight guys going to cause any
problems in here. I mean, there certainly has been a history of it. So, but I, but I think
like we were also, you know, we rolled up on our Harleys. Yeah, we had the leather jackets
and et cetera. Yeah. And my, I was wearing my, my, my short shorts that say exit only on
the back. Um, nobody like that. What is interesting over there because the troubadour is like just this
rock club. And then if you want to go to any bars in a three mile radius, they're like
hard core gay night clubs. Like they're like rage, heat, ass, you know, like they're all
like these one word intense names. When was called flaming saddles? Flaming saddles, which
is the, that's the most direct name I've ever seen on it. Um, so, you know, I was kind
of like, well, where else are we going to go? But I thought it was fun. I never hang out
I go to the Halloween parade once in a while, it's always fun.
I had a good time, I was on a couple weed gummies, as I said, but I had a bit of the
paranoia, but not from the neighborhood from you guys.
I get paranoid.
I was just talking to my own friends, I was getting paranoid still.
I was trying to explain things and I couldn't...
Yeah, you do some of that, but I was like, it's not unbearable.
Do you remember our Uber drive home?
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Holy cow.
That's when I got really paranoid.
Well, I was not high and very paranoid as well.
This guy picks us up.
I was worried that you were going to go off on him, and if you hadn't been high, I bet
you would have, because I know one of your big pet peeves is when you ask a lift driver
to go through it.
Drive through.
Yeah.
And they refuse.
So Joe says, hey, is there any chance you can run us through a drive through a quick and
the way home?
And he goes, just a flat no.
and you're like, okay, and he goes, yeah, you know, I got to get back over here to West
Hollywood by the big money time, which is 2 a .m. when the bar is let out. So, I need
to just drop you guys off real quick and get back. I'm like, but even I thought it was
a little ballsy, but you took it in stride.
I was two of my head. Yeah, and that's a real beef for that I've got with these Uber drivers
and these lift drivers. They're now doing the thing where they're saying like, I'd prefer
for to take you here instead of there and I'd prefer to,
hey, then don't be a fucking cab driver, I'm sorry.
Like, I'm sorry.
Like, you don't get to bend the job
to what suits you at that moment.
It's just not right.
Yeah, it's supposed to be a service industry.
Yeah, exactly.
Speaking of service industry, Pat, please, you got to get us that we almost went to last
night.
The way one of the bars we went to last night was service industry.
That's what it was called.
Yeah.
Are you serious?
Yeah, one of them was just called open.
That's correct.
Yeah.
Anyway, we had a good time in WeHo.
We did.
What, you know, I think you're forgetting the key part of this drive.
The driver Vince, you know, just talking to me and Joe, mentioned something about the
show Chips.
Right.
And this guy, never looking up from his phone, brings his phone up, he's scrolling through
it and then starts playing the chips theme right so we're like I said I hadn't seen chips
he's talking about chips then he goes you guys know this one looks through his phone not
looking at the street at all and plays the dukes of hazard theme I go I gotta be honest
I've never seen the dukes of hazard either does a full turn around to look at me and he's like
what then he just plays snippets of I would say almost a hundred it would come from the 70s
in 80s. Yeah.
So they were listening to the happy days thing.
He was going, and he was googling and scrolling
and paying no attention.
And he was DJing like where he would do like,
he'd be like, y 'all aren't ready for what I got next.
And then he would hate it and it'd be like the night ride
or theme. And he'd be like, and I know you remember this one.
Yeah. Happy days. Yeah. Like, I don't know if it was
something he did to everybody or what?
I think it's just because chips came up.
But then I was having a nice time.
We're heading home, but then things took a very weird turn
when he throws the car into an illegal U -turn,
as if he was in the dukes of God damn hazard,
flips around, and then there's people in the crosswalk
like beyond the halfway point.
You're not even supposed to enter a crosswalk
if a person is in it, people flubbed that,
but there are more than halfway across,
and he whips it at top speed, barely missing these two men,
and then he kind of laughs and drives off.
I was like, what's going on?
I got out of the car.
I had to walk home.
He was having a good time.
I had a nice walk, a 2 a .m. walk,
or whatever time it was, 1 .30.
I walked a couple of miles or so
from where I got out of the cab.
It's a little scary.
And there's a lot of rustling from bushes.
You know, it's a nice residential neighborhood.
I'm like, I feel uncomfortable.
I wouldn't walk through your neighborhood at night.
It's a beautiful neighborhood.
No, I know it's a beautiful neighborhood,
but it's up on that hill and there's too much,
There's too much brush up there.
Well, it's also a coyote country, which I kind of forgot about that.
Yeah.
And by coyote, it means because you live up there.
The coyote has come to town.
That's right.
That's what Pat would say.
He'd yell that through a megaphone to his neighbors when he first moved in.
When I'm about to make love to my lady friend, I like to say, coyote, he gone howl tonight.
He gone howl tonight and then I howl as I mount her I'll start at the bottom of the steps
well she's in the bed whoever my lover is at the time yeah and I'll I'll walk up the steps
like this like a shuffle kind of thing yeah just go coyote go on coyote go on oh boy and I'll say
that all the way up the steps now you're you're doing this on a on a first encounter
I'll do it as soon as they get here I'll take their coat. I'll say can you go upstairs for a second?
I just want to show you something and then I'll do that and that's usually a good gauge on whether or not we're gonna hit it up compatible, yeah
How do you think that would go over though with with a woman that wanted to have sex with me and she's up there waiting and I just came up the steps going
Kai, who would he go on a hook? Kai, who would he go on a hook? I would hope there would be some laughter there
I think that's the only reaction that you're you're good with because everything else is gonna be sheer horror
Speaking of sheer horror folks
Movie corner. I got something for it. Pat's movie corner
Uh
I'm gonna focus on some television shows today. Ooh. I am very much enjoying the
the Versacee, the death of Versacee show.
It's a fascinating program.
It's very well shot.
It's hopeless.
Just absolutely hopeless, dark.
It's just despair after despair.
Who plays Versacee, Travolta?
Or sometimes?
Versacee is an actor you definitely know
whose name I can't remember.
But who's one of the most effective psychopaths,
serial killers I've ever seen,
is this kid I've never seen act in anything.
I guess he was on Glee, named Darren Chris,
and he plays the guy who kills all these men
on this cross -country trip.
I didn't know anything about Conan,
he plays Andrew Conan,
but I didn't know anything about Conan and Orva Sachi.
Versace is barely in it thus far.
It's all about Conan, but man, it's rough.
It's just like, it's almost like an American psychotype thing,
but without the humor, it's just like a very real slog,
But I mean if you like dark shit. It's a horror thing too by the way, I mean, it's it's horrific. Okay, there's a you know
Like scenes that wouldn't be out of place in a slasher movie
I also finally finished after about a year the handmaid's tale and this is no
Slouch on it. I just for some reason it's one of those shows. I didn't watch all at once. I space it out
I should have been seeing it. It's very well done and that has some real horror elements as well
Well, I think the first half of the season was much stronger than the second, but yeah,
it's really good.
It's as good as people say.
It's very, very timely and good.
I'll watch it.
American Vandal on Netflix, the mockumentary about who drew Dix on the cars.
As everyone is saying, it's very funny.
It's worthy of your time.
Okay.
That's all I got.
I've got two for this.
Yes, I watched the documentary, The Man Who Would Be Polka King, which is an older documentary
at this point.
You wanna watch the Jack Black adaptation also on Netflix?
Well, maybe I did, and maybe those are my two.
Oh, all right.
Sorry, I thought it was our podcast.
You wanna come to the doctor with me, by the way, any interest in that?
Absolutely not.
No.
Just for moral support?
I had a friend like that in high school where like one is once he got his license
He's like would you mind just come with me to like my my grandma's funeral or whatever it's like he couldn't be alone
Like I why would I ever go to your grandma's funeral? Well, I'll tell you what you come to the doctor with me out by ice cream after
I
Can buy my own ice cream, but it's nice when another man buys it for you
Didn't you learn anything in WeHo last night, so I listen I watch the man who would be polka king
which is a really, really fascinating documentary.
It's very short, it's a little over an hour, I think.
I loved it.
I thought it was great.
I thought it was a great portrayal of this guy.
I'm blanking on the guy's name, but he was the polka king
of Pennsylvania.
Became essentially a national celebrity
when the polka craze was happening in the 80s.
Is this who John Candy was portraying in Home Alone,
the polka king of the Midwest?
I'm sure it was an adaptation of that guy.
you know what I mean like we're a play on that but what happens is he has this
idea that he'll have people invest in him for his dream to create a polka
empire because his fans are very loyal he then says I'll give you 20 % interest
on your returns the banks offering you six people do it and of course it
spirals out of control. He can't keep up with it. It turns into a pyramid scheme. He's robbing
Peter to pay Paul. That whole thing ends up going to jail for a few years. But what I liked about
the documentary was there was an interesting, there's no doubt that something shady was going on
with him in my own head. But I did like that they kind of took a balanced approach to it, where some
of the people were saying he's human scum. He's the worst person on planet earth. He took advantage
of us. And then other people are saying, no, there were a lot of people that actually made
their 20 % and the people that are pissed off right now were the ones that were being very greedy
and actually trying to take advantage of him by putting way too much money in to get way too
much money back. So, you know, it's always more interesting when it's a little bit of a balanced
perspective and it's not just saying this guy's the bad guy. The movie does that too. I thought the
They also didn't let them off the hook.
The movie was okay.
The documentary is better than the movie.
I mean, the documentary, the pacing of the doc is better.
The unfolding of the story is better in the doc.
The movie starts jumping into things so quickly
that I'm like, are they just assuming we've all seen
the documentary already?
Because if I hadn't watched the documentary,
I would have been like, wait, what's,
why is he asking these people for an investment seven minutes
into the film?
like right. But Jack Black delivers, he's great. Jenny Slade delivers, she's great. Jason Schwartzman
delivers, he's great. It's, you know, it's not a bad movie. Is it supposed to be funny? Yeah.
In fact, the documentary starts very jovial and funny and odd and then it takes like a real hard left
turn and get super dark and I was kind of sad that the movie didn't do that, too.
The movie keeps its spirit throughout and some really dark stuff happens, like I wanted
the movie to go a little deeper into that tone -wise, but it's not a bad film, but I would
suggest watching the documentary first, though.
All right.
Yeah.
So, there's your movie corner.
Fantastic.
Why don't we just get into what we're reviewing today?
I love it because we're scary stuff.
No, no scary stuff today.
All right.
And no, no interesting news doing shots as dark this week due to the untimely death of
John Mahoy.
Yeah.
We did.
I'll do a quick crane, I'll do a quick crane shot.
So I'll do a line, one of my favorite lines that I want to mention on the show.
At some point in the series, Frazier has sex with Roz when they're both feeling drunk
and vulnerable. And they both regret it and remain friends. But in the next season,
they're arguing. And Roz tells Frazier he's got an ego when it comes to sex. She's like,
here, ego is so big. And he goes, I don't remember hearing any complaints, Roz. In fact, I recall
someone using the term stallion like. And Roz goes, I never said that. And Frazier goes,
was, whoa, one of us said it.
It's a very funny joke.
He's referred to himself as Italian, like,
during sex.
During sex.
That's funny.
It's hilarious.
It's very funny.
You've told me it within the week, so I'm not laughing.
Well, I told you, yeah, I told you a week ago,
and you stepped on the punchline when I told you
by going, he had sex with Ross.
Well, it threw me for a loop.
But I did say the time I was going to say it again on here,
So I don't want to make it sound like I'm just repeating things.
We have a better friendship than that.
We do.
We're talking today about, let's say two films,
Blade and Blade Trinity.
Jesus Christ.
We're not talking about Blade Trinity.
I haven't seen it.
We're talking about Blade and Blade II cruise control.
That's the title of it, correct?
Yes.
It's just called cruise control.
It's not called Blade II cruise control.
I had seen both Blade and Blade II in their theatrical releases and not since.
So it was kind of like watching them with fresh eyes.
And I thought they were both really good pictures, they're awesome.
Blade, and I watched a little bit of the supplements, David Goyer, actually, even though I haven't
watched Blade Trinity yet.
I watched him on the Blade Trinity disc because when I looked up the little set that I have you can get all three of these movies for ten bucks
I have him on a lura. I have it on a DVD four pack in the fourth movie
You know those ones where it's like yeah, yeah the the four sections on the front and the fourth movie is the TV
Blade movie wow that was the pilot for the show TV show
So the full length feature, the feature like the pilot,
starting sticky fingers from Onyx.
Really?
As blade.
Where did this air?
It was on like, you know, USA or one of those.
Before every secondary channel became an artistic studio
making detailed.
Prestige picture.
Yeah, it was one of those things.
David Goyer is very full of himself in the supplements. He's also did many, many things
since your precious Batman versus Superman, et cetera, brilliant. Yeah, yeah, I couldn't
agree less. His pomposity, because they led him direct the third one, it reaches such
a level that on the supplements of the third blade picture, Trinity, Goyer, the writer
So, when I looked up the, I got this Blu -ray box set for literally ten bucks on Amazon.
I think now maybe it's fifteen, all three movies.
I just looked up a review of the set because I like to know if there's a great documentary on there,
I want to know about it.
Sometimes the documentaries are like, they were made up of, they were made up of, they were made up of,
at the time of the movie and it's just promo shit you don't want to watch and they were like whatever
you do with this set there's a lot of great material to get into make sure you check out this
boyer on boyer and boy did i it was something else that is magical yeah but um and also clearly all
this stuff was done before blade trinity was released and shot on because he is describing blade trinity
as if it is the jewel of the trilogy.
Well, it was supposed to be blade trinity.
Yeah.
First of all, look, my B -foot blade trinity is this simply,
I'm not here to see blade's new partners.
Right.
And Jessica Beale and Ryan Rounds got a lot of screen time
blade through three, they're part of the team.
Now, I'm fucked that.
I don't want a blade team.
I want blade.
A lot of noise happening, right?
A lot of noise.
And here's what's weird, nobody lives above me
and we both just heard a thump on the ceiling, right?
That's true. So what the hell is happening? Santa Claus?
Oh, God. Uh, I got to get my shit. I got to get out of this place. Anyway, I punched up a movie once with
Pat and Oswald and he was, he had some stories about Blade Trinity, but he said, I think they're probably online somewhere.
He tells them in his act talks about like just this massive cloud of weed smoke emanating from Wesley Snipes's trailer.
or blade, or Wesley Snipes would only answer to blade.
He stayed in the character of Blade, and then everyone else just kind of bonded together
because Snipes was in the early stages of losing his mind, which have now gone further.
Snipes is one of the people forget because, you know, I doubt Millennial's even know who
Wesley Snipes is, unless it's because of tax evasion.
right I mean he was a huge star huge who as far as I'm concerned was never great in anything he
was great and like white men can't jump and you know maybe in comedies he kind of came to life
but he's a good president shitty movies yeah but I mean he had a presence but like he there's
something so like unknowable about him he doesn't he didn't have like a star quality I never
knew anything about him. I've never seen him interview. Yeah, I don't know. He's an odd duck. Right. He's
fine and blade. I mean, he's, I don't know, that is the part. But like with all these superhero things,
there's not a lot he can really bring to the table. But yeah, like his little, you know,
smiley does and his little quips are kind of funny. But I think he's great in blade. I think that's
a hard part to play.
It is.
And I'm not saying it to be contrary.
I'm just saying, I like him a lot in that role.
I think it's the role he was born to play, a role developed for one LL cool, Jay.
Really?
Yeah.
Not, I love LL, but I would not, that's too distracting for me.
I agree.
Uh, I, I, well, that's, the blade, now blade Trinity, even though we're not, well, I guess
we know we are.
Well, let's start at the beginning.
We're hopping around.
Now let's talk about who the man blade is.
Blade is a man whose mother, whilst pregnant with him,
was attacked by a vampire.
She dies, blade lives,
and he's got all of the strengths of vampires,
none of the weaknesses.
He's a day walker.
He is not affected by sunlight.
And the guy who kind of keeps his cue, if you will,
who keeps him in weapons and keeps him healthy,
is Chris Christopherson, who kind of steals these movies.
I love Christopherson.
He's awesome in them and has the funniest line out of the whole
Shabang is in two when he refers to Ron Pearlman as Nipplehead.
No, Tidhead.
No, definitely Nipplehead.
Okay, because he calls, then he calls somebody else Tidhead in one point.
Okay.
He uses the term Tidhead in one of the movies.
Are you, are you sure you're not just thinking of Nipplehead?
I watched this yesterday.
Blade, you watched Blade 1 and Blade 2 yesterday?
I watched blade one two days ago blade two yesterday and he never says tithead. He said he but he does say nipple
All right, and I think you might be thinking of nipple head look
I've I've I've I've I've concocted crazier in my head before I show you. Yeah, I know
Anyway blade in the original
Is kind of going after one one villain who runs the underworld of vampires and that villain is played by Stephen Dorff
Who once publicly said he wanted an, he wanted an origin movie for Deacon Frost.
Of Deacon Frost. Yeah, he said he felt that there was an origin film there.
Holy cow.
Dorf, I mean... There's another guy that was huge.
Yeah, he, I don't, I don't remember him being huge, but he popped up and stuff.
He was certainly a good looking guy.
He had charisma and just never quite.
He was set.
He was on his way to being the next Ethan Hawke for sure, to be another Ethan Hawke, yeah.
And it just didn't turn over.
Was it a drug flame out, a temper flame, it seemed to have an ego, obviously.
I don't know what happened door.
He came back in that Sophia Coppola movie somewhere, which was excruciatingly boring.
I mean, he's in stuff.
It's not like he's not working, but he's not, you know,
I think they thought that kid started in the gate
for Christ's sakes when he was like 12th.
Right.
Great hard movie.
Never saw the gate.
Oh, we should do a commentary.
All right.
But yeah, Blade 1 was directed by this guy,
Steven Norington, who I looked up and kind of didn't direct
again, which is nuts because it's really visually incredible
to the extent that Guillermo del Toro,
who directed Blade 2, talks at length about how he didn't have to do much work
because Norengton had done such an amazing job as a visual stylist and
everything. And then Gamma D 'Oltoro probably went best director and Stephen
Norengton I assume is eating fish and chips somewhere. Now if it was the 90s
right now it would cut to a commercial of E true Hollywood story. The Blade curse.
Yeah. Everybody's gone down. Pat and Oswald never did another vampire movie again.
That's true.
Yeah, it's Blade 1. The most memorable scene by far is the opening blood rave.
It's awesome.
It's just an awesome scene. Like, you can't look away from it. It looks incredible.
To the point that they reference it in two, they walk into a rave and blades like again.
That kind of thing.
Yeah, my favorite part in one is when when they're like torturing him
Yes, and I do you know he's becoming weak and whatever and then he like breaks out of the torture stuff
And he's gonna go kill all the vampires and
Christopher's and I believe is the one that goes you need these and throws them the sunglasses. Yeah, that fly
I'm getting chills fly through the air and slow motion. He catches him the second he catches him the techno music kicks in
Yeah, it's a great thing.
You're like, go ahead.
be the hugest Del Toro fan. I thought that I was. I like to say that I really love him, but
there's something so hollow about his movies that they're all visuals. They are incredible visuals,
and that's enough for me. But I never, including the shape of water, which is supposed to be his big
emotional movie, I didn't feel anything in it. So I prefer Blade 1. I know you said you prefer Blade 2.
to. Blade 2 has way cooler creatures, effects, etc. But there's something about the story
of Blade 1 that just works better. It's a tighter script to me.
I'll say the same thing I say about John Wick. I think John Wick 1 is a better story, but
I enjoy watching John Wick 2 more. Okay. It's because Blade 2 does exactly what John
on which chapter two does.
They take everything you know, and they're like,
but now what if you got to see all the stuff
you didn't get to see?
Right.
And that's very cool.
And Deltour does a really good job
of introducing the characters into the movie,
the second one.
I love that it opens with him rescuing Whistler.
Yes.
I love that it's what's called the design of the vampires,
or those like, whatever, those mutant vampires,
that's a very, I forget what they're called,
but that's a cool design.
And it's cool stuff.
They do an autopsy in the middle of it,
that's like incredibly disgusting
and goes on and on, it's got great effects.
And what's this face is greater than, too?
Do I read this, Norman Reedus?
Yeah, I'm indifferent to him, but you're like,
this scrappy, I didn't know he'd been acting for so long.
Yeah, he's been around for a while,
but I liked him and I also like,
I also, here's my one gripe with Blade II,
and with most vampire movies.
And this is what I like about
one of the cool things in the frite night,
I'll get to that after this, but in Blade II,
and a lot of vampire movies is I get it.
The vampires drink blood.
I get it.
It's not the only thing you'd ever eat.
Do you know what I mean?
Okay.
So there's like, you want a scene of Blade
They'd sitting down at Zankoo chicken and having a meal.
Well, Blade does eat regular stuff.
He just gets those shots.
But like every scene with the terribly old vampire
who's like the head of the, whatever, his daughter.
You know, he's the daughter that betrays him or whatever.
Every scene where he's eating,
it's like plate with a blood shaped like steak on it.
Glass of blood.
Blood, jello for dessert.
gets up from the table, gets into a blood hot tub.
You're right.
It's just, look, I need vitamins to survive.
There's a shit in a blood toilet.
Yeah, it's like, just have, which is one of the cool things
in Fright Night, and they talk about this in the documentary
about it.
Chris Sarandon says that he pitched to the director.
He was like, I pitched, what if he's always eating fruit?
and he goes, you know, vampires or bats, maybe at this one point, this guy had some fruit
batting him or something. And it's a cool detail. He sucks blood, he has to do it, but
that he's an apple, he's eating an orange at one point. Break it up a little bit.
I certainly get why in a vampire movie you'd want to have the meeting blood. It's visually
cool. It's what you know about vampires. I've never had any issue with it, but if you need
And Dracula sitting down at Pizza Hut, you write it, you know, write the movie you want
to see.
Pizza Hut Dracula, a Jotaroza film, coming to certainly not a theater near you.
Pizza Hut Dracula, PhD bitch.
That's his catchphrase.
Yeah.
And here's the thing, he delivers pizzas for pizza and then he drinks the blood of the
people he's delivering them to.
The only thing crazier than the breadsticks is me.
Yeah, so that's crazy breadsticks.
Is that Papa John's?
That's it.
I believe little seizures is crazy bread, where they question the quantity of the food.
Crazy, crazy.
Yeah, they always big in our house and I even as a kid every Sunday night we would get you know
Pizza pizza little Caesars and I would be like mom
Don't you think two large pizzas for five dollars like what what could the ingredients?
Even as a kid something didn't sit right with me and it wasn't awful
But you did wonder what they had to be making money off it
So what did they use I worked in little Caesars? I thought it sucked
Okay, I thought their pizza sucked. I haven't had it recently. It might be good now. I mean for the price
It's but a lot of food if that's what you want. I grew up on the east coast
So I had a lot of real pizza that I could get to and if it wasn't if you weren't gonna get real pizza
Yeah, it was pizza hut and nothing else
Everything else was like you eat because pizza was it so it is it's its own thing. It's weird
Yeah, I got I never had a beef with pizza. I haven't been in years. I always like those big
dark red cups that they offer.
Yeah, yeah, it's great.
That smoky atmosphere kind of feels like a meeting room
for the departed with a salad bar in it.
It's a great pizza that sit down was great.
And then they went to pizza at buffet for a while.
That was awesome.
But pizza's its own thing.
It's like getting a chicken mcnugget.
You're like, I don't expect this in any way
to taste like the other chicken things.
Correct.
Whereas Domino's and Papa John's and Little Seasers,
it's all edible, but they try
to make a real pizza yeah and you're like don't try guys you're not just stop
right just make a fucking big puffy cake that you put sausage on top of now I've
never had this but have you ever gotten one of like the sweet pizzas like
cinnamon pizza I remember I even ordered a pizza in ages I remember being on the road
with Bill Burr uh -huh years ago when I sat around with him and the commercial for
the dominoes, Oreo pizza came on or whatever. And he went on such a rant of disgust. Like in whatever bar
we were sitting in, it ruined it. I couldn't even, I could never even look at it again. Right. It
was such a convincing rant of disgust. Yeah. Like what is happening in this country that this is
what people are eating. Yeah. And that was the end of it for me. Fair enough. I never had one. I don't
I don't think I ever had a synastic
or anything of that nature, but.
Well, I'll tell you this, and I don't like it.
I don't like it.
I like a savory and a salty versus a sweet.
Always a meat and potatoes guy over dessert and cake.
Don't give me a thing that makes me think
of a saucy sweet pepperoni flavor.
And then I bite it and it tastes like
fucking oatmeal cookies.
I hear you.
Get out of my face with that.
I don't want that.
I hear you.
It's got frosting cheese on it.
It's disgusting, how do I face?
Anyway, so Blade, you prefer two to one, I prefer one to two, but I think anyone could
agree, any fan of vampire movies would have to agree, Blade and Blade two are definitely
a cut above in terms of these pictures.
There are cut above the mythology makes sense, the visuals are great, the kickboxing is great,
the fighting, which you don't usually get in these movies.
And the special effects are great.
Two particularly came out at a time where that CGI was just
becoming really looking good.
It looked great.
And some of the effects, especially at the end
of one suffer a little bit, and they show you,
there's what I used to love about new line.
They used to do platinum series DVDs, which
were almost like criterion level supplements.
I keep saying supplements, Jesus Christ.
and they had a full discussion with everyone on what worked and what didn't work
about blade. They're like laughing about how bad the original ending was and
they were like boy people hated this ending. They were like people were
polite enough to stay till the credits to give us their thoughts but you could
tell they all wanted to leave kind of thing. But and they show you it in full on the
DVD and Stephen Dorf just turns into a big oozing mass of blood and the blood is
like coming at Wesley Snipes, they were like everyone loved Steven Dorf and the second
he became a pile of blood. And we all knew this might not work. People just really turned
against the movie and they show you the whole thing. Then in the midst of the blood, like
a little like cheesy almost like a max headroom graphic of Steven Dorf appears in the blood
and he's like, having fun blade, enjoying yourself blade.
It's so stupid.
Nobody wants a caddy vampire.
No.
And then, you know, what they want
of doing, he cuts dwarf and half,
and then you see him stretch and the blood
kind of pulls them back together.
It's much cooler, but it's also kind of dumb too.
All right, blade one and blade two.
Take your pick.
They're both excellent blade three kind of sucks.
I think it's watchable.
But it's not great, and it was supposed to be the peace -steely -resistance, if you will,
because he fights Dracula in it.
No.
What a cool idea.
Blade's going to finally face off with the number one vampire of all time.
And man, they just...
Is it Pizza Hut Dracula or a regular?
I think that is the problem, is that it's Pizza Hut Dracula.
Right, right.
it. So I was desperately trying to think of I want to suck your insert here. Yeah,
something. Anyway, yeah, that's that's your blade films people. We love you. Good to
see you. By now, I believe I will have announced it by the time this comes out, but I'm big
tour in April. The Jota Rosa in Bloom tour for spring time going all through the Northeast
in the some of the Midwest and whatnot, dates will be on my website, joderosainfo .com,
and of course I'll be posting things about it as well on Instagram and Twitter.
Joderosa comedy on both of those. Folks, we are stockpiling these a bit because Joe is about
to go to New York City. I don't know when this will air, but February 26th, Monday, 9 .30, 8 .30
central. May have already happened. If so, drop February 26, add seven days to it. We're
going to air 13 weeks in a row, living biblically on CBS. That first week, you're going to see
Mr. Joe DeRosa in prime time. I'm very excited about that. It's a very funny show. It's a
very interesting show. It's about something. I hope you check it out. I am on Twitter and Instagram
at the Patrick Walsh. We'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.