Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only, games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as non -mustrable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning, or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Monthly 21 -plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberer, offer not available in all states,
term -supply, see Fanatic's fourth book app.
Hey there for your post Thanksgiving week it's you will see you in hell and we're here
to talk about some damn horror movies this week predominantly clue not a horror movie
or a thriller or a thriller a murder thriller a murder mystery all right I don't know that
it fits and after last week's plans trans I mean we're we might just be opening this
up to just move it.
It's a murder.
If it was serious, it would fit.
All right.
It's a murder film.
I don't need to say it.
I'll tell you this right off the bat.
I don't need your fucking lip.
I'll tell you what, I'm going to watch next week that week should maybe watch and you guys
can watch in advance.
It's on Netflix and it's called Cam.
And the trailer started after I watched Buster Scrugs and I was like, terrible thing looks
erotic.
It looks suspenseful.
It looks terrible.
It's got like a 96%.
Yeah, it's another Blumhouse movie when I watch it. I mean, it's like somebody that the line where she goes you stole my face
And now I'm gonna take it back. Yeah, oh, don't you want to know how that happens?
Not really
It's a similar to the line on the star is born when Sam Elliott goes you stole my voice
You stole my voice. He says it to Bradley Cooper or Lady Gaga
Yeah.
Goops.
I was talking to Clue Star, Martin Moll this week, who is friendly with Sam Elliott.
Who is Clue Star?
Clue?
The movie we're doing.
Clue.
I thought you were saying somebody's name, Clue Star.
I was like, no.
Who the hell was that?
I talked to him a little bit about the picture because I thought, you know, I'm not going
to ask a 75 -year -old man to guest on the podcast, but he might have some stories, and he had
some great stories.
Oh, awesome.
Not really sure.
Yeah.
But I worked with both Mole and Leslie and Warren,
Miss Scarlet this past week on The Cool Kids.
They were awesome together and she's coming back.
How's L .A .W. look in these days?
She looks gorgeous.
I picture her just as the hottest like older woman of all time.
She is stunning and I thought that she was like 55 maybe.
She's 72.
Yeah.
She looks fantastic.
Well holding together not that you you know that you can't look fantastic in your 70s
I just was pretty shocked by it. I mean these days anything's possible. Yeah, and it was not a
Not that it's my place to say but it didn't appear to be a
Medically helped appearance like you often see and in this town. Yeah, it appeared to be with a real deal
I was just talking to my doctor. I think Vicky Lawrence looks fucking fantastic. She's 69. Great. Joy Bayhard
Yeah, there's like 77. Yeah, it's amazing sharp as a tack. I told my doctor that recently. Yeah, doc
I want to look tight when I'm 72 without surgery. How can I look tight? Yeah, changing everything you're doing? Is that what you said?
Yeah, I immediately dropped him as a doctor. I said sure. Well, you're quick get out of my face. Second opinion
Yeah, we're gonna be talking about clue
So we're gonna be doing the usual things we do.
It's after Thanksgiving,
you've probably put on some LBs sitting around the house,
maybe take it to the treadmill with you.
Get up off your ass, work off that cranberry sauce
and the candy, remember how amazing the candy dams
were that I brought to your Thanksgiving that one year?
I don't like candy dams, so I didn't eat any.
I didn't eat any.
You did a nice job, they looked nice
and everybody said they were good,
but I don't like candy dams.
Like the one thing I've ever cooked
and it was absolutely perfect and delicious.
I don't like candy games.
I like a sweet potato baked,
but once you take it out of that context, I'm out.
So maybe I should have wrapped 20 sweet potatoes
in tin foil, baked them for five minutes
and brought them over.
You would have preferred that.
It takes about an hour to properly bake a potato,
but yeah, yeah, I'm sorry.
Sorry if I don't like a side dish
that is marshmallows on top of it.
Yeah, sorry.
I didn't know it was a dairy queen right now.
I thought we were having dinner.
All right, all right, all right.
Joe and I are here a couple of days prior to Thanksgiving.
I still have to work this week.
Just nothing in the tank, folks.
I'm, you know, I become like narcoleptic,
but also insomniac.
You know, I'll sit down at the kitchen table
fall asleep and then I go to bed, I can't fall asleep. I just, I don't know where I'm
at, whether I'm coming or going. See, you know, when I, when I'm overworked, I don't get
narcoleptic, I become a necrophiliac. Okay. Which I can't explain.
As like a stress reliever. Maybe? Yeah. It's, I don't even know I'm doing it. Yeah. You
know what I mean? I do. Isn't there, aren't there a couple horror film, we saw one at
that Columbine Film Festival where they were fucking at corpse. That was real unpleasant.
Like a beautiful day noon Joe and I sit in there watching three people fuck a corpse
Was like what we've made some wrong choice and we've been yeah, we've been drinking since like 6 30 a .m
Yeah, there are screening was at 8 a .m
It was just was it called like the passion of Anna Fritz or something she was like a celebrity the body of Anna the corpse of Anna
Corpse of Anna Fritz. She's a big movie star. It's in a car accident
and these guys are like,
she's here, we could all fuck this movie star.
I mean, just a, who thought,
imagine telling your parents
that you came up with this movie.
Imagine telling your parents you're in it.
Yeah.
Oh, honey, you got your first role.
What is it?
I play a corpse like these guys, fuck.
Then I wake up.
I guess you just don't tell them.
You just treat it like you're doing porn.
Let mommy and daddy find it when they do a Google search.
Is the movie necromantics?
six. Is that about sex with dead people? Don't you have it? No. Necromancy, you have
something called that, I think. Necromicon? I don't think I do. The Book of Necromicon
or something. I saw it over here. It's why I'm talking about it. I think you're thinking
of the Matrix starring Neo. I don't know what you're, no, it's right there. Necromicon. Oh,
no, that's Necronomicon, the Book of the Dead. That's not, oh, I'm sorry. I see where you
might be confused when I said necromicon,
and it's actually necronomicon.
Well, it's not about, I could see why you,
be looking at me like I'm insane.
It's not about corp sex.
What's it about?
It's about the book of the dead,
bound in human flesh.
Okay.
Speaking of mommy and daddy, what's that?
I said, I said mommy and daddy find it
on their Google search,
but it triggered something in my head.
Yeah.
These fucking sling commercials
with offer men and what's your name?
With offer men in Malaylee?
Yeah.
They're goddamn disturbing.
I ain't saying them, what are they about?
It's the two of them like being like
one party with mommy and daddy, we're slingers.
And that's the whole joke, like with slingers, like swingers.
And not only is it weird and gross
cause it sounds like they're talking to you as their child.
Right.
It's the 87 ,000 thing I've seen Nick Offerman do in comedy.
He's a good dramatic actor.
I enjoy seeing him in dramas.
The 87 ,000 thing I've seen him do in comedy that is just completely derivative of a thing
Will Farrell already did.
It's the fucking member of the hot tub thing.
We like fresh meat.
It's that.
It's just that bit.
Love us, that bit.
Yeah.
Yeah, people love the shit out of Ron Swanson and Parks and Rec and that whole thing.
Ron Swanson, and it is Ron Burgundy.
I have a great deal of respect for those people in that show.
I get it.
I did not laugh at that show.
I did not enjoy it.
I think the office is far superior, at least the first five, six years of the office.
And I respect everybody involved and as I said, I like Offerman as a dramatic actor, but
I mean, his comedy, it's literally just, he just does what Will Ferrell does.
I haven't done a lot of laughing at all from an eye. I'll grant you that I
Got a thing with him. He was kind of a prick to a friend of mine once and it's it's really something about stuck in my crawl
Tell me about why this card dead. It's not my story to tell. I'll let him tell you when I'll when we see the friend
I'll have him tell you
You can't just tell the story and not name the I don't think I remember exactly what it is
And I'm afraid I'm going to tell it and it's going to look like I'm an asshole
Okay, because I can't I'm not telling it right all right, but I trust me if you heard it you'd be annoyed
It was one of those things like he made a joke to him and offer me just kind of stared at him like okay, yeah
It's like dude be a human being for Christ sakes actors get this thing where they they don't know how to be human beings, and it's really
Tough it's tough
I'm at Bob Sagitt last night did a comedy show with him. Yeah, great guy
I've always really nice guy the nicest guy in the world three minutes into meeting him
I said he was making dinner plans with somebody and they said Bob in the meantime till they're available
What do you say you and I go out? We get to know one another yeah, and I jumped right in he's like yeah
I'll bring the wife are you single? I go of course I'm single. That's why I'm asking you out. What are we doing here?
He's like all right. Let's go out and try to score man
Right fine. Well, we're not gonna really go out, but he yeah, it's a guy he goes. Yeah, I get it
I don't know you. It's weird. We're just joking around. I'm at Sagitt maybe an oh four. He came to Saturday night live
And he was outside and it's the kind of thing where like you bring him
You think you should bring him up because he's celebrity
But then that place was so fucking snobby that you were worried that he wouldn't be cool enough and I was like
I don't know man if I can just let you up like you do it if it was Paul McCartney or something, but he's like um well
I'm here to see Billy is that cool like he's like I can call up to him
I just, I'm here to see Billy.
Like, who do you mean?
I realized Green Day was hosting that week.
So I'm like, this guy's here to see Billy Joe.
I'm strong.
They were, you know, still it was American Idiot days.
Call up, sure enough.
They're like dear, dear friends.
I bring him up.
He's like,
ah!
Oh, fuck yeah!
He's friends with everybody, yeah.
I went to his birthday party one time.
Fucking beach boys were there.
Norman Lear was there.
was that was it was insanity guy knows everybody he's just a real nice guy
I think everybody just really likes him talk to him this is where my comedy
knowledge comes in handy like I was talking I was like I remember the first time
I saw you do comedy it was when I was about 10 or 11 and full house was still on
and and I recall the fucking joke and he was like yeah he's like yeah mom
upside down was dad's favorite thing I was like yeah dude I remember that me and
my friends could believe that you were like a dirty comic yeah nice guy very nice
guy very funny too who said was very very funny now Joe you've got
Gardeiros snack mix here I actually not only did I not know they still made it
I thought it was a Missouri only treat because I only had it in Missouri when I was a
kid it's every bit as delicious as it always was but still it all boils down to the
pretzels and the brown chips what are the brown chips and why are they so good
They're like pieces of a rye bread.
Okay, wait, what's that brown bread called?
Not rye.
Pumpernic?
Pumpernickel.
Yeah.
Because everything else in here is kind of worthless.
But the pretzels and the brown aren't there.
They made a, I was with her dear friend Pinkstone
once in a store, and I heard him exclaim,
finally, like my dream come true, grabs a bag,
all brown chips.
Oh shit.
Yeah.
Yeah, he goes, I've been waiting forever for this.
They finally did it.
That in a, I think a hummus?
Incredible.
Oh, fuck the hummus.
That in a nice orange juice.
Salty sweet.
Yeah.
You go with salty sweet.
Do they have different flavors?
Do they do like an herb and?
They did, the bag just said all brown chips.
I don't know if it had a flavor.
That's when you bought these today.
Were there only original recipe
or were there different flavors?
Pat, I love that you think that I was in any state of mind,
even look at the bag.
I just grabbed it off the thing on my way to the register. I was like this this will do
I hope the fans are enjoying me chewing directly into the microphone people don't like it
We've gotten shit for it before I try to pull it away
But then I also have to offer my great comments. How many mimosas in are we? I'm feeling it
What what what we have here is the end of the bottle. Oh?
No, we're out of them
Well, Jesus. That's a problem. Did you hear that reaction? That's a problem. You seem crestfallen
I don't throw the word crestfallen around. I got to be honest with you. It's why I bought the 12 pack of Miller Highlife. Oh, yes, I'm going drunken after this.
Now do we do we and I do you and I get to keep drinking and you got to go home and do shit. All I got to do is take a cab for 10 minutes from here at 4 .50
All right, so we can hang for a little while. It's about fucking time, you know, we hung yesterday. We didn't I went and got
But I got dinner with you while you bitched about your job.
It's like I don't even exist anymore.
But I hang it can be a bitch about you know, I'm kidding.
Pat I'm kidding.
It's just fun.
That was a good little anecdote.
It was it was one of the best I've ever heard.
Pat texted me and said I can't never mind.
Let's move on.
I can't get too deep in it.
Yeah.
Let's not get into it.
I also shared an anecdote with you that I can't get into.
Right.
But it was a real bitch session over there at the Tamo Shanner.
Yeah.
Chowing down on fucking fried chicken and prime rib.
The chicken wasn't fried.
It was organic and healthy.
Was it good?
It came with kale.
It was very good.
But as you said, $28.
Places over.
No fucking chicken.
You can get a hot chicken over at Vaughn's for $6.
Two podcasts now.
We've bitched about the prices at the Tamo Shanner.
And I think it's valid.
I don't know that it has global appeal.
but guess how much the shrimp cocktail is?
12. 18. No. 18. No. And it's not even like giant shrimp. By the way, the chicken you get at a
rouse, you can get organic for $8. And it's no different than the chicken you're getting at the
tank. Look, as I want, that's what I'm saying. Which size does it come with? They do great size.
There's none of them. It comes with no soup, no salads. Yeah, the waitress just goes,
was it only comes with the kale walnut, whatever the fuck it was, it was something nobody
wants.
Some of the kale flakes.
Yeah.
And I've said to our dear friend Vince Avril, you know, about the tan.
I said there's a lot of ramsy no -nose on that menu.
I'm a big Gordon Ramsay fan.
The man in my opinion is the greatest chef in the world.
I have followed his recipes sort of and it has made everything I have cooked 10 ,000 times
better.
Okay, I can't imagine how good it is when he cooks it. He's a practical
Resipist. Yeah, but he knows what he's doing and he's got where he's got menu no knows
Yeah, he's like, you know, if there's pictures on the menu, get the fuck out
Okay, you know, I don't think he means that a diner, you know, but like at a restaurant
They don't got pictures at the time
Huh, I don't got pictures. No, they don't but he would have a
You're one example. I guarantee you he'd shit fit over that fucking
in 18 dollars shrimp cocktail, he doesn't approve.
He goes to a restaurant and he'll be like,
how much is a meal for just one person?
Appetizer, and he means appetizer dessert.
It'll be like 75 bucks.
He's like 70, are you fucking mad?
You know, so we didn't even get dessert in appetizers
and our meals were 60 dollars.
He would have a fucking shit fit over there.
He loses mind.
They're also at the higher end of like pints.
It's, again, a spine and Irish pub shouldn't be $8.
Their mixed drinks shouldn't be $14.
Ridiculous.
And it's kind of a low spielous thing, like this is not a super affluent neighborhood,
but all these bars, including our treasured roost, are overpriced.
The roost, I gotta go down in and have a talk with them, man.
This is ridiculous.
I think we're keeping them alive.
A shot.
We certainly were for a while.
A shot of whiskey is $7.
What the fuck is happening?
That's crazy.
like the well is six for a shot yeah no granted it's a nice poor place I'm going
today as boarders where you and I went prior to the night member for Christmas and
he's referring to when we went shopping at the mall they do a four to eight
happy hour every day just a tremendous happy hour Sunday all day and it is any
Any appetizer you want, including a spectacular nacho, five bucks.
It is well drinks for four, any beer for four.
They have CBD shots, or they did until very recently for five, which means you get high
for five dollars.
It's an amazing place, and it's in the heart of Hollywood.
It's always packed.
If you drop your beer prices a dollar, you'll have double the people.
People don't get it.
I never understood.
It's you know you gotta I'm dropping 20 bucks on the jukebox every time I go there
I've yet to hear a song I played where?
Roost. Oh, you got to do the app
Oh, yeah, now listen folks if you find yourself in the roost and you see a little special they have there
She's a $10 Miller high life in a shot of Jim Bean
That's a courtesy of me
It's a shit special. No offense. Well, I know but here's the thing my dear friend Nick Rutherford and I were in there
and we pitched them for about 30 minutes one night.
We chewed size ear off, size the owner.
Like, sigh, you gotta have a good shot beer special.
Make it 10 bucks even.
But you gotta have a good shot beer and she really took it
and then she did it and when I went in she was showing me
like, look, I did it, I did it, I was so excited.
Then you get it and it's a smaller shot
than the regular one they give you and a pony beer.
God damn it, this is my legacy I said to her.
I feel like that is a worse deal than buying a shot and a beer separately.
Well, that'll cost you 14, which is crazy, but at least you're getting the full service.
There's a bartender in there who mocks me.
Yeah.
She's my favorite bartender on the city, but she mocks me.
She goes, you want the little baby drinks?
Where do they get off?
Or do you want the big boy drinks?
We're keeping the place on the map.
Yeah. I think so. I think we're doing a lot of good for them.
We promote them every week. I'd love to take you if I could.
No, you never too, I wasn't done down to the place where I say on with the show and in
I'm doing so on with the...
It takes two seconds to thought before you leave.
Joe, one, no, gang, gang, gang, gang, gang, gang.
Oh, there you go.
You could've said Joe won Joe's,
but then you're getting too far away from even what they say.
There you go. I can't believe you never did that one for the Joan age, folks. I saw Eagles of death metal last night
I know you did
They were great. They were really great. I was a sweet frontman is
Amazing. He got pretty weird after that like
Mass shooting thing at one of their shows. He got a little weird start to get an online weird
But I think he got some help. What do you mean? What do you mean weird doing a lot of like weird public posts about shit?
But you know, a lot of people died at one of their shows. Yeah. Yeah. Now it's terrible. I think he had some mental stuff
But he got rid of it. He uh, he is an awesome frontman and he's an old school frontman
He's one of those guys that he's like he's like Ted Nugent style. He looks just he's grizzled man
He looks like he's 58 years old up there just killing it. Jesse Hughes. Yeah, I really I really enjoyed them man
They were they were a lot of fun. So pretty good documentary about them on HBO directed by an acquaintance of mine
and Colin Hanks, son of Tom.
Yeah, I always went to meet Colin Hanks.
Very nice guy.
He seems like a nice kid.
And I feel like if you're talking to him,
you kind of feel like you were talking to young Tom Hanks.
No difference.
Yeah.
Yeah, great guy.
Yeah, that's great.
All right.
I guess I'll take us down to Pat's movie corner.
I think I got enough here.
We're not going to do hold the dark that Netflix picture on here probably you're not going to watch that
I
Don't know what hold the dark is I have a dark song which was also on Netflix. Are we going to do that or no?
I don't even know what that is either I did I watched hold the dark all right. Let's skip let's just do two each
Let's let's skip hold the dark and and I'll skip a dark song and maybe we do those. Oh gosh, yeah, but the dark song is a very
We critically claimed new harm.
All right, I'll check it out.
So let's just do two.
I saw, and we're gonna do unsane on here, maybe.
We're gonna do upgrade on here, maybe.
Upgrade, we are.
Sorry, I still haven't watched it.
I'll watch it.
What the fuck is unsane?
It's a Soderberg picture, and in truth,
I didn't finish it.
I thought it was.
I can't even sit through that goddamn thing.
Okay.
You know, they all shot on the iPhone.
I don't have a fuck.
I don't want to watch it. I'll just do a couple TV shows here. I finished
succession on HBO. I had mentioned that before. I had heard that it got better
and better, and it did. I don't think it's even amongst the even approaching the
upper level of the HBO dramas of the past, but it's pretty entertaining. It's kind
of good juicy trashy fun. Brian Cox is great and at the whole cast is great. I
Um, there's mine.
Joe, I'll add it to bonus because that was so short.
Culture Shock is a new documentary.
There seems to be no rhyme or reason to win the air at.
It's like every couple of weeks, there'll be one.
First one was about freaks and geeks.
It's like a two hour documentary about freaks and geeks
interviewing almost all the key players.
Fantastic, I loved it.
Then they did what on Bring the Pain, the Chris Rock Special.
really. Another great documentary, a lot of great insight from people, including my friend Tony
Rock, brother of Chris, who I always wanted to ask about Chris, but I never did because I always felt
like, you know, sometimes brothers get weird, they're both doing the same thing. He doesn't care, man.
He opened right up about him and how great that special was, and it was very cool. Yes. Great story
about arguably the best stand -up special of our lifetime,
bring the paint.
I recommend them both.
They're great documentaries about things
you actually give a shit about.
I rewatched Return of the Living Dead.
Not much more to say.
We've all, we've discussed it, we love it.
It's an amazing horror film.
It's the birth of the running zombie
and it's actually done right,
whereas a lot of running zombie movies are done wrong.
It's just an awesome, awesome, old -school zombie movie and it's what a zombie movie should
be.
The zombie should be goalish and slimy and things.
That's what makes them fun, you know.
This shit about an infection broke out, now everybody has the rage, who cares.
I want to see a decomposing thing, but just don't rewatch, which I did, you know, for Halloween.
This is a while ago at this point. I just think it's a perfect fall horror movie, and I suggest you you put it in your cue if you can't
Haven't seen it in 25 years. You should get the shout factory. I have it. I haven't even opened the doc is fantastic
I want fantastic three episodes of a show called maniac on Netflix. Can't bring myself to hit play on the thing
It looks like the most pretentious, annoying fucking thing ever created.
Well, it is.
I just, as much, everyone I know is like, I just can't bring myself to watch it.
What's keeping me at a distance from it?
It's Jonah Hill, it's Emma Stone, two actors I generally like,
Cory Fukunawa, who did the first season of True Detective, which obviously was incredible.
And just something was not calling to me about it.
I sat down, I force fed myself three of them.
It may get better, it may not, I'll never know.
I mean, this thing was just joyless, miserable.
It looked kind of cool.
It also just sort of looked like a blade runner rehash,
but it's just comedy, right?
I think it is supposed to be a comedy.
There's nothing funny in it.
Oh, good.
It wasn't good.
I don't know what else to say. It looked like it cost people a great deal of money. It wasn't good
I can't bring myself to look at the fucking thing and isn't it just another one of these goddamn like
We go in your head and implant memories like total recall things
Pretty much. It's like can we were you know remove painful memories and stuff like that
It's a lot like very eternal sunshine influenced
But just not not holding me
All right, at all.
And Jonah Hill, he's trying to do that sort of gym carry thing,
of just like, I'll stare vacantly into space.
And that'll be like a deep performance.
But, you gotta have a little more than that going on.
Like, depressed on screen does not read,
unless you're bringing some other element to it.
Like, one of the most realistic portrayals of depression,
honestly, is Billy Bob Thornton and Bad Santa.
Yeah.
That's real depression.
You staring into space nobody needs to make a show about a guy staring into space because he's so depressed
No, you want to see an active depressive on on screen a guy or a girl who's who's acting they're acting out because of the pain
Yeah, I mean, it's just sitting and sulking. You're like well, Jesus Christ
What is this movie about a couch? This is right like catcher in the rye is is justly a famous book because it gets into the head
The mind of a depressed person and like how everything just seems phony to him and then everything else like it's it's all
These years later a classic book and deserves to be it's beautifully written gets you inside the brain of a depressed person a movie can't do that
You can't have a passive vacant
Staring into space protagonist. It just doesn't work. You have to give me something else to look at speaking of Jim Carey and
The utter dipshit. He's become oh, yeah
He wants him that show I
Refuse I answered that either I refuse
He gets the fucking Charlie Chaplin award for comedy yeah
This happened a few weeks ago based on what has worked from 25 years ago. I guess so. I don't know gets up
Of course turns it into a whole political speech thing whatever I can live with that. That's what people do
As he's trashing these modern times and these horrid
people in power and all this stuff, whatever.
He starts spouting off about how we all need to follow the ethics of a man like Charlie
Chaplin.
This is a guy who had to go to Mexico to marry his second 16 -year -old bride, so he would
not get charged on statutory rape.
Right.
Are these people, have they lost their fucking minds?
Do some minimal research under these people.
It's just insanity, it's insanity, be consistent, in some way be consistent.
And then as he's going on about, he actually says, we live in a society of capitalism
without conscience, fair enough, behind him hangs Charlie Chaplin Award sponsored by American
American Airlines, the cock -sucker -e -ist of all the cock -sucking airlines, American Airlines,
the worst of the fucking worst.
Now I hate them all, but why do you feel American Airlines is worse?
They're fucking terrible.
Do yourself a favor.
Google American Airlines incident.
And it's just the Chinese guy that threw up.
No, that was United.
Okay.
United is the only one I would say could potentially be worse than American Airlines.
American are never on time, not accountable for anything.
They're horrific, they're horrific.
Go and Google it, you'll see.
It's just thing after thing, after thing, after thing.
They got a video on there,
one of their airline attendants.
The guy almost hits a baby in the face
with a scroller by accident.
And then a guy's like, and the mom's crying,
like, you almost just hit my baby in the face.
And the guy's like, oh, right, shut up.
It's insane.
So anyway.
So then, and then he's also one of these guys that goes like, hey, you know, I don't,
all of this is an illusion, it's all fake.
Yeah.
None of this is real.
This is simulation.
Yeah.
Those guys are the best.
And I watched him say that once on a red carpet for something, Cameron was.
Oh, I saw that clip.
Yeah.
The report is so great.
He calls him right out.
He goes, well, clearly, Jim, you must think, I mean, you dressed up for this, so you must think
something of it.
Yeah.
But he gets up to get the award and he goes,
that was a very believable illusion.
What a fucking dildo.
You fuck Jim Carrey, fuck you, you piece of fucking garbage.
Oh my God, go fuck.
What the fuck?
This was Ace Ventura for Christ's sakes.
What happened?
What the fuck happened?
Ace Ventura.
H. Ventura is punk rock comedy.
It's amazing.
H. Ventura is next level shit.
Got no respect at the time.
I sat in that theater with my jaw on the floor.
I had never seen a living color.
I did not know who he was.
Couldn't believe my eyes.
And this guy now, in fury, it's me as he acts
like he's no longer capitalist.
He's not trying to make shit.
that he's making like direct to DVDs, shit.
He's just not getting the parts,
so now he's gonna play the capitalism card.
Yeah. Yeah.
Now, and this whole thing is he's like,
I mean, I think he says this in the acceptance speech.
He's like, he's like, you know, it's just,
no, no, this was another clip I saw,
where he goes, you know, it's just,
it's just life is, you know, it's just,
it's just the turns you take, man.
You know, man, like now all of a sudden,
I'm a painter and a political commentator.
And I just I just don't make in movies people just don't want to see him. Oh my God. You're still making movies Jim
We all we all know they're out there and
These are his brilliant commentaries by the way on in the midterm election day
He made a painting is always like Trump eating a dollar bill. Oh wow, I don't know the worst
The poster of Trump's face on a piece of bread coming out of a toaster and he goes. Yeah, that one's called your toast
applause
applause break oh god damn it you know I used to love entertainment weekly and I
was I was leafing through one today trying out my my new elliptical machine and I
said I'm canceling this subscription I'm canceling all my magazine subscriptions it's just every
interview is the same they don't go in depth. Entertainment Weekly people forget this I was the first
subscriber. I got the first issue when I was like nine years old. This magazine is puff
pieces after puff pieces after puff pieces. It's supposed to be an interview with somebody
about the movie and it's just like it's like an acceptance speech. Every article is well you know
working with Emily Blunt. Just the most incredible experience of my life. Then they talk to Emily
Blunt working with Lynn Manuel Miranda one of the most incredible experiences of my life
What was it like working with Rob Marshall the director of Mary Poppins returns Rob Marshall?
I mean one of the most incredible experiences of my life. Why am I reading this?
What am I doing? I get the magazine to the house so I'm like I guess I got to read it
What I'm reading about how great everyone wasn't a set of Mary Poppins returns. Yeah, what am I doing? Oh boy?
Everything is so bad.
Everything sucks.
I see the white cow, you know what I'm saying.
I got one more for the new movie corner.
Yes.
Finally saw the horror movie Dolls.
Never seen it.
I liked it very much.
I'll use the term I've used frequently
on this podcast in recent episodes.
it plays like a dark fairy tale.
Oh, you know, it's low budget.
So, you know, it's about dolls that come alive
and kill people, obviously, like,
but it's a little low budget.
So, you know, they have to succumb to certain techniques
that aren't the best, like where you see a person
getting drugged on a hallway,
but it's supposed to be the dolls dragging them
but you can't see them.
But there are also some cool stop motion sequences
with the actual dolls and it's just a fun, cool,
I guess it's early 90s horror movie.
It's a perfect VHS type of horror movie kind of thing you would have rented back in when you were in high school
I remember seeing it all the time. I feel like it might be like an eighty -seven, but I remember it might yeah
Might even be that old. Yeah, but I enjoyed it very much
All right, and then the leader actor in it was was really great
And I was like this guy's so charming. Who is he? I look him up. I was like oh, he's been all this and he's dead
Yeah, that's the worst you look up an actor that you like you're like when this guy's good. Who is he?
I want to see more and then he's dead. Yeah, okay. Anyway, we should be due for a
Puppet master littlest rike
Did you really soon? Shouldn't we? I bet that it's not already it's already like streaming and stuff all right
We should do that on the show. We should watch it. I've never seen any of the puppet master
I own those rikes and say I own all of them. I have a hard time sitting through them
I find them fun and charming, but they're not movies that are gonna in my opinion keep your attention. Yeah
But littlest rike is supposedly yeah madness like really vulgar and really violent ridden by the guy who did cell block 19. Yes
brawler and cell block 99 and the upcoming
vehicle huh?
You you call it cell block 19 a salt on
Brawler and cell block 99 I'm
Thinking of a salt on precinct 13. Yeah, sorry Joe
So sorry Pat, let me give you a little screaming and get the nails Joe's crucifying me because I said something wrong. Let me give you a little screaming and news psycho.
They released the trailer for leprechaun. Is it resurrection?
Well, listen, that's one of the first we ever did. You and me leprechaun like two days before Christmas.
Leprecon is not a good film. Leprecon returns, it's called, excuse me. Leprecon is not a good film.
The sequels are even worse. Progressively, they just get worse and worse and worse.
However, I will say this. I always let the franchise had potential. I thought the idea of a
demonic Leprecon was very cool and freaky and they did a remake or a new version of Leprecon
a few years back that the WWE film company produced for some reason, and they said it was
going to be back to getting it, making it scary, and all of a sudden I was excited
about that.
Terrible movie, because they turned the leprechaun just into this faceless thing that runs
around and eats people.
Like it doesn't, it's not a leprechaun, it's just like a weird demon that you don't give
a shit about.
So then they announced they're going to do leprechaun returns, and it's going to be a direct
sequel to the first film. Danny McBride, Halloween style. Okay. I'm like okay so
not great. Yeah so I'm like okay I'm excited about this. They said we're
recasting the role it's not gonna be Warwick Davis wasn't thrilled about that
but I thought all right maybe they're just trying to get the old movies out
everybody's head so they can rebrand this is frightening they said it's gonna be
scary it's gonna be this. I start the trailer up it's got the guy from Francis from
a Peewee's big adventure, who's in the original leprechaun.
I'm like, holy shit man, this might be pretty cool.
How's he looking?
He looks literally the same, all right.
And I'm like, okay, this is the shit man, they're doing it.
This looks like it might be all right.
Then the leprechaun pops out.
And this fucking thing starts going for jokes
that I can't even, I mean, these like jokes
that Leslie Nielsen would have scoffed at.
Uh, yet every write up I read about this thing, people are saying like, they bring the
horror back with a little bit of fun.
It's like, no, this is a slapstick fucking comedy with the tiniest dose of horror in
it.
I just don't understand, man, look, I got no beef with horror comedy, but why the fuck would
you make such a big deal out of re -launching this franchise, we're gonna do a direct sequel
to the first one.
We're gonna make it scary again.
We're going to write the wrongs of leprechaun in the hood and all those awful sequels
And then you make something that literally looks worse than any of those and also doesn't star war with Davis
So why does anybody want to see this now?
Do you remember any of the jokes?
One of them he's flying on a drone like one of those remote controlled helicopter drones
That's one of them, okay
That's that point I shut the trailer off
No, I don't remember any of the, yeah, it's like,
but it's literally not trying to go for the old audience
because it seems like you're slapping that in the face,
but you're also not gonna get anybody new
with the guy from Peewee's Big Adventure
and a leprechaun on a drone.
It's literally things like where the leprechaun will be like,
you know, I think you stole me gold,
so I'm gonna stick this stick up your hole.
And then sticks is stick, I mean, I'm making that up,
But it's that bad like and then he sticks as a stick up a guy's asshole. It's literally that bad. Yeah, it's fucking
You know what I want to say I want to see a fucking leprechaun movie starring Jim Carrey that'd really light me the fuck up as the leprechaun?
I mean why not as all the characters Jim because you're so you're so enlightened. Why don't you play everybody in the whole fucking movie?
This is a horror podcast. Do you ever say a little picture called the number 23 dog shit appalling?
Dog shit, sort of the beginning of the end really Virginia Maddenson
Rivals only Travolta in the realm of
Amazing come back from bad decisions. Yeah right back to horrible decisions
Yeah, they both won those Oscar I think the 12 to win for Pulp fixture is nominated whatever the fuck it was nominated
Didn't win Tom Hanks won for forest gum. She won for
Sideways, right
it. And it's like, dude, you just got her house was she almost lost her house. It's like
an amazing inspirational story about somebody like picking it up and making it work again.
Did she went for someone? Yeah. I would say undeserved. She goes right back to like, it's like,
what are you doing? You said yes to the number 23, but no to the Candyman sequel. Yeah.
The Candyman sequel was better. I got news for you. Yeah. People are always, she was
She was nominated. She did not win. That was at a time where people were taking chances with Jim Carey because he was so famous.
Little did they know he was spiraling out of control of making terrible movies. Yeah, because Judd Appetal said once about the cable guy.
He was like, I made it. I'm producing the next Jim Carey movie and he goes and then everybody was like, you don't like this.
Even though the cable guy's a masterpiece in my opinion.
Cable guys great time is time is the only real real way you can know how good
something is and this race like right now we're in this position where there's
a month and a half left in the year. What what are going to be the nominees for
best picture? I mean can they can they find five? They're allowed to nominate 10
can they find three? I guarantee two of them will be like cartoons. Yeah. But like when you look
back at like best pictures past, once in a while, the winner will be something that like stands the
test of time. More times than not, it's it's shit like the artist. The artist won best picture. Who
Who will ever watch the artist again?
What was that?
The silent movie?
Black and white silent movie with a French actor
and a dog.
It was like sort of cute for 30 minutes
and then insanely boring, but it is about an artist
who used to like get to do what he wants,
but now he doesn't get to make his art anymore
and he's sad and all these washed up people who vote
for the Oscars are like, that's my story.
I'm an artist who doesn't get to tell my tale.
So that's the best picture of this year. And if you take any of this shit seriously, you should be ashamed of yourself.
I get the things about voting and whatever I throw them right in the trash.
You want me to vote for you? I vote. I feel like at least I can get some good, you know, performances and good scripts up there.
I don't know, fuck it.
Writers, guild awards, I vote, sag awards, I vote. I'm like, yeah, I'd at least rather something good get a nomination.
But my vote's not going to make any difference just like what the world, but I do it.
You vote this year, John.
I tried to.
You've actually made sure I'm alive for the first time in my life.
I tried to vote.
What do you mean, trying to?
I've found it the last minute that, because I never got a California driver's license, I was not registered here,
and it was too late to do so.
I'm not hopped over to New York City.
Yeah, let me just get a quick flight.
I don't, I'm not registered in New York.
Well, I guess I am because I have a driver's license from there,
but I get my new license on December 14th.
But this was the first time ever in my life
that I was gonna vote.
And I felt really good about it.
I felt like I was doing the right thing.
And then watch the news for like two days
after I wasn't able to and immediately was like,
oh, it's pointless.
This is awesome.
And the lady walked over to our polling place,
you know, 7 .30 a .m.
and I hand my ballot over to the lady.
She's like, thanks, I filled it out at home.
I had a time.
Thanks, throws it in a box.
I'm like, you don't need to see my ID or anything.
Something struck me is very weird at a time
when everyone is up in arms about this shit.
I'm like, I put my ID in my sweat pants
because I assumed you'd need to check.
Let me tell you something.
You go to a Meba Records.
Yeah.
Yeah, you go to a Mibo record show, there are, there are six plane closed security cards.
That will tackle you to the ground.
If you try to steal the new mudhoney record or whatever, you go into vote.
It's like some soccer lady, that sells Girl Scout cookies that vote on dear to time.
It's absurd.
and I'm sure like my another straight white Democrat vote needs to be counted in L .A. I'm saying
People are getting fucked out of their vote
polling places are being shut down people are using bullshit to keep minorities from voting so check my ID for God's sake
I mean you can't you can't get out the door target without somebody scrutinizing your receipt. That's right
And I said, do you need me to see my ID?
Then her answer should be, yeah, I'd rather double check it.
She goes, nah, and turns over to somebody else.
And I go, yeah, he go in, can I show you my ID?
She goes, are you who you say you are?
I go, yeah, she goes, you're good.
I have a feeling, if I was a black guy,
they would have checked my ID.
I hate to be, I hate to take it there.
But she was just like, nah, I know, I see you.
You're good.
You got Peggy Bundy running the fucking it was gross. It was real gross
Anyway, folks
We're at the 50 minute mark. We haven't even graced up against this chatty today must be the
Eight memoses we've drank. Did you eat anything yet today? Just a couple guardados pretzels. I'm gonna be in bad shape later
We should go eat something
I
Fuck it. I gotta go all night here on this is my food
This is my food! Look what they did to your father!
That's what I'm gonna do to my kids when I have them.
We're gonna talk about Clue.
I work with Mr. Martin Moll and last week Lesley and Warren became a love interest for him.
In real life, not on the show.
Yeah, well he loves or he requested her.
And she was great in the part.
It's probably my favorite episode we've done.
It's a very heartfelt episode and it's extremely funny the A story and the B story are awesome
But mole and Leslie Ann Warren we shot this joke. We're probably not gonna air cuz I don't tend to love shit like this
But at the blow of one of the scene Martin goes, you know
You look a lot like Miss Scarlet from that movie clue and then she goes I that's so so crazy you say that cuz you remind me of Colonel mustard
Right we shot it the crew laughed
I don't like stuff like that. I ain't gonna put it in the show. I find it gross
but I like stuff like that.
There was a great one on last man's standing.
Come on man.
Where they go, Tim, why are you always
so into home improvement?
Did you see that?
I told you about that.
I know, I'm joking.
That's why I'm doing it.
Like I was, yeah, I can't then do
the club bed and also gripe about shit like that.
Why are you so into home improved?
They did the job twice on last month.
But she couldn't have been more delightful.
She was a little odd which I liked
She has kind of like a Diane Keaton thing like
She can make any line interesting and like in infuse it with like some cool weird shit. I
Loved her. I love Martin Moe and I told Martin when we were about to shoot
I was like
Dude, I got a I watched clue this weekend. I got to be honest with you
You look better now at 75 than you looked in clue when they were 42 and he goes, well,
I quit drinking when I was 43, but so that tells you that win clue shot.
I was at my most alcoholic and he goes, I was a raging alcoholic from like age 13 to
43.
All right.
I got two more years.
He said, I basically put my entire life's worth of drinking into that stretch, but he goes,
I was constantly drunk at that time.
I would drink Tumblr after Tumblr of Scotch throughout the day.
I would wake up and do a bloody merit to get rid of my hangover and then be like, well, now
it's lunchtime.
I guess I could start drinking Scotch again.
Very open about all that stuff.
And he said like they called him up to do clue and he was like, look, man, it's this guy Jonathan
Lynn who's a great comedy director my cousin Vinny greedy all kinds of shit. Oh nice. And he goes
Look man, I'd love to come do this movie. I want to do it
But I don't look great. I look like I'd just been drinking for weeks. I haven't been working and I don't look great
So and he goes well see that's it's a British director
So Moll said that he goes, you know, I'm gonna tell you something that's gonna make your day, Marty
American directors, they always want you to be thin and fit
Colonel mustard, I want you fat, I want you bloated.
Not only do I want you to keep drinking like you're drinking,
I want you to start eating pizzas and burgers.
I want you fat, and just to be like,
you know, the movie's got a bit of social commentary.
You should be like a rich, fat, pompous asshole.
So Mark was like, great,
to have started pounding beers, eating pizza.
It is perfect for the role.
He does look much better now than he did.
He looks healthier now, but he looks bad in the club.
But that it fits the it does fit the role. I agree. He's like this this military brat. I agree. You know
The I love I love now let's get into the movie. I love it
Clu for me everyone that I knew always loved it when I was a kid and I'd always be like huh
I don't love it as much as you and I don't know why.
So when I revisited it, I respected the dialogue a lot.
I respected the performances a lot.
For whatever reason, this is one of those that didn't like become one of my childhood,
teen year classics like it did for a lot of people.
But I think it's a very fun entertaining move.
I love the film. I quote it, you know, first of all, the cast is stellar.
You've got Tim Curry at his best Tim Curry is all imagine having to memorize that dialogue. It's nuts
Every scene is an endless monologue. You got Tim Curry. You got Michael McKean
Madeline Khan. You got Madeline Khan. You've got Martin Molle. You've got
The woman from private Benjamin who I don't know her name, but she's fucking hilarious
Oh
Oh, what is she plays Miss Peacock?
I lean Brennan.
You've got what's his face for Ann Warn?
Mr. Body, Leslie Ann Warn, and then the guy that plays fear.
Yeah, Mr. Body's leasing her fear.
Yeah.
It's just a tremendous fucking cast.
And it is sinister at times,
but it's a very, very funny, farcical film.
It's my favorite Madeline con performance ever
because she's playing this woman that is like
like, on the edge of a nervous breakdown, who you think is innocent, but you absolutely
believe could have murdered multiple people.
Well, everyone talks about that model of flames on the side of my face, and that's what
I'm talking about.
I had heard this, like, built up and lore forever as being one of the funniest scenes ever.
It didn't make me laugh.
And I love Madeline Conn.
It was, it's just funny because she goes, I hate him so much.
Flames on the side of my face.
Yeah, like apparently it was improvised, which is cool, but she's she it just it just strikes me as somebody that's that's about to unravel.
Yes, my favorite line the entire movie is I got all my money in the war when I lost my mommy and daddy, which is Martin Moles line.
Oh, you've got well, the lady from my blue heaven is in it.
She plays the maid, Holy Christ.
Oh, Colleen Camp, yeah.
Wow.
Dan Ackroyd's wife really met her in New York
when he was passing around the drugs and booze.
He had, she was there.
Beautiful lady.
She's like, when I was a kid, I mean,
she was the most gorgeous woman I'd ever put.
And that's kind of the, I'm not reducing her role
to being hot, like that's kind of the part.
Like is everybody like the movie
like a super tractor. She's like this sexy French maid.
Well the movie I would compare it to because I love this kind of door slamming
farce type stuff. Frazier has a lot of episodes like this.
I'd like to do a remake a clue with grammar in the Tim Curry rule.
That'd be great.
Awesome. They're remaking clue with Ryan Reynolds's remake
and clue. I don't know who he's playing.
Oh, I'll piss on your fucking face right now.
I thought you like Ryan Reynolds.
I like him, but not for clue.
Ryan Reynolds would be great in any of these parts.
He's got that fast delivery. He's kind of our modern day Chavie chase. I like Ryan. All right. You're right
You're right. I like Ryan Reynolds. I got no beef with that, but I got to tell you fine
I like it, but I got to tell you grammar and David Hyde Pierce need to be in that goddamn movie of course
They should be in the course. I've been watching a lot of Frazier and those two and Mahoney their performances in that show are just incredible
It's impeccable grammar can pull a laugh out of anything. Yeah, he delivers lines so fucking funny
He's so much funnier than he was on cheers on fresh.
It's cheers is the superior show,
but when given that spot, like,
Grandma really brings that fucking beat.
He fucking runs with it, man.
Yeah, he's great.
High Pierce's physical comedy is insane.
The thing where he's trying to hop up onto the counter
to talk to, yes.
He's yet to do much on season four.
He's yet to do much physical comedy.
This is in the first season.
He's trying to hop up onto the counter to be cool.
Okay, yes, I remember.
And he hops so high, he hits his head on the light.
The hang light falls down, bangs his face on the fridge.
And it's fucking hilarious, man.
Yeah.
But yeah, grammar's delivery of like the one
where they're trying to fix the toilet.
And he's like, well, we wrote up our sleeves, Niles.
And we did.
Yeah, he's great.
DT is fucking work.
So funny, man.
I started this sentence eight, nine minutes ago.
sure a similar movie to clue that I prefer that meant more to me as a kid and
then I still think it's super funny is noises off yeah noises off was a huge
hit play in Britain and they made it as a movie with John Ritter yeah Michael
Cain Christopher Reeve Nicolette Sheridan plays the Colleen Camp role she's
running around a negligee the whole time right but it's behind the scenes of
putting on a play like this, a first kind of play,
but the behind the scenes is like a real life version of that.
It's, if you have not seen that movie,
and many, many people have not directed by Peter Bogdanovitch,
who we mentioned on the last podcast.
It's a great, yeah.
Man, that's a funny movie to me.
And I love the kind of racing around fast dialogue.
Clue, I just, like there are big last Michael McKean,
I'm gonna go home and have sex with my wife,
obviously very funny.
It's, freeze frame.
Yeah, freeze frame on that line. It ends. I mean, that is one of the greatest last slides of a movie ever
There's big laughs in it the three ending structure is cool
I am not old enough to recall the theatrical release where I guess every theater had its own ending isn't that cool ever
Well, every screening had different. Yeah, that's pretty fucking cool un -unquestionably cool and John Landis
Who murdered a
the Vietnamese family, as we discussed on a recent podcast,
John Landis, and it's a shame that that happened,
but easily a top comedy director for me of all time.
First stretch, you look at those credits
for about a 10 year stretch, he's unparalleled,
knows how to shoot comedy.
He was all set to direct clue, he had the idea for clue,
he had made a lot of progress on the script of clue,
and then had to go do spies like us.
So Jonathan Lynn, he had Tom Stoppert,
who wrote Shakespeare in love,
tried to crack a clue screenplay for two years
and then finally say, I give up, I can't do it, right?
Tom Stoppert, who's like one Oscars.
So he brings this guy, Jonathan Lynn.
He's like, I just want, for some reason
I want a British sensibility.
Jonathan Lynn writes that he's never directed
and Lannis is like, I gotta go do this spies like us.
So why don't you direct it?
never directed and it led to a long career are you spies like us fan I think it's
very funny it's okay that was a time when those guys could do no wrong for me
but yeah it's okay I mean the part that makes me laugh out loud is the when the
golf ball flies in the tent and Bob Hope walks in and they do the three stooages like
yeah yeah that that really makes me laugh every time Jonathan Lynn also had a
pretty incredible run on the lower end of the spectrum his biggest hit being
probably my cousin Vinnie.
Oscar nominated.
Yes, but he did the whole nine yards,
which is a very funny movie.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Whole 10 yards sucks.
Yeah, greedy with Michael J. Fox
and Phil Hartman is a super funny movie.
Kirk Douglas.
One of his final roles before he had the stroke
where, you know, where he could, yes.
Still, you know, talk fully, fully.
One of my favorite Phil Hartman lines ever.
You know, honey, I didn't like the Beatles
and I don't like you.
He directed Sergeant Bilko, which when I saw when I was 14, I loved.
Steve Martin still says he thinks it's a very funny film and it didn't get the shot that
it deserved.
I dug it.
I never saw it.
It looked, it just didn't look interesting to me, but the sitcom with Phil What's His Face
is considered, never seen that.
It's considered like, if you watch comedy documentaries and stuff about the golden age
You know, we'll talk about Phil Silvers, like he was the master.
Right.
Kind of like how we talk about like a tell, yeah, where you're like, you know, he's not that
famous, he's famous in his own way, but you know what I mean, like he's not a household
name.
Well, Bill Gohead, I mean, Hartman, Acroid, Martin, Chris Rock, it was a pretty incredible
cast.
To me, I haven't seen it in since theaters, but I bet I would still like it.
He also did nuns on the run, your beloved nuns on the run, which I saw at the Dollar Show.
Most diet is my beloved and I said I want to make a sequel called in a pope pre it. Yes. I saw
a nuns on the run of the dollar show. It was PG 13. There is a scene in it with 20 women in a
shower, fully frontally nude. My mom nearly had a heart attack, yanked me out of my seat, but I do
love nuns on the run. I think Robbie Coltrane is an amazing, amazing actor that has had
Margaret barely gotten, I mean, he's always working, but does the guy ever get recognized?
Did you see that TV show where he plays like the guy that gets, the entertainer that
gets accused of rape?
It's like one of the darkest things that are seen.
What is it?
Fucking amazing, Detective.
What?
Is it the singing detective?
Yeah, yeah.
No, it's not the singing detective.
The singing detective isn't about a rape accusation.
I've never seen it.
I don't know what it's about.
No, it's, it's like a BBC show.
Oh, okay.
But dude, it is like super fucking. It's really dark, dude. Obviously. He's a bread actor.
Uh, he plays these in another show where he plays like the grizzled alcoholic cop. Okay.
Then he plays Hagrid. Then he's in a nunsuit. I mean the guy can the guy can do it all.
The other movie I would ask you about the Jonathan Lynn did that I have only seen in the theaters, but I remember being like
Why is no one talking about this movie? It's so fucking funny. It's trial and error
with Jeff Bridges and Kramer and yeah, I remember that was that movie is
laughs in that movie really laughs in that movie hold up I don't know but is
the TV show based on that movie no not at all it's just another play on the
words okay the it was they were like get the guy who did my cousin Vinnie it's a
courtroom comedy but it's really funny. Kramer is really only shot at the big
time of like theatrical release name on the poster shit. Yeah, I heard a story once I was
complaining about like where my career was at. Yeah, I was in New York and I was complaining
and I was like, you know, I just got damn it. Like I'm just trying to get a break. Like,
like, what are we going to do? Like, and the guy was talking to goes, you know, I heard
the same story very recently about a man complaining to my manager about where was his shot that
man was Michael Richards and he goes it never ends the guy was on side felt it never ends so
apparently I was called that's true manager after I'm like what the fuck it's going on here yeah
like you know you got you got Alexander who's a tremendous actor doing he's back to doing KFC ads
I know. I know. And then like they do this very
great on a show called Big Time in Hollywood, Florida.
That's a very underrated comedy central show.
That new ad where he's the Colonel was like some weird play on George.
It's bad. Where he's like, I don't know what or whatever.
And then like there's a lot of track. It doesn't even make sense.
Now, anyway, you know, I remember something else, Michael Richard said a few years back.
Do you ever see the between word? Do you ever see the between two ferns with Jerry Seinfeld?
I did. I did. Introduces him as Jerry Sandusky. Yeah. Amazing. And he goes, why are you the only one since since the show that hasn't done anything?
Yeah. He goes, Elaine is on that that VHPO show. Kramer did that great stand -up routine.
Yeah. Between two far in the is reliably great. You can't really fault between two.
Uh, I don't know how he gets away with it. Yeah. He says to Hillary Clinton like about her daughter being
friends with Trump's daughter, do you think they're afraid of men hitting on them like
your husband, for instance, says to Obama, how does it feel to be the last black president?
It's fucking outrageous! I mean, it's got to all be cleared with them, right? I would think.
One would think. Outrageous. One would think. Alright, that's our show.
Clue is a fun picture. Check it out if you haven't seen it. I love it. I love it. I've been swimming
in raw sewage. I love it. We don't have anything in the hopper, but we will do a commentary
soon. We treasure you. We thank you. Check out the hoghouse on Etsy for merch. Check out
our Patreon if you want to hear the live episodes. It's seen a lot of people say that that
first live episode is one of our top five shows. And I agree. I texted Joe and I listened
to it. I feel like we've never been so on. I think it's one of our best hour pluses.
I am on Instagram and Twitter at the Patrick Walsh. The cool kids. Heirs Friday night
on the Fox Network. It is also on Hulu. If you would like to see this Martin Moll Leslie
and Warren episode, I think it will air after the new year. But be watching for that. And
That's all I got.
Joe DeRosa comedy on Instagram,
Joe DeRosa comedian on Facebook.
I will be, I guess January 3rd to the 5th,
I'm head riding Gotham Comedy Club in New York City.
So if you're in that area, come on out for a show.
Three nights, should be fun.
No, the 5th is my birthday.
Thank God I'm not here.
I'll wear it.
Wow, I never liked you, world.
That's a serenity.
Happy birthday.
Anyway, I'll be there, come through if you can.
Thanks a lot, folks.
But before we go, people, we got to do our shout outs for the month of November.
Anthony V. Manito, a .k .a.
Part of McFly.
Philippe Rashad, Caleb Sorenson, Tanner Rollins, Patrick Baxter, Julie Bailey, Violet,
you're turning Violet Violet, Michael Whitsett.
Kimani Cloudfelder, Anna, Sam Elliott, Brett Urway, Professor Papsmear, Patrick
Weithen, Truth Crab, Dave DeWitt, Zach Henderson, Tegan McLeod, Sadie Bug, Brian Morton,
Jay Covey, Cole Rothaker, Joey Mueller, Scott Engler, Waffles, Stephen Calpa,
Nak -Nak, who's there? Sam Mitchell, fuck that guy. Patrick Fitzsimmons. Andrew Tillichin.
Kelly Emmeroso. Beth Gaston. Sharifa. David Denahy. Devolo. Trevor Gage. Joshua
Christensen. KP Flynn, Tyler Moore. Alva E. Enriquez. Matt Wheeler, Leslie Coffin.
Well -fair dentist, Jackson C. Lomire, Lomire,
Geron Sanderson, Ash Ogden, Rain, Purple Peacock,
Sterling Abrigo, Christopher Sibelah, Steve Murdoch,
Not Medium Rare, Drew Tiberius Pull,
Monica, not from Friends, Taylor LePoint,
Steve Smith, Lupe Peta Pacheo,
Tancy Zonjic,
Dion Johnson, Matt Robin,
Will Foley, Kevin Ragoti,
Joseph, Christian Reynolds,
Josh Mallridge, Kurt Ziegler,
Brittany Ferguson, Sean Florn,
Danny Rudd, Natalie Hartline,
Scott Contour, Leo Lopez,
A. Ali, Emily Rock,
Rock, not rock, Emily Rook, not rock, sorry.
Scott Thue, Nick Mascara, Dave Del Greco, Kurt Ziegler, Chloe Paget, Matthew Roos,
Scott Birchett, Dennis Ormston, Travis Hines, John Wise and Gruber, Matthew McGuire,
Angela, Angela, oh boy, Angela Porcaro, James O 'Brien, Matthew Moon, J. Fisher, Sean
Lyle, John Hollywood, Jake McAlvin, Meredith McWilliams, Gregory Hassel, Jesse
I said that last one wrong. Anthony Rodriguez, Chris Passmore, Casey Jones, Syngy, Robert Haynes,
Natalie Haley, Hattley, Will Pittman, Kevin McNanny, Kevin Driscoll, Jen Wessels, Joe
Hoffman, Scott Sweeney, Jay Miller, Clayton Stamper, Amanda Lancaster, Michael Bolis, Ethan
Rolamo, Derek Adams, Sean Hall, Adam Loundsbury, Brett
Fanjella, Toby Bell, Vincent Franks, Joseph Ragoza, Steve
Burton, Anna Demario, Bo, Aaron Roberts, Scott John, Ben
Kara Kahnini, Joshua Taz Bozeman, Chuck Andrews, Tom Lavric, Tucker Rauch, John
Smith, Edmund Agabo, Andrew Brian Bolarrier, Will Helms, Jennifer Anna, T. L.
Michael Munholland, Melissa Alvarez, Jake Bullock.
Tangerous religion, zerofoxtrot .com, you fucks.
Matt Crawford, Jenna, Richard Deer, Lord, why aren't these an alphabetical order deming?
Brian Callis, Tim Drain, Michael Madrigal, please visit Mr. Suit Records and Lancaster
P .A. Richard Howleston, or Howinstein.
Bretton Frazier, Sean, Luke Physiock, Karen Kilgerif.
Please listen to my favorite murder.
Shelby L. Nathan Baskett, Gary Marone.
Dylan Lar, Phil Borrell, Edmund Dillon, the black magic ninja.
Scott Pauline Cerelle, Daphne Kellogg, Ryan Marks.
Tristan Avery, Hunk, Masterson.
Richard Iman, Matthew J. Brown, Julie Aguyer, charity Ferguson, Hank from Dankakes,
Nick Walther, Alexander Stein, Tyler Keatley, Emily Marvel, John B. Wat, visit his
Zombians horror craft, horror crafts store on Etsy.
Maury Benjamin, Nicholas Burns, Alex Nelson, Jeremy Cool.
Two fat to skate, Alex Shipley, Sean Pinnock, Amanda Leibson, Timothy Letso,
Shane Nazarene, Smelly Bubbles, Samantha Kiefer, I love you, David Belinger,
Hunter McDonald, Justin Bohagger, Adam Benbenick, Manny Rios, Demonio Rubio,
Brandon Gash, Jake Ferote, Rob Lines, Jacob Barrett,
Barrett, Jordan C, Maxwell Ashcroft, Ryan Kohler,
Barb Allen, Jonathan Face, Rebecca Cohen, Chris Bowen,
Mike Gibbons, Don Ye Joyce, Michael Dawson, Jennifer Smith,
Connor Denahy, Anthony J. Wohardo, Annie Johanison,
Timmy Kay, Megan Lybrand, Scott Blickensturfer, Brett Wemmer, Tristan Carlson,
Laura Sexton, Anthony Guajardo, Weston Thomas Veehill, Jared Blair, Richie
Verdugo, Chris Hopper, Emily Florence, our dear friend, and curator of all
things we'll see you at hell. Sean L. Dave Comerick, Abby Manuel, Kim D 'Angelo,
Jonathan Galatt, Michael McBee, Stephanie Power, Diego Campos, Stefan Musal, Zoe Blaskovic,
Aisley Kivinsland, Dan McLeod, Lorenz Bunganiers, Alejandro Salgado, Papa Spouche, Tracy Redding
Johnson, Sean Thomas, Amanda Alzemora, Jason Weibel, Mike Curry, Drew Spindler, Andrew
Cuvale, Sam Mitchell, Aaron Melanowski, Scott Nolan, Ben, Misty Zavar, Moly Russell's
Wart, Dejan A. Wilford, Johnny Ferg, Michelle Gold, Danielle Deuer, Eric Lamora, Kevin
Laurence Anderson, Jared Smallridge, Will Potter, Natalie Craig, Kyle Kinslin, the man
whose name we cannot say, Ani Babaduk, Scott Patton, the block watch, Paul Pickerel,
Rage Last Name Sounds Asian, Michael I. L .O. Read, Esthetic, and Max Unreth. As always, we are overwhelmed by your generous support. We thank you and love you all. We will see you next time.
We will see you.
It's a cool show!