I'm here for Bet Rivers Online Casino and Sportsbook with Poker icon Phil Helmiut.
And now thanks to the excitement of Bet Rivers, I'm also a Slots icon.
That's great. And a same game, Parley icon.
Cool, cool. A Blackjack icon, a Moneyline icon.
A roulette. Take it from Phil Helmiut.
If you love games, Bet Rivers is the place to play in Bet.
Bet Rivers.
Games on.
Must be 21 plus in present in West Virginia.
Void were prohibited. Terms in conditions apply.
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gambling.
Firestone Complete AutoCare's epic savings advantage is the sign you need to stop putting off your car's maintenance.
And you can save up to $100 on tires and services while you're at it.
Don't wait, call Firestone Complete AutoCare for an appointment.
Hello everybody and welcome to we'll see you in hell now on the head gum podcast network.
work. My name is Patrick Walsh and this week we will be discussing Stephen King's It,
the 1990 I believe CBS miniseries will also be discussing the trailer for the new version
of it that is coming to a theater near you soon this summer I believe. I guess without further
do let's uh let's get on with the show and while we're at it I mean it's a
crazy thought but perhaps we could also get on with the Joe it gets it gets
more and more enthusiastic every week it goes up I say the kids hit his
ceiling yeah and then the next week you come and you say I got more to give and
it's amazing my goal is on the the series finale when you and I are not
speaking and recording it in separate soundproof booths in different states.
Exactly. Yeah. That I get so high with it that I shatter a glass. Maybe even the
soundproof booth that I'm in shatters around me, like Emilio Estevez in the breakfast club.
Here's what I, this is the scene I'd like to set. All right. I'm with you through most of that
scenario. All the way up to the separate states, separate booths thing. We're not speaking.
you are sitting there going, I just can't wait to be done with this.
You get to the on with the Joe and you go and now on with the, you stop.
You try it three times. You can't get out. You go, I can't say it.
I can't do this. I love you too much.
Oh.
We have to keep going.
And then that's the show keeps going after that.
We keep going until
still, like sometime around like 20, 55, I go and now on with the show and on with the
and my heart stops and I die. And within about five minutes, not like with old couples
where it happens a couple weeks later, within about five minutes, you two are dead. And
it just records our last gasps. And that's our final podcast.
Well, it records forever. Nobody's there to hit stop. That's true. And then in a in a shocking twist our
obituary says the creators of we'll see you in hell wind up in heaven
That's what our obituary says. We hope and then the picture is of you and I sprawled across your floor
Which is covered with your dogs unattended shit. Yeah kind of still alive in
2555 and our fingertips are touching like we reached for each other at the last minute
Okay, both microphones on the floor blasting feedback a large bottle of tequila just spilling and spilling
For some reason naked so like everyone thinks that we've been fucking like but actually your dog just tugged our slacks down
Yeah, I'm gonna wake us up. I like that. I like that the
We've got a lot to discuss
us. We've got a lot to catch up on. Lots happened in the last week. I just want to squeeze
a quick joke in, but I think you'd appreciate it. Please. As you know, I co -host a monthly
live show called Can I Kick it here in LA with Al Jackson and Tony Bell. I do. And we watch
blocks of hip hop and R &B videos and do like a sort of beevus and butt head style thing
with them. But it's a celebration of hip hop culture. But last night's theme was the month
of April. So we did April showers. Yeah. It was one of the blocks. It was all songs about rain.
So we did candy rain. We did the rain by Missy Elliott. I was hoping. Yeah. That was my first choice.
The last one, you got to do it. We did blame it on the rain. Sure. And I said,
I hope the guy that killed himself, if I were him, my suicide note would have said,
if any of you are wondering why I did this, and I took a long pause and I went blame it on the rain.
Yeah. Yeah. Big laugh, Pat. I felt like it was your kind of bit. It was. I'm sure his family
would appreciate that joke as well. Well, I felt bad for inviting them down last night.
Yeah, that was that was a bit much than making that joke. Things are going well with your pilot.
I don't know how much you can talk about or not talk about. So say whatever you feel comfortable
saying about. Well, let's let's hold off till it's shot, which will be on April 12th.
And I guess I could say that I can't promise everybody,
but if you wanna reach out on the Facebook page
or Twitter and you're in Los Angeles,
I can probably get you into the pilot.
I don't know how many spots we're gonna have,
but it's going really well.
And I think in terms of specifics,
let's discuss it after that date on the 12th,
but had the first table read yesterday, it was great,
things are moving great.
I'm a lot more, you know.
I'm still not completely out of the woods.
It's a miserable experience.
I don't recommend it, but the rewards could be great.
So it's getting into a nice fun groove.
Good.
I'm glad to hear it.
There are many surprises that await in terms
of what's going on with the pilot.
I'll say that, but I don't want to discuss it till I know
for sure that I can.
That's not exciting.
All right, very nice.
This is my new thing.
I bought a Gallagher Arcade machine, now see I misunderstood I thought you would bought the Gallagher
Machine where you smash watermelons like Donkey Kong. It is that game. Oh, okay, good
They just didn't have any more Gallagher cacings to write and then if you play Gallagher, too
Yeah, it's better than the first one. Do you know the story of Gallagher, too? I know well
I mean just just very briefly you know Gallagher the the comedian whose whole bit was shattering watermelons
now he's a little more known for being very racist.
But he had a brother who looked like him
and he thought, hey, I can double my money.
If I...
Well, no, no, the brother went to him and said,
okay, yeah, yeah.
Can I do your show as Gallagher too
because the brother needed cash, I guess.
Right.
So there's only stipulation was,
yeah, as long as you let him know it's not me.
Right.
So when you're touring, you can play St. Louis
or you can play like Columbia.
You know like St. Louis is the big market Colombia is like a small smaller college town in Missouri for example
I you know every every state's got big city small cities. I don't think I'm telling you any news there
Gallagher 2 was like I'll play the smaller cities
I'll put on the on the poster Gallagher and big letters 2 and small letters nobody will know the fucking difference
We're both just guys hitting watermelons
so
eventually
Can you, maybe you know more specifics from there because all I know is when it became Spanish that part
I don't know all I know the only thing I know is take me up till there because I know is Gallagher's only role was you can't make people think it's me and
Immediately the brother broke that rule. Yeah, so that's so then he got pissed and he sued his own brother, right and
And then after that, I don't know what happens. Well the Spanish speaking part was something I just learned about and that that is that
that Gallagher started playing Spanish markets
to like make even more money.
Like he just was like,
I gotta really get as much money out of this as I can.
Wisely, because the market for watermelon shattering
is a pretty limited one.
He learned how to do his act in Spanish,
but he learned it phonetically.
He didn't learn Spanish.
He just was like, here's what I say in my act.
I'll have somebody translate it for me and record it
and just do it phonetically.
Gallagher one or two did this.
One, I believe.
Which is strange because all of his most racist jokes
are about Spanish speaking culture.
That's correct. That's correct.
I learned about all this on, you know, this has,
I'll plug it. It's not an ad.
We are starting to do ads.
We'll always tell you what is an ad and what isn't.
But I learned about it on the Gilbert Godfried podcast.
And I'm not a big podcast guy, but I heard that
But there was a great one with the writers of many films, Ed Wood, they also wrote problem
child with Gilbert Gottfried, Scott Alexander and Larry Karazuski, and they bring on kind
of fringe guys, writers, they had on Tom Sharplin, which I love.
But Gilbert Gottfried, we all know he's funny, but like my Christ is he funny on this show.
He's in a whole hilarious human being, but particularly in conversation.
Oh yeah, so that's why this podcast is such a, I didn't even know it existed.
it. But they talked for like 20 minutes about the making of problem, child. And I, I
mean, I was dying. And they went into the, the guys that did Ed Wood, they loved movies
about French people. They did the people versus Ed Wood. They did the one about the big,
you know, big guys versus, I'm sorry, the people versus Larry Flint. Oh, okay. They did
the, the one big guys about the lady and the Hunter husband who made the paintings with
the big guys that Tim Burton did. They did Mars attacks. They do a lot of, lots of great stuff.
But they wanted to do one about Gallagher and Gallagher too. And they were like, you've gone
too far. You've got too niche. Nobody wants to see this movie. I want to see the movie. I would
see that in a heartbeat. But they were talking about their research on it and all these things they
found out and it was just fascinating. But I ended one of my half hour specials. I have two Gallagher
stories. The first one is I ended one of my half hour specials with a joke about Gallagher.
I got him after it aired. I got a message the next day on Facebook.
book, long, hateful letter from somebody, you know, I was with you till the end.
Wow.
Who the fuck do you think you are to take a shot at a legend like that?
You're nobody.
And it wasn't Gallagher.
Well, that, I wrote back, is this Gallagher, and then, then the guy responded like, to
Shay, you got me, that was funny.
He actually kind of like, okay, which was fine.
But then, um, this is my favorite Gallagher related story, I used to tour with Patton
Oswald.
Yeah.
And we were doing a show, I can't remember where we were, but it was a theater somewhere.
And the guy who was like driving us from the hotel to the venue was telling us, Patton
was like, so who else has been through here recently?
And the guy's like, well, we just had Gallagher.
And Patton's like, what was that like?
And because it was before all the Mark Marin interview shit came out where Marin was kind
of like, you're kind of racist now and stuff.
So nobody knew where he was, and the guy goes, he came out, he started talking about astrophysics,
and then demeaning the audience for being stupid, because they didn't understand what he was talking about.
And he goes, you know, the craziest part of the whole thing was, you know, he asked me in his writer,
it said he needed a table, four foot by three foot or whatever.
Uh -huh. He's like, so I got out. I went out. I'm thinking he needs something to put his water on or whatever. I go buy this beautiful antique table. I bring it in
Gallagher takes one look at it. He's like, I can't use this
This is for the smash in the watermelons. He's like, I can't this thing's gonna break. I need like a sturdy table
Right, and the guy's like, so it's crazy. I'm running around an hour till show time. I got to build a damn table out of two by fours
So Gallagher can smash watermelons and there's the longest pause in the history of man like the longest awkward silence
I've ever been a part of and then finally Pat just goes
Gallagher needed a table in his contract and you didn't know it was for smashing watermelons
Yeah, that checks out
I got I got a wonder surely Gallagher now he goes out to play the club and he hits the watermelon and the crowd is just kind of like
Silent right he's retired now they can't still be cheering this are people that's all they want
It's the only part they want Jersey the video where he has the heart attack while he's doing it
He had an actual heart attack. Yeah, it's on YouTube
There's a there's like an iPhone video of him go picking the hammer up and then like having collapsing from a heart attack
Well, fuck. I'll fund this Ed Wood guy's movie. I want to see this movie
I mean everything I've heard sounds like this
This makes an amazing film, and I want to see it.
It's a wild ride, so.
Who would play Gallagher in the film version?
I bet it would be Johnny Depp again.
That seems like something he would do.
Look, these guys do a lot of Tim Burton work.
Johnny Depp does a lot of Tim Burton work.
I'd like to see a dark version with like a Christopher Waltz
or maybe a Morgan Freeman.
Just a real strange take on it.
Maybe, uh, uh, maybe, uh, uh, what's his face?
Um, the last thing at Scotland guy, he'd be a force whittaker.
For us, whittaker'd be a fun guy.
How much is Gallagher a millionaire?
I think he's broke now.
Oh, good.
Okay.
I was at the improv one night and he was there.
The Melrose one in Hollywood and he was.
Suspenders.
Uh, I can't remember.
All right.
But he looked like he just didn't want to fucking talk to anybody.
Yeah.
It was kind of a bummer.
I was like, deep in my heart, this was recently, they're not recently but like right before
we retired like a year ago, deep in my heart I was hoping like, I was going to meet him
and it was all going to be like, oh he's actually a good guy and this has all been a big misunderstanding
and I didn't meet him and for what I could see he seemed kind of like a dick so you know,
It just was kind of a bummer man
Anyway
Listen, do you have any movies for the roundup?
You know, I've been I've been busy again, and I've seen absolutely nothing. I haven't seen a single a single piece of entertainment
I like I like this Gilbert Godford podcast. That's that's all I really got
Uh, I have two things uh
Did I saw?
I don't have my damn phone in front of me here. Hold on. I gotta get my phone because I keep a list
Can you hold down the fort for a minute? Yeah, absolutely. Um, how are you guys?
It's funny um, I always think when Joe walks away that about that classic scene in Wayne's world when
And Mike Wayne leaves Garth to like carry it for a minute and he goes into a complete spiral.
I'm not feeling that now, but that that scene is so funny to me as is everything in
Wayne's world and Wayne's world too.
What do I got folks?
My cat puked in my bed.
That was the first hopefully that comes out of the sheets.
I know you're concerned.
And it's going to all come out in the wash as they say, well, it was, you know, to tie
it into horror.
It was an extraceous style, amount, color, and consistency of puke.
That's disgusting.
I know, and I don't really know what happened.
I look at him and I'm like, you know, a couple of times a day, we put out a few little pieces
of kibble.
What's happening?
Well, maybe to say some grass outside or something.
It is never in contact with grass.
That's never happened.
Maybe it a piece a leaf off a plant in the house or something they do that, you know con here will
Get a little too grass hungry outside and sometimes he pukes it up
Okay, they like grass for some reason. All right. Okay the movies I've seen
two
Well three actually I saw the movie microwave massacre, which is an exploitation movie from the 80s starring the comedian that voiced
Frosty the snowman
in the original, in the cartoon, yeah, that same guy.
I thought that was burlives.
No, burlives is the ice climber guy.
No, burlives is the snowman who's like,
see, they're in good.
Yes, see, they're in good.
Yeah, oh yeah, you're right.
But you mean the animated, like the boring animated frosty,
not the climation?
Well, the burlives snowman is not frosty.
He's just a snowman.
All right, fair enough.
Anyway, Mike, we have Frosty.
Huh?
I bet he was Frosty.
He got to stay cold or are you, are you going to melt?
Oh, I see what you mean.
Yeah, I got you.
You know, do you know Wendy's now does a vanilla Frosty?
I don't care for the chocolate Frosty.
Taste diet to me has always tasted diets to me.
There's an odd element.
It's probably just as fattening,
but does taste like a, like a weight watcher's bar.
It's never tasted right to me ever.
I agree. Anyway, Microwave Masker exploitation, sort of dark comedy -hard thing about a guy that can't stand his wife so he cuts her up and he microwaves her, and then he eats her, and he likes the taste of it, and then he begins...
She blows up on the microwave or he just cooks her.
And then he begins fucking women that are way out of his league and way hotter than he is,
and then realizes the only way he can be satisfied with sex is if he kills and
eats the woman afterwards. Which this sounds much more gruesome than it is. I mean
the body parts of the movie literally look like they stopped at Halloween
adventure on the way to the set and bought like a rubber leg. It's count probably it
sounds like like Frank and Hooker. It's very much in the vein of that. So look if
you like that sort of thing, sure. Where did you come in contact with it? Well two
great apps that I'm going to save for Joe's scary stuff. Oh, I think you told me amazing apps
that I but but let me get to those in a minute. What else did I see? I saw a waken fright
in an Australian film from 1970, I believe. That's a wild ride that movie. Yeah, I was
stunned. I believe for years. I was talking to somebody about it the other night after
show. Somebody that was a big horror fan. Actually, it was one Mr. Simon Rich, who I did a show with,
the creator of a man seeking woman. I was speaking to him and his wife, very nice people after
the show. They're big horror fans. And I said to his wife, I just saw Wake and Fright and she said,
is it a horror movie? And I said, well, it kind of is, but it's not by definition. But there are
There's some terrifying shots of like Donald Plezins
with the quarters in his eyes and you know,
you're watching animals mutilated.
I think that's why it was banned
is that there's animal mutilation.
Yeah and the big statement comes on at the end
that was like they didn't mutilate the animals,
they were doing it, they were using actual footage,
shot by Kangaroo Hunters,
so they could show that this was bad,
that this was happening or whatever.
But did you see the sequel Waken Bake?
No, no, how was that what what animals? I mean that's we're mutilated a lot of cows because they were eating cheeseburgers
Yeah, from the munchies. Yeah, no, I I think I saw it all it was on Netflix since tonight. I
Like Ebert had written about it as like you know
People are paralyzed with fear at this thing. It's always when you see that that about a movie from like 1971
You realize that things are a little different. I mean I don't love watching a kangaroo murder
But you know, it's also not gonna keep me up night really well
Yeah, and it's not just like that the spoiler alert. It's not just that like the kangaroos get shot
It's like there's a couple scenes where like well the main characters of like he has to kill the kangaroo with his hands
Yeah, it needs to get like close to it and stab it several times, right? So it's it's disturbing
It's a disturbing film. I think I also think
It's sort of implied that he fucks Donald Pleasant's when they're drunk
I got that I think more than implied. Yeah, that was a very interesting subplot. Yeah, but they don't show it
They just kind of almost show it's it's just it's an interesting film. Yeah, uh, finally
I revisited as I've been meeting two for many years now killer clowns from outer space. Uh
I don't know man. It's fun. I guess to watch
It's well done for what it is
Uh
The clowns actually look scary and that bums me out that it's so comical because the clowns actually are frightening looking and it's in the
The movie itself obviously is not scary. I mean, they're blowing people up with like popcorn guns and stuff
Tell you it really destroyed me when I was a kid. I every once in a while. I would be like maybe I'm
Not so much a pussy that I can watch a horror movie and then I would watch one and be like nope
I am a pussy and that one scared you as a kid
Horrified me. Clowns were a big issue for me and what a perfect transition into what
we're going to talk about tonight. Yeah, I know. Well, wait, I still got to do this scary
stuff. Sorry. Okay. Sorry. I thought we usually come back to scary stuff. Now, we usually
do it here. I just always forget to do it. Listen, real quick, some scary stuff to check
out that you enjoy quite a bit. Were you fan of Friday the 13th, the series? If you
were, did I do this one already?
I think I did.
You did?
Shit.
Did it?
Way off the pipe, Jim.
All right.
Well, if I did it already, I'm sorry.
You did.
Oh, definitely did?
100%.
You sure we didn't talk about it after, where I said no.
In the last episode you talked about it at length.
Oh, okay.
All right.
And I was like a Friday the 13th show with no Jason.
Well, yeah.
Okay.
All right.
Forget it.
Sorry.
Yeah.
Okay, well two apps you should go out and check out shop factory now has an app that I'm excited to check out
And it is totally free. They probably got SCTV and all that
I haven't dealt deep in so far
I've just perused it for the cult movies, which is where I saw microwave massacre as you asked, right
But it is totally free. There's no subscription nothing an app similar that is not through free, but it's just as well worth your time and money
the Night Flight app which is now on Apple TV. Night Flight was an old TV show
they used to show on like Friday nights and it was a variety of things. It
was crazy movies and interviews with musicians or musical performances and
interviews with directors and whatever. They have sort of curated all the
content of Night Flight and then separated into different categories on the app.
I think it's only $2 .99 a month, very well worth it, but they've got a horror movie section, they've got a kung -fu movie section,
they've got a cult movie section, they've got a sci -fi section, they've got
interviews with directors as a section, they've got musical documentary sections, they have a concert live concert,
it's a fantastic fucking app.
All right.
And shout factory and night flight, I believe it's called Night Flight Plus, these are two apps that I would say,
And I've never said this before must have oh for the horror fantasy sci -fi fans out there in our audience
These are the ones to not skip and with that pet
With that I'll quit clowning around. Oh
You brought it back because I was going to say in the history of transitions
We have really never so seamlessly had one as killer clowns and it and you blew it
But then you brought it back with the with the clowning around folks
Yeah, going back like I would see a you a poltergeist because it was PG
But usually I couldn't see horror movies because they were rated R
But when I would see one at a friend's slumber party or whatever it was they really just
Chill me to the bone and I wouldn't sleep and I would be scared to take a shower and I would be scared of
You know walking down the hall at night and just it was always really bad for me and
I think where that all began would have to be it I would have been about nine years old which sounds right
Mm -hmm zone CBS and
For some I guess just because it was on CBS. I was allowed to watch it, but I
Definitely shouldn't have been and I watched it again very recently. It's a it's a really terrifying and fairly graphic movie
I've always loved the book. I would I would put it honestly probably in my top 10 books of all time Stephen Kings
it. Yeah, it's a great book. And, you know, a lot of us haven't had time to read the book.
The book is 1200 pages. It is. I read it as a kid and I was getting ready to read it before I
brushed up on the new one, but I haven't yet. Let's before we dive into the actual film. Let's talk
about that three minute trailer that hit the net this week. See, I think, can I challenge that?
But I think we should talk about the old version and then address whether or not what we've
seen in this new version is repping any of the grievances with the original.
Now, do you like the original?
You still like it.
I love it.
Exactly.
I love it and I wash it again and everybody's grievance with it is the ending.
And I don't remember because I read the book when I was probably 12, 13.
I don't remember if the book ends this way.
I think it does, but essentially after all this beautifully building tension and suspense,
it basically becomes a giant spider.
Yeah.
I'm not a fan of that.
It's kind of dumb, and yet when I watched it, I was kind of like, all right, I mean, it was
still an effective ending to the movie.
It felt like, you know, you can't really overestimate how much stranger things rip off everything,
but it really rips off it.
Yeah, in a really big way, and I guess, you know, in the same way that the finale of Stranger Things
is kind of like, all right, whatever, that's how I felt about the ending of it. But I didn't
thought it, I didn't think it'd derailed the rest of it. It's, it's Stephen, I love Stephen King,
I'm a huge fan, of course. But I think his one flaw is that he, he explains too much sometimes.
Yes, and that to me is a problem in the story of it, whether it's the book or the movie or whatever is that it
Bringing it to this sort of literal explanation at the end of what this thing actually is or whatever
So that always kind of bumming and Stephen King always does I remember my friend Dan once said like Stephen King pulls that move a lot where at the end
It's just like oh, it's just a big spider, right? You know or whatever or
or it was from another dimension that opened up,
or you know what I mean?
Like I don't always need to know that stuff.
Yeah, and that's also because of how effective
everything is with the clown.
It's just like truly unsatisfying.
Like it's so much better if it's,
honestly it's better if it's like the ghost
of some fucked up clown from the 50s or something, you know?
Yes.
But with the what the best aspect of the miniseries and
Also, I'm kind of upset they don't do miniseries anymore. I think they would be really successful
The first job I had out here in LA was it's in CBS miniseries
And I started the job and the guy was like just so you know this department is going to be completely eliminated
in about two weeks
And I was like, no way.
And it wound up being about four weeks.
But in the meantime, I wrote like entire scripts
at this job because he was like,
they're not doing many series anymore.
It's not happening.
Just a rotten business.
Yeah, no it is.
So I miss them.
And especially when they were good.
Cause they, I mean, you know,
you look at roots and all that.
I mean, there's amazing many series
that you should take place.
And they just don't.
The Thornbirds, Pat.
The Thornbirds.
Yes, of course, but it for me the selling point of it is the direction
Which is I mean they they bring it up. This would be a hard PG -13
bordering on an R I would say and the performances the performance is not just from Tim Curry
Which will always be the it by which all others are judged but these kids are fucking great all the kids are great
I don't know everybody's names
But you got a brand us of course. You got Jonathan brand is great. You got Seth Green in there
RIP DSV. Yeah, you got Seth Green in there. That's correct. Yeah, you got the Husky blonde -haired kid who I've seen in a million things
And I don't know his name love that kid. Don't know his name either. Yeah
So you got a nice cast of people in there
I can't remember any any of the kids names except for Seth Green and Jonathan Brandis, but they're all great
And then they're played by equally great adult counterparts, you got John Ritter in a dark role, which is interesting.
You've got Harry Anderson in a dark role, which is great.
You've got, I'm blanking on her name, the lady that's married to Michael McKean.
And Magninson.
Nope.
And I'm looking it up.
It, an Edo tool.
An Edo tool.
Yep.
She's wonderful.
She is you've got and then I don't know the name Thomas from the Walons. Yes. You got Richard
Mass or the president of the screen actor's guild. It's just a lot of great actors and and
a in what you know like because of course you want to cast the best actor for the part but it is
one of the few movies to do the thing where you have the kid and their adults where you completely buy
all of them. Yes. Like, um, you know, for example, there's, there's a pilot being shot for CVS
where Bobby Moynihan is going to become John Lara Kett. That, that I don't buy. What do you
mean? Bobby Moynihan plays the character at 40. John Lara Kett plays him at 65. Yeah, I don't
buy that. That's ludicrous. So there's a, what are they going to do? Get a big fat John Lara
I'm kidding.
I don't know, but it's just kind of, it's rare that it works because it's almost impossible
to find a great child actor, but especially one that looks exactly like the adult actor
you're going to cast.
I'm going to tell you this, Pat.
I haven't seen that much of a negligence between the older and younger versions since that sweet
love and mercy film.
Oh, love and mercy.
Yeah, where Kusak couldn't even be bothered to die his hair.
I know.
I let alone gain weight.
The fattest years of the guy's life.
Yeah.
And he just, just a trim fit, John Kusak.
Now, I love John Kusak, but Dano, like,
and I'm on the fence about Dano,
but he completely channels Brian Wilson to the extent
where you're like, you're like,
am I watching documentary footage?
Yeah, he's great.
And then it cuts to the modern day of Kusak
and he's like, hey, what's up?
I'm Brian Wilson, wouldn't it be nice if we were older?
And yet I like the movie.
I just kind of, I like Kushek in it,
but it's not, there's a big, big difference
between the Dan and me.
One of my favorite things I ever heard in a sitcom,
writing room, and it's something I use all the time.
And not just in writing, but also in watching movies,
is that somebody, I don't, I don't, I don't, oh my God.
I had a stutter when I was a kid
and sometimes it comes back.
It's like the movie it.
This is what happened.
It's exactly right.
Maybe it just made that happen.
But I don't remember who did it.
I'd like to give him credit.
I don't remember, but he basically referred
to something called the House of Bies.
So you'd pitch something and it was like,
what if these two characters bump into each other
at the mall?
Then he's like, let me call the house of buys and he calls him like, you buy it?
And he'd be like, they said, yes, they buy it.
But then it's like, what do you say then?
The next day they bump into each other at the same mall and he would call the house of buys and be like,
no, we're not buying that one.
Right.
So when I watch a movie, you know, like, I think of that all the time because I'm like,
all right, that's a stretch, but there are crazy coincidences in life, so I'll buy it.
But you don't buy more than one, you don't buy certainly three, four.
Sure, and some movies just go like the those in a rock to movies 21 grams or if they thrive on those massive
Coincidences that are often a little fan of that guys movies
I like oh, I love babble and I love a more as pedos
But didn't he also do Birdman and the Revenant? Yes, that's correct didn't really like Birdman thought the performances were great
But didn't enjoy the film I dug them both
And the Revenant I thought was just precious in the woods it was just so long and I
bad thing after bad thing. I was not enjoying it. Anyway, back to it. You know, look, we have to talk
in some detail about the greatest performance in the movie. It's Tim Curry as Pennywise the Dancing
Clown. And for me, I mean, Tim Curry, you look at Clu, you look at Rocky Horror, you look at
to a very lesser extent, Home Alone 2, Lost in New York. Tim Curry's had a lot of very memorable
performances. You look at him, I still remember him in the trailer for Congo with an inexplicable
accent saying the myth of the Kila ape is true. Like what rolling his Rs but it's also
like French. The man is great. But whoever thought to cast him as it is a fucking genius.
and every time he shows up, you completely forget that it's Tim Curry.
I still do. Every time I watch it, I don't see Tim Curry.
You just buy it as like a horrifying demon clown.
And he plays it like not even not even a performance.
It seems like you're watching an actual demon clown.
He plays it with such nuance.
Yeah, it's friendly and he's and he's playful and happy and then it cuts to those
Crazy shots of him with like the fangs and the yellow eyes. Yeah
It's kind of funny too, and then you'll be like why was I just laughing at this guy? That's not cool. Right, right?
It's it's a tour de force performance. It's why the first
The original DVD I had of the movie I since since bought the Blu -ray
But the original one it was cut into halves see to flip the DVD and on VHS a blockbuster. Yeah
Yeah. So the first half of the DVD was my favorite because that was the kids and a lot
of the Pennywise stuff. I love the scene. I'm looking at it now to see if he got an
Emmy nomination and the answer seems to be no.
The scene where he comes up out of the, and this is the other cool thing, the effects they
use in the original, because this is pre, you know, basically pre -CGI or this is before
it was readily available. So they do a lot of claymation effects and stop motion things so that
But that's where he comes up in the bathroom showers and he has to like, he puts his hands
up in the drain and like shoves the tiling side so he can come up.
It's like this weird claymation, like what's his face?
Harry, Halzen, Harry, what's that guy's name?
Ray Harryhaus.
Yeah.
It's, it's, it's just, it just makes it a lot creepier for some reason.
I love the film, you know, there are many people that say it doesn't hold up. And those are the people I think that are probably most excited about this new version coming out sometime this year.
I know I was excited about the new version coming out because I always want more of a thing I love and I love the original it.
But I also, oh, by the way, there's a great audio book of it that Stephen Weber reads.
That's what I'm listening to now.
I'm listening to it right now.
I listen to it when I go to bed at night, and it's fun to go to sleep too, but then when
you wake up to it in the middle of the night, it's creepy.
I loved it.
But anyway, I think a lot of people are excited for this, it remake for different reasons,
and at long last they released the trailer.
Now, I got to say this, right off the bat before I even saw the trailer.
you know my skepticism was running pretty hard and high because God bless Bill
Scarsgard he's a great actor he's too damn young to play Pennywise he's just on
different TV shows and stuff but he's he's Stellan's scar I think it's Scarsgard
he's his kid yeah and Stellan I was talking about it the other day and he goes
because Stellan's Garzgar should have played Pennywise.
Yep.
You know, like get somebody like that,
like with some character in their face and some age.
Well, we were talking, I mean, I, like,
and we talked about it a work amongst the other day.
Like, Boshemi seems perfect.
Right.
Maybe two on the nose.
Michael Shannon, to me, seems very interesting.
Right.
Sam Rockwell, I think, could have done it.
But I love Sam Rockwell.
He's, I think he's two, Sam Rockwell.
Maybe so.
But when that when they talked about what about a Giamati now Giamati that's right in that curry wheelhouse
That would have been fucking them. That's a great call Jim
But I just don't I'm looking up scars garden now I
Gotta say I don't like it being a kid. It wasn't a kid in the books. I don't know why they went there
He's like 25. Yeah, you asked me
You know what I would think about
Tim Curry playing it now like if he didn't have the stroke would they have asked Tim Curry to play it now
Right, they wouldn't have because everything has to be new in movies everything has to be different it 2 .0 or whatever, but
I thought the trailer was cool and we'll talk about it, but for me
When I heard that it was gonna be two two -hour movies from the creator of true director of true detective Fukunawa
I was like this is gonna be one of the highlights of my year. Yes
I could not fucking wait
Somebody sent me the script and I was like, I don't want to read it. It's written by Fukonawa and some other guy
I was like, I just want to go in cold and excited and
Then what I heard is that Fukonawa wanted to do a very hard -ar version including the very uncomfortable
Pedophilia sequence from the book. What is that sequence because I've not gotten to that part yet? Is it the girl the little girl's dad
He had to abuse his her, I assume.
I mean, look, I'm going through the audio book now myself
and it's extremely long.
I seem to remember like a lot of kids
having an orgy almost.
Oh, well, she...
She fucks them all.
She sleeps, she has sex with, I think it's sex.
She has sex with each one of the boys
because they discover they have to have a bond
as a group and they figure out
that that's the way to have the bond.
So she has sex with each one of them individually.
yeah and then also the bullies I think blow each other which is a great
fucking detail yeah that these kids are late in homosexuals and don't know how to
deal with it because they're in this like right one horse closed -minded town
and now they're they act like assholes because of it yeah my favorite thing
about Stephen King and you know it was during his very coked out period as well as
many of his books are but my favorite thing about Stephen King is not you know
one of many. It's his portrayal of bullies because bullies in movies are, they're like, you
know, push you down and take your launcher, whatever. A Stephen King bully will put a knife in
like, not hold it to your throat, like puncture your stomach with a knife, right? You know,
with that to me is from my experience, what bullies are like. They always have a switchblade. Yeah.
No limits, you know, like truly terrifying. And they don't care. They truly don't care,
because it's usually because of their parents, but like they'd be fine dying.
My biggest bully, you know, when I was young or helped me down on my first day of first
grade, sat on my chest and fed me worms and then forced me to swallow these worms.
Right.
Among many other things, I had a bully my first day of kindergarten.
I was wearing short shorts.
He punctured my upper thigh with a knife.
He threw me in the bus next to him.
Yeah.
Pushed me against the window of the bus and the entire right to school.
Well, twisted a piece of broken glass.
Excuse me, broken mirror into my upper thigh
until he drew blood.
And I never told anyone about it.
Yeah, it's, yeah, I had a bully when I was in seventh grade.
He was in eighth grade.
Yeah.
Greg Murdoch, I mean, if that's not a great bully name, sure.
But yeah, he used to threaten to smash my face
in with a metal folding chair to the point
where he would swing it and bring it an inch from my face
and tell me almost lustfully how bad he wanted to do it.
Yeah, like that element of like true horror
is never in portrayals of bullies in books, movies,
except with Stephen King who was clearly bullied, obviously.
But who was a bully?
Yeah, make sure he's out.
But, you know, it does it stand by me, does it, et cetera,
but that's a great detail that I even forgot
that the bullies blow each other in the book.
But I try to have high hopes but when I heard that they were replacing Fukunama with the
guy who did Mama, maybe because it sounds like Fukunama, I don't know.
I couldn't get through the film Mama.
I thought it sucked.
Mama sucked.
And I was to think that this guy is the guy to pin your
Massive franchise on is crazy to me. Well now Stephen King has given it a thumbs up. All right, but
Look Stephen King is what?
70 he's got to be 70 right? Yeah, he's 70 70 early on Twitter. I'll tell you that he's great
He's still great. Yeah, he doesn't have quite the angst he had during his coke phase, right? He's not running around screaming
I mean, you know, that Stanley Kubrick fucked my book up and he's not that guy anymore.
He gives a lot of thumbs up to things that are done, you know, that are adapted from
his work.
So I'm not saying I doubt the man, but I also don't think he's as hard a critic as he was,
which is fine.
But he did give it a thumbs up, he said fans have nothing to worry about.
I don't like that they cast, again, the young kid as Pennywise.
I don't like that so far what I have seen in the trailer and in the still pictures that the that penny -wise
Always just look sinister now that might be different in the movie. I don't know. Yeah, I'm sure it is
So I hope that that's the case
I don't like that literally a kid from Stranger Things is in it. Right. Well, that was it. I was a given
And we reached out to fans to hear what you guys thought and a bunch of you DMed me
Well, let me ask you first, maybe you know,
because I don't, I still have the script on my laptop,
but I was wondering if they're still,
apparently now the plan is if it is a hit,
then they're gonna make the second one,
but only if it's a hit.
So, they're gonna tell half a story,
are they only telling the kid's side
and not telling the adult side?
What's happening?
Well, I think that's an easy thing to do,
because don't forget that the kids do think they defeat it.
Yeah, that's true.
So I'm assuming that the first movie will be the kids
and the second movie will be the adults.
I like that.
I like it too.
How it was done in the miniseries, but okay.
I don't have a problem with that at all.
That's fine with me.
I think that's a good type of storytelling for...
And I guess they haven't cast the adults, right?
I don't think so.
I mean, I haven't heard peep about one adult being cast.
So are you I'm assuming they're not even in the movie? Um, the
The main problem I had with the trailer trailer looks fine. It doesn't look bad
The main problem I had was that
Is this to me jump scares. It's not it's not a jump scare kind of thing. Yeah, it's a creepy
Also sell in the movie. I mean, that doesn't mean that's the movie. I hope not. Yeah, I hope not but it is not
you know and neither was the original adaptation. It's not a jump scare kind
of thing. It's not the conjuring. It's a very different, very unsettling thing.
You know, it's a lot to do with shame and the dirty secrets people have and
all these things. And it's not about a clown jumping out and starting you. Is it
the kids look about perfect, I do agree that the kids do look pretty much how
they're describing the book. The casting looks solid, don't like the moving
towards you fast and shaky shot of Pennywise. Yeah, that to me felt very
again like conjuring -esque. My thinking like, and here's why I'm an idiot, I'm
thinking okay, they know how much everyone loves it and has loved it for years.
either the book or the movie. Surely they wouldn't rush this into production and fuck it up.
However, you look at Poltergeist. That to me, as I was driving to Poltergeist a year,
two years ago, whatever. Poltergeist is one of my favorite movies horror or otherwise ever made.
And I'm driving there and I just felt in my stomach like, no, it's not going to be right.
And that had Rockwell and I was like, you know, I'm going to go in, I feel good,
Sam Raimi's involved. I mean, the movie was like 89 minutes or something.
It was terrible.
They just seemed tossed off and pathetic.
And there's an element of it that I feel very prepared for it to be that same feeling.
But I'd like to think that it's not.
Look, it's the curse of a book adaptation.
I think people that aren't that familiar with the book will probably get a pretty satisfying scary film.
and I think the people that are familiar with the book will say this you know
somebody said on Twitter it might be in these DMs here I can't remember but
somebody wrote to me it looks more like a remake of the TV movie I agree versus
an adaptation of the book and I that's what I thought too. Clive Baxter says not
a fan of mama or any harm movie with noticeable CGI but this looks promising
okay I almost think sure I'll give it that Paul Roseberry writes the
trailer looks sick definitely brings out the chills or brings on the chills
but seems to intentionally keep a clear look at Pennywise hidden I agree
given that the reveal better be his scariest look yet otherwise bullshit all
the way yeah I mean every every shot of him he's like got you know his face is
Obscured every every still online his face is obscured
You know, I just read on the in the trivia section here on IMDB that curry was like
I'd like to play this part, but I played that devil and legend
He's awesome in that he is awesome in that, but he's like the fucking makeup on that movie
It ruined my life. I never I went everyone do that again. He's like, would you just trust me?
Slap a little clown makeup on me and let me be scary out my own
Hopefully, that's the kind of thing they're doing here.
I don't know.
The MCT -2 Esquire strikes me as odd that Pennywise didn't talk in the trailer.
Room for an interesting choice from whoever the actor is playing him.
I disagree.
I'm not surprised he didn't talk.
They're clearly waiting.
They're clearly trying to parcel out.
And I am excited to see what he does sound like.
Cause I mean, to me, that's when the character's gonna come to life or not.
I'll tell you, I was gonna sound like like every other demonic clown.
Like, we all float. It's gonna be the same shit.
All right. Well, yeah, it's a good point.
Like how every Joker sounds the same, et cetera.
Uh, Carla. Oh, right.
Pennywise looks scary as fuck looking forward to it.
The trailer changed your expectations for this movie.
Uh, it did. It did. I'm not as excited as I was because for the reasons I've
already said I don't need to reiterate what do you think yeah I mean for me what I kind
of responded to was was were the shots of the town at the beginning because I felt like
that was at least showing a nice sense of of place you know like at least that they're
taking a little time you know they have the the little movie theater and that kind of stuff
I was like all right all right they're not setting it in New York or what they always do
with these reboots.
And they're not setting it in modern day, which I wrote.
Yeah, I mean, when the kid hits his head on the thing,
I was like, all right, but what worried me about that
is that so George is running down the street
and then he hits his head in the slips and falls,
I was like, this is a shot for shot remake
of the opening of the miniseries
and they were probably like,
I don't know, let's just have him hit his head,
make it a little different, because that's what it is.
I mean, it's every shot is the same
And then when he hit his head, I almost jumped because I was like, oh, that was something that was slightly different.
Right. Yeah, that's what a Cassie says here.
Lapped out loud when the kid hit his head on the sign.
Overall, looks promising. Definitely not as scary as the original, but still creepy.
I really hope it's not all jump scares, which we also said.
The kid at the end of the trailer was creepy as fuck though.
Yeah, you'll float too. You'll float too.
I don't agree with that. That to me felt like, that felt like a six -year -old kid.
going, I'm scared of this fucking kid, it wasn't, I've seen way, way from, I mean, you
look at the girl in the Ouija Origin of Evil movie, she's fucking creepy, man. I've seen
way creepier kids, and way more convincingly frightening kids. I didn't buy that kid in
that scene. And that's it. Those are your thoughts on it. And Pat, that brings us to the end
the episode, give out whatever info you want to give right now.
Folks, I'm still just doing my thing. I don't really have any plugs for you. I'm on Twitter
and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh. That's all I got. I urge you to check out the miniseries
because I think it is a very, just a nice version of it in a weird way. They put the
care into it. You know they took their time with it and that's my only concern. Who
am I to say that you know you watched three minutes of a movie? What do you know? But the
concern is very real. I'd be happy with a movie as effective as the original. I'll say that.
And the original left out all the stuff we're talking about like the kids having sex and
the big jobs and all that. Yeah. Yeah. The big the biggest thing with the original left
out was the gay bashing and stuff because the appearance of it is directly correlates
with these violent events that are happening in the town.
So I hope that that is a theme.
It sounded like that's what the original director wanted to focus more on.
He wanted to focus on what the background of this worries me actually, sorry, and I said
we were done.
But the original director said I wanted to give these characters stories
There had to be what who were they what were their experiences before this clown appears
To so we can justify why they're scared of this thing and why it's happening and he said and of course the studio just said
We don't give a shit about that. Yeah, slap some generic characters up there and like let's make it a scary movie
So that concerns me because the move the book itself is very very very
Much about your background and what you're dealing with in your life personally and
This guy, I mean he has a history of kind of walking off a lot of things
He walked off the second season. He walked off a lot of things but
His complaints about it all sounded like how do you not know that that's what horror fans and Stephen King fans want?
Right is for somebody to really dig in and because if you're not gonna do that and you're just gonna turn out the same shit
We've seen it right
I feel like this is probably not going to be our dream version of it, but if it's as effective as the original great.
Fair enough, I'm at Joderos Accomedy on Twitter and Instagram.
And as always, please go give me some nice reviews to help me bring the average rating of my albums up because of the trolls.
Uh, and this comes out next week. Oh, uh, when this drops, I will, I am in Australia right now for the Melbourne comedy festival.
So if you're around, come say hello, come see a show.
Good day, mate.
That was a hate gun podcast.