Hello everybody, welcome to we'll see you in hell.
Oh, the tales from the dark side episode.
You know that, you read it before you downloaded it.
Am I wrong, Pat?
You're not wrong, Joe.
This is Joe DeRosa, one side of your head.
And Pat, Walsh and the other.
That's right.
We're on either side of your head
so you can watch the movie up the middle.
If you choose to do so,
the We'll see you in hell podcast
is now part of the Fangoria podcast network.
For more info about the network,
including other programs,
how to follow this show, how to follow those shows,
or to find episodes of any show.
Please visit Fangoria .com.
Let's get on with it.
I'm excited about watching this tonight.
By the way, people at home,
start queueing up your Netflix.
Do you want to tell them about how we're going to be
at the Mile High Horror Festival?
Yeah, well, we'll tell them about that.
Well, you find tales from the dark side,
hit play, pause it on as soon as it starts
so we can all start together in a few moments here.
Yes, you want to tell them, Pat?
Okay, I'm just a little concerned.
I'll get the date wrong, but we're going to be in Denver,
Colorado, doing the podcast live.
We're not 100 % sure we're allowed to tell you
what the movie is, so we're not going to.
We will close it to the date.
And that date is October 3rd, which is a Saturday.
And we will be, if I'm not mistaken,
8 .20 in the morning.
I think we can tell them now because this
is going to come out the week of the festival.
Okay, then let's do it.
It's we're doing Maniac Cop 2.
Maniac Cop 2, which I have never seen.
I'm going to watch it ahead of time.
Yeah, I'm looking forward to it.
You haven't seen it either.
I have not seen it, and I'm embarrassed to say that.
I've seen Maniac, I've seen Cop in a half.
I've seen Stopper, my mom will shoot.
I've read Maniac McGee.
I've seen Mr. McGoo.
I never knew, whenever Maniac Cop 2.
I always thought Maniac Cop was, I didn't,
I didn't know it was like so lauded as a series, but.
I wouldn't have even thought horror necessarily.
I thought I would have thought Maniac Cop
was like an extra violent dirty hairy kind of thing.
Well, yeah, they told us that what we were doing
is Maniac Cop 2 and.
Be loved, and we're going to seem like buffoons
because it's apparently very beloved in the horror community.
Well, here's the thing.
We're not going to seem like buffoons, number one.
Have a little hate seeming like a buffoon.
Have a little more self -esteem than that.
We're going to do just fine.
There's nothing wrong with vulnerability.
That's what I've learned in this business.
Sure.
Is you got to have a little vulnerability.
The only comedians I like are vulnerable and let you in.
Who wants a conceded comedian?
Yeah, exactly.
You got to go out there, you got to say,
hey, folks, I'm not perfect.
I'm sorry, I've never seen this before.
But I just watched it last week and I loved it.
Right.
You come out and you're like, hey, I had a threesome last night
that everybody's like, oh, you come out and you're like, hey,
I don't know how to talk to a glial
than everybody loves you.
Exactly.
That's my advice for upcoming comedians.
And I would also say, glial.
I agree with that.
Let's start this movie.
Right.
And we can, you know, oh, and that was the one other thing
I wanted to say was when I, when
in February, I told us eight, thirty in the,
eight, twenty in the morning.
Yeah.
I was like, what?
Who the hell was going to come to a live podcast at eight,
twenty, and their response was people will always come for
maniac too.
Yeah.
That's when our maniac cop too, excuse me.
I love it.
That's when I knew we had a goody on our hands.
Yeah, I can't wait to watch it.
I'll be drinking at eight, twenty in the morning that day.
You know, you think, well, it's insane.
How could I possibly drink at eight,
twenty in the morning.
And then you remember old friend, bloody Mary.
Well, I go for screwdriver.
That's fine too.
There's a whole line of breakfast drinks that you forget about
to help the alcoholic who might enjoy a brunch.
You should have an aisle for it.
Yeah.
Super market.
All right.
You should be all cute up by now and paused on the first,
you know, frame or so, the movie will say,
one, two, three, the star is starting to come into the
Paramount logo, which is my favorite logo.
We'll say one, two, three, play, and we all hit play on play.
Here we go.
One, two, three, play.
And we're rolling.
The stars are swirling their way around the mountain.
All right.
This is Tails from the Dark Side.
The movie came out in 1990.
Turned a nice little profit for Paramount Pictures.
I thought I had never seen it, but as I watched it earlier tonight,
I started watching them ahead of time because otherwise I focused on the plot
and I don't talk as much.
I realized I had seen the opening, which we're about to see,
where Deborah Harry has a young Joey Lawrence.
It's not Joey Lawrence.
Daniel Lawrence.
Yeah.
The kid from actually Planschines, I don't believe it was one of my favorite movies.
They are brothers.
They look exactly alike.
Yeah.
And he's locked up in the kitchen.
And I remember being horrified by it.
I watched it now.
It plays as a comedy, if anything.
Yeah.
It's like the light -hearted wrap around story,
even though the premise is that she's going to eat him.
Right.
But...
I like a movie with a good reach around story.
Folks.
Let's start with you.
Let's start with the jokes, folks.
But yeah.
I saw this in the theater on opening weekend.
I couldn't wait because I was such a...
Tails from the Dark Side TV show fan.
And I was mesmerized to the entire thing.
See now, one part of it scared me.
I loved every minute of it.
Yeah.
See, you said one of your favorites of all time in the horror genre.
I'm nowhere near that.
And I think it probably has to do with when you saw it.
For example, I showed you tremors,
which I would consider one of my favorites of all time.
And you were...
You know, you enjoyed it, but we're fairly indifferent, too.
I was...
I was in a different...
I enjoyed tremors.
But to me, tremors is more of an...
of an action comedy with horror elements in it.
It's more of a...
a canine, if you will.
Or a turn up in my pitch.
Tremors was...
That age where I...
It's not...
I could handle...
Literally not scary.
There's literally nothing scary at it.
Oh, there...
There's a lot of monster attacks.
I'm saying I couldn't handle much, and it was right up my alley.
No one would say like, oh, tremors was fucking sick, bro.
I also like a monster with a personality.
I like a monster with some personality.
I'm not a fan of just a big, you know, lumbering worm.
I think doesn't really...
You mean a grabwood?
Yeah, a grabwood.
Sorry, excuse me.
Now you're going to see the...
The new tremors when it comes out.
I think it just did or it's about to.
They're up to like five, and I've been talking about it for years,
and they actually just discussed it on key and peel,
that I went with the series for about three
until they had them up and walking around like dogs.
Which is...
The whole hook is that, hey, we got a movie about giant underground worms,
and they just make them walk around like little dogs.
Right.
Just make cool joke, again, if you're going to do that.
Tremors people.
I'm not on a beef with a worm dog.
No.
That's one of the animals I'd like to see.
If I could...
Thing was definitely had the most effective worm dog.
Yeah, there's that twilight zone where the kid imagines the monsters.
Yeah, yeah.
And he always imagines them with like eight eyes and stuff.
He'll probably imagine a dog with like eight eyes.
It's called it's a good life.
And then the kid will be like, the kid will be like,
that dog was funny I made it at eight eyes.
But I got bored with it, so I made him go dead.
So my point is, if I was the kid that could do that,
I'd invent the worm dog.
And then I'd make it go dead.
Well, I didn't really follow that joke,
but I hope you enjoyed yourself.
I did.
The first and last, there's three segments on this wraparound deal.
My favorite type of horror, anthology horror.
I love it.
Yeah, I know you love it.
I like it kind of like, it's fun.
I wish this movie had had three different directors,
like a twilight zone in the movie.
It felt very stylistically similar to me.
Well, it's, but it's, it's what, now here,
let me tell you why I love the movie.
All right.
My favorite franchise in horror is Creep Show.
Creep Show one and two to me are masterful films.
This is arguably maybe the best of the three.
It's not called Creep Show, but it's the same group of people.
It's Tom Savini, George A. Romero and Stephen King.
We're behind this.
One of the stories in this cat from hell.
It was supposed to be in Creep Show two,
but they, I guess because of budgetary reasons,
they cut two stories out.
So it did make it into this.
And then the money to have a cat chase around a guy in a damn wheelchair?
Well, that's just a little more to the story than that.
But I guess the one special effects.
But the most part, it's a guy in a wheelchair yelling.
Tom Savini has gone on record as saying,
this is unofficially Creep Show three.
There is a movie called Creep Show three,
but none of the original Creep Show people have anything to do with it.
It's an abomination.
So how do they get the rights then?
I think they probably, the rights to the name were just probably up.
And it's not like they recreated any characters, you know?
Yeah.
But in my opinion, Creep Show one, Creep Show two,
and Tales of the Darks of the Movie,
it's a virtually flawless horror trilogy,
which is very hard to come by,
as even the most astute horror fan would agree.
Yeah.
And I think I find them pleasant diversions.
What is that?
You know, like they're kind of middle of the road,
cool little scary stories to me,
but I don't think of them as being great horror films or anything.
You mean the anthology stories?
The whole Shabbang, yeah.
Well, look, I will say anthology is not for everybody.
Certain people get annoyed because it's two,
they feel like they can't settle into it.
Yeah, it's a little too short to get,
you're too invested in anything,
and then right up my alley,
it's right up my short attention span alley.
Well, for this MTV generation, Joe.
Give me.
And you know, you're about 30, 40 years younger than me, so.
Give me a hot 12 to 18 minute tale any day of the week.
I mean, I love it.
Twilight Jones.
How about a hot 12 to 18 year old tale?
I'm not into that, Pat.
But you neither.
I'm glad you squeezed in another pedophilia, Pat.
I certainly did.
Yeah, there you go.
I held back a terrible joke just there that I,
I guess I'll share with you after.
Let's just say it involved the phrase,
squeezed it in.
I imagine.
I imagine as much.
Folks, tales from the dark side of the movie,
stars Steve Hashemi and Julianne Moore,
and maybe, if not their first film,
an early one for both of them.
Well, that was kind of cool for me.
If you're watching along with us,
the first story is starting now called Lot 249.
Right.
It's based on an Arthur Cohnin Doyle tale.
Starting.
And Hashemi.
It starts Bouchemi, Christian Slater and Julianne Moore.
Talk about a different time.
Slater's the big name in this.
Slater's the big name.
When this came out, Slater was the guy.
The other two, it was like, who cares?
Hot off, pump up the volume.
Yeah.
Which is a great movie.
Still a big Slater fan.
I get, I like that Mr. Robot show that he's in.
And I always get excited when I see it.
I haven't seen it, but I may check it out.
It doesn't, it's not jumping off the shelf at me,
but I've heard a couple of recommend days.
It's pretty great.
It's pretty great, but that's for another podcast.
All right.
You want Mr. Robot talk?
Go listen to the Roebot podcast.
All right.
You fucks.
What would the name of that podcast be?
The Mr. Robot podcast.
I don't know what out, what out.
You're a classic riff, Mr. Jones.
Look at these sweaters.
Actually sweaters of the time are these guys
just being painted as douchebags.
Well, they aren't.
They're douchebags.
I mean, this is very on the nose.
I think this is how douchebags dress in 87.
Did they, and this is 1990,
or were they just going off other movies of the 80s?
Is this 90?
Yeah.
Well, this is how douchebags dress back then.
It was a lot of sleeveless V -necks.
It was a lot of tennis rackets.
All right.
The douchebags in school used to play tennis.
That was what the boys used to do.
Sure, they still do.
Now, bullies now are real bullies.
They'll beat the shit out of you.
The douchebags at my school, high school,
I'll play golf.
Now, for the four year,
you're like more fratty type douchebag guy.
And then the football players were all just wild degenerates
like horrifying people to be around.
Yeah.
They spit sunflower seeds into your face.
Certainly the frightening people at my school
that I attended were not tennis players.
Right.
You know?
These guys are, this is how it goes in an Ivy League.
Sure.
That's how it is.
Bouchemi, by the way,
this was my introduction to him as a kid.
I had no idea who he was.
And I remember seeing when I first saw reservoir dogs
about three years after this.
Being like, oh my god, that's the guy
from Tales from the Dark Side.
Yeah.
It was so weird for me to see him in another role
because I only knew him from this.
Pretty much always been one of my favorite actors, really.
Now, has he had his teeth done?
Because his teeth looked particularly big
and crooked in this.
And I don't remember them looking like that recently.
Oh, no.
If anything, they look worse.
If you could say, if you could look at a picture
of Bouchemi from today and say that you think he said his teeth
done, I'd laugh you out of the goddamn room.
What are they?
So they still, he's still got those same teeth.
Yeah.
Like, open a tin can, you know?
Like, not think anything of it.
Kind of teeth.
Oh, hey.
God bless him.
Yeah.
Those teeth bottom a career.
Like chopping, remember those old cylinders of high C?
Like with one big triangle on one side
and one small triangle on the other?
Like, he'd just sort of chop in and then down it
and one disgusting gulp.
This would be, this would be my response
if I would, I'm Steve Bouchemi criticized my teeth.
Yeah.
Okay.
Yeah. Big old teeth Bouchemi.
These teeth bought me a Ferrari.
That's what I would say to people.
I, he definitely drives a Ferrari.
He seems like that guy for sure.
Favorite Bouchemi?
I'm gonna go with a fairly obvious choice and say Fargo.
I don't know how you could possibly do better than that.
You're nuts.
All right.
What do you got?
You put Fargo over reservoir dogs.
Yeah.
I put Fargo over reservoir dogs by about 5 ,000%.
It's insane.
One of my least favorite comb brothers.
Oh.
How do you live with yourself?
There's no one at home being like, yeah, he's right.
Fargo sucked.
There's no one at home doing that right now.
No one.
I didn't say Fargo sucked.
I just said it's, I like reservoir dogs better
and it's not one of my favorite comb brothers movies.
All right.
It's a good movie.
What do you, a lady killer's man?
Not tolerable cruelty.
Number one.
Lady killer has some laughs and so is the top of a cruelty.
I'm joking.
My number one obviously is Big Lebowski.
Yeah, that's fair.
I would follow it with possibly maybe a Miller's crossing.
Those crossing is great.
Raising Arizona might be my favorite.
But I love the show in Fargo, which was the question
because I said performance.
Now, Mr. Pink, I don't even understand the hell you're saying.
It's fine.
You're not a very tolerant man.
I'm very tolerant, which is a line.
I'm sorry I don't have the patience of a guy
that watches the same movie back to back in one night.
I mean, I don't know what kind of psychopath you are.
Well, I'm not watching it all right now.
I'm talking and I had never seen it.
So I would have been like, what's going on?
What's going on?
Why did they just do a terrible 80s wife?
But the fact that you're able to just sit in front of it
twice in a row is nuts to me.
No.
You're a synophile.
Well, I'm talking to you.
I mean, an insult.
If I, if it had been a movie I'd seen a hundred times,
I wouldn't have to do it.
But it's not an insult.
I just said it's nuts to me.
Look at this refrigerator.
They're supposed to be really wealthy
and they got that 50s Donna Reed fridge in the kitchen.
Maybe it's a classic.
What happened to this guy?
I like this guy that plays Julian Moore's boyfriend
who's like, who's like the definition of a white guy.
I feel like he might still, he looks like a character actor
who's in movies now, but it's not him for sure.
Yeah.
He's probably by this point either
strolled into the porn waters
or, you know, he runs a tire shop in the valley
or something like that.
He's got a good porn look.
I like it.
Yeah.
I think even now 25 years later he'd be one of those kind of
55ers hanging in there.
Yeah.
Coming by, you know, playing the neighbor who's visiting
the babysitter or whatever it is.
I don't know.
Oh, sweet boy.
You think they still have storylines in porn.
They still do.
And everything I watch.
I'm usually fast forwarding it.
The hell you're seeing that has a storyline in it.
Maybe bang brothers where they put a girl in like a bus
or something, you know.
Maybe I kind of seek them out, but I tend to go for something
a little longer.
I like to treat myself like a lady.
And those always have story in them.
I never like a mop.
A clip that like opens on a gaping butthole or something.
I don't need that in my life.
I like to be romance a little bit.
You'll still watch a thing where it's like,
you know, let's turn this into a porn now.
That guy goes, I inherited a mummy.
And then he opens the coffin and he's like,
oh, I mean, a mummy.
And a milk gets out.
Like, you would go over.
This is a real milk.
A mummy I'd like to fuck.
Should we write this?
You would watch that kind of porn.
Oh, no.
I'm not talking about if the story is just ludicrous.
I just mean if it's a simple, hey, you know,
your dad's out.
I'm your new stepmom.
You're home visiting for the weekend.
Give me a little back and forth.
That's a lot of the clips.
You know what?
I'm going to say something kind of profound.
I like a little back and forth before the in and out.
And that goes for life and in the erotic cinema.
All right.
I get the stories you're talking about.
I thought you were saying, like, old school, like,
everybody works at a hospital.
No.
No, I'm not doing that.
But I miss that.
You know, nurse, time to make the incision.
Right.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, yeah.
And then he sticks his penis in her vagina.
Right.
You get it?
I got it.
You need a shot.
Nurse, you head off down the hall.
I think Mr. Herman needed a sponge bath.
I like my incision bit a little bit better.
I would not as fucking competing with you, Joe.
You weren't.
But I didn't just, I didn't lift mine from Seinfeld.
That's all.
You're going to lift the Seinfeld bit from the famous episode of Seinfeld.
I don't know how you live with yourself.
Do you do this at work?
Well, I didn't know Seinfeld was a hardcore porno film.
What's that?
I'm saying, you know, how they get.
I know.
The side nurses and doctors off down the hall on their own stories.
Sort of like a pulp fiction.
You didn't also feature in Stevenson.
Which was an anthology film.
Well, sure.
Yes.
It is.
Three stories.
Yes.
Anything with three stories I wouldn't say is an at all.
I like the shemmy and pulp fiction more than I like them in Fargo.
I don't know what to say.
I'm joking.
Did you also love William H. Macy in Fargo?
I loved him in it.
Yeah, he was incredible.
He's great at it.
And so was McDorman.
She's wonderful in it.
And so is that Austrian guy whose name I can never remember that played in the past.
Peter Stormair.
Constantin.
Also in Seinfeld.
Well, we're bringing it back.
He played the guy who got the frog or thing across the street.
His name was Slippery Pete.
Folks.
Peter Stormair.
A bit of a resemblance to our leading jock man in this short story.
I wouldn't argue that.
You know.
What's your opinion of Julianne Moore as an actress?
She's wonderful.
I thought she was and then I hit a point where I never wanted to see her again.
And I've been there for five, ten years.
I think she's fantastic in almost everything she does.
I mean, she's unbeatable in bookie nights.
That bookie nights was twenty years ago.
So you're talking right into what I'm saying.
I'll name a recent one.
That David Kronenberg movie she was in about Hollywood maps to the stars.
Well, one of the most upsetting films I've ever seen in my life.
She's fantastic in that.
She was.
I just, you really see her acting these days.
She was terrible on 30 rocks.
She did a boss and accent that just really, you know,
sent me into my room for a couple days.
I couldn't quite deal with it.
And then, you know, she's just a little hammy.
Even in that still Alice.
I didn't like her.
I didn't see that.
She was great in Don John.
Yeah, I did like Don John.
I actually like Don John a lot.
I'm a great movie.
Still Alice is the Amnesia movie.
Or not.
Amnesia Jesus Christ.
Alzheimer's.
The subject I want to see the least.
I really hate anything to discuss with Alzheimer's.
Yeah, it's terrifying.
The whole movie.
I think I talked with this on Pete's podcast.
Was Alex Baldwin going.
But Alice, your glasses are on your forehead, Alice.
Alice, the car's parked right down here, Alice.
Alex Baldwin talks in that English accent.
Yeah, you know, when Alex Baldwin's in like a drama where he's not supposed to be like a tough.
Yeah, he defaults to like almost like a 1930s.
Sure.
Accent.
Now the story of still Alice is she's a younger woman that gets early on said Alzheimer's.
Yeah, she gets it's so depressing.
And then you know, Baldwin kind of.
I don't know.
He just keeps.
He tries to hang in and he winds up leaving her spoiler alert because the movie wasn't depressing enough.
Jesus Christ.
I used to work with people at Alzheimer's and there was a woman who was in her late 50s that had.
She was, she was gone.
She was off the map.
And it was very sad to see somebody that young.
I mean, it was sad to see anybody with it, but somebody that young with it.
It's my biggest fear.
And now we're really into a horror podcast.
Yeah.
What are your, what are your fears now?
That's why a horror movie about Alzheimer's.
I might not see that.
I don't like anything to do with Alzheimer's.
We've established that.
Let's, let's, let's lighten it up.
I don't need money to them.
You should.
You should treat people sitting in their cubicles right now wanting to split their throats.
All right.
Well, let's talk about Christian Slater in a blue tank top.
Turtle neck.
Did you wear turtle necks?
Now, my posture was always too bad for a turtle neck.
I look weird in one.
I, no one looks cool in them.
It looks that maybe like Bruce Wayne.
Bruce Wayne looks fantastic in one.
But I always wore turtle necks under a sweater.
It was kind of my signature look.
Oh God.
I look real, real nerdy for many years.
You look like one of these jocks at the Ivy League school.
But in a nerdy body.
You carry a tennis racket around with you.
Imagine the, the jock wardrobe, but with a real dorky face and body.
If I may say so, Pat and I had a poor ourselves a drink before this podcast.
I'm about halfway down my whiskey.
I'm so tired from working all week that I feel completely drunk right now already.
All right.
We'll keep it together.
It's together.
I just feel, I mean, I could, I could go to sleep in your arms at this moment
and not feel strange about that at all.
I would feel very strange about it.
I don't blame you.
I'm just trying to tell you where I'm at right now.
I think our listeners might enjoy a solo pod from me.
Or it might be like when Wayne left in Garth had to take over Wayne's world.
No, I don't look at it that way.
I look at it as the, as like when Joe Perry did the solo album.
Sure.
I look at it as a positive.
All right.
The fans are going to like it.
They're going to support it.
What was it?
What was Joe Perry's solo?
I can't remember.
It was the first thing I could access in my head.
Oh, one of my, my friends out here is his son.
He's a delightful guy.
He's at my house for the party.
I am friends with, I am friends with his stepson.
My friend Aaron is his stepson.
My buddy, Anthony.
I'll just shout him out.
Anthony Perry.
Junior.
It was Anthony and one of the kids in the band.
The three brothers band.
Yes.
Tab the band.
Yeah, me and Burry used to hang out with those guys.
Nice guys.
I missed him at your party.
Unless he was there and we just didn't recognize each other.
He was there.
I love those guys.
Yeah, they're great.
They're great guys.
Look at us.
Name dropping again.
Folks, if it's your first listen.
Themes that reoccur on this podcast.
Pedophilia.
Name dropping.
Yeah.
Both despicable.
Who knows which is worse.
But we're not dropping like fucking huge names.
We're saying my buddy is the son of Joe Perry.
You were going on and on about.
About it.
That's a great shot.
By the way, when the camera goes past the mummy.
It's a great shot.
But you think that mummy might be a guy with a mummy helmet on.
Like could there be any?
I guess mummy's a real.
It's a real mummy that they brought to life.
Just mummies to me.
It's always like.
Mummies.
You know, even in the mummy.
I was just kind of like just push him over.
It's a mummy.
They're not scary.
We did a monologue when Pete Holmes still had his talk show.
And it was about what monster is the scariest monster.
Uh -huh.
And I wrote a lot of the monologue.
And I remember the section on zombies and mummies.
I said zombies aren't scary.
Because they just they just wander around slowly.
Right.
They'll look like your grandfather got loose from his bed at the home.
Sure.
You know, you just want to see if he needs if he needs somebody to if he knows where he is
And if he needs somebody to escort him back to his room.
Right.
You know, that's all I feel about mummy.
Did you not think that joke was funny?
No, I'm with you.
Why didn't you laugh at all that joke?
It's a funny joke.
It's like your grandfather got loose from his bed at the home.
Yeah, I mean, we just get off Alzheimer's.
And now we're talking about a grandpa not knowing where he is.
All right.
Well, you know, these people got to get through this.
Brains in the fruit bowl.
Mummy pulled out the jock guys brains.
And what brains in the fruit bowl?
And the seal of a spoon.
Mummy in the light of the moon.
Julianne Moore is hamming it up.
Now, she seems kind of natural here.
And she did to me up until like magnolia.
She's way, way, way over the top.
And she's playing like a real coked out, drugged out lady.
I've never seen her be hammy.
You said you thought we saw.
It's a newer development for her.
We saw black mass the other day.
And I thought Peter Sargegar was phenomenal in it.
And you said you thought he was a little hammy.
And I didn't.
I thought he played it like a guy that was on a lot of coke.
I liked him.
I wanted more of him in the movie.
But he just was in kind of a different thing.
And it gave the movie some energy, which I felt it really needed.
The thought black mass is surprisingly very slow.
I got to tell you.
I rewatched the documentary tonight about Whitey Bulger.
And it reframed the movie for me.
And it made me appreciate the movie more.
OK.
And I also think that Bulger wasn't an informant.
And I actually believe his story over the FBI story that he was.
I mean, everybody was lying.
So it's really anybody's guess.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I just for some reason I believed his story a little bit more.
OK.
Yeah.
You got Julianne Moore sit in front of a bloody fridge.
Your boyfriend's been murdered.
Christian Slater looking like a young John Travolta.
Always doing a, a, a Nicholson impression in these early days, especially.
They couldn't cliche this up more.
They're now at the funeral of the dead boyfriend.
And Christian Slater and his rich sister are drinking brandy out of snifter.
Sure.
Would have killed you to throw me a snifter tonight by the way.
I don't even own a stifter.
Look at that chair.
That's a terrible chair.
I'm trash.
I don't own a snifter.
Who does this?
It's like an episode of Frazier.
Yeah.
Serticulous.
We had the guy on our show this week.
Gil.
Remember Gil from Frazier.
Well, you just watched the entire series for some reason.
You remember Gil.
Who the hell plays?
Who's the hell is Gil?
He's like the chef.
I'll do my impression of you.
And you'll know who he is.
Oh, Gil.
Yeah.
The food radio guy.
I go, where do I know you from, man?
You know, he's 70 years old now or something.
I go, where do I know you from?
I mean, because, well, I did only live in seasons of Frazier.
He talks like a real?
That's how he tells.
Yeah.
Really?
He was also, well, no.
Oh, I don't want to say anything.
He was a little, I kind of stayed in character.
Like, he came out last night and he was like, where's the bathroom?
My friend goes, oh, it's right over here.
And he goes, I know!
We're like, what was that?
I don't get it.
It wasn't a joke.
I think he was just kind of like, don't tell me where I'm going.
But why did he ask then?
Joe, that's the point of the story.
We were all kind of like, what's this guy's deal?
I don't know, but what was his character?
Was it a man that would ask questions about you?
He was a snooty butler, you know, a very annoying butler.
Uh, he's 70?
Oh, at least.
Yeah.
Really?
He's very funny on Frazier.
He was great.
Uh, yeah.
He's got a very distinctive voice.
I love the show so much.
I'm rewatching many episodes of it.
Well, outside of Seinfeld and Curb, you're enthusiastic.
Yeah.
Seinfeld, Curb your enthusiasm.
The Golden Girls.
The Honeymooners.
Mr. Belvedere.
Frazier.
Those are my five where it's like Mrs. Belvedere.
I'll rewatch them.
I don't care.
I love it.
Belvedere, vodka.
All right.
I haven't seen Frazier in, uh, at least 15 years, but I used to like it.
I would go as far as to say there are moments that are hysterical.
Oh, wow.
Okay.
It's one of the most last.
They got a good farce thing going when they would.
It's great.
Hit it.
Yeah, for sure.
And it's one of the most laugh out loud sitcoms to me.
Those five to me are like to me gutterly laugh out loud sitcoms.
For the most part.
If you were texting with Frazier, you would text LOL.
I would text LOL.
All right.
I'd also text STFU.
Shut the fuck up.
Yes.
Mhm.
Because he'd probably say a thing like, do you want to meet for a brandy?
And I'd say shut the fuck up.
But not telling him like shut the fuck up.
Like I hate you.
Saying it like, how Frazier shut the fuck up.
I love it.
Yeah.
You know what I mean?
I bet Frazier would have a lot to say about emojis.
What do you think you'd say?
Well, now I'm just want to talk like Gil, because I got that in my head.
I don't, I can't really do my, my Kelsey grammar on Twitter corrects people's grammar,
which I love.
When somebody corrects my grammar, I say thanks a lot, Kelsey grammar.
And nobody laughs ever.
Uh, on the...
Just like how when I order a drink at a bar, I go, I think I'm going to have a little ditty about Jack and Diet.
Never got to laugh at any bar ever.
I do it at least once a year, because I'm like, somebody go laugh.
Even if I got a bartender, I'm like, this guy's got a good sense of humor.
I'll do it.
They always get it.
It's not like they don't get it.
They just never laugh.
And it hurts.
You want to hear my bar bit?
Did nobody ever laugh that?
Sure.
I should try to do a guy that didn't know how to order drinks properly.
Okay.
And I'd go, uh, give me a white Russian.
Uh, no line, please.
You know, stuff like that.
It's pretty dead material.
Do me a, do me a favor.
Bloody Mary.
Easy on the whiskey.
Yeah.
And just a pinch of the canoe.
Like I would just drink order wrong.
Nobody ever thought it was funny ever.
Yeah, I'm, I'm big on like at a party when you first get there.
These are all very dead material.
I love dead bits.
Sure.
They don't die, they don't hear me too.
Any party like when you first get there and they're like, you want to drink, what can I get you?
I'm like, I'm going to do a white wine and red bull, please.
You always try to get it as a funny, funny blend.
But you'll never be Tanckere Antonik from Kingpin.
Tanckere and, no it's not.
I'm sorry.
Tanckere and Taps suites.
Tanckere and Tanks, you're a real dreamer.
You've got a long drive ahead of me.
Well, what we've talked about previously on the on the podcast.
Kingpin has the two funny string quarters of all time.
Tangerine tab as you just said and then later when the dickhead boy for in bowler guy is to get the party goes
Hey sport
Coca -Cola Coca -Cola. What an asshole. That guy is only in Farley Bros movies, and I think he was like an entertainment tonight
Correspondent who is not a great actor and throughout kingpin is wearing eyeliner
Yes, which I find the troops are and in a movie where everyone is insulting everyone's appearance the entire time
No one says a word to him about wearing it, but I will tell you his delivery of hay sport Coca -Cola
Yeah, oh, no, like this guy this guy should have wanted to ask him. He was a very effective use. Yeah
Yeah, the now we're at the part in the movie now if you're watching along with us Christian Slater is about to he was he's putting lighter fluid all over
Steve Bouchemmie because you know Steve Bouchemmie has
Somehow gotten this mummy to kill his sister and his best friend and
Now he's gonna try to have the mummy kill
Well, not he's gonna just burn Steve Bouchemmie alive. Excuse me. Now Slater in this scene
Even if you're not watching I'd suggest you go watch it
Afterwards because Slater is really Nicholson. Yeah, yeah, Nicholson
In up the entire scene his most Nicholson he was probably heathers or maybe cuffs
But he he was just doing straight impressions for like a 10 -year period
I find his pump up the volume to be incredibly super. Yeah, this is all in that same two or three year period all the great themes have been turned into
Theme parks. Yeah, I still love that line. It makes no sense. No, it's completely
It's a very 80s 80s lawn where you're like that's deep man, but it's not yeah
Well, he used to say that Nicholson was his idol
Well, sure and but here's the thing. He naturally sounds like Nicholson. Yeah, and almost I mean a little bit has a look of a young Jack makes yeah
So, you know, it's not all you know, it's kind of like how it's kind of like how action Bronson sounds like Ghostface killer
Yeah, exactly who in a video said that action Bronson should be killed
I saw that I didn't really approve Ghostface's response. I didn't either over the top
I understood why Ghostface was a little upset, but I didn't think he should all call for a man's death over it
No, I mean stealing somebody's flow. That's been going on for centuries
Paddy, I mean, you know, sometimes I think people in this town are stealing my flow. They're not job
They're not this I thought was this supposed to be a little blowjob bit because it sure felt that way to me. No
Like the director wasn't like hey, we've kind of framed this so it looks like that guy's really blowing Steve bishammy
I never once in my entire life ever thought that and I've seen this movie a hundred times
You're a pig with a filthy mind. That's where I went. Sorry, you're disgusting pig
I just want to see Steve bishammy get blown up. Maybe they let that pig talk flight CPS on your foul mouth sitcom
You were fun, but not on this podcast. Did you like
The mummies and the scorpion kings and all that garbage?
I'm sort of tipping my hand on how I feel about them, but they're okay
I mean I the first one's pretty good
You know, it's that's more of an Indiana Jones type of thing than a horror movie
I want to date with this girl once
I would say six minute sorry to brag six minutes into the meal she goes
Like so like you like movies so like what's like a movie?
You can just watch like whenever it's on you just have to finish it and I probably said Fargo, you know or something like that
And she's like for me
It's the mummy
I will always watch the mummy when it's on and I was like that bad
Okay, but I was like losing interest rapidly, but I'm gonna hang in here and then this girl talked about that mummy a lot
It went on and on and she thinks Brendan Fraser is so cute. I think this is very endearing
But it wasn't funny. It was just like the girl seemed to have a real Jones for the mummy
I think it's I think it's endearing
I don't I don't think it's endearing because it sounds funny
I think it's endearing a girl really loves the movie the mummy all right
It didn't didn't work for me somebody being passionate about the mummy. I don't have time in my life of that
Not be passionate about it. She was and you're heartless bastard. Yeah, exactly that couldn't understand
She's not into your indie house drama bullshit. I like a wide variety of movies
But speaking of a indie house drama bullshit. I did just like I saw
Good night mommy
Dying to see it. I might go tomorrow night. It is so scary
You should see it's gonna leave the Los Filos up here again tipping my hand as to wear me and Joe live
but it was
Really scary and really tense and I loved it good night mommy. It's a German horror movie basically only three characters
Some other people pop in but it's two
Twins they're like ten years old their mom comes back with her face all wrapped up in gauze much like a mummy keeping it on story
Was she in an accident or is it plastic surgery?
Well, I'm not gonna answer any of those questions
But it comes back and the kids start to suspect that it's not their mom basically and it was that's the premise and it's very very scary
You should see it. It's great. Okay, very good
Now isn't this cab driver in the scene somebody famous is that Joe pantoleoni it wasn't right
No, but I now you mentioned I think he might have was it I don't know. It just look like a way buffer dude
I think I feel like that cab driver is somebody that I should record by the way that was another trope in eighties movies like the cab drivers were always like these
SNM
Leather there's chains all through the cap. They do that in a trick plane chains and automobiles
Yeah, the other well the guys got pornel over his car. Yeah
Speaking of the cab drivers the next story that's gonna be on in a few moments cap from how it starts buster point
Dexter played a cab driver and Scrooge yep, you know it
Yeah, with William Hickey, so
He was in Scrooge. No, he's in christification
as you know on the Lewis. Yeah, but what we even you're just saying they're both ahead next year about one year prior
They were both in some great classic Christmas movies another in this together with a cat Scrooge could be my favorite Christmas movie
I would argue with that I love Scrooge
I have my favorite Christmas movie. I would say
It's a wonderful life is one of my favorite movies. Mm -hmm homalone
I love homalone, but I saw when I was 10 too, but I mean for God's sakes. It's your favorite
Yeah, it's a favorite Christmas movie of mine. Christmas occasion is a favorite Christmas. I love Christmas vacation
Grimmlands is a favorite Christmas movie. I love grandma's out. Yeah, I'll tell you what my second to just
Scrooge to disgusting your voice when we slightly disagree on something look and the cat from our stories opens with a cab
Yeah, I
Will tell you my second place to Scrooge. I can't wait to hear it love actually. Yeah, I love love actually makes me cry every time
I think though that it's you know
It doesn't feel at all Christmasy except for a few little sections. Oh, I disagree wholeheartedly. I don't know
I think they covered the Christmas bases nicely in that film
I think that movie would be a nice
entertaining picture, but I think that the Alan Rickman
Emma Thompson story takes it over the edge into something better
It's a wonderful film. It's a wonderful line. It's the huge grand story. It's touching. My favorite story though is is a bill
Bill Nye
Is that his name?
Definitely not Bill Nye the science guy. Who's the guy that plays the rock star in it that was in Sean of the dead?
Oh, yeah, his name is Bill Nike. Yeah, very close. Yeah, yeah
My that's my favorite story him and his manager. It's it's it's it kills me at the end when he tells his manager
Like you're my best friend. I love you. Yeah, it's a pretty great movie anytime really anytime in a movie someone is telling someone something
They have wanted to say for decades that'll always put a little lump in my throat. I'm a sucker for it
I'm a sucker for it now William Hickey. Yeah, the star of the bill Hickey bill Hickey
Well, sometimes he went by William. He always went by William, but I called him Bill
Uh
My friend used to do that like he'd he'd like refer to stars like bobby denara movie stars like with familiarity Jimmy com
Yeah, he'd be like he'd be like that's the great thing about math out
No, I always wanted to be like you're a you you you're you're a social
Your social studies major at a state school, but he you don't know math out. Yeah, calm Walter math out, you know a lot of
Things it depends on the person, but there's so many things people will do when talking about action stuff that bothered me so much
But really like you know if you were to say to me. Oh, you know
Pacino was so great that would
But William Hickey I remember this when I studied that was a theater minor in college and when uh
William Hickey died
They had his obituary up on like the Bolton board in the theater department
So he must have gone there, right
Now it was just like they would post when famous actors or whatever past
I think though. I don't think he went there, but anyway um
He was like
When he died he was only like in his 60s. He had like some kind of yeah, he had some kind of physical looks like a god damn cool
I thought he was
He was so funny in christmas vacation. Yeah, he's great. I thought he was like 95 years old
He was he was actually young he had like you know he had some kind of
Disorder or something and he just he looked he was sickly, you know, I guess I like when his wife who was the voice of Betty Boop by the way
That's who the place is wife. I never make a stale the original Betty Boop from the 30s
And she was oh dear did I break wind and he goes jeez says did the room clear out Bethany hell no she means presence
Yeah
Then later on she goes I hear something a weird squeaky sound and he goes you couldn't hear a dump truck driving through a nitroglycerin plant
Yeah, yeah, he just makes kind of a lame old wisecrack seem new
I was like when he goes grace
The blushing. Yeah points to his mouth to his teeth. Yeah
That's the mark of a good actor anybody can point to their mouth
He points to his teeth. Isn't that the guy that plays like breaking bad
But isn't he also like isn't he in the usual suspects? No, I'm thinking of the other guy
Yoshi. Oh, yeah, well that guy had a huge role in breaking bad. He was the guy who winds up with the
Yeah, bomb, you know thing on his wheelchair. Yes
I like that guy. Yeah, I also like the Kobayashi guy. He passed away recently
Yes, people always die unfortunately
Eventually we all die
So the times that the hands have an evil cat most of the time with the hands of an evil cat
So this one was written by Georgia arrow marrow. No, this is based on a Stephen King. Oh, yes
I'm sorry based on a Stephen King story. Yes, and the first and third were written by Malcolm McDowell
Who I always missed took with Michael McDowell from a clockwork orange no Malcolm McDowell was from a clockwork orange
And this is Michael McDowell. You're right
I actually was in the process of confusing it while I talked about how I confused. Yeah, not to be confused with Roddy McDowell
No, or Andy McDowell
Yeah, hey, I'm gonna tell you my joke about Andy McDowell. What you ready for this? How many people have a joke about Andy McDowell
This is what keeps me big in the stand -up circuit. Go ahead
What do Andy McDowell and my uncle Gary haven't common? What?
They both ruined four weddings in a funeral. Oh god
Fuck you
That's a good joke
When I hear a one -liner I wrote for work the other day. Yeah, well, I'm not gonna laugh at it now
After I get an oh god from you
This is a good one -liner. I had to write a one -liner for like a bush belt kind of thing. Okay. They said uh
Either my cook is becoming one hell of a nag or my wife is becoming one hell of a cook
I
Mean maybe I had to be a part of the scene. I don't think that's a good one -liner. Okay. It's a it's like a Milton Burley kind of thing
Look, I'm still a little wounded from the treatment of my endemic delta. It wasn't a well -crafted joke. I'm sorry
Well, of course it was and it's a huge hit on Twitter and if you're gonna spike that's all that really matters. Wow
Congratulations 13 you know who loved it think you're funny our friend genius comedian Karen Kilgarif
She loved it, Joe. I bet I could get a different take out of it on her. Well go ahead and try
I'll call her tomorrow. I'll ask her what you really think of that four weddings in a funeral tweet
And then she like she'll be taking the phone away from her head laughing
Michael McDowell
Yes, we're also wrote beetle juice
A masterpiece I'm concerned. It is with somebody named Warren
Scarin so which I I would have to assume with some sort of pen name
But I think the reason I was watching this is because I was trying to seek out other movies the writer of Bealjuice had done
But this doesn't really have that feel to it
um
Bealjuice like and the guy hadn't done a lot of other stuff especially nothing in that tone
Bealjuice is a real special thing. I think Burton must have had a lot to do with it too. I love Bealjuice
I'm excited that they're doing a sequel. Yeah, it's just what pet what I'm gonna keep my hopes at a
60 % because why would I not Burton's directing it ketens in it when owner writers in it
What's not so like well? They keep going back and forth on it
They got the guy who wrote fucking dark shadows to write it which was a
Terrible movie. It was better than I thought it was gonna be
You must have thought it was gonna be real damn bad John. I mean, I don't know hold on though
I want to look up Bealjuice and see now. Why do you think the original writer isn't writing it?
Because he's dead he died at age 49 from what?
I don't know. I just looked it up and he was dead at 49
I'm on the old iPad here and of course. It's an iPad mini
From however many years ago. It's the first iPad mini and as soon as iOS 9 came out the thing doesn't work properly anymore of course
Unbelievable
All right, I'm looking up Bealjuice and Wikipedia Wikipedia Glenn Shaddick's also dead who played. Yeah, Otho. Otho
One of my favorite characters in the whole film. I've probably I would say I've seen Bealjuice
Maybe more than any other movie other than maybe home alone or Roger Rabbit
They were they hit me in that 10 -year -old. I'll watch something a million times wheelhouse
Warren scaren died at 44
44 sorry, not a screen name. That's his real name Warren scaren. No, no, I was
Okay, Warren scaren is dead, but so is so is so is Michael McDowell at age 49 well that must movie was cursed
Warren scaren
What's it say here first success was getting the film the getaway shot in Texas
I like the guy driving force behind the distribution of the Texas chainsaw massacre
That's great notable writing works include Beverly Hills cop two very funny. Mm -hmm Batman
Yeah, he was in the Burton camp
He also
He had also written unproduced sequels to the jewel of the Nile
Now did he write the Bealjuice goes Hawaiian sequel that was bandied about or did that never actually go to script well how about this
He wrote a he wrote a Bealjuice sequel that was never made called Bealjuice in love. Did you know that no
But Bealjuice goes Hawaiian. I think was offered to Kevin Smith
Bealjuice goes Hawaiian yeah, who was a project that was like
Shopped around for a while about 10 years ago and what was it about
Bealjuice in Hawaii
One of the worst things ever heard in my life. Yeah, of course. I have no I mean Burton
Can't make a sea movie these days for my money. I heard big eyes was good. It was fine
It was fine. Look
You know, I hate to say it. I'm a fan of Burton's earlier work
But for the most part Burton's stuff was a lot of was a lot of look and not a lot of substance. Oh, I
Completely disagree as always with you Jim
Uh McDowell died of AIDS
Michael McDowell, he died of AIDS. Jesus Christ says he was terrible diagnosed with AIDS in 1994
Well, AIDS all simers were hitting all the fun topics tonight folks to real pick me up of an episode tonight
Whoo
It's getting a little dark. No, but I mean I look I'm I'm gonna say I'm gonna say this right now and I don't care who I piss off
I you know, I never thought Edward Siserhands was that great
Oh movie, I don't know. I don't know what to say to that
You know, I loved Edward Siserhands. I love Peewee's big adventure. I love that man
I love Batman Returns. I know you hate Batman Returns. Batman Returns is not a good film. I think it's an A plus. Oh, just stop it
It's idiotic all those early Burton's I think are just fucking classics, but then again Batman Returns is an A plus for me
Yeah, you can't get out of here. I don't believe you believe that but I do
And I'm saying it and why would I not so you you never problem with penguins with missiles on their backs?
That's just fine. No again
That's the movie I saw when I was 12, but when I watch now I still love it just as much
I saw it when I was 13 and I knew it sucked in I was like this sucks. I saw it in the theater. Well, no, you would have seen it when you were
17 because you're older than me
I was not 17 so you didn't see it when you were 12 it came out 92
I was born in 81 and I saw it in the theater. Let's look that up. I'm gonna look that up. I'm so I know that is true
I'm gonna I'm gonna look it up. Hold on a second. I was so I was 11
and you would have been
I'll tell you in a second that's a very different age
But I don't know why you wouldn't love it because Batman Returns was so fucking dark
Like way ahead of its time. It first of all, it wasn't dark
It was it was it was weirdly dark in certain places it was like psychosexual and weird and awesome
It was weirdly dark in certain places
And then it was
Oddly stupidly comedic in other places. It's dumb
That people go to the penguin speech and start throwing tomatoes at him
Where the where the where the gag is the penguin actually says
What kind of people bring fruit and vegetables to a press conference? It's like it's stupid
No, the gadgets are dumb like they're they're too ridiculous the way they work
It's not political. There's the thing where Batman pulls a chunk of concrete out of a wall
And it like see you always get hung up on this shit. It's Batman
It's still like you put your magazines pulling a hunk of
Concrete all Max Shrek Max Shrek not even a character from the comics like why are they adding
Don't add a character. We'll see. I never give a fuck about that shit
That returns to me is so much better than any comic book movie made in the last 20 years that everybody thinks is so genius
I think it's great. It's in tone of what it should know when it's fun
It's been the dark night
Don't you can't better than the certainly better than Batman begins both of Burton's Batman's are better than Batman
Oh god. Yeah, you're just and the dark night
It's an odd comparison, but I'd say they're they're about on a par the dark night is probably a little better
Oh my god, but depending on the day I might like Batman returns better than Batman one
Pat you're out of your what are you talking about? Sorry, I know I'm not alone here either
They may they took so many liberties with it the way catwoman becomes catwoman. It's like ridiculous liberty shit. We'll never bother me
well
Look that this is this is what the difference is with for being logical nerds who are super into
Comic book which at this point is the world everyone is into comic books. I'd never have cared about them at all
So when we go into a
Movie like this you guys are all going in like and well what's gonna be different than my graphic novel
And I'm going in like a child ready to be entertained. I'm not entertained by these I wasn't going into it like that
But I was smart enough to know by the way
I was 14 when this film came out I was smart enough to know that when this came out catwoman
Becoming catwoman because catch chew on her fingers makes no fucking sense
Now whether or not they're making up their own origin stories a different argument
Well, I was all bite her and she's you know what happens in the book? Is there like radio active?
No, she's just like a cat. She's a cat burglar. She's like an anti hero in the books
And she has no cat power. No
And even if she did why would cats chewing on your fingers give you cat power?
Well, they're like they there's a bunch of cats like attacking so stupid so you can either go
Okay, I'm in a ridiculous world and like this scene looks amazing
That's the penguin the penguin one of the coolest like
Sort of like John Gotti meets Donald Trump characters in comic books like this super billionaire like
Pulling the strings puppeteer kind of crime boss villain and they turn him into this like mutant
Like it's fucking all that dumb Tim Burton shit like I want to find beauty in the obscure. I want to find beauty
prettiness in the
Dream of a better
Burgess Meredith. That's a penguin for you
It's ridiculous. It's just and then they add this third villain and it's too much. It's like it like what
Christopher walk and extract. I'm extract barely makes an appearance
Oh so bad you must like it more. It's not so bad. I can't even put up with us
I think I'm playing his son. It's literally like daddy
Moody daddy. It's stupid. It's a it's not a good movie. Do you prefer Batman and Robin?
No, those are dogs shit
Okay, well, you're talking about Batman returns as if it's dogs show to make your point
I will not dog. I will put this is this is the height of Batman returns to me
It's Christmas time and I want to take a nap
That's Batman returns to me. It's Christmas. I'll put it on a fall asleep to it
Because I don't care enough to keep watching it
But it's Christmasy enough that I find it comforting. That's it. The first Batman I'll watch
I'll watch the first Batman
I love them both dark night. I love them. I have to dark night. I'll tell you how much this world allows
For all these things. It's a democracy
I can't believe it. I'm looking it up. No, it's got an 80 % what does
That returns. People love Batman return. You're stupid
Here's another thing
Let's have a whole new villain with the penguin. Okay, cool. I'm into that. Let's make all the penguins henchmen exact rip -offs of the jokers henchmen
They're all clowns for some reason. It's stupid
It's it's not creative. It was like a paint by numbers movie. It's a bad movie
I think it's a visually spectacular movie that gets into some really weird stuff about how we all wear masks and relationships
It's very sexual
It's very exciting. The action sequences are great. I love the winter vibe
I love walking though his part may be superfluous. I really love Michelle five for his cat woman nobody's ever done that better
She's are sure and I don't think anybody's done the penguin better
She plays a good cat woman
But the the the the writing of the cat woman the her origin and everything to me is stupid. Well, it's stupid
By the way, Selina, but it's all stupid Selina Kyle isn't a fucking raggedy beaten down secretary
I love that to hurt transformation in that. I fucking loved it and I think a lot of people did
Selina Kyle is like is like a is like a borderline like prostitute
That's like like that lives in like a slum made a different choice which I think is a better choice
Seeing a prostitute then put on a leather out. That's not a transformation. That's not an arc
Well, you're the one that likes all the weird sexual stuff. You probably like a couple hookers running around that film
No, I I don't have any opinion on how hookers would have factored into that
While you expel all your perverted
fantasies through one of my childhood heroes
Batman yes, okay
No room for your filthy thoughts in my Batman mythology. Well, I said I liked her being a
Dowdy secretary and you said you wanted her to be a
Perved out prostitute and now you're lecturing me on morals
This looks terrible by the way this whole thing with the purple fringe around the outside
What's the cat's perspective looking at yeah because all cats see things with a purple ring around the lens
It's
It's just a bizarre choice
Cats have green eyes at least make it green. It's black and white. It's black and white with the faintest yellow
It's black and white with the like tiniest hint of purple around the edge
It's so it's like the I never even noticed the purple so you just said that all right
All right, Joe, but you know
Look you've got a more stewed eye on it. We got to make this trip to Denver. I don't know at this point
I just have never also by the way has screamed to me in a restaurant about aliens being a terrible movie
No, I never said that is a lie. Oh, we can call alien three no you hit Joe
As God is my witness you're upset about aliens and you're very very upset about Terminator 2
Oh, yeah, I lost stand by that and these are just kind of movies that are just generally considered classics
But there's no like fun back and forth. You're always just like so angry my argument with you about aliens was
I said some people make the argument that it
Turned the franchise for being a horror suspense sci -fi movie into an action movie and some people don't like that about it
That was mainly argument they made an interesting choice and I went with them
Uh, and if we were having a discussion about the big picture of James James Cameron's work
I probably said if aliens is I don't think we can survive that time after that badman returns
Because we saw a Ford Fairlane and the writer of Ford fail on and badman returns was in attendance
And we already had kind of an early version of this argument
Uh
Now did and that guy said that guy said
They said you wrote
The adventures of Hudson Hawk Batman returns and they named one other one of his movies and he said yeah
That was my failing down period. He said that
That was my failing to I don't think that guy would think that badman returns
He's shit. He's he said. I'm one of the most hated men in comic books. He said that
Well, okay, I don't like comic books the writer said it
Jesus Christ. I don't like comic books. Joe saying a movie about you know
Jesus where he's a pimp is good or something if I could watch the fucking Avengers or Batman returns 10 times
I'd watch badman returns 10 times. Listen, I'm not saying you got to love the Avengers. I'm just saying Batman or everybody loves the Avengers
I don't love it. Everybody loves badman returns according to you. I love a movie that doesn't have to be three hours long
Look, I'm not sick. Do you hear me do you hear me defending the Avengers? People do love badman. I like the Avengers and they they they really don't
All right buster point my friends love Batman returns
But I've met your friends. Yeah, not a bright bunch. No, they're dumb
This the cat is killing buster point dexter. This was pretty effective. I guess this is what they couldn't afford in the original creep show
I don't think it was that they couldn't afford one of the effects in the story
I think they didn't have enough money to make five stories so they only made three and they cut two. Oh, okay. That's all
That's all this is pretty gross. Yeah, it's great. I thought the cat would burst out the tum tum
It's grosser that it comes back out of his mouth
But I like that the cat crawls into a stomach
Mm -hmm and just kind of incubates in there for a little while. Mm -hmm. Is that the right term?
Uh, it works. Why not? I'm very excited for the next story to come on first. We got to get through the end of this story
Yeah, the last story was the best. I mean it's fantastic
And it's got a real dirty 80s New York feel to it
Yeah, we're minding me a little of after hours, which is great. Scorsese movie that
It's always under scene. I would say it always makes me think of the fly. Mm -hmm similar to the gold bloom one
Yeah, like these people live in these big lofts and they're all artists and creators
That's what after hours was as well and they have no money or anything like that
I wonder like you think William Hickey's like all right. He got a sprained with blood fine
You got to do a couple takes whatever arse like just a miserable guy about it. What do you think?
I bet you I would be willing to bet William Hickey was probably a joy
Maybe I would think maybe I would think he was probably a joy
To be right. He's got a Burgess Meredith vibe. I bet you Burgess Meredith was a joy
He was also William Hickey was in
What's oh my blue heaven yep as the mob yeah, I hide now and he was in yeah
Yeah, my blue heaven does not hold up there you okay watch it how do I own it Pat I do too I watch it frequently no it does not
Steve Martin Rick Moranis two of my all -time fifth Steve Martin is so miscast in that part and he is
So unrealistic and not even attempting to be realistic in that part
Watching it as an adult. I was like this is one of the few movies where I can just say I was wrong as a child
I disagree
I say Steve Martin walks a fine line between cartoonishness and realism
Oh, well then watch it again. I've watched it a few months. Realism Joe. I always watch it. He made me realize him
He's ridiculous
It's a broader character than most of his comedic characters like his non -Mafia characters
I like the role. I think he makes it somehow believable. Oh, I buy it the whole time
Because the guy was a pastor
What it what it what is some of the lies he's telling when he's like dribbling that basketball
Why do we find all those stolen textbooks in your truck your car because I was delivering them
This whole thing is that he's always lying here stuff. I can't remember any of it though. I forget
Well, that's because it's a very forgettable movie
It's not it's structured terribly. There's like no story to it at all
That's stupid. You're stupid sometimes. I would have loved it as a kid. It's it's a horribly structured and plotted and acted film
I love Jane coon music is bad. Her name is Joan Kusak. I always love her. She's always a bright spot, but come on
I love the soundtrack my blue heaven is a wonderful song
Yeah, well that's fine. You can like the song my blue heaven. There's a wonderful version of it in the film
It's it's the version. That's the version of it. Well, there are many versions of it. Pat, it's a standard
It's the biggest one for sure. Yeah, it's an attribute of a version of it many people
I don't know if there's one that you know, you know
What's that people? This might be the final episode
Well, this might just be the final episode. Why are you getting angry? Never like this guy stand up
I'm just gonna say that Robert Klein. Yeah, every time you're there interviewing any comedian over 50 is like well, obviously Robert Klein was a huge inflow
All right, great, but he's not funny. I think he was like the first of
He was like sort of like they think the first like alt comic like he was the first guy to kind of like yeah
Be casual and wear sweaters and yeah, I've never seen a full set or something even I just I never
I own his box set. I own every one of his specials and it's you know, it's not totally for me
But I respect what the man did okay, you know sure can I tell you that?
Sure, and he plays a good agent in this story. It's kind of the right looks like Neil Brennan a little bit to me
He does and I can't remember what else I've seen him in
Everyone bars like this existed. Look at this bar. They're in well. They existed in these movies for sure
They also exist everywhere in St. Louis, Missouri if you want to come home with me this Christmas
I get involved in a darts tournament or tell you'd never ask
Hey, if you ever wanted to play a three -hour game of darts while pop a roach plays
Head to St. Louis and go to a bar, but this is a great little dive bar. Look at this. This is what you call your legal
I love spots like this man. This guy has been in a thousand movies James Remar
He's in so many movies to Django and Shane. He's always fine, you know, I love James Remar
Yeah, he gets the job done plays it good
When they when they put him up to it and he plays a dirt ball. He's very good at it. Yeah
Yeah, and he's about to make love to radon Chong who was a big 80s babe. I think she might have a body double in this
That how happened to her?
She's a good looking woman still she fills out a sweater. I'll tell you that much
I dated a girl briefly that looked like radon Chong
I mean it didn't work out unfortunately. She's radon gone, you know, oh Jesus
Yes, she is. I'm looking her up right now. I tell you this, Joe
You say to me she's radon gone. I'd laugh and we'd have a nice time
Out this you're just in this mode where you got a shit on everything. I say I don't think the listeners want them
Teasing you a little bit for God's sakes. Don't get all sensitive on she's radon gone
She's radon she is maybe patch everything. Maybe it hurts that she's gone
It was like I'm ready to joke about it. Sure. Have you ever thought about that? No, I didn't I don't think of course here at all
Didn't I did she die radon Chong? I believe she did
Did she die? I thought she died. I might be okay
All right, Joe
I don't think so wonder why radon left
Jesus
Squatted over
That's down worry that she died. Give me a second here. No, she's not dead. How about Maria, Kansita, Alonzo
Did she die another try named 80s? I believe that she did die. Oh, yes. How about
Mary Elizabeth, master Antonio from the abyss
No, she's like the abyss
No, oh fuck the abyss is such a great great movie. You don't like James Cameron
I'm not a big fan of his work and I hate Avatar. I'll give you that but I mean the abyss terminator two and aliens like what more do you want
Terminator two
Sucks all right. Well, let's let's move back. I can't do this tonight. I can't let's him. You watched it
I watch it a lot. I mean you want to shit on my blue heaven watch turn your two. It's just as ridiculous
But it's it's a science fiction movie so
Oh
My blue heaven was the anchor man of its day was supposed to be real Joe. I will slap the drink out of your hands
My blue heaven should have starred and he was he was the perfect age and everything
He should have it should have starred Alec Baldwin
coming off a beetle juice and a Miami blues
And he could have done it all in that moment. There's your ray done. Yeah, she's beautiful. She's hot
No comment on Alec Baldwin being the perfect choice for my blue heaven. You don't you never comment when you know I'm right
Listen, I didn't say you were wrong. It's an interesting premise. I haven't really thought about it. Yeah, sure
It'd be good
They're just I'm just kind of getting sad now because I'm looking at radon and thinking of that girl
I dated that looked like her and all right. I didn't work out give her a call tonight. She'll appreciate. There's radon naked for real
Okay, then maybe they're they're the real deal she looked in this movie
What I I paused it. I'll be honest with you
Also, this is a great monster for a $3 million budget
That's her now though. Oh
All right, she said I didn't I hate that I had that reaction. She's not a woman. Naturally. I'm sorry
So she's probably in her 60s at this. None of us would want
Them 25 years later put up against a photo of them from back in the past. She was born in 61. So what is she 56? Yeah, yeah
So there you go no 54
That this demon is really scary in this one
Yeah, I said it was a great demon on a low budget. No bullshit
I also dated a girl my time to look like that girl's bird beer
You dated a girl look at that demon kind of look like that demon in a weird way
Like if there was like a pretty version of that demon. That's what she looked like and once
Once now once I realized that I couldn't get past it. Mm -hmm had to break up with her over
A
A lot of relationships I've had are just something that I've been like
Hmm, and I get fixated on
I think my a lot of that might be growing up with Seinfeld. I called my buddy out on it the other day
That he finds something with every girl like date two and they're always ludicrous and I think it's growing up with Seinfeld
And he start to seem like normal reasons to end relationships
Every week Jerry having like Matt. She has got man hands. She's got a high voice. She's got a low voice at whatever it is
They start to seem like good reasons to end relationships with beautiful intelligent women because of Seinfeld
Well, I believe that those
Premises were written because they are good reasons to break up with somebody and that's where those jokes came from
And that's where they're so relatable. Yeah, I mean
But in order to survive and be in a relationship that goes anywhere
You have to be willing to look past stuff. That's a lot smaller than Jerry and George
Through away. Yeah, it's it's it's the women that George Cassanza threw away looking like he did or are just mind -boggling with no money
He's worse in uh, he's even worse in shallow how where he dumps that like really hot chick because she's got the weird long tail and then all along. He's hiding a tail
A tail here's a tail
That's the final gag in the movie. He has a vestigial tail
Is that a real thing that people get?
Maybe one or two probably but hell is it? What's a vestigial tail? What does he just he like you don't remember this he shakes his tail
You start talking about shallow how then I chime in with another fact about shallow how I'm just asking a question Pat
We can't go on like this. I'm asking a question
What no, I don't know the fairly brothers process. What does that mean? What's a vestigial tail mean?
I don't know what the word vestigial mean
Well you're holding an iPad looking up pictures of a topless right on Chong why don't you google vestigial you use the word you
I think vestigial means like you have a little bit of a tail but in the movie he has an actual tail
How long is it?
It's like a very small flaccid penis and he wags it at the end of the movie. I spelled vestigial wrong first I wrote correct
I spelled it correct first try. Maybe it's a tail that falls off
Oh, that can't be a real photo. No, of course not. It's like an elongated spine sort of situation
Here we go human
vestigiality
It says
That involves those traits occurring in humans that have
lost all or most of their original function through evolution although I don't fucking know
All right, they've already lost me with this description
Speaking of shallow how I went the other night buddy of mine had floor
Tickets to see the food fighters who I loved in high school and really haven't liked their music since
That's the real physical
Why did you show me now? It does look like a little dick man. I don't like guys back. Go ahead. Sorry
So yeah, I went to the food fighter show. I knew I didn't like their music anymore
But it didn't matter it played a lot of the old classics
They were great and Jack Black came out and sang a full and pretty amazing version of
Russia's Tom Sawyer
Oh, that's pretty cool and it was great and then Stevie Nix came out with Hyme
And they did stop dragging my heart around and gold dust woman and that was really awesome too
Hyme
Is sort of our modern dayfully would mac. It's three very young girls and they make awesome
Pop dance kind of music and they're great and the food fighters played the the Tom Sawyer music and Jack Black sang it
Yeah, and he was it was spot on and Jack Black was looking heavier than I've ever seen him and he's a heavy guy really
I hope he's okay
Tell me
Give me the food fighter shit
You know they
Played from their entire career, but like you know they definitely picked the songs from the later albums that are pretty good like a best of you and
You know pretender in those songs that I'm not interested in them anymore
But they kept the hits coming and they played enough of the first three albums that I was interested. Look at that
That's that's that's Ray Donne is that old Ray Donne? That's Ray Donne's Chong
So making my Ray Donne long there you go there you go
You think Ray Donne Chong could get a job on Ray Donne of them
Ray Donne she's two -thirds the way there Ray Donne of in Chong right Donne of in Chong
Is this something is this a hot sketch? We could pitch over at the UCB now. This is the 80s
And they just said sex after meeting 10 minutes ago
In I didn't see a rubber warehouse loft if I lived in New York in the 80s
I wouldn't have sex with anybody it just felt like a like a living STD
Yeah, yeah, you know and it was during the scare of everything. Oh god. I would have been terrified
I guess now I mean
Obviously, it's still a big frightening thing, but
You never hear anyone say like oh my buddy got AIDS. I'm gonna. I'm just talking any STD
But you heard it a lot back then I would imagine from people I know who lived there
It's just like oh another friend of mine another friend of mine
Hopefully we're kind of out of the what you hear about this douchebag hedge fund guy who
bought the rights to the AIDS pill jacked it from $13 to $750
Wait, what?
Look up the story once we're done, but it's this head fund dude the picture they have of him is like with two thumbs pointed at his dick
He's like the ultimate like douchebag bro fraca, right
He bought the rights to the
AIDS pill that like takes care of the most serious form of AIDS not ATZ, but another
You know very
Obviously, it's a very important pill to people with the AIDS bar. Sure
He bought it and he raised the price from $13 .50 to $750 per pill
And they confronted him about they were like you're a monster like what are you doing? He's like
You guys really shouldn't be mad at me about this
Yeah, you guys should probably calm down about that like just like these weird deferring methods. What?
But he's just kind of
Destroying lives like he like he's like if you want these pills
750 bucks
It's a six sick man and how many do you need? He's the most hated guy in America if you get on Twitter or whatever. How many do you need to survive?
It's for a certain it's for a certain
Symptom of AIDS that like more serious patients need I believe I want to look it up right now
Well, I would look it up after it's just a it's an interesting fact
All right, I'll look it up after and by that I mean
Sort of now. There's interviews servicing with a munchet. It's a big news story
Jesus I didn't hear about that. Yeah, then again, I'm terrible at reading news
You know
I often go back and forth. I the anything related to the news the world whatever is so depressing that I avoid it
And I realized that makes me one of the head and the sand kind of people
But also like what do I need to be more depressed about other things too?
Like I know everything sucks. I don't need to read all about it
It's I mean I just look I listen to the news every morning and I try to read a bit too
I know enough
It's a lot of bad news. You know, it's all bad. I mean, that's the game they're in. It's like wait
I asked people to work. Hey, what's going on this weekend?
Well, you know, it's supposed to be 110 degrees out
Why are you looking up the weather just live your fucking life?
You're gonna on a Wednesday be dreading the weekend because it's gonna be hot. I got to admit
I'll often I'll often look up the weather early
I mean and people don't have acation too. I can go on vacation. It's like, oh, well, you know, it's gonna be this like
Come on, man. It really sucks. Yolo. It really sucks. But the but you know the weather the weather can impact your weekend
You went, you know, you maybe say I want to go outside on Saturday and then you see it's gonna be 110 degrees. Yeah
What are you doing this weekend?
We got a wedding
What's that about buddy Sean Clements who does a great podcast called Hollywood Handbook that I recommend. I was on it
But they're all very funny
Um, that's it
Saturday at the national history museum natural history museum in town here. Yeah, all right. Well, that's I love an in town wedding
All my friends have weddings on Saturday. I don't
The hell am I gonna do going to any of them sit around my dick in my hand on Saturday sounds like a good Saturday to me
Hey, am I wrong? Hey
That's my reaction to that. Am I wrong? I'm giving you the hey. I'm giving you a hey that that was that was a that was an affirmative response
There's an element of uh
Right of a Walter Sobchak John Goodman and Lebowski to you to me not certainly not in the weight
But just in the uh hair trigger temper
Oh the anger about a lot of things the argumentative nature who's got a heart
Listen when I first saw the big Lebowski. I said I related to the that character actually
Uh -huh, so I can't argue with you totally. That's a hilarious care. I just read a great
Ah fuck. I think it was on film drunk
I always hate this when I read a great article and I want to give the person credit, but I don't remember who it was
but uh
It's about this big giant theory as a giant article about how they thought that big Lebowski was about
How the real way to be is to just be like
A sponge and absorbing what people say and not engaging with their bullshit sure the time about the dude is very
Just like anytime anybody's yelling and whatever he's just walking away and he's like oh, I don't need this
So whatever and people talking too much is uh, what drives him nuts and like what the downfall is in the movie
It was all about how the movie is about
The needless talking that people do
And whether it was with Cohen's intended or not it's a fascinating article. I urge you to look it up
All right, I would like to uh, I would like to read this article. I love that cash
I think I talked about in this podcast. I had a I did first one. I had a film professor who would find the gay agenda in any movie
And even though you knew it wasn't intended most of the time it was just fascinating shit
I like people's theories people's weird ideas on stuff
That's it nice all right fair enough look it up. I'll look it up
If you're watching along with us, we're really like a goonier Neil Brennan the guy does yeah if you're watching along with us the weird -looking Neil Brennan
Guy is on screen again
And they're at James Remar's I can't remember his character's name
They're at his art showing he's he started drawing pictures of this demon right thing and uh
But not showing them anybody but the but the the process of doing that inspired him and invigorated him and now his art is doing well again
And he's with Ray Don Chong who's
super hot and yet
Sleeping with this man even though it looks like
He fell into a vat of Crisco right
Earlier that day
I mean is now is Remar? I mean, I'm not trying to shit on the guys. Is he a good -looking guy by 80 standards?
He looks greasy
Remar I think it's given me a poor man's Mickey Rork 80s vibe, you know, right. He's just kind of there
Nowadays he's much more of a character actor type dude. Yeah
But yeah, I mean he's all right
Yeah, we have bad -looking, but it's a it's a it's definitely a time where everyone could have fucked up teeth
I mean our DC though is like a 10
Sure, but I buy these two as a couple and I like the casual interracial vibe of it without calling attention to it if I can be promise with you
That's like, you know, it's something I always admired about this film my mom said that to me when she took me to see this
Did you really? No, no no pet. I mean this was very unusual for the time period didn't strike me as odd when I saw it
That's good. You're a very enlightened kid. I was really very open -minded. I remember going to see the Pelican brief at the dollar show
with my dad and
That was kind of my first discussion of race with my dad because I was like so wait like
Denzel Washington, Julia Roberts for two and a half hours are like running around together
And in any other movie they would have been a couple they would have hooked up at some point right why did that not happen to my dad was like
Well, you know, I think it's
Just hard for a mainstream audience
And I was like oh, okay, all right, but your dad was for it
Uh, he seemed to be I mean any discussion of sexuality caused the car to become
Isoli silent so we kind of stopped talking about it, but right
But you got the you got the idea that he saw the flaw or fault in the public
Yeah, not that he agreed with it. Yeah, I mean, it was a pretty shitty thing
I mean like obviously any movie like that especially a big John Grisham kind of thriller the two
Incredibly attractive leads are gonna fuck and in this movie they were like pals
Denzel Washington, Julia Roberts. It was kind of fucked up now. Who does Tom Cruise bang in the firm? Does he bang with a firm?
That's it. I love the firm. I just rewashed it and I was being I was saying we're talking sex and it's called the firm
Exactly what what is who does he bang in it his wife is gene triple horn
Who used to be Ben Stiller's wife?
Gene triple or I always think that's the lady from all in the family. No, it's gene Stapleton. Yeah, but
No, he cheats on his wife
And like the Bahamas or something and it's one of my favorite scenes ever in the movies
His will for Brimley because the movie has the best cast of character actors ever. Yeah, Holly Hunters awesome and a gene actman
All these amazing people Tobin Bell who played jigsaw down the line in the saw movies
but Brimley has
Pictures of Tom Cruise fucking this woman on the beach who they like set him up to fuck to blackmail
and
Brimley starts going through the photos and he's like
you know
wives by nature
tend to be okay with the occasional
slip up early on in a marriage
But these are the kind of intimate acts
oral and such
That a young wife won't forgive
So if you can imagine a tight shot of Wilford Brimley saying oral and such
It's just such a fantastic scene. I was cackling when I watched it recently
Oral and such he shot one of the best scenes on Seinfeld ever when he goes. Oh, that's the poster guy. Yeah
Yeah, I work for the post office and I also happen to be a general. Yeah
It's also wonder like that he know he was funny because he seems to be humorous. I
Him and in and out
The great Kevin Klein movie in and out. Yeah. Who does he play in that again? He plays the
Joe Q -sex father to bring it back to Q -sign and
Best line of that so it's based on that Tom Hanks speech where he outered his
High School drama teacher when he won for Philadelphia, but Kevin Klein's not ready to come out
It's a very funny movie if you haven't seen. Yeah, I love it in and out and
So they it's on the Oscars and he's like
You know, they reveal that Kevin Klein is gay and
They're all talking about how outraged they are. They go around the room with how outraged they are
Then Wilford Brimley goes
He mode my lawn once
never again
It's like talking about like an academy award -winning actor
Really cracked me up at the time
He
I that in and out was a was a special genre of comedy
That came out in the late 90s. It was a very specific type of comedy. So I don't know double feature with the game
Star Michael Douglas loved it those comedies in the late 90s as made sure God was very
very
Glossy shiny look to them. Yeah
Very whimsical quirky soundtracks a lot of horns and things and and people sneaking around and stuff. Yeah
Grumpy old man is one of those
Like you know like an orchestra. I actually hate that style of music and comedies
It bugs me most comedy music bugs me. I like a silent awkward comedy most of the time sure
But uh, yeah, 80s and 90s were bad times for scores and comedies. Plancers on all deals is
Pretty much my favorite comedy I would say
And the music in that is really fucking annoying. It's like this weird digital
At one point they do a remix using Steve Martin's dialogue from the movie. Yeah, I know like a rap song
It's so terrible and but I just block it out and I love the moment when they turn that digital music music sad
It's it's I mean, it's just it's horrible. Yeah, it's it's hardly is
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom. That's so sad. Got it. It's because it's so cold. Yeah, detached. Yeah
I uh, we talked I think on this podcast about how I sold this old copy of Gatorbait
This like VHS movie like I used you know sell things once they go out of print
And I because I love the movie so much I had a copy of the soundtrack to plain strands of automobiles a used copy
soundtrack was terrible
Yeah, and I sold that for
Wait for it
$500 dollars
Of a CD it had gone out of print. I found it in a used record store and I was like one dollar. Yeah, it's I love the movie
I'll buy the soundtrack and
Five years later. I'm like wonder what this is worth anything like that
I you don't hear a lot of people talking about the planes trains. I don't be a soundtrack. It was on Amazon for $500
I put mine up for like you know, $4 .99 and it sold the next day
The next day the next day at a time when I really fucking need a money and that's
Something I'm gonna recommend all of you out there
You got a big collection of anything hop online see if it's worth any money
Is that got me through some really rough times. This is a strong recommendation for the audience pet
You heard to hear first guys try to find things that are rare and out of print
Settle them for I'm saying. I don't say try to find them. I'm saying you might have them
That's what I'm saying and then sell them online to people. I guess that culture has become bigger now at the time
I felt like I'd really stumbled upon something great because I that's the only way I made rent each month was doing little scams like this
Right. Hereions are great to buy and hold on to they go out of print now. Here's my question
uh
We're at the big twist of the final story here where James remar
Was attacked by the demon that he meets Ray Dong Chong the demon makes him promise will never tell great effects
Ten years later. He's got a beautiful family. He finally opens up to Ray Dong Chong and says
This is what attacked me the night I met you. Did you see this twist coming?
Yeah, totally you did I did from the jump of it
No, not from the jump but I knew that once he was like don't tell anyone that obviously he was gonna tell someone
But I mean, did you think he would tell her and she would be the demon? Uh, no, I guess not
I thought the demon would pop in through the window or something like
Hey guys, right
Sure, did I think the demon would have that rack? No
Do I know if you now
Pretend you're a single man. Yeah
Well actually, we could just do this with your current girlfriend. Okay, your girlfriend comes to you tomorrow. She says Pat
Here's the deal. I'm actually this demon
Uh -huh, but you love me and
And as long as you never mentioned it again, we can just stay together and always look like this to you
But just know that deep down underneath on this
Demon and if you ever mention it, it'll come out. Do you do you go?
Is she cool that if we break up or does that trigger the demon? Yeah, no, you have the option of breaking up
Do you break up or do you go? Yeah, I can why put me in this position? Out of sight out of mind
Why put me in a position that's gonna like jeopardize my relationship won't jeopardize you
Such a absurd thing. I
Truly curious because I wonder how I would be with a demon
You figure she's got like contacts and hell
but there would be no
Also, if you're a demon's not gonna be very trustworthy. There'd be no party that's like out of sight out of mind
No, not with a demon
Here's the sad news. You're saying she's a demon with a heart of gold
No, well, it's it's just she's like right on. She's like a nice girl and
You know unless you say something and then just a yeah, then she turns into a demon
Well, it's it's real sad when the kids turn into the fucking demons. That's rough
Isn't it they I think that's why they made them cute so it would seem less rough
I guess they're kind of cute
But then they all turn to stone here at the end their gargoyles
I understand
Here's sad news for the guy that paid $500 for your oh, I bet it's worth nothing now
You can just download the soundtrack or stream it for free on Amazon music
And just the CD though
Well, I'm only seeing the cassette for $45 still that's pretty good
Because that's just an example of movie that was kind of like an okay thing and now it's become like a
Beloved thanks given classic. Yeah, well, like oh, I'd love the soundtrack and then they go up and look online
If they got a lot of money, they're like all right. That's what it costs. I'll pay it
$45 for a cassette. I mean, you know god bless
I mean the weird thing is only would you put the iPad down pat? It's by job as it's not as trying to connect with you
I'm connecting with you. I'm the information guy on the podcast all right
I look things up Deborah Harry. We didn't mention his lead singer of blondie who didn't know that hopefully you would know
She was so hot man. I imagine a lot of people didn't know that Joe who are listening to the podcast
Who not everyone knows that the lead singer of blondie is Debbie Harry
I think everybody knows that is this law is one of the Lawrence's dead
Joe what's talking we're probably talking a half the people who don't even know what blondie what is with you with people dying tonight
You thought radon chong was dead. She's 54 for critics. Well, I know
Jonathan Brandis killed himself. Yes. I'm gonna look up
I thought one of the Lawrence's was dead, but I might be right and don't yell at me now. Why do the iPad?
This is why. Yes, question league is one of the Lawrence's dead. What do we gonna just let it hang out there?
But when I look over in your perusing, you know, Etsy for a
You know, nothing of the sort has happened a new blouse nothing of the sort is happening a new blouse with a print of Ryan
Gosling's face on it
Hold on a second
Let's see here
Joey Lawrence whatever happened to him. Whoa
Joe Lawrence is alive and he's on the show Joey and Melissa or something on the
Kids network. What is that like a like a Nickelodeon sitcom? Yeah, it's like a
You know what Disney Channel or one of those does he looks weird look at Joey Lawrence
He looks like he's made of claymation
Yeah, why why does he look like that probably had filler plastic surgery?
Is that what that is it looks like filler to me which I learned about very recently. What's filler?
filler is similar to Botox, but you're basically putting a skin -like substance into the wrinkles in your face and then you wind up looking very strange
Oh, yeah, and a lot of people do filler. He looks so weird. Yeah
The movie's over just ended because I'm looking up and I miss the endings. I'm looking up this god damn Joey Lawrence question yet
You don't have to I know Joey Lawrence is alive. I don't know about Matthew Lawrence. No, I know I know
Joey's alive
Matthew Lawrence holding it together look at that kid look sharp looking really good good for you Matthew
Who's the other one Andrew Lawrence Matthew Lawrence is in Plants and Son of Beels
His Steve Martin's very cute son. Yeah
Matthew Lawrence was also on Boy Meets World was you know
No, that was Fred Savage's brother Ben Savage
No, but Matthew Lawrence played his friend didn't he?
No, that was Ryder Strong, which is a the a poor name if I ever heard one the other friend hold on
I'm looking this up. I don't think so, but maybe
Television he was on give me a break
Okay, that seems right. He was on blossom as young Joey
Okay, Drexel's class. I bet Joey went into the producers and he was like hey, you gotta get my brother on the show boy meets world
Just like me boy meets world 68 episodes. All right play Jack Hunter
You want to talk about another gay porn Jack Hunter and Ryder Strong
Uh
He also was on Drexel's class to bring up our old boy Dabney Coles. I used to watch Drexel's class
It was on at the same time as the Sinbad show
I think I was watching the Sinbad show and during a period when the Simpsons was on Thursday if I'm not mistaken
Paddy we got another podcast center about here. We did
I hope you guys enjoyed it again
We're on iTunes. We're on all those little fringy side podcast places
We'd love a review you click the stars you say Joe and Pat are great. We love the show if you do I don't need you to lie
Where if you're listening to the fifth episode you probably like us
We'd love to hear your suggestions and we love your tweets. I'm at the Patrick Walsh
Joe is at Joe Derosa comedy
And that goes for all social media and we'll be at the mile high comedy festival October
Third sat whatever the Saturday Saturday October 3rd and we're at 8 .20 a .m
maniac cop 2 maniac cop 2 come on out drink with us. We're gonna drink all the basically pat my plan is
We get up at 7 a .m. To do an 8 .20 a .m. podcast
Uh, and then we're just gonna drink all day. I'm gonna say this
I am at my funniest with a drinker 200 my belt and also at my funniest when I wake up way too early and I'm in a bad mood
This could be a real funny combination. I think it's gonna be a great time. I'm probably gonna break Joe's balls a lot
I think we're in a laugh and have a real nice time. I think it's gonna be great. I'm looking forward to it
I've done a lot of morning radio my day. I'm good in the morning. Okay, especially if I'm drinking like morning sex
No, no big fan. All right. Well, that's another time
Another discussion
Save that for the mr robot pod. You're fresh. You know, you feel fit because you just woke up. It's not fresh
I feel like it's it's been sleeping all night things are caking up and
long -stale I'm a sexual being if that's a crime let me up
You've been listening to ladies were coming to your town Denver
October 3rd. Yeah, and I was a morning sex. Consider having sex with you even if you're a secretly a demon
Because I do believe in the out of sight out of mine. Sure
This has two stars on Netflix by the line. It's ridiculous. They're they're so harsh with the Netflix ratings
It makes me furious everything is two stars. It's absurd about my return. It doesn't
You've been listening to we'll see you in hell a presentation of the fangoria podcast network produced by Thomas Defeo
Executive produced by our friend Ken Hanley of fangoria entertainment for press opportunities advertising inquiry
Inquiries and information about we'll see you in hell contact Ken at fangoria .com. Thanks guys