Huff, Puff, and spin the house down at Golden Nugget Online Casino.
Right now, new players can deposit just 5 bucks and get 500 total spins on Huff and
More Puff, the slot that's blowing players away.
Download the Golden Nugget Online Casino app and use promo code Nugget1.
That's code Nugget1 to enjoy 50 spins a day for your first 10 days.
All on our players' favorite game of the summer.
Now's the time to score daily bonuses and spin for all the bacon on the game everyone's
hoffat about.
At Golden Nugget Online Casino, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberler.
Please play responsibly.
21 and over, physically present in Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia
only.
Void in Ontario.
New customers only.
Non -withdrawable casino spins issued as 50 spins per day for 10 days valid for featured
game only and expire each day after 24 hours.
C -Terms at GoldenNuggetCasino .com slash promos ends at 11 .59pm, Eastern on August 31, 2025.
The football season is full of guarantees.
And here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if your
football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning, or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to Fanatic Sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Monthly 21 -plus gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gambler, often not available in all states, terms
apply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
And welcome to another episode of We'll See You When Hell. I'm Joe DeRosa.
Crossed for me as my dear friend and lover. Love your first friend second.
Yes, I think so. Patrick Walsh, we're here tonight to talk to you about classic
department film called The Fury. As you know, we do it on this podcast. We review,
we commentate and we discuss all of the big heart fantasy sci -fi things. So I think we should
get on with the show, Pat. Joe, let's, and while we do, let's get on with a Joe. Oh. Oh.
Now what was that a reference to? Well, I remember that the last second I was supposed to do like a
90s pop hit like I did in the last one. Oh, yeah, but my brain is dead and I couldn't think of one so I did sort of a
pirates
Sea shanties
Like a yo ho ho. I thought I thought you were gonna go three stoooges with it like the Joe
Well, no that would involve you and maybe con here. It's dog. Um, I think you're gonna do all three voices at once
No, cuz you're that good pet
I don't think you're ever going to top it, to be honest.
It was unexpected, even to me.
How are you, Pat?
I'm fine, Joe.
You know, I'm working.
I got less than two weeks left at this job that has nearly brought me to my knees.
I can't wait to be done.
And speaking of being brought to my knees.
No, this isn't, this isn't about the timely climate we live in, folks.
There goes the phone.
Oh good, and it's glassed down.
Did you share it with your friend?
Thankfully I took my case off a few days ago.
No, it's fine.
It's fine.
But Friday night, we go, I'm at the taping of my show, and I asked the stage manager.
I said, hey, do I have time to go take a piss?
She's like, yes, you got about five minutes.
I walk out, I'm in the restroom, I'm pissing,
and I hear the, eh, that indicates the scene
is about to start.
I have to be there for this.
So, I'm about halfway done.
I clip the stream, miserable.
There's like four or five crew guys,
and there's the crew bathroom.
So there's always like three inches
of non -descript liquid on the floor.
Yeah, and it always like it's the kind of restroom where you always hear someone go like
And then like a giant fart
Just like people just being disgusting if I may for a second interject
That's my only problem with unisex bathrooms
Because they were all over Amsterdam when I was there and I thought it was very forward and very cool
But you know, and I'm like, hey, I'm in the one stall ladies in the next. We're all sharing everything's good
Yeah, but I you know, I don't need the woman did that I'm attracted to you hear me going
Christ, we'll see oh yeah to make such noises in the restroom
I make a lot of noise in the rest certainly not in public and
You know, it was just like it was gross. I clipped the stream which is already unpleasant
disgusting I zip I button I turn I
Take two steps and I turf out so hard slipping in the three inches of
of bathroom floor liquid and came down so fucking hard that several grown men were like
stopped their streams to turn and make sure I was okay, because it sounded and looked
terrible.
And I came down very, very hard.
I don't know if I've broken a rib, but I may have, I can't sleep on it.
Breaking ribs, they just tell you to just leave it and it'll fix itself.
something went wrong with my rib.
Is that what they say with a broken rib?
They do.
You can't do anything for it.
Right.
Both my knee and my rib are in excruciating pain.
I didn't need it.
I just didn't need that added to my line.
Well, this is like the time the week before we shot.
Yeah.
I went to executive.
The folks, this was before I was fired.
The week before we shot the pilot,
I went to executive producer Johnny Glecky's house for some celebratory drinks, and I'm not going
to lie to you, Pat. I had a few. Sure. I had quite a few. That's all right. And I believe he had a
no shoes in the house policy. Okay. I was excited to be in Glecky's house. I'm zipping all over the
place. We're having a great time. The racial estate. Yeah. And I went down some hardwood stairs and
So I took a nasty spill, just landed right on my back.
I had a big bruise the whole week we were taping.
And then I threatened to sue, no, I'm kidding.
He's got a lot of money.
No, but I had a big bruise on my back the entire week we taped, and I felt the same way
that you're talking about.
I was like, did I break something?
Yeah.
It's not a good feeling.
No.
Yeah.
And I should probably go, I just don't have the time, but I just, I already just felt
so we can exhaust it and then this just really exacerbated it and let me tell you how how I
cool -ly covered for my spill so I'm lying basically in a pile of grown men urine my slacks damp
and he still hasn't changed people I did I can smell it and I stand up
I look around the room and go boy they really ought to get a mop in here huh
That's how I chose to diffuse the awkwardness right now. You write that into a script for next season
Boy, they they could really use a mop in here, huh applause break. Yeah
But I'm fine. I'm fine. Good. I'm glad you're fine
And you look and you're looking fine. Oh, thank. Can I mean that in a sex way? No, I got I mean that in a in a in an inappropriate
It's sex way I take every compliment sexually and it's in our work very well
We are in the workplace folks as you know shows coming to you live from me thick uncut dick house
Not Joe. Yeah, why did you tell Matt Lauer to do what he did I
Wanted him off the show I was up for that job
At the same time he was you've got a face for mornings. I've always said I morning television. I've got a voice for it too. Yeah, and
Like very hungry. Maybe still drunk even. Yeah, like for you. Yeah, yeah dried coke on the nostril the he uh, he
I was up for that gig and uh, it was in the bag. They said it was pretty much my job. I it was my
pop the champagne and then it incomes this young hot shot. Right. Matt Lauer. They can
his shit doesn't stink. It stings. You know, it gets up under me and takes the gig.
Now, also, I also, here's another thing I pissed about. I had patented the lock, the office
from the inside. But that was yours. Yeah. And he never, he never gave me any credit or money
for that. So that, that pissed me off too. I understand that. Yeah.
Lauer worked at 30 Rock when I was there in 2003, 2004. And a friend of mine, who, of course,
I will not name what worked in his circle in the NBC News division. And he called out to her and
like, he got to come in here. This is an attractive young lady. My age at the time, 23 or something.
Hey, you got to come in here and check this out. He got to come in here and check this out.
She goes into his office. He says shut the door looking back. Perhaps he used the secret activation dungeon lock. We don't know
And he had her sit with him and watch the Paris Hilton night vision blowjob video and he didn't know her
This is not so this is he knew where she she worked beneath him in the department beneath literally. Yeah, but is this but I mean
She was like I think I'd like to go and he's like, but can you believe this? Just check it out. Just check it out
That's very inappropriate or the story 15 years ago. Is this somebody he's like friends with like and being like
Isn't this nuts or is it somebody that he's doesn't know that well?
No, I guess but now what workplace would you be in where you would ask a female even friend to come watch pornography on your computer?
I don't are you that dumb? I don't think I ever would
Like and if I did it wouldn't be in a in a seducting seducing kind of way
We were not in a power position over her yeah, no, yeah, you're right. I guess I've never watched much porn at work
I can't even imagine partly because I work at Warner Bros
And if you bring up anything questionable a picture of Sylvester the cat
Pops up on your screen and says thuffer and thuck attached. I remember once playing
When we worked at when Matt McCarthy and I worked at the p -home show together
No, did you ever get a thuffer and thuck a tash?
Uh -huh.
Did you ever get a thuffer and thuck a tash?
No.
Is that real?
Yeah.
If you look up anything questionable.
No.
No, I never looked up and it goes to the WB headquarters that you've looked at something
questionable.
Oh no, I never...
I've gotten it.
It was never porn.
It would be like googling some actress or something and it would be like, wait a minute.
I never looked at anything or knowingly inappropriate.
But one, there was a day where we found that we were like,
we had some down time, we were on YouTube,
and we found this Andrew Dice Clay special
that we had never seen or heard of.
Okay, I was like, what is this man?
And so we started watching it.
I think Dice is very funny.
And you know, we're laughing.
And then he suddenly launches into this real hard,
real hard joke about Chinese people.
Okay, we couldn't dive on the mute button fast enough, so that's when we learned the lesson that you don't watch
Anodized clay in the workplace, right, you know
Well, see yeah, that's inappropriate and you can get fired for it
and meanwhile a
Movie they're heavily pushing for the Oscars this year downsizing
Contains an equally horrific portrayal of Asian -American people. I will say we were in a comedy room and we were watching comedy
So it's probably fine, but you know, and I know that this is in favor of most things that happen in the comedy writers room
But people let it go too far
The but I'm well pat is tired folks. I bought a 1983 Star Wars arcade cabinet
the
Bay it's the that's the joy of my life. I mean, this is my life's blood at this point
It's the greatest thing ever mother's milk. Yeah
Yeah, it's it's the it's a prize possession. It's it's everything to me.
Pat didn't know I was buying it hadn't been here since I bought it.
Walks in. I mean almost circles the thing four times and finally go pet.
Are you going to mention next to it?
You're going to mention the elephant in the room.
There's a giant star wars or Kate cabinet suddenly just sitting in this room.
Your favorite chair is gone. Yeah, it's upstairs now.
You know, you're sitting in a much shittier chair.
That's true.
But I don't notice things.
I'm not the guy who's like, oh, honey,
you got your hair cut.
Tell me you got your hair cut.
I'll tell you, it looks nice.
Bitch, but I'm probably not gonna notice.
That's how you freeze it too, which I don't agree with.
That's right.
Tell me you got your hair cut, bitch.
Don't make me do all the damn work.
Pfft.
It's a given give.
Hey, what do you say you can take what do we what do you say we put all this this nasty talk aside and take a trip together
You mean over to bath movie corner job. I'd like to go with you
All right, I saw the new Woody Allen picture wonder wheel
And I think I mentioned this to you, but not on the podcast.
It stars as a married couple, Kate Winslet and Jim Belushi.
Jim Belushi is supposed to be like the Marlon Brando and Streetcar thing, except this is
Jim Belushi walking around the entire movie in a skin tight wife, Peter.
Way fadder than I've ever seen him.
And just like he's dying, he's the whole movie is like I just want to drink.
I need a drink and then wins. It's like I know I need a drink too. Do they drink are they sober or something?
They're sober because you get the feeling things were bad when they drank, but then they steadily turn to the bottle
He now doesn't anymore. I know his daughter her stepdaughter played by Juno Temple
Do you lovely as all believe it or not folks a beautiful young actress in a Woody Allen movie? No wait
It's her daughter his stepdaughter. No, it's her stepdaughter his
daughter. Okay. She married him fairly recently, but she knows the daughter. She is having
an affair with Justin Timberlake who was playing a Jewish wins guard. Yes, wins it was
having an affair with a Jewish Justin Timberlake. Okay. Who is good when being the narrator
and then bad when he has to act in the movie? He never reached the movie. The first shot
it like pans up him like Henry Hills style and he's like, there I was on the boardwalk
1955.
It's an odd narration track because the film does take place in 1955 yet Timberlake is
like, what's up, yo?
Yeah.
I mean, this movie, yo, I ever tell you my story about him and Cammy Diaz and the other
better.
No, but there, I could, I'd be hard pressed to think of two people I'd like to let
meet less. Then Cameron Diaz, you what? Who I'd like to meet less. Oh yeah. I mean,
Cameron Diaz and Justin Timberlake. Well, I met Cammy, of course, in the infamous James
Lipton story. Yes. But Cameron Diaz was hosting SNL. And I was working at SNL. And Timberlake
was the, he was her guest. And he also did the Bee Gees talk show sketch. Leave it in
I never understood it. It was kind of funny, but I never understood what they were doing.
So afterwards, I had to take them in the elevator, not just down to the street because this
was fucking timber like in his prime. I had to take them down to the secret under the
building like hella pad. Where are they dating at this point? They were dating, yeah. But
it was kind of like, you know, they didn't want the paparazzi, whatever. So you had to take
sound, wing, downstairs wing. So I'm in the elevator with the two of them, and Eddie, my
old security guard friend. And as we're going down, then Cameron Diaz goes, why is it
that I always have to fart in an elevator? And Timberlake laughs hysterically. And he goes,
I always got to fart at the library. Oh God. And they both laughed for 14 floors down, endless laughter.
And you had to fake laugh. I'm sure we I looked over the security guard and we kind of exchanged a look as if to say
Boy, this isn't funny. And also a look that seemed to say how often are you at the library just in Timberlake?
I was wondering that myself
But I saw I saw the love I saw that these two people were so dim -witted that they were in love with each other, and it was kind of sweet
I mean, I think they're both talented, but two people I find I mean
I couldn't think of two more boring human beings.
Yeah, they were boring.
I don't know what to tell you.
They were nice pleasant, certainly,
especially for two people that famous at that time.
But Timberlake's bad in the movie.
Basically, Junotemple and Winslet both lust after Timberlake.
There's a sick aspect to it because she's married
and shouldn't be cheating,
but she's trying to end their love relationship
because she's into him.
It's just kind of a sad, slow, boring, depressing movie.
Any good or no?
No, it's not good.
It's better than his old, his Amazon show,
which was to me the worst thing he's ever done.
I like the Amazon show upon second watch.
It took a second watch though.
A second watch?
It took a second, well, that's not true,
not a second watch.
But once I got past the second episode,
I started to like it.
Because I was putting it on in my hotel,
but I was on the road because I was like,
Like, well, this is so boring, I'll just fall asleep.
Right.
And then the third episode started and I started kind of laughing and I was like, oh,
and then I actually started to like the story and thought there were some funny jokes.
I think you are the only one.
I think I am too.
Yeah.
There's a very funny joke where he has to jump from a rooftop to another rooftop and he goes,
I try never to jump anywhere with his gravity.
It's not funny.
It's a funny joke.
That's not a funny joke.
There's a few joke attempts in this wonder wheel and then it's like clearly like the blow to the scene
But then like all through the next scene you're like was that even supposed to be a joke?
He's look the guys in his eighties and he's yeah, he doesn't have the it doesn't have the juice in the stick anymore
So to speak it's his best -looking movie he's ever done
He got the guy who shot like apocalypse now, right. It's all shot and very cool colors and shit
It looks better than match point because I thought match point was pretty stunning
No, this is like a big budget just for the sets like, you know, they dropped a bunch
of money into it.
It looks great.
But it's a boring movie, one of Woody Allen's worst for sure.
That's a bummer to hear.
All right.
Well, I know a lot of people are happy that it sucks.
That's true.
So at a brief appearance by our friend, David Crumbholz.
Yes.
David Crumbz.
I have no interest in seeing it.
His last few films I've just had here.
I enjoyed the one with Joaquin Phoenix enough.
Irrational man.
Yeah, but I just really.
No, not really.
Except one part of Posey invited him up
to smoke some grass.
Yeah, yeah, that was ridiculous.
Anyway, what did I see, Pat?
I saw just a wonderful film that I've celebrated
for years, got the Blu -ray, smokey in the bandit.
30th, I think, or maybe even 40th,
anniversary edition, Blu -ray came out.
I've only seen the Arige.
It's the only one worth seeing.
The sequels are terrible.
Okay.
But the original to me is a fucking masterpiece.
Jackie Gleason, arguably at his funniest.
Yeah.
And I'm a big honeymooners fan.
And I think few things are funnier than Jackie Gleason
in the honeymooners, having like a goddamn meltdown.
Sure.
And looking like he's gonna have a stroke, he's so angry.
Right.
but he, you could argue that he tops that in this.
But anyway, I got the Blu -ray and it had on it a feature length documentary called The Bandit
that was made two years ago or a year ago that was just the story of the film, how they made it.
It was awesome. All right. Current contemporary interviews with Bert Reynolds talking about it.
I remember that movie being advertised and then never knew it came out. I would love to borrow an
and view, if I may.
It was wonderful.
Reynolds in the full, like, you know, like bad to pay.
Yeah, it's him now, like the pencil thin mustache too.
You know, there's a great thing with Gleason,
where he's, where it's like an old interview
and he's like, he's like, I said I was gonna play this thing
as sideways as possible.
I mean, I'm a Southern red neck cop
and I got a pencil thin mustache.
it doesn't make any damn sense yeah it's just a great documentary a lot of
interviews with Hal Needham like talking about like why he made the movie
and I won't ruin anything the story is actually really interesting like where
he got the idea from and and Bert Reynolds in a time of desperately wanting to
be like an Oscar -winning actor like a serious actor Hal Needham was his
at the time. He was like, just come live with me. And they were like being like bachelor
boys like and needing folks. I barely knew him. And this big mansion together and need
him is like, can you do this movie? And Bert Reynolds goes, it's literally the worst script
I've ever read my life. It's terrible. He goes, but you're my friend. If you can get the
money, I'll do it. You can use my name. He gets the money. At the same time, Reynolds gets
an offer to play this villain. And in the interview clip, he says, I mean, the role had get the
Tuxedo out written all over it and he goes what was the role do we know he didn't say what it was and he goes
But I didn't do it because I promised how and like everybody else reinforces that thing in the movie they're like
Bert Reynolds is an extremely low guy
And he promised how needed me to do this so he did it and then it turned out to be this huge fucking hit
It made like 250 million dollars at the box office
That seems like the sort of thing where Reynolds would have said like he got a couple points on it and probably made an
that's low to money.
I would imagine so.
Yeah, I would imagine so.
I'll do your picture.
But my favorite part in the documentary,
he's Reynolds is doing an interview in the 80s
and the reporter goes,
Bruce, are you ever going to,
Bert, or Bert, excuse me?
Bert, are you ever going to do some serious roles?
Are you just gonna keep doing these little stunting roles
that you do, right?
Shots have been fired.
Yeah.
Doesn't lose it, cool as a cucumber,
looks down to the ground, takes a beat, smiles, looks up, and he goes, well, I am of the
opinion that 20 years from now, these little stunting roles, as you refer to them, will
be looked upon as tiny pieces of art.
What a fucking smooth come back.
And he's right.
It's a fucking classic. It's a classic film it's great. Yeah Jerry a lot of Jerry Reed in the doc
Not interviews, but just they talk about Reed like he was Christ like apparently was the greatest guy in the world
And all right. It was just a really wonderful movie to watch all right. I love it. Yeah
Um, I know you're gonna get to your oh and Sally feel too who I'm I've never liked Sally feel
I love Sally. I don't know what it is. I've never liked I absolutely love her and she's but there's no interviews with her
I'm assuming she said no. I can't imagine they didn't approach her to do it
Uh, so that was a bummer, but um, but she's
It's that's uh, that's the movie where I fell in love with Sally feel and I was like
You know, marry me please sure take me away from all this death. Sure. Yeah
She just seemed a little square from my test
And I didn't like that. You really like me. You really like me. Speech gross
Imagine some actors doing that now. You like me. You really like me. You can't come back from that
It's embarrassing. I like field. I'm a big fan. All right, and I want to have you talk like this
I know you're getting to your sitcom in our in our new segment PS. I love this
But I would like to talk about a couple sitcoms. I've been watching
One, a revisit of my old, deep favorite news radio.
Yeah.
News radio is one of the best written sitcoms of all time.
It's an amazing ensemble.
I can, I realize watching it, it's like an inspiration to me
and just because I saw it, it's such a formative age.
Like, Seinfeld was kind of blowing the shit up
but a news radio was like the classic
just like people in an office version.
But like weird shit.
I gotta tell you,
I don't think ever saw an episode
where they weren't in that fucking radio office.
They almost never leave.
Yeah.
And this,
that's never boring.
The jokes are great.
They're all character jokes.
Show gets weirder and weirder as it goes.
Phil Hartman,
maybe one of the best vehicles the man ever had.
Yeah.
Bill McNeil.
And he got into that.
He did.
You got Andy Dick. You got Joe Rogan who I'm not a big fan of but he fits right in somehow. Yeah, he's very funny on the show. Everybody's it's a fully perfectly cash show. Great guests more a tear and everybody's great. It's funny as shit. And the commentaries are amazing because they just shit on NBC the entire time. Right. And if you want to find something great. Look up Paul Sims, who was the creator of news radio. Look up an interview he had with Roller. He's a great guy. He's a great guy. He's a great guy. He's a great guy. He's a great guy. He's a great guy. He's a great guy. He's a great guy. He's a great guy. He's a great guy. He's a great guy.
Stone as they were about to cancel news radio. It's I'm going to have it framed. It's one of my favorite things
I've ever read where he just is like these fucking cock suckers talking about the network that has his show on the air
And he's like, you know, they put this shit sandwich on the air every Thursday night
They can't give us a goddamn break. It just goes on and on and on and on and on and I'm going to have it framed
It's one of my favorite things I've ever seen. That's amazing and they bring on the president of NBC at the time
Warren Littlefield who Bob Ballaband played on Seinfeld and they're like and in the
late shift. Yeah, that's right. They're like, did you know that you moved us 11 times
around the like they bring in these guests and then just like roast them? Good. They're
like, no, no, no, shut the door. Why did you fuck our show in the ass? Like it's, it's
fantastic. I love it. I think it's out of print probably because of all the controversial
remarks, but I've had it forever. You can get the whole series of news radio for under
20 bucks on Amazon. Under 20, the entire five season, including the John Lovitz fifth season,
which is not anywhere near as good, because Phil Harman was dead, of course. But his love,
it's still Lovitzy in the fifth season. He's Lovitzy. And if it was a, if Harman had been there,
you wouldn't have minded. Right. But it's not as good. Oh, and Stephen Root, of course.
Yeah, Stephen Root. And then I always forget the red -haired lady's name, but she's
Lewis, X, Y, F of,
Nick Nolte, I didn't know that.
She's great.
She has great.
Candy Alexander.
Yeah.
She's very funny.
It's taken on over to the new segment.
Oh, all right.
Right?
Sure, go ahead.
Well, I like when you announce it.
Oh, well, I mean, I wasn't quite ready to leave Pat's movie
corner.
Oh, I thought you were saying you were.
No, I can be done.
I got another sitcom, but I'll save it for the next step.
Yeah, I got I got one or two for the next step as well walk us over to PSI love you country perfect strangers
I love you pet. I'm gonna be honest
I don't really have that specific of an episode to talk about this week because it has become a fever dream watching this thing
I'm sure and I can do a commentary on the finale
I assume there's an hour long finale and we should do a commentary on I'm fine with that all right good
I'm sure the listeners will be as well pet. I can only pray that your show
So, last, this long, that you start getting into plotlines, like they've gotten into on this
show, but there's just nothing else to explore.
The last episode I saw a music mogul comes into the newspaper for some reason, discovers
is Balke and says you could be a star, a music pop star. Cut to Balke as MC Balke B rapping.
Oh no. Rapping. In a like CNC music factory style video. So this, can you tell me is this
I'm drowning in an ocean of your emotion potion
Does he say that me and my sister used to sing that to each other and it came from perfect strangers?
I don't I don't think he says it in the rap song
I don't remember if he does because here's why Pat. Yeah, that sounds like a line that you'd play for laughs
Yeah, they play this entire song with balky rapping and dancing with a chorus of women
To no laughs. It's presented seriously
Is he in hammer pants, I assume?
Yeah, of course.
Yeah, the whole thing.
Then is he doing a questionable voice or his own accent?
No, he's wrapping his balky.
Okay.
They probably thought they were going to release
this to radio, by the way.
Absolutely, it was like, you know,
I don't know if you kids remember the tales
from the crypt TV show from HBO, I'm sure you do.
But they released the crypt jam,
which was the crypt keeper wrapping.
It's a bonus feature on one of the seasons.
as a joke two years ago, our dear friend James Pinkstone,
for Christmas gave me an out -of -print,
and he told me this, it cost him $40.
Tales from the Cripped Christmas album,
where it's the Cripped Keeper
Well from the Cripped's, I hope.
I don't think it's even called that to be honest.
I can't remember, but it's the Cripped Keeper like rapping.
And I remember the worst song on it is called,
It's a, it's a jingle bells parody and it's called juggle bills.
And it's the crypt keeper going, juggle bills, juggle bills, so much debt to pay.
What?
That's not even spooky.
No.
We listened to this thing.
The night he gave it to me, it was me and Jim and our friend Scott and Jamie and Dan.
We were all drunk and really stoned.
We put this thing on.
And we were, I mean, we were on the floor.
It was so bad.
Chugal bill.
It was one of the, it's the word,
it's one of the worst things I've ever heard in my life.
The entire album I mean.
And then that's the high point.
Anyway, here's the kicker with MC Balkyby.
You ready for this?
Yeah.
They're all excited.
The video's gonna be a big hit.
Larry's his manager.
They're all gonna make millions of dollars.
The whole thing.
Larry wearing gold chains.
No, nobody's wearing gold chains or anything like that.
They watched the premiere of the video on TV because for some reason the video is premiering
on TV. Yeah. And it's a merely vanilla thing. It's they've dubbed Balky's voice. So now he
doesn't want to do it because he's like, I'm not doing this because it's lying. It's dishonest.
And the mogul actually says this when they confront him. Balky, I didn't sign you for your voice.
I signed you for your unique look.
Wow.
So you specifically did a music mogul, like the Santa Claus guy that fucking Celine Dion
was married to.
Right.
Walks into a newspaper.
She's Bronson Pinshaw.
I was thinking Frankie Sharpe of Frankie Sharpe Records in Wayne's World.
Yeah.
Frankie Sharpe, Frankie Sharpe or Trustless Jones from CB4.
She's Bronson Pinshaw and goes 40 -year -old Bronson Pinshaw.
Yeah.
Uh, so I don't remember where it goes from there.
Pat, like I said, it's a fever dream at this point.
I can't even tell what I'm remembering correctly at this, it's just, the show is insane.
The show is fucking insane.
Have you seen, I'm drowning in an ocean of your emotion, potion, it comes into the office
thing.
So thrusting.
Yeah.
It might have been like a number one hit where it's like a runner on the show that they
can't get the song out of their head or well, that's a running gag on the show that they,
They always
They'll start many episodes with like
Larry walks in and he's like Baalkey. I need to tell you something and Baalkey's singing like can't touch this
And then they he forces Larry to break into a song and dance routine. They do that frequently
Yeah, and they'll do like a two -minute of something works on perfect strangers. They did it again
Yeah, yeah, and again. I mean and they're still going strong with the catchphrases every episode still oh my lord I
I have a plan has started recurring more, and also, of course, not don't be ridiculous.
And they're still not living in the house with the girls.
No, still no house with the girls.
Well, we need to watch the finale together.
Let's do it. We will commentate on the finale together.
Let us know your thoughts on that kid.
Then it's in the form.
And in fact, they just realized this is the second episode for December.
So we need to do shout -outs for the old Patreon folks.
Well, you know, we haven't even gotten to the topic of the show.
No, I know. I'm not saying, like, I'm going to do them right now.
Oh, okay. I'm just saying it. Just popped in my head.
As I said, when I said back, he's catchphrase.
I remembered our Patreon contributor who's thing is don't be ridiculous.
Well, while you're looking that up, I will take us over to Joe's scary stuff,
because I have something.
Uh -oh.
I purchased the brand new.
I came out a couple days ago.
Collectors edition, I believe shout factory edition
of scream factory, excuse me, misery.
Oh wow, loaded with special feature.
That's great.
Reiner commentary, you know, documentaries, et cetera.
I just started scratching the surface,
but I did start the movie.
They got a new 4K, whatever that means.
Printed this bad boy, it looks incredible.
Um, what's the other thing better than 4K?
There's a better than 4K now?
Well, there's 2K, which I guess might not be better,
But 2K is worse.
So you, when you buy a 4K blu -ray,
mm -hmm.
Because this is just a blu -ray,
but it says it's a 4K transfer.
Mm -hmm.
That doesn't mean it's a 4K disc, correct?
Well, it means it's a 4K rendering of the film,
and if you watch it on a 4K television,
you're gonna get the best picture possible.
So these 4K Blu -rays, I'm not going to go up to them, just I think Blu -rays look perfect
as they are, but that would require me buying a new television and Blu -ray player, correct?
It's, yeah.
It's a lot.
It's probably horseshoe.
I have a 4K TV.
I mean, here's the thing.
It's all in what the movie is, and if you care enough about the, you know, there are certain
things.
I have, for instance, a Necronomicon, book of the Dead, which is an anthology horror movie
starting the guy from Reanimator.
I'm blanking on his name right now.
I even on VHS.
It's like, that's a thing I don't want on.
I don't want to see that in crit.
It's not available on Blu -ray, but my point is, it's like, I wouldn't buy that on Blu -ray.
But then I bought the Tarantino XX box set on Blu -ray because they all look, it's fucking
Tarantino.
It's stunning.
So I think it just depends on what you want.
it. Some things that might be worth it. There's not so much tend to not need better clarity
than blue ray. It seems to be the top. Like let's say you bought the perfect strangers
or mom's family complete box sets. No point. I don't even think you'd need a blue ray
versions of those. You don't. No. So yeah. These my news radio DVDs look like dog shit.
Yeah. But that's kind of part of the charm of what it means. And there's boom mics and
several scenes. Oh, but anyway, misery. I can't, we've, we've never done the movie on here,
but I know we've talked about it a ton. It's one of my all -time favorite thrillers.
Arguably the best Stephen King adaptation. I would say 100%.
And next to it, it's that are the missed. It's probably misery though. Yeah.
Shining. The Shining's great. I wouldn't count it as high up the list only because it's such a departure
from the book. Right. As far as like true adaptations of a Stephen King thing that really hit all the beats,
like I think part of it is being true to the book. Misery arguably even clasped up the book.
Speaking of which. The movie. I just rewatched the it miniseries. It's insane how much better it is
than the new movie. We talked about it on the show. I know, but three months ago. I just watched it again
and I was like, this is crazy how much better it is. I agree. And people are shitting on it and saying,
Oh, and shitting on us for saying we liked don't get me started
You brought it up, John
You're right. Let me stop
Maybe that's a new kit the thing that people could say let me finish the uh, all right, so the misery that's great
Yeah, it's you know, it's 20 bucks on Amazon. Very good
Pat
I'm gonna I'm gonna tap out on Joe's scary stuff this week
Mm -hmm, I don't really have anything, I'm sure I could drum something up, but
Well nice sometimes for you to have one I mean not to have one
Let's get to the film in hand which is streaming on Netflix if you haven't seen it you can do a pause
The movie is called The Fury, directed by Brian De Palma, and it's coming a couple years
after his horror breakthrough, Kerry.
And Joe, I gotta say, I had seen this movie when I was probably 12, 13, and I just watched
it for the first time, and however long that is, 20 years, it's fine, but it pales so much
in comparison to Kerry, that it just kind of doesn't register at all.
It's corny and an important thing to note for those of you that haven't seen it.
It's a hard, I think calling it a horror movie is a little strong, but it's considered
a horror movie about telekinetic powers, so you have to make the comparison.
Yeah.
He's dancing quite close to Kerry territory.
Kerry territory.
Oh, God.
Do you ever turn it on?
Carey Tory folks, the uh, I
It's I agree with you. It's a bit of a snoozer. It's it's a real slow burn. Yeah, it's look
I think when Dupama does it right he nails it. He's made some of my favorite films Scarface carry the untouchables
What's the documentary? It's a fantastic documentary Dupama
and it'll help you know where to start with his career.
I mean, he's truly an incredible filmmaker.
Yeah, he's one of those guys that can make shit,
really exciting just by virtue of the way he shoots him.
That being said, when he's doing a slow burner,
sometimes I'm not in the mood and I can't take it,
I felt this way about blowout.
People say blowout is like his finest film.
I know people that say it's their favorite movie ever.
I mean, I tend to know it's his favorite movie ever.
Yeah, I was, I was, I love blowout, but I wouldn't even put it in the top, you know,
fourth of his career.
So it's a, this is a very slow film.
Now, I will say this to its credit, great cast, Kirk Douglas, uh, Amy Irving, Kirk Douglas,
constantly shirtless.
Yeah.
And he's like 70.
He's like old man ripped where like there's still like, just things hanging off of him.
It made me Google Kirk Douglas.
Yeah. So it's like I think he's still alive. He is a lot. He's 101 years old. Yeah.
He looks insane. I mean, he's a 101 year old man. But he looks like the grip kid. He's still
coherent. Right. Yeah. But uh, he, uh, which is, which is pretty cool. But uh, anyway, Kirk Douglas,
Amy Irving, uh, John Cassavetes, who is just tremendous to me. Amy Irving's really great in this movie.
It made me wonder why I feel like she wasn't in a lot of stuff. Like I'm like, she's a really
good actor. Why was she not in more stuff? Well, she and I just don't know. No, like if you watch
that Spielberg documentary, I got the impression that Irving was almost kind of passed around and
wound up like Spielberg's wife. And he kind of wanted to take her out of that world of coke -fueled
filmmaker parties and stuff. She was like going around and like, cooking up a lot and stuff.
I might be reading too much into that. I know she wound up with Spielberg, but it always seemed like
like she was dating around that camp, John Millius, Brian De Palma, all those guys.
All the lookers.
Yeah, exactly.
What she likes, you know, like filmmakers or whatever, and they start, this movie starts
with like a 10 minute lingering close above her ass in a bikini.
It's interesting, I mean, she's obviously a beautiful woman, but it's interesting to notice
how different the standard of women's bodies is.
She has kind of like a soft mom type body.
It's wonderful.
And we just opened this whole thing up with like this long lingering shot of her ass.
What's it walking this is it? Oh, this opens with the beach scene with Kirk Douglas and his son and then it cuts right to the two of them walking down
Okay, I didn't notice that I didn't notice that the uh, but yeah
She's she's if it was not no actress would ever show off this ass in a movie is what I'm saying. I love it
She's I found it as well stunning. I loved it as well the uh because I'm more open -minded than you
I'm commenting on societal changes
That's what everybody says when they make remarks like that. They go, no, it's a commentary
on the way people are. Uh, no, I'm kidding. Of course, but the, uh, the great cast,
great cast, some great. It's always fun to see John Casavetti's two -play bad guy. Like,
it's, it's, uh, you get to see him explode if that interest. Yeah. That was great. That
was a hell of an ending. I like that they didn't try to go past that ending. No, the ending
is tremendous. The last 20 minutes are a fun romp. It becomes like a crazy, telekinetic
fucking freak show thing and everybody's going nuts and there's a lot of blood and it's a lot of fun
the rest of the movie is a little uneven but I will say this as far as all the
department movies are concerned it is the most hitchcockian of the department movies in my opinion
Noah well here's why I'll say well it reminds me very much of like the 39 steps
or some of the earlier, not earlier,
but you know what I mean, older Hitchcock stuff,
where there are moments of like whimsy,
there are comical moments,
there are moments of dread,
there are dramatic moments,
it really hops around.
And it doesn't mean like Dennis Frons
driving him around town in the cab.
Yeah, yeah.
Stuff like that.
Were you LOLing throughout that stuff?
Well, I mean, that's supposed to be funny
when he's got the two,
well, not the Dennis Frons,
but well, that, but, you know,
the thing where he's got the cops in the car and the cops were scared and he's that was
down his front. Oh, that was he was one of the cops. Yeah, he doesn't remember he treasures
this car and then it goes off the here and that's I thought you said cab. So I got confused.
Anyway, that's like supposed to be comical and you know, and then like obviously, uh, John
Kessavitz exploding is not. No. Um, so you know, it just reminded me of some of those older
or Hitchcock things like, what's the one?
Torn, it's called Torn curtain.
Yeah, like Torn curtain and, you know,
they would get like sort of goofy and like light
and then they would get super heavy
and have things about murder and them or whatever.
It's not a bad flick, well shot.
I think it's a long way around the road there
to get to the point.
It's a very convoluted plot in my opinion.
in like you've got CIA operatives,
you've got, it's a stupid plot.
Yeah, you've got kidnapping, you've got telekinesis.
There's a lot going on and it's like,
this would have been a lot easier if it was just like,
Kirk Douglas wasn't in the CIA.
Yeah.
His son was telekinetic.
The CIA abducts his son.
They make it clearer.
The reason's clear why they're abducting the son.
And then it goes from there.
But instead it's like the CIA betrays Kirk Douglas
and then Kirk Douglas is on the ounce
And then he's hiding from them, but then he's dating the lady that works at the hospital where the kid is because he needs to get to the kid
And it's a lot of it's a lot of
Shicka much and they're the first half's like way too many high jinx
It was just kind of stupid. I thought uh the Jones Williams score
This great. Yeah, always good to see John Williams in a non -speelberg thing
Well, it's funny because there were moments
There were moments where I would forget it was John Williams. Yeah, and I'd be watching it. I'd be like
Oh, man, that almost sounds like a Star Wars riff and I was like, oh, yeah, John Williams.
Yeah.
So, you know, check it out, but yeah, I would say run to the Netflix and turn it on right
now.
Certainly see Carrie first, another certainly top tier Stephen King adaptation.
I did see an interview once with John Casavetti's where he was bitching about the current state
of cinema.
Sure.
And he goes.
he goes and you go to the movies now and it's just the gunshots and a man's the blood splattering on
the walls. And this is entertainment. Yeah. And I was like, wow, he's really not into violence
in movies. But then this movie, he literally explodes and blood splatters. And I was like, is he talking
about the fury? His head and slow motion falls back into the camera. Yeah. So I don't know.
I don't want to blow your mind, folks, but people in Hollywood tend to be hypocrites.
Ladies and gents, that's our fury episode.
Check me out.
Jotaroza comedy on Twitter and Instagram, uh, panel's calm.
You let me down.
Check me out at the Patrick Walsh on Twitter and Instagram also finally, as of Friday, received
an air date from my television show starring Jotaroza called living biblically.
and it premieres on February 26th after the Winter Olympics at nine 30 p .m. Check it out.
And here come our shout outs, Patty. Thank you so much to the Patreon contributors,
to all the fans and everybody supporting the show Derek Clark, Jenna, Anthony V,
Minneto, a K party McFly, Philip Rashad, John Wolt, Justin Boehagger, Nate
Roundtree, Adam Benbenek, Mindy Mani -Rios, Demonio Rubio, Brandon Gash, Edmund Agabo, Paul
Pickerel. Pickerel, Pickerel, Pickerel, Pickerel, Jake Ferote, were ferret. Tyler Watson, guys,
these are really tough names tonight, man. These are, these are some tough ones, man.
Tyler Watson brought you to your names.
Well, it's, but it, because with a Z, it's W -A -T -Z -I -N. So when you see that at first glance,
it throws you a little bit.
All right.
Not making fun of your names, folks. Just want to make sure we get them right.
Chris Lind, Jake Bullock, Tony Quinn, Rob Lines, Danny Rudd, Jacob Barrett, Jordan C, Maxwell
Ashcroft, Ryan Kohler, Joshua Christianson, Barbara Allen, Jonathan Face, Rebecca Cohen,
Smelly Bubbles, Chris Bowen, Mike Gibbons, Danyay Joyce, Michael Dawson, Jennifer Smith, Luke
Vaughan, don't be ridiculous.
Connor, Denny, Michael, Stephen Copa, Copa, Calpa,
Kevin, Swiss, Swiss duits.
Thomas Cosa, Anthony J. Guajardo, Annie Johansson.
Nope, Annie Johansson, excuse me.
Timmy K, Sean Floren, Dolores Martinez,
Will Foley, Megan Librand,
Scott Blikken's Dürfer, Alec Walker, Brett Werner, Tristan Carlson, Laura Sexton, Anthony
Guajardo.
Did I already say him?
Maybe he contributed twice.
I don't know.
I feel like I already said that name.
Brett Klingkner, Alex Lowe, Weston Thomas, oh boy.
This one's always tough.
David, David, this is the one where he said, believe it or not, it's pronounced Smith.
Yeah.
All right.
Weston Thomas, you know what we're trying to say, buddy, shout out to you, man.
I don't know how to say the name, I'm sorry.
Jared Blair, Josh Smallridge, Richie Verdugo, Chris Hopper, Emily Rosenbaum, Emily Florence,
Hi, M .O .A. Sean L. Jordan Parker, Dave Comerick, Abby Manuel, Kim DeAngelo, Jonathan Gallott,
Pats Tijuana Handmaiden. I think that's for you. He's saying that he's or she's saying whoever
it is, saying that they're your handmaiden. I got to get back to Tijuana. Carla, oh, Mike Willes.
That is Willes. Yeah, Stephanie Power, Hunter McDonald, Sterling, Abrigo,
Giron Sanderson, Diego Campos, Stefan Musal, Zoe Blaskeweck, Edmund Dillon,
Aasley Kivensland, Dan McLeod, Lorenz Bunganiers, or Bunganers, Alejandro Salad Gado,
Joe Puppa Spush, Tegan McLeod, Matthew Little, Tracy Reddington, Sean Thomas, Amanda
Alzen Mora, Jason Weebel, or Weible, but they don't fall down. Michael Curry, Drew
Spindler, Andrew Covell, Sam Mitchell, Aaron Melonowski, Scott Nolan, Jack Gertz, Greg
Sironson, Benjamin Tahia,
Misty Zavar, Brandon Knock,
Dajne Wilford, Johnny Ferg,
Matthias Pagwai.
Oh, he even put the pronunciation in there.
Matthias Paujo, I think I said Paujo,
but Matthias Paujo, thank you for the pronunciation.
Superfan Giovanni, Michael Gold,
Daniel Duer, Eric Lamora, Michael Madrigal,
go to his record store
in, uh, Mr. Shoot records in Lancaster, Pennsylvania. Stephen Reese, Walter Keegan, Kevin Merkinnick,
Erica Banning, Lawrence Anderson, Jared Smallridge, Zach Schoendorf, Will Pottorff, Natalie
Craig, Nathan Baskett, Anthony Kyle Kinsland, Brooke Adams, the man whose name we cannot
not say, Auntie Bobbiduk, Scott Palin. No, sorry, Scott Patton, excuse me. Read aesthetic,
Brian, whoo, Brian Boe Larrier or Boe Larrier, Barbima, M -O -L -E, Marvel, Robert Pearson,
Boring Dan Clark, Michael IAO, Max Unwraff,
Heighten Davidson, Brian England, and John Wiesen Gruber.
Thanks, everybody. Take care.
That was a hate gun podcast.