Huff, puff, and spin the house down at Golden Nugget Online Casino!
Right now, new players can deposit just 5 bucks and get 500 total spins on Huff and
Mortpuff, the slot that's blowing players away.
Download the Golden Nugget Online Casino app and use promo code Nugget1.
That's code Nugget1 to enjoy 50 spins a day for your first 10 days, all on our players'
favorite game of the summer.
Now's the time to score daily bonuses and spin for all the bacon on the game everyone's
hoffat about.
At Golden Nugget Online Casino, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberler.
Please play responsibly.
21 and over, physically present in Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia
only.
Void in Ontario.
New customers only.
Non -withdrawable Casino spins issued as 50 spins per day for 10 days valid for featured
game only and expire each day after 24 hours.
C -terms at GoldenNuggetCasino .com slash promos ends at 11 .59pm Eastern on August 31st, 2025.
The football season is full of guarantees.
And here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if your
football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fancash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fancash,
guaranteed.
Switch to Phenatic Sportsbook, winning hits different here.
Monthly 21 -plus, gambling problem called winning 100 gambler, offer not available in all
states, terms apply, see Phenatic Sportsbook app.
Guess who's back in the motherfucking house with a podcast for your motherfucking mouth.
Pat and Joe, whereas you call us the boys, the boat, well, you told me to guess.
So I was guessing the boys are back in town, yes, who just got back a town again.
That's a song. I always thought it was a shame that Sinatra didn't cover that song because
that's got a real Sinatra voice of back in town. Yeah, that'd be good. Yeah, because he
covered sunshine in my life. You are the sunshine of my life. Yeah, yeah. And he does, and
he hits life like that. Life. Yeah, I think I've heard it. And he did a, he did a wood
Billy Joel song did he do he did I think he I think maybe just the way just the way you are
sounds right I know he did something in the way she moves that's something in the way she moves
and he does a beautiful cover of it but he can't resist going Sinatra like towards the end and he
He goes, something about her, Jack, up until that point, it sounds, it sounds great.
And I got no problem with throwing in a Jack.
Maybe it was the lady's name.
You know, we don't know.
Jack, he was singing about Jackie O, Jackie Brown.
I walk in tonight, Joe's, it was confirmed at first.
I just thought he had left the TV on, but I just confirmed that he was watching Charles
in charge.
Yes.
Yes. So then we're talking a little bit about breaking bad and I go, you've seen breaking
bad, right? Cause I know Joe's never seen sopranos or he's seen a couple of them. Never
seen breaking bad. But he is watching the entire run of Charles and charge rewatching. Let's
be free watching. Also supporting a man who's been me too. An active supporter of the
movement. I'm not supporting. There are several other people involved in that program.
Yeah. I don't even remember what Charles and Charles was. You got to stand up in every episode.
You got to stand up guy on there like Willie Ames, who's an alcoholic that plays a Bible man super
hero. In what? You never saw Bible man. Bible man. Bible man. You never saw Bible man. You never
saw breaking bad. Gonna give you shit for not seeing Bible man. But I mean you've never heard of it.
it was it was crazy because like he so he after that show ended he got like
super religious. And he started doing the superhero show. There was like
really low budget. But it did it was on the air. And it was called Bible man.
And there were action figures of it and shit. I had an action figure of it at
one point, like ironically because I thought it was funny. But then this before
or after zapped a movie about where the two of them could remove women's
dresses with their minds was Bible man after that or before which if
If Charles goes to court, that, that movies, that, that's not helping his case.
Exhibit A.
That, well, you're honest, this is just a clip from Zapped.
I didn't actually do this.
It's the first, I'm only watching the first season, because that's all that's on Hulu, but
I never knew this.
My friend, Jennifer Runyon, is in the show.
She places girlfriend throughout the entire first season.
And she owns running canyon. Yes, she started it. She founded it with her with her father.
Jack Canyon.
Jennifer Runion, if you're not familiar, is a wonderful actress and or actor, excuse me.
And she is the, she is the woman in Ghostbusters, the blonde. Oh, sure.
That Bill Murray is doing the ESP test with. Beautiful gal. Yeah. So I actually met her years ago
to show where we were they were playing a movie she had been in that was that was very bad yeah
yeah and and you know it was one of these things were the audiences like yelling out and whatever
but she came to the screening it was at nerd melt she came to the screening she was a total sport
and I had to do a set at it and during my set I was like I I go I'm gonna just say this because
uh when else am I gonna get the chance when I was 12 and my or 11 and my best friend at the time
Billy Morgan. Uh, when I would have sleepovers, we would, we would write down what our dream
person was like the attributes of our who we wanted our wife to be. And I was like mine
was always Jennifer Runyon who I just added young boy thing to do right down the attributes of your
dream bride. Yeah. Okay. So mine was always based on her. And then we spoke after him. We became
friends. And now, you know, where we've been friends ever since she came to my special taping.
and lovely, you know, she's a very lovely person.
All right, I believe you.
Anyway, so I'm rewatching Charles in charge season one.
But what triggered the rewatch?
It was on Hulu, they just put it on Hulu.
Is it funny?
It actually is pretty funny and it's pretty edgy.
It's way edgier than I remembered it being.
Can I get an example?
In the pilot episode, I know in the pilot,
he says, Charles is in charge of this pussy
and sort of spits that up.
And the dad says it as he's spreading his asshole and bent over. No. No, there's a joke in the first episode where it's his first date with Jennifer
Runyon's character. Yeah. And they're talking about how she's like the most beautiful girl on campus and all this stuff and how like buddies like I can't
believe you have a date with her. So he's got to watch the kid. So the date is she has to come over to the house. And he's like nervous because he doesn't know what to do. And the dad
like pulls him aside. And he's like, Charles, you're a good kid. You got your whole life ahead of you.
Yeah. You don't want to make any mistakes. Right. And he's like, how do you mean? He's like,
there's two words you don't ever want to hear a woman you're dating say. And then just then the wife
comes in and goes, I'm late. Uh -huh. I was like, wow, that's a pretty edgy joke for a mid 80s. Sure.
Like this huge applause break. She meant her period. Well, the wife was saying she was late for her work.
Right, but the double meaning yeah, the double meaning was and then and then the daggers
I guess that about sums it up and then he just walks out. Yeah. All right. Good job. So
Surprisingly funny look before before we go any further
I would just like to get
On with the show
and in doing so on
with the Joe's
Joe's
I love it. Never done it before. I love it. That's the first rap one you've ever done. Maybe is he alive?
Nate dog. No, he's been dead for quite some time throat cancer or something. He had
like he got like leukemia or something like that. Yeah, like, uh, but all time great
voice and the best things in, uh, with snow, who started the show with guest who's back
in the mother bar. Yeah, I changed the lyric to make it podcast appropriate. Yeah. Uh, he
still said mother fucking, but we're not PG as I'm sure they've learned. No, but the second
part of that lyric is much more graphic than Motherfucker.
It's a testament to you and I Joe that we just saunter into doing this podcast, but there's
a lot to talk about.
We're on a new network.
We've been off the air for months.
You guys have really not been cool about that.
Constant tweets and Facebook and Instagram attention, which made me feel good, you know, but
maybe feel good too, especially once we announced the return date.
I was like dude back off. I love that people care. I love that they care. I can't imagine
I don't love myself. I've never really liked myself. Sure. So when others like me
I'm it's always a nice surprise. It is nice but we're on uh star burns
podcasting uh network um and you know let's let's be uh cordial here a nice
sign off to head gum you know it wasn't a good fit ultimately but uh they put on
on this show during our sort of formative years
when people really found us.
Thank you to them.
Yes.
But we're happy to be on a new network and a fresh start.
We're happy to be at Star Burns.
It's an exciting network.
They've got an amazing studio.
They've got an amazing catalog of podcasts.
Right.
It's a great roster to be a part of.
We're thrilled.
We and we're doing a live show.
We can we can mention that again in during the plugs.
I'll look at the dates and stuff,
but there's a live show coming.
October 20th to that night.
730 and 930, I want to say.
I believe so at O My Ribs, which is on Santa Monica Boulevard
in Los Angeles is a small theater.
Pat and I will be there, obviously, doing a live pod.
The 730 show will be different from the 930 show.
So if you want to stay for both,
there's an option to buy a dual ticket.
Merch, I'm assuming we'll be on sale.
And then afterwards, for no additional charge, yeah, wash me, Emily Florence, Ken Hanley,
yeah, we're going to a bar with whoever's hanging.
We discussed throwing a charge down.
I said, it doesn't, doesn't seem right first, first show.
You guys are, you know, absolutely incredibly loyal fans.
And we thank you.
I have seen people say, you know, I'm going to fly in from, you know, New Orleans or something, don't do that.
I'd hate for something to happen and you get you to get fucked.
I'd love for you to get.
I'm not a guy flying or a guy flying.
I just saying we want to tour.
This is not the only time we'll be doing a live show.
Don't kill yourself to be a show.
Yeah, do not kill yourself.
Don't miss your child's birth to be there.
Right.
But if you got some money to throw around and you want to be wild and fly in.
Hey, fly in. You fly in. I can promise you this when I tell you we're going to go to the
bar with the afterwards, we're going to go to the bar with the afterwards. Yeah, it's not like
we'll be monitoring how we come across. I imagine there'll be clumsy passes made between me and Joe.
It'll get sloppy and I think that's what you want. And speaking of clumsy passes, Joe, why did you
tell less moon best to do what he did.
Wait, when did when did that come out?
Oh, I've been dying for this one.
You know, I, I've been waiting for the CBS network to come up.
Wait, when did this come out?
This was last Friday.
It was the new, it's the new Ronan Farrow joint.
Oh shit.
It was rumored to be the last one, but I remember he came out
what he came out with was like kind of half -ass.
It was like, we found another thing Harvey Weinstein did.
and it was like, wait, this was teased
as some big juicy thing.
My thinking is Moon Vest paid to have that one killed off,
but he couldn't do it again.
Well, this guy's a notorious scumbag.
He runs a shit network full of shit people.
You got no beef with me there?
I'm happy to see the man go down.
And he's not been let go.
That's how sleazy the CBS network is.
They're kind of like keeping him around.
He was on an Anita Hill honorary, like, like board, like about like defending victims
of sexual harassment.
They threw him off that board, thankfully.
What was the, what are the accusations?
Are they super?
There's only six.
And I imagine many more come forward.
The first one.
I was trying to say super harsh.
It sounded like I just said, they were, they super, though, and they weren't super.
The first one was Ilyana Douglas, who is a beautiful actress that I have long loved.
Really?
The woman who gets her cheek bit off and cape fear and a very funny comedic act.
She's hilarious as well.
She is great.
She's a highlight of Turner Classic movies.
Whenever she's introducing a movie, it's just as entertaining as the film she's doing.
I love her.
She dated Scorsese for many years and was still dating Scorsese.
It was the end of the relationship.
that Moonves calls her up, wants to do something,
she goes in, second the door shut.
He's on her tongue down her throat, you know,
hand on her panties, skirt up.
Jesus, you can read the details.
No, it appeared no one got to a, you know,
a full penetrative assault.
It just seemed like he would shove his tongue down your throat
with whenever he had a meeting with seemingly any woman,
and they would tell him, stop.
He would keep them from ever working again.
Oh boy.
Well, I stand with Iliana.
Yeah, except for his wife, Julie Chen,
who has come out and stood up for him,
but she was a much younger woman who,
she's like probably accepted those advance.
Julie Chen is, she hosts big brother, Asian lady.
No idea.
She's standing by and you got these other women coming forward
and they're like, I work in marketing. Less moon vets has never made a pass at me. It's
like, so he's never done it to anyone. What the fuck is wrong with you? It's just shameless
sucking up in case he beats it so then he can promote them. It's a sick, sick time as the
custodian of this building. I would like to say he has always been a gentleman. Yeah. And
look, I've seen some sexy custodians. We're not talking shit here. But moon vets, the one
time I met him I they were like it's very very important that you shake his hand it was at the up
fronts in New York. And I was like but I'd rather just drink with my friends I don't why don't
need to meet less movement like you have to you have to do it. And I waited for upwards of 30 minutes
while he finished a conversation with Jeremy Piven. So that's like that would be like you know
So Rachel Ray and Martha Stewart swapping recipes and a cooking convention.
If only we'd known, we could have flown in a helicopter and dropped a net on the two
of them and just sort of scooped them up as we had them in the same location like the
old Batman 60s.
Right.
Now have you seen Piven out doing stand up in the clubs?
I know he's I've never seen him physically, but I've seen him.
He's played many clubs that I have played.
prior to or or he's been to places that uh that uh that you know where I'll see he's coming or whether
people love it. Does he do the RE character? Does he do some of his catchphrases like Lloyd,
you're a gay slur screamed at the top of his lungs, anything like that? I never watched
on it throughout the show. I don't know that one I'm fine with. Thank you. Thank you. I hated that
fucking show from the day it premiered. I hated it. I'll admit I started watching it when I moved to
L .A., because I thought I needed to know like how to dress and how to behave in meetings,
which I know is kind of sad, but maybe somebody thinks it's cute.
I think it's the kind of sad where it could also double as cute.
I ain't every episode.
It's a ludicrous show, but it passes the time.
It's entertaining.
Now, I knew, I knew on the first episode back for this new season four, season four, yeah.
I knew you'd be throwing at me, Joe, why did you tell so and so to do it?
I knew that.
I had to be part of the first episode.
I can't believe you didn't do it with Charles in charge.
Bale.
You had it right there.
It was right there in your pants.
I had already referenced Charles in charge and Bale's crime.
Or a legit crime.
I'm saying, I can't, when you brought up Charles in charge,
I'm surprised you didn't then go, why did you tell Scott Bale
to say what you did?
Right, right.
These are allegedly did.
Sorry, we got to keep it legal here, of course.
We're dusting off some of our catch phrases here because,
you know, this might be your first time.
I don't know how podcasts work.
Um, let's hold on a second here.
By the way, our, our film today is hereditary, our film is hereditary.
I think that's the most requested one that I've seen.
It's been a while since I've been to the Facebook page.
I will say all you guys all with the Joe's that I saw were incredible, but I still haven't
seen all of them.
And I worked the correct winner was chosen.
I don't know.
They were wonderful.
They were all wonderful.
Some of them were very moving.
Yeah.
I'm touched that anybody cares that.
So thank you guys.
I really am, you know, like it, I mean that.
Um, do you want to get, I mean, we're about 20 in.
You want to get to the, uh, we got to go to Pat's movie corner, right?
Yeah.
Um, take us there.
I've got a lot.
I've obviously seen a ton, so I'll just sort of pick, pick a few.
And these go back months, we've been off quite a while.
I saw, well, I'll say I'll start with something that made me feel great at a terrible time, won't you be my neighbor?
That's the Mr. Rogers thing.
Mr. Rogers, and Mr. Rogers, I definitely knew how important Sesame Street was to me when I was a kid.
I remember it. My parents always talked about how I was obsessed with it, but I didn't
really remember what a huge part of my life, Mr. Rodgers, was until I realized I recognized
every clip from this movie. I've seen it all. And just a great man, there's a long clip
of Fox News saying that he is the devil because he ruined the only negative word said about
Adam in the movie is like a recent Fox news thing where the like he's the devil.
He made every kid think they're specials and everyone thinks they're special.
Oh, wow.
Real bleak in the middle of it.
You're like, get off the screen.
But by and large, I sat and I have a problem accessing emotions.
I sat with tears just streaming down my face.
And I did my best to hide it from Heather, who was also crying, but it was no use.
I cried from start to finish.
It's a beautiful movie about a beautiful person who devoted his life just to making kids
happy.
And you see him get enraged at shows that you and I both loved, you know, but like they
ask about he man and yeah, and he gets enraged.
I've seen clips of that.
Just to see somebody care that much about such a great cause.
It was a very special movie.
I loved it.
I'd like to tell him to tone it down on the he man stuff.
I mean, it's a little over the top, but he's a good guy.
Yeah, he cares.
What are you going to do?
I saw, I'm going to cut right to this.
This is a rewatch, Pat.
OK.
I rewatch both fingers.
I feel like we spent most of the time on this podcast talking about both.
No, but here's where I bring it up.
The last time it was mentioned, I mean, I told you the Bobo and Kirk choke.
Yes.
What could possibly be in the special edition of both finger?
I looked at said fine Prince said does not contain the movie both finger right you were very offended by that joke
You said it's a fine movie. There's absolutely nothing wrong with it. It's a funny film
I don't think a guy in comedy should be taking a shot at that comedy because it's well done. I rewatched it. Yeah, I
Always thought that too. This movie is a fucking shit show. It is a terrible film. Wow. I rewatched it so recently. It is a terrible
terrible
terrible, terrible film. The jokes, there's a handful of very funny jokes in it.
Eddie Murphy kills in it in both roles. Eddie Murphy is great. The rest of it is not
up to that standard. I don't laugh as hard as I did with the him running across the highway
bit. No, that, that part's funny, but I thought it was extremely entertaining. Brief. It's
Good satire.
It's good God, it's just terrible.
It's like a stock movie.
Like it's the way it's directed, the soundtrack.
I will say every part of it is so generic
and like manufactured.
And then it has these great elements in it
where like Steve Martin is taking shots at like Scientology,
but they don't fit with that movie
because it's a tonally, it doesn't fit.
like it. I don't know. I don't know. It's just it's just not and I love Steve
Barton. I watched that Martin Schwartz, Steve Barton, terrific standup special that no one has
talked about. Yeah, it was fucking hilarious. So I mean, but I'm a fan, but I mean I just I couldn't
believe how much I didn't like it. And I was just a movie I owned at one point. Yeah. I still do and I
really enjoyed it. I don't know what to tell you. I loved it in high school. I loved it. Now I think
there it certainly takes some swings that miss. But how about the joke of when the dogs
like looking at him and he's like you still believe in me don't you Betsy and then the dog
goes and walks away you're like it's just it's just a terrible joke. I mean you you always
go joke for joke. You gotta look big picture. You gotta look big picture. All right I'm looking
big picture. I mean what somebody who like one bad joke is gonna ruin a comedy. What do you want me
I mean, they get the dog wearing high heels walking it. I mean, it's just it's the the actual like fake filming of the movie stuff is probably the least successful stuff in it with
Baran scheme. Yeah. I'll grant you that. But I do like the whole cast. Sure. Um, I saw sticking on documentaries.
another excellent documentary called Three Identical Strangers and I will not
spoil it for you, but basically this movie starts. It's a guy 18 years old in
Long Island. He goes to college and everybody's I don't remember their names, but
everybody's like, hey, Jerry, hey, Jerry, girl, I'm up and kiss him. Hey, Jerry and his
name is Bill. What's going on? It's really weird. Then somebody reveals to him
that there is a guy who looks exactly like him who they all know from the school and they
go wait a minute were you adopted he goes yeah so was this guy they go over they find
out their twin brothers but they're like 18 19 years old they immediately are like mirroring
each other like they love each other so much and they're truly identical like same interest
same taste in women same everything then obviously because it's called three identical strangers
They start getting some publicity on the news.
Newtons revealed that there is a third identical twin
triplet brother.
So the first half of this movie is just like a delightful
almost like a comedy and the brothers not the twin
sequel triplets.
No, but that's supposed to be happening with Eddie Murphy.
Yeah, I know.
I know.
But it's like a really entertaining kind of fun romp.
And they show you all this like Phil Donahue clips they were
on in the day and you know, like old TV.
and the three guys are funny and really entertaining.
So you're going along with it.
Then I'll stop telling you anything about the movie,
but there's all sorts of dark turns that come your way.
But a near -perfect documentary.
It was excellent.
I can't recommend it enough.
Documentaries are always in theaters for three weeks
and then on Netflix.
So you can probably wait at this point,
but just a really good movie.
Really interesting.
A lot of food for thought afterwards.
Alright, um, I'm torn here. How many more are you going to do? I'm going to do one more. We'll do three a piece. Okay. I'm doing an all documentary evening.
I'm going to go with another older thing that I watched.
This show is wild, man. Go on. I never had heard of it. It's on Amazon Prime right now. You're watching the Marvelous Miss Maisel, aren't you?
This is an old Delta Burke sitcom called Women of the House.
Have you heard of this show?
A whorehouse?
No.
Okay.
No, her husband is a house representative and he dies.
And she's like supposed to be like a southern sort of trophy wife and then who doesn't know politics
and then she comes in and takes his seat.
She inherits his seat.
And then as you can imagine, takes DC by storm with her.
Of course.
How do they explain that the wife is the next in line to take the house of representative seats believe they just say that?
Yeah, you could back them
Or she gets elected in because it sounds familiar because the state loved him so much something happened
I can't remember CBS show. I don't know if it was CBS, but this show is wild. You got Delta Burke
playing like a sassy Southern lady, right?
You got Terry Gar as her press secretary
Terry. Terry Gars coming into every scene drinking and drunk. All right. And what's her
character up to folks? Lung cancer, like hacking in every scene. That's like a running joke
is that she's like hacking up Flem constantly because she lives so unhealthily all the time.
Okay. You got Patricia Heaton from everybody who loves Raymond. Okay. As like the straight
Laced she's like she she run she's like the campaign. I'm not the campaign. She she
Sir Secretary the manager of the office. Whatever the fuck that's called. Is there any dick in this thing?
Or is it all ladies? There's one man in it. Okay. Mr. Jonathan Banks. Oh nice. Who plays Delta Berks?
And I'm using the words from the show. Yeah. Retarded brother. Oh boy
You text him? I didn't text him
Now, how is he doing like other sister level broad?
Is he doing it?
It's more of a, it's more of a far as gumpish kind of thing.
But one of the jokes in the pilot is Delta Burke going, this is my brother.
He's retarded.
And I know we ain't supposed to say retarded no more, but honey, I got to tell you, being
retarded, it's a hell of a lot harder than being mentally handicapped.
That's a joke in the pilot.
This show is wild.
It sounds like it was written by Diane English who did designing women and I believe Murphy Brown. It's very
Diane English, it's very murky, it's very like feminist like like go fuck yourself. So Joe I shoot from the hip. I loved it, but it's wild.
What made you watch this? Like how does it happen with all these options? I was scrolling through
my Amazon prime and I saw woman in the house during Delta
Burke breaking bad no sopranos no deadwood no woman of
the house women of the house women of the house because
she's got an all female staff gotcha it probably was
Diane English nobody else could have gotten that made but
it's very very sassy yes in a in a in a good way in a in a
in an edgy way and uh wait Joe she's she's poor
trying Suzanne Sugar Baker. It's a spin off of Designing Women. Oh, it is. Yeah. She's the
character from Designing Women. It says Suzanne Sugar Baker. I mean, yeah, that's her. I didn't
realize that. Spin off of Designing Women. Wow, interesting. Had reconciled with the producers after
a bitter, highly publicized off screen battle. Yeah, they said she was too fat. Remember that?
Yes. And her husband Gerald McRainey, a major dad himself, a major dad, was like,
Fuck you, which I always liked. Yeah, me too.
Interesting. It's a fun show, but it's CBS, but it's it's it's like an edginess that you can't put on TV anymore. It's the lady who did designing women. Yeah, that's awesome.
My last documentary film will be Whitney.
The story of Whitney Houston. I had seen the showtime documentary on Whitney called Houston. Yeah, he was called Houston. We have a problem.
Oh, you have a lot of problems.
Yeah.
And I thought that was kind of exploitative, but decent.
This had a lot more access to her inner circle, her family.
It is, as you can imagine, a deeply tragic story.
It's great to hear those songs in like amazing sound quality.
I'm a Whitney Houston fan.
You're a Whitney Houston fan.
I love the hits.
Yeah, I grew up with those songs.
I want to dance with somebody.
beautiful song. But I mean, you put, you put on voice. I don't got any of our albums.
I'm not saying like it comes on you, you're, you're not mad at it. That's fine. But I'm saying
you would purposefully put on. I want to dance with somebody. Sure. Still do. Like to clean the house.
I think particularly for that reason. Yeah. All right. Now what are you wearing as you clean?
Sort of a frilly negligee. And of course, the feather duster. Uh -huh. Pink feather duster with
the white handle. Yeah. Right.
Bunny ears. No, I'm a professional. But, uh, you know, a deeply sad movie of course,
I mean, as I'm sure you've heard, they get into her being molested by an aunt who was
Dion Warwick's sister. Oh boy. And the family has tried to cover this up forever. You get
into her, you know, closeted girlfriend situation, the Bobby Brown situation. Um, and then
Bobby Brown lives like on camera. He's like, Whitney Houston didn't have a problem with drugs.
Whitney Houston didn't do drugs. What are you talking about? That level of denial.
I remember, I guess I can say this because I'm not going to name names, but I was doing a tv show once
and there was a makeup woman doing my makeup who knew Whitney Houston. It was like right after she died.
right. And this lady, everybody was talking about it. Yeah. And this lady goes, I swear
to God, she goes, she goes, let me tell you something, honey. I knew Whitney. She always
did drugs. Yeah. They're trying to pin it on Bobby. Bobby didn't have shit to do with it.
Like she was a drug. She loved drugs. They say that in the movie. And it also hit her brothers.
I think we're a much bigger part of getting her into drugs, who were her bodyguards. She
was just surrounded by all the wrong people and very sad. Similar to the Amy Winehouse documentary,
Amy, which was somehow even sadder than this, but I thought it was very interesting and great voice,
gone too soon, blah, blah, blah. I'm going to close it out because I've been on a bit of a
Scorsese, De Niro kick lately because I'm so excited about the Irishman. When's it coming?
It's I guess in the either this I think in the fall or early 2019 one of the other. I'm trying
to read that book, but I'm incredibly excited about it. I'm trying. I mean, I've been looking at
it across the room for six months. Yeah, I have it too. I got to get to it. In fact, in the time I've
owned it, I didn't read it for months, bought it for my mom. She finished it and it's been months since
that. And she said it was great. But I watched The Wizard of
Lives on HBO. Good, good, good, good. The Bernie made off
film. I loved it. I thought it was great. I thought it was
superbly directed. It was great. It was, it was what's his face
did? It's on the film. Levinson, excuse me. Levinson does nice
work. You know, sometimes he misses. Sometimes it's a little
to emotions on the sleeve, but I liked this one quite a bit. And it was great to see
De Niro acting in something again. Yeah. It was great to see him and he was so good in
that role. And I was like, this is why I love De Niro, man. Like this is awesome. You know,
I don't want to be trying again a little bit, but I loved it. I thought Michelle Fifer was
great. You know, like the little moments, like the like ordering the lobster and all that
stuff, you know, like at the party. Yeah, that's how you bring a lobster. Yeah, they take the time
to show you like the little minutia is in a biopic at my always my least favorite genre. All I care
about is the weird shit in minutia. I never care about he was born in Queens. No, who gives a shit?
They jump right in. It opens on the day that he gets caught. Yeah. So like, um, which I didn't know
he turned himself in. I never knew that. I didn't. I thought I thought he got busted, but I'm
But I love Hank as areas fucking great in it.
There's that crazy scene where he's like where it's all crumbling down around him and he knows he's gonna go to jail and but nobody else does yet.
And he starts screaming at his granddaughter right at dinner and she because she's like what's Wall Street like and he's like I don't have to answer to you or anybody's like what the fuck is wrong with you man.
Yeah, it was a good movie.
I tell you, you know, you know, what a lot of people were saying at the time is Bernie
made off with my money.
They say that in the movie and it's from an actual news report.
I wrote that but they play a real news report who says that who, who, who,
I'm a man named made off made off with their money and people wonder why this country's
a fucking toilet right now. Anyway, it's because of that newscaster. Joe scary stuff. Yeah, walk me
through. I got one for you for the video game fans out there. Do yourself a favor. If you've got
a PS4 or an Xbox one, go out and get the Sega Genesis collection newly released for the Xbox
box one and PS4. I almost didn't get it because they've put out quite a few Sega Genesis collections
at this point since the system has passed into the ether. But I got this because this
is by far and away the best one. 50 plus games, rewind features, fast forward features,
save states, it just amazing high -definition quality. This is basically, this is, you
know, Sega didn't put out the the Genesis mini like everybody hoped they would like Nintendo
did with the SNES and then Nintendo mini. This is basically a Sega Genesis classic mini on
a disc that you just, you know, don't play on a mini console you played in your modern console.
But it is so, so good, so many good, fantastic, insane games on it, you know, it constitutes
for the segment because it's got the golden X games, it's got the street of rage games,
it's got the sonic games, it's got plenty of high fantasy, you know, spectacular content
on it.
And I can't say enough good stuff.
If you like Genesis and you have one of those systems, you need to go get this.
It's like 30 bucks, so worth it, so worth it.
These games individually would it would run you a fortune to get all 50 of these games
For your actual system. So anyway, that's the that's my scary stuff
I watch a two -hour documentary on the A &E network about making of Ferris Bueller a
Movie about the horrors of that a lessons
So it fits it works. I think
Doesn't work because you're talking about watching a thing. This would be more for your segment
it. Well, let's pretend it was on a DVD of Ferris Bueller. That you bought this segment
about special features of horror movies. It could be. Yeah, when I talk about a DVD,
I don't talk about the movie I watched. I say, like, there's this new addition out with
all these great special features and packaging. Right. It's about the product. It's not about
the film itself. Well, it was great documentary. And it can be hard to find behind the scene,
shit on John Hughes. It was a very private man. I recommend looking it up. They also have
one of jaws. Maybe that counts for this. It's closer but it's still wrong. Yeah. Yeah. Nobody's
ever going to side with me on this. Everybody seems to side with you just spitting in the face of
this segment every week. I don't see how talking about Sega Genesis has anything to do with scary stuff.
It's a product of the horror, sci -fi or fantasy genre, a product that's not usually just talk about
video games. But well, those games are sci -fi video games. All right. You know, I talked about
slaughterhouse before. That's a horror video game. But not tonight. Tonight, I talked about
Golden Axe, which is a fantasy video game. All right. The gent, you know, what do you think
the genesis fucking video games are? You think you go, it's a lesson in accountancy or something?
They're crazy. They're insane like laser gun video games. I block out these parts because I don't
video games. I do often talk about video games, but I'll also talk about a horror book that came out
that's interesting. Right. I'll talk about a new release from criterion or something. I read,
I'll be going to the dark about the, it's whatever Sacramento killer. See, that would have been perfect.
Shoot. I don't understand. Yeah, written by Pat and Oswald's late wife.
And I feel honestly terrible that that's how I know we're not her name, so I'm not going
to look it up.
But I heard about that book through the great podcast by our dear friends, George
Ardstark and Karen Coguerreff, I urge you to check them out, and the author of the book.
And it was a fascinating and extremely well -written true crime book is Michelle McNamara.
and I am truly sorry, I didn't know that off the top of my head.
That's not perfect, you know?
That's how I also heard of that book.
And here's the thing about our friend Karen particularly,
she'll never side with me when it comes to you and me disagreeing.
I love that.
Karen just got a little promotion ever in my rola decks.
Had a problem with the food delivery guy the other day.
Yeah.
Texted you about it.
Texted events about it.
Texted Karen about it.
Ask you all the same question.
Here's what happened.
and we'll tell them the story.
The guy didn't want to come up to my apartment.
And I said, no, I paid for delivery.
I put directions in the app on how to find my apartment,
come up to my apartment.
Yeah.
And it was the sole thing.
And then I texted either three of you.
And I said, am I an asshole for this?
And you and Vince both said no.
Right.
And said, yes.
You're being lazy, you're ordering food.
Go meet the guy at the gate.
that's insane that you make them go through that complex. And I said, you're the only one that
disagreed with me, Pat agreed with me on this too. And she said, he just did that to shut you
up. She just won't agree with me. Look, there's always some truth to that. There's always some truth
to me agreeing with you to shut you up. But in my mind, I, you know, I do get tired of when it's postmates
especially because the charge is so great when they're like, Hey, I'm here and you go out and
and they're sitting in their car.
I'm like, you couldn't walk the 10 steps to the gate
when I'm paying you like $18 before you even get tipped.
It's crazy.
I got no tolerance for it.
Now this place, I'll go to the door that I'm in now
because it's a much faster, I moved everybody.
It's a much faster walk, but I'm sorry, man,
I'm giving you a 20 or 25 % tip on top of a 6 .99 delivery charge,
Yeah, on top of over -priced food that sucks. You're coming to my door, man. I'm sorry, fair enough
Anyway, I love you Karen. I just wish you'd support me for once
Let's get to our movie let's get to our picture a little movie called
Hereditary. It's been a lot of requests. If you want to prove it, that way you can.
Herodotry. I believe it's that. Herodotry is the name of this show.
Herodotry that grows hair. But when you touch it, you grow hair as well.
So that's a nice sort of side effect of the hair tree.
I love this movie. And I know because during the off season,
and Joe and I had to talk about movies off the clock.
And we disagree on this one.
So we're coming back with a disagreement
because you all like those, even though they threaten
our very friendship and the thin fabric that it rests on.
I don't see what there is to disagree with.
This was an overhyped, overblown.
And there it is.
Finish your, finish your thought.
but almost carbon copy of Rosemary's baby. You walk into this thing. People are telling you
it. It's a peerless film. Nothing like this has ever been committed to the to sell you, Lloyd.
And you watch it and you go, all right, it's a 70 style slow burn horror movie. And in the end,
it's Rosemary's baby. They're trying to bring the devil personified to earth. Whatever demonic name you
want to give that character, it doesn't matter. And this demon that they're trying to bring
to earth in the end is he's coming to lead them to salvation, which is exactly the plot
of Rosemary's baby. But here's the thing about Rosemary's baby. The baby was smart enough
to just understand what it was that this fucking movie had so many inconsistencies and had this
demon by the end of this thing, when they, when you, they finally explain what this demon is,
you're like, they're like, he needed a male host, but he went into the woman by mistake.
You're like, what kind of fucking idiot demon is this? He can't tell the difference.
And why does he need a male host? Like, like, give that, uh, give that some meaning. Sure.
There were, this film made no sense. It was a, it was beautifully shot. It was beautifully
directed, this kid that directed it has got a bright future. I even look forward to seeing
what he does next. But this movie is incoherent. It is a bunch of trying to be sort of shocking
imagery strung together. None of it makes sense. There are no rules to any of it. It is long,
it is fucking boring. And you know, at the end of the day, it's like, everybody's like, oh my God,
it's so brilliant because Tony Collette is great. And it's like, she is great in it. It doesn't
means a good movie? I'd like to address all at that point, five point. Sure. I
knew you weren't going to like this movie, Joe, when you said to me at a bar
or something, it's hereditary, man. I don't know. I don't know. I said, oh, you
saw it, thinking I had a friend that could talk about it. No, I just keep hearing
things about it. Well, because it was I was so what what when I was you're too
influenced by the hype and the movie was hyped up, which is why when I told you
about it. I kind of talked it down, even though I loved it, because if you get hyped up stuff,
you'll never like it. It's something you gotta get past. I was listening. I went into it with an
open mind. I was ready to watch it. I enjoyed a lot of it to a point. And then it got away from
itself. And then that made all the stuff I enjoyed have less value. I can't argue that. And on those
points we are different whereas if like I always say if I laugh out loud three times at a comedy it's
a good comedy if a movie has some effect on me I tend to like it but you are a guy who on many
hours on this podcast alone have railed at jump scares and things ripping things off and et cetera
and while this has some surface similarities to Rosemary's baby don't get me wrong this felt like a
very original and originally put together an originally shot movie with almost no jump
scares that I remember outside of a really really cool like throw away in the background
of a scene jump that I thought was very earned.
I like that was the one scary thought was good and I thought the head on the side of
the road was good, but the head on the side of the road was just shock value, but let's talk
that for me personally, whether you want to count it as horror or not, that scene from
From the moment him and his sister walk into that party to the moment she is decapitated
and then the next morning when the mom is going out to get in the fucking car and then
you see the head on the side of the road, that was one of the finest 20 minute sequences
I can remember.
I was so tense for that 20 minutes, I didn't know if I was going to last the movie if it
it maintained that level of tension, which it didn't find, but I thought that was just
so perfectly put together.
The party sequence is literally just the party sequence from, uh, from, uh, uh, what's
the fucking movie?
Can't hardly wait.
No.
What's the movie with Paul?
Uh, Rudd and a little stifler, stifler and Paul, uh, a role models, role models.
Yeah.
It's the party.
The big brother to the little kid, he takes him to the party, he goes off to like fuck
around and do it smoke weed and the kids alone and it's tense and you know, something bad
is going to happen.
So I'm watching that party.
See, and I'm going, all right, this is the role model's party scene, but, but whatever,
I get it, we're heading towards something.
The decapitation thing was amazing, the reveal with the mom going to the car was great.
right. But as the movie goes on and you see that that has zero significance, zero. What
is the significance of it other than the mom needs to go crazier? Why does the sister
sort of come back, but the grandmother doesn't come back. Why does the grandmother decapitated
just because the granddaughter was decapitated. Why is Tony Colette suddenly decapitated at the end?
Why when Tony Colette burns the spell she catches on fire, but then when she burns at the second
time Gabriel burn catches on fire. It doesn't make any fucking sense. None of it makes sense.
I'll say I felt lost in the in the back third of the movie. I to me lost does not mean bad
ever. And I think it does to you. And that's that's a difference. No, no, no, no, my defense.
I'll say this. I said after I saw it. Maybe I didn't get it. Maybe I'm messing something. And
the more I've talked about it and brought all these points up to the people that have loved it, I
have not yet heard one counter argument to say, no, this is what that was. Well, it's a kudos to you,
Joe, because even when you shit on a movie that I love, your points are always funny and valid. I can't
to Nia, but unless they're not, by the way, like you getting mad that there wasn't a
Wilhelm scream in last Jedi was the stupidest criticism of a movie I've ever heard. But
I don't know, some of those I could argue, I'm sure all of them the director could explain,
but I would like to see it again. Immediately when it was done, I wanted to see it again.
and immediately I was on the Wikipedia page,
which helps with plot points sometimes,
but it didn't bother me.
It wasn't like a mother, which is a movie that you loved,
where it seemed just designed to piss you off
and kind of intentionally made no sense,
unless you look at it as an allegory.
I thought it made enough sense,
and then eventually started kind of doing its own thing.
The man has planted as a trilogy.
There may be answers.
I think he will get that trilogy
because it's done very well on a low budget, but for me, the amount of time I felt really uncomfortable
in a way I had not felt uncomfortable before. For example, that 20 minutes, for example,
several other moments in the movie, I got to tip my hat to that. And I watched after I discussed
with you at The Roost, this guy's 20 minutes short. Yeah, that's brutal. I've seen it. It's great.
It is about basically a 30 -year -old man who has been steadily raping and sexually abusing
his father for decades and it was, I really, really wish I hadn't watched it in a different
way than her editor.
I found it too much in a way that I'd like to replace the parts of my brain that remember
that shortly.
But that's a guy with talent that can make you do that.
Look, I had seen that before her editor.
Right. One of her fans suggested we watch it. I watched it.
I found it wholly disturbing, but I thought it was very well done.
And it made sense to me this and I watched some of his other short films.
And he's got some short films where it's just weird shit with no fucking point.
Right. So weird shit with no point.
To me, look, absurdist is absurdist, but there's got to be some kind of,
there's, for me, there's got to be some kind of spine,
there's got to be something weighing it down.
You know, even in some of the crazier Samuel Beckett plays,
you can see the metaphor.
Yes, you know, you can see the metaphor
and as crazy as what's happening on stage,
it seems to be, you can see there's an interpretation,
there's something there to take away from it.
I didn't feel this had that.
I felt like this is like when you watch a comedy movie
that thinks comedy is just saying stuff that's bizarre.
And I was invested for the first half.
And then as it went, I thought it was a,
I didn't think it was that great of a reveal.
Like, like that, I thought it was kind of a cool reveal
that like you found out that her friend was sort of in
on this ploy to resurrect this demon.
But I mean the say onslaid.
Yeah, but I was like okay if that's another great performance. I was she's that she's great in everything the guy's name is Ari Astor by the way
I feel like sometimes we should shout these people out better
But I just didn't understand I'm like so wait. She was working with the grandmother
But now she's working against the mother
Why wouldn't she try to work with the mother because the mother thinks she's on her side
So why wouldn't she try to right pull the mother all the way over to the dark?
It's just that those kind of things bother me, man. Like I'm just like it's I'm sorry
You you have to fucking follow your own rule book. I'll say this demons are unpredictable
Always have been
but
To me and especially as I get older
Which I think most people would go the other way, but and maybe it's my love of weed, but I like a
A movie that does its own thing even at the expense of plot
This movie I knew was pissing people off because of the amount of talking in the theater at some point a 40 -year -old man grabbed a
14 -year -old girl's arm and screamed shut the fuck up better
Which made me feel a lot better about my bad Santa 2 incident that I talked about on this podcast
But she goes don't you fucking touch me in the whole theater turns around and this guy kept her arm
And was like, no, you're ruining the movie.
Shut the fuck up.
And I will say, I don't know what caused it,
but people are talking throughout entire movies now.
And it doesn't matter what they are.
And it's driving me fucking insane.
And I want that theatrical experience,
but at what cost?
I find myself more and more sane.
I got a nice TV I'll wait.
So I don't have to listen to people get wrong.
It's, listen, we don't live in a society anymore.
No, it's I'm working on this it's I'm glad you brought this up. I'm working on this new bit about
This is obviously just the premise, but the bit is about how like
When iTunes first came out and Amazon first came out and all that all that convenient shopping stuff first came out
And we were and I was very much, you know at the front of the charge of this is ruining us the brick and mortar stores are disappearing
We're not communicating anymore. I look outside now
I'm like, Oh, no, they were being like, we need to get you into the house because it's
going to be a shit show out there pretty soon.
We need to get everything set up so you don't leave your house anymore, so you don't have
to leave your house because it is going to be unlivable out there.
And day by day, it gets worse, yeah.
So full, like full volume, long conversations and you'll be like, excuse me, could you please
stop?
And the look at you, look, you're a fucking asshole.
Yeah.
It's insane.
I don't know who's raising these these kids their their their shithead fucking parents. That's who who are probably talking through movies to the worst anyway. We have a
difference of opinion on this one clearly. I think hereditary is like kicking off an awesome horror career. I hope this guy makes that
trilogy. Tony Collette. I think it's better than just great in this movie. I think she's absolutely incredible. She's great. She's always great. Yeah.
That scene where and the kid her son is incredible the scene where
She's like come watch this little say -ons and the daughter starts talking through her
Which felt like really real and cool to me his reactions to that it was like watching somebody go through something that horrible
I think that's what people were responding to about with the movie and saying it was like it shook them up or something
It feels real considering how insane it is and Gabriel Burns performance as I was telling you
to have me dying laughing the whole time.
I don't know why, but I do know why.
I've never seen this reaction in these movies.
The husband is always like, honey, what's wrong?
Can I get you a glass of red wine?
Every time she complains to him or goes a little nuttier,
Gabriel burns size heavily and rolls his eyes.
Like, oh, why did I marry this fucking woman?
And it made me laugh every time.
I will say nobody else was laughing.
But like when he drives home after the kid
has bashed his face into the death near the end. And she comes running out of the house
like there's a skeleton in the attic, whatever. Right. He doesn't even roll his window down.
He just rolls his eyes and sighs and parks the car. Like there's going to be another fucking
night now. I've never seen that at a horror. I thought it was awesome. I'll tell you this.
I thought that was awesome. Up until he discovers the body. Yeah. And then shows the same lack of
emotion. True. And then that's when I went, oh, Gabriel burn his sleep walking through
this movie. This is not a character choice. He's not into this. That might be right.
Because that was terrible. He, he, he finds it decapitated corpse in his attic and he comes
out and he goes, well, he did you dig her up? What did you do? Yeah. From that point on
break, you should argue that the movie is not operating at its, at its finest. I'll give
of you that. But just from that point on, I do want to see it again. At any time I
ever want to see a movie a second time, when more and more I find myself wanting to walk
out of movies, I think you got to commend that. I think this is a very, very well done horror
movie. And it was influenced by Rosemary's baby. But I think beyond that, a super original
movie as well. Yeah, I'm not saying with something to say, I'm being a little harsh with the Rosemary's
parallel, but I mean, it's, it's, it's, there are some striking similarities. I don't
think he stole Rosemary's baby, but no more than many other demon position movies have.
Sure. And it's, you know, the whole, yeah, so that's fair. That's fair. The, um, dammit.
Oh, I think it was a nod to, uh, what is it? Geolo cinema? Is that how you say that?
Yes, I thought it was a nod to that kind of cinema and to, you know, the, to the, you know,
the Italian hard directors of the 70s and 80s and Bava. Yeah. And, you know, that's great.
And I like some of their movies. But, you know, for instance, and I've heard this movie described
this way, Susperia. Sure. The original. I've heard Susperia described as, look, it's a wonderful film
as long as you're willing to not care about everything making sense, if you want to just kind
of let yourself go to the experience, you're going to have a lot of fun, which is typically what this
guy, Argento does. And, um, and I agree with that. You know, that's why I was never a huge
conspiracy thing because I was always like, I don't feel like they, like, I don't know, like, it's not
enough. I, I really like twists and turns and like, plot and, like, I really get off on that,
like I envy well -written plot lines because they're hard to do. So I hear that completely and that's
just people of a different mindset. I was talking, you know, we're trying to break a story at work
today and I was like, for me personally, like I like the first act of a comedy where everybody's
sitting around breaking the chose balls and laughing before the plot starts, before they go to Vegas
or before they become Ghostbusters or whatever. I always wish we could stay in the hangout.
No, that's not a movie. That's not a story. That's not a plot. But and part of it's just that I get so sick of breaking stories all day, but I don't know. I've always kind of been that way.
I like comedies that are like that like diner that are just kind of incidents of people hanging out and on a horror movie. I've seen this.
I've seen the structure of horror so many times done exactly the same way roughly that when something's different or doesn't quite make all the pieces fit.
Hey, I'm willing to give him the benefit of the doubt and B, we don't know what demons
would do. You know, maybe demons do shit a little different demons do it a little
differently. The new romantic comedy starring Gina Davis and Jeff Goldblum. Folks, that's
our show today is as Jackie demons. It's her name in the movie. I believe this is a,
It's August 6th. Today is my birthday. Really? Yes. I honestly didn't know. I'm sorry. Happy
birthday, Joe. Oh, wait, they were airing the day it airs Monday, the August 6th, right now
we're keeping it a little listening. All right. Happy birthday, then, Joe is my birthday. So
it's I love that the premiere of season four was on my actual birthday. Yes. We're happy
to be back. We'll, we'll finally start speaking to each other again and plugs. I'll be at the
the D .C. draft house in Washington D .C. this month, August 17th and 18th. I'll also be performing
at the Red Clay Comedy Festival in Atlanta last weekend of September. Some other shows
will be happening around that in the sort of southeastern region of the United States.
Joe DeRos' comedy only on Instagram now. The Twitter account has been shut down. I am
me. I mean, I should. Yes. I am the Patrick Wall should Instagram and honestly probably a pretty short
live Twitter account as well. I might be shutting down. The only reason I'm on Facebook is to read
your guys comments in the fan page, but I'm not long for that site either. Personal plug. I am
running a new show called The Cool Kids. It is basically always sunny in a retirement home. It is
executive produced by Charlie Daye who co -wrote the pilot. I took it over episode two. It is Martin
Mul, David Allen Greer, Vicki Lawrence who played Mama of Mama's family, and Leslie Jordan.
They are extremely gifted comedy actors. I am very excited to be writing for them. It premieres Friday
September 28th on Fox. I'm not going to talk about it much till then, but it's going to be very funny.
Okay. Our show is on October 20th at Omai Ribs, $7 .30 and $9 .30.
In Los Angeles.
Each show is $20 or if you pay $30, you can attend both shows.
The ticket link is not yet live but it should be coming soon per the venue.
We will let you know when that goes up.
People have been asking Joe what movies we're going to do.
we are going to be doing on the Patreon.
We'll be discussing our viewing of Gotti.
Oh, for this month, you mean?
There will be a Patreon coming this month.
By the way, apparently people were asking about that as well.
I am gonna reactivate it this week.
Gotti and coming up next, we'll be doing solo,
the Star Wars prequel, and I think also,
we'll be doing the new mission impossible.
Definitely MI6.
is I guess really not horror sci -fi or fantasy but close enough.
Yeah, I mean, it's like kind of in that John Wick zone, and maybe Castle Rock.
We'll be doing Castle Rock. We got to talk about it because Pat's seen the first two.
It doesn't sound like a walk in the park. Check it out on Hulu. Maybe get caught up.
We'll try to be caught up by the time we do Castle Rock. I asked about the merch. All of the t -shirts
that we are selling, we're on presale, so they're spoken for, which is pretty cool.
But there's going to be more shirts available, of course, at the live show, and on the
Hoghouse page on Etsy.
We do still have stickers, posters, hats, etc.
Thank you, gang.
Thank you to the creators of all that wonderful merch.
Thank you, Emily and Ken, for putting all these cool events and stores and things together.
and thank you to the artists that are doing that and the fans that are buying it.
So you guys are all amazing.
Thank you very much guys. We'll be back next week with Solo
and we look forward to creating new memories on a new network.