Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from Anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM game sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Waiter, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal, durable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
Gambling problem? Call 1 -800 -Gamber.
Welcome to the show.
This is Will See You In Hell, your hopefully favorite horror movie sci -fi fantasy podcast.
We're happy that you've joined us today's topic will be Blade Runner 2049, the review,
the diehards of this podcast have been waiting for you know how we feel about the original
Blade Runner.
Right.
That it's a steaming pile of shit.
So has the sequel outdone the original wait to find out on this episode if we'll see
you in hell.
So I will say I accidentally saw Blade Runner 2069 in which Ryan Gosling and Harrison
Ford on a couch both sucked each other's dicks at the same time.
Right.
Did I enjoy it?
You know, honestly, yes, did it need to be two hours, 45 minutes, no, but it's hard for
an older man to come and Harrison Ford is probably 70 years old. Folks, I'd love to
get on with the show and help. Why don't I also get on? Oh, we the jaw. Very good.
Very good. Here we are in a Saturday night. Pat and I are on my couch in my living room.
Uh, it is a touch of sadness in the air, frankly, it is, it's 9 .30 and we're sitting here
recording. Well, we are drinking steadily.
Pat's been hitting this weed pipe. Yeah, you always have to tell them.
You don't always have to tell them, but the weekend comes and daddy likes to put on his
briefs and slide across the floor to some Bob Saker, risky business style.
And it's not a crime. Uh, we're going to go to the bar after this.
that'll be fun. I will tell you folks we just recorded our bonus episode over at Patreon.
I would be remiss. I would be remiss congeniality. If I did not tell you that we now have a Patreon,
if you want to donate any amount of money, we'd love it. We're doing this out of love. The money
will kind of keep the show going. If you want to shot it on the show, it's a five dollar a month
donations like a buck a week and if you want the bonus episode which we just
recorded in folks, it's an hour plus and it is me and Joe each discussing our
all -time favorite horror movie. If you want to find out what that is, plus with
plenty of bitching and oh yeah there's at least 50 minutes of bitching before we
get to the point of the episode. But yeah it's a $10 a month donation and each
month you will get, you know, a truly special and stands on its own episode of the show.
It's not like some quick fuck off.
We take it very seriously.
Yes.
And this week's episode is fantastic.
We wanted to launch it right.
Joe, do you have the Patreon address off hand?
It's patreon .com slash WS, IYH, IYH, we'll see you in hell.
No, no, no, WSYIH, that's what I just said.
Is it patreon .com slash WSYIHTOD, and that's it, and we're going to, this is the first
episode we're going to do shout outs to everybody that donated five bucks or more.
Those will be at the end of the episode, though, so the people that weren't able to donate
or donated under that tier don't have to sit through all the damn shout outs at the beginning.
You know, it's, you know, we don't want to, we don't want to want anybody to feel excluded here
We're just trying to give little bonuses to people that are helping us keep this going and
For those who can't that's fine. You're still going to get this damn podcast. Don't worry about it
We just started a week ago not even and we've been pretty overwhelmed by the response. It's very nice
Thank you very much. Thank you
So I'd like to start today, if you don't mind, I don't know, but I assume I don't mind.
With a segment that I said was going to be a new segment, I think we did it at one time.
But I said we were going to do a new segment now on the show.
And we did it, as I said, at one time, I think, and never returned to it.
But I can't even remember what the fuck we were going to call this segment.
But anyway, I do think that, you know, there's some value
on us doing, you know, an interesting horror sci -fi or fantasy related news story. In the
past, I know we did the, I believe the Jeepers Creepers, something about Jeepers Creepers
3. Anyway, today's news story comes to us via movieweb .com. John Carpenter will score the
new Halloween film. That's fantastic. Yeah. And for those of you that have not heard them,
John Carpenter fans, he's released two volumes of the Lost Themes works and both of them are
exceptional. The guy is really, really, really doing some really cool musical work these days.
And as he always has. But the fact that he is returning to orchestrate this and the second bonus is
They also announced that this movie will be a direct sequel to the first Halloween film
It's apparently ignoring all the sequels
Yeah, I'm excited and frankly I think don't careful the chord there. I got it. No, no
No, don't keep it because it might distort the thing don't you consider two better than one like a dummy?
I love to and I know nobody agrees with me on that
But here's why I like to they should all be thrown out here. No, that's here's why I like to
one I
agree is a moodier piece
It's it's one is much more of a film
Two is much more of a movie I get good to his bad two is not bad two is a fine sequel to his
great because one gets all the exposition out of the way and two hits the ground running.
So I like that. It's fun. It's fun. It starts right up at the top and it never lets up.
There is no, we need to explain who Michael Myers is. We need to explain who this doctor is.
We need to explain why he's coming back to this. There is none of that. It's just the body
is gone at the end of one. What the fuck? And then two starts and it starts right then
At that moment, there's no atmosphere. There's no suspense
I don't agree with that. There's literally a scene where like a nurse takes her top off. It's it's shit
Frankly, it's shit. It's not shit. It's an okay sequel to a masterpiece. Well, here's what I'm one shit
You're an idiot. It's shit. Three's better than two
Shut the fuck up. Three's more interesting. Stop it. Stop it. I'm sorry. It's stop it
You should be ashamed to say that Halloween two is better than one.
I'm not saying it's better. I'm not saying it's a better film.
I'm saying I enjoy it a bit more because I like the pacing of it and everything.
All right. I'm not saying it's a better movie.
All right. It's like, I really want a bit.
I realize Nightmare and Elm Street two is not structurally a better film than far and away.
But I enjoy watching Nightmare and Elm Street two more.
That that that's far away with Tom Cruise doing an Irish accent. Yeah. Yeah, okay. Yeah, you know what I'm saying now
I've see I saw far away when I was kid, but
That is a a period piece is that right?
I've never seen the goddamn movie. I was just taking a blind. He's a boxer in Ireland
All right, let me let me let me change my thing
Okay, my example, but now I want to know what far away is I realized nightmare and I'm straight to is not a better movie
than the remains of the day.
But I'd rather watch that Murray now on the street too.
That's all.
That's all I'm saying with Halloween too.
All right.
Here's my question.
If this one now is going to pick up after the first or, you know, be a direct sequel of
the first one, are they going to eliminate that Jamie Lee Curtis is his sister because John
Carpenter said he only did that in a moment of desperation and writing the sequel because
he didn't want to do another, he didn't want to do a direct sequel.
Well, he wanted to do a completely other story,
which is why three is a completely different thing.
And he said that, you know, he was sitting typing
and he had drank about a six pack
and he said, he had no ideas
and he was just like, God help me,
I'll just make it that their brother and sister.
Yeah.
You know, put a little star wars twist in there,
you know, right thing.
So I'm just excited that the guys making
like the darkest, most interesting comedy right now
are making this horror movie.
And I think they'll take it in a different tone than fucking Rob Zombie. Thank God, but
That said folks the second season of ice principles says
Almost unwatchable and I loved oh really the back half of the first season
I thought I that show got better and better maybe the second season will be the same where it starts out
We can get better. I've been hating it. I've been hating it. Why is it bad? And I love those I like I was so I was thirsty for it
I lie eastbounded down is is an all time favorite for me. Why is this season bad?
There's not a laugh to be had
And then in terms of the darkness like the darkness in eastbounded down is this guy who just can't stop fucking up
And anyone who's ever had a problem with drugs and alcohol can relate to it in a big way and it even when it got crazy
It was relatable
This season
And I mean, Goggins is beating the shit out of a fellow teacher in a wheelchair.
And he's in the, he's in the handicapped stall in the men's room.
He beats a shit out of a guy in a wheelchair.
I'm like, you know, so what did you do?
Spin a wheel of what's offensive and land on beating up a guy in a wheelchair?
Like, it's embarrassing.
I, I've hated the whole season.
And these are my favorite guys.
I, it's, it hasn't been good.
Wash is not having it, not having it.
He's had enough of that's all there is to it speaking of speaking of what you're having
or not having.
Yeah.
Let's move on to Pat's movie corner.
Have you have you seen anything in this last whatever it's been weak?
Oh.
I had that's a that's my impression of Al Pacino in center of a woman being derogatory to
a woman.
Ready?
Yeah.
you're a whoah. That's good. Get it. I got it. Yeah. Got it. Maybe I could take that
to SNL. I'll put that in my packet. I saw. Oh, and speaking of jokes, it
aren't that funny. Sorry, Pat. You're cutting you off. No, it's fun. You got me good.
Pat and I were at a bachelor party this weekend. And we were sitting around a table
playing some sort of a board game. The worst board game ever. Fascist versus
is something predator. What was it called?
Dear friend, Moshecatcher tried to explain this thing to us.
We were higher than shit.
I couldn't make heads or tails out of it.
I could tell you, I read the directions today.
So, where's the judge?
I couldn't make heads or tails.
I don't go for a cerebral board game.
Get out of here with that shit.
But Pat and Pete Holmes are from across the table
with one another started doing some sort of bit
about a magician in a ball sack or something.
Yes.
Play on words, some sort of a thing.
Well, it was a previous bit of mine,
and Pete's where we basically outlined an entire movie called Flabra Cadabra, wherein Ben
Stiller is a David Copperfield type magician who based on actual David Copperfield events.
Apparently he has his own little island.
That's how rich he is.
And on his shopper field, not shopper field.
When he finishes the show on Friday night, he does like the Motley crew thing of like he
He surveys the crowd.
He picks out a woman that he wants to maybe ask to come on his island and he brings
a woman with him.
So he pitched this thing.
We're Ben Stillers playing David Copperfield basically and he points it.
I love that blonde in the third row.
They accidentally get Rebel Wilson.
She goes them to this island.
The movie's called Flabrikadabra and he's alone in this island with Rebel Wilson.
But in the end, they find love.
Now we had this thing broken out to the point where I think we could sell this tomorrow because
It's just that stupid idea that it could maybe get made today. Right. That's what we were discussing and then P was making some sort of weird, you know
Magic, yeah, he's making a joke, but I didn't realize this whole thing that Pat just explained. I didn't hear any of that at the table
Because again, I was higher than shit. Yeah, I also had about seven to kill us at this point. Yes, I thought it'd be funny to yell out the term
Magic dick
Across the table. Yeah
A hard thud. I yell it across the table. It gets nothing. Pat goes yell out magic dick again
I think he's being sincere. I yell it out again if bombs are gonna go it got nothing the second time he goes
Yeah, I know P and I have pretty much figured this thing out. Yeah, and
It hurt at the time it hurt a little bit and then I realized oh this is like a bit. They had I was just on another fucking planet
I was on another planet
I will say I've I've been around you high before I've done the podcast where you were high before I
Recognized you as being super stoned, but you were way more together than normal in that in that situation last night
Yes, I was on another planet. I'm telling you when
Motion was trying to explain to us the rules of the game. I was I could not stop laughing at how complicated it was and you did say to me at one point
but you go, you go, dude, you're on your own thing right now.
Like you're really, you're somewhere in your head.
I was laughing so hard.
I couldn't, to the point where I felt bad
because then he started getting self -conscious.
Like, I'm sorry, is this too much?
And it was like, no, it's just funny, man.
Well, to me, there's not, even since I was a kid,
there's nothing funnier than the guy
who was trying to teach you a board game.
And it's getting angry because nobody's listening.
It's just it's always hilarious, but with everyone being high, it contributed with the rules being so complicated, it contributed.
And when 20 minutes into the instructions being read to us, I noticed Mosha suddenly getting confused on something and consulting the instruction book, the guy who's telling us about the game, I was like, this is fucking ridiculous.
And I was ready to leave but then in the game the person who has to say till the end is has the Hitler card
I sure enough I peek into my envelope because the game involved envelopes and I was Hitler
So then Josh our buddy was like I got to get out of here
And they're like are you as long as you're not in Hitler you're fine to leave and I was like well fuck they just confirms
that I have to stay here then Pete launches into this bit about how our friend Josh was this will
never translate but it was I'll try to explain it was so much harder than I have in five years he
was so this made me laugh in like I'm in college and I got high for the second time yeah this was
that kind of you remember you filmed it it's on your phone I did you filmed like the highlight of the
Remember that I filmed it you film oh, well, I'm gonna enjoy that for a long time. Yeah
This was like literally college high laughter. I was I was laughing uncontrollably at this
Yeah, he starts doing this bit of Josh leaving and and he's doing an impression of Josh driving home
Being so elated that he has somehow got out of playing this game that none of us understand
Yeah, and Pete is miming a man driving for some reason a semi truck. He's spinning the huge. He's doing the underhand steering wheel
Honestly, there's no way to explain it to make it as funny as it was, but the bit was just that he was so happy
He was driving and and the song kept changing and he was singing along to on the way home
Yeah, and it was all just like some sort of feel good celebratory song.
Right. It started with with whatever that song is.
Yeah. Then when Josh left, I took the bit in the direction where Josh then also escaping the
game. High fives Rob on the way home. Rob left first and then it was Josh. It was Rob first
driving and then Josh. But now I realized they would not have been driving in opposite directions.
My premise was flawed it's tough. It was hilarious. So then they're driving by one another and they're high -fiving. Yeah, as
What are some of the other songs? We did we did woohoo. We did a we did a Santoria by sublime
We did a horny
Yeah
As they drive past each other high -fiving
We and then honestly when I thought the the bit was completely worn out
He hit us with some body once told me though, and that song is always funny
And he by the way, wait you you had a real big one that you're forgetting
Santa Rio was no, it was my her name is Rio and she dances in the song. Oh, that's right
Yeah, her name is Rio and they're high five because they drive by yeah, we're out of the game
The uh now up until is a terrible game, but I had a blast up until the point of the
the Smash Mouth song coming in.
It was just us singing the songs to each other
and miming driving and laughing hysterically.
When Smash Mouth came in,
Pete set it up on the stereo.
We think the bit's dead, he just starts playing the song
and then the actual song, and that was like,
I thought I was gonna die, I was laughing so hard.
Well, the first song that he played,
and Moshe was annoyed by the bit,
but eventually he could not deny it at all.
It was the first song he played was the blur song.
Woohoo!
But when that song started, I was like, holy shit.
It was really just an all -time classic bit
that I think will be referenced for decades to come.
And yet it was so stupid, which is the best way for a bit to be.
Yeah.
And then he did the Smash Mouth, then he did Rio.
He played the actual Rio.
It was a lot.
It was a great time.
Anyway.
Very fun. Very fun. I cut off your your past movie corner. What have you seen? Oh God?
I
Ain't seen much. I watch
A couple of programs I guess I
Saw my first episodes ever of Will and Grace
That's a bad show. I had never seen it before and I watched three episodes the new one. How's the new one?
It's fun. It's good. I will say I like it because there's jokes and we live in an age
of the joke -less comedy. Yes. It's relentless jokes and those actors are all really, really
great. I will say to be watching Primetime NBC television in 2017 and hear the F .A .G. word.
They say it on the show I nearly fell off my couch. They say they say it in jokes
You can say it you're quoting a joke from I don't say it
I don't say it. You're not like saying it in a bad way
You're just quoting something I had also never said the C word until I finally started dealing with a true C word
And now I say it all you never said cunt. I don't say it. I love that word
I know it's of course, but I say I were ever saved it for 36 years until I met one that warranted it if I was ever
on inside the actor studio. That's my answer. What is your favorite curse? Yeah.
Cunt. Not in a sexual way or a gender way rather. It's just a great word. Yeah. Man, it cuts glass.
That was a joke that Pat would do around the set of the pilot of the TV show he runs
I was fired from the uh uh that was a joke you would do it like ever you know we'd be sitting
around talking about past projects that so you know whoever did yeah and like for instance
David Cremholz would say yeah I remember I did this film once and I played this guy Harry who was
a whatever and Pat would cross his legs in the go David may we speak to Harry because he was on
that show numbers with a three for the day and I was like David can I talk to John numbers
which is, of course, not the characters, man.
Robin, can I talk to the bison, teniel man, please?
It would, that always made me laugh.
That was a very funny bit.
And again, I say it every week, Joe,
but every week at the taping on Friday night,
they show the pilot and every week,
the hugeest laugh is your scene.
Well, thank you.
That's nice to hear people to see it.
Here's, here's what I'm hoping.
The show's been going into test things,
you're doing it's test, right?
Hoping these audiences come back and go,
where the hell is Gary?
Yeah, and then CBS has to go,
we gotta get this Gary guy.
No, I would love it, but they told me they were like,
so we're doing, we're testing episodes two and three
on Tuesday, it's at four,
so we'll need you to be there at 3 .30,
they're like, read me this shit.
And I literally put my hand up
but I said, I will never go to any of these
testings. Right. I don't want you to ask me to them. Right.
I won't be there. I go, you can give me a synopsis after.
How would you want to sit through that? All I do is
stew and stress about every joke and every line. And then to go
and have these fucking idiots, the people who go to these
testings are people who are free at 2 p .m. on a Wednesday. And
and they go in there and say I didn't understand this
or that I would break through the glass.
It's a two -way glass.
I'd wind up breaking through the glass and killing them.
I love that they do that.
They do it all like CIA style.
Yeah, the two -way glass.
No, I went to the testing of the pilot
and it was like, you know, like the boss character is mean
and they'll be like, I thought the boss was mean
and I had to walk out and I can't do it.
It's the testing, I need to listen to my heart.
The one thing I have is that I am fine.
Well, you're, because you're a Tom Petty, man.
That's correct.
I gotta listen to my heart.
Here you go.
You can top off your tequila drink.
I'm just handing Pat a bottle of hornitos,
which describes my pelvis right now.
Oh, pelvis, wrestling.
Okay, so stuff we've watched, what did I see?
I saw, well, I've got the Herschel Gordon Lewis box set, the feast box set.
I got it for Christmas last year from my very generous parents, and I've been going
through it slowly.
Today I watched Wizard of Gore, which was a lot of fun, and I started to watch a taste
for blood, but I did not get very far into it.
So far I would say a taste for blood looks like, as far as the construction of a film is concerned,
at least the ones I've watched on this thing it seems to be the the most well
constructed of the Herschel Gordon Lewis films but I haven't seen much of it
I've just kind of gotten into the beginning and stuff what's Hersch's big one
blood feast is the one blood feast is the one biggest movie well none of them by
any stretcher big but blood feast is a huge cult classic it's been remade there
were sequels and it was notorious because I think it was made in the late 60s and there's
a scene where a man cuts a woman's tongue out of her mouth and the way they did it was
they literally pulled like a cow tongue out of the lady's mouth.
And you know, for that time that was extremely graphic.
So the movies are very bloody and gross and gory.
It's kind of like if John Waters made straight up like horror movies
Like that's that's what it feels like to me and I like them. It's a fun. It's a fun set to it's a fun set to
Peru's through and he was actually a really cool guy like
He was like his own DP and he shot it and he you know and directed it and produced it like he kind of did everything
He was a very business -minded guy and he did everything himself for the most
part, uh, and then like left movie business and went into like crazy, like real estate
and shit for a long time. I think you've had a bit of teacher for a while. He's an interesting
guy. He's just a cool dude. Um, uh, and I want to marry him, Joe. Hey, folks, I think that's
all I've really, yeah, I ain't seen much seen in the last week. Oh, and then I, I mentioned
this last time. It's still holding up. I'm still watching it. It's still great. Gotham is just
really hitting the fucking home run this year. There are four episodes in. Riddler's back. Penguin
is in full fucking swing. Scar crow. I'm sure Freeze will be back. Bruce Wayne is essentially Batman
already at like 15. And they're just doing really cool stuff. It's like really cool seeing like
Bruce Wayne is learning how to be a detective from working alongside Gordon and picking up
tips from Gordon.
People are dying because he's making mistakes because he's impetuous and he's young,
which is cementing like the philosophy of the future Batman saying like I'll never kill
anybody.
They're just doing a really, really, really cool job of developing the character, all the characters.
So watch that.
Anything else?
You got anything else for this one?
Well, this may be Joe's scary stuff. All right, you want me to then then let's move on to Joe's scary stuff. All right
What do you got baby?
When I was probably eighth grade
my buddy Aaron Crozier
tried to show me the Texas Chan saw massacre two which you have a giant poster of in your home
French poster French poster give it all the give it all you know and I couldn't
handle it. It was traumatizing for me. Even though I know that's supposed to be the comedy one.
Yeah, when when I was a kid and I saw it, I found it extremely gory and upsetting and then when I
got older, I was like, oh, this is like ridiculous. Right. It's supposed to be funny.
So I had bought the shout factory edition of it with all the special features. I fantastic.
I'm starting to think that maybe this will be the first time I actually have something for Joe's
scary stuff. Pat, here's how right you are. I did this as a scary stuff once for myself.
No, okay.
And I was going to watch the movie
and found that my memories of being traumatized by it
as a kid were so strong, I couldn't watch it.
And so instead I watched the 90 -minute documentary
about the making of Tex -Chancellum Act II,
which was fantastic.
Yes.
And still I have not seen Tex -Chancellum Act II.
It's a great blu -ray.
They did a really, really wonderful job.
The artwork on the front, as I've said before in the podcast,
It could be my favorite horror movie artwork ever.
You know, our poster here is a spoof of the Breakfast Club.
You know that?
Yeah, it's phenomenal.
It's, this is a really, Texas Chainsaw 2
is a really heady and layered sequel for what it was.
Like it was, it was fucked me up, to be honest.
I think it was, it's basically what a lot of sequels
try to do where they try to satirize the first one
to make a commentary about it.
And sometimes they succeed, sometimes they don't.
And they're very polarizing.
There are people out there that love Gremlins 2.
I am not a fan.
Oh, really?
I don't like Gremlins 2.
But I don't have any good reason not like it.
I just for whatever reason don't really like it that much.
But I love a bowl for very different reasons.
I understand why people like it.
But Texas Chainsaw 2 is very much
like a Gremlins 2 kind of thing.
right so um but that screen factory release is a wonderful wonderful package
uh all they rivaled only in my opinion by the exorcist three release that they
did don't have it just fantastic it's got a it's got a whole it's got the
directors cut of the movie on it which is a different film uh and it's great so
um what am I hearing are there motorcycles in the neighborhood it's my neighbors have
their speakers against that wall okay so it's not it's not distracting it's just
I thought it might be this recording and I was worried about no, no, the sons of
Anarchy are in town the Mayans. Joe's scary stuff. What do I have? You know I don't
know if I have anything this week to be honest with you. I've talked a lot about the
video games I've been playing. You know, look, I played my first video game in
15 years today.
Would you play?
Oh, I was gifted a PS4 and it's called something two.
And it's a big, like, almost like thing from Fantastic Four, looking guy who like beats
the shit out of things.
It didn't get small.
What's it called?
I wish I remember the name of it.
It was really fun.
And their graphics were incredible.
I haven't played a game since, like, Paperboy.
It's something two.
And it was really fun.
They gave me the game for free. I wish I knew what it was called. You know what I'll say this for Joe scary stuff
Joe are you about to do the Universal Monsters set you did last week? No, okay
I can't see what I'm holding all right. I was at Barnes and Noble
We like to call it B &N
But I was at Barnes and Noble if you're a Batman the animated series fan, which I am a tremendous fan of this show
So I believe that the entire four seasons are masterful and that Mark Hamill is the greatest
Joker of all time, and a lot of people would agree with that.
But anyway, Barnes and Noble right now, volumes two and four, just two and four, for some
reason, they're like ten bucks each for the entire second and fourth seasons.
So I bought them.
So go get those.
Why wouldn't you?
I'm very Batman -heavy today.
All right, they're nice sets, you know, they're all the episodes, they're not available on Blu -ray, these are DVD sets.
You know, and they got some boy, some bonus features. I almost said boy wonder features. Jesus Christ, it's whiskey starting to hit me a little bit.
The game I played today was called NAC 2.
I don't know NAC. I've never been heard of it. It was really fun. And it sounds like bullshit and like you made it up.
I don't believe you. I have like six games and I have the VR thing and I'm excited to try them on
I you tell me that the Batman VR games supposed to be incredible. I don't have the psvr. I want to get it
It's $400
That's I was gifted this shit
So I've been hesitant to pull the trigger on that because I'm like well, that's a lot of money to spend for a VR thing
I also am fairly sure that
25 seconds into playing the VR I will start vomiting everywhere
But I've heard the Batman game is awesome.
It's Batman VR.
It's like, I get this game for 16 months.
It's the only one.
It's not very long.
These games aren't, the VR games are not long.
Okay.
But I hear the Batman ones want fun.
The one I hear at the most rare reviews about
is Star Trek Bridge Crew.
Now here's how that works.
I'll eventually get this thing
and come to your house and play VR games with you.
Because why not make our lives even sadder?
But bridge crew is the one like bridge crew is the game where now that's where all your Star Trek favorites play bridge, right?
Yes
They have the glasses with a little
Strings on that keep Natasha their head and they play bridge. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Star Trek bridge crew. Yeah is
It's a game where
You everybody has a different post on the bridge of the Enterprise. Okay, and literally
it's like you make decisions based on orders coming down to you from whoever's
playing the captain or you don't and if you don't all work together your
fucking ship's gonna like crash or whatever so it's supposed to be crazy like
because it's literally like you're the second mate it's like your job is be the
second mate you're the engineer or the navigator whatever that's your fucking job
And it's like you get told to do something you have a choice whether or not to do it
And if you don't do it right, you're gonna fuck the game up for everybody else
So it's supposed to be really incredible now. Let me ask you this are you are you and I
Because I signed up and I had to do an hour or fucking passwords and shit
Are you and I ever able to play a game together on the PlayStation Network? Yeah, well we got started doing this
I don't play online much, but I'll do that with you. It sounds fun
I'll tell you what I'd like to get into the only give you one controller like it. Well, really
That's shitty. Yeah, that sucks. It's fucking shit damn thing for free
That aside. Yeah, well, I got hooked up with an incredible PlayStation package because you judged a thing
But they should really give you a second controller like you get the old Nintendo you get two controllers
I used to play with my sister all that you don't know, the NES classic yet to get a second controller you to buy
I find that really shitty. Well, here's the thing. Um, yeah, that's they could put into but um, here's the thing
We can play online. Here's what I'd like to get into playing with you is Marvel Capcom
Infinite, which is the latest edition of the Marvel Capcom franchise. I'll do that. Just came out
It's a fighting game and it's Marvel characters versus Capcom characters as you might have assumed I did
But those games are a hell of a lot of fun. I've got some old one. I've got I've got the earlier
versions of these for my Sega Saturn, X -Men children of the Adam Street Fighter Alpha 2. I'm
gonna be getting Street Fighter versus Marvel soon for my Sega Saturn. And then the Marvel Capcom
started to come out and they're really a hell of a lot of fun. Tell me the best PlayStation 4 game and
and I will order it right now.
Well, the best game of all time that's about to come out
is Star Wars Battlefront 2.
It comes out in November,
and there was a first -person shooter campaign
of Star Wars.
So there's a single -player campaign in that game
where it's gonna be like Call of Duty, except Star Wars.
Okay.
I don't know how much better life can get than that.
I'll get it.
We've all been waiting for this for a long time.
It comes out in November.
I also got some game with some sort of gun
Now I sent you that picture. What is that? I don't know what that was
Okay, it's a light gun game and I
Can't I maybe you put the hat on and the VR. I don't know. I don't have the VR
So I'm a little I'm a little lost with the VR stuff because I just like I said it's it's four five hundred bucks
It's called far point. Yeah, I've heard of the game. I you know, it's
supposedly pretty good
All right. Let's get to our movie. Yeah. Show when I saw this one together.
Blade Runner 2049. Blade Runner 2049. The long -awaited sequel to Blade Runner,
and let's just get right to it, Pat. Everybody wants to know, was it better than the first one?
Did you guys like it more than the first one? You guys weren't fans of the first one.
Would you think of Blade Runner 2049? And I will say, I was thoroughly impressed that a movie
somehow outshitted the first blade runner that I hate. Now see, for me, I really admired
how it perfectly replicated, if you'll pardon the pun, the spirit of blade runner, especially
for that much time between sequels, it really landed that classic blade runner tone
being almost unwatchably dull from start to finish. I was, I was drifting in and out
of sleep. I didn't understand a single minute of it. I was bored beyond belief. They keep
calling, you know, like it's a real trudge. This goddamn thing. Two hours and 48 minutes
or something. You go see Force Awakens they call back to Star Wars the place like does a standing
ovation and this thing it's like here's a photo of Sean Young and I'm like I don't even
remember what she did in that. Who gives a fuck? It was the one positive and it's a big positive.
It's the guy that did prisoners Dennis Villanuev and it is Roger Deacon's the best cinematographer of
long time, who shot, I don't even need to list his resume.
I'll just say he shot Fargo, the best shot movie of my lifetime.
It's a visual masterpiece.
It is a visual masterpiece of art.
Yes.
And if the story backed it up, we would be talking about an all time
classic, but it was boring and to me made no sense.
And I didn't give a fuck.
The plot didn't make sense.
And here's why.
Go on.
I'll start here.
second movie in a row where they go we got to kill these replicants. We got to get rid of these
replicants. And I'll say it again and I know some of the listeners have combated this stance. I'll
say it again. Why? They're not bothering anybody. Opening scene is Ryan Reynolds going to a
replicant's farm, or Gosling, excuse me, going to a replicant's farm, Dave Batista, because he's a
and it's like,
this guy's not bothering anybody.
He literally is a very nice seeming worm farmer
who is living completely off the grid
and not bothering anyone.
And that's how you're gonna start
the dramatic tension of this movie
by assassinating an innocent worm farmer
living away from public view.
So that's the first thing.
This movie gets so convoluted plot wise, you've got, no, there's going to be spoilers here.
You've got, I wouldn't even know how to spoil it because I don't know what happened.
You've got gunsling working for the man, so to speak.
he's a replicant working for the cops and his job is to go out and kill all
the replicants or retire them as they put it. Then comes into the play Josh
or Jared Lido excuse me. Oh boy. As the guy that makes all the replicants so
somehow even though the replicants were a problem they still let the like
Bill Gates of replicants still make the replicants or something. I didn't quite
I don't understand that part either.
But anyway, he's making the Republicans.
So you think naturally these two would be on the same side.
But for some reason, Jared Lito's team
doesn't have Gosling's best interests in mind.
I don't still don't really understand why.
Nope.
At one point they go to question Rob and Wright
who plays Gosling's boss at the LAPD, where Gosling is.
She covers for him and sacrifices her own life
to protect him, which doesn't make sense
because it's like, why are you protecting him
when you've sent him out to kill other replicants?
Beautifully shot scene?
Yeah, when they killed her.
I was like, wow, that was a beautifully shot scene
that I didn't give a fuck about.
Then he goes down into a sewer at one point
and there's other replicants down there
and they're like, we're gonna rise up
and show people we deserve to live.
And you're like, okay, that's a good cause.
And they're like, here's the catch.
You gotta go kill Harrison Ford now.
And he's like, yeah, but he's on our side.
Why do you want me to kill him?
I just do it. Yeah. That never even gets followed through. There is no resolution to the storyline
that gets introduced in the 11th hour of the Replicant Revolution, which is clearly just an open -ended
thing to create another sequel, which is dumb. And it won't happen because I feel like this movie
lost a lot of money. Yeah. Harrison Ford finally comes in, and you're excited, and you're like,
Here he is, the old ass kickin' guy is back
and I love it and everything.
Then you proceed to see a series of scenes
where Harrison Ford is unconscious consistently
and Ryan Gosling is continually having
to save Harrison Ford, which I don't wanna see.
I still believe that Harrison Ford
could beat the living shit out of anybody
you put him against.
I love when you see him staggerin' around the bar,
you can barely walk anymore.
He's put his body through so much shit. I love it. He's an old fucking battle axe
I love this guy and then instead of showing how bad ass he is
He's like unconscious all the time and because he's getting knocked out and he can't help and then it's like
Well, wait, why does he have to kill him? He doesn't have to kill him and then and then he doesn't bother me
I am the goddamn movie doesn't make any sense. I I of course like Star Wars
But I am I always prefer to you know Jones. I'm not a huge Star Wars guy
but to get the force awakens two years ago one year ago whatever it was and
Get that triumphant return of Harrison Ford. That's probably why this whole thing got greenlit
But he comes out in blade runner and you feel nothing
It's not like you're throwing your fist in the air like dickards back baby. Well that's cares
I mean, as I said, the narration of the original Blade Runner is the least interested
I've ever heard any actor be in any movie ever.
Well, and then they released the director's cut and everybody said, well, the reason
you don't like Blade Runner is because of the narration.
I said, okay.
Yeah.
And then you watch the one without the narration.
It's somehow more boring.
Yes.
And it makes less sense.
And that's the other problem I have with this film.
There are so many fucking versions of the original Blade Runner.
It's like, well, which one is law?
Which one is canon?
And which is the one that I'm supposed to follow?
And did this thing?
We did Blade Runner on this show.
It's one of, I think it's one of our best episodes.
Let's go back and listen to it.
The preferred version is the director's cut,
which I went and saw on the theater.
I, I'm not going to, I'm not going to name her but there's a young there is there's there's there's there's this is stupid
I'm gonna I'm gonna I'm gonna abandon this, but I've never given anything more of a chance than Blade Runner. I was gonna reference
the next girlfriend of mine except her. I have never tried again and again with something more than Blade Runner because I'm like
I want to I for some reason I want to like it. I don't know what to say and everybody who likes it feels like they're smart
So you want to be in on that on that game?
I'll tell you this
I had the pleasure many years ago
Before he was named as the guy that was gonna write Star Wars. Yes force awakens and he eventually left the project
But I did meet Michael whatever his name is ardent whatever. Oh, yeah
I got a right to a to a story three. Yeah, to a story three
a masterpiece. I met him at a cartoon.
I met him at a party. New that he wrote to a story three. Yeah,
he had again had not been named yet to to write Star Wars,
force away. He's a little masonry. Yes. Okay. Go on. And we
were talking about sci -fi stuff just coincidentally. I don't know
how we got on to it. But we did. And I remember saying to
him, everything on paper says I should love Blade Runner. But
Can I be honest with you? I hate that fucking movie and he doubled over laughing because even
though he liked it, he understood what I meant. Yeah. And that's how I thought about this
new one. Beautiful visuals, spectacular effects, great acting. Yeah. Not a movie I ever want
to see ever, ever, ever again. Do you follow on Twitter? One perfect shot. I don't know.
You should but they they show you a Twitter anymore. They show you like amazing stills from from movies and they pick great stuff
And they're the kind of stills you want like blown up and put on put on the wall of your house
any shot
Of this blade runner and the original blade runner
Would make for a beautiful painting in your absolutely and yet
folks
And ain't enough. I'm sorry
I don't know what to tell you and I know film is a visual medium and I get it
But it's not but film is not strictly a visual medium. That's right. And that's the thing. That's right
That's the thing. So now I have seen movies where I didn't care about the plot
I didn't understand it whatever where the visuals were enough to carry me a little movie called enter the void that I I don't know if I've ever mentioned on here
Sorry flick
I was obsessed with it for a period of time.
I think it's one of the best looking movies ever made.
And that put me over the edge,
just by the fact that the story is kind of non -existent.
This just, man, and I went in with high hopes
because of Villanue.
But it's nothing.
I went in with high hopes
because of him in Harrison Ford being back.
I'm a sucker for Harrison Ford
and I just didn't enjoy it.
And I love Gosling, and I love Robin Wright.
But I just want to mention about this thing.
Do people have love for the new Blade Runner?
People, you know, I got a text from my friend, Brian.
He said, drop everything you're doing right now
and go see Blade Runner.
And I was like, oh, OK, this is exciting.
And then I went and saw it and didn't feel that way.
No.
In fact, felt the urge to go hit him in the face
for saying that.
So anyway, don't see Blade Runner, folks.
Uh, here's our shout outs as promised to the Patreon folks that donated five dollars
or more.
We can't thank you enough.
Start with our true hero.
Start with our boy.
Derek the Gooch Clark with a huge donation.
We don't need to name numbers because we don't want to do nobody's, it's not a game.
It's not a competition.
Thank you.
The Gooch.
Thank you to everybody equally.
Derek the Gooch Clark, Matthew Little, Tracy Reddington, Sean Thomas, Amanda
Alzamora. Jason, I've seen all these names on the Facebook page. Jason Weebel, Wybel.
We all fall down. Michael Curry, Drew Spindler and Drew Koval, Sam Mitchell, Aaron Melanowski,
Scott Nolan, Jack Gertz, hell yeah dude, Benjamin Tahia, Misty Zavar, Brandon Knock,
Brandon Webb, Dijane Dijane, Wilford, if I'm saying that wrong, I apologize, I think
it's Dijane, Wilford, sounds like you're saying it wrong, problem, Chris Thornton, dial
Lorama super fan Giovanni. That's a good name. Super fan Giovanni. Uh, Michael Gold, Daniel
Durr, Eric Lamora, Michael Madrigal. Oh, is that my, oh, yeah, it is my, that's my buddy, Mike,
Madrigal. Uh, Mr. Suit Records, check out his store in Lancaster, Pennsylvania. If you're
over there, it's a great record store. Uh, he's a friend of mine from college. Good dude. Stephen
Marcenek. What would you do if I was reading these in like, like one of them was like Russell Crowe.
And it was Russell Crowe. Erica Branding, Lawrence Anderson, Jared Smallridge, Zach Schoendorf.
Okay. Will Pottoff, Natalie Craig, Nathan Baskett, Edmund Agabo. I believe that's how you say that.
Anthony, no last name, just Anthony. Kyle Kinsland, Brooke Adams, Monty Buckles, Holy
Shit. That's a great name. That might be the best name I've ever seen in my life.
That is Monty Buckles. Yeah, that sounds like a direct to Netflix, Adam Sandler vehicle.
Monty Buckles. Yes, we're Christopher Guest character. Yeah, yeah.
uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh
One wreath, Dominic, Dominique, Bander,
Heighten Davidson, Brian England, and John Weissen Gruber.
Thank you all.
Those are your shout outs.
You guys are the best.
We appreciate it.
And thank you everybody else that donated to.
We're not excluding you.
We're just not giving you a shout out.
You didn't donate five bucks.
But thank you for the donation still.
We really appreciate it.
Yes, thank you to everybody. I honestly was not expecting this at all. It's a beautiful thing and we very much appreciate it.
We can't tell you how much we appreciate it.
And as I said on the exclusive Patreon only episode, you know, obviously we weren't doing this for the money. We've been doing it for two years without trying to monetize it.
But it hits a point as Joe and my life get busier and busier where you're like, why the fuck are we doing this?
And there's two reasons. One is the positive feedback on both Facebook, Twitter, and Instagram. I don't think you can say both if there's three things, but whatever.
Uh, and the other now, frankly, is like, look, all of our friends with a podcast make a tremendous amount of money on them.
If we can make a little money, you know, it's, it's a job.
You know Joe and I could be talking at a bar right now
But we very much appreciate it. I want to make that very clear. We very much appreciate it and it ensures that the podcast will continue
Thank you
That is it for us this week. Jody have any plugs
Yeah, Pittsburgh this weekend nice by the time you're hearing this I might even be there already
I'm at the Pittsburgh improv. I have shows Friday night two shows Saturday night two shows
Sunday night one show come on out to the show and God damn it if you know some fun ship to do come tell me where it is and
How to do it? Do you see your pants? No, that is Philly
They're in South Jersey pretty. I thought there were as burgers a good five hours probably from Philadelphia
I think a pants weren't filled off. Well, that's where we're from there. They live in South Jersey
Okay, but still Philly is is a hike from Pittsburgh. No, I know
Do you know Pat? I do I live do you know city and I've been to Philadelphia many times
Uh, but yeah, so if you're in Pittsburgh come out to the shows, it's gonna be a lot of fun
I'll be doing what's roughly this new hour of material and
Let me know what is good in your town. I
Am on a comedy on Instagram. Come follow me. Sorry. Thank you. I am on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh and
my
Television program living Biblically also starring Joe Derosa
We'll be hitting the airwaves.
I don't know, but I know that we have started shooting promos.
So I think you will start hearing about it very soon.
And in this crowded television landscape, folks, anything you can do to get the word out
as much appreciated because I think we got a real special show and I'm excited for you
to see it.
Don't see Blade Runner.
That's our time.
and folks we'll see you next week where I believe we'll be reviewing Cult of Chucky and we'll
also see you in hell.