Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal, durable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning, or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Monthly 21 -plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberer, offer not available in all states
terms apply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
Hello, everybody and welcome to another scintillating episode of We'll See You In Hell.
My name is Patrick Walsh with me as always is Joe DeRosa.
We have decided this week to return to the way this podcast began, the commentary format
beloved by many of you, probably hated by some of you, but we're doing it anyway.
Yeah, this week's movie is Ernest scared stupid.
I was going to go ahead and explain why we chose it, but you know, I mean, it's one
of the classics of American horror.
The Ernest franchise stars the great Jim Varney as Ernest P. Whorell and scared stupid,
I would say is generally considered among the top Ernest films.
If we're counting, you know, Ernest goes to Africa, all the ones that came later, Ernest
goes to school, scared stupid, quality wise is near the top.
I haven't seen it since I was a young man.
I know it used to terrify my little sister, the trolls are pretty, pretty graphic from
what I recall, surprisingly.
And we just want to start this thing off.
We got 93 minutes ahead of us.
So, Joe, are you ready?
Yeah, we're watching on HBO, so you can watch this if you have HBO go or if you have
HBO Joe or if you have the HBO add -on for your Hulu, which is what I have. By the way, four bucks a month for limited time. Get on that. That's nice.
Or, you know, HBO on pride, you know, some HBO streaming bullshit. So, here we go on the count of three then play. One, two, three, play.
Hey, we're seeing the HBO, the, uh,
Dan, uh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
screen.
There's the rating screen.
Now, when you, when you see that HBO,
uh, what show do you think of?
I go to sopranos, of course.
Uh, curb your enthusiasm as well as first, sure.
And then Dennis Miller alive, really?
Yeah.
Okay, which the HBO app has put two seasons of up and I was very excited because I used to really like that show
Yeah, but they put up the last two seasons when he's like
It's not as fun because he's like way more right wing right
Wing and I like when he hits it up the middle a little more
Well, they are I mean now I see his tweets retweeted into my timeline all the time because he has become a
A complete parody of himself but it's actually pretty funny like if I mean that you nobody can do it like him
The references are so obscure and so stupid and he's you know basically talking about how
How bad Barack Obama is so it's this weird
dichotomy of a very intelligent person
Saying very stupid things he uh, he's always funny. I mean even when he even when he's being
ultra -right and I don't agree it's he still makes me laugh like there's
something about the diverting in the demeanor in the delivery that makes me
laugh I think it's nostalgia I mean these tweets are just straight up bombs but I
do enjoy reading them I gotta say I am loving this credit sequence I really am I
mean it's there got the old movie clips can you make this full screen and can we
not look at that jumping icon which you know triggers my OCD in a big way
I don't know how to stop that jumping icon it's an it's a printer software update and to my knowledge
You don't have a printer. I have a printer. I don't have that printer anymore, and I can't I've tried time and time
You're gonna get this software off the goddamn thing and I can't get it off
You can't drag that icon of the trash and be done with it watch this
Ready yeah
what? What's it right back? I mean, that's sick. It won't let you do it. But at least
full screen. Here's why we can't do a full screen because you don't know if it fucks
up the all. Yeah. I got a, I got a lot of eyes and a lot of places right now. All right.
Mainly on that, the back of those tight, jeans you're wearing, Pat. Thank you. It is
Just look in juicy today, folks.
Well I did my personal training this morning and legs evidently.
Well as I'm doing this, I mean I, you know, priorville, Missouri, not far from my hometown.
Well this is where the film starts with a, with a storyline in the, what do you say this
is the 1700s or something like that?
Yeah.
Well, we all apparently a big influence on the witch was Ernest Scott's too, but it does and
Arch strangely like the witch in school. I mean we would always hear about this incident and
You know, it was kind of Missouri legend
Ernest Troll incident. Yeah, this is the actual documentary footage that kicks off the film
They had video cameras since the 17 they did they did Missouri way ahead of the curve
Missouri is always ahead of the curve, especially when it comes to technology.
But anyway, I was working out this morning about a month from the wedding, and I feel
much stronger.
You know, I feel like you do abs, legs, arms, etc.
And today, I'm carrying this giant like 50 pound kettlebell and doing these squats.
You just feel your leg like being ripped to shreds.
And I was like, I don't know that I need my legs to get any more jacked.
Right. I I've always had strong legs. Look, let's work on this upper body a little bit. Let
me get to a place where I can be one of those guys who's walking down the school hallway
and he does a push up on a door frame. You know what I mean? Sure. Pull up. Sure. And Heather,
your lovely fiancee soon to be wife. Yeah. She's told me about the beauty of the strength of your
way. They're strong. She has said to me at time, she says, Joe, when I get him, and
this is some details about your love making, but you'll say, Joe, when I get him up on
the sink and he wraps those legs around, yeah, there's no safer place. Um, I feel like
that's probably true. You mean when she's sort of strapping me on as we call it? I didn't
quite understand how the sex would work that way, but apparently you were seated on the sink
and she was standing. I'll say this, we've never made love and not involved the sink.
And at first, that was a practical issue for cleanup. I am what is known as a squirter.
But it just became sort of a requirement. The apparatus is erotic.
It got to a point Pat couldn't get aroused anymore unless he saw a sink.
Right. There was a lot of therapy involved.
Well, something we'll like to do because the danger element sort of gets me hard is I'll actually have sex with the sink and then Heather
will fire up the
Dispenser the disposal disposal, right?
And you know, she's got me before she's she's caught my dick with the the blades
Okay, and that sense of adventure is is what keeps us happy five and a half years into the
What does that do to your dick?
It's not great, but it heals like anything else.
You know, you put some back teeth on it.
Have you seen the...
I hear something weird real quick, though.
Yeah, before you asked me this.
I started working on a new horror short story yesterday.
Okay.
And it begins with a man in therapy,
telling his therapist how he stared at his running garbage
disposal for an hour straight the day before
and how he wants to put his hand into it.
That's the beginning of the story.
It's very strange.
Yeah, right.
Anyway, go ahead.
By the way, much better.
You had mentioned this before we started recording.
To both of us, much better energy this week.
Yeah, I mean, we've had ones where I'll walk away
and be like, well, we didn't bring our A -game
and then they become like people's favorite episodes.
So you never know, but this week I felt like we both
Both were real down and tense, and you know, as positive a thing as it is to remove alcohol
from your life, you know, it's hard to get into that performative, fun, funny mood
without sometimes, especially because it's become a habit, a bad habit.
And I would say the other night, it was tense and a lot of people agreed.
I can tell you why I was in a bad mood the other night and why I'm in a good mood today
and they're directly correlated.
All right.
I went to a video game flea market swap meet thing the other day before we recorded I bought a Sega game gear
Which is an old Sega handheld
For $50 which was a good price and these things are known to have capacitor issues meaning the capacitors go bad
The screen and sound doesn't work as I'm paying the guy for it for this thing that I clearly cannot test out we're out in the wild
were literally outside. He says, the capacitors have all been replaced, the things in great shape,
so you're not going to be proud because they say, great. Yeah, you talked about that maybe just
to me prior to the show. Just you prior. Yeah. Bring it home, capacitors are completely shot.
Right. Furious. I call the store that's hosting the flea market, not the guy that sold it to me,
but he owned the facility where it happened. Right. The guy that runs, that owns this place,
by the way, let me give him a plug.
Game Realms in Burbank, just a phenomenal video game store
if you're into retro gaming or even present day gaming.
I call the guy, go, look man, I know it's not your fault,
but the vendor at the thing that you hosted
sold me this thing, it doesn't work.
Maybe it was a mistake.
I don't know.
What can I do though?
Can you put me in touch with the guy?
Again, hats off to the game realm guy.
He goes, I want my customers to be happy.
You bring that thing in here, I'm gonna give you
the 50 bucks back. Out of my pocket. Wow. I go in this morning. He does just that. I say, buddy,
now I'm going to put this 50 back in your pocket. I'm spending it in your store. Sure. It's
just a love fest all around. People just helping each other out. I walk in. Guys got a Sega Dreamcast
for 50 bucks. I wanted to say a Dreamcast forever. It was a no -brainer. I not only got rid of the
thing that didn't work, I upgraded to something I wanted more, didn't spend a dime, I love
it. It was a great morning. I love it, Joe. I love you. But oh, and I you, but it's strange
that that would make you so upset as what transpired here on Sunday night. Because as I commented
on the Facebook page, because people were really dissecting it, where it all went wrong.
So someone speculated that because John Krasinski works in comedy, you were jealous of his success and I was like, I don't think that's it.
But, you know, I commented that you were essentially talking about how much you enjoyed the movie with a seething hate.
That's generally reserved for movies you would not like.
And that's what kept throwing me as I was like, why do you seem so angry when it seems like we both really enjoyed the picture?
But did I felt that you were also not in a great mood either was that well
I was I would be like sitting there looking at you and you would be like you're you're high
You're angry at me you're giving me all this hostile energy and I think that comes from no longer being
A little buzzed. I think that it takes a while to wean off it and you take just
That's someone sitting and looking at you as an attack and I feel it myself, I understand.
I will admit this because part of change is you got to admit your faults.
I will admit that for some reason I was getting aggravated a bit with your energy because
I felt like you didn't want to be here and I'm not putting that on you.
I'm not saying that gave me an excuse to be aggravated but I was saying I was being passively
aggressive because I was feeling like you didn't want to be a part of it or something.
And I was starting to get more and more angry.
I didn't want to be here and by here I mean alive, right.
And I didn't want to be a part of it and by it I mean society.
That's where I'm at.
And sometimes, especially without the aid of some sort of substance, it is hard to get into
an up mindset.
That's a shame.
I mean, that's what we're working on.
Well, and that's what I felt too, on my end.
It's, but I did read rough.
I did read some of the comments,
and it did seem that the general consensus was
that I was more the aggressor.
Yeah, well, that came out much more on Facebook.
Instagram was pretty respect.
But they get into it, it's fun to read.
I always enjoy reading it.
Now, if I read it, will I get depressed,
or is it just like, man, Joe, was in a mood?
good. Now sometimes the criticisms of both of us get a little harsh. I don't take them
personally anymore because I'm like, here are people discussing us talking on a couch
for an hour. It's kind of cool. Alright. Let's at least briefly touch on earnest. So what
is your history with the earnest franchise? I remember once on this podcast you said you
saw earnest goes camping the theater and you despised it. And then randomly last night,
Joe's like, hey, I'm watching Ernest Scared Stupid by choice.
Let's do it for the podcast.
I'm like, okay.
Well, I watched when I was a child and I was a huge Ernest fan because of the morning
show and the commercials.
Yeah.
Really the commercials are like Wendy's or something?
I looked it up.
He did like Taco John's Coke, he had a few big campaigns.
So I, you know, I couldn't wait to see Ernest goes to camp.
My parents took me to the drive -in theater to see it and I remember not liking it
Fascinating that you could love the earnest character, but not earnest goes to camp
It didn't it's this and I remember having the same feeling when I saw the strangers with candy movie
Okay, I love the show. It's got some laughs that movie. Yeah, not saying it's without humor
Yeah
But there was something that felt darker about it to me and like not fun like it just made me sad kind of
Sure, a lot of the parts had been recasted.
Sure.
So I guess it was that sort of a thing,
but you know, I never liked the principal on that show.
I hate to single out the black guy,
but I never liked the principal
and I never liked the art teacher.
I loved Colbert and I loved, you know, Jerry Blank.
There, you just named my two favorite characters.
The principal and the art teacher were, I loved so much.
Maybe a rewatch would help me out,
but I used to always just be like,
I guess I just wanted to get back to scenarios, frankly, but I loved the Princeton a little because I am a fan any time that they write a character
And I'm you know sort of mundane environment like our high school. Yeah as if he was like a super villain
I thought it was funny that everything he said sounded very like Darth Vader -esque. I should give the whole series
I bought the whole series and I haven't rewatched it since I was 18 or something and the art teacher just watching him slowly
Like his sanity slowly crackle away throughout the series made me laugh, right a lot
But but anyway, so I saw Ernest goes to camp. I didn't like it. Then I rented Ernest goes to jail and I loved it now had you
seeing Ernest say it's Christmas the one that proceeded. No, I I went off I went off Ernest for for a long cold turkey for a long time
and then for some reason I rented Ernest goes to jail and I loved him playing the dual role in the mean
The evil criminal and the dumb earnest and right. I really liked it. Well him with a pen is a fantastic scene of ghost of jail
When he's chewing on the pen and it gets ankle over himself. Yeah, yes, but I don't know if that would hold up either
I remember he controls lightning in that movie at one point. He's a electoral magnet
You know conductor. I don't think any of these movies hold up
I mean he was the Larry the cable guy of our day. Yeah, I guess that's true and nothing against Larry
But I just mean like I don't think anybody's gonna watch those movies 20 years from now and go you know
They're classics right well now when I was a kid. I watched all these a lot and I never felt like they were kids movies
but camp
Christmas this one
There's lots of kids in them. I mean, I I assume they were designed for children
Yeah, and Hicks
Yeah, it's it's very Larry the cable guy. It's a clean
humor that's meant for like
like, kids and like, yeah, like, like, picky people, I guess, I don't know.
But like, right there.
No offense any of the hicks.
No, I liked it myself.
But right there where he was playing all the different characters, what was that?
Like his inner brain?
Who were they?
Well, if you're watching along with us, we just, we just, or if you're not, we just watched,
we just crossed the sequence where Ernest plays like six characters.
Yeah.
Always liked him as the woman.
in one scene. Honestly, Pat, I didn't understand the other night. I thought it was him with
these kids, like he's devising a plan. And I thought it was him with these kids running
from outfit to outfit. Right. And then at the end of the scene, he's just earnest. And
it's seemingly that he wasn't in any of those outfits. A bird just shit in his eye.
Could they have made that bird should look anymore like come and why?
Well, bird shit looks as white usually, I guess.
But at the end of the scene, whatever the kid says indicates that Ernest was not changing
costumes, that he just, that maybe all this was happening in his head or something, and
Ernest is insane.
Well, at the end, he does it again, like in the climax scene and the kid goes, great, just
This is what we needed a multiple personality.
So yeah, the insinuation, the harness is deeply troubled.
Yes, that he's like crazy.
And the plot of this film is that a troll has cursed Ernest's bloodline and that the
ancestors of this guy from the 1700s will get stupider and stupider.
And now the idea here is Ernest is the end of the line of stupidity.
So maybe a little insane got in there too, I don't know.
Well, I'll say that I barely remember Hocus Pocus,
but I remembered feeling like Hocus Pocus
was almost identical to Ernest Scared Stupid.
And it came out years later, our couple years later.
I never saw it.
Everyone now loves Hocus Pocus.
People have a lot of nostalgia for it.
I know my sister loved it.
I never thought it was that great,
but maybe it's better than Ernest Scared Stupid.
I don't know.
I used to confuse it with the witches and then I realized they weren't the same movie and I really love the witches
Witches is a great picture. Yes. I've never seen Hocus Pocus. I tried watching the beginning of it
I tried watching it recently at maybe last Halloween, but I'm just too old like it's yeah
I think something like that is is very much a product of the age you saw it that
Now did you see Ernest scared straight because that is a very different film
They're prism -themed.
Well, yeah, he gets caught shoplifting and he gets sent to the straight, it's a lot
of people telling them they'll rape his sweet ass.
I did not see that one, though.
A lot of guys telling him you'd be a real cherry in here.
Now, disturbing.
It's not funny at all.
Ernest goes to jail, seems a more adult picture.
Were there prison rape jokes?
You'd almost assume there would have to be.
Drop the soap.
I can't remember.
In a prison movie that didn't have rape jokes, I can't remember I wouldn't be surprised
I do remember one of the gags in it is like he gets a bar of soap and widows it into like a machine gun
Yeah, yeah, that happens that that's that's that right? That's not naked gun 33 and a third right?
I don't think so
My favorite joke and naked gun 33 and a third and I'm contradicting what I said was my favorite joke the last time we talked about it
but my favorite joke is probably when Leslie Nielsen first gets put in the cell and he takes
that tin cup and rakes the bars and says, kill whity.
Attica.
Yeah.
Mine is, yeah, it's like a midget at a urinal.
I was going to have to stay on my toes.
Gritjo.
Um, yeah, I remember renting this a lot.
my sister hated it because of the trolls who we have still not seen. In doing a little research,
believe it or not, for the podcast, I learned that the trolls are designed by the same people who
made the killer clowns, for matter of space. It makes perfect sense that the trolls are mildly
disturbing. Yeah. And I read into Jim Varney himself. I mean, I guess when you're a kid,
anyone over 30 is 100, but Jim Varney died at age 50 and I thought he was quite a bit older than that.
Yeah, heavy, heavy lung cancer lung cancer and apparently, you know, he basically had like
Blood on a handkerchief type situation. Yeah, and thought that
severe cough
Coughed up blood on the handkerchief and then thought well, I should maybe get this checked out. Yeah, still not thinking
I don't think that it was lung cancer, right
But apparently he was like a chain smoker
Jayne Smoker and he had done non -smoking PSAs and everyone thought he did them post lung cancer, but he did them pre lung cancer
I see we read the same Wikipedia page. Well, there's only one. Yes
Do you remember Varney and Beverly Hillbillies?
I see that because that that was a strange one. That was a movie where I was like
Does anyone have any nostalgia for this and they didn't do well, but that movie came out at a time and I didn't watch it
Yeah, uh, it was, I remember very clearly,
Nick at night had just become a thing.
Uh -huh.
The old sitcoms would play on Nick at night
and there was this nostalgia craze
for the 50s and 60s and the sitcoms,
and the sitcoms they produced.
And they started making all these new versions of things.
So they did the Beverly Hill Village movie.
They did the Car 54, where are you movie?
Massive bomb.
They did my favorite Martian with Christopher Lloyd.
Yes, they did the movie of that.
None of these move they'll leave it to be over with Chris McDonald none of these made it made a dime
It's also around the time the monsters today came out. Yeah, well the atoms probably the atoms family kicked off the trend because that was a huge hit
And a great movie as a pretty much movies were good too pretty much movies had some they had that extra layer to them where it was like
Both a celebration and a parody of them, which was very small. Yes
But the Beverly Hillbilly's I mean just even from the trailer. I was like this is this is this should have been direct to video
This is horse shit. It was rough stuff and I remember being excited because
Again showing off what a nerdy kid. I was I was like ooh Penelope Sphiris directed it. She did Wayne's world
So this will be great, you know, but you know, it wasn't didn't Dietrich Bader play
Jethro
He did
Dietrich Bader of NBC's outsourced
in the Drew Carey program, in the Drew Carey program.
Super nice guy, Dietrich Bader, and very funny,
and weirdly now at age whatever, 55,
you see him all the time and critically acclaimed stuff.
He made like a switcheroo at some point.
He's in VP and he's in that Pamela Adlon show,
better call mom, or whatever.
And he was bigger than his line, is it anyway?
The American version.
Yeah, I never got into that.
Neither did I, but I mean, he said a good career.
When I wrote on Jeff and Somalians, the cartoon,
we had to do a table read, Brett Gelman,
who played the main character, couldn't be there,
and Dietrich Bader came in and did the read.
Really, which was so crazy to me,
and I sat next to him and I was like,
this is a hell of a favor this guy is doing
for somebody right now.
Yeah, that's very strange.
Yeah, but he was really nice.
Couldn't have been a nicer man.
um before we forget Pat and I hate to remind you we're to tell you how to do your job that we
should get on with the show and also on with a Joe oh come on I dare you you don't you don't
That's how I knew you would the XX very popular indie band I heard the song on the way over here. All right, it's called I dare you
It's a very pretty song. It's the actual I'm trying to get us a little more indie, you know, we do too many big 80s hits
The XX are a great band. They're one of those bands where you don't know if their brother and sister or their fucking or what's going on
Like the white stripes used to be they don't know to this day. Yeah, and
and they're British and they make really cool music.
They've had three albums that sound kind of identical,
but I like them.
And that song completely rips off the kings of Leon's song,
use somebody where the chorus is,
oh, it's the exact same melody.
Okay.
And that was a massive hit.
And the songs came out two years apart.
Nobody said it worked.
Meanwhile we got Radiohead, Sue and Lana Del Rey.
Sounds like their X is on fire.
Oh boy, oh boy.
I tried, that laundry thing is so similar to creep that I still haven't heard of.
I was like, she didn't steal this.
This is like comically similar, like she clearly just fucked up.
But who knows?
I mean, she got busted with the not being able to sing shit and everything.
So I don't know how deep that river runs, doesn't she go out with axle rows?
If they're still together, yes, they were together when I saw guns and roses and he was like, I'd like to send this mix song out to my girl
They cut to this gorgeous woman looking adoringly up 20 years younger at Axel Rose that money and that fame do not
Let you down. No. I mean, but but but she has money in fame
That's what kind of throws you, but Axel's Axel's the kind of guy where I'd imagine he's got
about $250 million.
I would think he has more than that.
Yeah, I mean, he was making huge number one hits
at a time when that actually paid some money.
Should we head on down to Pat's movie corner?
Sure, I guess I forget about the old classics
when we're doing these commentary ones.
Yeah, well, my phone was wiped out.
I lost everything that I've seen,
but I can remember stuff. I've been watching some older films, most notably, I watched, well, not notably at all. I watched Outrageous Fortune.
So, it was starting one night, I couldn't sleep, and it was starting up, and I was like, this movie was a huge hit.
But it launched Disney's R -rated adult division, touchdown pictures.
Who's it again?
These are all blend together.
Was it Goldie Hahn?
It was Ben Middler and Shelley Long.
That's right.
And briefly, Chris from McDonald.
And I just remember when I was a kid, I would really go up and down the comedy section in
particular at the video store, scouring it for things that weren't rated R. And I was
I was always thrown by that movie being rated R because I saw every comedy that wasn't
until I learned how to sneak them out.
And it's not like I was dying to see it, but it developed this kind of strange fascination
to me because I was like, what could be so bad about outrageous fortune?
And I watched it.
It was a bad movie.
It's one of those 80s movies where they have like long comedic chases where the saxophones
are playing.
And like, yeah, yeah, there's nothing funny about the chase.
There's nothing suspenseful about the chase.
And every 80s movie has 20 minutes of chase
with bad horns in the background.
Then at the end they pulled out a mission impossible to
in a relatively grounded movie.
A guy pulled off his face as a mask.
Scooby -Doo style.
It was the actor Robert Prosky who you'd know if you saw him.
Okay, and so Robert Prosky's in the first spoiler alert by the way
He's in the first half of the movie as this pretentious acting coach with a bad to pay
so then at the end of the movie when you're learning that everybody's double crossing everybody
Prosky turns around on the front seat and it's very clearly
Beloved character actor Robert Prosky of course, and you're like okay, so he's got the to pay off now now
I get it sure then he completely pulls his face off to reveal
he'll basically the same Robert Prosky face,
but now he's got the two pay on.
And he's like, it was me, in case you couldn't put it together.
It's one of the craziest things I've ever seen
in a mainstream film.
Jesus.
I don't recommend the movie at all.
It was very bad.
Shelley Long is doing a different accent in every scene.
She's playing an aspiring actress.
Why was it rated R?
Well, it was Disney's first break into adult stuff.
They had stake out, you remember Touchstone?
Yeah, yeah.
So, they dipped their toe in with like adventures
and babies sitting three men and a baby,
like more adult movies,
but then they also started doing R -rated movies.
They did ruthless people, which is a hilarious movie.
The armor we have.
The suckers did with Batmiddler, Danny DeVito,
Judge Reinhold, very funny movie.
Yes.
And this was continuing in that vein.
It was rated R for a lot of fucks from Beth Middler
You see Shelley Long give head to a guy. Ooh
They play rousing no no they play two women who find out their date in the same man basically and they learn that he's
In the CIA or he's a crook and the CIA's involved and blah blah, but he's got
An outrage is fortune. He has now. I don't know. I have no idea why it was called outrageous fortune
And then at one point, Bet Middler goes, oh boy, they're heading into like a bad neighborhood,
there's a lot of suddenly racist humor as well. And she goes, oh boy, I guess we're gonna get
murdered and raped in here. Joe kind of like thuds. And then she goes in and there's like a 10 -year -old
boy who jumps out at them with a gun. And she's like, oh, well, at least we can cross right off the
list. I was like, holy cow. That was Batmidler's thing in the 80s and 90s. She was like the sassy,
you know? Yeah. Well, she was playing a porn star in the movie, which I found very odd
to imagine that she would be a porn star, but it's an interesting movie. And there were some real
Questionable racist jokes. Here's one. Now I will say this is both racist and also the only joke in the movie that I thought was like
Good, okay, which you know like at least I recognize that it was a well -written joke while being shocked by the racism
So they're driving through this neighborhood
This is the most anyone's ever talked about outrageous fortune by the one
They're driving through a neighborhood and she's like oh boy
Well, yeah, what are we supposed to do?
I think we're the only two white people in this neighborhood.
So it's really long since.
And Beth Middler goes, no, there's one right there.
Oh, they got him.
And it was so bizarrely well -written
while also so, so racist.
That I was kind of blown away by it.
Woo.
But any hoot.
All right, that's, I don't know why I even watched it, but, but here we are.
You watched it.
What are you gonna do?
It's one where a lot of my friends have seen it a hundred times because it was in the
early days of HBO where they play the same comedy over and over.
Sure.
So even if something wasn't good, it would kind of live on in your imagination.
I've heard friends discuss it, I'd never seen it.
Just a brief update in the movie, Ernest is running up and down with a bullhorn yelling to people
that there are trolls descending on the town.
Right, nobody's listening.
There was a woman drinking out of a brown paper bag.
That was a weird, that was a weird,
just like, you know, like throw away joke.
So that's where we're at in the movie.
Anyway, I watched my finally Blu -ray
of Conan the Barbarian.
I didn't talk about this last week, did I?
You didn't, I've never seen Conan
And I've heard that it has the best commentary in DVD history. I look forward to watching the commentary and watch the commentary
Yet I did watch the documentary that came along with the movies a lot of fun. Yeah, it's Conan and on blu -ray. It looks great
The effects look really cool
It's a fun movie. I enjoyed it quite a bit
But the best part was the documentary they did where they went back and interviewed everybody
you know, as they do on these special features and John,
whatever his name is, the guy that wrote a apocalypse
now that directs you.
John Millius.
Yeah, great documentary about him called Millius.
He tells a story about Robert E. Howard,
I believe is the guy's name that created Conan.
And he said, you know, this guy was like a real eccentric
and he would like board up his windows
and he had like rifles in his house
because he was convinced the town was gonna like try to kill him.
Okay.
And they said he wrote Conan
because
He was sitting at his desk one night and Conan appeared to him
With a giant axe and said like right about me or I'll split your body in half
Wow, and he would write all night and then in the morning you would finally get the guts to turn around and Conan would be gone
And then he would have to like sleep in the day and get his energy back because Conan would return
and so I'd force him to write his like tales.
I wonder with this shit, how often people aren't
just like, they'd get tired of saying,
I don't know, I thought about, I thought of Conan
and then I wrote the script.
Like sometimes I'm like, I don't buy that.
Well, he wrote these stories in I guess the 30s,
okay, or something, or 40s.
So, I mean, it's a really incredible story.
It's probably a more, the Robert E. Howard story
is probably more interesting than the actual Conan story,
but the Conan stories are great.
These jokes are funny that I'm saying, by the way. He's selling no -troll strips.
I mean, I always liked these two characters. They're in all the movies as well.
Yeah, the guy on the right that looks like he has no teeth. Yeah, but he does.
He looks like Steely Dan. Who's he? Steely Dan, Donald Fagan. What else is he in?
I think he's in all these movies, and that's because when I saw him immediately
recognized them, I think it can only be from these. I think they were all a part of Ernest
World and the early TV specials and stuff and they came along.
The plot of this film, by the way, because we haven't really touched on it, is this troll
has now resurrected, and it's trying to raise its troll brethren from the earth, and the
only way it can do that is to get five children and turn them into wood figurines, which
which it's exceeded already with one.
It's pretty dark for an earnest movie, you know,
that this troll is turning children
into tiny wooden figures.
And then Eartha Kit is a witch.
Right.
Eartha Kit gives it 110.
You know, it really does, man.
Here comes Uranus now ready for battle with the trolls.
I saw a tweet online the other day
that shook me to my core.
It was like, how did Anthony Hopkins pull off
best actor for Sounds of the Lambs.
He's clearly doing an Earth of Kit impression.
And of course, that never would have occurred to me,
but then you think about it, and you're like,
that's very funny.
Kind of.
I saw Isle of Dogs.
Well, boy.
And as you'll recall, I kind of went off
on people being upset about this being cultural appropriation,
what have you.
Um, I will say every Japanese character in the film, although they are played by Japanese
people, talks on that kind of like, oh, right.
And it's a little unsettling knowing that it was written and directed by the widest man
alive, Wes Anderson.
Um, but by and large, I thought the movie was pretty harmless.
It was, I really thought the fantastic Mr. Fox was fantastic, frankly.
I thought it was funny, I really enjoyed it.
This movie looks every bit as great.
Every single shot of it could be framed
and mounted over a fireplace.
Didn't give a fuck about any, I mean,
the story is complete nonsense.
The, he's always been like the driest possible sense
of humor, but like, I think a big part
of it was Owen Wilson co -wrote Royal Tena Bombs
and rush more and bottle rock it and that and that the jokes really hit in those movies.
And here they're just like barely even attempts and the cast is Bill Murray and Brian Cranston
and all this and there wasn't a laugh to be had.
I wish I could recommend it because of the amount of care that went into making it.
I like stop motion.
I think it's a great and underused format.
But the movie is is nothing.
Frank.
All right.
I had no interest.
Yeah. And I do love dogs. Yeah. No interest. I watched HBO's Andre, the giant documentary,
one of the best goddamn documentaries I've seen in my life. I saw it myself. Wonderful.
Wonderful. I saw it myself and I think just because I was never much into wrestling,
although the era I was into it was the Hulk, honor the giant era. I wanted to know more. I felt
It wasn't quite in depth enough and that might be coming on the heels of the fantastic four -hour Gary Schanling documentary
I had just watched a couple days prior
But it left me a little cold
I
Was a huge wrestling fan as a kid. Yeah, I still enjoy it. I was a huge huge Andre the giant fan
I never knew about the darker stuff in that documentary. So learning that was really
interesting to me and heartbreaking, right, let's just pause for this bit here in the movie.
This was the trailer, by the way. Ernest just slammed his hand in a dumpster and you can tell
how unpainful it is. It barely is resting on his hand, but I remember that being the trailer
for the movie. Slams his hand in a dumpster and does the gag of, and I like the gag, he has to look
at it three times to make sure that he's done what he thinks he's done yeah and
then he starts screaming right right anyway I I love the documentary I was
howling with laughter at times sure I was he's gotion of his thoughts was very
funny yeah discussion of his drinking was very funny tearing up at other times
you know I really liked watching the Rob Reiner Billy Crystal carry L .A. commentary
about what it was like to work with him on Princess bride and I just
I just thought it was a wonderful piece of work,
and I thought it really humanized wrestling.
You know, especially when you get a documentary
where Vince McMahon is crying at the end of it.
It's like, it's not something you see every day.
No.
Yeah, Vince McMahon just comes across as the usual piece of shit
that he always has.
I mean, this is a guy that in an interview on real sports
when the reporter challenged him about the steroid use
in wrestling and goes, don't you feel bad?
Right, don't you feel guilty Vince Vince baby and it's my favorite thing. I've ever seen an interview
He starts going
Like making this rock crying noise and then slaps the guy's papers. Yeah
What's that that's not in beyond the mat. What's that in? It's just like a thing from real sports
Oh, I have I've seen one of the it's the funniest thing I've ever seen in an interview in my life
I've watched over and over so to see that guy crying at the end about
the falling out he had with Andre and like the loss of this guy and what he
meant to him and every it's it's a it's a really great piece of work I really
loved it. Well then I will I will end the movie corner. I want more. Oh well
in my movie corner by talking about three HBO documentaries so I as I just said
the owner of the giant was pleasant but I think because I had watched two four
hour documentaries in the same week I was missing that level of depth with the
the genre of the documentary.
That thing was cool, like, 85 minutes.
It was, yeah, very short.
Now, Judd Apatow made this Gary Shanling documentary
four hour.
You're probably not aware of it, because Apatow
doesn't mention it on Twitter.
But he did do it.
And it's a beautiful piece of work.
It's fantastic.
I'm a big Shanling fan.
And in addition to just being a good documentary about the man
in his practice and his creativity and his art, it is a really exceptional look at the
toll that being somebody in comedy, that being a creative person takes on your brain,
your self -esteem, what a failure can do to you, they go into that movie, what planet are
you from, and how it...
I like that movie.
I thought it was entertaining as well, but this was definitely a warts and all kind of
look at a guy who just could not get happy, but it lived his life in an endless pursuit
of being happy. I related to it immensely. I thought it was a fantastic documentary.
I haven't seen it, but I will one day. Yeah, it's great. And remind me to tell you a story
that I need to tell you after this podcast. Oh, I forgot the record. OTR. Oh, I love that.
And one more documentary, if I may, I also watched the four -hour Elvis documentary, which,
I don't even remember the name of, it's called, I don't know, Promise Land or something like that.
But I have been a huge Elvis fan since I was a very little kid.
I still put his records on. I love the man.
Yeah.
And it's this weird thing where I've read two giant,
or a two -part biography about the man.
So I knew maybe too much,
but the early stuff where it's like,
he was doing things with black music.
That's like, I've heard this 45 billion times, right?
So there's an hour of it where I was like,
if you know nothing about Elvis,
I guess would hold your interest.
But it's like, yeah, we know what he did.
He brought an elements of gospel
and black music and blah, blah.
They talked to Tom Petty and Bruce Springsteen
and various people and it's all very cool.
Well, when they really get into Jess, and I had heard a little bit about this, but Colonel
Tom Parker, who was his manager and just a complete charlatan, just kept this man who
was without question one of the most talented performers in American history, kept him completely
under chains, would not let him tour the globe because he was worried he would like Japan and
not come back or something.
Elvis really wanted to act in things
and we'd get offered like big parts
in big Oscar caliber movies.
And the Colonel would say,
no, you're gonna make this piece of shit.
He was doing three movies a year
with zero quality control.
Jesus.
I didn't know that.
And they're talking to Priscilla Presley
and Tom Petty and all these people.
And they're just like,
they he completely ruined this amazing man's career.
And like he it was all about the merchandise
He would book him for all these shows and then be like selling Elvis pins to the audience like a like a popcorn vendor during the show and
Just wouldn't let Elvis be Elvis then the one time he did the Elvis live in Memphis
Which is unquestionably his best album. It's got your suspicious minds and all that stuff from those sessions
Uh -huh
It's like this major triumphant comeback and he finally got away from the colonel's producers and
And it also was his biggest seller, and he finally did something without this guy.
And then what did he do for the album next?
Went right back to Colonel Tom Park.
Now is there the illusion that Parker got him on the drugs and all that stuff?
It's not mentioned according to Priscilla, he never did anything not prescribed, which I kind
of believe.
The Elvis seems like a pretty kind of moral man who just was he was too much of a people pleaser is what it seems like right and
You know, he got into this thing where he had a terrible fear of not being able to sleep
Which if you've ever had insomnia, you do kind of talk yourself into
This weird like paranoia where you're like maybe I'll never sleep again as you as you get crazy and crazier
Right periods of insomnia
And he was so scared of that he started taking sleeping pills and then he
got addicted, he'd be groggy and he started taking the uppers so he could perform, right?
And that's when you get into this period where, as Tom Petty says, you know, let's be
honest, Elvis put on weight and that is a number one punishable by death crime and show
business.
You cannot put on weight and show business and to have to get up there and have been a
sex symbol all this time with 20 extra pounds, he had to kind of numb that pain and blah,
blah.
It's a sad story, a great documentary.
And if you have any interest in Elvis,
I recommend it, it's a great movie.
All right.
Is it by the guy that did the Sinatra one
and the Scientology one?
Ah, I don't know that those two
were by the same person actually.
No, those definitely are by the same person.
And he did the James Brown one too.
He did not, no, I don't think it's the same guy.
Okay, different guy.
Um, uh, uh, what oh, well speaking HBO, we can close with this. I finally saw the last
season of Kirby enthusiasm thoughts. I liked it. You know, it was, it was funny. It
had its moments. There was a lot of recycled stuff in it. Yes. Um, from both Seinfeld and
earlier curb seasons, absolutely. Um, but for the most part, it was, it was enjoyable.
Well, I thought JB smooth and funcows are stole the show.
This time around a thousand percent and the scene
with funcows and smooth,
where he's talking about his son.
That a son.
The nephew does.
When, and I don't even remember the situation,
but smooth's like, you're doing too much.
You're doing, you're trying to do too much.
I remember that was my biggest laugh of the whole season.
It's yeah, Jamie Spood had some some home run fucking lines the the are you to start by him wearing
Full du rag and every scene no, why it's it's feels like an old
White man's idea of black America, and I it's it's always troubled me that he always shows up like drinking a 40 with
with a bandana on his head.
But maybe I'm reading too much of that.
I don't think so.
No, because it's not like that's the only way
black people are ever portrayed on curb.
And I think the whole idea of that guy was he was that sort of dude
and then the family left and it was funny
that Larry and him formed the bond over.
Right.
Larry and anybody else in the family.
But I, I mean, JB smooth was a legend.
I started in the urban comedy circuit and he was a legend when I started right and nobody in the
mainstream at all knew who he was. So to see him now have such success in the mainstream is pretty
great because I'm telling you like the guy was talked about it was like a lure around him about
how funny he was. Well, I was at SNL. He was a writer who would occasionally be the guy in the cold
open who'd be like, oh, I have a question, Mr. Cruz, and I was like, why don't you put him on the
fucking show? Oh, because that was the season they decided to put finesse Mitchell on the show over
JB smooth. I was like, what is wrong with the show? Like, what are they doing? What are they doing?
Mitchell is such a fucking asshole. And for anyone to look at those two people and think that finesse
is the funnier of the two is insane. It's crazy. He's playing that big fancy theater in Glendale,
the one over by the Americana. I was like, how did he book this? Unless that theater's
Tiny and so I don't buy it. I think yeah, I don't buy that he's going to sell those tickets. No
Yeah, he sucks. There's one of a few people I I never even bat an eye talking shit about. No, he's the entertainment
He's a him airy spears is another guy where I'm like fucking asshole. Yeah
anyway
Yeah, but JB Spood
Some home run lines the line. You're gonna fuck around forget to plug up the chimney fat to aqua
Laws is gonna come down and kill your ass. Yeah, uh, fun Calisars outburst at the table. I hate your water
I feel like I stuck a straw in a frog's ass. That fantastic. It's just they they they really killed the season
Everybody killed David, you know, there was the episode with
Garland deciding he's gonna dress as a cowboy now was like where you see him from the woman's point of view
Garland humping away, wearing a 10 gallon hat.
Yeah, this is my look.
It's gonna be my look now.
I had my first manager that I ever had did that.
And I wondered if that was in any way based on that.
He started wearing a cowboy hat.
He started off by wearing the hat
and then went full cowboy.
Okay.
And I was like, are they making fun of this guy?
Is this who they're talking?
It was very weird, but it made me laugh
because I could relate to it quite frankly.
Right, the the curb stuff that bothered me this season and and part of it. It just happens to somebody with this amount of money for this long is like the full episode with Stephen Weber, who I love where they're like, you know, hard is to get a good sugar, a good oyster sugar in this town.
We've got the best oyster sugar for our parties. I was like, you are in such a niche world now that you're alienating your audience.
Yeah, we don't all have oyster shuckers at our parties.
It went a little deep into the sort of privilege lifestyle
this year. I agree with that.
I also didn't like why is Steven Weber playing a character?
Why is what's her name from Gilmore Girls playing a character?
We know who these people are.
They, well, they switched back and forth.
They do that kind of stuff, which it doesn't bother me that much.
But he told John Favreau, you're too famous to play,
you're not famous enough to play yourself,
you're too famous to play character.
It's like, I think Gilmore girls is way more household
ever told recognition than John Favreau would be by face.
I agree.
I like that stuff about the relationship clause
and all that, I thought was pretty funny.
Where it hit a, I didn't love the thought to law
and I particularly thought it hit a snag in the last couple with comedy killer,
Lin -Manuel Miranda. Those scenes...
You didn't think he was funny?
Those scenes shook me to my core. There was an icy silence reverberating throughout my house
and the whole thing about Larry David now is suddenly too sensitive to tell a man
that he'd like him to not sit at the desk. I was like, but this is the man who screams
James in the face of everyone.
Well, that was my one criticism.
I know I just said two other ones,
but those were not really criticisms.
Those were just like, yeah, that's weird.
My one criticism of the season was,
I was surprised at how much,
there were many moments in the plot devices and stuff
where I was like, why didn't you just do this?
Like, you seem to just kind of throw these two things together
because he had ideas and he tossed them together.
There didn't seem to be that like sort of expert weaving of everything that they're used to be in the in the previous seasons
For a season ten of one of the all -time great comedies to be slipping a little. I was happy we got the season
I I agree. I thought Lin -Manuel was funny, though, man. I I I was actually shocked
At how much of a fucking asshole he portrayed himself to be that
That dude is not my thing for some reason.
And they did that Broadway shit with the producer season,
which I thought was beautifully done.
That's what I mean.
It was like another,
we're gonna do another musical thing again.
They did the Seinfeld finale thing again.
Where it's like,
I'm barely looking at the screen.
Ernest has hit himself and three others in the face
with Cardors.
Well, you also missed two.
They showed it once,
and I believe they've already called it back.
The flashback to him is a kid
where his teacher hits him in the back of the head and his face slams into the chalkboard.
Which if you did now, you'd be not just out of a job, but you know, sure, God only knows.
Anyway, so that was curb. Scary. Shit, I had a scary stuff. Damn it.
Where's my phone?
Now how many of these gaming systems have you never played?
I've played all them.
Okay.
All right.
So down there are the ones in reserve.
So there's the Dreamcast.
I haven't played that yet.
I don't have a place for it.
I haven't played that Sega Genesis model one yet.
But I have a Sega Genesis CDX over there.
So I don't need to...
It's just the same.
It's just a different model.
And I never played my Famicom.
Okay, because the started by you saying you'd played them all.
Well, I'm saying like I don't need to, the only one that I haven't, the Famicom is
just the Japanese version of the Super Nintendo mini that I have over there.
All right, so it's like it's not like, it's not like, oh, I've, it's literally saying like,
you know. Well, you make an interesting point, yeah.
It's like saying it's like saying have you seen Star Wars and you go yeah, I saw you know
I saw these three additions. I didn't see this one version of the specialty. Okay, that kind of different. All right
What did I have for scary stuff Pat? I don't know what's happening, but my quitting of alcohol and substances
My brain has not gotten any sharper. Yeah, I would say less sharp. It's it seems to be dulling down
There's probably a rebuilding period of the brain where it has to
to get used to creating its own sensations
and feelings and emotions.
Okay, I'm gonna plug the Metroid
Samus Returns video game for the Nintendo 3DS.
It's a remake of the second Metroid game
that was only ever released on the first Game Boy, the black and white version.
This is old. This is not a new game. It's been out for probably a year at this point, but
you know what? It is a fucking fantastic Metroid game. I really like it quite a bit. A couple
people have some criticisms about the game mechanics. I actually think the game mechanics are pretty
great once you get into it and get used to it. But if you're a fan of a sci -fi alien inspired video game,
I would, I would greatly suggest you check out Metroid and even more so Axiom Verge, which I just got from my Switch.
Just awesome. Just two awesome games that are cut from extremely similar cloth.
So check them out. Axiom Verge is a lot of fun because it's a lot of like
Bustules and tumorous things that you shoot that are alien growths and they splatter and shit. I like stuff like that.
Anyway, check them out for your gaming pleasure.
Great.
And that's Joe's scary stuff.
Do you have anything you want to talk about a dog you saw in the street or something?
No, I didn't have anything particularly scary happen this week.
Good.
Yeah, no, I don't have anything.
I'm sorry, and I don't, let me think.
I watched, no, that was the in -laws, that's a comedy.
I watched all the special features on the criterion of the in -laws, the original or the
Michael Douglas.
I've seen them both, I actually didn't just, why I watched it on a plane, so you always
have to give it a 50 % advantage on a plane, but I didn't hate the Albert Brooks Michael
Douglas in -laws, but the original is so fucking good and funny.
with Alan Arkin and Peter Fock.
Yeah, the originals and masterpiece.
And I was just thinking like, you know,
Alan Arkin and Peter Fock are sort of
legendarily great character actors.
But like, there are zero comedies made today
where like those two guys would be the star of it
and it would get a release.
It doesn't happen.
I would agree.
There's 10 people in comedy according to Hollywood
and they're the only ones who make movies.
But like, there's gotta be so many,
you know, like Gosling, for example,
I've always really loved Gosling
and I think he's got impeccable taste
in terms of the roles he picks.
And he knows when he's got been too indie for too long
and he'll throw you a crazy stupid love
or whatever that, which was an entertaining movie.
But I just think he's got good taste
and he's a great actor and I wanna fuck him.
But folks Ryan Gosling is a guy who you think of as a serious dramatic actor who must not have any sense of humor
But they trusted him with the nice guys and he's so fucking funny and the nice fantastic in it
He's so funny another thing that makes you go fuck you Ryan
I know the man is unstoppable. I know and I guess you know
I'm good. Well, I'm proving my point here because the in -laws was not a successful film
and either was the fucking nice guys.
I bet the nice guys lost $40 million
and it's two really strong dramatic actors,
Russell Crowe and Ryan Gosling,
they did try it and it didn't work.
So I guess that's why.
I mean, these things I want more of in movies,
apparently, unfortunately, they're just not successful
so they'll never happen again.
Yeah, I agree with you.
The in -laws, just a masterpiece.
peace. The comedic chops of folk and arc in it are pretty, they're pretty goddamn impressive.
I mean, these are two guys that can turn this drama on its ear and then jump right into
comedy. And how much it, I mean, I guess you could say inspired, but pretty ripped off by
meet the parents. Yes, extremely. I mean, it was kind of crazy. He's in the CIA. Everything
Everything about it is almost the same deal.
I meet the parents as hilarious comedy as well, but.
It's utter thievery, a little bit.
Cock suckers.
And I learned in going down that Wikipedia whole last night
that meet the parents was based on a short film
called Meet the Parents that they bought the rights to.
Didn't even know that.
And was it by the same guy?
No, the guys never been heard from again.
Because the guy that did, forget the writer or director
or meet uh... well the writer of meet the parents who went on what's his face
any jim hamber and he wrote now any wrote uh... dinner with for schmucks and
writers are hurts felt and and jim uh...
and then he directed hold on
give me a minute i'm looking it up
give me a second here it's the same guy that wrote directed safe men
hurts felt
i don't think
It has two writers. I forget the other guys name Jim something and the people who are John
Hamburg. It is John Hamburg. Is it? It's Hertzfeld and Hamburg. I believe are the two guys.
So Hamburg wrote, say, oh yeah, Longkein, Polly, meet the parents. He directed Little Fockers
right because Safeman was based on a short that he made. Okay. I love Safeman. Bonus, which
which is a bonus feature on the DVD.
I love Safeman.
Now trivia question, do you know which acclaimed filmmaker
did the final pass on Meet the Parent's Script?
No.
Well, it was Alexander Payne and Jim Taylor,
the gentleman who wrote sideways about Schmidt election
and then several bad movies since then.
They did the final pass on me at the parents. I love stuff like that. I love when the Cohen brothers are like
Yeah, we'll do this giant budget movie like Cohen brothers writing on bridge of spies is fascinating to me. What is the
What is the last pain movie that came out? Was it that it was absolutely worse downsizing? Oh
Geez downsizing Nebraska was very slow and I thought it was fine and then the descendants
I thought was pretty bad as well.
I hated the descendants.
I did as well.
It was like a schmaltz fest of what he usually does
really well.
Yeah, agree.
I fucking hated it, man.
Here's something for deadlines from Scream and End.
Yeah.
The 24 hour new psycho.
And it's old Kulgera, if it's still pushing that
but Bloomberg, Scream, Screamberg.
Oh, it was a real desperate attempt.
Didn't make it, like call it Doomberg or something.
That's what we both said to him.
Oh, I hung out all the other night,
she was like, I'm still mad you shut that down
and I was like, you mad at me or you mad at yourself?
Well, you know, we didn't shut down, Karen,
is coming to you live from the uncut thick dick house.
Yes, that was yours and we used it.
That's true and speaking of which folks the hog house store is open on Etsy on Etsy go to the Etsy and find the hog house is at the store shop shop
Braille shop
So go check out the hog house place on Etsy
Thank you again to all our patrons on patreon and thank you to our friends that have been so or fans that have been so
supportive, and also a big shout to Emily Florence, who got all this stuff set up and
our dear friend Ken Hanley, formerly of Fangoria, the guy that is responsible for greenlighting
this podcast.
We got a nice email from Emily and Ken today saying that they are looking into setting
up a live show for us.
So I don't know where we'd be without those two, honestly, because we would love obviously
love to do it.
Pat and I can't even, you know, get through a week without a drink without throwing our hands up in here.
We should do one at the Lyric.
I think we should do a bigger room than that.
The Lyric is very small.
It's true, but I mean, I just love it because it's a five minute walk from my house,
but I saw two of the best comedy shows I've seen
at the Lyric in a two week period.
I want to do a weekly at the Lyric.
Yeah, you should and I don't know why nobody's doing that
You should I want to do it like you know like a showcase thing, you know where everybody does 10 minutes. Yeah
You know, I think I will pet and then the Pepitone guy authorized the youth of use use of his name Scott Patton
Okay, we're at the fan fiction
He had a very funny recap of our brief meeting at the thing. What was the meeting?
or what was the recap, brother?
He said, he came up, said all with the Joe,
we talked for a bit, but he had every detail of the exchange,
except I told him I couldn't vouch for the first part
of his story, which is that he ate a burger in his car
before going into the show.
And that sounds good.
I'm very hungry right now.
Yeah, I've been eating a vegan meal delivery service
in addition to the working out.
So it's just diarrhea all day.
Jesus Christ. So you don't want to get lunch after this. I can't get lunch. I'm sorry. You got to go get vegan
What are you gonna eat like a vegan turkey sub or something? I wish nothing is made. Would it's I wish it was supposed to be it's
I mean, I have eaten a few dishes now where I'm like I don't know as I'm eating it if it's gone bad or not
It's like vegetables and they drop the bag off in front of your house
So you don't know at what point of the night it came if it's I mean it were we're finishing up the plan this week
but it's me and Heather they're trying to plan a wedding while eating only vegan food and working out non -stop and we are both
Really pushed to our limits
Now I'm thinking about without exercise. Yeah doing a 10 -day
Or seven -day whatever it is green juice cleanse
Okay, my dear friend Nate Bergatsi just did one and he said that it was amazing and he lost weight and
It's worth doing. I do one every year with much less nutrients than green juice. I swear by it
I like it it helps you kind of reset your shit and yeah, I mean because I I got a I got a shave off about 10
Sure, and I think that's a fast way to do it. Yes
And you know, I'm already not boozing, so what's to stop me?
I'm just terrified of how hungry I'm gonna be.
Yeah, it's maybe the first and second day,
the novelty of it is still there and you're fine,
especially if you eat a bunch the night before you start.
But then like the third, fourth,
you start getting kind of a headache and very irritable.
Many people drop out at that point.
But if you stick with it by day 10,
and you feel like you could do 30 days, no problem.
Okay.
And it's a 10 day thing, it's not a seven day.
You do whatever you want.
I would start with a seven, myself.
Should I start with a three or a five?
I mean, if you're doing a 10,
you're starting with a three anyway, aren't you?
I've just never done it before.
So I don't know if it's like dangerous to go.
It's not dangerous.
Where do I go by one of them?
I mean, a doctor might tell you it's dangerous,
but what do they know?
Where do I go buy one of these things?
Well, you're in Los Angeles, so literally anywhere.
All right.
I don't need the flippant, there are hundreds.
My place that I go to that does great work in this realm,
and they hook you up with everything you need,
is called Super Cunts.
Super Cunts, yeah.
Oh, it's not, do you be confused with Super Cunts?
it's super, super, I'll send you the link.
These people don't care about this.
All right, but I'm gonna,
so I'm gonna go into a green juice cleanse.
But if I go into this store, cold turkey,
I go look, I've never done this.
You can't have cold turkey on the juice cleanse.
It's just juice, you can't have the cold turkey on the juice.
We're gonna start with a pound of shaved ham.
No, I'm saying I go in and I go look,
I've never done this before.
I want to start tomorrow.
What do I need?
They go, here's what you need, all right.
and it's like a hundred bucks for like a week.
Seven days?
Yeah, usually.
Which is less money than I would spend if I just ate regular.
Correct.
Alright.
Now, are these trolls designed for their noses to look like dicks?
I know in nothing but trouble,
Acroids Nose was obviously modeled after a dick.
I feel like this is as close as it can get and a PG rated kids moving.
We did talk through the scene where Ernest is trying to tell the sheriff
that there are trolls in the town.
Yeah.
And he goes, share if there's no shot come on me.
That didn't happen.
Yes, it did.
It did.
You talked right through it.
How do they find out that the trolls can only be killed by milk, basket up with milk now
and cottage cheese?
I mean, it's just a come reference to this whole movie.
How do they discover this?
Oh, and checks.
Ernest used to do commercials for checks.
So there's probably got some money there.
Not me.
No one I mean?
burn you never see Vern right never and who even was Vern was it was that part of his
you know what this is a puppet by the way you know why you never saw him he was he was horribly
disfigured oh no yeah was he also a figment of Ernest imagination no because you'd see his hands
and stuff you just wouldn't see his face and they were just just friends yeah he was like his best
And Vern would always be a I read the thing on Wikipedia like they did these burger commercials for some
Like new Mexico burger chain. Yeah and the gag was like Vern was always inside eating the burger and Vern was always
I mean and Ernest was always outside right like what's you eating in there Vern? Yeah, yeah a bacon double cheese burger
Yeah, I was this Ernest impression is it pretty good?
It's one of your best, but it's a terrible impression
Give me a scenario to do as Ernest because I got to be honest with you Pat
I'm hitting that hour 15 mark where I want to go to sleep right now
Give me Ernest get purchasing a seven -day juice cleanse
Now I hear you I'll have the best seven -day juice cleanse in all of Los Angeles
Oh boy, I would like to lose weight to become fit to become
Cut to become slim. So I can it's not bad. It's some getting the rhythm of them. That's kind of how we would say it
Ernest P. Will I haven't even heard him speak in this because we're watching it with subtitles Jesus Christ
There's another 21 minutes. It feels like we should be in the home stretch and yet this I got to tell you I
I knew 15 minutes ago we were in trouble because we weren't at this part yet, right?
And I knew that this was the beginning of like the sort of finale and that it went on
for fucking ever.
Well, it's structure.
I mean, the movie's 93 minutes.
I feel like Ernest are generally like 79.
This was the last theatrical release.
And I also know it wasn't.
And Ernest Rides, again, was the last theatrical release, and it bombed really bad.
That's not what I saw.
The Wikipedia, are they wrong?
They don't look it up now, hold on.
Because it's actually, it said like, this movie made a meager 14 million.
So it was the last theatrical release, and I thought to myself, what could the budget have
been?
60 bucks?
I guess the trolls cost money.
Hold on.
I'm going to look this up.
Quite frank, quite frequently, I'm positive, I'm correct, and I'm 100 % wrong.
Right.
Now, Ernest is bowling for trolls, trolling, if you would.
I guess he does look like a young man, young enough, not really.
He's like 40 there, well yeah, if he died at 50, he was in daddy in them, which was Billy
Bob Thornton's picture and he did a good job.
I, I assume he was just a guy who
People could only see his earnest, but Billy Bob Thornton seems like the kind of guy who would love Ernest
Where is it here? The Ernest films. He also played slinky dog in the
Yeah, Toy Story first two films. Do you remember a picture called fast food with Jim Varney?
That was on cable all the time back into the very vaguely. It was a shitty PG -13 sex comedy. God damn it
you're right. Thank you. And I got it confused with a hamburger of the motion picture, which
was a hard r. And I know I was right. Yes. Yes. Ernest rides again.
Sixth film, the feature of the character Ernest, the fifth film in the last to be released
at least theatrically, Ernest rides again.
I mean, Wikipedia for scared stupid says this is it.
So, no, it doesn't.
It says it right here.
But you're not looking at the scared stupid Wikipedia.
It's budget was $7 million.
It's the plot of it is, he's a history professor.
I think I remember that being.
Ernest played released.
Ernest and a history professor discover
a long less revolutionary work hand
and because it's and it's filled with precious jewels.
oh boy there was an earnest in space being discussed I read what is the cover of this one
why is confetti falling down in his face that looks like a greeting card yeah that's uh
uh and then also it's never good when on this poster it says also featuring Mr. Bill goes to
Washington yeah boy there's something I never found funny it was Mr. Bill yeah I just never gave a
Fuck no, due to its modest gross of 14 million it was the final Ernest film to be released under the Disney label touch -stone pictures
Which weirdly we were discussing at the beginning of the yeah all future Ernest films were independently produced
And following the financial failure of Ernest rides again they shift to straight to video Ernest goes to school as your first
Yeah direct to video and there actually is a picture called Ernest goes to Africa
Which there is I'm not I know there is I know and I don't know what that thing looks like
But I'm certainly curious slam dunk earnest was the second directive video. It stirred him and that I remember
Kreme of the old Jabbar that I remember the third was called earnest goes to Africa
Oh boy. Yeah look at the cover of that thing. What do you got? Oh?
Uh, let's see with the, with the, uh, I don't care how little a budget you have, you
can do a better fucking cover than that.
In this film, Deacon County, Ohio resident Ernest, a knowingly comes into the possession
of some stolen jewels, back to the jewels and his kid mapped and brought to Africa, where
he must rescue the woman he loves.
The film was shot entirely in Johannesburg, South Africa, why after that came Ernest in the
Army. Yeah. Holy Christ.
Look at the color of that one.
Oh, these are, these are sub -blurry of the cable guy.
Well, yeah, these are, these are bad.
Ernest Roy is the army because he wants to drive large vehicles, but ends up being sent
into combat. It was shot in Cape Town, South Africa. There's got to be some kind of budget
cut down there where they were left. Yeah.
We can shoot it for cheaper or they're popular and Ernest's popular in Africa or something
Which I can't imagine John Cherry's the director his son played
Corporal Davis. That's a weird fact. I remember that the old
That he just did. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Really sort of a precursor to an ace fan
chair. Yeah. No, that was his catchphrase. That and know what I mean. Yeah.
I want to see what else John cherry nothing looked them up. He was he was a rider die Ernest guy
His last film was called Pirates of the plane
Oh Jesus he directed the new adventures of Laurel and Hardy a film in which
Apparently the people playing Laurel and Hardy aren't even famous enough to get a credit in
in the starring section, there isn't even a starring section on the Wikipedia page, holy
shit. Oh no, Bronson Pinchot. I remember that. Played Laurel, Balky himself, Gallyard
Sartane. I heard Sartane, yep. He was, he was in Ernest Ghost Camp. He was also in the
outsiders. Yeah. He's like a big fat dude. I would imagine because he's playing Oli.
Uh, do you remember who played himself in the new season?
A curb.
That's right.
F Murray Abraham gets to play himself.
You got god damn Ingalls from fucking Gilmore girl, whatever their god damn name is on
that show.
Is it Gilmore?
Gilmore.
You got her playing a NBC sensor doesn't make any sense.
Do you remember when Jerry Seinfeld was, I mean, still as big, but he was so big
they gave him a two hour block on NBC to do an Abedon Costello special. Do you remember
watching that? No, I do not. I watched. It was like Thanksgiving night and it's Jerry
sign felt like everybody loves Abedon Costello. It was clearly he went to NBC and they were
like, yeah, we got to do whatever you say. Here's two hours. The show was on. Yeah, it was
during the okay. Or if not, it was right after. But they just like show clips of Abedon Costello
and you know, that's a strange thing to have in primetime television.
Now, fast food, not only start Jim Varney, also start Tracy Lourdes, was this like a
TIT movie?
Like a T .A.?
Well, as I was saying, I watched it excitedly thinking it was going to be tied to hamburger
in the motion picture, which was the first nudity I ever saw, and a real sexual awakening
for me.
But then fast food was actually PG -13.
Oh, did you say all that?
I did I it might be because you're literally reading off your phone. I didn't hear god damn word of it
I know somebody who made love to Tracey lords. Oh, who obviously I'm not going to say what did he say about it?
He said they were drunk. He was very young perhaps not even quite of age and that the next day
He had a complete panic attack because he had made love to a pornography star
which I don't think is is appropriate.
No, especially.
Although I'd be in the same boat.
She's been out of the game so long.
You got nothing to worry about there.
Those girls are probably cleaner than most women.
They get tested with such regularity.
They always say that.
And they have to do whatever two weeks.
I'd just be concerned they caught something on day one
back in the game.
I think there's an honor code
To your frequency and all that sort of stuff, but my point is is they're getting the best kind of test available every two weeks
Sure, you don't there was a brief porn star outbreak of like HIV, but I've never heard about anything serious happening
Yeah, once in a while there's gonna be a little outbreak, but that's like you know
I mean like our our presidents comfortable raw dogging a porn star. Did he raw that's true? Yeah, did not use a condom you're sure
It was on 60 minutes because that's the world we're living in I didn't
She's still the president speaking of which I'll plug
Stormy Daniels is on the May, June double issue cover of the double issue of penthouse
My column you let me down will be seen in that issue as always so go check that out
But stormy might read your column. I believe that this is the first
magazine cover to feature her I think okay
It's pretty crazy so she's on the cover so anyway, and I think she's actually you know, she's in the magazine too
It's not just like she's on the cover
Anyway, so check that out. I will
How much does the penthouse run you know if you go to the newsstand? I have no idea I would guess
It could be like 1495, but they know they got to keep it tight because people can access pornography
Playboy, which is now available at my gym, is now just like Indy, Waf, very thin girls,
like in, you know, like boy clothes and underwear and like, yeah, it went all maximum, right?
It went beyond maximum into more of like an Indy Goth vibe, which Indy, what do you mean?
I mean the girls like have a lot of like mascara and they look like kind of malnourished at
least the ones in the cupboard.
But they're not naked anymore right?
Right.
And they look more like goathy indie.
They don't look like, you know, your standard playboy model.
I never gave a shit about playboy, even as a kid, I was like, yeah, put clothes on these
bras.
This stuff is boring.
Get me the fucking break me out that hustler over there.
Let's get down to it to this, you know, if we're going to do it, let's do it.
I cannot say the same because I found a playboy in the woods that I believe had been used to wipe someone's ass
And still I was like, how can I fumigate this and bring it back to my home?
Did you I wound up tearing off the pages that appear to have shit on them and I put it up in my tree house
And I would go up there and masturbate, of course and
And Jesus God, that's a really disturbing story.
I also watched when I was probably nine,
a 15, 16 year old couple fucking my clubhouse
because they asked if they could use it.
Came to my door and asked me.
I never would have known they were up there.
And I was like, it was the couple neighborhood kids
that were like, do you mind if we use your clubhouse
for a little bit?
I was like, no, that's okay,
but I was like, I wonder what they're doing.
I climbed up the ladder and was able to, you know, basically watch a butt thrust away,
but it was enough.
Wow.
It was a strange childhood.
I remember when I was nine, I peeped on my cousin's neighbor, getting out of the shower
and I saw her naked through the window, like a window in his house, into her house.
Sure.
She was like 19. It was like one of the
Great thrills of my fucking young life. I mean, I couldn't believe I was seeing a naked woman in real life
Yeah, it was rare. I mean I
People joke about you know using the serious catalog. I was using that serious catalog through age 16 the bra
ad section and then what I used to do was go to like be Dalton or Walden books or whatever and I would
would get a large magazine like a Rolling Stone, which used to be like twice the size
it is now.
And I would place inside of it a penthouse, let's say.
Then while pretending to read Rolling Stone, I would carefully, with my fingernail, remove
the plastic from the penthouse, look at it.
And then if I was feeling real risky, I would tear a page out while covering it with the Rolling
stone, slip it in my pocket and run out of the bookstore. I did this all the time because it was my only
way to get like one image. We used to do a thing at the newsstand where we would, I believe I've told
the story before, we'd put a porn mag inside of a regular mag and then go up and just buy the regular
mag. That's smart. And the guy never seemed to notice. And then we finally just started bringing the
porn mags up and he would sell them to us still. He didn't give a shit. This guy didn't give a shit.
my mom I remember was starting to be like you don't have to go in there anymore because I think she
knew like yeah you know well that's I mean it's much smarter I I never would have been that
ballsy but it's good because then you have the backup of saying oh I'm sorry I didn't know that was
in there anytime I would steal or do anything like that I always had a good backup that I could say
oh but I thought this or that yeah I'm surprised I went through all these lengths to tear one image out
but when I could have just put the magazine in.
Is he dancing with the troll?
Yeah, in typical, they're friends now?
Yeah, I was gonna say in typical children's movie fashion,
the troll has somehow turned good and lovable,
and Ernest and the troll now are dancing and hugging
and they're friends.
The troll looks more disgusting than it's ever looked.
Yeah, like thing style tentacles coming off its head.
Oh, Ernest kissed it.
And he's got.
But he's got a slimed string connecting to, oh, what's happening?
This thing just keeps twisting and turning.
You watched this last night.
I didn't get this far.
I got to be honest with you.
I got up to like right before.
Oh, he kissed it and the trolls head exploded.
Ernest really looks like he just took a facial to the mouth as well as he did and the bird poops in.
I don't understand.
That was supposed to be like it was good that he saved it or that it turned good and then it turned...
What the fuck just happened?
I don't know.
Yeah, this thing I did notice,
they keep twisting and turning everything
that happens in this thing.
I wonder if the Ernest pictures got notes, got studio notes.
I'm sure they did.
There are pictures like any other.
Yeah.
The kids are now turning back from wooden dolls
into regular children.
This kid here, the blonde hair girl.
Yeah.
She looked familiar, so I looked her up.
Oh boy.
She grew up to be like,
she's a gorgeous indie musician.
What's her name?
I forget, I had never heard of her,
but when I looked around,
I was like, oh, that she was on third rock from the sun.
That's what I was recognizing her from.
But they had new pictures of her,
and I was like, is that the same person?
She's like, turn to this like strikingly beautiful singer songwriter, Shea Athstar.
Yeah, yeah, that's her, never heard of her out of there.
She's married, bummed me out a little bit, but what are you going to do?
But so she's single.
What's your next move then?
I guess in this day and age, you can always follow some Instagram, and if you have more followers
maybe, you know, you got to shout out to, I don't know.
Right. The Stranger Things Have Happened. Yeah. Stranger Things Season 3 Have Happened.
Kerry L. was added to the cast of Stranger Things Season 3. That's a weird, you know, he's an 80s guy.
Yeah. He has had some face work done. I could really seem in the Andre the Giant Documentary.
That's a strange career.
I mean, Princess Bride, I guess that was not a big money maker at its time.
But then, like Mel Brooks is like, yeah, you're going to be my Robin Hood, hot shots,
you know, then kind of gone for a decade, then saw, which didn't really lend itself to like
a big horror career either.
He just kind of hangs in there, but it's strange.
It's an odd career.
It's like Matthew Modine who's also in Stranger Things. Yes. Now I agree. Uh, is this fucking movie over yet? Jesus Christ
That let's do plugs now because we're approaching the credits. All right gang. I'm on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh
My show living biblically heading into the home stretch, I don't see a season two in the
cards people.
I'd love you to watch these episodes.
The one that is airing tonight is my favorite episode of the entire run.
It is extremely funny, even if you watch it early on and didn't like it, I recommend checking
back in because it's genuinely funny.
And it is the one that I told you about that features two crumb holds folks jokes
Which you will appreciate
By night origins is now available on Amazon Prime
For you horror anthology fans are just horror fans out there
Go watch it. I was proud to be a part of it. And I think it turned out pretty great
So go check that out joderosa comedy on Twitter and Instagram and that is it for now folks
We'll see you next time
We are still going to do ready player one by the way people keep asking and we'll see you in hell