I'm here for Bet Rivers online casino and sportsbook with poker icon Phil Helmuth.
And now thanks to the excitement of Bet Rivers, I'm also a slots icon.
That's great! And a same game, parlay icon. Cool, cool. A blackjack icon,
a money line icon, a roulette. Take it from Phil Helmuth. If you love games,
Bet Rivers is the place to play in Bet. Bet Rivers. Games on.
Must be 21 plus in present at West Virginia. Void were prohibited. Terms in conditions apply.
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gambling.
The football season is full of guarantees. And here's another. No other sportsbook has
an offer this good. With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until
October, if your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash. If you bet on football
with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan cash, guaranteed. Switch to
fanatic sportsbook. Winning hits different here. Must be 21 plus. Gambling problem called
1 -800 -Gambling. Offer not available in all states. Terms apply. See fanatic sportsbook up.
Welcome to will see you in hell. Your favorite podcast covering horror sci -fi fantasy.
Sometimes comedy, sometimes drama and also action films. My name is Joe DeRosa. To my left is my
co -host and dear friend. Hello everybody. You got Pat Walsh. I'm drinking a shockingly potent drink.
I was like, yeah, I could use a cold one to get into performance mode. So I get something called a
cold brew cocktail. These are not a sponsor. Fugu horchata. So I'm taking a sip. I'm like, holy shit.
This thing tastes more like vodka than it does coffee. It's got 13 % alcohol. I'm going to be on my
ass. It's a can. I'm drinking a can of vodka. I'm happy to see you back because as of the last episode
you hadn't drank at all for a little bit. Well, nobody wants that. Nobody wants it. I was, you're
killing me with that shit, man. Now tonight we can dip in, have a little fun. Joe and I are going
to see Cyprus Hill. And you didn't like the new album though. I on a first listen was not blown away.
But I'm excited to hear the tracks live. Okay. They'll only play like two of them. Right. You know,
you know, then it'll be all insane in the membrane. You know, sure. Pat, Pat, Pat. You think they'll do
for you. So you want to be a rock superstar and live large, a big house, five cars live large.
No, you're in charge coming up in the world. Don't trust nobody. Got the look of a gush on their
constantly. Right. All right. Listen, I don't think I need to go to the concert anymore.
That was so spot on. Look, that was a huge song when I was in. Let's say junior year of high school.
It's a good tune. Um, I've been drinking this new thing, Pat.
I've been drinking. I've been drinking. See, this is the liquor yesterday. Paps Blue Ribbon Easy.
Joe is drinking Paps Blue Ribbon Easy for the alcoholic on the go. It's a, it's in a blue and gold
can. And it's, it's low. It's their version of like a Mick Ultra. They don't list the calories anywhere
on the can that I can see. So I have no idea if it's less or not, but I'm going to do the inaugural
sip. Is it going down smooth? I haven't sipped it yet. Let's try it. Ready?
Oh boy. It's literally dribbling down his chin. That's the company I'm keeping today.
Oh boy. You could drink this all day long. You wouldn't even know you were drinking. Okay.
Oh, that's nice. That is, uh, that's what you want. That's what I want. That is a piss beer.
I run a piss beer. No sweetness. I hate when a beer has a sweetie flavor to it. Sure. Sure.
Now we did when a sweetie has a beer flavor to her. If you catch my drift.
Pat, I do catch your drift and I drift your catch. That's a kind of a joke you would make where you
flip the words around like he just did. It didn't make any sense. You know, here's the
next sense. You, you like to do that? You're, they call you the flipper in, in, in writer's rooms.
You know, they'll say this script needs work. Bring the flipper in. Yeah. And they've got to do it if
it makes sense. Like yours, for example, did not make sense. I know, but I know. But you know,
can we just have a little fun today? Uh, on today's show, we're talking about the Hills,
Have I's remake 2006, Ellie, Andrea, uh, babe, uh, coming off out tension, which is a very
scary, uh, film from overseas. And we'll get there. We'll talk about it. But in the meantime,
I'd love to get on with the show. And if I may, at the same time, get on,
leave the show.
Very good. Right. Very good. Excited to discuss, brass band.
Excited to discuss the Hills have eyes much was, was surprised to see it wasn't a movie about the
paparazzi and Hollywood. She's crazy. Okay. That's really good. Oh, yours was, yours was brilliant.
And that the Hills have eyes. I thought, uh, oh no, uh, Dolly Parton finally found a way to trap us
when we're looking too long. She's, that's not, that would be eyes on the Hills. She's got
eyes on her hills. Yeah. The hills have eyes. Her breasts have eyes on them.
I made more sense because the, the paparazzi would be up in the Hills and Hollywood.
No, yours makes sense. It just sucks. What is with you today? What is it? It's just, it's not good.
Why are you coming at me? How much plot did you smoke already today? I had a, I had a little bit.
Yeah, it's always obvious. You drug ease. It's always easy to tell. When you're all drugged out,
folks, I'm, I'm sharper on a little weed.
Frankly, sometimes I got to take that edge off.
A lot to talk about bonus episode this month. By the way, coming up, it's going to be our review of
us. Yeah. Jordan Peele's new one. Us. We're taking it behind the old pay wall. If you don't have
the Patreon, we're doing a lot of great stuff over there. We give you guys some of our best episodes.
And you get in at, you know, whatever level you want. You throw us a buck if you want.
Throw us a little more if you want the free content. It's a nice thing.
It's not really free content when you're paying for it, but you get, you know, you get the extra
content. The, that'll be our bonus ep. We've got a lot to talk about. And as you guys know, we don't
usually do movie reviews on the Patreon episodes because they are, they are segment free episodes.
But twice now, Lightning is struck with the remake of Susperia and now us, where we felt like there
was so much to talk about, we could do it as a bonus episode. That's right. So I'm excited about it.
But today, we do have segments. Now, I want to do a quick screaming and news cycle. Great.
I got one too. Did you see that there was a high school, and if not, I'll send you those because
you're going to love this high school. And I want to get the city correct. But they performed a
very faithful adaptation of alien, the original alien, Northburgen high school drama club made an
incredible stage production of the Ridley Scott classic alien using only recycled materials.
Oh, that's cool. And then, I mean, look at the pictures of this thing.
Oh, wow. Let me see that. It looks incredible. Let me see that. Wow. That's very cool. So, you know,
there was other cities reaching out like we'd love to have your production come visit us and stuff. So
there's a chance maybe they'll tour a little bit, but I heard it was something special to be hold. And
why don't you go over reading article about it? What the hell are you doing? It's really cool. Read an article.
Got a little video going at the bottom. Oh, I probably want to stop that. No, it's video of the play.
Oh, yeah. I know, but why do they do that? Why do they pop shit up? I don't know. It was cool. I
enjoyed it. What's it? You just, it's, you know, that's a nice thing. I just, it's always with the
phones. You know, they're like, hey, I overheard you talking about this today. And I'm like, what?
Excuse me? I'll tell you, you're in the perfect laid back spirits for a Cypress Hill concert tonight.
The, uh, uh, I'm sorry. Am I a little paranoid for you? Joe DeRosa?
I, uh, I've got a screaming in. And it's a, in fact, I've got two.
The first is because I'm a little lighter in the movie corner this week. So I want to do two of these.
I'm plenty. The first is Joe Bob Briggs, the last driving weekly show now in shutter.
I think it's every other, something like that, but I am so excited. It's going to be a double feature
every other week or something like that. I think it's, it's, I thought it was every Friday. I
read it, but it's every, it might be every other than the, so well, either way, it starts this weekend,
this Friday night, March 29th, I believe. And, uh, I mean, those are some of my favorite things in
entertainment of last year. I loved them. I'll tell you what's cool for us in LA. In LA, it starts at
6 p .m. Right. Live. So we could have a Friday where we watched the double feature and then still
plenty of time to go out after. Right. Pretty neat. Joe and I, excuse me, like to roll these streets
like kind of like the outsiders gang. Joe, Joe, Joe roll up his t -shirt sleeves and they'll have a
cigarette pack in them. I've got another screaming in. I do kind of the leather jacket, greased hair
thing. Uh, the mid -summer or summer or summer, however you pronounce a trailer came out. This is
the new film by the gentleman that made hereditary. I'm blanking on his name. Ari Aster.
Ari Aster. Um, Ari Aster. She said no. Uh, here's the thing. Does it look good? It looks interesting.
It looks very, um, can't wait. Anything that guy does on my list want to see it? It looks very, uh,
what's the, uh, what's the, uh, what's the, uh, what's the Nicholas Cage thing where he goes, the
island with the witches and the bees. Uh, it's the remake wicker man. It looks very wicker man. Uh,
here's my question to you, Pat and all of you out there. But mostly the man is there a look.
There's a big risk factor here. This thing, this came out hot on the heels of hereditary. Right. How
could it possibly have gotten the time it needed to be, uh, you know, it happens a lot right after
the breakthrough movie, a lot of directors go directly into a second movie. So the first one will
take 10 years of thinking about it and working on it in your mind and fine tuning it, getting it
down on paper, thinking about it some more, then you're ready to release it to the world. Now all of a
sudden you're doing that same process in two months and the results are sometimes a little sloppy.
Well, my question is it's not, it's like, we're under a year from hereditary's release.
Right. And maybe it'll be great. I mean, look, maybe it will be great. But to, to write, maybe
already on it written, but to completely produce a film soup to nuts in this little amount of time,
I mean, it goes beyond even like, well, is it a, is the script ready or whatever? It's like, you're
really moving fast. And I would assume accordingly to other people's schedules and things where you're
saying, you know, look, the first film at Tony Collette in it, this does not have a star of that caliber
because you're going, well, we're shooting it now. Who's available? Right. You know, the little
things like that. But I'm curious to see if it's any good. Um, it looks even more, um, I don't know
it looks a bit more artsy, I guess I would say than hereditary. You know, looks, it looks to have
even less of a sort of grounded, right, footing than hereditary does. But, you know, it's hard to tell
from a teaser trailer. But I do want to say it and I hope that it's good. It's just fast. It's less
than a year. It's fast, you know, it's less than a year. Also, the drag to cross concrete trailer
finally came out. It's playing up at the arc lot. I almost saw it the other night. Oh, it's playing
already. Yeah, I saw us. And then as I was walking out, I was like, should I, but I just went home.
That trailer also, not thrilled. I want to see the movie very badly, but the trailer was like,
it almost makes it look like a cops that are going to turn into robbers movie. Mm -hmm.
I think it's a pro cop movie. It's what I've heard. I don't know. It's a dangerous thing to do
at this time. I heard it's, I heard it's a challenging, you know, sort of exercise out to
provoke. But the trailer, for all I heard about what this movie was going to be about this video that
goes viral and police brutality and all this stuff, the trailer does not look like that. The trailer
looks like it's like two cops that can't make a living that are going to like pull off some kind of
heist or something. I'll see you in either way. I want to see it. The man knows how to make a movie.
I said it follows his usual pattern of like two hours that are entertaining but slow,
and then a horrific escalation of violence for the last 20 minutes. And I'm ready for that.
I mean, I don't know how he's going to top the last two unless he has like
mel Gibson face fuck Vince Vaughn to death or something. Like, I don't know how, maybe that's coming.
How much worse of two kills you could have. But I am. That's not a knife. That's Paul Haggard. That's
not a dick. That's a dick. Right. That's the dark crack it out, doesn't he? Yeah.
Cockadile, Dundee. Cockadile, point down. Anyway, I look forward to seeing both films. I'm curious to
see what my reaction will be to both of them. But I'm looking forward to it. I'm a more excited for
drag to cross concrete, but because I did not like her red it Terry. Well, let's go up and see it at
the arc like this week. I mean, we'll do it on the show. How? Sounds good. That sounds good.
Folks, I'd love to if I may take you over to Pat's movie corner. First off, I'd love to talk to you about
Gaspar Noa's new movie. Gaspar Noa directed one of my favorite movies of recent years.
Enter the void. That movie would not be to everyone's taste, but I fucking love that it's very
experimental. It's a great like recreation of what it feels like to be on drugs. And if you watch
it when you're on drugs, it's incredible. He also did irreversible. That's the last movie I saw of his.
That's a movie. I'll never watch again if you paid me. I found it too sick. I don't know why I stayed.
And when I saw it, an old man in the front row stood up after the first scene, yelled filth and walked
out of the theater. And then he was right. And then that lady went on to play Mary Magdal. And he was
right, Phil. So I approached his new one with some trepidation. It's called climax. So I was like,
oh, here we go. Folks, I love this movie so much. It starts with a 20 minute dance musical number.
Like we're talking like sort of like disco music mixed with a daft punk vibe. These young hot people
dance in for 20 minutes. Some of the coolest choreography I've ever seen. I'm just enjoying the hell out
of it. Then they start following the kids around Robert Altman style, getting you involved in their
little dramas. Little by little, the conversation gets darker and darker. Then they find out somebody's
spiked the punch that everyone's drinking with LSD. So then for the back half of the movie, first
you're like, this is the most fun movie I've ever seen, all the dancing and the singing and the fun.
Then everything goes horrifically awry. So it's the perfect movie to see when you're on drugs
because then it just fucks with you because you're like, oh, what a great movie to see while I'm high.
And then it turns against you violently like a bad trip. I mean, my buddy and I had a great time
loved it. And the come down is so horrifying that people were laughing in parts. She tries to hide
her son because she's like, oh no, all these drug addicts are going to start turning south. I better turn
my eight year old son away and lock him in this little closet. She's like, just stay in here,
but she's fucked up too. So the kids like, mommy, don't lock me in here. Don't lock me in here.
Spoiler, right? No, I won't take it too far. She shuts him in. He's in this room with a big
electrical thing. She's like, don't touch this. She's like, oh, god. So the music's like turning
against you and getting more paranoid and weird. And then you hear the kid. Every time she runs past
the door of the kids in there saying like, mommy, there are cockroaches in here. Mommy, horrifying.
I think it definitely counts as horror, even though it's not a horror movie. It's like 90 minutes.
I had a blast, but again, not after everybody's taste. I don't know how it got on our rating, frankly.
And there were parts of it that felt if I'm being honest, weird and racist. And I don't know if
there was supposed to be a commentary on racism or if Gaspar Noe is racist. And that wouldn't surprise
me either, because the man makes kind of insane films. But whatever, it's a great conversation piece
and it's an incredibly shot movie that I urge you to check out. I read some reviews of the film
that said, I read an article about it that said like, you know, what do you do when the shocker
isn't shocking or whatever? And it was like Gaspar is beside himself that his new film is not
upsetting people. Right. That people actually find that it has some hope in it or whatever.
Yeah. That was his, you know, and I was, and honestly, I didn't know him by name. And I was,
as I was reading the article, I was like, this has to be the guy that made that irreversible movie.
Yeah. And then sure enough, it was. He likes fucking with people. That scene at the top
irreversible where the guy's face gets bashed in with the, that's what that's what got the
cause of the old man to jump up and yell at the screen. I still think maybe we watched a person
actually murdered. Now on the DVD, they, they, there's a vignette where they show you how they did it.
All right. And it makes you feel a little bit better. All right. I've got one thing for the movie
corner this week. I started watching episode, sorry, I started watching season three of channel zero.
I only got through the first episode so far. But boy, oh boy, was it a fun ride? It's got monsters.
It's got supernatural stuff. It's got ghost stories. It's got urban legends.
It's creepy. It's, it's got everything that I like in horror. It's very, very spooky. And I think
that's sort of the best word I could use to describe the type of horror I like. It's, it's setting a
tone for a really fun monster movie ish ride through the season. I look forward to it. I enjoyed
season one of channel zero very much. I did not watch season two. I hear it's great. I will watch it.
But right now I'm on season three because our dear friend Pinkstone called me and said you've got to
watch this first episode. It's so up your alley. And I did. And I loved it. And now I look forward to
seeing the rest of the series season. And then also season four is already out. So I've got, I've
got my work cut out for me here. But I'm more to come on that. Folks, I watched used cars.
A film that Robert Zemeckis and Bob Gale made right before back to the future came out in like
1980. I want to say use cars stars a very young Kurt Russell as a guy trying to like get his
low level use car dealership on the map. Cross the street is the villain played by the great Jack
Warden one of the all time great character actors in a dual role. I know we so we hate dual roles.
But this one really works. He creates two very different characters. The kind of dim -witted younger brother
and the crazy power hungry older brother. These two war and car dealerships fight with each other.
And it all builds to a pretty amazing climax that's kind of like the road warrior where they try to get
a mile they say on a commercial that they have a mile of cars that the lot. But they don't. So in order
to prove that correct they've got to get a bunch of cars like cross country to the lot. It's a great
like third act hook. The movie is action packed. It's funny as shit. It's got some great early 80s
nudity. Kurt Russell is hilarious. I laughed out loud many times. My wife came in from the other
room but halfway through like this movie is fucking great. Sat down and enjoyed it. I highly recommend
used cars. All right. Great new shout select blu -ray of it that looks like they shot it yesterday.
Check it out. Pick it up. All right. I'd like to see that movie. You never seen it? I've never seen it
and I feel like that's killer. That's what oh god. What was that movie with Jeremy Piven that sucked
the goods? I feel like that's what the goods was supposed to be like a nod to that kind of
it was you know and I thought the goods had a couple laughs for some laughs and my buddy Neil
Brennan directed it so I was happy for him but I think overall the movie was not good. Yeah it was
about it. It kind of it kind of fell into the mix of all those you know that was when all the every
movie had those goofy titles like the goods the legend of Ricky Jervaxi or whatever. I almost said
Ricky Jervace. Well speaking of Ricky Jervace went to hop in and do one more. I watched the first
season of Ricky Jervace's after life. I had of course deeply loved the office and I deeply
loved extras and then as they went on I kind of started losing interest. Not that they were
terrible but they just weren't amazing. Then I really dropped out. I didn't even watch Derek. I
thought this seems borderline offensive. I don't want any part of this. It wasn't offensive. It was
just too schmaltzy. Schmaltzy. Yeah it was just like really desperately trying to tug at your
heartstrings but then it would be really funny at times. Right. To be honest I try to not let myself
get sucked away and how annoying Ricky Jervace is in person and online. I still like him as a performer.
When he's not trying so hard to be. Oh cheeky or whatever. Yeah. I love the David Brent movie. I
thought it was hilarious. It was very funny. And after life is a show about a guy who's just basically
an asshole after his wife dies and just a huge asshole and he keeps seeing her like visions of her
drinks too much. He does drugs. He tries to forget his wife. He's an asshole to everybody and then
basically you're watching. Does he or does he not change his ways? And it's a very very simple story.
Very simply told it takes three hours of your time to watch the entire season. I don't feel it was
time wasted. I don't feel it was any sort of classic but it's entertaining. It's funny. It's
Jervace it is most likeable in quite some time. Although there are about 8 ,000 too many jokes about
Twitter trolls and you're like Ricky. Not everybody in the world has Twitter trolls. Step away
from Twitter. I have no interest in seeing it. I'm a Ricky Jervace fan for the most part.
You did Derek but you're not going to do after life. I did some of Derek. I didn't do all of it
because look I think the first really good thing he made when it was with Stephen Merchant and it was
life too short with Warwick Davis. I like life too short. But I felt that I felt that you know look
it's the it's the sum is greater than is greater than the parts and I really enjoyed hey ladies
but it was missing. I really like Tello ladies a lot. Hello ladies excuse me but it was missing to
me the bite of Ricky Jervace and I liked Derek but it was missing to me the bounce that Stephen
Merchant brings into it. So you know them without one another and it's the same thing I enjoyed the
the David Brent movie as I said that was very funny but it it becomes so small to you know and there's
it's he he he wants to be Robin Williams he makes these things now where they're funny and then there's
a scene where you're supposed to cry right and I felt that this new movie was a very cliched like
or this new TV show looked like at least and I it might be wrong and I'll watch it if I you know
I'll give it a shot well I can't because I'm a Netflix but what I saw in these trailers was look to
me like a sort of a Malcolm of Ricky Jervace cliches like I'm going to play the guy that has the sharp
thing to say about humanity and kind of hates everybody from the outside right a darker Larry David
we've seen him do that many times and then behind it will be this backdrop of sorrow and tears
so you're supposed to feel sorry for him and you're supposed to learn how to feel love and it
I just was like this just look small to me man yeah you know it looked like a dark you know Chris
Columbus movie to me but but you know if I ever have Netflix again maybe I'll check it out
uh I've got a uh scary stuff for the fans go for it
video game this week uh I was lucky enough to find a copy of this for $38 it's hard to come by for
that price but I found one on Mara McCarrie which is a great site if you're trying to you know kind
of get eBay type of shopping going on without using eBay every time I can really highly recommend
McCarrie I found some amazing amazing deals on collectibles on there uh all kinds of stuff but it
seems like it really shines with collectibles and when it comes to video games I've found some great
great deals and I got a game for the Sega Genesis called Castlevania Bloodlines obviously a hard
base game uh look for hardcore gamers out there you know what this game is and for casual Castlevania
fans I would say this was a hidden gem it was the only Castlevania ever to come out on a Sega system
and it's fucking amazing it is an amazing amazing entry into the side scrolling Castlevania series uh
it's of that time it's the 16 -bit generation the animations are gory and fun the monsters are
well designed the game the settings and and level designs are are intriguing and it's hard as
fuck like most Castlevania games but I can't recommend this thing enough I think it's a great game and
if you can get your hands on a copy of it affordably you know usually you see it for around 50 bucks
cartridge only like I said I grabbed one for $38 by the graces of the gods but you know some
between 40 and 50 bucks you can probably find a card only if you're looking for a complete
inbox if you're you're talking some serious cash at that point way more than I'd be willing to
spend for a Genesis cartridge but um check it out it's a lot of fun it's a lot of fun and it'll have
you laughing giggling gasping and yelling things like you fucking cock sucker at the TV because you'll
die over and over and over again uh but it's still enjoyable and there's your scary stuff
okay yeah I don't think you're supposed to use cock sucker as a uh negative
is that bad now too yeah
I mean what what what words what what what what what what what what what what what what what what what
curse words like assholes that bad now because we all have assholes assholes fun
I mean cock sucker it's it's everybody's a cock sucker it's it's a pretty general thing
there's no it doesn't really apply to just one it's got a connotation preference it's got a
connotation the uh I'm just trying to keep you honest I am honest that's my problem I tell it like
it is uh what else is going on in your life are you happy inside uh
yeah yeah yeah I'm feeling pretty good these days works good uh stand -ups good my set is very
good right now tight very tight I'm very proud of the stuff I'm doing right now it's I'm very happy
with it and the audience has seemed to like it so that's a good thing you still doing the uh the
airline peanut bit come on Pat come on you doing the airline stuff what if I am what if I was
no I just I thought I told you you should challenge yourself a little bit more
we started doing a new biweekly show Brian Moses and myself at the comedy store called our show
oh you are show uh it's every other Wednesday at the comedy store in the belly room we did our first
one the other night uh it went off great uh Morgan Murphy did a set she was wonderful funny lady
Beth Stelling did a set she was wonderful big fan of both Andrew Santino did a set don't know him
he's hilarious he was he was on he was on him dying up here yeah uh uh and uh uh uh uh uh
Eddie Pepitone oh kick things off the game so uh the dark master when I was on stage I said uh at the
top of the show I said look the reason we're doing the show is because we want to have an a -list
show where a -listers can come in and and work out right we don't have enough of that open
micers have a million bar shows and they all trade spots and they'll get all the stage time and they
can experiment and work I go we don't have that all of our things are like you got to get booked
and then you're paid and then you can't fuck around I'm like we just want to have a loose show where
our friends can come in and just have a good time and work out and uh it was a lot of fun before
Pepitone went on stage I leaned in jokingly obviously and said don't fuck this up with your bullshit
and uh so then he went on stage and he was like uh he goes derosa was up here he says this is a
place for people to experiment you know what he says to me before I go on stage he says don't fuck up
how is that conducive to experimentation it was very funny uh we had a we had a really good time
folks we've talked about Pepitone a lot but if you want too great comedians to seek out I've worked
with both of these ladies and they're incredibly funny and decent human beings Beth Stelling Morgan
Murphy check their stuff out online go see their live shows yeah all right yeah I'd like you to plug
me like that once in a while I do you know I do you go around town you say my buddy I do go see
Joe Derosa they go I got a thing that night I go I didn't say what night they go even so I didn't say
what night I think you said Wednesday Saturday Friday the door shut and they turned around to go
schmuck you're you're door to door selling my yeah he's got a hot chunk
Joe do do the chunk the new chunk we're both sweating
pitting out our shirts oh boy come on come relax buddy come on uh my buddy and I were laughing
the other day my buddy kept saying it sounds nice what's that you and your buddy laughing
together laughing my buddy kept saying he he thought that there should be a parody of
that out in john song called don't let your son go down on me okay he kept saying that on the phone
and I was making me laugh because I have a sense of humor of a two -year -old yeah uh but then I said it
be funny there'd be that'd be a great scene in a movie where you get the actual weird out and a
character meets him at a party he's like you know I was one of the I was one of the pitch you one of
those songs that you do I think they're free whatever this don't let your son go down on but you
know he's just pitching him the most filthy thing the weird house is like yeah yeah yeah sure
Barbara strives in to send me a more screaming in woo today she goes she says about the Michael
Jackson thing woo those kids wanted to be there they were thrilled to be there thrilled and Michael
wanted what he wanted and why not give it to him it was one of the craziest things I've ever seen
it's 11 said his needs were his needs she's pro pedophile because of the way he was brought up
and nobody died just a hot take why come out with that take just stay home stay home well look
she's 80 years old she's living in a fucking castle somewhere she's losing her goddamn mind you can't
live at there's a reason why people this famous fuck up in one way or another they're you can't live
in that mindset for that long no especially when you start to get old and you start to really think like
you've been around the block enough that you know what the score is like sick town sick people
it's they only get sicker it's nuts dude and now James Brolin's like well there goes the goods too
I'm not gonna be in that I guess you just fucked it up honey because he was in the goods one yeah
but Piven fucked it up more than one now yeah but yeah he's another one it's like it's like
these people nobody is saying no to them and I don't mean I don't just mean like Piven sells out
stand -up shows all over town oh god can't even I heard I heard recently he said to somebody I think
I got this I get it yeah it's like oh god and then I heard Will Smith is doing stand -up now
oh brazen answer brazen answer can you guys not do anything
is there one thing you don't have to get your hand into to let somebody else who's working really hard
make some fucking money I mean unbelievable man you got Donnie Wahlberg pimping AT &T you got
what's her face selling fucking Hilton hotels now the short one from all the movies
who let's stop right there who are you trying to sell the short one from all the movies what are
you my brand -bapping real tiny lady that's in all the movies that aren't that good old young I
said on the podcast once they go she looks like if you're cousin got famous Anna Kendrick oh my god
Anna Kendrick you said it on this very podcast yeah that's not a fault she she she she's fucking
selling Hilton it's like guys can you take a breath you got George Clooney selling fucking coffee
and coffee machines it's like guys keep telling me the middle class isn't dissolving as as these
fucking celebrities take every job that a struggling artist was able to get at one point in their lives
he got fucking Jeremy Piven booking like the ha ha hutch it's like a place that was supposed to be
for the people that failed in this business and now he's going in it's like dude
unfucking believable man they're so fucking greedy and then they get on TV and go Trump what a pig
yeah you're you're real different you're not living in this capitalist fucking disgusting culture you're
not adding to it at all it's Christ what we're gonna be like broadcasts out of YouTube
maybe before you know it why you're gonna be like an Alex Jones type why because I'm criticizing
celebrities taking these jobs from people I just I see you going that way the route of a man who
screams annually into a webcam in about five years not not soon but in about five years you were
furious today about what were you yelling about on the podcast earlier the guy in front of me I go
to buy tickets for us to go see Cypress Hill tonight you buy him on Saturday morning you don't
pay service charges in this case we would have saved about 30 bucks 15 a piece that's four extra
drinks you know I'll take that trip beautiful day I'm waiting in line all fucking morning they have
one person working there finally the guy in front of me takes 20 plus minutes and he's just scrolling
through they sell tickets for three different venues Saturday morning no service fees he's going
let me get one for dito what's the max tickets you can buy for dito eight yeah give me eight then
on to the next one there was that really how he talked Engelbird Humperdenk yeah get me what's the max
is are you being are you doing a diplomatic voice right now I'm not doing any sort of voice it was
that no I'm saying are you not doing a voice because he had a voice if you don't want to do the voice
I don't remember what the man's voice was okay okay but it was a nightmare they would not stop his
total was like over a thousand dollars and the line's getting impatient and finally I'm like I got
to go I just left after waiting in line for over an hour I got so frustrated I just left and I said
it's easier to not leave your house to not engage with human beings and that's not a fun revelation to
have folks but it's where you're at it's where this world is that all right damn it
why does he if you got one line up and why does he get 30 minutes when he's clearly just a scalper I
thought you were gonna now I thought you were gonna one up me and not do an Alex Jones thing and you
went down the Alex Jones Road I thought you were gonna make me look dumb by not doing it but you did
it the uh yeah he was a scalper he said he said as well said I'm a scalper as you
walks up as he walks up the lady behind the counter goes hey jam or whatever good to see it like
she sees him every Saturday he buys all the tickets that have gone on sale and it's like yeah but what
about all these people who are waiting here kindly the reason I asked if he had a voice was I've never
met a scalper a bulk scalper that didn't have a accent now I'm not putting the accent on any one
group of people I'm just saying there's always some accent involved that's all I'm saying yes is that
bad to say I don't know I don't know what you can say anymore I'm walking away from it I'm walking away
from it whoa now folks uh we talked a few weeks back about West Craven's original hills have eyes I
watched it on Joe Bob Briggs's show I must admit I was let down by it uh it wasn't particularly
scary to me I didn't think it had a lot of atmosphere I didn't think the cast really worked well
the remake I remember seeing in theaters I remember it being a little gross from my taste
watching it this time it went down smooth I watched an unrated version um I know it's a well -loved
movie it just didn't do much for me I thought it was well shot it moved certainly it had good pacing
I guess but at the end of the day this isn't what I need to revisit what did you think Joe
I thought I thought it was a import taste that all of the mutiny deformed people from nuclear
waste weren't played by actual mutiny deformed people by nuclear waste I thought that was some of
them seem to be though I thought that was a bit of whitewashing if you will sure uh no I thought
it you look it was okay it's better than the original it is better than the original and like you
know you can just freely say that like granted the other one may have uh opened a door or something
or might have been novel at the time but sometimes you look back at the shit and you're like yeah but
it's no good now sorry uh this moves a lot better it's more entertaining I thought it was a more
entertaining version there were certain choices in it I didn't quite understand um or I didn't like
I should say was it the use of God smack over the end credits that was my favorite part God what a
shitty time for music uh I actually saw God smack in concert once because they opened for Metallica and
they were pretty good actually I was surprised that that I liked it as much as I do I'm not the one who
so far we when you feel the sneak bite into my view I can't see sounds like share I couldn't
I couldn't tell you one God smack song I just remember they put on a decent show um if that is God
smack and I think it is I actually I take back what I said because that song as I'm singing it I just
realized what's fucking awesome and I do remember why you're keen there is a belly dancer vibe to
God smack I will yeah uh look eating some uh some hummus with some friends you know who cares baby but
then they also had you know like all those bands had those I tried so hard you know they go
into that shit Lincoln Park ship all right he is in a mood today can I not be in a mood
oh can I not express myself can I not express myself this is you sure that's pot you smoked yeah
yeah
Hills have eyes well wait let me let me tell you where I was gonna I was gonna say what I didn't like
go ahead made some new they made some changes that I didn't think worked as well and they they
took away from the sympathy you had for the family the dad being an asshole dad Levine I thought I
liked him in this movie yeah but he's he's not supposed to be likable he's not supposed to be
likable debatable it's he's not all the kids are walking around going fucking Republican and he's like
right why don't you have a gun what are you pussy you know like he's not supposed to be a likable
character true I guess that's true um and then the wife being sort of the kept Kathleen Quinlan Academy
award nominee for Apollo 13 in a great underrated thriller with Kurt Russ called breakdown check it out
she's she's great but she's sort of playing this sort of kept she's been a bit of a kept character
where she's kind of like oh John yeah she don't get much to do so that's you know it so right off
the bat you don't like the parents as much as you do and you don't feel as bad for them I guess you
could say um and then the son who's married to the woman who's got the kid it's like within two scenes
as soon as she's not with him anymore he's talking to the little brother going fuck your sister
right and like really cut it and I'm like why why is everybody unhappily married in this because
that that theme is not explored at all right it's not like Kate Fearwell that's like half the story is
that you know the the lawyer and his wife and their marriage troubles and all that is half the movie
they're just using it for ship so I guess it's supposed to be some sort of commentary on like hey the
the typical American family has their dark side too and you know Wes Craven said with the
original film it was supposed to be about this is what people will will reduce themselves to when
put up against it who are the real monsters that whole thing lord of the flaws yeah which I never
got out of any of it I mean it's like if you've got maniacs trying to murder you you might fight back
you know it's not gonna kill the maniacs before they kill you yeah you're not becoming sadistic at that
point right you're just like you know you're just kind of fighting back but um I uh so so some of
those writing choices I thought were not great but I did think it was very well shot it was well
shot thought it was much betterly betterly wow holy shit I thought it was the structure of the film
was much better it made more sense they gave you some insight into well how does this work how do
these people survive and like connecting the gas station owner to the family in the hills helping
them trap the families and I thought that was really cool I love the reveal of the of the abandoned
car lot where they're stashing all the families cars yeah um little stuff like that was cool uh the
the nuclear the fact that the nuclear like testing town was still there and that's what they lived
in I thought was cool I thought the makeup was very good the mutants were cool and very disturbing I'll
give them that that one that's in the wheelchair that just goes that's rough yeah that one's that one
was the most upsetting uh but for me I mean in terms of these kind of movies and they made a bunch
of these updates especially at around this time mid -2000s the gold standard is the dawn of the dead
remake Zack Snyder's dawn of the dead is Zack Snyder's one truly great movie written by James gun uh
masterpiece that's the gold standard this is nowhere near that it felt like a very perfunctory remake it
felt you know even the stuff that I looked at because I watched the unrated cut and I'm like what
depravities am I gonna watch when I looked up what changed it was like none of it bothered me to
disturb me I guess I'm just getting a harder uh exterior but uh I don't know um it wasn't it wasn't
as shocking as I think it wanted to be I'll say I say maybe at the time it was who knows you know
we're we're we're we're about 15 years past the release of this movie at this point but uh you know
the the other thing is too is um the I thought it was an odd choice that the father um big daddy
whatever the fuck he was called um Papa John I believe Papa John right and he sang in a band called
Blues Traveler uh no the the the main you know the in the original film it's big it's it's not big
mama but her name's mama mama something I can't remember and in this movie it's Papa something
it's a guide's that and it's the guy that plays of course it is right it's the right lady of course
it is it's the guy that plays uh uh he's in the untouchables and he plays Frank Nitty uh I'm
blanking on his nose Martin Smith no Kevin Costner no Sean Connery it was Sean Connery in the Hills
have eyes remake it was Dell close uh no Andy Garcia I forget the guy's name but I'm a fan he's
he's a kind of a weird sort of idiosyncratic actor but I like what he does but anyway he plays like
the the leader of the mutant cult but he's not mutated at all in any way so I thought that was kind
of strange the guy in the original no no in this remake the guy at the end that they end up blowing
up in the trailer oh yeah okay he's not mutated at all right like everybody else is so mutated
yeah give this guy something you know like give him a weird eye or something you know give this guy
something folks that's all we're saying uh unless I guess all the other mutants were his kids I
don't know anyway uh this is you know for that for that time of horror movie you generally got
something like this an updated sicker version of an older movie where he got something just
unwatchably grotesque like captivity or something more like a beautiful young girl is being tortured
in a basement for two hours that was very popular in the mid -2000s uh I never get into that shit
other than hostile hostels about as much torture point as I like I love hostile one but then hostile
two and three uh are very whatever I didn't see three I like two though oh I hate two I love
three better than two three I think is better than two I hate it too I thought two lost everything
that made the first one great which was which which was you realize at the end of the first one what
you're watching is this very tense escape adventure it's not torture porn it's got moments of very
grotesque imagery no hostile becomes one of the most exciting action movies of my lifetime it's it's
great and then two is literally just now we're gonna show it from the perspective of the people that
kill them you know like well that's not what well while I don't agree with that choice and I don't
think it holds a candle I don't think two is without merit um and I didn't see three three is better than
two I think but you you would disagree with me I think I feel like but I like three got back a little
more to just what the first one was three's not Eli Roth right no okay he just produced it but I
mean look in Eli Roth I'm sorry I respect the man and I like some of what he does he falls into a
long history of directors where when they do something great like hostile one you watch their other
stuff and I'm stepping back going does this guy even know why this was good right I mean he's never
he's never paralleled that at all yeah you know so it's it's you know not to knock them but
uh but anyway uh I do like the history of horror I think that's pretty cool that not to knock
him like knock knock the other Eli Roth movie that recently came out is that Eli Roth I like that
movie so there was a nice little like I think that's where he he should thrive now is like doing little
thrillers and horror pictures he's great at him yeah yeah he he tried to go too big with like the
green and furno and and I think green and furno was not my bag at all I watched that and wished I had
in fact isn't Kathleen Quinlan in hostile too doesn't she play the woman with the sickle that
like bays in the blood or whatever that doesn't sound right to me but maybe she was man dynamite
in that doors flick I love Quinlan and uh yeah again one of the best of those mid 90s thrillers is
breakdown with JT Walsh my name's sake one of the great character actors Kurt Russell and Kathleen
Quinlan the biggest role JT Walsh ever had really he got to be the villain and damn it's fun have
you seen breakdown Joe no it is fucking great I think I think I have I had the DVD you can probably
buy it on Amazon for three bucks you can probably download it for five bucks or whatever it is for you
for free you can borrow it from me yes it is such a great fucking thriller it's not even on blu -ray
but uh seek it out well worth it I remember it came out about the same time as scream so all the cool
people wanted to go see scream it was sold out I slid over to break down I had the time of my
goddamn life whoa whoa whoa Patty we haven't done our shout outs yet for this month here we go with
them right now AF broad Bradstone Aaron Malinowski Aaron Roberts Abby Manuel Abram Wright Adam
Benbenek Adam Lownsbury Alejandro Salgado Alex Lowe Alex Nelson Alex Shipley Alexander
oh god this is not showing us the full names oh there it is Alexander Monter Rubio
all right can you could you have said it faster better Alexander Stein Alexander Thomas
Alice Ryan Amanda Alzumora Amanda Lancaster Amanda Lebson Andrew Andrew Koval Andrew
Telchin Jesus Christ Angela Porcaro and a Demario and he Joe Hanson Anthony Rodriguez
Anthony Guajardo Anthony Guajardo a double donor amazing thank you double dip in ant we
call him Ash Ogden Ashley McCarty Asla Kavinsland August Kamella Barbell and Bo Ben Benmedi Ben Wright Ben
a Dick Beck Bessie Telefero Beth Gaston Brandon Kool it's coming up handsome fun it's worth it
Brandon Gash, Braden Love, Breton Fraser, Bret Urway, Bret Friendjella, Bret Warner, Brian Bollaria,
Brian Callis, Brian Shactor, Brooke Adams take it back Joe.
One of the next page. As always blown away by the amount of donors.
Absolutely. Bryce Buckmaster that's an awesome name. Casey Jones, Casey Sturgeon, Charity Ferguson,
Chase Ophus, Chloe Paget, Chris Bowen, Chris Hopper, Chris Larson, Chris Passmore, Christian Reynolds,
Christopher Klinger, Christopher Musil, Christopher Sibelha, Chuck Andrews, Sinji Clayton Stamper,
Cole Rothiker, Comedians of Wrestling, Connor Denehy, Dan Smith,
Dajane Whitford, hello Dajane, Dan Hapanawhits, Dan McLeod, Daniel Paschal, Daniel Rivera,
Daniel Duer, Danny Rudd, Daphne Kellogg, Dave Del Greco, Dave DeWitt, Dave Walk,
David Bellinger, David Denehy, David Crumholtz,
Demonio Rubio, Dennis Ormston, Derek Klesmer, Derek Adams, Devlow, Diego Campos, Drew
Tiberius Pol, that's another hefty name, Duke of Swirl, Edmund Agabbo, Edmund Dillon,
Edward Gray, Elva E. Enriquez, Emily Florence, hi, Emily Griffith, Emma Lee Marvel,
Patty, it's going back to you. I'll take it from here. I'd like to give a special shout out to
Nicolai, who I saw in the bar before I went in and saw us. He said he was a huge fan of the pod,
made my day. I wished you had done it in front of my friend so I would have looked cool,
but unfortunately he was in the bathroom. I forgot to tell you,
I'm supposed to remind you to give a shout out to Nicolai. I just did thanks, Jim. So here we go,
Eric Lamora, Ethan Gammage, Evan Barrett, fucking rich, till
fun, Gabriella King, Gary Milron, Myron, Glenn Beesman's, Haley Twist,
Hank from Dance Cakes, Stan Cakes, Hannah Perez,
Hey, Samantha Kiefer, we're married now, crazy, sweet. That's very nice congrats.
Hey, sport, Coca -Cola. Oh, that's from Kingpin. Yeah.
Coca -Cola, Hunter McDonald, Heighton Davidson, Isaac D. Lorenzo, Jackie Aldis,
Jackson C. Lomire, Jacob Barrett, Jake Bullock, Jake Farot, Jake McAlvane, James O 'Brien,
Janet C. Jared Blair, Jared Pacquan, Jared Smallridge, Jason Weeble,
Jay Miller, Jayden Brady, Jed Patton, Jeff Henry, Jen Wessels, Jennifer Anna,
Jennifer Smith, Jeremy Kool, Jesse Janicki, Joe Hoffman, Joe Kennedy, Joe Miller,
Joe's super secret fiancee. What? John B. Watt. John B. Watt, visit the
zombie and horror crafts store on Etsy. Yes, John. John Devers, John and B .K. John Smith,
John Hollywood, John Wiesen Gruber, Jonathan Jolotte, Jonathan Sprouls, Jordan C. Jordan Parker,
and those also check out the Hoghouse page on Etsy where Emily Florence has a lot of merch from
this show. Joe? Joseph Regosa, Josh Smallridge. Whoa,
Josh Smallridge, Joshua Christensen, Joshua Taj Bozeman, Julie Aguire, Julie Bailey,
Justin Boagger, Justin Tyler, KP Flynn, Kara Konini, Karen Kell -Garrett, go give my favorite
murderer a listen. Katrina Elise Gozen, Kelly Amaroso, Kelsey, Kevin Marcenick, Kevin McNanny,
Kevin Riggote, Kevin Sorbo. Could it be? Could it be? All right. Now, that's somebody
changed the name because look, he's donated for months now. We've never seen a Kevin Sorbo so you
so far. Kevin Stickers at PINTServices .com, Kevin Swistowicz, Keel Kyle Kinsland, Laura Johnson,
Leo Lopez, Lindy West. Who knew? She was a fan. Lauren Sanderson, Lorenz Bunganiers,
Luke Fizziak, Lupe Pita Pacheo, Manny Rios, Marcus Magahi, Marcus Podlich, Martin Murray,
Matt Matt Chairs, Matt Crawford, Matt Murphy, Matt Robyn, Matt J. Brown, Matthew Moon,
Matthew Peterson, Max Unrath, Megli Brand, Melinda Ring, Meredith McWilliams,
Michelle Aiello, Michael Aiello. Oh, Michael, sorry, Michael Aiello, Michael Bolas, Michael
Burke, Michael Dawson, back to you, Pat. Got it. I'm going to continue with Michael Madrigal,
Michael Rios. Wait, wait, I got to plug Mike's store. Go to Mr. Shoot Records and Lancaster.
Pennsylvania. Do it. Michael Rios, Michael Ruayne, Michelle Gold, Mike Cook, Mike Curry,
my old friend, Mike Curry, Mike Gibbons, Mike Grant, Mike Greenwood, Mike Willis,
Minky Tinkles, hog wallop, Misty Zavar, Monty Buckles, Mori Benjamin, Natalie Hartley,
Natalya Hartley, Nat Tilly Craig, Nat Tilly Heartline, Nathan Baskett, Nick Beck Beck,
Nicholas Burns, Nicholas Edward, Nicholas McCall, Nicholas Edward Fallon Allbeck,
Nicholas McCausland, Nicholas Uey, Nick Weather, Nicole Quinn, Nopt, Medium -Rae, famous story.
Ani Babaduke, Oh, Nana Miss Boner, Papa Spouche, Pat Flanagan, Patrick Baxter,
Patrick C. Brenner, Patrick Driscoel, my old friend. Hey, Pat, Patrick Weythan,
Paul Fucking Pig Person Merchie, Pauline Surrell, Peeve, Phil Barrell,
Philip Rashad, Preston Anderson, Purple Peacock, Rain, Rebecca, Rebecca Cohen,
Reggie Lastname Spounds Asian, Rich Caldwell, Richard Deming, Richard Howinstein,
Richie Verdugo, and RJ Killman Joe. We're in the home stretch here. Rob Lines, Rob M,
Robert Haynes, Robert Moran, Robert Nesbitt, Rocky Hawks, Ronan Farrity, Ryan P. Hall,
Hi, Ryan, Sam Mitchell, Sam Mitchell's, extra -wide socks, Sam Street, Samantha Dagenau,
Scott Blikensdurfer, Scott George, Scott John, Scott Nolan, Scott Patton, Sean Floring,
Sean Hall, Sean L, Sean Lyle, Sean Thomas, Seaman Demon, that's a good one. Shane Nazarene,
Sharifa, Sean Pinnock, Shelby L, Sophia Anderson, Stefan Musau, Stephanie Power,
Steppenwolf, Gang Bang, Sterling Abrego, Steve Burton, Steve Smith, supportive guy,
TJ Spellney, T .L. Mohalen, Tanner Rollins, Tanning Chatham, who knew? Taylor, the blank magic ninja,
the block watch, Thomas Braille, Christensen, Tim Drain, Timmy Kay, Timothy Letzo, Tom,
Tom Holt, Tom Laverick, Tom Van Curin, and I think this is the final page.
Tom C. Zonjick, Tom C. Zonjick, sorry I was off mic, Tracy Reddington, Travis Hines,
Tristan Avery, Truth Crab, Vera Shrankun, Vincent Franks, Violet, Your Turning Violet, Violet,
Waffles, Wallace O. Fetzer, Weston Thomas, Hividjid, Will Helms, Will Nolton,
you missed this guy. Wild card bitches, sorry, Will Pittman, Will Potorff, Zachary Martinez,
Zoe Blaskevich, folks we are humbled. Thank you for your support of the show,
at times when we seem busy or whatever else. We do not forget you. It is what keeps it going.
Of course, we're never doing this. For the money, it's been free for a very long time,
but it really helps. It helps put us back in these seats week after week. It gives us a little
incentive. Thank you so much for your support. We're glad you loved the show as much as we love
putting it out. That's our show. John Arosa comedy on Instagram. I'm in Vegas this weekend,
Friday and Saturday night at Topgolf doing shows one per night. New story, menu change,
available now in the March slash April issue of Pat House.
Dates coming up in April, I'll be at the Valley Forge Casino. Mid April, I'll be in Milwaukee,
Wisconsin at the something or other casino in April and I'll be at Moon Tower at the end of the month.
When will you have time for us, Joe? The review? Menu. There's going to be time. There'll be time.
All right, I'm on Instagram, Twitter, at the Patrick Walsh. If you go to that Vegas show,
I think the odds are pretty good. You're going to see me. I'm going to decide here shortly.
We'll see you next time. We'll see you on the Patreon with our review of us, if you're interested,
and we'll see you in hell!