Hello everyone. Hello. Welcome to we'll see you in hell. It's me. The podcast is now part of the Fangoria podcast network
For more information about the network including other programs how to follow this show in five past episodes
We'll visit
Korea .com now on with the show and I was singing Hello by Adele in the background. I thought
You were singing we just had a convert not you and I but I talked to somebody
About hello and it was the Lionel Ritchie. Well, yeah, they were saying like Adele now owns like hello
Whereas he doesn't own it not own it
But you know what I mean like that was Lionel Richie's she's she's leasing a sizable part of the house, but she doesn't own it
No, Richie owns it baby. I think she's got a lot more than Richie
father of
Nicole Richie I never noticed until right now that his the root word of his name is Lion
And and to be honest with all the plastic surgery
Hey man smokey Robinson look like lions. Yeah, like majestic lionesses. There's a little lioness a lioness a lioness
There's a little lioness thing about them that makes them look lioness lioness like yeah
folks love them both and
Oh, well, yeah, go ahead. Let's tell people what they're listening to before I tell my smoky Robinson story
Well, they know what we're listening to and we're in one ear
I'm in one ear pats in the other and you know why because you play the movie if you want up the middle and
That's just how this goes, okay, so you can listen to this with us or without us
Well, no, not without us you have to listen to with with us
But you can listen to it with the movie or without the movie and if you didn't want to hear us then you just watch the movie today
We're doing the woman in black
Starring Daniel Radcliffe, which is the remake never seen the original, but I would like to
Have you ever seen the original? I didn't know it was it's an old like hammer movie, right?
Yeah, but the remake is also by hammer. I meant starring MC hammer
He did that action movie with DMX called two legit two quip. Yeah, yeah
So that's the time if you want to line it up pop your DVD in
Find it on we're on Amazon Prime today. It might be on Netflix
I don't know, but if you want to queue it up now is where you stop our podcast can get your movie queue it up and
Now that you're all cute up
We're gonna do a count off we do it at one two three four three four play
Wait, but I know yet now I'm gonna lean forward to hit play you count it off. Okay, then I'll hit play
I'm not saying one two three four. I'm gonna say one two three play you give the first ever four count off
Here we go folks one two three
Yeah, we're rolling woman in black. We got some sort of CBS logo coming up
Is that CBS like the TV station? It is they they stuck their hand into a few films and they do pretty well actually did they yeah
Really they do now
I have to change the sad sound output because I just realized it's not correct
And that's why we can't hear anything so talk for a moment would you pet absolutely?
I'm gonna tell the smoky Robinson story so if you get a chance to see Smoky Robinson before he passes away
Which may be a while because it looks like he's been embalmed or
You know it frozen in time something like that, but we go to see Smoky Robinson at the Hollywood Bowl
He's got the same amazing voice songs sound incredible
But between the songs
This son of a bitch had the funniest band trip I've ever heard of my life
Funnier than most stand up, and I'm looking right at judo so what I'm saying this
Funnier than most stand up, but he gets up there and
He goes folks. This is off my new album
Fire and ice
It's only available at crack a bear and the audience like laughs hysterically and he goes oh no, no, I'm quite serious
It's only available at cracker, but we looked it up this album was only available on cracker, bro
But he had a sense of humor, but you do you think he was trying to be funny when he said that he was definitely trying to be fun
Okay, then he goes folks up
We got we're gonna do one more now off my new album the title again is fire and ice
Right he looks out of the crowd the crowd of silent and he goes oh, thank you both
His his one liners were destroying the crowd. He was making fun of himself. He looked ridiculous
He sang like a damn angel. Where the hell did you see Smokey Robinson? I saw him at the Hollywood Bowl
Which is how the story started? I wasn't listening because I was fixing the volume. Yeah, it's fine
It was great. He's one of the funniest men I've ever seen you just went to see
Smokey Robinson headline the Hollywood Bowl. Yeah, you're a two ago
I also saw the Reverend Al Green at the Greek theater and he was amazing as well now does he still sing like let's get it on and like the sex tunes
Let's stay together. Let's get it on as Marvin Gaye. Oh, that's right. He's saying some songs about you know
Making love to your woman not fucking her. You know what I mean?
Yeah, but that's not what he was singing about back in the 70s. No, no, he was singing about fucking
But what I recommend people is if you get a chance like a lot of times
You'll see or wreath of Franklin's coming to town and you're like oh, man
It'd be cool as your wreath of Franklin, but you don't buy that ticket and they're gonna die
Very soon and you're gonna wish that you were going to see him
So I go see Al Green. I go see Chuck Berry when I'm in St. Louis. You go see all these people because then when they die
You've seen a piece of American history and if you put it off too long, they're gonna die
That's how I thought when I saw Elton John
Absolutely, he probably did all the hits, right? It was wall -to -wall hits
Not including can you feel the love tonight? Thank God. Oh, yeah
It was not a hit it was wall -to -wall every song you ever wanted to hear
He was tremendous. He was wearing a jack. He was wearing the captain fantastic jacket nice nice, which was awesome
He opened with the bitches back
Sure, he's the bitch. I think he is right. I think that's what that means, right? Did he say Saturday?
Saturday, yeah, that's his most rocking song. I think that might have been the encore
I love that like that's his toughest song and he's like breaking beer bottles over people's heads and stuff
But then in the second verse he's like
Admiring his sister's wardrobe
And you're like oh, I think this guy might be lying about all the macho stuff
The uh, he's like my sister looks good in her braces and boots. So it's like come on Elton
He did is he did the most focus on the fights
He did one of the most ballsy not ballsy like like cock rock moves. I've ever seen in a rock show and I loved it. Yeah
Uh, the second song was Benny in the Jets
Benny
And all he did was this he just went
boom
And stood up and from the one chord everybody started going crazy
Sure, and I was like how awesome is that when you
How awesome is that when you can do that? Yeah
I'm gonna do the one chord and he stood up and looked at everybody like yeah
Fuck you. It was great. It was great. It's like uh when I saw the Baja man they all go who
Same thing right five minute because you know let the dogs out is coming yeah
And then when they let those dogs out Joe the sad part is old dogs
I would I didn't even I wasn't sure if you were kidding or not because you've seen every goddamn concert that comes
You're telling I wouldn't be that surprised if you wanted to see the bar. I wouldn't go see the bar. Oh man
Right now when I sell in John. He's saying Benny and the June's
I don't get this in the June's we've discussed it on the show
It's a movie with Johnny Depp and Mary Stewart Masters Benny and oh Benny and June. I thought you're doing a play on Jets
No like that there was some correlation between Junes and Jets and I for a minute I thought you said Junes
These are Jews it made me uncomfortable. Sure. That's not what you said though
As you're watching the film with us by the way Daniel
I mean this is the most we've just completely disregarded a film. Thank you for reminding me as if I was a listener that we're watching a film
I mean we haven't called one bit of attention to it
We're in the scene now where Harry Potter is
Sitting with uh, he's always just gonna be Harry Potter poor bastard. He's sitting with the guy
Cutting the cigar and they're talking about
Something I actually very much like this film. I've seen it before and you have to you just painted quite a picture
That's gonna make people want to turn it. I mean Harry Potter saw going to this guy who's cutting a cigar or something
Hard enough to speculate on who this guy is. He's a ledger or something
A ledger's a book. He's Heath ledger, but he's like a lawyer. It's his boss or he's got a lot of books and things
I don't know one of these English guys. It's probably a ledger. I picture every guy in England having a room like this
Oh sure with paintings and cigars books. Yeah, rugs probably yeah a desk
Yeah, I
I always admired the English I think it seems like a very nice life. I did so I went to this part of the other night and this guy
Uh was British very handsome gentleman. He starts talking and this entire room
Just stops milling about and talking just stares at him while he talks the women like
The hottest woman there made a b -line for him the second she could like they it's a very sexy thing and we don't have it
We sound boring. I love the English accent and English accent on a woman and I find to be terribly sexy and on a man
Even sexier. I just find it pompous usually and boring, but this guy was
I love it. I love the accent
Then you got your Australian accent which is sort of a rough and tumble good day, mate
That's normal cousin. That's a shrimp bobby
Right yes, uh, that's the quote yeah
Uh
Now do you find that I have some sort of Southern accent or Missouri accent because I get told it by some friends
But not that all if if that by that you mean do I think you sound like a dumbass. Yeah. Yeah
Okay, like a real American dumbass. Yeah, when you talk. I'm like he sounds like a fucking podunk dumbass
Every word is it is an eternity. Just shut up. Well like kid rock. I'm an American badass
No, I don't hear that with you and that's my and I'm joking of course about the South
I got quite an affinity for the South. I'm from the Midwest and I'm also a fan of the South will rise again
I'm a fan of the Southern accent as well
Not that I'm not a fan of it on a man, but I date women and I find it on a woman to be quite sexy
I'll take a Southern accent over British accent on a lady
That's why Holly Hunter was my favorite gal in movies for many years
How these sexist woman alive Holly is a little too
Like like like auto shop for me. Yeah, it's a little for doing it turn to the right. Yeah, it's a little too hard for me
I think she's the best, but I think she's a lovely woman
She's in the suicide squad. No, no, she's in Superman Batman. Yeah, which I'm excited to see you just saw Hail Caesar
I did
Last night I saw
Hail Caesar and I liked it and what happens more and more with these cone brothers movies
Is I'm sitting there. I'm enjoying the hell out of it. It ends I go. Oh
That wasn't quite what I was looking for or quite what I wanted. I did it with Lewin Davis. I did it with
Uh, what's the one prior to that?
Burn after reading where I'm like I enjoyed so much of it, but it kind of left me
Simple man perfect example. That's now one of my favorites is a simple man. I loved it from the first time
I saw it, but I'm just sharp like that. Yeah, I just got it. Well, it's called a serious man, right?
Serious man. Yeah, what's the the Woody Allen one is a serious man. No simple man is
The one directed by the fashion designer
Okay, what's the Woody Allen one not wrong? Serious man Tom Ford Tom Ford directed a simple man
And a serious man is the Cone Brothers movie. What's the Woody Allen
That is a something man. Yeah, an inconse
Son of a bitch. I really like the rational man a rational that's right
And the soul man is where see Thomas Howard dresses like a block right now get
I'll often get soul man confused with the plot of every other one of those films. Yeah
Uh, but yeah, I like all those movies. Okay, good
um
You're talking about Hail Caesar. Hail Caesar. I thought was
Very funny in spots
It's super weird. There's a bunch of pieces in it that don't seem to connect and you don't really know if they do at the end
And now today I woke up and they asked me when I walked into work. Did you like it? I'm like, yeah, it really did
Then you asking me now. I'm like, yeah, it's actually all I thought about all day
And I think it's a fucking amazing movie and that that's why I think they're working on a different level than anybody else
Now, I'll tell you this folks
Yesterday was a Super Bowl
Pat and I went to two Super Bowl parties together. Yep, and then to a bar. Yeah
Uh, it was quite a day of intake. Yeah
And after all that when I was so drunk, I decided to go get four tacos and a quesadilla
Uh, for matruck pat went to see a movie
So how drunk were you in that theater by yourself?
Uh, not very because I quit drinking long before you guys so at the
When we went to the second stop
Second party house
I left fairly early
Went home. I didn't drink anymore after that when I went out but you left literally five minutes before we went to the bar
And then you came and met us at the bar. Yeah, but I met you like two hours later. That's amazing
Maybe an hour. I think it was at least two hours. You probably didn't notice the time because you were so very drunk
Uh, but when I got there, I was fine. I didn't drink anymore after that and you guys were all pretty amped up at that point
And I thought you left
When I guess you just went and took a massive dump
And I said I'm gonna go see Hail Caesar
And I did and I wasn't that drunk at all really and I followed the plot and I had a good time
And I was in such a foul mood that sometimes it's a better move to just go watch a movie by yourself
I was in horrendous shape
Yeah, I woke up at
We're depressed. That's what Joe and I just had a delicious home -cooked meal home -cooked by Joe to roast himself
Yeah, contributing to the will they are won't they vibe of this podcast
That people comment on on Twitter
Joe made me a lovely dinner and we talked about how depressed we are
Describe the dinner because I feel like I will get some points for what I cooked he made
Some perfectly seasoned asparagus a potato that at first seemed a little tough
But grew on me to become my new favorite way to cook potatoes
And a piece of lamb is that correct?
Lamb with some delicious seasonings that Joe ordered on Amazon Prime
Amazon Prime who's also bringing you the movie we're watching tonight. That's right speaking of which we are no money
We are watching a movie. Yeah
Man the people that complain that we don't talk about it but the movie enough are really gonna be unhappy this week
People have kind of stopped because they know what they're getting now
Now here you got Daniel Radcliffe in a creepy room in an old haunted house where we assume he's gonna meet the woman in black
He's wearing a Henley shirt which I don't even know they made back then
Even weirder it's a Don Henley Henley shirt
Right, so it's got a Don Henley end of the innocence tour poster on it right and that album came out in 1991
That's what Don Henley should do now make Don Henley Henley is yeah
Henley's by Don Henley well. I love
Glenn fries fries
He made those are delicious season curlies those are delicious favorite part of this nation is delicious seasoned curlies
I
When the drive through the funniest sketch in the history of music
What I don't know I'll play it for you after this tenacious D album thankfully the only made one
It's perfect from start to finish the songs are no they made three albums
Not album album yes, they have no none of come out after this
Self -titled tenacious day yes, they have you mean the soundtrack to pick up destiny
And then they made another album called the about like the phoenix rising from the ashes and that was like their follow -up album
They absolutely did it was like a big true. It's 100 % true. I'll bet you
Please bet me a large amount of money. Well the phoenix rising is that's the tenacious D album so there must be one before that no
Tribute to the best song ever. No, that's the first one
Okay, then came the soundtrack to the movie and then they did a follow -up to the first album which was officially their second album
Oh, I got to find this. I didn't know that even happened
We're in the phoenix song they apologize for the pick of destiny
Okay, like we you thought we were down and out, but here we're back all right
It's not as good as the first album, but it's enjoyable let me look it up so yeah now I got to hear him
Anyway season currently is this from that
Yeah, he goes through the drive -through and he's like you know he keeps ordering things. It's so it's so funny and you would
Would love it so much he's this jack black so he's ordering food and he'll order like a lot of food
And then feel really guilty about it immediately
So he'll be like
Do a large soda or whatever then he's like can I get half diet half regular in this
Then just everything he says is great and then he goes could I get a
Bacon cheeseburger please and he goes excuse me a junior bacon cheese
Junior bacon cheese sure bacon cheese. There's no fault
of your way to say
Junior bacon cheeseburger then junior bacon cheat
And and then it's one point. He says season curly so I'm assuming yeah, he goes some curly fries please
seasoned
Curlies you're gonna have to give it a listen. I love it. I think it influenced a lot of the way I speak because I listen to it every day
When I was a kid I've heard a lot of that kid first out, but I've never heard that sketch. Yeah
Big fan. You know I can't work a haul like how does he not add him divine? How does he not pay jack black 10 % of his salary?
I think Adam divine is very funny, but like he's doing jack black. How does anybody not pay anybody what they owe them?
It's true, but he is everything he's a little too much on the agree. No, I'm not disagreeing with you, but the
Here's the thing
My favorite tenacious D sketch is the one where
Cage is standing outside. This is a video sketch. Yeah, where he's standing outside
With a poster board that says blow jobs five dollars. I think I sell it. And then jack black pulls and pulls over and with sunglasses on and he goes
Hey, man, you know, I'm looking to party. Yeah, KG gets in the car blows jack black not realizing it's jack black because he has sunglasses on
Jack black comes they literally take a bottle of lubricant and just squirt it into the air to simulate jack black jizzing
Jack black takes off the sunglasses KG goes oh
Man, it's you jack and then he goes you don't have five fucking bucks
Or is jack the one that blows him. I think jack blows KG
They played that when I saw them in concert. They played that that's an amazing sketch
I saw if you want to talk about a great classic early 2000s concert. It was weezer headlining
uh
Tenacious D
Below them and Jimmy eat world as the opener one of the best shows I've ever seen
I mean you lost me a Jimmy eat world. I love Jimmy world. Especially the big songs
Uh, the middle is their big pop. How's that one go edges take some time
Which okay, I can see how you get sick of that beautiful song
But the rest of that album many other other songs you would enjoy. I have a feeling
Not dare you they're great. You don't know what I would or wouldn't enjoy it. You don't fucking know me
Well, thank Christ. You fucking asshole. Thank Christ. You don't know. Shoot about me. Joe's drinking again gang
So we're at his home from the factory gang you're drinking too. I'm having a gluten free beer. That's good
Yeah, and I have a glass of white wine all right. That's all you know, I like I'm swinging out of a flask
Which I'm not above. No, I'm sure you'd be swinging out of the flask by the end of this
Swinging out of the flask is what I just said folks. Hey
That sounds like a good name for an album like a like swinging out of the flask like a Brian sets her orchestra with BSL
Swinging out of the flask
Well, let me talk about hell season for a moment um
I want to see it again. I think no Colin Brothers movie you can figure out make your mind up on until you see it a second time
That's when a serious man became one of my favorites of theirs because I got way more into it the second time
Uh
Clooney I'm tired of him working with the colons. I think they can do better. I like when they give
Really funny character parts to people who are not necessarily that kind of actor right George Clooney. I'm sick of it
I've seen it. I know he's kind of funny enough
Doesn't mean I want to see him in every fucking comedy right same with fucking Brad Pitt by the way
That said we'll say Brad Pitt steals the show and burn after reading no question
And Clooney too Clooney and fucking Richard Jenkins who is amazing and everything and Clooney's off the in my opinion off the charts and in burn after reading
I got a problem with my larynx. Yeah. No, he's great. Yeah, I'm a little tired of it as I'm tired of de caprio on score sazing
You know, you want to see people work with different kinds of people
Uh
Jonah Hills in one scene uh kind of funny nothing else Christopher Lambert was in a scene the Highlander himself
Christopher Chris Lambert is in this film. He's in it. Scarge. He's often quite fun. Ray finds his great and the who steals the movie
Is Channing Tatum for one. He does a musical gay like sailor dancing number that was amazing right and sings pretty well
And he's really funny in it right and then the other new guy who's playing like the cowboy and the trailers is off the charts funny
And I think it's gonna be a big star. How's my boy JB
Josh bros
By boring to be honest with you. That's I hate to hear that. Brolin was fan. Brolin was perfect for no country for old men
He can't do any bigger characters than that. I like Josh. Brolin
Uh, I found him to be the only redeeming and immensely enjoyable part of that that shitty
PT energy movie and her advice absolutely agree. Yeah, the way he's sucking that fucking possible short
I didn't even get to the martin short part because I couldn't get through the goddamn movie. Yeah, it was uh
Not not fun. Yeah, what are you gonna do?
DLCs are I liked I also at the theater on the aisle this week with duroza and walsh
I saw a little movie called dirty grandpa folks. I mean now you see
Grand Paul you've been waiting to tell me about this now for those of you listening at home that don't know Pat Walsh on a personal level
Know this
He's the type of guy that will text you
several times in a week
asking you almost desperately. Please go see dirty grandpa with me and I'm like I don't know
I don't want to see this movie yeah
And he's not saying like it'll be funny because it's I will go ironically and no, I don't do that
We'll get like drunk before and it'll be a who he really wants to go and see if it's any good
And then of course you can say something beautiful about me as a human that I'm optimistic about
I text you the day after so I said how was dirty grandpa you said
Disturbingly bad. Yeah, it was off the charts bad folks
And but I am glad I saw it. I went with our buddies Jake Weisman mad anger brats and brine to guyer
Uh
I saw with brine to palma
Okay, myself. You split that was worth it. He kept saying he wanted more split screen and lesbian action
Yeah, yeah, yeah
He kept asking why there weren't more chase scenes. Yeah, well, there certainly couldn't have been more cocaine and dirty grandpa
Was there a lot of cocaine stuff a lot of cocaine ecstasy Xanax everything
Okay, now the movie's gone out again. We're still here with you folks
um
The dirty grandpa Robert De Niro just completely goes for it
He never looks embarrassed which is embarrassing
and
Well, what I think happened is there's no way he knew any of the references in this movie
So janeeros like oh
You know, this this reminds me of like queen Latifa taking a shit on us. So we're great
It's stuff like that and I just imagine rather than you know, we'll just like look at a frame like what's the line again
They tell him and he goes a queen Latifa taking a shit on a I don't think he thinks about anything he's saying
For a moment in the movie. It sounds like he's just
Drily reading a script at the first glance first time he's seen these words. Oh, that's upsetting. Efron is
Beyond bland and boring and should not be a movie star although of course he's a good -looking guy
I've had enough. You're not a comedy actor Zach
Uh, I'm getting upset. Well, are you excited for neighbors two? No, but I didn't despise neighbors
I hated neighbors one. I would say it was the worst of theirs for sure. I hated that movie
It was really haphazardly written and I didn't care for and I'm not shitting on Seth Rogan in those guys
I like a lot of the stuff they do, but I hated yeah, of course
um
But yeah, it was really bad
But maybe because I was there with comedians and people who like to like study comedy
We talked about it for a good 45 minutes afterwards and about how depressed we all felt by it
and how sort of lazy and sad and desperate it was
And like deniro there's a gay black guy that rolls with them
And deniro calls this guy like every name in the book
He says insanely hateful
Uh, things against gay people to his face that aren't funny and there's no like bounce to them
It's not like when bad santa says something and it's funny because they wrote it funny
He's just says these awful racist things into this guy's eyes
The audience is so silent
Well, what like give me and then the gay black guy never
Says anything in response
So you just sit there and watch the hurt on this poor gay black man's face as he registers the hate being spewed by deniro
What's one of the things he says and he doesn't respond
I wouldn't repeat them, but it's the whole movie is like I bet you want to gargle this guy's ca ca ca like all this kind of shit
And you're like okay, none of this is really funny, but I know the black guy's gonna get back at deniro
But he doesn't he never gets back he never says a word and retaliation
They it's like when david spades telling chris farly you're a big fat piece of shit
It's funny because chris farly tries to come back at him right like or makes a joke back
Are that he says well you're an asshole and they go back and forth. This was an old man hurling
racial epitats
And sexist things at people and then you sort of watching the hurt absorb on their face terrible in a comedy
I don't like the sound of this. We were so blown away by it and it was interesting and I'm glad I saw it because
You couldn't believe what they do in this movie. It was like it was like watching birth of a nation. I was a study in yeah, exactly
Then you know at one point deniro beats up a gang which is an actual gang of seven black guys
He beats the shit out of all them except two in the back are just standing there watching
I heard you complaining about this yesterday
You're really mad about maybe I wasn't clear he beats the shit out of seven guys and there's two just standing there like not fighting
No, you guys doing that clear yesterday you were really they haven't heard what I said
I know I'm just saying
For the audiences sake you were really hung up on the logistics of how this fight would have went to my my overall point here
And I realized that makes no sense if you haven't seen it and don't see it but
There were so many things in it where you were like
How could everyone have been just asleep that day? How did no one say wait a minute guys?
This doesn't make any sense or hey this jokes terrible. Let's come up with a new one you work in television
You have to ask that question. Yeah, no, I mean we've all worked in television. It's not we've all but you and I you we all in this room two people on this couch
You know we you know how it happens. It's you know everybody says something and this has got to change and this has got to change
Then people tap out and people say fuck this and yeah eventually gets to the finished product and it's terrible
Yeah, you know, so yeah the director was this guy Dan Mazer who was Sasha Baron Cohen's riding partner and helped do all those movies with him
Like these are people who knew comedy
Wasn't working. That's a shame, man
That's really a shame. I hate to hear it. It happens Joe happens. Yeah, it's it's a shame. I regret writing and directing dirty grandpa
I
Just read I read an interview with TJ Miller who we've known. Yeah for quite from before when back when I
We could say we know him when WBW, baby, but way back when I read an interview with him about Deadpool
Which I'm sure if I want to see or not. I've decided I am excited to see it
I because my problem with all the Marvel movies is they take themselves too seriously and this doesn't if the jokes suck
Then I won't like it, but maybe it's going to be funny. I know I don't think the Marvel movies take themselves too seriously
I think
I think they get a little bit masturbatory to be honest with you
They get very like pleased with their humor and everything
Yeah, and they're two hours and 45 minutes. Well, that's stupid
But so I'm not I'm not against Deadpool. I love Ryan Reynolds. I want to support boy
That guy's been in need of a good vehicle for 15 fucking years. He's so talented
He might either as a bad agent or the other people above him get the offers first right well in any case
I'm not against seeing the film. I just don't know if I'm excited about it
But I read an interview with TJ Miller where he talked about the jokes that were too much for the movie
They had gotten cut uh -huh
And he was only allowed to give an example of one or two apparently the studios said don't talk about these they were cut for a reason right
But one of them that was apparently too much was when he's like telling him what he looks like
How bad his face looks. Yeah, he goes you it looks like
Your neck took a shit and then grew ears something like that or or somebody showed was too much for the
Shit on your shoulders and then it grew to they grew ear. Yeah, that's what I was confused about
He got billboards up all around town. I don't know if they have these where you live folks
But out here in Lala were billboards. Yeah, probably they got they got dead pool billboards everywhere
That literally say wait till they get a load of me like that like the sexual innuendo is almost not
Even in you window a load of jizz you're saying
Somebody I don't know who did it on Twitter, but somebody doctored one of the Deadpool billboards into like Photoshop and said
You know like they're really going too far with this Deadpool marketing and the the
The thing they put on it it was Deadpool laying there and it just said I shoot bullets and come
Deadpool well, what was the uh
Like I don't understand he's saying wait till they get a load of me, but is he coming in the photo or what
No, it's just he's saying load. It's very beevison but he okay, all right, but my point is I don't know Deadpool's style of humor
I know on the trailer the this girl beats a shitter to somebody and he goes ooh
I'd hate to be the guy who tries to rape her on prom night. I was like that's not a funny joke
Is that in the commercial in the trailer? It's I guess I assume was a red band trailer, but yeah
Don't try to have four sex with her on prom night like that pool. Which does he say?
You're better than that baby. He says four sex, I believe I can't believe a comic book movie is rated are
I don't think a comic book comic book movie has been rated are since the original Punisher film starring Dov Lunger in Lungy, baby
Dark man a comic book. No, it's a comic book style movie, but it's not it's a superhero movie
But I don't believe that was ever comic book. Yeah, that's Sam Raim's at his best big fans. The plan is his best
But yes, go on, but I'm saying I'm not saying that's his best film
I'm just saying that's him top of his game. He does a really great job with that movie speaking of your boy Liam Neeson your girl Frances McDormon
Hell of a flick and your boy love it. It's on Netflix actually your boy
What's his face? They played Larry Drake Larry Drake. Yeah has only ever
I think I've seen almost every Larry Drake movie only ever plays a retarded man or a villainous scumbag
There's no I mean talking about a hot type casting. We got to run a movie where we can cast him as a retarded villainous scumbag
Mentally handicapped folks
By the way
I'd go see that movie and you know Larry Drake will do it
The actress named the guy from Rome
I don't know. I'm calling Daniel Radcliffe Harry Potter. Yeah, by the way
Let's get back to the film we're watching. Okay. This is perhaps a molestation attempt brewing
We're watching the woman in black folks starring Daniel Radcliffe. This is the remake of the hammer classic the woman in black
I remember when I tried to rent this movie. I misspoke at the counter at blackbuster. I said do you have the black woman?
For rent. They didn't know what I was talking about. Yeah
Looking for a black woman told me to get out of the store
That I was being thought I was being racially provocative. Sure
You were singing brown sugar by the Rolling Stones odd that this guy's got paintings of small boys on his wall shouldn't
Agree more
Unless it's his son actually looks a bit like my dad whoever the sector is he's a great actor
I can't think of who he is though. He's from Rome
He's on the show Rome and then he was in every movie ever made for like 10 years
I never watched Rome because that was my breaking point. That was my brief breaking point with HBO
Because they had at that point
released too many TV shows
Devon mortified to hear that you you had left they had released too many TV shows that opened with
Credit sequence that was clearly done in after effects right and some sort of
Kind of like Middle Eastern -y
Passion of the Christ kind of music and by the time they got to Rome I was like I can't do this anymore
This just feels like the opening to Carnival and I yeah, you know
That was really weird when Carnival started with
Joe's very tasteful recreation of the theme to Rome
Well, I was actually I think doing the Carnival theme
Yeah, the uh I think there was the theme to how to make it in America
A show about making jeans. I like that they just sort of close up
Cut away of the painting over the boy now. They're doing a second close. Yeah, and that's not supposed to be funny
Although it is kind of odd. Yeah, uh the master of the house here who was also in Rome as you pointed out
There's a bit of an Alan Rickman vibe. He does. I still find myself getting quite sad that Alan Rickman is dead
I just think about him and I get sad he was one of the best
I feel like I could do an Alan Rickman impression if I really tried
Well, I used to do on vinyl a
recurring sketch called pool party at Alan Rickman's house. All right. Do it
where he would be
All right, let me think
Friendly reminder that there is to be no intercourse in the jacuzzi. Thank you
There you go. That's great
That's really good intercourse hold hold your asses
That's really good. Hey Alan do you do it really well? I really bad. Alan do you have any more checks mix?
Are you sure you wouldn't prefer the muddy buddies
Which is the best kind of checks mix? That's very funny. It's muddy buddies with the chocolate. Yeah, puppy chow's another name for it
Muddy buddies to me sounds like a pair of underwear coveted. That's exactly my point. It makes me think of shit
Yeah, like you ask hey honey. Can you go
Clean up Brian. I think he's got a case of the muddy buddies. Yeah. Oh, I got to get out of this party. I have had muddy buddy
You ever show yourself, Joe
More times and I'd like to remember oh wow
Never like I can't control my battles and I've now shit myself. I wish I had a diaper on
But laying in bed probably sick right
Flu whatever and I push your fart out and I get to I get to way too confident and and then you got to miss
Wow, and then you just got to lay there in it for hours. Yeah, she's the worst part
I wish you had called me because you didn't have to do that
I
I did not I was getting off the highway once coming home from Vegas
And if you miss this one turn off the next one's like an hour and 20 minutes
And sure enough about 10 minutes into that john. I was like oh no
But I wasn't about to turn back because you just want to get home from Vegas as quickly as possible. So my guy can make it an hour
Not not true
So I'm like okay, this is a problem and I
Parked my car outside of this bathroom and there was a huge line
Because it's like the one stop
There's two gas stations across the street from each other and I pushed my way through everyone to the front of the line
And I just yelled in this woman's face. I'm really sorry. It's an emergency. I'm really sorry
And everyone in the line got it nobody gave me any shit no pun intended
And the guy comes out and I jump in there and as I'm walking in the guy looks me in the eye and go sorry man
I go what I open there and this is how much of a germ freak I am
It looked like he had been throwing shit
Around the bathroom and I was so disgusted that I almost vomited
But I also was about to go to the bathroom and I looked at it and I was like even in my state
I cannot do this and I sprinted taking a chance a big chance
To the gas station across the street. I got there a little like paddle wheel attached to a key
I threw it open. It was immaculate and I thanked Christ that I had made it and you made it and I made it
She didn't shit your pants. But even if I had I would have felt good about not going in the
I thought that was going to end with you shitting your pants
No, it's the closest stuff come I've never actually crossed the threshold
I was in uh
There's more stories
Where the hell was I?
Church Denmark Denmark
Or Norway I did a tour over there a little while back and uh we were on the road drop
Yeah, we were on the road and I had an attack
Because I'd eaten at a McDonald's over there
Which not that it was not clean or not good or whatever
The weird thing about McDonald's over there is they try to make it taste like you made it at your house
Yeah, which is fucking gross. It makes it worse for some reason right
If I went to your house and you you came over here and I was like and you didn't know what a big Mac was and I was like
Hey, man, I
Gonna put these two patties on a roll. Yeah
Thousand I would dress you be like this is disgusting. Yeah, get it out of my face. So uh
Anyway, I ate this stuff and I was like oh my god
I'm gonna I have to I was in emergency and I went in every stall
There were now the nice thing about it over there was the doors for the stalls and the rest up
floor to ceiling
You're fully in a closet. Wow, which is beautiful. You never get that in the rest room and a public place
But everyone I went into the first one was no way
And then each consecutive one was worse than the last one. Yeah
It's a real problem and I well women don't understand. I don't think how bad guys restaurants get I shit
I shit standing up. I had to stand up and shit facing the door
And two things
Happened when you do that number one you feel like your eyes are gonna shoot out of your head right the pressure
The pushing and the pressure is insane
The second thing you it's three things the second thing you think of is
If somebody manages to get this door open, I'm gonna be knocked out right right
The third thing is if somebody gets in here and I'm not knocked out
I'm already in prime like rape condition. Uh -huh. Ass is out. I'm standing up with it perked
Perked up in the air because odds are somebody's gonna open a restroom door and just go straight into rape mode
Your only defense is that you could shit on the guy
But then if he's got a really bad fetish
You're in trouble. I think the odds for this are about at powerball levels the
Well, let me tell you when you're in that five -minute span of experiencing it those odds don't seem that crazy
Okay, okay, especially if you're in another country where you don't really know the language. It's a little frightening
Right, but I got through it. I shit and and then I was like oh that I think this is how they shit in Asia
They should standing up right? Uh -huh. I believe. Well, why not? Well, they squat, I think
I think some of those bathrooms. It's very
You're standing like a hover over it. Yeah, and I was what I was doing. I was kind of squatting. Okay couldn't sit on it
I mean it is an immaculate country. I mean you could eat off the streets yet the bathroom stalls are like yeah
The most beautiful people I've ever seen. I didn't made no sense. You realize you still haven't told us what country this is
Oh, I had a few guesses. I think it was Denmark. I can't fucking remember
Joe stores are red because his attention to detail. What do I give a shit? You know, I'm ready to check out of this whole thing anymore. I don't care
Finland who gives a shit? That's how Joe sets the scene for his debut novel
I think I was in Finland
Denmark. I don't know who gives a shit. It actually is a good person. It is a great sentence. It's very Bukowski. Yeah
Yeah
Very honest this guy writes from the heart
Okay, you know, we're all gonna die. What's it matter? Boy, that's the truth isn't it though
I was thinking today you double my age. I'm pretty much dead
So like if I once I live what I've already lived I'll be close to dead. That's crazy
Well, I'm 38 and I figure if I can get at least another
30 years out of this thing I'd be pretty happy but uh, you know, I'd like to get more than that. I'd like to get another
50 60 I'm 35. I think I'm gonna hit probably 7580
Why do you have a history of heart problems in my family?
You know now a history of mind problems in my mom's side
It's just a recipe for disaster
Well, you're giving yourself a pretty liberal age for a guy that's for a lunatic with a heart problem
Not a lunatic, but you will be. Yeah, no, definitely
You're not gonna be remembered to take those blood thinners. What are you gonna do? I don't know
You don't know I think I have a lot less stress in my life than the men in my family who have preceded me because they were all
Men who I admire a great deal
But they were really scrounging for that next paycheck every single week
Maybe they wouldn't put food in their family's table. Maybe they wouldn't hard work in men
My dad was doing a lot of drywall construction. I've had a much more charmed life
You know what I'm saying sure that puts a lot less miles on a man
Well, since you're only a pussy some might say I'm not but theoretically
But you also work on television would I which I would say could be the most stressful of all industries fair enough
It can be mentally taxing sure
But right now my life is not that stress
I truly hope you don't die of some kind of heart mental condition
Thank you. It would break my heart to see you out on the streets talking to yourself in a bathrobe. Yeah
I'd say we're made
Patations three four years away from that happen good. That's good
If you're watching the movie with us folks Daniel ride cliff is now going through a box of letters. He's inside the woman in black
We have not had a woman in black sighting yet. No, which is odd because I feel as if we've been watching this film for four hours
Where my women in black at
How long has this been on you see crimson peak we talked about now
I like crimson peak but like the beginning of crimson peak the woman
This creepy old woman is telling her daughter. She's like I'm going to die now
But beware of crimson peak
Beware of crimson peak there's like ten times rather movie this ghost of this old woman comes to her and is like always beware for crimson peak is at hand
then
What is crimson peak she marries this guy the first place he takes her is this blood red mountain
And she's like yeah, all right looks pretty cool to me. Let's stay here. It's a red mountain
It's like a red mountain
You tell me to look out for creamy peas
Here we are. I'm looking out for creamy peas. So what is the thing to beware now?
Let me guess what the movie is about all right. It was a beautiful looking movie. Yeah kind of stupid
I didn't watch it. It's worth watching. I didn't care to see it because it didn't look at all scary to me
It looked like a graphic novel and I thought this will probably look pretty, but I don't care. You're right
But it looked real pretty. Okay, so first thing first. I was right about that
Let me guess what the plot is okay
The brother and sister have to kill the wife of the brother as some sort of sacrifice to the haunted house
And the brother and sister might may or may not be sexually involved
You're not that far off at all will tell me that
No, you're not that far off. I mean to save any more than that would be kind of spoiling it. I'm saying spoil it
I don't care what our listeners might. It's not
We're saying spoiler alert. It's all right, Joe. That's all I really remember. They're they're happening. I mean they try to kill her
And they're bad and their brother and sister who might be sexually into each other. Okay. I don't believe the tell you remember
Did you notice now the road to the island where Daniel Radcliffe is staying is buried? Yeah, underwater
submerged. What did you think of shutter island?
Uh, I like shutter island. I thought I was interesting
I'm always a little disappointed when in the end it just turns out to be
Out of his mind like it's yeah, it was all in his head and he's crazy even though even though it all came together very clever
Yeah, is it cleverfully or cleverly cleverly cleverly cleverly
You know when you're like oh that person was his nurse and this was that and when that was cool
But um, I liked it, you know for Scorsese
You know first time out into the into the world of horror and suspense it was it was impressive
I gotta say I really fucking loved it
And when I watch it again recently, I really fucking loved it really
I think a lot of times with a movie like that, you know, and I bet Shyamalan could benefit from this as well
is you're so built up
For the twist or the thing at the end or like what your expectations are the movie
That if you watch a movie a second time a lot of times you know where it's going and you can really respect it a lot more
I do that all the time. Who else is in Crimson Peak? I don't even remember
Vodiac became one of my favorite movies. I like it over and over and over. Who else is in Shutter Island? Excuse me
it is DeCaprio. It is
uh
Who's the old guy in it?
Cromwell James Cromwell that might be wrong. It's tutorial in it
No
Is Jackie Earl Haley in it? Yes, Jack Earl Haley is he is and uh he's ledger's wife Michelle Williams. Yes, that's right
She's a real intense scene when she drowns her fucking kids in that movie
But she's like the nurse in the end, right?
Yeah, she's not a bad guy at the end. I think that's right. I don't want to say
Fair enough. I tell you the more I have to take in the more stress as we talked about mental stress the less I remember about movies
I like specific plot details. I would have been able to write a lot for every move I've ever seen in my life
And now I just let stuff out. I don't need to remember this specific plot of Shutter Island. Sure
I loved it and I'll move on. I at one point in my life was able to tell you the real name of every contemporary rapper
Yeah, I was such a rap fan and and where they were from right?
Easily you could have hit me with anybody. I could have told you their name. Yeah
Barely remember now at this point. Can you still do your states and caps which I used to be a master of and now would probably fail
Never knew my states and caps never cared too
Yeah, didn't see the point. I was sort of known as and again folks. I hate to brag
I was kind of known as the states and caps guy
In like third grade. I knew them all baby. Uh, I I I knew about secret states that they never told the world about or what their capitals were
Couldn't care less. Don't see the point in knowing the states and caps. Yeah
Couldn't point out most states on a map. I know where the big ones are your key states your California's your New York's
Your Florida's your Texas's yeah, here's it you want to hear this joke that I just in my mind wrote for Woody Allen
Sure, maybe maybe I can get it on his new Netflix series whatever the hell it is Amazon Amazon
We're giving them more. Is he gonna be in it? Yeah with Miley Cyrus. He's in it. Yeah, but I hope hopefully not fucking Miley Cyrus
Miley Cyrus isn't it? Yeah, it's those two
It's the two of them. Yeah, that's great. And he's writing and directing it
Yeah, that's awesome. I love and Elaine May is in it who is a comedy genius. I love Elaine May so much. Oh, that's great
I love it. No way. Here's here's the joke. I just wrote for Woody Allen
I guess you could say I live in two states say
New York and confusion
God
It's a horrible joke
Your two states in New York and anxiety is that better?
No in a state of anxiety
You see it the you see it coming for a mile away. You got to mask it a little better. Fuck you
I just came up with it. You got to mask it a little better
You put that in his joke tonight and it kills
Tonight this is this is how you got to do that one. You got to go playing clarinet somewhere
You got to go a little bit a bit back about me my background
Is born in the state of New York
Eventually I took a president since state of turmoil
That's how you do that joke
That's how you do that. That's how he would do it. We go out there and we see
What the public decide we'll let the guy who lives above you who almost spat in my hair tonight
decide
Well folks here it is the first ever we'll see you in ill contest
Send your votes to Twitter
Who had the better version of the Woody Allen show?
I don't think I'm gonna win this one, but that's fine
I was I the guy didn't spit at me the guy who lives above Joe spat a lugi that just missed my kind of upsets me
That the upstairs neighbor is hawking snotty lugi's off of the balcony. He missed me. He wasn't aiming for me
I know that's an important thing to know. There's only six of us that live here. It's like, you know
Yeah, it wasn't a great way to to come see an old friend, but well
He also doesn't live there. He's just visiting. Okay
So listening to us waiting to spit on me when I leave. Yeah, you can probably hear every word we're saying as you can hear there's not
There's not a problem with noise transfer in this apartment
Folks, I've moved into a one bedroom and I mean you just hear everything yeah everywhere
And it's been a good exercise for my nerves because I'm not going crazy even though I wake up every morning at 7 a .m
And having had a decent night sleep in two months
Uh
And by the way, I'm not saying like oh 7 a .m. Oh, who who who I'm saying my job I work at night mostly so
You know my eight hours ends at like 10 a .m. Usually
And I'm not getting that I'm not even getting anywhere near near close to that. I feel like I have a kid
Maybe that's what this experience is about. I'm maybe I should just go have a baby now
Because I'll be used to waking up. I said this on the last podcast. Maybe the two of us need to have babies
Oh with other people when I kill myself
Could you imagine anything worse?
I mean friends enough kids they seem happy. I can't do it. I couldn't do it. It doesn't appeal to me
Yeah, woman I work with I was like how was your weekend she goes uh my son just shot in my bed
Kids like 10 years old took a shit in her bed. He's shit in her bed
Yeah, I mean, I don't know if I can deal with all that really
There's only one guy I shouldn't in my bed and that's me baby and that's
I'm why and sadly my girlfriend as well
We both have pretty severe issues with it
Well, she's not a guy so that doesn't count right. She's a gal
Uh
Have you seen any movies lately that you enjoyed John
Well
I believe we said we're gonna talk about this. I watch goodnight mommy
Yeah, and I
Thought was a blast and you hated it. I'm surprised by that look. It was very well acted. Yeah, it was very well shot
It was very well written
All sounds
The reveal at the end of how it all kind of came together was well executed
This is a rave review. Well look my problem was I signed on now. I don't care
I'm gonna say the spoilers if you don't want to hear this cover your ears. I signed on for a movie
About two kids
thinking
The woman in their house was not their mother. It was a lunatic imposter
Within three minutes of the movie beginning it becomes painfully obvious that one of the brothers does not exist
Uh
That this is not going to be what the movie is about it was not obvious to me
But I'm still it was within five minutes. I'm not exaggerating within five minutes. I was like
Oh, so that other brothers dead
Okay, and like I don't like to ruin movies for myself
I let them wash over me. So anyway, I didn't try to it. Just popped in my head because it was so obvious
She's never talking to the sun. She doesn't know who has two kids
Uh, she doesn't make the other kid food. I mean, it's like it's like it's like that's like the first three scenes you're like all right
So anyway
So that that was too obvious and I thought okay, well, I'll give it the benefit out
Maybe that's what they want me to think and then it's like no, not really. That's just kind of what it is
Um, and then it becomes very obvious soon after that like that this is their mother clearly
And she's experienced some kind of traumatic event and that's is why she's acting so strangely
And then it starts to become even more clear like oh the mother's not acting that strangely the kid is fucked up
There's something with this kid. I really love that journey. Have a moment. That was very cool
And then it turns into a torture movie. Yeah, and it's just this depraved thing where you're like
Okay, so this kid's a psycho, and I just feel horrible for this woman now
It's like terrible. I don't think I'm like I'm gonna watch this
I was excited about this scary thriller where it was like this fucking crazy lady lives in our house. We don't know who she is
Well
Every movie doesn't have to put you at ease Joe. I don't know. I don't like stuff like that. I should go watch that uh
Log in front of a fireplace for a couple hours calm yourself. Yeah
Hostile is the only movie that involves like torture and stuff that I like I love to hostile and hostile to starring
Beauty Phillips who I made out with once I didn't care for hostile to but I like hostile one quite a bit
And the main reason I love hostile one is because there's vengeance at the end like the kid gets the kid gets his
Gives them their come -upence and you're rooting for him and it's exciting and you want him to win in the end
Whereas with good night mommy. It's like
It's just like oh no so nobody wins
There's a nihilistic movie. It's just it's just like typical of a lot of like the overseas horror movies
Where it's like it's gonna be this one thing for a little while and then it's gonna turn out to not be that and it's just gonna be somebody to
Priavidly torturing somebody for for 45 minutes. The best version of that's audition. I hate auditions. I fucking loved audition
I hate it to me. That's one of the best horror movies ever met. I hate it. It's not a horror movie
I actually screamed when I saw audition. I hate it. Look. I made him do it. Put pins in his eyeballs. Oh, okay great
So this is like just like an awful. Joe that's part of horror too
Uh, like that's a part of horror you don't enjoy. It's fun. That to me isn't horror to me horror has to involve
You can't just show me something disturbing and go that's horror
Because that's not entertaining to me
Do you know what I mean? Like yeah, oh look. I'd always much rather like a six -sense type movie than a
Fucking Texas chance on master. That's kind of more my thing, but here's the thing. I love Texas. I gotta place my heart for all of them
I love Texas chance on master girl, but Texas chance on master has suspense. It's not against slasher movies
I thought audition had a ton of suspense. Oh, it was just it was like okay
So she's gonna be crazy and obviously from like three quarters of whatever it is
And then it's just like she's just gonna do horrible things to him now and we just sit here and watch that you're like
But that's why some people some people go to horror movies. I don't know. I didn't care for it. I didn't care for it
That's fine folks if you're gonna see one of the movies in that genre auditions a good one to say and so it's hostile
Frankly, I thought I was the best one. I was more of an action movie really, which I thought was awesome about it
I love hostile. I think it's I think it's a masterpiece. I think yeah
I really loved it to elaborate on what else makes hostile such a great film that these other movies in my opinion don't have
There's an amazing social commentary to it about yeah, and a great sense of humor to the buying and selling of people
And a lot of nudity uh the justification people make in how it's in what ways it's okay to pay for people to give you services right
It was it was it's tremendous. It's a great movie. It's got a lot of depth to it and uh
And I don't think those other movies do now on the flip side of that
For Eli Roth is I watched this weekend
The grain inferno
I want to see that I haven't seen it yet. I despised it and
I mean here's basically my big problem with it the whole movies about like how people
Exactly exactly we were talking about on the last episode of this podcast
How people will like get on a cause and be all about it, but never do anything more than just like update their Facebook status
You know, it's like what you're doing
Actually less than nothing by saying on your Facebook
You know power to Paris or whatever
um
That's what the movie was supposed to be about starting from that point
He puts these people really through the ringer
So clearly the movie should be like they're gonna go on some really expensive senior trip
You can keep the same beginning where they're very insensitive about these issues, but they're all like pretend and do their drum circle
So it seems like they're interested in this shit. Okay, you have them going like a expensive vacation and the plane crashes in this
Cannibalistic society that's like these tribes that they claim to want to help, but they've never done anything about it
All right, I wanted it so far that to me would be a very interesting movie what actually happens
Is they are activists and they set up trips to like
Stand with guns to their head and try to stop the destruction of rainforest. So they go
Uh, they're playing crashes
And it's like but these aren't fake activists. They went to the Amazon and stood in front of guns
Right to like stop this place from being torn down so when they're punished by
All these cannibals who are literally eating them while they're alive eating their brains and arms and legs and everything for hours
You know
Then it would mean something sure like it just it really was like these are people who are trying to actually do something good
And now they're gonna get eaten where the whole point and in interviews that I've read with him since because I was so frustrated by the movie
He's like this movie is a straight -on critique of
Doing nothing is him or whatever you call it fakedivism fakedism or something
Uh, hacked his bism something like that. Okay. Uh, he said it's gotta be a direct critique of that
But it's just not because these aren't people
updated in their like if they were like I hate
Let's say okay, here's the short twilight zone version of it a little girl writes on her Facebook
Um, everyone please support the Amazon rainforest send your money. I love them. Right
Then she goes in a trip lands in the Amazon and they eat her she didn't do it. Okay. She's getting punished for not caring
But you can't have this woman do a lot of activist work
Right and start to like really get into charity and like thinking about people other than yourselves and then have them punished by those people because actually the message
Is not only a bad message, but the message is like don't ever try to help people right including these poor third world countries and stuff because they're all gonna eat you leave them to die
If that's the message of the movie then what what the hell is that and it made all this disgusting cannibal shit which is part of the genre of course
But it made you just feel terrible for these people
And actually the worst person in the movie a guy who
Master bates seconds after this girl and the cage with them is killed and eaten and they go
Why are you masturbating and he goes you all should do the same thing because it'll keep your mind clear
Okay, he's sitting and jacking up like he's clearly the worst of these characters. That's disgusting
And he has never killed
The good people in the movie are all killed one by one. It's like what are you saying here?
Uh, it sounds like the plot to the last Rambo movie
Except I love that one. I like the last random. Yeah, and that had a fucking message too where those activists are going up
And they say we want to make a change and he warns them you're not changing shit up there don't grow up there
And then they do and then he has to go in and save them
Uh, and they get slaughtered. Yeah, I guess they didn't bother me there because it was just such a dumb movie otherwise
Rambo
but like
To me salon is saying like it's not worth helping these people
um
Which isn't great either right doesn't bother me because Rambo is like a nihilist dude, right this movie was just like
I don't know it just made all the disgusting shit and it like there's there's several cases in the movie of female
General mutilation that you just sit and watch they show it to you. Yeah, I mean not you know close up
Uh, now
Like what I am I watching these people punished who are trying to help
Ah, yeah, I was listening to the Eli Roth podcast
He does a podcast. I'm sorry. I was listening to the bread eastern Ellis podcast with Quentin Tarantino
And they talked about this movie on it and bread eastern Ellis said the the death of the fat guy was very disturbing
It was what was it tell me about it
Ah, he's the first one yet said but he didn't what happens
He's a big fat guy. He's been really nice the whole movie too
uh
They sort of make him drink this stuff
Then they lay him down and this woman like looks like she's kind of giving him the sign of the cross
And she jams her thumb into his forehead pulls out some brain starts eating it
He's still alive and like children are ripping off his legs and arms. He's still alive
She saws his tongue off. He's still alive and they don't cut away from it
Just goes on and on and on and he had been like a nice dude
That's it
That's it and they all eat him, you know, okay, it's gross. How does she manage it or thumb through his forehead?
That was not explained
Unless it was this they there were always rubbing like creams on them
They like loosen them up
Loose that's really good. Yeah, I just wish I hadn't watched it was really gross
and uh
My favorite movie in recent years however is wild tales which I told Joe to watch
Rancid it fucking loved it. You know my girlfriend kept running around my house going these are some wild tales
These tales are getting wilder by the minute and they were really wild. It was six wild tales tales of revenge
Argentinian movie it is the fucking shit if you have a problem with foreign movies it won't bother you
There's not a lot of subtitles and it's just six amazing stories
I fucking loved it. You should check it out. All right. I don't think it's streaming for anywhere
But you can probably run it for three bucks on items and you told me that this was a sort of a pulp fiction -y kind of thing
Yeah, the stories don't intertwine in that way, but it was just as like
The stories were just as cool and surprising and everything all right twist and intern and anybody we know in this picture
Or is it all just it's all overseas people overseas people okay, who are people to Joe? I'm not saying that I'm not saying that that that don't you put those words in my mouth
Don't you do that to me? Don't you put those fingers in my mouth by the way. I haven't said anything for the last hour
It's really annoying when I'm trying to speak on a podcast. Don't you put that thumb through my forehead and soldier entire
Fingers in hand into my mouth
If you're watching the movie with us Daniel Rackler
Cliff that is now being haunted by the woman in black the mattress on the bed is coming up with some sort of ghostly period scenario
Uh, and there's a figure now rising out of the puddle yeah on the bed which is gross? Uh
And who is that figure is it a young boy? I believe it is
It's a child that was left in mud
It looked like that you ever seen that peanut butter baby
No, I did not what that's a vine. I think it's like they've covered like a two -year -old baby from head to toe and peanut butter
And the baby looks at the camera and is like hey, it's horrifying
It's one of the most popular vines which tells you how
Who covered the baby in peanut butter the parents I would assume
That's not like abusive in some way it probably is but people are laughing too hard to care
Is that that's disturbing yeah, all right. Yeah, I mean can he breathe and stuff
Uh, yeah, he can breathe
I assume they didn't like jam it at his nose
Now after our potter looks a bit like McCulloch in these days
Who rat cliff? Yeah, a little bit they got a bit of he's got a bit of a kulk invite a modern day kulk
Um now I'll tell you this uh, we just watched rat cliff experience
Sights of terror one after the next
He looks like he's about to fall asleep
Yeah, he's now going back out to the main land or whatever from this island where the haunted houses
You think the director would have been like Daniel
Let's try one where you look like you've ever been scared in your entire life
I mean, I don't know why he goes back to the house after this he doesn't look that scared but what's happening now
There's people being burned there's a fire and he's going into save
What I think he believes is a child inside because in the house he saw a thing on the wall that said you could have saved him
So I think he thinks that was a sign and now he's going to go in here and try to save somebody from this burning building
And he just ran right in
You know what I liked
Uh, which is what I would do that's why I liked it
I'd be a hero like that you know what I mean yeah
I you see that in me right
I
I mean, you know, I'd put you at a 50 -50
You know, I just I feel like a real hero, you know, I feel like I really have it in me
The woman in black is there in the fireman being
What are you singing a real hero
Well, we just watched a child commit suicide
It's also very loud
It is kind of loud, but this is the first part that's been loud because a child committed suicide
So I guess they cranked the music up a bit for this
Lot of smoke
He's let me tell you if you were in that amount of you know how quickly you'd have smoke inhalation in that amount of smoke
Joe, do you feel it's true the old expression where there's smoke there's fire?
You know, I always believed in that one. Yeah, but I was equated to STD's as my dad taught me
What does that mean like if you see a bubble there's probably going to be more bubbles in your future?
No, he literally would say if you see smoke coming out of a lady's pants
She's probably burning. Yeah, no, I he never said that. Yeah, you know
What else would there be if there was smoke a fog machine?
Yeah, but I mean, I guess the expression means
If you suspect something, it's probably true. Yeah, okay. I suspect it
Well, I don't agree with it because I suspected that we were almost done with this movie
And I think we're about 50 minutes in yeah
I am
Truggling right now because I stopped paying attention to the film. I don't know what's happening
He's plus I've seen it before just go same by same
Yeah, even though I've seen this before I'm lost. I can't remember why he took this job
I don't understand why he won't leave this house. They said how would you like to work in a creepy house with ghosts that are trying to kill you?
I mean
Do our book work? Why are the
Why are the ghosts showing up everywhere?
I don't remember that either. I think somebody killed ourselves in the house, right?
Where is he now? He's in this guy's house. Yeah, this guy's bringing him a whiskey rack up looks like he could use a ham sandwich
Before he gets that whiskey. Yeah, Radcliffe does look quite a macy. He has a very Fiona apple vibe to him right now
Dark shadow potter baby, right is that Fiona apple shadow boxer, but I made it shadow potter
I couldn't sing one video shadow potter baby
I couldn't sing one Fiona Apple song if you had a gun to my head right now. I couldn't remember you ready when you cast your spell, right?
I'm gonna get weird out on the horn
Is
You've never heard of Fiona apple song Fiona apple is I know her song is just I couldn't an amazing song right?
I couldn't recall any a by the way gorgeous is a distant seat. I couldn't recall any of them from memory is what I'm saying. Yeah
What if you had to do a weird out spoof what would you do? What song would you do?
Well, I already wrote it and it was a big hit in the sixth grade
Little song called losing my pet pigeon
Oh, she was a spoof of losing my religion. No, I got it. You didn't need to explain people loved it
Mine was also in our EM song really. Yeah, it was a spoof of stand
Was it shiny crappy poop hole? No, that's all the top of my head
No, it was a takeoff on I get zero from Joe
It was a take off because I want to tell you about mine and you're just telling me more shiny crappy poop hole
Well, I was starting with the song stand and you're just coming in with your own ideas. Okay, which is selfish your song was called what?
Quief oh, no
Quief in the place where you pee oh, god
Quief from the place where you pee man, it stinks. Oh
Joe you gotta stop singing that
Just look around and see everybody sick
Quief from the place where you pee
How how do you have sex ever?
I just made that up on the spot. I thought that was funny. Oh, I thought that was something you wrote when you were a child
Oh, I believe that just now. I made it fun and hard to believe you just wrote that as an adult. I made it up
All right, you wouldn't listen to that song
I just did and the answer is no again knowing what I know now I wouldn't
I
Why not
I don't have to answer my questions to you don't have to answer your questions
Uh, and often it funerals. I'll sing this. I'll sing. Would you believe they put a man in the tomb
Man in the tomb
All right. Oh, that's good and it's clean you didn't have to work blue
And I respect sing it just like bill calls, but you select your people on remember build say you guys don't have to work blue
You gotta be like me
You gotta be an upstanding member of society who wears his pants buttoned all well
What he said and then what he did and it's terrible. It's a very disappointing story. Oh, sorry Joe if my truth bothers you
It's just I'm still not over losing the childhood hero. It's still heartbreaking to me. Hey, sorry America if my truth's too much
Hey, I didn't know I was doing a podcast with Jamie Kielstein. I don't know who that is
He's a truth teller man. Oh, well then yeah, I guess I am Jamie Trillstein Kielstein. Okay. I guess I am Jamie Kielstein
Girls look out for that woman in black
Now I would losing my pet pigeon go I don't remember the lyrics
You know the chorus
Uh, that's me in the corner
That's me with the bird seed
I don't know right? I was pretty good. Excellent. What the hell could you do with it? I don't even know
Uh, no right there. I think you just answered that
Losing my pet pigeon. Did you love where it all has a boy? Of course
There we tell a story to you about getting where it all is your autograph when I was very young young boy. No
I was at six flags over mid -America in St. Louis. It was my first concert and it was to see Weird Al and I was shaking
I was so excited
She tired day. I was so excited. It was about 11 years old
My mom took me
And then we're waiting in line for the Buccaneer, which is the big pirate ship that goes back and forth. Yeah
And my mom goes oh my gosh Pat
I think that's Weird Al and he was in line like one row behind me
To where like when our rows crossed we were gonna be like right next to each other
Holy shit. What the hell's he waiting in lines for? I don't know. He was probably just a nice guy
Weird Al can't cut off kids in line at a amusement park, you know good point
So he's got this beautiful blonde and his arm possibly a prostitute like hiding her face from the sun hiding it in his arm pit
You think he had it was a hooker?
Maybe it just seemed too good to be true for Weird Al but he's a rich man, I guess right
um
And I had told my mom this joke earlier. Oh, we were waiting in line. I go mom
How much does a pirate pay for corn? She was how much I go a Buccaneer
Oh boy, you wrote that yeah, well, we're in line for the Buccaneer. That's very good
So she goes pat you should tell Weird Al your joke and I go no no and then as we pass each other my mom goes can my son tell you a joke real quick
And I'm like mom and he goes yeah, sure, so I tell him my joke Buccaneer
Guy it gives me a big hearty laugh
Signs a piece of paper that I still have to this death
Could have been nicer and that was that and if I wanted to
I wanted to lie like everyone else exactly like in the movie fear
Now see when other people tell this story uh and lie like everyone does with their like origin story
Then uh, they would be like and Weird Al told me like you got to keep writing jokes kid
And now I'm Dave Chappelle. No, that never happened of course
That didn't happen, but everyone who tells their comedy story tells it like that and I don't believe you
Well, everybody's a lying piece of shit. Yeah
Now I want to get in touch with Weird Al and pitchqueeth
He works clean though. Is it too old of a song to reference at this point? It absolutely is
Also, it should probably rhyme so you know what's being parodied
Does it have to rhyme?
Stand I don't we've definitely they all rhyme. I will say America is bad
That's what's close enough. I think America's ready for a song about quince
I love quay humor. I always have uh, I think it's very funny
I like period jokes quite a bit. Yeah, I just like that kind of thing
Smelly balls. I just like this sort of stuff. Okay shit jokes. I'm not above them
You're kind of like a
Sort of a high brow
Like a George Wallace type
like a
Who's the guy? Not George Wallace the comedian who's one of the funniest men a lot. I this has already fallen apart
I meant George Wallace the quote humorous to used to be on 60 minutes all the time
Yeah, I'm a very New Yorker type. Yeah, but I like this concept. Let's see like this seen the movie Danny Ratcliffe is is
submerged in mud and I'm pretending it's poop and it's making me laugh. Okay
It's just making me happy. It helps you out. That's fine
Yeah, pretend he's swimming through poop. It makes the movie funny makes it horrific to me
My favorite part in Austin Powers when he drinks the poop and goes it's a bit nutty
No, see that's my least favorite part of Austin power. That's your least favorite. Yeah, that's not for me
That kind of joke. I love that joke
I love that joke. It's coffee tastes like shit. It is shit aust
Yeah, that's not for me. I find it very funny
Now I really this is a moment where I wish we were paying attention
What does this guy doing here? He's got Danny Ratcliffe tied to a rope
Right, he's pulling them out of it. Very on never -ending story move. Yeah
He's trying to pull he's got the rope tied to his car
He's trying to back the car up to pull Ratcliffe out of this mud hole that he's right right he's having no luck which I don't get
I mean how hard could it be I guess I guess the suction is you know. Oh no, they're trying to pull that thing out
I'm sorry the rope was not tied to Ratcliffe the rope was tied to this
To this thing they're pulling out of the mud. I tried to solve the mystery
I assume with the dead shoulder and look at this they're pulling a goddamn car out of the mud
Joe you're giving like a true play by play of the same well, I mean you know
I
It's the least I can do for the people that really want to know what's going on in the woman in black
They're not only a car, but a goddamn carriage is coming out. Well, it's just a carriage
I thought it was a car and I missed what if there was a horse on the front being dragged out too covered in poop a poop
He's got a little boy's body there. Yeah from the carriage
The horse looks on the camera and goes get me out of here and I ate horse and around
Right and then they never mention it again. It goes right back to being a whore move
Right
Right, right
Yeah
I'm screaming myself horse over here and I thought the horse they shot had a bad day
I can't think of a famous horse that died
I was gonna say old Yeller don't look a dog gift me in the mouth
That one doesn't make sense
Now he's calling the body of a young boy covered in mud who is dead. Yeah
Oh now we couldn't show us a little uh
Little Medreff Potter
I want the way they dress back then this guy just got pulled out of a mud pit
He had to get cleaned up. He's now putting on a full white silk button down shirt
Yeah, he's putting essentially another suit on it right right
He's got a vest on a tie. This is this is this is cash. Yeah
You know, I'll tell you give me a bathrobe and a towel for around my head any day of the week when I get caught in the rain
Well nowadays, I mean
People aware, you know, a pair of boxer shorts to uh to a casino to a fine casino. That's right
You know you find a nice casino like the commerce here in LA. Yeah
That serves a money crystal sandwich. There's no uh, there's no sense of dressing up for things anymore
And California's even worse out at the most
My friend John Harwoods dear friend of mine once took me to the commerce casino here in LA and and wore a suit
No
Because he felt that it was better to let it was a swim suit. He made a mistake
I wore suit because he felt like it was good to doll it up for the dealers and maybe get some free stuff
And uh, I think ordered a money crystal sandwich and spilled the white powder sugar all down the front of the suit
I mean it was just a picture of trash in action
It was really nice. The money crystal if I'm not mistaken is a ham sandwich on french toast ham turkey cheese on french toast with powdered sugar on top
It's a delicious sandwich. I don't blame for it
The
Commerce casino is very disgusting. It's the one I'm thinking of it just looks like a right elx lodge
Like a recall kind of
Yeah, it's a kind of like a big room with all the games in yeah, I just want to admit
Uh, and thank god. I hated it because I would have been out there every couple nights
But there was an old Chinese man next to me
Leaning completely into my space and gnawing
Like gnawing as if he had no teeth on this giant turkey leg
Ooh at the Commerce casino. He's balancing a plate like almost on my arm
Big pieces of chicken falling out of his mouth
I love a giant turkey leg. He was eating it almost in my mouth
Do you ever get the giant? You're supposed to be real or a toy
No, it's real. The what the rabbit thing he just found up. Oh, it's just a toy. He's this is like the
He's luring out the woman in black. Okay. I thought that was supposed to be an actual animal. I was like
Come on guys. No, no, it's supposed to be that he's whining up the tool. You don't have to have ILM, but let's get
It's not good. Let's let's at least get spielberg on the job
I mean that we're supposed to believe a monkey's playing the maracas. Oh, man
That's I see some maracas there in a front row with my plan with don't get mad at me
Don't get mad at me you. That's Pat famous skeptical Guido is the name of that character
That's the name of that character. I don't know why we got to go in a haunted house. I mean
Didn't see that cool to me. I don't know
I'm supposed more of a scared. I was gonna join in
But you just don't want to seem let me get a word in it. Would you shine? What can I let you shine? Oh, I don't want to anymore. All right good
I just saw that we have about 10 or 12 minutes left in this film and that the relief that washed over me
It was like it was like we're gazing
Joe we are supposed to be putting out a product that people love to listen to listen people you can't even get through the people seem to like it
No matter how much we complain. Yeah, no matter how slow that the conversation gets
I thought tonight was a was a good time. I had a good time. I almost said a lot of fun that I downgraded it to a good time
I had a good time wasn't a lot of fun. I had a good time
But I'm a little hot my apartment's very hot right now sure is
I paid too little attention to the movie this week. I've no idea what the hell's happening even though I own this film
Yeah, I don't know what's happening right now
It's okay. We each had one drink which is now left me in that weird
Kind of sweaty. I had one drink zone, you know
I had a gluten -free beer and it was disgusting. What's disgusting about it?
Well, it's missing like some key ingredient of beer and you you really tasted it tasted like
spoiled water. It was disgusting. It was like bud light with like a hint of an expired cranberry in it and I hated it
I hate an expired cranberry. Yeah
You just favorite cranberry take them off the shelves when they get expired folks
I'm in there buying cranberries five six nights a week and I like them fresh
Your friend who I met yesterday who was very lovely has a son who's 11 yes, who writes a blog
Yeah, the kids are damn genius and I read the Buddhist by the way. Yeah, I read the blog to this 11 -year -old kid. It's like
The kid's kids not published. Yeah, he's like a doogie house or time
But at one point he made a joke in one of the entries where he's like
He's like let's say you're eating a Fiji apple parentheses because all other apples taste like and they shit on all the other apples
I can't remember the analogy. He's roasted apples and then he puts an asterix under the piece
He get through the whole piece and then under at the very bottom of his an asterix and it says promise
I won't be an apple racist ever again. It's nice. I mean, I was like this kid's 11
Yeah, he's great. I mean, he's got too funny parents. It's probably a big part of it
One of the one of the entries was called I don't care if God exists or not
Yeah, and the first sentence of the blog entry was
In quotes and I don't care if you exist comma said got says God petulently. Yeah, the 11 -year -old wrote this. Yeah
What is what is he's a very impressive young man. I've wasted everything. I've wasted it all
That's scared me check out the kid's blog. It's called some idiots blog is the name of it. Yeah
He's a very smart very funny kid. Yeah
What pet what uh, I thought of when you were talking about him making fun of apples
Is this a funny sketch? It would be like a 10 -year -old boy and it's the comedy central roast of like brussel sprouts
Okay, would that be I think it'd be a pretty funny sketch like five kids get up and rip on wide brussel sprouts
If you could get the kids to take on the demeanor of adult
Yeah, no, of course then it would be very fun and like maybe by the end
It's like some kid who's like real crude about it. Yeah, you know, yeah shoved these up your mother's twat, you know
Yeah, like a five -year -old boy. Well, you gotta have the kid that's doing like the nick -to -polo like all hunched over
Like like you don't I mean like close to the mic. Let me tell you some folks if I want to eat brussel sprouts
Yeah, this thing would be amazing. I think yeah, and you definitely need a a Lisa Lamponelli some heavy -set young girl
She's very thin these days. I don't like it
I do often find a bit of sadness when somebody I
Know as being heavy -set loses weight. Yeah, I know Lisa
Oh as a friend so I I was happy for her that it was good for her to do that obviously
But I never I don't know I don't know in any way on a personal level Seth Rogan or Jonah Hill
I will say this I did not like Jonah Hill thinning out. I was happy to seem to get fat again
Yeah, I agree and I'm not crazy about thinning out Seth Rogan. I like these guys husky
All right
Not in a mean way because I want to see them fail. It's just weird. I hear you there
Newman slimmed down Wayne night. Newman's in kind of a health sazer actually
It but he kind of puffed out again, right?
Yeah, yeah, he's fat again. Is he Newman fat again? The audience there was such a huge laugh of delight when Newman came on the screen
I love Newman. He doesn't even say anything, but he was good enough. He just has a couple lines
Now is he Newman heavy again or is he just heavier than thin
He looks like a guy who lost a ton of weight and then put a ton of weight back on
But it's not as bad as he was an early Newman does. All right, well, that's good
He's more like buttoned up paraslacks Newman by the end
Okay, that's fine. I can live with that
She only had a jam happy or a healthy. I just know I hear you just get used to it
I hear you we need fat people on this planet now
Of course far earlier John candy had lost a ton of weight
I don't know if they would have been that's funny
I'll tell you what's his name goodman is shaving him off, man
Yeah, he I mean he goes up and down and I like goodman no matter what he's in. I love him
I just saw the trailer for 10 clover field lane. It looks amazing. I love clover field
I have not seen the trailer for 10 clover it's apparently not related. It's not a sequel. That makes no sense. Why would you do that?
I don't I don't know Pat am I JJ fucking Abrams?
No, you're not
I bet that the
I just thought of I just thought of the nictipolo joke for the brussel sprouts roast okay go for it
Oh, wait, Joe the comedy central roast of brussel sprouts. Yeah, roasted brussel sprouts. Oh, that's funny
I got you. Yeah, you're goddamn right. That's fine. I got you. All right carry on
Let me tell you something folks if I wanted to eat green disgusting balls. I go suck her
mit the frog's cock
It's got it
That's a perfect brussel sprouts roast Joe. Could we find parents to let their kids do these jokes?
I think probably so in this sick fucking town. Yeah, they can offer a month like Simba in the line. Yeah
They're parents paying you to let their kids know it's gonna be he's gonna be
Under our supervision for like a month and a half you won't be able to see him take him. Please take him
Have some money. Yeah
Please treat yourself because you're all who's
Yeah, it's a disgusting town we live in we live out here in Hollywood. Holly weird. I call it. Hey, that's yeah
I call it hazy wood because everybody's in a fog
Just made that up just now. Hi as well
Look at Radcliffe's adorable son in this movie
Not for me. I think that kid's adorable. What kid's not for me and this is the park now where
Radcliffe dies. I think the kid dies too. It's not a very happy ending. No
The train and the woman in black comes and yeah horror movies don't have to end happily Joe. Well, I like that
It's not a happy ending most horror movies end with too much hope in my opinion these days American ones
Just fucking chat on good night mommy for ending without home
I listen. I don't like I didn't mind the good night mommy ended
It does end with hope it ends with the three ghosts like we're finally together. Oh wow
I don't mind that it ended oh
Well Radcliffe and his son just got run over by a train and now you're gonna see the dead children
That's pretty cool in the train. That's a cool movie. It's a cool movie. I'm glad we watched it so carefully
And then the woman in black
And everybody's dead now whenever that guy's looking out on the train track can't be pretty
He's looking at the remnants of Radcliffe and the kid. They're not gonna show it because it's a PG -13 film
Do you know that website that people we got real into in college
That was like pictures of horrific things the now are probably on NBC. I didn't know either way. Oh he lived
Like a you know like somebody got hit by a truck. I do but hold on Radcliffe lived. I forgot that that happened. Okay
Maybe he does now or no they're dead. They're in heaven. Yeah. That's right because they see the wife or whatever
I think yeah, they're dead
This is very similar to the end of the last Harry Potter movie isn't there a whole thing on like a train thing and
Trans were always backward into Harry Potter. Have you seen all you don't know if he's alive or not
Have I seen what all the potters? Of course I have they're fucking incredible. You take me for I'm excited for magnificent beasts
I am and I'm not I can really give or take that guy
Well, I think it'll be a fun flick. Yeah
Apparently, it's a prequel and uh your boy Gandalf is or a dumbledore excuse me is really campaigning to come back
Has anyone ever done this as a character James Gandalf feigning
No
Hey, we gotta get to the twit that was
Right, I like that. We gotta get the ring back to Bilbo
I like that. I think it's very good. You should not pass so
Did you hear me? You dumb fuck you not pass you dumb fuck and you could tell your ugly sister she cannot pass needed
Um
Here's my character. I want to do William H. Macy Gray. I don't know how to do it though
We gotta get we gotta get these characters up and right. I don't have there's not enough famous William H. Macy or Macy Gray things to do that
All I know is I try
And I barely remember that song. Yeah, you could you could do something out of that
And that's our film folks
It just ended with them in heaven finally reunited as a family because the mom had died early on
But then the woman of blacks watching them and so what does that mean? Maybe they're not in heaven
I got a habit over here. I got a habit over here. I got habits coming out my goddamn ease
And now AJ won't do his homework
Carmella
Where's the ZD? Huh? I like it. You can't say Carmella though. You gotta say Samwise. Oh, you're Samwise
Gangey
Which Samwise Gangey Gangey sounds like Angie which sounds like an Italian name Samwise Gangey sounds like it could be like a villain
They bring in for season four of this prank. Oh wait, isn't one of the guys named Sam
No, no
Who's the guy with the white hair? Hey, Tony. I want you to a tape
There you go. I want you to meet my cousin. This is a Samwise Gangey's
Hey, are you doing Samwise ever say you're Samwise you'll be where you want
And what you know, I know your father. I know you father Sam dumb Gangey's okay. I'm gonna I'm breaking your balls
I'm breaking your bull I break it your bull Samwise Sam dumb you get it
You know what joke? I wish I would have been earlier
You know what joke? I wish I would have been earlier what
When we were talking about bad dirty grandpa. Yeah, we should have said
I don't know why didn't arrow keeps making these movies. Maybe he should change his name to Bobby no deniro
That's pretty good. I know. I wish I would have said that. See Aaron Hines is that dude's name. He's a great actor
Well folks, you've been listening to we'll see you in hell the podcast brought to you
By the Fangoria podcast network produced by Thomas DeFaio and executive produced by Ken Hanley
Of Fangoria Entertainment for press opportunities advertising inquiries and information about we'll see you in hell contact
Cannotfangoria .com
Follow Pat Walsh on Twitter at the Patrick Walsh y 'all follow me at joderosa comedy on Twitter
And if you are in the
What's my next?
I
Can't even remember. Oh, yeah tour in in March if you're around that South
Not a bunch of places. I'll be in Wilmington, North Carolina. I'll be in
Hadisburg, Mississippi. I'll be in Greenville, South Carolina
Uh, I will be in Minneapolis, Minnesota. So come on out in March. That's all I got
I will be eating at the Glendale suit plantation
Uh, this coming Thursday
I'll probably start with the salad bar and ease into
Perhaps Sunday sometimes I like to put the soft serve in my coffee there
Uh, thanks everybody. We hope you had a good time and I'll see you at soup plantation