I'm here for Bet Rivers online casino and sportsbook with poker icon Phil Helmuth.
And now thanks to the excitement of Bet Rivers, I'm also a slots icon.
That's great! And a same -game parlay icon. Cool, cool. A blackjack icon,
a money -line icon, a roulette. Take it from Phil Helmuth. If you love games,
Bet Rivers is the place to play in Bet. Bet Rivers. Games on.
Must be 21 plus in present in West Virginia. Void were prohibited. Terms in conditions apply.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another, no other sportsbook has
an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning, or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
winning hits different here must be 21 plus gambling problem called winning 100
gambler offer not available in all states terms apply see fanatic sports book
app there's a new podcast app that delivers chilling true crime stories straight
to your mobile device every day they release a new episode that
investigate the gruesome true acts of America's war serial killers and you can
explore into the minds of psychopaths and murderers to get started find and
download murder minute from the app store or visit murder minute dot com that's
M -U -R -D -E -R -M -I -N -U -T -E dot com to get your daily dose of true crime creepiness delivered
and straight to your mobile device.
How are you folks?
it's, uh, you know, it, you know, what it is, it's the damn podcast that you download every week.
Uh, it's, we'll see you in hell. We're here to talk about some horror flicks and whatnot.
God.
I really gotta start taking over that intro.
No, it's mine.
You do the on with the Joe's.
It's just so sloppy, you know.
Like if it was your first listen, you'd never come back after that.
Well, I mean, it's, look, I think after they hear that slick tune at the top,
sure they know that we're they know we're the real deal. All right, the real deal with
Bill McNeil. What's that mean? It's from news radio Phil Harman's character. Oh, you
never watched much news radio. We've discussed it on the show. It's one of the best sitcoms
ever made. You want the whole series? I can loan it to you. You can buy it for 20 bucks
on Amazon. All five shoes. You're gonna just take me through it. No, but you would absolutely
love news radio. I mean, what an ensemble. I don't doubt that I would love it. Why doesn't
get a lot of syndication love. It did when I was growing up in Missouri, it was on all the time,
but it was always the 130 AM rerun. But luckily, I was just up and I would watch it. I loved it.
I never miss an episode when it aired on NBC back in the day. Okay. But it doesn't get the love,
honestly, because the lead is Dave Foley and not Dave Schwimmer. You know what I'm saying? Hey,
look back when Dave was a was a pretty good looking fella. You know, it's kind of cuteness about him.
The show it's the kind of show I really aspired to and the fact that it was on for five years is crazy because it was a
Multicam that just did refused to dumb it down, you know, that's nice
And they'd also get insane sometimes which I loved amazing cast
Feel that much Phil Hartman, you know
It's just a treat like you can't go wrong. Especially you I assume you love Phil Hartman
Yeah, knowing that there's five seasons of a great show where he plays maybe his best role
I hope that is he's only in four of them though, right?
Yes, Joe.
I'm not saying it to be funny.
I'm saying he died before the fifth season.
Yeah, they're placed him with John Loves, which is those episodes are fine too, but they ain't the same.
I enjoy Loves.
There are some really incredible news radios, but I'd love to before we get into those,
get on with the show and at the same time, get on with a Joe,
Yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo
Why is it even called Jermaker maybe for Jermaker?
It's got a little bit of a caribbean feel to make her make crazy.
I just remember everybody always like the hard course couldn't correct your pronunciation
of that one.
Yeah, because they're so cool because they like Led Zeppelin.
This whole subculture of people when I was in high school who were like, you'll never
forget it, man. I like Zeppelin and Pink Floyd, like two of the biggest rock bands in the
history of music. You're not in some weird cult. Shut the fuck up.
Would you do tonight, man? What didn't I do? Joe, I took an hour and 15 minute drive home
from work, which is a new record for me. Wow. And then I met a friend from like sixth, seventh
great. And we had a fantastic time. I was telling Joe before the show, what are the odds
that you go meet up with a friend from seventh grade? And he's normal and nice and fun to
be around. I was expecting the worst. I had a great time. What he's an editor. He edited
a horror picture. A lot of people have seen on Netflix called We Come At Night. Okay.
Yeah. That's pretty cool. Let me make sure that's the right one. Sure. What made you guys
lose touch after the seventh grade. That's that's a weird year to kind of lose touch with somebody.
We were in young performers theater together, which was a non -school related theater thing.
And I met him there. He was very into both. You would have, I mean, you would love this guy.
His two obsessions are old school hip -hop, the oldest of school hip -hop, the history of hip -hop,
and also horror movies.
He showed me one of the first actual horror movies I ever saw, which was Texas James
Amasker part two.
And it traumatized me so greatly that I have not seen it since and I saw it when I was
about 11 years old.
All right.
Yeah.
It's, that's, that's funny because now when you watch that one, it's kind of.
I'm going to rewatch it.
But I was so shook and up by it and the guy like eating his scalp, which I remember very vividly.
That disgusted me and I remember my mom watching it with my mom and my mom being like oh Jesus Christ
Yeah, that really disgusted her that part. Yeah, I found it genuinely nauseating. It's pretty gross
And at the time I had seen almost no horror
But the guy was great
He's my buddy
I hope it leads to an adult friendship here in Los Angeles because he was recently moved here
you know, nice guy. That's great. What do I want to look them up? And you have no service in your
goddamn apartment. I have service. I have, but I have Verizon. Okay. The best. The best of the best.
Only the best for a guy like me. You know me. I'm a man of great tastes and a man of wealth and
test. Yeah. And leisure. All right. Now I'm on your Wi -Fi and I can report that he edited the film's
steak land. Oh, really? That's a that's a pretty popular
horror movie. It is. And also the film, and I had seen this
one, I just mixed the words up. Why would this not be in
your list of movies, dude? Or maybe it's not out yet. No, I
recognized it. Well, you weren't sure about the title. Maybe
you thought it was the thing that you'd seen. Well, I said we, we
still here. We are still here definitely saw but I mix them up. There's so many movies
called We Are Something. I remember hearing that title. I don't know what the movie's
about. It's a very cool little ghost story. I recommend it if you haven't seen it. It's
on Netflix. Would you call it a ghost with the most story? I would. Okay. Fair enough.
He also worked on cold in July with Dexter, which I thought was a pretty cool movie that
It was on Netflix as well.
Dexter or the actor, Michael C. Hall, yeah.
Okay, I don't know that movie,
but it sounds like he's doing some good work.
I won't spoke with a exotic dancer
who told me that the filthiest customer she'd ever had
was one Michael C. Hall.
Why do you blow the guy's spot up like that?
He was a single man.
She said he was a charmer, he tipped well,
but he just loved bringing the ladies back.
Yeah, you know?
He liked it all nasty.
Right, style.
Now what are you doing?
that every record's like, you got to dance with the night, dance with the day, dance at
home morning away. We got a rock. You know, like every, like almost like a nursery
rhyme. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It was, I think it was $10. It's a double record anthology from
Amoeba. Well, you put on your coat. You put on your pants. You come out with me for a little
romance. Yeah. Yeah. I think you get it. Yeah. I mean, it's not, you know, man apparently
was a drunk. Nice. Like a complete drunk. He looks like a drunk on that cover. Um, but
it's an enjoyable record. I went through a little phase where all I wanted to hear was
that sort of 50s, like, you know, early Elvis. Uh -huh. That's sort of, I guess they called it
R &B back then, but
was really yeah, yeah, race music.
Yeah, yeah, it was a lot of fun.
I'll tell you this.
I love Elvis Presley.
I don't need to see those hips jar
right in the round.
Why not in my home.
See, I like that.
I like a guy that tosses a little
pure sex into it.
And little Richard, I don't need his
who's who's they're too exciting for my teenage daughter.
It's the devil's music, you know, are you aware of this?
It is, right? Well, just just so you're aware.
Joe, let me take you over if I might to pass movie corner.
You didn't ask how my day was by the way.
How was it, Joe?
It was nice. All right, what'd you do?
Had some drinks with a very lovely person.
All right. I got I finished a story that I'm giving to an anthology sci -fi comic book that
we'll be coming out next year. Penhouse forum, Joe. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You can call
what it is. It's it's actually a thigh high comic book. Okay. What's thigh huh? Like like you said
penthouse like thigh house and I said sci -fi and it rhymes. You mean pantyhose?
Like thigh -high boots. Like they're like, you know, like what they call hooker boots
or whatever. Where are you getting that from penthouse? It's sexual. Okay. Why, do you really
not get the correlation? Oh, that's fine. Oh, fuck you. And yeah, I just did some work
and had a nice day, ate some chicken that I'd baked yesterday.
All right.
Big to hold on.
Don't bury the lead.
Sorry, it's not as exciting as a reunion from the fifth grade, seventh grade.
But, you know, I do my best.
I do my best to keep up with your wild rock and roll lifestyle.
Thanks for trying.
Hey, try what do you got for movie quarter? I saw a couple films from the Joe Bob
Bragg's shutter marathon. Uh -huh. I've been loving the hell out of it. I got my free trial of
shutter. I think when you go beyond free, it's like $4 or something very cheap. What a treasure trove.
And I'm going through it in order. I started with a picture I've never seen called tourist trap.
Acclaimed by Stephen King and many others as being like a really unsung gem of the horror scene.
And I figured if Briggsie, Joe Bob Briggs, was kicking off his marathon with it, it must be pretty good.
but folks, I wasn't let down.
I have not watched that film yet.
It's good.
It's terrific.
It's very weird.
Okay.
But in like the best way,
it was compared unfavorably,
but how many movies can really rank with it
in the horror genre?
Two Texas Chainsaw Masker
and I don't think it's far off.
It's got this like really weird feeling to it
and it's deeply unsettling.
And sometimes in the next moment, it's just stupid.
It's kind of like a David Lynch in that way.
Okay.
But they got a bunch of mannequins in it, dummies,
which, you know, I haven't seen Be Creepy in a long,
they never freaked me out.
These were creepy fucking mannequins.
You never know if you're looking at a mannequin
or a real person.
They have all these people in like mannequin masks
that are terrifying.
Okay.
And then, you know, the one scene where I was thankful
to have Joe Bob Briggs interrupt because I was terrified is the bad guy while wearing
like a mannequin face. Are you ruining anything by telling me this? All right, movie came out
in 1976. Well, I mean, I've never seen it. It's not, it's not a big hit this year. No. I mean,
he's an unsung classic as you said. I feel like spoiling a movie like this or a slasher movie is
pretty hard to do. Okay. But he's done. He covers this woman's entire face and wax. Like he's
going to make her into a, you know, a mannequin and it suffocates her and they just stay right
in a tight shot of her just like, like Lou, it's like someone being buried alive, sort
of, but with wax is very disturbing.
Okay.
And then they cut back to Joe Bob Briggs and he was like, that was pretty intense, wasn't
it?
And I was like, yes, Joe, yes.
I really loved it.
I see it in horror thons in LA fairly often when they do their yearly like five movie marathons
of the new Beverly.
I've seen it there.
But this is the first time I've actually watched the movie.
It did not disappoint recommended on shutter, watch it with the Joe Bob Briggs interruptions.
All right.
Well, I'll check it out.
I'll check it out on here say so.
I watched the newest anthology series on Netflix creeped out.
Okay, which is geared towards children. Okay, but the trailer was actually really fucking creepy.
There's a kid that walks around in very much like a mannequin mask and he's sort of the entity
that makes weird shit happen. And the trailer sells it as like a very dark thing. Unfortunately,
when you watch it, it's, it's, you know, it's another RL -stein kind of, you know, a girl gets us,
her dream smart phone. Right. And it turns out to post a little too much about her life.
You know, it's shit like that. Uh, I guess if you didn't hate goosebumps, the movie,
I didn't say goosebumps too. I Halloween style or whatever the hell. I mean, I didn't care for
I was too old for it when it came out. I recently went back and tried to re what like for the first
time watch goosebumps. And like, are you afraid of the dark and those shows? But did you see the film
goosebumps. I watched about half of it. It wasn't very good, but it wasn't very bad.
Um, it was too, it's like all those kids movies that come out like house with the clock
and its walls, the house with the clock and its walls. Behind the high, high, yeah, it's,
you know, it's, it's more of a say. It's a little too child. They don't get dark enough
That the kids movies these days that are supposed to be dark don't have a dark enough edge and I find it boring
Do you think that they were way darker when we were kids or that?
We were kids and they seemed way darker. They're absolutely way darker watch something wicked this way comes
He puts a child on the merry -go -round and and as it spins he turns into an old man
Right it's fucking creepy and then and then he does the thing with the old man that turns him into a baby
it's fucking, it's weird, man. It's dark, right? They just don't have, even if you took
those scenes out of that film, you still have this great storyline of the, and the, the
waiting us in the drama of adjacent robots were regretting his life and thinking he didn't
do enough and showing like the limbless, the ex football player who's now limbless from
the war, he could have his limbs back, right? You know, it's like, there's just, there's
there's no weight like that in goosebumps. It's literally just my dad's nuts. And he doesn't
want to stop in this folder because of the puppet will jump out of it. Right. You know.
So that's all that's all. You know, we've, as we've discussed, returned to us, never
writing story, peanut butter solution. There's so many movies when I was a kid that are what
the fuck is peanut butter solution? There's a movie about a boy who has cancer and he starts
putting peanut butter on his head to grow back. Someone tells him to do this. And he winds up
growing like incredibly long hair. It is, I know I'm not doing any sort of justice. There's paintbrushes
made of human hair. It's deeply disturbing. It's supposed to be dark or is it supposed to be like
kids movie like funny. Came out like around the same time as like the boy who could fly. If you remember
When I wrote for Cinematical, which was AOL's movie site, I wrote for them for a few years,
and I did a piece called, I say a piece by that, I mean it was several thousand words
and I made $25.
But it was about, it was the top seven or whatever most disturbing kids movies.
And the comment section on this thing was in the thousands by the end of the day.
and I was responding with people and they were like, holy fuck, the peanut butter solution.
I remember that, like it ruined my life. I don't even know where you'd find it. I bet it's not
even on iTunes. But is it a comedic film? No. It's just, it's an unsettling, disturbing kids film.
It was Canadian, so that kind of, but something wicked this way comes is in the same ballpark.
Just movies that were for whatever reason came off as really disturbing and they were for a child
audience. And why are there paintbrushes made of human hair? I don't remember. I just remember
being troubled by the film. All right. I'm going to look it up now. My next picture in the
Joe Bob Briggsathon, I'll stick to that theme tonight was, uh, slip away camp. And people have
been requesting on this show for years. Um, you know, I'll just go ahead and do it.
I think we already did it because I talked about the Joe Bob saying we talked about sleep
away camp.
Maybe you said you didn't want to give away the ending.
I think it's got one of the best endings in all of horror.
Wild ending.
Wild.
The picture really held up.
The one thing I found baffling about it was the chef character who two minutes into the
movie is vocally lusting after 10 year old girl and then tries to molest one.
Yes.
rough stuff. I mean, I was blown away by this. Um, and it's it's back in the time when
the, when the boss is just like, cut that out. Well, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Right. Exactly.
Yeah. Yeah. Like the, uh, the other people around him while while he's plotting to molest
these girls are like, this guy's too much. It was crazy. It's the, all the people around him
are a jazz ensemble. Well, the one guy, yes, he had a scat man. Crothers quality. He really
didn't. But I'm going to, I'm going to say this. I don't know if this is controversial or not.
Sleepway camp is better than any film in the, uh, Friday the 13th series.
It's not saying much. It's not. But I would agree. Except for six. I like six,
quite a bit. Never saw it. Well, then you can't really. I guess I can't say it. But yeah.
I saw this movie once, uh, in New Jersey with a young woman I would eventually make love to.
and I always thought I have it in my head as this really great movie and it's
simply because I banged from it. You know it was one of those first bangs for me
like I just moved to New Jersey. It's the way camp you mean. Yeah we watched the
picture and it's not like it turned to so on but it was like a third date and we
made love and I was always like I never want to see this film again because it
couldn't hold up to that great night. He said baby let's do the roleplay where I'm
the cook. Right. Yeah. Yeah. It was a, it was a really great, I mean, trash, of course,
but at the end of the day was really fun trash. It's driving, chalk at its best. It's very,
it's very fun. And it's, and for that kind of thing, it's pretty well made. There's also
the member of the old man who like runs the camp who's a good guy. Yeah. He like makes
a date with like the hot ass 17 year old. I couldn't believe that. And like nobody is like what
you're beautiful. Why would you fuck this? He's 50. He's 50. He's more than 50. I think. I
believe that was his last film that he ever made. It was really crazy. So nuts. It's just not even
called upon. No. Um, and I cannot recommend enough. It is worth getting shutter to do this,
Joe Bob Briggs, I wish I had the free time and the awakeness stamina to like do it as
a marathon.
Yeah.
Me too.
It's just tough.
I'm actually really enjoying doing it.
One movie at a, at a time with his commentary because he's so funny and so interesting.
They're not censoring him in any way.
Every female that comes by the set, he essentially groves them.
He doesn't grove them.
He's just say these things.
He's very heavily flirtatious with them.
I actually I disagree. I feel like he was very appropriate with the girl from I'm I'm saying it as I found it refreshing. I
Found it refreshing. He's not trying to grow up and that's way too much to say, but he's just not concerned about like it
My is this too much or yeah, I like that he jokes. I like that he jokes and he's like, yeah, when he's giving the girl shit from
people came and he's like, who else did you date on the damn set?
You know, like, yeah, I think that's I like that.
I like it. And I just have found it a real treat. I love the marathon.
And now I know they're doing one for Thanksgiving. And they're also doing one for
Christmas. And I have invited Joe over. I hope maybe we do a few. Maybe we'll do
a commentary. I'll be away for both holidays. But we'll try to make it happen
somehow. All right. All right. Is that okay?
don't disappear. They'll still be here when you get back. Yeah. I watch the witch in the window
speaking of shutter, which is a movie on shutter that, I guess it's a shutter original.
Shutter is, you know, now I'll know if I should watch these things on shutter, which I now possess.
Uh, it's a, it's a, it's a, uh, it's, you know, it's a prominently featured film on shutter.
Right. Uh, it's certainly more there.
Don't get into the which in the mirror and I'm asking her to change her way which in the window
What did I say mirror? Don't do it again. You always start up. No, no, no
Which of the window it's it look I don't want to ruin the film for you
I can say this as you were watched the guy that plays the father is tremendous in it
He's a really good actor. I don't know who he is. I'd never seen him in anything, but
he's great. It is Tom Arnold. Roseanne plays the kid. Oh, cool. Well, she's free. Yeah.
The, no, it's, it's the guy, the guy the actor plays the dad is great. He takes his son
up to this lake house to sort of renovate it. Their divorce, the parents are divorced.
And the place was haunted by a witch. As you're watching it, you'll be very intrigued
And then in the middle, you're going to start to be like, uh, this isn't that scary and
I kind of don't give a shit anymore.
And then in the end, the way that all ties up, it's actually worth watching for that.
That's all I can say.
Um, but I mean, in the, the fucking things like literally 80 minutes, yeah.
So you know, you're, you know, that, that's one episode of God damn the house on fucking
haunted, or the haunting of Hill House or whatever the fuck it's called.
I haven't let's do that as an episode. I have. We will. We will. I'll listen this week. Oh, we will. I'm ready. I've seen about six of them. That's enough. I want. I the other night. I was like, I'll check off one of these Roman offs before bed. See if I like this show. And I, I'm eight minutes in board cross side. I hit pause and the thing goes like to an hour 36. It's supposed to be a show a TV show.
Oh, look, maybe I'll watch it.
Come on.
What's your third word?
My third one, I started rabid, David Cronenberg's rabid, which I had never seen.
And I was very much enjoying it, but it was moving at a slow pace.
It was late.
And frankly, folks watching these joe Bob Briggs things remind me of my childhood, USA up
night cranking one out upstairs with an eye on the unlocked door to the TV room to see if I could
get it done without my parents seeing my genitals. Jesus Christ. And I switched forward a few. I skipped
ahead in the marathon to sorority babes in the slime bowl bowl arama. Because I was like, I can't
wait for this one. And that was a movie that every time I went to the video store, I was
very into that box. Hey, no pun intended folks. But I remember this was at a time when folks,
the internet was so far off. My younger listeners might might not believe this, but it's true.
through. I would make a mental note of the VHS box to sorority babes in the slime
bubble around the, remember it, go home and pleasure myself to it. To the memory, it's
such a sad, you couldn't sneak a goddamn playboy into the house. It's a child. I was doing
this from age nine. Still, get crafty for Christ's sakes. Eventually, I would use a playboy
that I believe somebody had wiped their ass with. And you also fucked an out of the woods.
All bets were off. Yeah. I took my entry points into this world where I could find them.
But so we're already babes in the slime bowl. A ram, uh, it did have some great nudity in it.
It has a five minute shower scene where three nerds watch these girls just full frontal shower
with no plot point. Then the next nudity is an hour later where this beautiful woman is
trying to have sex with this teenager who keeps refusing it, which I found just baffling. They
spend the whole movie wanting it, get it, and they don't want it. Didn't didn't follow that.
The nudity would have changed my life when I was 13. Now it was not enough. This movie was absolutely.
It was absolutely terrible. The movie was so bad. And of course, but with that title,
you're like, okay, they know what they are. It's going to be a little, you know, a funny
romp, a spoof, a wink. Folks, I don't think it was. It was a stink. It was terrible. And they had
a little, it was called an imp, but it was like a puppet that like insulted them and controlled
their minds and shit, voiced by like the same voice as Audrey too in Little Shop of Horrors.
So it's like this little impuppet going like, oh, baby, what's your talking about?
Like Shaft or something. And I've just, I despised the movie.
Joe Bob is all that made it worthwhile.
But he gave it four stars, but he rates them by how many breasts they have in them.
Okay, I mean, it was that's one you can skip when you go through the the Joe Bob Briggs.
I get that a lot of his stick is bringing you these trashy movies, but the other ones
all have a lot more value than that one.
I would skip that one.
I will close us out with a new docu series on Netflix, hip hop evolution.
You know, we were talking about old school rap earlier.
if you're a fan of rap music truly of the music and its history, this is a must see. I've only
seen a couple episodes to stand out for me so far with the origins of gangster rap,
where they talked about schooly -d making the official first gangster rap record and then how
that inspired iced tea and iced tea put gangster rap and LA on the map. And then I've always thought of
cool it was being the first gangster rap. A lot of paradise point the term gangster a lot of
people do and that's why you need to watch this series. Okay. Uh, it's just a really great show.
There's tons of very cool old footage in it. There's a man. And it doesn't go for the it goes for
the legit product. It, you know, they're doing a thing about gangster rap and most of its roots being
in LA and they interview real LA gangster rappers from the era. They interview Kid Frost
and the interview corrupt and they interview DJ Yella and they interview the Arabian prince
and iced tea. It's not one of these fucking things where they talk about, you know, they
talk about gangster rap and then and then it cuts to a 55 year old white guy in a turtle
neck, right?
Being like, well, that was the thing back then, you know, it's nobody'd ever heard anything
like this before David Wilde from Rolling Stone is always in us. Yeah, it's it's the genuine
article. I I recommend it highly. Now do they confirm or deny that if corrupt gave a fuck
about a bitch, he'd always be broke and that he'd never have no motherfucking endota smoke.
They go into that centerpiece of the entire series. Okay, good. Yeah, it revolves around that and
And you know, each episode sort of ties into that. And so yeah, Pat, I got some for the
news psycho. Oh, all right. We touched on it briefly at the live show. By the way,
guys, as we already stated, the live episodes will be the bonuses for October and November.
I'm waiting to get the files from the venue. I hope to have the first one up by the end of
the month, but I am at the mercy of the engineer and him getting me the file.
So you might get two bonus episodes in November instead of one in October and one in November.
Uh, you're going to want to hear these shows, but they, they are coming.
I promise classics, you know, classics, we're trying to do.
I know, I know we've had a little irregularness lately with the schedule and whatnot.
But we're trying to really bring you guys the best thing we can and do as much new and
different stuff as we can. And it's just, you know, there are a lot of cooks at that point.
It's not just Pat and I deciding when and what happens when and where. So when I go
on my hiatus, I, uh, which will probably be in March, I, because we got the full season
pick up and I'm glad I'm alive show as well. But, uh, I would, I think our goal should be
to do like a 10 city tour. I've never done that. I think it would be a blast. Hey, if
we can do it, we'll do it. Chey town. St. Lulu. The biggest little city in the world.
But ring now. No, no. I got it. Something we touched on this at one of the live shows, but
we really didn't get into it. Freddie Krueger. Goldberg. Goldberg. Do you watch it? No.
Um, never seen the gold.
Isn't it enough that in the goddamn actual movies,
they turn this guy into a fucking comic strip character?
Now, Freddie is literally appearing in a comedy show
where there's no element of horror whatsoever.
It's just going to be like the trailer,
the mom's like, whatever, Mr. Kroger.
And he's like, hey, that's Kroger.
I'm like, I can't watch this.
Is he like a house guest in it or what's?
No, I think like they watch Nightmare in Elm Street
and then like they have a nightmare and he comes
and because it's the Goldbergs
it's gonna be Zany and Goofy and I was thrilled
to see England suit up one more time as the character
but this isn't how I wanted it to happen.
I saw the creator, I interviewed him once
on that Cinematical. He wrote fanboys and I used to interview screenwriters on there.
And he had tweeted Freddie or England said he'd never do the role again, but I got him
back in the makeup and now he's saying he's up for it. I did my job, Hollywood. Now you
do yours. It's everybody anymore. Everybody, everybody stands on Twitter now. I was like,
Hey, just so you know, people over there that I have nothing to do with and I am not in their shoes.
If you don't do this, you're complicit or whatever.
And it's like, what the fuck?
Yeah, I saw something other day that was like, if you don't, if you're not actively fighting Trump,
you're as bad as Trump. I was like, no, that's, that's simply not true.
Well, Amy Schumer tweeted the thing where she was like to you white NFL players, if you
don't kneel with with Kaepernick or whatever, um, you're complicit and it's like hold on
a second, they're not complicit. Second of all, you're not an NFL player. Right. Third of
all, Amy, this is a real easy stance to take after Nike already backed Kaepernick. Yes. Everybody's
So I'm cappin' excited.
You're not saying anything, that daring.
Where was this?
It was going on for a year.
Yeah, where was this two years ago
when it was a daring thing to get behind the guy?
Right.
Oh God, I can't anymore.
Anyway.
I, every time I'm about to close all my accounts,
I just think that like some, you know, like Martin Scorsese
will DM me the day after I take it down.
Does he ever?
Of course not.
I don't think he even asked Twitter.
Yeah, it's I'm done. I get on there, you know, it's it really is, you know, so many people are
off it because you're just seeing the same names over and over. I follow a thousand people and I
feel like they're just people who are on Twitter all day tweeting. Twitter is, if you're still on
jokes, if you're still on Twitter, this goes for everybody. I'm not, I'm not, I'm not, I'm not taking
a personal. If you're still on Twitter, you're on save by the bell, the college years.
Everybody has left. It's just, you're just screeched now on there trying to hold it together.
But it's hard to give away all the followers. I always think like, what if I really need
something or I need to tell people something, but that's never happened. It doesn't work.
It doesn't work for publicity. When you, I kept it for an extra year because of that.
And every time I publicize something it would get two likes right or whatever and then you see these tweets on there
Where it's like 7 .9 million retweets and then you look at the guys profile. It's like 246 right it's pointless
Well, they'll also, you know, I didn't I didn't do anything on this show in terms of promotion
I retweeted one really nice article and just kind of left it at that
But you also get these people who all day are like
unbelievable that there's still people making jokes on this site with what's going on in
the world are really you got to promote that comedy show with everything going on in
the world. It's like, yeah, for some people, that's all they have. That's, that's their
only source of income. Yes, of course. And that used to be, again, it's whoever saying
you is some fucking idiot who sits in an office every day or whatever. And as God damn job
security and doesn't have to self start in any way. Right. And then like the fuck I'm doing my part
to shut down Trump by tweeting that he's orange 45 times a day. Why do you have to make jokes? Yeah,
I love that shit. Yeah, you're a real, you're a real activist. Why don't you peel your fat ass off the
couch and go do something? Okay. You know, I'm not saying they're fat. I'm just saying, you know,
the, you know what I mean? In the, in the figurative, you know, what's the term for that? I'm speaking
You know, you undercut me and it bothers me. You're the problem. You're complicit.
What was the new psycho? Do we even go ahead? It was Freddie. Oh, Freddie. Which led us
into the greater the Goldbergs yelling at people that he's done his part. Yes.
us. Did you do your part? One of the biggest hit shows on TV, you got an marginally working
actor to reprise a role. Oh, wow. You really? Boy, did you go to the fucking wall? I had
a meeting this year on the Goldberg spin -off. What's the spin -off now? It's about the gym
teacher. I'm not going to place the gym. Brian Callum. And what's the spin -off? I watched
the pilot. He teaches Jim Joe and Tim Meadows is like the assistant principal and they
have an uneasy alliance. Yeah. All right. I'll just leave it at that.
a scary stuff. For you video gamers out there, people this was such a nice surprise for
me. I never played the game when it was out. I don't know how I missed it. I think
it's because I had a GameCube during the Xbox PS2 phase and this didn't come out on the
game, but it came out on the other two systems. And I just got a copy of it. And I almost
didn't buy this game because I was looking at it like, well, that's probably sucks. That's
probably why I never heard of it. And I looked it up and had rave reviews. Indiana Jones and the
Emperor's tomb. If you can get a copy of this for your original Xbox, I'm playing it on my Xbox 360
or your PS2. Get it. I am, I am swept away in this game. It's a whole new, it's, it's,
takes place before Temple of Doom. I am just swept away in a whole new Indiana Jones
adventure. I didn't know existed. The guy doing Indie's voice is close enough that you
buy that it's Indie. The animation is good. Like they capture the spirit of the films.
It's lots of fist fights and like swinging on vines and you got the whip and your gun
and it uses all the sound effects from the movie. It's a very, very fun exciting game.
I'm having a great time with it after Pat leaves tonight. I'm going to play another mission. Have you tried the VR which I gave you?
I haven't tried it yet. Okay. I'm trying to find the right thing to try with it.
And there is an
exorcist VR
Which I'm scared to try. I think I have one I can give you have to dig it up though
It's got a demo disc in it, but those always sucks. I'll just find, I think I'm going to download that.
That may be our, huh? No one. It's VR. That'd be pretty cool. What bothers me with demo disc is it
teases you. You know, and you're like, I just get a game. I'd rather just buy a damn game and play it.
Anyway, so that's that's scary stuff for this week. You don't have anything. I'm assuming.
Now, I just, I watched a couple of the special features on the event horizon, Blu -ray,
which we're discussing on tonight's show, and they were boring as hell.
Yeah, I tried to watch the, I didn't care.
There was a much more interesting story to be told on the Wikipedia page and a much more
honest story about what the long, arduous process of that movie making it to the screen was,
are we heading there now? We're about there, buddy, because yeah, event horizon was, you know,
this Paul Anderson, not Paul Thomas Anderson, because it did moral combat. And all the, yeah,
all the resident evil flicks. Not any of my favorite films by a long shot, but the guy was making this movie,
maybe it was, you know, a big deal for Paramount, and then Titanic was supposed to be released
in the summer of 97. And James Cameron was like, I'm not going to be ready. We got to put
this out at Christmas instead. So they said, we don't have any big summer movie now event
horizon. I need a cut of this movie in like four weeks. I was like, I just finished. Like
I should have four months to edit it. Right. We need it for the summer. You'd be doing
as a huge solid. He does it. He gets it edited. He turns it in. They're like, this is horrific.
It was a two hour movie that was insanely gory apparently. It was disgusting. The the
blood orgy scene that you see incredibly briefly and faintly in the movie was a much longer and more
involved thing. Sounds awesome. Yeah, they were really traumatized by it. They said, we want a half
hour out of this movie. We want all the gore out of this movie. We hate it. So in our rated
hard movie they went all the gore out of this correct and then they released it and you know it
wasn't what people wanted it to be it was not a commercial success it was not a critical success but
I remember I'm pretty sure I saw private parts which I love the return of the Jedi re -release
and the third movie in this triple feature that I snuck in.
That's about the right time, right, I'd say.
It was a Van Horizon, and I thought nothing of it,
and I remember being so horrified by it,
I was not a big horror aficionado by any means,
had not seen many horror movies.
I thought it was terrifying, disturbing.
My friends and I all absolutely loved it.
I watched it again a couple times.
It got a reputation amongst me and my friends
as being like one of the most disturbing movies ever made.
And that's how I have been thinking about it all this time.
I re -watched it last night.
Could not have been more bored, disinterested.
I did not think it was good.
Well, let's give a brief of the synopsis of the film.
A Venerysen, it's essentially a haunted house movie in space.
A ship called The Arendt Horizon has disappeared.
Sam Neill was the designer of the,
he plays the character who was the designer of the ship, and he is joined with this sort
of military space crew led by Lawrence Fishbird to go out and basically the ship has been
lost for years and years and years and they have finally pinpointed it and they're going
to go out now and see if any of the crew is still alive or what's going on and what happened
and bring the event horizon back home
for further inspection.
The thing that made the event horizon special
and led to its disappearance was
it could essentially time jump,
like not time jump,
but it could travel great distances instantaneously
by bending planes of reality, you know?
Like a mad magazine folding.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah. So when they get to the ship, obviously nobody's alive, something's afoot, you get the
impression that something with this reality bending bullshit they were doing has led
to it. And then, you know, they all go into the ship and slowly the ship takes over all
their minds and people go mad. And it's a lot of house movie. It's a, I was just comparing
it to, um, it's in the mouth of madness, really. It's basically the same kind of thing.
Like, why are we going nuts here and why are we seeing all these horrifying things and eventually they explain why.
So that being said, I really like the film. I think I think it's a lot of fun. I think it's a different take on space that I haven't really seen.
You know, you've seen aliens in space be frightening, but I had never really seen sort of ghosts in space.
And I liked that. I liked that it had a devilish sort of hell raise or quality to it.
Sam Neil Lawrence Fishburn always deliver the rest of the cast is stellar.
Everybody's really great in it. It's got the guy from.
Oh, the pilot is what's his face.
Son of a bitch.
hold on a second. Let me look this up. The pilot is the guy whose eyes bleed out.
Well, I think everybody's eyes kind of bleed out at one point or another.
Yeah, put out the hatch. Oh, that's right. Sean Pertwee, who plays Alfred on
the new Gotham series, who I'm a fan of. He's in it. I think he's the pilot. I can't
And I just really liked it.
And there are some really tense disturbing sequences
where they have to save somebody
who's in terrible, you know, peril and stuff.
And I bought into the suspense.
I bought into the crew caring about one another.
And I don't know, I liked it.
It's not perfect, obviously.
There's a glaring foreshadowing at the top
where they get under the event horizon.
And there's all these like little boxes
lining the main corridor and they go, what's that?
that. And uh, same goes explosives in case you ever have to split the ship in two. Right.
Okay. So that's going to be the end. Yeah. Uh, you know, I like how it started with
a long, uh, tracking shot of the ship. I had never seen that in a science fiction film before.
But um, I look, I think the only reason I didn't like it was that I had it built up my mind
is being this like masterpiece of disturbing horror. It ain't that. It's a fine movie.
You know, the the scares are not particularly scary anymore, but like the set design of the ship
pretty fucking awesome. There was a lot of really cool shots. It was a very cool interior of a ship.
It's almost on a par with like Ridley Scott ship, you know, like the Prometheus and all that.
I thought that was cool, Sam Neal walking around in his underwear, a little weird off the top.
Sam Neal, an actor who I'm sort of indifferent to, I liked him in this, he was creepy.
Fishburn, I thought, phoned it in.
I don't know, to me, I liked him in that part.
all right. I've spent 20 years with this movie in my mind as this just much more intense thing
than it was. I think just because I hadn't seen much horror, but there is some hell -raiser
influence to it, I would say. Well, basically, the explanation is, right, when they do one of these
space -time continuum bends, the ship actually went through hell, and that's why it's now possessed
or whatever. And yeah, some of the stuff like, you know, him having to watch his wife kill herself
and stuff, he had pretty disturbing. There's some, some intense stuff in it. You know, it's kind
of an average movie. It's gotten a lot of praise in recent years. I think people have a lot of affection
for it. So Paramount wanted to throw some money into them releasing a special edition with all the
deleted scenes, a half hour of extra footage, unrated director's cut. They had actual porn
actors act out the blood orgy and like actually fucking stuff. And you know, to like really
make it intense and real and that scene is the little you see is very disturbing. That stuck
with me up to the first time I saw it. Yeah, for sure. All that got cut, you do see a faintly
someone getting butt fucked. But that would have been interesting to me. They said that Paramount
lost all the footage so it'll never be anywhere. And all the director had was a VHS copy of those
deleted 35 minutes or whatever and he lost the VHS copy. So we'll never know. I think that might
have been a much more interesting film. I think what is here part of what makes it work so well is
that it is kind of like just weird and doesn't make sense all the time and you know it's not a bad
movie. I just I wish it had been more and I think what would have been more would have been that
original cut. But who knows? I, uh, as I said, I like the film and I like it even more
when you compare it to the shit that was coming out at that time period in horror. Yeah.
I mean, you're right. This is right in the late 90s. So I mean, you got, you know, it's funny.
Carpenter, who was invited back to direct H2O, which we discussed at length of the live show.
We don't need to get into that, but it was invited back said no, he wasn't interested so we can go off and make fucking ghosts of Mars and vampires
Two of the shittiest farm movies of all time two of the shittiest movies
Yeah, and I love Carpenter, but those are bad fucking movies
I'm both, but you know that's what you had at this time. You had I know what you did last summer
You know yet final destination. These were okay films. I mean you know passable baby. Yeah, but I thought this was a real standout
for that time period. I'll give you that. It puts an interesting stamp on it. Yes. Most people
disagree. Roger Ebert gave the film two out of four stars stating the script creates a sense of
foreboding and afterboding, but no actual boating. That's fair. Which almost sounds like a
sign felt bit. Where's the boating? Washington Post, Stephen Hunter, wrote, if you want to have
that event horizon experience without spending the seven bucks try this instead. Put a bucket on
your head and have a loved one beat on it vigorously with a wrench for a hundred minutes. Holy cow.
Same difference in thinking the gas you'll save. That is harsh. But seven dollars on a movie,
that doesn't sound too bad. Yeah, those were the days where I'd say, I remember when I was a kid,
you could see a movie for $7 and still have enough left over to buy bread.
You know, steak dinner for a nickel.
Um, anyway, you know, that's the movie in a nutshell.
Oh, out of the fans of the show wanted us to review it.
I don't know if it's because they liked it or they didn't like it or they just
wanted to hear our thoughts.
But I, my, my feeling is that people also remember it is being much scarier than it
is, but I don't know.
I, I think it's a movie with, with more originality than these movies.
sometimes have, especially during the time it came out, but ultimately fairly forgettable
for me. I'd love to see that uncut. I bet it's awesome. I bet it is. I bet it's awesome.
Folks, it's that time of the month. We got to do shout outs. Shout outs. But before our next
episode will be the people on the stairs. Yes. Cravens, people on the stairs. Our live episodes
will be on the Patreon shortly. They are excellent. Thank you to Emily for putting on
the spectacular show. Thank you so much, Emily. Thank you to the Helians who came,
especially the ones who came from out of state. Jesus Christ.
Everybody. Thank you all. The people, it was, we was such a supportive crew. We loved
spending time with all of you. We had a blast. Pat and I got particularly drunk. I believe
everybody did. No hangover the next day. Really great. But it was great. It was. I'm on
on Instagram, Twitter, the Patrick Walsh, cool kids, Friday nights on Fox, also on Hulu.
Joe.
Joe DeRosa comedy on Instagram, if you can find me, Hardbot pod on Instagram, by the way.
New Hardbot vids coming soon, I'm about to shoot some new stuff next week.
So keep your out for those.
And I'll be at the punchline and filly Thanksgiving weekend.
and come out for a show after you stuff your fucking face, like the American slob you are.
All right. All right. Shout -outs. We're going to go back and forth this time. Let's get
it off. Anthony V. Manito, AK Party McFly, Philip Rashad, Trevor Gage, Joshua Christensen,
KP Flynn, Tyler Moore, LV and Reekas, Matt Wheeler, Leslie Coffin, welfare dentist, Jackson
and see lowmeyer, Geron Sanderson, Ash Ogden, Reign, Purple Peacock, Sterling Ibrigo,
Christopher Sebella, Steve Murdoch, Not Medium Rare, Drew Tiberius Pull, Monica Not
From Friends, Al Roberts, Tyler Laporte, Steve Smith, Lupe Pita Pacheco, Tonsi, Tonsi,
right? T -O -N -C -I?
John C?
John Ejik?
Deon Johnson, Matt Robin,
Will Foley, Kevin Ragati,
Joseph, Christian Reynolds,
Josh Smallridge,
Kurt Ziegler, Brooke Adams,
Brittany Ferguson, Sean Florent,
Danny Rudd, Natalie Hartline,
Scott Contour, Leo Lopez,
A -A -L -E, Emily Rock.
Pat, do you want to take it from here?
Joe
You're starting right under Emily rock there. Oh boy. I hit Alexa for Christ. I know
It's like when you hand your oh
You know it's like when you hand your dad the phone and you're like dad
Do me a favor Google this what cuz I'm driving? I bring my glasses down on my nose
Oh, I did the what did I do? I'm watching a YouTube now
Sorry guys, all right, so you're gonna start after
Emily Rock, who I think at this point should give three times for three shout out. I'm kidding. All right. You got all these buttons on the side. Don't touch the fucking button. Well, all right. It's hard not to touch the button. It's a touch screen. Just scoff you.
Nick Muscarra, Dave Del Greco, who we met at the live show, Kurt Ziegler, Chloe Paget, Matthew Ruiz, Scott Birchett,
Dennis Ormston, Travis Hines, John Weasen -Groober, Matthew McGuire, Angela
Porcaro, James O 'Brien, Kamani Cloudfelter. Thank you for your gift. You gave me
Kamani. Thank you Kamani. Matthew Moon, Jay Fischer, Sean Lyle, John Hollywood,
Jake McAlvane, Meredith McWilliam. By the way, if I could step in for one
second. Please. I'm terrible with names. Forgive me. Thank you to everybody that gave gifts.
Everybody got some really nice gifts. That obviously is never the point of any of this.
It was very generous of people to show up and say I want you to have this. Yes.
Uh, and thank you for that guys. Yeah. Got some really awesome shit. And thank you to all the artists
who they contribute to the show. Yes. Yes. We spoke to them. Yes. They're making the posters
that you love so dear. Yes, it was everybody's amazing. Uh, Gregory Hassel, Jesse Janicki,
Mike Greenwood, Brianna Alqueer, Cole Rothaker, Matt. Come on, Matt, you can spruce that
up. Supportive guy. Oops. I said that last one wrong. That's not me saying that. That's
somebody's name. Anthony Rodriguez, Chris Passmore, Casey Jones, Sinji, Sam Mitchell
is a fat piece of trash. Jesus Christ. Robert Haynes, Natalia Hatley, Will Pittman, Kevin
Like nanny, Kevin Driscoll, Jen Wessels, Lewis Bell, Joe Hoffman, Scott Sweeney, Jay Miller,
Clayton Stamper, Amanda Lancaster, Ben, Michael Bolis, Ethan Gamage, James Girolamo,
Darryk Adams, Sean Hall, Adam Lownsbury, Brett Friendjella, Toby Bell, Vincent Franks.
You think it's a plan toob in Bell? I just realized perhaps, yeah. Joseph Ragoza, Steve
Burton, Anna Demario. Is there an Anna De La Weegee? Bo, Aaron Roberts, Scott John, Ben
Maddie, Kevin Eason, fucking rich Tillman, Sarah Catherine, Paul Merchee, Scott Swayze,
Kara Konini, Joshua Taj Bozeman, who gave Joe and I a copy of Sneakers on DVD.
Thank you, Joshua.
Great film.
And thank you.
Chuck Andrews, Tom Laverick, Tucker Rouch, John Smith, Edmund Agabo.
So good seeing you the other night, I don't, some of these people, I don't know if I
meant them or not.
You're using code names.
And Will Pottoff.
Yes.
One of the artists and Brandon Gash.
Brandon Gash.
Andrew Brian Bolerier, Will Helms, Jennifer Anna, Stan T L. Monholen, Melissa Alvarez, Jake
Bullock, Tanges religion, zero fox trot .com. You fucks. I guess that's a plug. Matt Crawford,
Jenna, Richard Deming, Brian Callis, Tim Drain, Michael Madrigal, Richard Howan,
stuff. Go to Mr. Suit Records and Lancaster. Do it. Bretton Fraser, Sean, Luke Physioc,
the fantastic Karen Kilgarith. Karen, listen to my favorite murder. With Georgia
Hardstark as well. Joey Mueller. Shelby L. Nathan Baskett. Gary Miren.
Syrod. Dylan Larr. Phil Barrell. Edmund Dillon. The black magic ninja. Scott Pauline
Sarah L. Daphne Kellogg, Ryan Martz, Tristan Avery, Hunk Masterson, Richard Iman, Matthew
J. Brown, Julie Aguirre, Charity Ferguson, Hank from Dan Cakes, Nick Walther, Alexander
Stein, Tyler Keatley, Emily Marvel, John B. Watt, Zambianz, horror crafts.
Yes. On Etsy, correct? On Etsy. Yes. Check out John Store and Etsy.
Mori Benjamin, Nicholas Burns, Alex Nelson, Jeremy Cool, Derek Clark, Alex Shipley, Sean
Pinnock, Amanda Leibson, Timothy Letzzo, Shane Nazarian, Smelly Bubbles, Samantha Kiefer,
I love you. Oh, that's nice. But I'm saying it. And now I've broken you two up because
because. Well, maybe that's Samantha Kiefer. That maybe that's she wrote that about herself.
So you would say it to her.
I get judged by the email address. Okay. David Belinger, Hunter McDonald, Justin Bowhager,
Adam Benbenek, Mani Rios, Demani O 'Rubio, Brandon Gash, Jake Farot, Rob Lines, Jacob Barrett,
but Jordan C. Maxwell Ashcroft, Ryan Kohler, Barb Allen, Jonathan Face, Rebecca Cohen,
Chris Bowen, Mike Gibbons, Donnie Joyce, Michael Dawson, Jennifer Smith, Connor Denney,
Kevin Swiss -Towitz, Anthony J. Guajardo, Annie Jo Hanson, Joe, can you believe how many
Patreon sponsors we have. I can't. I can take over. Starting with Timmy K. I can take over.
Timmy K. It is awesome. Timmy K. That's three for Timmy K now. That's four. Okay. Here's
said it again. Megan Librund, Scott Blickensdurfer, Alec Walker, Brett Werner, Tristan Carlson, Laura
Lair, Richie Verdugo, Chris Hopper, Emily Florence, our pal Sean L. Dave
Comerick, Abby Manuel, Kim D 'Angelo, Jonathan Galat, Michael McBee, Stephanie
Power, Diego Campos, Stefan Maso, Uso, Usayo, Uso. I think I said that right.
I apologize. Zoe Blascavic, Azal Kivinsland, Dan MacLeod, Lorenz
Bunganiers Alejandro Seldago, Papa Spouche, Tracy Reddington, Sean Thomas, Amanda Alzemora,
Jason Weibel, Mike Curry, Drew Spindler, Andrew Koval, Sam Mitchell, Aaron Melanowski,
Scott Nolan, Jack Gertz, Ben, Misty Zavar, Moli Russell's Wart, Desjane Wilford, Johnny
Michelle Gold, Danielle Doer, Eric Lamora, Kevin Marcenek, Lawrence Anderson, Jared
Small Ridge, Will Pottoff, Natalie Craig, Kyle Kinslin, the man whose name we cannot
speak on a Bavidook, Scott Patton, The Block Watch, August Rydell, Paul Pickerel, Rage
last name sounds Asian. That's a weird one. Beth Gaston, Julie Bailey, Michael Aiello,
Reed, Estetic, and Max Unwraith. We're overwhelmed as usual by the amount of support. Thank
you all. You're the best sauce. We will see you next time and we'll see you in hell.