Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer, or check out
our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz, only available at Bed
MDM Casino.
Spin on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM game sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Waiter, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as non -mustrable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees and here's another, no other sportsbook has
an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 -plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gampler, offer not available in all states
terms apply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
This is a headgun podcast.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to you.
We'll see what hell is James Gattelfini.
Is your favorite podcast with a horrible movie,
the sci -fi flash.
I actually do a decent James Gattelfini.
Well then do it.
I've just been watching this.
Come in.
I don't disrespect for as well.
I never said it was good.
I just like doing it.
All right.
Do yours.
Well, I can't I can't with pressure. I can't I can't with pressure. Sounds like when we were in bed last night folks
This happens to all the guys I said. It's never happened to me before
Folks, welcome. Hello. We're here talking about
An Isleation the new Alex Garland picture
starring Natalie Portman and Oscar Isis, an interesting picture that I think we're
going to have a lot to talk about tonight. Oh yeah, I got a lot to say, but
first let's get on with the show and also on with
Can the make of this world seem bright?
John Lee, you almost didn't have one there.
Talk about not being able to perform under pressure.
I mean, Jesus Christ.
look do you know what it's like people to have to perform once a week on a podcast
that was like a that was like a movie scene where the guy you know the zoom in
the power station is doing his speech and season dead wife standing in the back
or whatever like a quiz show and tied on my face yeah sweating it up but I got it
You did you don't focus on the negative you could choose to focus on the positive that I got it
Speaking of politicians with dead lovers. Oh, I was referencing
Quittic. I was referencing it. No, no, I was referencing it. Is that what chapequitics about?
It's about the Ted Kennedy scandal. That's what that's about right? Yeah, yeah
Starring
top billing
Jason whatever's name is
Shortsman no seagull no the guy from fucking from fretta 13th no
the guy from fucking
Good rouse key my friend from sixth grade who fell off the roof while throwing a ball rock and a blister. Oh Jason Clark. Yeah, yeah top billing
Has the man ever been in a successful film it was in zero dark 30, okay?
Oh, I know from his Terminator Genesis, playing a John Conner that looked way too much like my friend John
Horowitz. He didn't know that. He was the star of Brotherhood, the showtime original drama that I
love. Okay, so that was 15 years ago. He was the star of Winchester. Terrible movie that bombed. Yeah.
Look, I didn't know we were going to be beaten up on Jason Clark. I'm not hanging on the guy. I'm just
saying it's it's I don't understand how certain people get these breaks. Sure, where it's like
they ran Chris Elliott out of show business because get a life wasn't a smash success TV show.
They gave him cabin boy too. You know our cabin boy, which is hilarious. But I mean for Christ
six, you didn't hear from the guy for 20 fucking years. Right. Jason Clark could do whatever he wants.
And he gets top billing and chap a quiddick.
Who else is like that?
There was somebody else who were talking about recently.
A lot of tons of people.
We're just like, what has this guy done?
That's successful.
People can hang around in this business forever
without ever really doing anything of note.
Well anyway.
How many chances they give Sam Worthington?
Hundreds.
But he was at least in things that made money.
He was an avatar but it wasn't like that was a
That's that's the mistake they made everyone was rushing to this because of Worthington he was an avatar
He was in Clash the Titans which made enough money that they made a sequel
Didn't say
Called Wrath of the Titans
Okay, and I was positive. There'd be a third film called War of the Titans and they're never never happened
Probably because the first two stuck yeah, I didn't say him but the original with Harry Hamlin the original is a masterpiece in my opinion
It's a beautiful film. Ray Harryhausen. Yeah, Ray Harryhausen, Burgess Meredith,
what's his face? The guy, you know, the guy, the guy, Olivia Lawrence, Olivia. Sure.
What a, what a tremendous piece of film that is. Love it. Made with care, made with love.
Anyway, Chip, I was referencing when I said the politician with the dead lover.
Sharky's machine. Right. That's a scene in Sharky's machine. A Bert Reynolds vehicle that stars him and was directed by him. And the reason I'm referencing stark Sharky's machine is because Pat and I, and this is what we teased on the last episode last Saturday night,
Spend our night in the Egyptian theater on Hollywood Boulevard watch theater especially especially
Well the new Beverly's getting renovated go check it out if you're an L .A. watching not one but three
Bert Reynolds films smokey in the bandit hooper and then sharky's machine and folks when you thought
it couldn't get better it does Bert Reynolds was there and did a Q and a after smokey in the bandit
And that, if you said to me, what's your best case scenario for Bert Reynolds event?
I'd say smoking the bandit and then he comes out after and that's what happened.
And it was fucking great.
Yeah.
He was very funny.
He was kind of hitting on every woman that asked a question, which was, oh, he was not.
He was.
What are you talking about?
He had a couple of like, how are you, how are you doing, honey?
I love, he, oh no, he did not.
He had some creepisms.
Pat, that's a lie.
But I'm saying that's a lie.
Ever wasn't lapped and enjoyed it that never happened though you that never happened what you just said did don't happen once
He made several references about like the ladies the ladies in the movies he did
Man in life. I don't I thought it was charming and funny nothing nothing sketchy
I just noticed he'd be like, you know, the lady was like I just wanted to say I love you Bert Reynolds
You are a dreamboat. You are the best movie like can you be like I love you to yeah or he'd be like
like, uh, what was your name again?
Or, but he'd put a little, I liked it.
He still had a little sex left in him.
And I like that.
I wasn't saying he was tweaking.
All right.
I got you.
There's still some engine under the hood.
Yeah.
The two pay looks good.
He's not walking great, but he was funny.
And he made fun of the fact that he can't walk great because, uh, he said it was because
of all his previous stunts and he goes, I don't walk with this thing because it looks
good.
Right.
I had never seen one on the big screen either.
It is one of my favorite films of all time.
It's not in my top 10, but it's up there for me.
I love the movie.
Seeing that on the big screen.
And the crowd with a crowd that was of 600 people
that was so excited, people were applauding
during smoking in the bandit
like the way people do at Star Wars screenings.
It's like, you know,
like Jackie Gleason's name comes on in the credits.
People are erupting cheering when Sally Field comes into it.
Like the Jerry Reed song starts playing.
People are fucking hootin' and hootin'.
It was awesome, man.
It was fucking awesome.
And the movie killed.
It did.
I laughed so hard at one point I was crying.
Yeah, I mean, I had been there for nine to five pretty recently
and I was impressed by the laughs it got, you know,
30, 40 years later, but smoking the band, it played just like a standard big comedy coming
out. Every joke was hidden. Then Hooper, nothing to sneeze at either. It was a very entertaining
picture about a stunt man. Very kind of simple movie, not much going on in it.
Yeah, well, a bar brawl and bar brawls. A lot of scenes that are really just time killers,
but very charming. It's Sally Field given nothing at all to do.
She's burials in his team are all fun.
Sally Field literally will disappear for 30 minutes,
and then walk in and be like, when are you gonna quit being a stuntman?
And Bert's like, never, baby. And she's like,
and that happens six times in the movie.
Brian Keith, I believe that's his name,
of Bonanza fame, Keith Bryan, whatever his name is, gives a pretty stellar performance
in Hooper. The guy that plays Roscoe Pico train in Dukes of Hazard gives a nice performance
in the film. Wait, which one was the older guy that was drinking out of the bottle of
jazz? That's Bryan Keith or, I think he's also in our next picture, Sharky.
Yeah, he's also in Sharky's machine playing essentially the same character that they just
shift over. Yeah, buddy. He's good at playing that character. He's very enjoyable. And then a young
Jan Michael Vincent in Hooper, yes. Uh, which Pat was unfamiliar with Jan Michael Vincent. And
I was explained. I've always heard the name. I've always heard it uses the punchline. And I did not
know what he looked like until tonight. I was explained to Pat the tragedy of he's not missing a leg.
He had to have a leg amputated from in inject. I believe from injecting heroin. Okay. Um,
He was in a deal.
He was several DUIs in Karex.
One of them was so bad that he now is when he talks like if he ever gets interviewed
which is rare, they have to put subtitles up because you can't understand it because
his voice is so gravely, I don't know that we needed the witch's rare on top of everything
else.
Well, he's, as he said in a recent interview, I'm just laying low.
That's what he said.
You really follow the career of John.
Well, it's a tragic story and you know, you see him in that film. He's like in perfect shape. He's a fucking beautiful looking man
and you know, he's got the world by the tail. He's called the rest room on more than one occasion.
I would say an inappropriate amount of time. Yeah, I'd jump up and go, I got another phone call I got to take.
But you know, he had the world by the tail. You know, one of his first things he ever does is he's
co -starring with Bert Reynolds at the top of Bert Reynolds career right and then you know it's
tragic. He was in the TV show Airwolf. Okay. Anyway, Hooper, a lot of fun. Yeah, an underrated
flick. Yeah, there's a great, there's a great bar fight scene with Terry Bradshaw. Yes.
Where Terry Bradshaw says that Bert Reynolds is talking too loud over his songs that he played and he
to give him 50 cents and they lean into the fight. The fight ends with not one but I believe
five different men being thrown through the same window out onto the trash pile outside
and then they just get up and they're like, that's young, let's keep drinking.
And this was about a week into patting my dry spell. I turned him half way through the film. I said,
no movie has ever made me want to drink more. Every scene they'd like walk through drinking
looking for a bottle of Jack Daniels.
Sit down, but talk about how much they love
the sweet smooth taste of bourbon.
And they jump a car over like a ravine.
Yeah.
And it's goddamn business.
Woo!
I love it, man.
Yeah, there was that scene where there were
24 cans of beer set up like a pyramid
and they were drinking and driving,
which also looked very fun.
Yeah, yeah.
There's a scene where they are,
this was how much times have changed.
Jan Michael Vincent and Bert Rales are sitting on a parked car at the beach, as Pat said,
a pyramid of beer cans to each of them, two separate pyramids that they've both built
from the beers they've drank.
Cop comes up, all he says is, just don't go driving right now.
The million open containers are fine, the public trunk, and this is fine.
Just don't drive.
Jan Michael Vincent then proceeds to call the cop old man in sweetheart like four times.
right. And then they drive past the cop drinking beers, hanging out the window. I think given him the
finger. Yeah, they do. And you know, it's the 70s. So it's like as soon as you're out of the cop
sites, you're, you're, you're clear. Right. He hits his hat on the steering wheel and goes, oh,
it was a good picture. I thought that for the first 30 seconds of that bar room scene, I thought that
Terry Bradshaw was dober from coach and I was like, it's Bradshaw took me a minute.
He looks, dober looks like a Bradshaw, a young Bradshaw.
I can't imagine Bradshaw wasn't brought in to test for the role and I can't imagine
he wouldn't have been better at it.
Maybe he had a big broadcast for dober.
I don't you feel like for dober they wanted Terry Bradshaw?
No, he was too old.
Was dober a current player on the team?
No, but he was like a more recent player.
Well, they could age them up.
No, I think that would have dropped.
Bradshaw was coached, he was the same age as coach,
it wouldn't have made any sense.
All right, you got, you got a guy older than coach
being like, hey coach, listen, I don't remember
the specifics of coach.
And I was like, I'm proud of that.
Wasn't that show supposed to come back?
They started shooting it and shut it down.
They shut it down.
They started, they stood, that was really hard to say.
They started shooting it and shut it down. Yeah, why they shut it down?
It's it's something that happens. I mean
They'll be shooting something and be like this is not gonna ever make to air. This is bad. And they pull the plug. Oh
geez
I would have liked it. I've had friends who've had shows like that. Although they'll shoot four or five and they're like, yeah, no
We're willing to throw away, you know 20 million dollars. Yeah, it's how bad we think the show is. It's I'm sure it's not fun
uh... or you know it doesn't even mean it's bad maybe they don't like it
now you don't know people the third film in this in that night
sharky's machine surprisingly
they didn't stick with the how -need and burnt Reynolds theme
uh...
and show cannonball run
right or
stroke or ace
right uh...
but i i can only assume it was some sort of a rights issue or something
uh... because i mean the cannonball run was the no -brainer it's like
Like, how was the third movie, not the other car,
uh, Bert Reynolds movie, that, how neat I'm directed also, like, but, uh,
but, uh, it was Sharky's machine, which took a dark turn in the evening,
because that's a much heavier film.
Yeah, I was happy to have something a little more weighty at that point of the night.
Still had plenty of Reynolds, like,
gags and gaffes in it.
Yeah, I mean, it's weird because both Smoky and the Bandit and Hooper are movies that were kind of, like,
dismissed upon the time of their release.
Well, Smokey was, and Smokey was the biggest film of the year next year.
Critics say it.
No way.
Got very good reviews.
Not Smokey at the back.
Watch the documentary.
Got very good reviews.
I watched the documentary.
I don't recall that.
All right.
I talked about how shit everybody shat on it.
Agreed to disagree.
But they knew that people would want to see it.
Okay.
That was the story of Smokey.
I thought.
And Sharky's machine had rave reviews.
And I've seen Tarantino talk about Sharky's machine.
and he used the song Street Life from it in Jackie Brown.
So I've always heard about this movie.
I never saw it available to rent anywhere,
but very like critically acclaimed movie.
For me, it was the weakest of the three.
I agree it was my least favorite of the three,
but it was also such a tonal shift.
It was hard to kind of put it up against the other two.
You know, you got a movie about like beer, drinking
and car racing and then all of a sudden
you're into this prostitution ring
and people are being murdered and there's a scene
We're a woman literally has her face blown off and they show the body with no face. Yeah, so you're it's much more graphic material
But Reynolds had his whole crew in there. He had Charles Durning and and Brian Keith and
Yeah, from mod squad. Yeah, they got from mod squad
Nobody was trying too hard on this. What's what's that guy's name? What's the city Casey? Bernie Casey and
Richard Libertini, his friend who died and they never mentioned again.
Yeah, Bert Reynolds did say during the Q &A that somebody asked about Charles Durning
and he said there was nobody better as an actor.
He was the best that ever lived. We'll never have another one.
And somebody also said, how do you direct Dom Deloise in a scene
and he said, quite simply, you don't.
Which leads us.
Yeah, to Pat's movie corner because I have a segway here. Well, we'll be quick because that we just talked about several
But I saw I watched off of the piggybacking off of the Reynolds stuff
Yeah, one of my favorite films it is in my top 10
Fatso I re -watched Fatso. I
Had borrowed it from you and watched it as well and loved it. I love the film. It's it was of joy to re -watch
I can't understand how Dom Delewee's wasn't nominated for an Oscar. He's brilliant in it. It's hilarious
and I can't understand why the hell and
Bankcroft never made another movie after that. She wrote and directed this thing. She acts in it
She hits a fucking grand slam on all three fronts
And look now. I love Mel Brooks. I'm a huge fan. She's married to Mel Brooks. This movie's better than any Mel Brooks movie ever
Mel Brooks made 87 goddamn movies. She made one movie. It's a fucking masterpiece and that was it
Well, I certainly disagree that it's better than any of Mel Brooks movies, but name one Mel Brooks movie
It's better than that young Frankenstein blazing saddles. Oh stop blazing saddles
Listen, I love blazing saddles. It doesn't have the heart that fucking fatso has doesn't have the drama
We're just asking which is better
That's a better film, it's better constructed I'll argue this to the day I die because I'm not a sexist like you are that things just because a man did it's better now. I like that's a quite a bit. I thought, you know, there were some things that were not a grand slam for me and that's a and bankruptcy performance actually it was a little much for me know that some of the fantasy type sequences were a little.
There are no fantasy type sequences. Am I remembering it wrong? What the hell are you talking about aren't there?
There's a few there's a few like broader moments in it that did not work. No, there are not any fantasy sequences
There's something I'll think of it. You just watched it. So you and bankrupt's performance is pitch -perfect
I grew up in a family like that and she nails that type of woman at that time period in that type of family. All right
Look I like just means when you talk out of your ass it makes me upset
That's what this movie is important to you when you were a child that seeing it with with cold new eyes
It's a master piece. I saw it in my the first time when I was 30 years old. It's a masterpiece. All right
I love it. It's a very good movie
It's a very good movie. It's an excellent movie. Yeah
Go ahead Tina Fey's favorite film by the way. I didn't know that yeah my friend Max Brooks their son
Yeah, he told me that personally, okay
Got a real chip on your shoulder about this move. I
Think she should have made more movies. I don't understand, you know
Well, she probably didn't want to I mean the movie. Well, no, that's what I that's what I think
I get the feeling that she maybe just like I got it out of my system
I wanted to do it and I did it and that's it she might have been very happy to not do it again, but it's a shame
She didn't make more movies I concur
All right
I watched on Amazon Prime, the Handmaiden, which I believe was nominated for best foreign
film last year.
It is by the guy who did Old Boy, Chao Woon Park, I hope.
Okay.
Is that correct?
I'm going to look up his actual name. You can't just guess it's something like that.
Fun fact last week that I meant to mention by the way, uh, it was directed by Brian Taylor who did crank mom and dad.
Oh, yes. Yeah, I guess he split up with his partner, but I love the way their movies look.
And his partner is doing what now?
Neville Dean. I don't know. Oh, I'm thinking of how the Hughes brothers do separate stuff now.
Oh, one guy is doing the two -pock biggie thing. I don't know what the other one is doing. I know
but Brian Taylor did mom and dad did a great job directing.
Yes, and it had that crank vibe to it.
Yes.
Handmaiden is directed by Park Chan Wook.
I think if I didn't have it, I was at least close.
I'm sorry, but he did old boy sympathy
for Mr. Vengeance, Lady Vengeance, blah, blah.
What's the film about?
Have you seen old boy?
No, I'm not a big fan of those types of films
where it's a lot of like where they're awesome.
I don't need to see a film where the guy takes a pill at the end so he can fuck his daughter
again without remembering it. Isn't that old boy? Isn't that how old boy ends? You should
really watch old boy. No, isn't that the end though? No. Isn't there some incestuous relationship
in old boy? Do you want to know or do you want to see like an amazing movie? Somebody told
me the whole plot once and the incest factor, I was like, I don't want to see it. Why would
someone explain the whole plot of old boy? Because I probably said. It's a pleasure to see it for the
first time. All right. Yeah. He's like fucking his daughter or some shit at the
end of it or some things in there that are for adult audiences, Joe. Yes. Um, I'm
not a big fan of that kind of thing. And if that's the kind of sick shit you
like, then have at it. Now, did they keep that in the Josh Brolin Spike Lee
version? They did. That movie sucked. I love Spike Lee. He was the wrong man for
the job on that one. But I was rolling in it. Brolin usually is pretty good. I
I didn't like the whole move.
I didn't like anything about it.
Okay.
Which sucks because I love Spike Lee
and I hope they bring him back to Hollywood
at some point soon.
He's directing something like major coming out.
Good.
He's doing something like big.
I can't remember what it is.
Good.
I mean, he's at a point now where he needs
a little structure support from somebody above.
I mean, his movies that he's making for himself
lately are kind of for himself alone.
Shirok, your sweet blood of Dracula or whatever that was called.
The sweet blood of Jesus. I tried to get through that one. That's a wild film, man.
Yeah, I mean, they were just like, they had no appeal, really.
You know, they were just like kind of painful to watch.
Well, once I realized everybody was talking in rhymes and poems in Shirok,
that's right. It took me, I couldn't, it was it. I couldn't, I couldn't not think about that anymore.
but the man's made 10 classics. Malcolm X, one of the greatest film ever made.
Anyway, the hand made. He wouldn't say blazing saddles is better than that too.
No, it's not what we're talking about. The hand made it. It's about two and a half hours,
maybe more. That's why I had put it off forever. I heard it was great a year or two ago and didn't watch it,
But it was sitting there last night, just an amazing story, incredibly well told.
If you're a fan of old boys, I'm sure many of our listeners are, I don't think we ever
talked about it on here.
It's not as violent, you know, but it's, it's as great a story.
So like basically, it is a guy who says, I'm going to marry this woman, put her in a mental
hospital and take her fortune. He needs a maid. He hires this maid to help him a handmaiden to
get in there first. They're like auditioning for a new maid. So you go in and start talking me up.
Okay. Like, oh, you know, I came from a he thinks you're beautiful. I think you're beautiful.
Then when when he shows up, the work's been done. She's laid all the groundwork. The two of them
hook up. He throws her in a and saying, a silent takes her money splits it with a handmaiden
and they leave, that's the plan.
That's already, this is too much for me.
No, but it's so clear.
Like the fact that I can just calmly explain it
when I sometimes have trouble with the details
of movies after I've seen them.
No, I'm not saying too much like confusing,
I'm saying it's too sad.
Like these movies are too, a lot of these.
Oh, no, you gotta watch this fucking.
A lot of the Asian thrillers are just too dark for me.
I can't do it.
They're real dark, but this I thought
I was a pretty powerful love story in the end.
And I don't call a lot of things a powerful love story.
Would you refer to this as a powerful?
I would, and it's also, no, this, me and you.
Oh, me and you, yeah.
You could have gestured to us.
Sorry.
There's a lot of really, really hot sex in it
to tell you more about that would be a spoiler oddly enough.
All right, daddy. I'm listening. But and it's in three parts. So if the if the running time is
Daunting to you, you could space it out over three nights. I thought that's what I was planning to do
But I was so fucking hooked on this story. I watched the whole three hours. I can't recommend it enough. It's just an awesome story
It looks amazing. It's very like exciting. It's got a feel of like a drama kill bill like not the action
Okay, but it's got that feeling as opposed to like an audition feeling like what you're describing where it's kind of wallowing into
Previty kind of thing. Okay. It's not like that. Yeah, great great movie
All right, well
I
Don't know if I have anything else for
Now I'm just checking my phone here. I think I saw something else give me one second. Oh
Well, night of the creeps.
Night of the creeps.
Never seen it, I own it, never seen it.
You know, classic 80s horror.
Hell of a lot of fun.
Stars the kid that plays Rusty in the second
in European vacation.
I wouldn't know who that is.
It stars him and Tom What's His Face,
the guy that plays the cop in a Halloween three.
and he plays the dad in Creepshow.
And others, my favorite line probably ever in horror movie history, that Pinkstone and
I say constantly to one another, that's why God made fathers, baby.
That's why God made fathers.
He says that as he puts his feet up and sips his beer.
He usually plays a kind of a darker personality.
This film is no exception, but he is heroic in the movie as well, which is nice to see.
It's just fun. It's just a fun kind of gross out 80s horror comedy. It was written by the guy Fred
Decker who went on and wrote the monster squad. After this he co -wrote the new predator movie
that's about to come out with Shane Black. I feel like that's supposed to been about to come out for
a very long time. Yeah, typical re -shoot shit, whatever. But anyway, Fred Decker does some great stuff
and it's it's really just a lot of fun. I don't even know. So check that out if you like that sort of thing.
Yeah, I own it. I'll open it and watch it. Yeah, it's about alien worms that get inside corpses and
turn them into zombies. I mean, it's, you know, it's just fun, 80s, gross romp, whatever. Do you remember the
stuff with Garrett Morris? Yes. I like the stuff. It's not a great movie. Well, with Garrett Morris,
with Paul Servino.
Yeah, that's right.
Not a great film, but it's fun.
I remember being very scared of it as a kid, but it's not scary at all
when I saw it on cinematics the other night.
Folks, I guess we're ready to talk about the picture at hand
and there's much to talk about with an iolation.
It is the follow -up for Alex Garland to the much beloved by myself included.
ex machina. I love that movie. And he was clearly given, you know, as always
happens when you get a big, here's what happens nowadays when you have a big
indie hit like ex machina. You either go the Marvel route immediately, which
I'm sure he was offered, or you do your big personal project that you've been
I wanted to get the funding for forever.
Sometimes that pays off.
Start your career off right.
Sometimes it pisses a lot of people off.
An Iolation has been doing both.
And at the theater where I saw it,
a lot of the arguments I was hearing,
people had very, very different opinions on this movie.
Which can often be the sign of a movie
that sticks around that people are talking about
for a long time.
I thought the movie was,
It's suspenseful, very entertaining,
starting to lose me near the end
and then kind of lost me until I started thinking
about what it all meant and I have a take on it
that I like and I think the movie is kind of open
to interpretation.
Well, in the end, I come away from it liking it,
I would be hesitant to recommend it
to a certain kind of person who needs a linear storytelling
but I liked it.
Well, Pat, I gave this film two glistening hogs down.
Wow.
I thought it was terrible.
I thought it was a completely masturbatory film.
I thought it was fucking pointless.
I thought that first of all, X Machia, X Machina,
some of the best special effects I literally
have ever seen ever in a movie.
You believe you're looking at a woman who is whose body is like part circuit board and whatever and
This film these effects
Would go from find to pretty good to horrific like there were scenes where I was first of all
Let's start with the plot of the film. It's about
It's about a government area folks
Called the Schumer well. No, that's what's in the government area the government area itself is called
area X. We're already off to a bad start. Inside area X is this freak of nature occurrence
that's happened where there's a glistening wall called the shimmer, which is, and I know
he didn't write this, it was based on a book, that's one of the dumbest. He did write the movie,
and he changed a bunch from the book. Okay, well I don't know if it's called the shimmer in the book,
but the shimmer is one of the dumbest names I've ever heard for anything ever in my life. Okay.
And the whole plot is, is there are these, this team of all women, and I only point out
that they're all women because in the movie, they go out of their way to say, huh, the
team's all women.
Natalie Portman actually says that sentence, yet it has no significance whatsoever.
There's never a point where you go, oh, that's why they were all women on this expedition
or that's why she pointed that out.
they never point that out.
She just says it and it sits there and that's it.
As far as I can remember, I guess that's true
that it's not, but perhaps that's open to your interpretation
as well.
Sure.
I mean, I sort of took it as they tried it with dudes.
Everybody died.
Let's try it with ladies.
But in this day and age, you would never try,
you like in a military thing like that,
you wouldn't do in all dudes.
That you would send the top people period.
You wouldn't be like, no, only dudes can go in.
That's not how it works in the military.
You'd send your top people in to do this fucking expedition in any case.
Then point and look, if that's the point, then point out that all the other expeditions
were all dudes.
They don't do that either.
But give me some reason that you're or don't mention it and nobody's thinking about it.
Anyway, you know, I just thought that was an odd thing to go out of your way to point out
And then just don't point it out.
Why are you putting it out anyway?
It doesn't matter.
None of this stuff bothered me in the slightest.
That's fine.
Well, here's why I bothered me,
because it felt like it was supposed
to be some anti -sexism statement that was sexist.
It's more sexist that you're pointing out
that they're all women right now.
I'm not even thinking about that.
I don't need you to point that out to me.
Anyway, the team is being led by Jennifer Jason Lee.
who gives, I mean, this performance, I was like,
did she get hit in the head before the movie?
I mean, what the fuck was she doing through this whole thing?
I'll give you, I'll give you, yeah,
and I like her a lot as an actress.
Me too.
I'll give you, I was not sure what she was doing.
Literally, every January, January,
January line, she'd be like,
can I go in the shimmer, it was the shimmer.
Cause I was happy to get in the shimmer.
It was terrible.
So anyway, the backstory here
There is nobody's come back from this thing alive except for Natalie Portman's character's
husband who's played by Oscar Isaac.
And he's deathly sick and internally bleeding and having a hard time existing outside of
this thing.
But he's the only one that's ever returned.
So here's what they know.
We've sent several teams into this weird thing from space.
by the way, that spans, it's like a 20 mile area,
yet nobody seems to notice that it's there.
You got people managing to get cell phone shots
of like Britney Spears vagina
as she gets out of a fucking limousine.
Yet nobody notices the giant 20 mile radius pink bubble
on the western coast of the fucking country.
Just nobody just sees the woods, isn't it? Huh? It's in like the woods. Yeah, people go into the woods people hike people hunt
I mean look there's not one part where they're like look at these people that somehow wandered in here
As usual, I can't really argue with any of these points you're making and yet I didn't care or think about any of them
Here's here's where the real problems start. Okay. These are nitpicky things all right the thing
The thing that nobody has ever come back from alive except the one guy who's bleeding
to death on the inside, cuts to the new expedition of people going in, not one helmet, face
mask, gloves, they're just walking into this thing.
Now they hadn't seen the video of the guy with the tentacles in his stomach yet.
when they're monitoring oscarisic in the military hospital after he comes back from the shimmer,
the people monitoring him are wearing hazmat suits. When the movie opens and they're interviewing
Natalie Portman after a return, everybody is wearing hazmat suits and they have an
isolation chamber. I miss that same, but these four women walk in no nothing. We're just going to walk
into this thing. Ridiculous. They get in there, time starts shifting. One of the first things
they notice is that basically DNA mutates in a strange way out here. And how do they notice
this? Because they see things that aren't possible. And how do you know they aren't possible? Because
they say that every single time they encounter one of them, even though they just saw like a moose
with a shark face in the last scene,
they'll find like a branch that has two different flowers on it.
And Natalie Portle will be like,
it can't be, it's impossible.
It's like, you just saw a goddamn walking,
a sea bass.
You don't believe this is happening right now.
Fair, fair.
And all the mutations, correct me if I'm wrong,
look like shitty art projects.
All right, so you were telling me you were not scared
by that wolf scene. You didn't find that very intense and cool.
Which wolf, the bear scene in the house?
The bear, sorry, yes, the bear scene.
You know, I'm glad you mentioned it.
I wrote a couple positives at the bottom of my list here.
The one thing was the bear scene ruled.
I thought the scene was awesome.
Yeah, but that's not, that doesn't make a good movie.
That was a great scene.
Okay.
Were you, I mean, were you from the jump like this movie sucks?
Or were you into it?
No, I was interested to see it.
In fact, I said I would tell this story this week and it's a very short story.
I thought the movie started at 10.
and I got to the theater, it started at 11.
I was already tired.
I was so mad that I attempted to go see Red Sparrow instead,
because it started at 10,
and I hated Red Sparrow so much that I left
and then went to see annihilation
because I was excited to see it,
and set up, so the two hour experience
was a three hour experience.
But I wanted to see the fucking movie, dude.
I didn't wanna leave.
As I said, all the mutations inside the shimmer
or look like bad art projects.
It's literally like crystal trees.
And then there's like bones in sand.
These are all things.
I thought all that stuff was cool.
These are all things that like your friend
that doesn't have a job when they go,
hey, come see my art installation that I did.
You're like, what is it?
They're like, well, we cleared out a blockbuster video
and we put bones in sand.
And you're like, I don't wanna go see this
and I have to go see it because otherwise
this person might kill themselves.
Woo! This friend you're talking about is me, by the way. You could have at least changed it from the blockbuster video that I held my exhibit in.
The, uh, just like the effects, the soundtrack would go from amazing, like amazing like synth
weird, like, how do they even think of this to compose this to like the shittiest
John Denver acoustic guitar where you're like what is happening right now it doesn't
make sense there's no consistent mood here everybody's performance was
completely flat except for the one woman that goes crazy right and starts
trying to kill everybody and ties everybody up in the house that was Jane the
Virgin then you get to the end of this thing and there's a video camera in the
shimmer, just conveniently. They just keep conveniently finding video cameras throughout the place
that where they can watch videos of past expeditions gone wrong. Because that's what you do when
everything's going horribly wrong as you take videos. Anyway, they get to this lighthouse they're
trying to get to where this all started. They go in, there's a video camera in there.
Not only Portman watches the video on it, it's her husband, Oscar Isaac, who suddenly
now for no reason whatsoever has a deep southern accent that he's doing.
I don't understand what it is, it doesn't make any sense.
And then he kills himself and then what you assume is an alien walks from behind the camera
and it looks exactly like him because the Oscar Isaac in the real world, folks, isn't
actually him it's a doppelganger which you know what if I hear the fucking word doppelganger
one more time in the description of a sci -fi movie go fuck yourself I'm tired that is such a
that is that plot device is up there with like it was he was the killer the whole time he was hunting
himself it's ridiculous it's fucking ridiculous well look here is after much thought much discussion
with my girlfriend after, here's what I kind of came up with, and then I got into some
fan theories that were on similar tracks.
I think, and I was frustrated by it too, I was like, the story was kind of not that cool,
so I think I'm made to create some sort of other meaning to this.
I thought that was the intent.
Okay.
Mother is a similar kind of let's give this Indie guys some big money again see what he can do
You like that I hated mother. I will tell you this mother has a very clear metaphor to it
It's very clear. It's a it's it's it's it's it's it's a what's it called a
Not a parable well mother earth and the Bible were two different sort of I mean
It's you know, it's it's it's once once you realize that you're like oh, okay, this I don't I didn't
Now, tell me if there's a theory about that with this, but I like an open -ended movie once in a while
They don't make them anymore. I like movies that make you think I thought
Everyone was going in there with some
Serious issue one of the women was suicidal one of them had cancer, etc
What I took from it was that these women were all extremely depressed
Important about the loss of her husband
They go into this thing and the other women don't want to live.
They are suicidal, ultimately.
Portman says something about that at the end.
She wants Portman wants to live.
She said she had a reason to.
So people that go in there are depressed, Isaacs went in because of the affair.
Portman has an affair that that's what made me start a vest.
in this shit. I was like they never mentioned the affair again. What was up with that affair?
Right. So I think the news of the affair put him in a place where he was like suicidal.
And the movie, to me, how I took it, and this might just be me being depressed all the time,
is people trying to break out of depression. So the Jennifer Jason Lee character
is like, I'm gonna stay in here and just wallow in it,
et cetera.
Portman gets out, I just get out.
But are they really themselves?
You know, are is depression ruling them?
If you look at it through that lens of depression,
it's not exactly a perfectly clear narrative there either.
No.
But I found that I got a lot out of the movie thinking
about it under those terms.
And they're not all depressed.
Why is the lesbian woman depressed?
They all were given specific backstories about their depression because she was like drinking beers and having fun and hitting on Natalie Portman
She must have had some
All right
Well the one what they they the one -lost her baby, right? I mean like they all had some tragic tale
Maybe she's the suicidal one. I don't I don't remember that part. I don't know specifics either, but there are there are
There has to be a reason to me they have this big affair in the movie to never be mentioned again
There has to be a reason to me that all these women are going in I didn't think about them all being women so much as they're all
Going through something very serious and painful. So then why doesn't doppelganger for escrow as it come out at the end
That's the healed him we're all just shells of ourselves once we're healed of our emotions
That is exactly how I took that, yes.
I'll tell you this.
That doesn't mean that my theory is right.
When I did some snooping with the, basically, when you Google with the intent of finding
what you want, like, when I typed in, depression, annihilation, I read some really great articles
that articulated what I'm trying to say now better.
But and then some took what I was thinking a little further, some different on what I thought.
But I like having a big budget did relatively well movie that is open -ended and makes you think.
I got a problem with that.
That's fine.
I have no problem with an open -ended movie that makes you think.
But at the end of the day, it must be entertaining and this movie was not entertaining.
This was film school bullshit, in my opinion.
Take it back to film school.
You want to go do a bunch of weird visuals and have people turning into light for no apparent reason and
Weird trees that are shaped like children go to fucking film school and and do an existential film class or something like that
All right, make the goddamn movie entertaining X Machina to to a certain extent was open -ended
And there was things that could be interpreted and there was weirdness in that and strangers
But it was an entertaining movie. There was there was a there were characters you could connect to you feel bad
When the redhead dude gets killed cap general hawks from Star Wars when he gets killed
You feel bad you like the Oscar Isaac character and that and then when he becomes a piece of shit
You hate him like you feel bad for the girl you want her to win and then she becomes evil and you're like what the fuck
There's there's something to invest in this movie is is five monotone people walking around in a fucking state park
Yeah, looking at things that it looks like a six year old made it in an art class like a like a branch that has four different kinds of flowers on it
Right, yeah, I liked it a good deal less than X Mahina. I don't think it was some piece of shit. I thought it was an
interesting movie that
To you I'm gonna say something to my point and something to your point
I think in the same way as mohalon drive where I was like I have a pretty good grasp when I think this movie's about and then you watch it again
and then you're like, yes, and it just keeps kind of
strengthening what you thought.
I think that could happen if I watched an Iolation again,
but to your point, will I do that again probably now?
Exactly.
I can't even really call it a noble failure
because I was pretty entertained by it.
I just thought it was a really interesting movie
that I wish had been a grand slam,
but I certainly enjoyed myself while I was watching it.
I had a great talk afterwards,
Whereas a lot of times it's like, let's not talk about that movie we just saw because it maybe want to hang myself.
Yeah, I was bored to tears, come.
And I thought it was dumb.
Alright, anyway, that's our show folks.
We're split, we got one hog up, one hog down.
Joe DeRos' comedy on Instagram and sometimes Twitter, the Pen House column, as you let me
down.
And my apologies to anybody that was planning on coming out to the in bloom tour that
I had been plugging on here for a while.
I had to cancel the whole thing due to a different commitment that came up that was entertainment
related.
And we'll hopefully have some news about that soon that I can actually discuss.
But I apologize and we will we will re -schedule so all right guys. I'll talk to you later
I would be remiss if I didn't do a couple of these annihilation questions real quick
I found the self -destruction as part of being human theme in annihilation very interesting. What do you guys think about that?
So what is it self -destruction self -destruction as part of being human those women were all self -destructive
to, I would say, I mean, yeah, kind of, sure, talk about that bear, please, I've never
been so disturbed by a single scene. We did. Why was the team so unprepared to go
into the glimmer given that they've spent so much time studying? Exactly. It's, it's
a huge fucking, why did they even have radios and shit knowing that it doesn't work? And
why didn't they leave a trail of breadcrumbs or just a very long ropes that don't get lost?
I guess what I want is answers says Mike Urbina
All right, fair
Your feelings on some of the world getting such a visual movie like a annihilation straight to streaming
I think in Britain and stuff. They went straight to Netflix
That's it's the way the world's going. Mm -hmm. I don't know what to tell you. I think it's deeply unfortunate
What do you think of Alex Garland as a writer in general?
Seems good. I only know those couple things, but is that the director? Yeah, I think you also did the beach
which I was not a big fan of, but I didn't break that caprio thing.
Yeah. I didn't read the book. So yeah. All right. Um, and then why did you ask the
Renon Stimpy guy to do what he did? What happened? What did the Renon Stimpy guy do? They found
out he was flying out 14 year old girls to live with him. Wait, which guy? John reference
rifles. Okay. Not Billy West. Not the. Oh, no. Okay. Good. Did it not mean not good. That
It's another somebody you don't even know just that would have been very bad situation. This one was so the guy that created
Ren and Stimpy did what he was flying out girl saying it was like an animation internship, and then he would you know
moloss them. They were 14 16. He had a girlfriend for years who was 16 then 17 then nobody mentioned it
Jesus Christ. All sounded pretty dark. I don't know way to end the show. I already did my plugs. I'm on Twitter and Instagram at the
Living Biblically is on CBS Monday night 938 30
We don't know what we're gonna do next time, but it'll probably be ready player one
Which I have seen and Joe has not so get out there and check it out. See you next time. We'll see you in hell