Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer, or check out
our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz, only available at Bed
MDM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Bet MGM game sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM dot com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and
West Virginia only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal, durable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Monthly 21 plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberler, offer not available in all states,
terms apply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
This is a head gum podcast.
Hey yo, coming to you from the big thick uncut dick house, go ahead. It's Pat
Walsh and Joe DeRosa's. We'll see you in hell. Your favorite horror sci -fi fantasy
movie podcast uh here we are people to my front right in front of me on his knees come on
we did this last time I know sorry um you know Joe a lot of controversy this week on the
Facebook page because I didn't even realize this the last step you and I did not do on on with
the Joe or I did not do it on with oh jeez it feels like we always do it but I guess we did
and a lot of heat, a lot of talk.
So I just want to real quickly get that out of the way.
Okay.
I'd love to get on with the show.
And in doing so, get on with the joe ho ho, it's magic.
You know, you better believe his name's joe.
I never know what the song is,
so you hit the second part.
Yeah, like when you go up. I didn't know what you're doing then you hit magic and then it all makes sense and it makes me laugh
I don't even know who sang that song, but you I hear it at concerts all the time weirdly now
I know we did do this bit last week, but seriously are you gonna get off of your knees or not?
I mean if you don't want me to to call it out
You guys week it was a bit this week. I am actually belating my friend Joe
No, hello folks. I the Facebook page you don't you don't see this stuff and I'm about to get out of it myself
people are starting to feel real comfortable just throwing out criticisms. And I
gotta tell you I don't need to get trolled in the Facebook page for my own
podcast that's free. God damn it. Well maybe it's patrons that are making
criticisms. I doubt it. Well maybe who knows. What's what are the criticisms? I mean
They come hard and fast and it's about everything and now they start digging through our past somebody put up some metallic a video you did like
Five years ago where you're in like a tank top that nobody was being critical of it per se but oh
I feel like people are like like
Googling our past and I don't like it. Well, that's not criticism pass. I don't know that that's that's a bad example
Yeah, but there's a lot of criticism going on
I know the, I know the videos are about, I did a web series for Warner Bros. music called
or what are we waiting for, and I played an insane, annoying music fan from Philadelphia.
Okay.
So there was a Metallica one with Rachel Feinstein and I, where we were janitors in an
office.
Yes.
And we were pushing the trash can around, whoop, whoop, and about Metallica.
All right.
It's just, it's hitting a place, there are two different, there are two different issues
I have the one and by and large it remains a fantastic community. I think they're wonderful people. Well, you're not on there
I I requested to be honest. I don't think I was ever approved. No, that would request would have gone to me if you had requested
I requested to be part of Facebook group and then I revisited and I still wasn't able to get in. Wow
Well, do it again. I guess I don't
All right, do you have you don't have a friend page? Do you don't have like a? No, I have a fan page. That might be the reason that's how Joe Joe rolls it in
And ho ho, that's what I call hollywood, ho ho ho, ho ho, that's good, that's good.
You don't need to be on Facebook, you shouldn't be on it, it's infuriating.
But you know, I'm just a person who like, I don't want to log in there someday and everybody's
been laughing for 12 hours at my fourth grade picture or something.
I'm too paranoid about you to stop.
That's love baby, that's love.
I know.
My other issue though, is the criticism.
You're clearly fans of the show. You're in a fucking fan page. I'm too sensitive, man. What is too sensitive?
What kind of criticism I could go on. I'm not even gonna give these trolls the the hate -or -aid. They so desperately crave
Some of them. I'll just I'll just delete it. I'll be like fuck you delete
Delete what they leave with some nasty comment. I'm like boom out. How would you have control and deleting things on the Facebook?
I'm an administrator
And now people will try to get believe it can't even get into the damn group. You're an administrator
Well, it's me and Emily, I mean, she does a lot more than I do.
Now, I know Emily's very swift to kick like any haters didn't hatin' out.
So I think maybe you're being a little...
No, well, I think hers was some guy who was saying racist shit or something, right?
But I am being too sensitive, of course.
But just anytime somebody says anything, I'm like, well, fuck you.
I remember you once got offended that I referred to your hair as red, and really threw you off
that.
I was like, I don't understand.
It's not that bad of a thing.
It's it's not a bad thing at all the hair is not the beard has a tinge of Auburn to it. Yeah. Yeah, that's all
I do I get offended to easily. That's all right me too. That's why I got off a Twitter. Yeah, no
I'm gonna have to I'm gonna have to get off of all this stuff. It's infuriating being off of Twitter is magical
You know, it's happening. It's happening magical. It's it's been months. I dip in I
I once don't once a week I'll dip in make sure I don't have any DMs even if I do I might not even look at them
I'll retweet like a plug for a show and
I'm out dude like it's it is been
Wave before Christmas. I didn't know this for a while now. I don't know how long it's been but it is
It is such a stress removal not going on to that fucking I admire it slinging website
I I was hitting a point where I would wake up my hand to go over to the phone
Yeah, and I'm I'm mad before I've even fully opened my eyes
It's it's a and then I go to bed doing it
And then you also get the you also get the pit in your stomach
How many shitty at comments? Oh you get for for something I tweeted that was just meant to be funny or right?
Then it's like celebrities you don't you not only do not care about now, but you never cared about and suddenly
It's an up. It's an uproar about this person or something they said and everybody's like
But can you believe, this week it was an interview with Erica Baddo.
So now, I would put my opinion of Erica Baddo as favorable, but I saw her once in concert
with a few other people.
She's fine, but I don't think about her ever, even at the concert I wasn't thinking about
her to Baddo.
And so she had an interview, it says she had an interview with Vogue or something, I'm like,
okay.
And I'm sitting there the whole time going, why are you reading this?
Right why right because they that's what they do they write Erica bad who stirs up some heat with her new you know
Like stirs up heat right sometimes you click on it. There's no heat
And then you click on it and you find out it's literally a story about how she is like oh, she brought a walk new stove
Yeah, yeah, so she goes here's what she said I
Try to find the good in everybody and and people will get pissed at you for that. She's like I I
You know like Hitler is a good painter. Let's be real. She's making a fucking joke right should not a comedian either
Right, but she's like her her the whole point was I try to find the good and everyone right and people were outraged about this
And I'm reading it. I'm I'm getting angry at the people who are outraged and then they'll after 10 minutes of this
Clicking on other links, right. I'm going Pat. You've been reading about Erica bad dude for 10 minutes
What are you doing?
What are you bad doing oh very good
No, it's nuts. Do you see that so the David Copperfield was the one I was gonna tell you about and I need to ask you Jim
Why did you tell David Copperfield to do what he do? I didn't even know he did anything apparently it made some girls dress disappear folks
That was a terrible joke
Yeah, what did he do this one really cracked me up right? So you want to I care less about David Copperfield
than I do bad do by about a hundred percent now can I make it please just tell me one thing make me
one promise in the david copper field sexual harassment right we're assault story yeah does the
misconduct take place inside the box when he brings the lady in during the show uh it did not
not okay all right it did not okay it was a terrible story that's why I'm hesitant to riff with
you on it oh it's it's like a real bad thing you know I literally have no idea what it is I know
we all know that. Copperfield or David Copperfield folks, more like it. He, uh okay he takes to he
puts out an open letter to the entertainment industry yesterday and it's like David Copperfield
releases statement on me too. So everything everything in my power is saying don't click on this
like you don't care Pat. And I clicked on, I opened it up. He's got this big
statement. And he's basically saying obviously me too is very important. We need to support these people.
It's we got to hear them. We got to listen. That said, we also need to not necessarily
believe everyone because years ago this girl accused me of rape. And she was proven to be a complete
and then just shitting all over.
He's like, she was a complete liar.
Everyone knew it.
We called her out and then the whole me too thing
takes this dark, weird turn.
Then it ends and I'm sitting there like,
why would David Copperfield release this statement?
Cut to today, David Copperfield.
Not 24 hours later, used of sexual misconduct.
What was, by the same lady or by the same lady?
It was the same lady, but she was 17.
She dropped to a bad start.
She, you know, he slipped something in her drink.
She woke up.
He was raping her or something.
Oh, my God.
Or, you know, they kept the details fairly vague.
So it's like, all right, Dave.
What, what, what, what did you think yesterday was going to accomplish coming out
with that statement that we'd all be like, okay, so now.
Yeah, like, like he's literally trying to be like, see?
What a coincidence.
So the day after I say it, I was blown away by the stupidity, like, there are
publicists. Somebody at his level has a publicist. Do you not talk to them?
It's like, it's he's literally, what's his face? He's literally the incredible
Bert Wunderstone. Yeah, that's right. That's terrible. How about I lighten it up with, we like,
Oh, go ahead one last piece, though
this girl
May release her statement and said I just want to let you know. I'm not at this time nor was I ever asking for money
I'm merely saying this happened
What why would I say this happen, right? You know, and it's like okay, these are all complicated matters
But uh Jesus Christ I feel like I might have made this comparison before but every time you get online
It's like opening that that like book of the dead or something
Yes, it's just like screams and horror coming at you had I've taken a drinking a bottle of wine a night
Okay, I don't know if that's a lot. It's probably not
To it's probably a little too much. It's no I mean I think moms do that. I mean, it's four glasses
It makes me feel good about myself. It lets me tune out you wake up without a hangover
Sure.
But you like the white one, I like a red one.
Well I read in a paleo blog that the best alcohol you can drink if you're trying to keep
the weight off is a dry white, really, yes, it's low in sugar.
So you find a dry white that's high in alcohol, like a 12, 5, 13, 5, that's going to be way lower
in sugar than your average red, but you can find a dry red too, it's just, red's a deeper,
darker grapes. So I think it usually just carries more sugar.
You know, the original title of Frazier was Dry Whites. I've been watching the show
non -stop. I can't get enough of it. You rubbed off me. I'm about 15 into the first
season and I'm enjoying it. Haven't laughed out loud, but I'm enjoying it.
It starts to get laughed out loud funny in the second season. Okay. First season,
like I said last time, they're still working out some of the kinks. Like the dad's
still a little too mean right you know like but once they get rolling niles I
mean once niles takes flight it's just yeah the physical comedy every he's the
greatest cast a grammar is very funny I love it's easy to forget you know I
heard that being a camera operator on that show was the hardest job in town
because it was all crane shots oh god speaking of that kind of joke folks I found
three folks jokes in my iPhone that I haven't looked at in forever. I'm going to do them on stage
tonight. I just had a document called OneLiners. These are all folks jokes. I'm just going to
do these on stage of my show. I'm going to open with these. Are you going to say folks? Why not? Yeah,
you should. So the first one is, hey, my, the hospital says if they can deliver my wife's pregnancy
and under 30 minutes, it's free.
Okay. I wouldn't start with that one.
This is the one I really like, but it has a questionable word in it.
Folks, I got off with a handicap. My caddy's retarded.
Now, why can't you say—
You're going to get booted.
Why can't you say retarded in a clinical sense like that?
I'm not saying that guy's retarded who's not.
I'm saying a guy who is retarded is retarded.
Why can't you say it like that?
I have a couple friends, friends of friends who work with
the handicap, the mentally handicap.
They explained it to me.
I wasn't 100 % clear on it, but for whatever reason
that word is the end word of that community.
It just is.
All right, you know, I'm sorry, I'm not buying it.
I had retarded cousins, we all said retarded.
Nobody was offended.
It wasn't meant to do drugs.
It means stunted in some way, correct?
Which is what handicap means.
So I don't personally quite get it,
but I don't say it.
All right, so do I have to change?
Well, I don't say it like,
I don't say it like in the sense of like,
I wouldn't, if you were being,
if I thought you were acting dumb,
I wouldn't go, you're being retarded right now.
I'm gonna do that.
Cause to me that's derogatory.
But if I'm referring to a mentally handicapped person,
I say, this is a retarded person.
That's a term.
I don't understand.
Are you introducing the person when you say that?
That might be the issue with the drumroll yeah, all right, so don't don't do that on stage. Don't do it
I did it before it worked really well, but it was 15 years ago
You think maybe things have changed
No, no, no, it's a change in the last 15 weeks 15 minutes. Oh
How do I break so how do I do it work? How about this? I got with a handicap my caddies in a wheelchair
Is that okay? Yeah, that's fun. Is it funny?
It's not as funny, is it?
No, of course it's not as funny.
But I mean, I'm telling you, it's not an L .A. joke, it's not an L .A. joke.
What if I call the audience a bunch of high -falutin cuts after I do it, will that work?
If they don't laugh, then I would call them that and get off stage.
All right, here's the third joke, ready?
Folks, folks, I got cat called the other day.
You can imagine my surprise.
How the heck did that cat figure out how to work a telephone?
That's my favorite of them, yes.
That's my favorite too.
Maybe I'll just open with that and then workshop
the correct word for the handicap joke with the audience.
Hey guys, I'm gonna bring you behind the curtain here.
You tell me which word would be funniest,
but also effective and not offensive.
You know, I was in a band in college called the PTA.
and uh... we're pretty good
but any who
i opened our first show by i went up to the microphone and i said uh...
well i just flew in from new york city
and boy is my plane tired
and i thought about it for a second i go fuck
and then we started the first song
like i had messed up the joke
it was a it's a fun way to start a thing
that's funny
it's a fun way to start
well huge laugh but then
It led into everyone being blown away by the healing power of our rock music of your rock music of your rock and roll
Right, so I you know it was the kind of thing where I'm like I'm laughing
But then I'm also like coming a little bit was the vibe I was getting from the audience. Oh God
Have you ever seen the George Carlin thing about euphemisms before you get to park in a park where driving a driveway or whatever?
No, that's just a bit, but well, I don't know what that's part of that's not part of it
No, that euphemism where he basically says it's from the late 80s so it's from a
while back but he talks about all because this all these word change things we're
happening back then to be basically says like guilty white people have created a
language to conceal their sins. It's as simple as that like and he goes into like the
whole thing of like you're not allowed to say handicapped anymore handicapped person
go I'm handicapable because that was a thing that used to happen right now you just
kind of breaks it all down with like words and saying like there's nothing wrong
with any of these words, like people just decided one day that they were somehow offensive,
and then if they change the word, it would change the condition, and it doesn't.
It's a very interesting bit.
Where does disabled fall is?
That's allowed now, right?
Disabled?
Yeah.
He doesn't say that one.
I don't know.
But I'm talking about asking you as a man, as a disabled man.
I am disabled.
Yeah.
I've got a cripplingly large penis.
Yes.
I know cripple isn't allowed.
You can't say cripple anymore.
No.
That's probably fun.
Which, but I mean, to say crippled, here's the thing.
This is my problem when people start saying, this is like the N word for us.
No, it's not.
And don't, how dare you put yourself in a category with the N word?
It's, that is a word that was used to promote slavery and to hold the people down completely.
Sure.
The word crippled was never used for that.
It just wasn't.
People weren't enslaved under the word cripples.
And just because a certain asshole takes it out of context and uses it to be funny and
goes, go, when you trip over its twig, he goes, what are you, a cripple?
You know what I mean?
Like, it's like, that doesn't mean that there's anything wrong with that word.
It's like, yeah.
Sure.
I can't stand the adjusting to the stupid people that misuse things.
Well, what is the acceptable word now?
Is it disabled?
I don't know, but my point is this.
I mean, I don't notice when someone's in a wheelchair.
I don't notice those things.
So I just see them as a person.
Right, right.
I just see them as differently abled.
I think it is differently abled.
Yeah, it's, but that sounds condescending.
But here's the, it is condescending and it's gross.
And you know who hates it?
People in fucking wheelchairs.
They don't like when you say, when you say shit like that.
Right.
But I mean, it's, it's somebody told me one time
that somebody said, see,
this is the problem there is no you can't set parameters for it we can all go well that was then
this is now and now this word is kind of offensive then but now your new words gonna be offensive
in ten you there's your ending it but because a guy told me once that he was uh he said um we need
to stand up for women's rights or something positive and he said he was talking to a person and the
person is starting to go, you can't say that, you can't say stand for something that's
insulting to people that can't stand.
I mean, dude, what the fuck, it's all going to get worse.
The world's only going to get worse.
It's only going to turn into two bottles of wine per day for me without a doubt.
Now, you're a guy that likes to throw slurs around, free and loose when we're, I'm kidding
everybody.
stop. Yeah, I'm joking. Uh, that'll be my version of why
you tell him to do it again. You're a big slur guy. Yeah.
Let's take it over to Pat's movie corner. And before we do our
Our movie for today is Raw.
Our movie is Raw, a documentary about the WWE.
No, it's the French horror film that's streaming on Netflix.
If you'd like, there will be spoilers, but we're not going to talk about it yet.
We'll get to it.
But it's on Netflix.
It's French.
It's got subtitles.
I'm sorry.
You need to start expanding your horizons a little bit.
Definitely a lot of spoilers.
There's no way to review the movie without spoiling it.
I need to get this list down so I'm going to be quick again.
I'm just going to do three here real quick.
Trip to Spain, you saw it, it's exactly like the other two.
I loved it.
It was my least favorite of the three.
I thought it was funny and entertaining.
I like it better than the second one, but I loved it.
Fair enough.
Good time.
Bobby Pattinson.
Oh, I didn't even know about it until yesterday when you were talking about it.
It wound up on some top 10 list. It's an extremely entertaining well done movie.
Very 70s feeling very exciting. Pattinson is fucking great in it.
He's a great actor.
I check it out. I check it out. I love that he made his money and now he's like,
I'm going to do my shit. Yeah, he's a great actor.
It's a good actor. Colossal. I made a promise that I was going to discuss it because it's been coming
up a lot on the Facebook page. Is it any good? It's a little like you're kind of watching
it for a half hour, like, come on. But it's an halfway in Jason Sudakis. Right. That's
good. And like essentially a sci -fi movie. So you're, you just don't know what to make of it
for a while. It's a comedy though, right? I wouldn't say so at all. Oh, because the trailer
very much made it look. Oh, I mean, I, I didn't even see any attempted jokes, but maybe people
find it. That's how I feel about a lot of comedy, to be honest, right? I, you know, for 45 minutes,
That's maybe I was kind of like I don't know if I'm feeling this and then it gets really
kind of interesting and good but the premise to explain it to you is basically to tell you
don't watch this movie.
It's a there's a playground that when halfway goes to it she controls a large monster in
In Japan, right, her actions on this playground control a monster in Japan.
Right.
I don't know who came up with this fucking thing.
I don't know what they were on, folks, wacky tobacco, perhaps, but by the end, it was
really, really interesting.
And she's kind of a recovering alcoholic and they that plays into it very well.
Okay.
It's a cool movie.
It's on Hulu.
So he has to be on the playground to control it.
Yes.
And then I'm going to stop there from revealing some of the twists.
I'll say though, I mean, it's not good for about half the movie, but it is worth watching
I think for the back half.
It was cool.
It was interesting.
Joe, take it away.
You only did two.
That was two.
That was three.
But I'll use this opportunity to do a fourth.
No, that was two.
Trip to Spain.
Oh, good time.
I'm sorry.
Good time.
Cool.
I'm sorry.
All right.
the Beguiled. Zero interest. I mean, folks, title from the second you say the title. Zero, that's
like going remains of the day. No, see you later. I like to mention that too. The Beguiled is based
on one of my very favorite Clint Eastwood movies that no one has seen. It's a Clint Eastwood movie from
the 70s. It's very weird and very interesting and unlike anything he ever did any which way but
loose the one with him in the chimp chimpanzee the whole time never saw that's
a clean east would move I know I never saw I was making a joke they took
everything interesting about that movie did away with it it's Sophia Coppola I
loved virgin suicides loss and translation and then from then on I I don't
really know what she's doing I didn't like loss and translation I really like
virgin suicides quite a bit I fucking love loss and translation but I think she
You can direct the hell out of a movie.
I've sort of been on the fence about her.
I like some of her stuff.
Bling ring was okay.
They always look cool.
The music's cool.
This was a real swing and a mess.
The cast is great.
It's Donst.
It's Kidman.
It's Colin Farrell.
It's the girl from Neon Indian,
Elle Fanning, whatever.
But they just didn't do anything with it.
They...
How is Neon Indian?
I'm sorry.
The Neon demon?
Demon.
Oh, the end Indians a band a good band a good band
So anyway, I can't recommend the beguiled I don't know. I don't know what's going on
This was a this was another for your consideration thing
I'm just the movie. I'm gonna get to it. I watched from like 15 years ago last night
I was like I think movies really truly were better. They were you know, they were just not good
I have a quick one. I saw finally
Finally, after all these years, where it's not been available on DVD and if you can
find it on VHS is extraordinarily expensive, but Amazon Prime finally put up a streaming
version of Fright Night Part 2, the original sequel to the original Fright Night.
Never saw it.
I'd never seen it, I had wanted to see it, I got to watch it.
Is it great?
No.
does it have scary moments? Sure. Is it sort of a lazy rehashing of the first film? Yeah.
Tom Holland involved? No. So, you know, we've got a lot of strikes against it here. But at the end of
the day, it's Peter Vincent, played by Malcolm, not Malcolm McDowell, for Christ's six. Malcolm,
the guy from plan of the eights.
McDowell.
Roddy McDowell.
Roddy McDowell, excuse me.
And William's something I forget the guy's name
who plays the main kid.
And then the plot is Jerry Dangeridge's sister
comes back to get revenge on Charlie
because she is pissed, obviously, that Charlie killed her brother.
And her plan is to slowly turn Charlie into a vampire
so she can torture him for eternity.
Which is a cool plot.
That's a cool premise.
Some really creepy scenes, some kind of funny parts, look, it's not the original, it's not
gonna be.
But I enjoyed it, and it's a fun popcorn movie, it's worth checking out.
And I did go into a bit of a rabbit hole as I was watching it, and I was like, well, who
directed you?
You went into a rabbit's hole.
Like, fuck a rabbit while I was doing it.
All right.
Now, is that offensive anymore?
Can you do that anymore?
The fuck a rabbit?
Yeah.
I don't know that you could you never you probably never could right? Yeah
What is the penalty though for fucking around? It's bestiality pad. It's it jail time. Yes, it's jail time
You could go to jail for fucking an animal. They can prove it
That's actually it's discussed and raw. That's why it's on my mind. It's the disgust
Space in space raw not disgusting raw right right. They talk about what they talk about aids in the monkey fucking a
Yeah, okay, and how technically any time you fucking animal it's rape because the animal doesn't know what she thought it was equal to human rape, right? Yeah
But I went down a rabbit hole. Yeah, and found out the guy down on a rabbit's hole
All right, go on Jesus and you're offended by my caddy's retarded bit the
My anyway, fat at the director Billy. I think his name's Billy Lee Wallace possibly also the director of the mini
series version of it. Tommy Lee Walsh. Tommy Lee Walsh, yeah. So that was cool. Yeah.
Did a little more searching. Got into Carpenter and some other stuff. Do you know this?
The guy that played Michael Myers in the first Halloween movie is also the guy that directed
major pain. Who directs a major pain? Nick Castle. Oh yeah. Yeah. I guess I did know that. Yeah.
He directed major pain. Yeah. And amongst other things, right? Yeah. He's directed a lot of
Yeah, major pants were kind of fun.
Get the fuck out of here.
There's no way.
Well, I see the glick where he goes.
I saw when I was 12.
Do you ever see the day when he shoots the closet?
I never saw it, pal.
Well, what do you, Pat, there's no way major pains, I'm sorry.
There's no way major pain is funny.
That's something that always really annoys me.
Not about just you, but everybody is.
When it's like, ah, fuck you, that fucking piece of shit,
you didn't see it?
You're talking way past living color,
are Damon Wayne. So you're already in trouble there. You're talking like blank man era.
You know, you're a way past blank. No, you're not. Yes, you are. This is all the same
period of time. And he's doing that like voice that voice he's doing, right? Which is never
good when Damon Wayne's does a voice. I love the movie. We've been boozled. Damon Wayne's
voice is terrible through the whole thing. Yeah. It's distracting. Yeah. It's the reason
I didn't see little Nikki. I like Adam Sandler. Fine. But but you see the trailer and
And you're like, I'm not listening to that voice for an hour and a half.
Little Nikki's unwatched.
But anyway, did you ever see the glic with Damon Waines?
Yes.
And he goes, major pain.
He just lets it hang there.
And Damon Waines appropriately starts laughing hysterically.
Yeah.
He's like, yeah, I know.
Look, when you're 12, it was mildly amusing.
I'm not recommending it or saying anybody should watch it, but it wasn't terrible.
Very.
It was along the lines of like Renaissance man or Sargent Bill go Christ. There was a lot
of those military comedies that came out or I tried to get through Renaissance man out
of pure love for Danu DeVito and the kid from juices in it couldn't get fucking through
it. I gave Sargent Bilco a second chance because I saw an interview like 15 years ago where
Steve Martin was like I was always sad that Sargent Bilco didn't get the shot I thought it deserved
I really thought it was a funny movie. I mean it is a pile of shit.
Well, again, I liked it enough when I was 13, but it was Steve Martin Phil Hartman and Dan Acroyd.
And of course, I was excited to see it. Yeah. Yeah. I might have told this one here.
But when I went to see Renaissance Man at the Mid River's Mall, six cinema, I rode my bike.
I go in, the picture has started and I sit down and when the lights come up
for the movie to start, I realize I'm sitting next to the only woman in the theater.
How old are you? The kid. 14 or 13.
It was weird, but I was so uncomfortable that I didn't want to make her uncomfortable
by getting up and leaving, so I just sat there next to her.
Who knew your kid?
You don't have the extra thought of, I'm creeping on this woman.
You're just like, you're just sitting there watching.
And then at the end, she turns to me and she's got a Kleenex and she goes, thought, you might
need this.
She's crying.
What happened to you?
And I was like, no, I'm good.
Thanks.
It's Renaissance, man.
I don't know.
Something moving, probably.
Isn't Marky Mark and Renaissance man?
I think so, and I think he still is Marky Mark at that point.
I think he is too.
Oh, Christ that movie.
Penny Marshall's low, lowest point is Renaissance man.
Why doesn't she direct?
I don't know.
That's a really funny thing when Jersey looking for comedy in the Muslim world.
I did, and I remember hating it, but...
Well, there's a real funny scene at the top.
The cold open is him.
He's going in to meet with Penny Marshall.
Yeah, to play the Stuart Jimmy Stewart role in the remake of Harvey. Yeah, I remember them and before he comes in the room
She's like who's coming in?
Albert Brooks. Oh God, and she's just trashing him
And she's like why did he remake the in -laws? Why would he do that? Yeah, you don't remake a classic
Which is funny because she's remaking Harvey, right? And then he comes in and he's like, you know big
I just want to say big was on last night
Just just a wonderful film. He's really gushing. She's just area that she goes. I love the end line
Yeah, that's Hollywood and not shell folks. Yeah, it's really funny
Phantom Thread
The Noah's it worth watching Paul Thomas Anderson film. There's another master all over again
Well, if you mean was it an awesome
Visually spectacular masterpiece. No
No, is it as good as there will be blood?
Is it fun?
I think love the master.
I know.
But you took me a second viewing and I fucking love
there.
I'll be blood.
That took me a second viewing as well.
I love that first time out of the gate.
But now, you know, Bougainites, Magnolia, Punch, Drunk Love, these are favorites of mine, all
time -faves.
I love the man.
He's never made a bad movie in my opinion, except for an hair and vice, except for an hair
and vice.
Phantom Thread.
I would say ranks one above inherent vice,
but it's way better than inherent vice,
but it's my least favorite of his,
but I mean, he's one of my favorite filmmakers.
I thought Phantom Thor was fantastic.
I need to see it a second time
because I think I'll like it a lot more.
What's interesting is it's about trying to be
in a relationship with a creative person
is what the movie's about, he's a dressmaker.
But the whole time watching, I'm like,
like, does this play at all outside of Hollywood artists?
It can't.
I gotta say, one of the things that has kept me
from watching my screener is,
you know, I don't think anybody is rushing to the theater
to see Daniel Day Lewis play a pleasant dressmaker.
You know what I mean?
Oh, he's very not pleasant.
Oh, good.
Oh, now I wanna see it.
He's a prick.
Oh, okay, good.
Cause the commercial makes him look too nice.
The reason I wanted to see it there will be blood
is because they're like, he's playing a crazed oil tie
I was like, oh, let's see it.
I want to see what he's going to do with this.
So he's a prick in it.
He's a complete prick.
Oh good, okay, then I want to see it then.
I don't want to see a nice dress.
I thought he was going to be like this kind -hearted dress now.
He's like a misogynist and he's a prick.
Well, I don't approve of the misogynist part,
but I do, I'm more interested in him being a bad guy.
Yeah, no, I mean, the trailers are,
make it look like something no one would ever want to see.
They've done a terrible job marketing it,
but it is a really entertaining movie.
It feels a little merchant ivory like it like it remains the day type thing. Oh those are movies
I would never have seen when I was a kid but when I watched them now I tend to really like them
I like repressed people dealing with their shit
But I'm not a big period piece fan my period piece interest starts in the 40s
Yeah, anything prior to that you're you're gonna have a hard time getting me to sit down
I I generally would agree with you. They have to be exceptionally good for me to like them
Maybe a western here or there, but you know.
I'm currently gonna give Phantom Thread a B plus
and I think it'll head up to an A minus
because it's good.
Like there's a lot of stuff about like
when you're in a relationship like your girl,
I just related to it a lot myself personally,
the lighter aspects of it, but you're sharing a house
with somebody and your girlfriend, wife,
whatever comes into the room while you're working on something
and it's just like shooting the shit about her day
or whatever, and then leaves.
And that should be completely fine,
but you can't help but be like,
I was in my creative zone or you don't say it
because you don't want to be a fucking asshole.
Day Louis says it throughout the entire movie.
He's like, he makes her feel like she's bothering him
at all times.
And it had some really interesting things
to say about relationships.
I liked it quite a bit.
All right.
Let's pop into some scary stuff.
Go ahead.
But this is going to be quick.
I got a video game.
I know a lot of you out there might not be video game enthusiasts.
And I know the ones of you that are
might not have a Sega Saturn.
It's an older console, but I do have a Sega Saturn.
It was Sega's second to last big swing in the console market.
I love the Sega Saturn.
It's particularly good for fighting games
because it was the first generation of consoles
that was able to port fighting games.
essentially identically to the way they looked in the arcade was a very good time for fighters on the consoles
And I went to a video game festival or convention or whatever you want to call it last weekend called retro city
Fest and I had a blast and I bought a bunch of cool stuff that I wouldn't be able to find on average in the day -to -day
Searchings for video games, but I got a game called Golden Axe dual that I
I believe was only released in Japan.
I got a Japanese import of it.
Surprisingly, the Japanese imports of the Sega Saturn games
are significantly cheaper than the American versions.
They got this game for $15.
I don't think it was ever released in the States.
And it's awesome.
It's the game Golden Axe,
which is one of the best video game series of all time
where you, you know, it's a sort of load
of the rings beat them up kind of thing.
It's that except Street Fighter.
It's all those characters in a street fighter kind of thing tournament fighter. It's great. It looks awesome
The graphics are amazing the sprites are nice and big. It's a really really really fun fighting game
If you do have a Saturn and you want to get it again, you should be able to find it for 15 or 20 bucks
You are gonna have to get the region break code card for your Saturn
If you have a Saturn you know what I'm talking about. I can't remember the name of it right now
But it's the thing that you put in the slot so it can play region -free
But it's a great medieval fantasy bloody old time. So yeah, there you go. All right
Excuse me. It's fine. I appreciate you doing it into the mic
Well, I want the listeners to know that this is real, you know
This isn't one of these apps where you buy it and you type in parameters and it does a podcast for you
We're still real people doing a podcast here. Joe. You'd even say it's raw
You're very good today with the word play which breaks me doing to
Feel raw. Yeah
Raw is a French film
But finance by the Belgian government, which is odd
Is that right?
It does at the top of the movie like in participation of the Belgian something that's weird like always with foreign movies
It'll be like it'll be like Dutch and then it'll start to be like the Irish film society presents. Yeah, something weird going on
I don't like weird. It's almost like in Europe. There's like a way easier time to get art made. Yeah
Shit hole we live in I gotta say there are some people and I know who won't even watch a foreign movie
I find that so stupid. I'm always so happy I did. It is a bit of an arm twist to get me there sometimes
but
What I love about it now in this day and age is that it forces you to put your fucking phone down and watch the fucking movie
Because you got to read it. I like that. I
Agree when I first started watching it
I had a text drafted to you that said this son of a bitch in movie as subtitles. Yeah, and then I didn't send it
because I thought, don't be that guy.
And I, you know, you get used to it.
Look, I don't have a problem with
staring at the screen, not looking at my phone.
I don't even have a problem with the fact
that you got to read.
The only thing I don't like about subtitles is
it creates a real focus on the bottom of the screen.
True.
And there is a learning curve in any subtitled movie
where it's, and it's, look,
you're talking about a drama, that's one thing.
A horror movie where there's a lot of visual stuff
going on that you want to see.
And then you're also trying to read.
it's not ideal. I'd prefer a dubbed version but that being said it was it was
an overall enjoyable experience. This movie is now in France it was called
Grave which I thought is actually a cooler title. By the way I said sure but I
would never have watched this movie dubbed in a million. Who would watch a dubbed
movie? I would watch outside of a Kung Fu movie. What's the difference? Well because
that's like silly fun. Why is it silly? Why don't you just watch a dubbed movie?
A Kung Fu movie is silly fun. I don't mind it being dubbed, but I can't take that seriously.
Some weird American voice coming out of nuts. Look, they don't even do dubbed anymore, do they?
I haven't seen it in a long time and I think it's a lost art and I just wanted to say my sure that I
said was just trying to be nice. I don't agree with Joe at all. Thank God nobody thinks less of you now.
thank you. The movie is very raw. It was called Grave in France. I think that's a cooler title.
That's a very cool title. Ross a little on the nose, but how the grave makes any sense.
How it's grave circumstances? I don't know. Just Grave is just a cool title.
Ross is a cool title too, but I like Grave a bit better because it's less used.
But look, what can we say? It's a film about a young vegetarian who comes from a strict
vegetarian family going off to vet school for college to learn how to help animals.
Think so highly of animals that as we already said in one scene, they're debating rape and
she says that raping a monkey is the same thing as raping a woman and women get mad at
her for saying that, and where did you fall on that debate, you know, I've been strongly
against both. My whole life. I'm strongly against both, but I would have to say, it's
not equal by any stretch of the imagination. I don't think it's equal. I mean, if I want
to, I don't think it's equal. Smear some peanut butter on my nuts and have a nice time with
my cat and I don't think I should be sent to jail for it.
Well, you know, that's up to the cat, really.
That's true.
Anyway, I didn't David Tel of a joke where he goes,
if I fucked an animal, it definitely wouldn't be a parrot
because he'd talk.
Well, there may be already lying stole it
or is it already lying?
Oh no, where's it already lying joke?
Yeah, already lying had that joke.
That's so, that's such a funny joke.
Yeah, it's a great one.
Why would you fuck the one animal that can talk?
Oh, that's right, that's right.
A tells was, a guy got went to jail for fucking a cow,
which means he had been warned many times.
He goes, I wouldn't fuck a cow.
I'd fuck a horse.
That way you always knew you had a ride home.
I've heard that one as well, yeah.
Anyway, she goes to school and there's this big freshman
hazing at the school.
Her sister is already a student there.
And her sister who you can tell she looks up to
is like the sort of wild child in the family.
Pushes her to partake in this hazing and go with it because if you don't, you're going to be an outcast at this school forever.
So she decides to go along with this crazy freshman hazing. And one of the things she has to do is eat a piece of raw meat.
I can't remember. It's an organ or a rabbit kidney. Yeah, rabbit kidney. She doesn't want to do it. She does it.
That's lighting the fuse to three scenes later where she's eating human flesh.
Yeah.
Doesn't take long.
It's a real off the rails kind of alcoholic as one drink and they're back at it again.
Yeah.
I mean, I dug that about it that it got right to the point.
And what I was saying with Joe that it was sort of a relief to me because I am a little
bit of a pussy with these horror movies.
And I had kept reading that people passed out at screenings of this movie, and they had
ambulances come to screens of this movie so people were passing out.
I can see that.
I got to tell you, I had no issues with it at all.
It's certainly an unsettling movie, but in terms of gore and all that, it was fun.
So there's a scene where things really start to turn, where her sister, which is a very
strange thing, but her sister's giving her a bikini wax, pretty up close and personal.
And at one point the tape catches and it's stuck on the pubic hair and she's trying to rip it off and keeps yanking on it
And I'm like here we go. Here's where something she's gonna rip off her vagina or something's gonna happen
And I was kind of like looking away. It doesn't go there. It goes to certainly strange places graphic places
But I would I'm just saying don't be terrified to watch the thing to me the hardest thing to watch was like her scratch and that
rash at the beginning that was disgusting couldn't take it hardly that was
disgusting and then the scene where she goes to the doc yet she has like this
breakout in massive highs for meeting the meat for some reason yeah and then
she goes to the doctor and the the hives are so severe the doctor has to
literally peel skin off of her and it looks very real yeah that was gross it's
gross that was gross it's really gross I texted pat at one point during the
movie and said literally every aspect of this movie is upsetting which is true
That's true. There is not a bright spot in the movie. No. You got the kid sister eating flesh. Yeah.
She accidentally, in the pubic hair scene, she accidentally cuts off her sister's finger, her sister passes out from the side of it.
She eats her sister's finger. Yeah. Blames it on the dog. Blames it on the dog. You then find out that the sister is also
a cannibal because, and here's what she does, she runs out in front of cars, so cars
swerve and crash and the people die, and then she goes and chews on their heads, like
as they're dying, why not dig up a corpse, you know, or like, because it's rotten, and
it would take so long.
I don't mean like a, I mean like a fresh corpse, but go to a funeral, that's, that's, no, this
is the best way to do it, if you're going to do it.
Well, I'm not going to do it.
Yeah, I'm just by the way why wasn't this movie called wait for it fine young cannibals. Oh boy. You made that joke yesterday too.
To you. I know. I'm just saying. I know when you recycle a bit. They don't. I know. I'm kidding. Come on. I'm breaking your
bo. Damn it. But it should have been called fine young cannibals. Um, because she dressed me. Uh, the only scene,
I mean, the only sex scene in this is between the younger sister and her gay roommate wild.
And even that ends in the gay roommate being like, I didn't hide for 20 years to fuck women
now.
Leave me alone.
Like, every part of the movie is upsetting.
Well, you're leaving out the sex scene of her like sniffing him and furiously fucking
him in the whole time.
Like, is she gonna eat him while fucking him?
And then she ends up biting her own arm to not eat him and making herself bleed
and the whole time he's telling her to stop and she won't stop.
She's like, she's like, got him pinned down
and he's going like, stop, please stop
because he knows something is wrong here.
This isn't right.
And then what's not right is she bites her own arm
until it bleeds.
Yes.
And so everything in the whole movie is like this.
There isn't one happy fucking moment in the whole thing.
That being said, it's a solid horror movie.
And I really respect the fact that France
or wherever it premiered, it was met with critical acclaim.
And I like that they can go dark like that over there on a big movie.
I mean over here it's, you know, Christ, it's the most polarizing film.
All that poor shit.
Right.
You know, I loved it.
I mean, I like foreign horror.
I liked, of course, let the right one in a lot.
It was the last one that kind of made a big splash like this.
that I could think of but you know the beauty of it too not one watch this thing I go this is
this is the plus of far and hard not one person is going well why are we rooting for this person
why do we like this for everybody is troubled from the fucking jump yeah this thing weirdly there's
a whole different critical critical viewpoint to foreign movies for some reason they you can tell
they review them differently. You feel smarter watching a foreign movie, so I'm sure that critics
are like, well, this is a horror movie, but it's smarter because it's French, sort of.
It is a smart movie, but it's just a really good, scary flick. It's gross, it's disturbing.
I wish more horror movies were like it. And also, it's logic makes sense, which is real
rare in a horror movie. You know, like, what they explained to you all makes sense. Then
when you think about it after it's over, you're like, okay, you know, the parents, she got
That's so mad about the little piece of meat being in her meal in the opening scene.
Remember the mom grabs the thing out.
That's a really cool way to open it.
It makes you think back and go, okay, that her parents went to that school is very cool.
The final scene where the father reveals that the mom is this way but they make it work.
Right.
I thought was an awesome ending to it.
I just, I loved the move.
I really did.
That was great.
Yeah.
I thought that was great.
I also really liked, no, I thought yeah, the ending was great.
Now I thought I was positive.
It was, we were diving through so many levels of sadness and depravity at one point.
I was like, there's no way these sisters aren't boned by the end of this picture.
I thought that's where it was headed.
I'd squirted God, I'm not, I'm not trying to be crass, I thought that's where it was headed.
I was like, this is going to, and then when at the end, the crazier sister eats the gay
roommate that she, the younger sister, it's up with, she takes her in the shower to clean
her off.
And I was like, this is probably going to be it.
I think they're going to like great, but on that older sister, by the way, great, but on
that older sister, uh, they both had, they both had shining bodies in different ways.
I thought, uh, but it didn't go there.
So I was, you know, I was actually relieved that it didn't, uh, to, to me, the most sort
of, uh, just unsettling miserable scene was when the, the gay roommate shows her the video
of her sister taunting her with that corpse and her,
like, kept jumping up at it when she's on the floor.
And everybody's like, stop filming it.
She's drunk.
I was like, Jesus Christ.
That was a lot for me to watch for some reason it.
Even though it was not gory in any way,
I was just like, this is sick.
Well, it was unsaddling.
Yeah, unsaddling.
But it's a good picture.
And overall, two hogs up from the hog house.
A lot of criticism on the hog house.
People people are I think have turned against it, but they don't they don't care for it
It's still going something something like it, but people like the uncut thick dick house
Oh, no, they don't like either. Oh, okay. Okay. No all right. I think one guy referred to it as crass
I was like if you listen to this fucking show crass. Yeah, I mean it is, but that's all we that's what we do
Yeah, anyway folks that's our show stay tuned next week is gonna be a black mirror
Yeah, I guess this one will come out first.
Sure, sure.
That's how it's gonna be.
All right, so Black Mirror,
we're gonna do the first three episodes, correct?
Yes, and season four.
Yeah, and it's on Netflix.
This comes out Monday, so this coming weekend,
I'll be in Vegas with Bobby Slate and his friends
at the, what's the place called the Star Dust?
No, you told me, I told you where it was.
South Point, the South Point Casino, it's off strip.
And folks, I'm not going to make any big promises, but if you do come to the show, there's a chance you might see one pat
Walsh.
Folks, I'm not going to make any promises either, but I'd put that chance at about 90%.
So I'm not going to perform, but I'll be there.
They're going to be in Vegas, hopefully, together having some fun.
Come out to the show if you live there, say hello, have a drink.
I'll also be headlining Gotham Comedy Club, the weekend of the 16th in New York City.
Come on out, say hello. Let's have some fun. And that following week, I'll be performing
at the Patrice O 'Neill Benefit. Nice. I think it's the 10th or 11th anniversary. It's been
going for quite some time. But that's going to be a really great show too. It's Sam, Sam
Jay is on it, and I'm on it, and Brendan Burns from England is coming in, and I think Robert
Kelly's on it, Rich Voss. It's going to be a lot of fun. Of course, Bill Burr. It'll be
great time. So anyway, that's that's that. I'm at the Patrick Walsh Twitter
Instagram. We'll see you next week and we'll see you in hell. That was a