Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal, durable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
Gambling problem, call 1 -800 -Gamber.
Firestone Complete Auto Care's epic savings advantage is the sign you need to stop putting off your car's maintenance.
And you can save up to $100 on tires and services while you're at it.
Don't wait, call Firestone Complete Auto Care for an appointment.
This is a headgun podcast.
Hey howdy folks, you know what time it is, I don't need to fucking tell you what time
it is, you know what fucking time it is, it's time for this fucking podcast to start.
All right. We'll see you in hell. Are you sons of bitches ready to laugh in a podcast setting?
You sons of bitch bastards. That's that what you want. Is that what you want? You want you look fucks?
Hopefully say like James get all feeding. Is that what you need AJ? Come Ella
Yeah, gotta do folks have breathing of course. Yeah, great loss great actor great man. I love him
Folks, I wanted to talk to you about
Getting on with the show
And also I'd like to boy. I can't even think of one. Let me think oh Jesus Pat
What did it come on? I wasn't ready. You bailed that that that moment you bail well
I can't just start singing a song maybe you have a little preparation
No, we're on wait Pat till you're ready and let's get on with the Joe
Wow
Real fuck you to everybody. It's got all with the Joe
Anyway
Okay, folks, today we're talking about season four of Black Mirror, the arcade fire band
sang about it, which I assumed came before the show, remember that song?
Black Mirror.
Yeah, I've always been touch and go with arcade fire, like they're pretty good, but I don't
go out of my way.
Not their best song.
The chorus is black mural.
I really like almost like a Dracula voice.
It's stupid.
Now, Pinkstone, our dear friend, his interpretation
of that title is it's the black mirror.
It's your phone.
It's your computer screen.
When those are in rest mode, he goes, those are the black mirror.
You can see your reflection in it.
I could see that.
That's about technology.
I thought it was a pretty insightful take on it.
And I can't imagine what the hell else it would mean.
Well, I might just come from that song. I don't know what that song is about. I just know that it goes black
mirror.
You know, they're one of these bands where I'm like, do we need you guys around again?
Haven't you put out enough?
I really love their first album and then I just kind of get further and further away with each additional album.
But remember when I worked at Colonial Brian, they were there and they had not...
They're out mad and even come out yet.
There was 15 people on stage.
They were all wearing helmets
and they're playing each other's heads like drums.
And I was like, what the fuck am I looking at?
Yeah.
That energy seems to have gone away from arcade fire.
That's not who they are anymore.
It always bothers me at the end of return of the Jedi.
The Ewoks do that with the Stormtrooper helmets.
Yeah, that's stupid one.
I'm like, what is this?
What are you guys doing?
Yeah.
These were like the meanest people in the galaxy.
see. I thought that should have gone like from a little mermaid. I never saw the
under the sea. Never saw a little mermaid. No, I've never seen most Disney films.
Okay, Lion King. Never saw it. Holy shit. Literally could not have less interest in
seeing a Disney animated film. The only ones I caught on animation guy either. But I've
seen them all because I was a kid. I mean, as a kid, I even knew I was too tough for that
Bullshit. Yeah, I always preferred like, you know, a PG comedy to like, you know, some cartoon.
The only ones I ever had interest in are the ones that have like witches in them. Like sleeping beauty.
You always look kind of cool to me or Cinderella. Yeah, not Cinderella. Snow White has a witch. Sure.
Those are the ones I kind of like, but, but anything else that old, old animations kind of,
kind of beautiful. It's beautiful to look at. Yeah. I do want to get a blu -ray of Fantasia for that reason.
I have Blu -ray a Fantasia that has remained unopened for years.
It's Fantasia 2000, any good?
It's on the same Blu -ray.
Yeah, is it?
Let's get baked one day and watch them.
Maybe we do an episode.
You guys want to hear that?
No, seriously.
You guys want to hear an episode of this podcast?
We review Fantasia versus Fantasia 2000.
I don't know.
Do we start our new podcast?
That's just Fantasia.
Minute by minute.
The Fantasia, boys.
I have a great idea for an activity for us.
What?
And it might be something we add to the Patreon when we also add the buffet thing, which
people have been asking about by the way.
It's called Ready for This.
Yes.
It's called Achiba.
And it means we smoke Chiba.
They go to Amoeba.
That's just a great, that's just a great on a Saturday morning.
Hey, you feel like you feel like an Achieba today?
But then what do we record it live in store, the like in the loudest store in America?
I'm saying this is just for me and you to do, this is just the name for our new activity.
Look, I'll Achieba, it doesn't have to be Saturday, I'll say that much, we can do whatever
you want.
And I'm saying maybe if people sound excited about it, one of the things you can purchase
his weak smoke weed with you and walk around the movie section of of a meburet I'd be
down with that. And as I desperately try to not have a pub panic attack in public, I must
admit, a dream of mine is to do one of those what's in your bags for me too. They just had
Camille and Emily do one. I would love to and I'll never be asked, but you know, I'm dying
to do one. What do you got to do to get it fucking what's in my bag? I mean, you know, Jake
Fogalness did one. I'm as you know I'm I'm more special than that guy does. Yes, that's true
Why can't I get a fucking what's in my bag? I mean, I know I'm not getting nominated for Oscars over here
But can I get a what's in my bag?
Folks, yeah, so we're talking about the first three episodes of season four today
You get it you understand Joe. What's new in your life? What's happening?
Well, I was talking on the last episode how I went to that video game convention
I got some new video game stuff that I'm always excited to get.
I love collecting these old video games, so I got a Sega CDX, which is a hard console
to come by, and especially for the price I got it for, and it's a combo of the Sega
Genesis and the Sega CD, it's like a very compact version, so it's cool, I got Dragon's
Lair for it.
The game youth thought they made up for things.
things. I got a port of that and it is as fucking hard as I remembered it as
hard as they make it look in that in that TV show. It's so hard. But you know I've
been enjoying wine lately. Right. A crisp white as we also talked about last time.
Yeah. What do you have that's new to talk about? Because people already heard the
other stuff that you just said on the other podcast. I mean what what is new? We
recorded it the other one an hour ago. You don't have to tell them this. Yeah,
that what doesn't matter.
Nobody cares.
You gotta act like it's a new day.
A new dawn.
I watch the Raw 25th anniversary
with our dear friend Vince Avril.
Okay.
I can talk about that during Pat's movie corner
if you want.
Sure.
There's nothing new.
It's the same old, you know,
working, living, hustling.
Yeah.
You know, I was, here's how excited
my week's been.
I'll tell you this to me.
I was driving down the street today.
You know how Indian food they have,
but basamati rice or basamati rice?
I don't really eat Indian foods, who know?
I mean, whatever, like most places they have white rice,
brown rice, Indian restaurants for some reason
they have basamati rice.
Now, what does that mean?
It's just a different grain of rice.
It's like a, it's a little longer, I guess.
Okay.
So, for whatever reason I'm away over here,
I got this happens to you once in a while in L .A.
where like a giant truck will make a turn and you just sit there staring at it like there's no way
this thing is gonna hit me it happens with buses all the time right and they barely pull it out
at the last second so I'm sitting there staring at this truck wincing like this truck is 100 % gonna hit
me and it rounds the corner bear like our mirrors probably brushed up against each other our black mirrors
and it starts past me and I'm reading this sign and I'm like what is this giant fucking truck
And I watch as this thing goes down the road, and here's what it says on the side of it.
Some company, Bassapni rice.
The longest Bassamti rice in America, they're advertising this on the on a giant truck
that they have the longest grains of rice.
Right, right.
Who gives a fuck, Joe?
Why would you advertise how long your rice is?
I think it's a, you know, a phallic kind of thing.
Maybe.
It's a subconscious.
Well, I don't know.
I mean, I guess that's, I guess if you like that kind of rice and it's not long, you're
like, this is bullshit.
But just eat more of it.
I mean, look, when you put rice in your mouth, you're not eating it grain by grain anyway.
If I got, well, there's a texture that the length can add to it, obviously, or affect
And I would say this if I was eating white rice and they were cut in half, I'd be like this is weird
I don't like this weird small rice. I need a big rice.
I didn't expect you to be on the side of this truck, but but so bad.
I think it's a sexual thing. I really do. Everything in advertising is sex and I think that's so weirdly
We got the longest rice. Right. You know what I mean? Well, a woman was
pushing the rice into her body and I ain't talking about the mouth. Folks I also
would like to say that I am doing my yearly cleanse and I have a lot of fun
for all of us this week's a lot of fun where Pat doesn't do anything except
drink lemon juice with peppers in it not peppers it's cayenne pepper yeah you
can't fucking can't eat anything can't drink anything comes and hangs out for
30 minutes leaves, I've been entirely pleasant. I've been funny. I've been delightful. I don't like
that you're doing something good for yourself. You do. You get mad. Joe gets mad if you if you're
not going to have that 12th drink, he gets mad at you. You're my partner. I don't know what else to do.
I know. You are my partner. You're my hetero life mate as they say in J and silent Bob.
I'm verging on Homo, sometimes purging, fully bleeding into Homo, emphasis on fully
bleeding.
You know, so when I can't meet you and soak over a few drinks in the cesspool that we've
chosen to take up our lives in, it's hard.
I understand that.
It's also, I know you've never thought about this, hard for me to not eat or drink anything
for a week.
It's not natural.
You're not supposed to do this to yourself, but I do it and it's it's a nice little reset for me
And there comes a point always around the holidays where I'm like
Just fucking give me that 18th drink. Let's get let me get high at noon
Let you know just everything and and you don't care and this
Gets me back on track. It's something I like to do. Can I it helps me think clear and everything else
And I tell you that I do that same thing at the holidays and you know what I do to fix it?
I just stop eating whatever I feel like and drinking the 18th drink.
I'm just like, all right, if you cut these things out and live a little more responsibly,
you'll lose weight and you do.
Sure, but I do this.
All right.
And different strokes.
You can eat salads, you know?
And I do.
Not on this, you don't.
No, I eat nothing.
You eat nothing.
That's right.
So what is in this concoction that you drink?
It is, it's what you said.
It's lemon juice and cayenne pepper.
That's it, just those two things.
And then what you're supposed to do is maple syrup,
I found that disgusting, like organic maple syrup.
So I do one from a health place here in town.
They do it up to like 30 day cleanses,
which would kill people.
And you just drink it out of this bottle?
Drink it out of the bottle, and it's raw cane.
So raw sugar cane is what makes you feel fulfilled,
I guess, but it's not like sugar.
It's it's the plant. Okay, is it the only juice is the lemon juice? There's that it's not like diluted with water or anything
I mix with water it tastes too bad to do it otherwise because the cayenne is nauseating
But then the part that often gets lost that truly the worst part is
That then you drink this all day you drink a quart of it
then
At night you drink a laxative tea
smooth -moved tea
it's called smooth move. That's correct. Jesus Christ. Then you wake up sort of
crampion uncomfortable and you drink a quart 32 ounces of lukewarm salt water
which is nearly impossible to get down and then within minutes you blast out
your ass. For about a half hour, you know, on and off. Today I was running some business
calls while taking care of business. And then you feel great, light, better. I honestly
haven't really felt hungry on it, but the weird thing is, and it's true, and it's immediate.
My girlfriend was watching TV upstairs last night. She watches it all the time when I'm downstairs
and I can't hear it. I heard every word as clear as if I was on the couch. The smells are
crazy. She was cooking dinner. I had to immediately come over here because it makes you, it's like
raw. We talked about last week your ravenous and hungry. And you know, you smell, you like the fruit
loops, you know, parrot like it trails to your nose. Your senses are heightened. For some reason I like
to do it. It makes you, by the end of it, your face looks clear, your hair is like fluffy,
and then you're done with it. And I like, because I was raised Catholic, I like torturing
myself. But then you just go back to your lifestyle the next day.
I don't know. I do a special green drink that gets you off it, chlorophyll, and then I do
a day or two of orange juice and then I work into just orange juice right usually a day
of orange juice and then I ease into you know vegetables, fruits, salads and back on then
you're then I'm just eating healthier again you know I mean I'm doing better all right
what is one of these cleanses cost can I ask on air is that tacky no it's fine I got the
seven day plus the green drink at the end plus the smooth move it winds up yeah well they
to give you the tea and the salt and all that.
Which is literally named after smooth move x -lacks
when you used to say that as a kid.
Remember that?
Yeah, correct.
So they ain't literally named it like the shit tea.
They're telling you this.
Oh, it's unquestionably shit tea.
And then, you know, I think it amounts to about $10 a day.
If you went and bought lemon's cayenne pepper
and all this shit which I used to do,
I've been doing this for 10 years.
You chop it all up and then you got your drinking seeds
And it makes it so much more miserable to do about 10 bucks a day
It's 10 bucks a day. You'd spend more than that if you're eating solids. Of course you would I could tell you that much
Yeah
Well, Pat if that didn't constitute for a scary stuff. I don't know what does
Sounds fucking horrifying to me. Yeah
Yeah, I have no stories like that. I've been out and about I've been taking long walks no strange encounters of any kind sure
know, no confrontations, you know, just nice leisurely days of light work and enjoying
myself. I'm happy to hear it. You get bored? Yeah. Yeah. Life, I've learned this now that
I'm done with work for the, it's life's very, very boring. Yeah. It's, it's, I'll take,
I'll take two mile walks at a clip, not even hikes just walks through like the neighborhood
It's just to see people and be around activity and listen to music and I'll write while I'm walking and do it all the time
Yeah, it's like you know, but uh, in a way that's boring too
I like it because you're moving around, but yeah, I mean, it's not you know, it's not gonna
Not just soft stuff
I got on my treadmill twice yesterday, okay, or my
yeah, elliptical, excuse me, because I was like,
yeah, why not?
I'm trying to build it up.
I got this elliptical, that's like,
it's like a part elliptical, part like stair step thing.
Sort of a hybrid.
It's just really fucking hard to do,
because it's not long strokes with the feet.
It's more like up down.
So the first time I did it, I couldn't get through 10 minutes.
The second time I did it, I could get to 10 minutes,
but I had to take breaks.
Finally did it where I was able to get
through a full 10 minute straight. So I just got to get that up to, if I can get that
up to 20 minutes and do that every day, I'm fucking gold. I'm gold. But I got to get,
I got to get there, though. Folks, I apologize for the content of this, this week's podcast.
What's wrong? I mean, we're both talking about the healthy choices we're making in the new
year. It's, where it's a mommy blog, essentially. What's wrong with mom or daddy blog? There you go.
There you go. What are you looking at your phone for? I was going to rate it take us to Pat's movie
corner. Alright, let's drift on over to the other side. How long? How long? I'll strive.
Separate. There is an album right there. California case. Yeah. You want to talk about an album
that I, when it came out, I loved it. And now when I hear any song from it, it disgusts
me. Even at the time. Cheesy. Even at the time I was a little anti -red,
actually papers, but I was like, I gotta admit, these are some good songs. And the follow -up to it
has some good songs, some pretty songs. But I feel the exact same way. Like, you hear that with
this song, it's like, do do do do do do do do do do. I'm like, give me a fucking break. Yeah.
Or round the world. Yeah. The last time I went to Coachella, they started up, and of course,
of course, they were big there. And you know, the bass thing starts up, and then I turned to Heather,
there. I was like, let's get the fuck out of here. We did. When saw New Order, there
was like 40 people there. Yeah. One of the best shows I've ever seen. You got a new
order. Yeah. But that new order followed by pet shop boys. Oh, that's great. Yeah. Yeah.
I'm driving around the other day, listening to serious XM and I, you know, the grunge
station, whatever it's called, you know, fortified or whatever. I don't know. I'm fucking
whatever title it's got. Right. In bloom or something. And then the, the, the song
californication comes on yeah it's just so that song is
damn terrible californication dream of california
the um he also is so crazily auto tuned he's
be beyond t -pane like yeah he them live
i've seen them a couple times they tour with the food fighters once or
something his voice is so
horrible and he doesn't play an instrument
Yeah, no, he just sings literally what are you bringing the worst they did a there was a thing on Netflix for a while
Where you could see this tribute concert to Joey Ramone?
Uh -huh. No to Johnny Ramone. Excuse me. Uh -huh. So all these bands came up played
Ramones covers and all of them were like bands you'd hang your hat on except the red hot chili peppers were there
And you could kind of I got the feeling that everybody was like what the fuck are these guys doing here?
It's like if you're having like a comedy like a basement comedy show and like John mayor shows up
I mean, like, yeah, right, buddy, you know, but, uh, anyway,
we'll tweet from it. She, yeah, so I heard.
So anyway, she, uh, but they open with what I want to be
sedated. And it's, I mean, just picture this. It's Anthony
any kid is going, 24, 24 hours ago.
I want to be so dead.
It was fucking terrible.
I've seen this.
Was there a pro jam there?
Pro jam?
You're precious.
Yeah, I've seen this.
I believe my precious pro jam he says, you know, come on.
Joe, by the way, last night,
raving about Stone Temple Pilots number four.
It's a good album.
It's an album.
My die hard Stone Temple Pilot friends from high school
used to squat over and shit on any chance they got it.
It's a good album.
It's it's the last good album they put out the last two are terrible. You like sour girl
Yeah, that's how it goes. It's good. It's creeper any one of those fucking songs. It isn't all right
Well, I like it. It sounds like a follow -up to core. I like cool. I like that look
Here's my problem with tiny music your precious fucking tiny music album great album
He sings like such a fucking pussy through the entire album. It's annoying. It's annoying that he does that voice
where he's going. It sounds like Cartman. It's annoying. Right. Well, I think his voice is
probably shredded from heroin. No, he's trying to do like some of the voice. He's trying
to do like a T -Rexy glam rock thing. And I like the glam rock aspect of that album, but I
don't like the way he sings. And I like that on number four. He's back on. I got a
Scott Wyland again. Now we can agree though that even though Anthony Ketus is a bad rapper, he is
perhaps our best rapper. Anthony Ketus. Did I say rapper twice? Yeah, you did. God damn it!
Bad singer, perhaps our best rapper. Perhaps our best rapper. I only put him below the guy from corn.
The fieldie, John of the day. Well, corn makes the chili peppers look like the fucking Beatles.
I mean seriously yeah I know corn is a and and and limb biscuit makes corn look like the stones. Yeah, I mean Jesus Christ. Yeah. Yeah, no that's
I mean we're not sure the peppers knew how to write a fucking catchy song don't get me wrong, but it's the stuff that that ages
Particularly badly is like the
He's terrible. I never liked it when blood sugar sex magic came out and all my friends were like this album's amazing
It's a game changer.
I was like, no, it's not.
It's white boy bullshit.
It is.
It's white guys mimicking black music in a shitty way, fuck this album.
It sucks.
Suck my kiss is a pretty good tune.
One of my least favorite of theirs.
Give it away.
I don't give a shit.
Under the bridge, please let me never hear that song for the rest of my fucking days.
It's like Van Morrison shit.
It's like, okay, they're fine songs.
I never want to hear them though.
Do you ever want to do ever go out and go and go to a jukebox and go, you know, I'm gonna put in moon dance
No, no, that's never happened. No
Well, it's a marvelous night for a moon dance
Well, that's all my parents fucking listen to is Van Morrison, so I've had my fill
Well, and there are kids out there now. They're like all my parents. Let's do it the chili peppers
That's some poor bastard is sitting in his dad's house right now and his dad's telling them the chili peppers
are a great band.
I was in a record store at Christmas time.
Okay.
The King of Pressure Mall in King of Pressure, Pennsylvania,
which is the town next to where I grew up.
And this was my mall growing up.
It was one of the biggest malls in the country.
It's a great mall.
We went in, Pinkstone and his lovely wife, Jess.
And I went in for a,
gone Christmas Eve.
It's a tradition.
We go there.
It's the mall at Christmas.
It's fun.
And we just kind of window shop.
And they're low and behold.
There's a record store now at the King of Precious Plaza.
I'm flipping out, Jim Sullivan out, I'm like,
do you realize we haven't seen a record store in here
since Sam Goodie?
Right.
Like, this is awesome.
There's vinyl or what?
Vinyl and CDs, but mostly vinyl, of course,
because it's, you know, the...
Wow, that's crazy.
Awesome store.
Yeah.
Awesome.
I got my favorite Sinatra album ever,
which is the Sinatra and Antonio Carlos Jobim,
like Boston over records. Most romantic record ever heard. I got a copy of it sealed. It's never been
played. Original pressing. I got an original colored vinyl of living color times up, which is my
favorite living color album sealed. It was a great store. I can't remember the name of it of course,
but it's a great store and I will be back. But anyway, I'm in there and it's real busy and I'm like,
this is great man these guys open a record store it's in this mall which you
wouldn't expect it's busy people are appreciating art this is great and then
a guy next to me he goes I look over he's holding Dave Matthew's band
before these crowded streets on vinyl which look it's not a terrible album it's
not when you go I got to go get that on vinyl one of my proudest things is
is that I avoided getting into that world.
I was 17, I was like, you guys are all fucking stupid.
And he's discussing with the clerk, bro.
Like, where can I get, but where can I get crash on vinyl?
Right.
Like, I think we might have it at our other store
and I was like, I guess there's a guy out there
that's like, I need to own Dave Matthews on vinyl.
Hey bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo bo
I gotta tell you, the crowd of the Red Outchlee Pepper Show,
I walked in, I was like, oh, I'm going to be beaten to death here.
I'm gonna make a bet.
I'm gonna bet right now that the whitest place
you could be on Planet Earth is the finale show
of the fish run at Madison Square Garden.
I don't think there's any wider place on Planet Earth
that you could ever be.
Probably not.
Aside from the opening show of a Dave Matthews run,
probably not at the San Francisco Fairgrounds.
They're playing well they have that one black guy in the band though. So at least there's a matter
It's I think he'd like to experience the one black. I did the black other black guys the drummer. He's still in it
Okay, the guy that played
Like violin sure or something like that yeah, saxophone. Yeah, I don't even see any band any rock band with a fucking violin or a saxophonetic
Fields who are incredible, but that's not rock music
Anyway, anyway elephant in the room. I sneezed there
And there was no bless you when you didn't even notice did you I didn't I was real
Wap wrapped up in this discussion we were having okay, we got bless you wouldn't
I hate it a bless you as long as I bless you
Did you ever own a Dave Matthews album? Yeah, I own the for not the first the first the first famous one with ants marching
What is the song ants marching? Oh god damn damn
I had that cassette, hey, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
these are all bad so I'll give you a satellite my friend Dan insisted
we were college that the lyrics were sample nine and he would sing it to me
sample nine yeah you would do that when we were like high and drunk and it was
for some reason one of the funniest things that I've ever experienced that was
and then my friend Brian English who was one of the funniest people I've ever
known used to insist he used to rewrite all the lyrics to the to the system of a down
songs. So for the one. Yeah, the wake up. He said that it was a way. He was like, I love
that song. He goes, he would go is wake up. Jopsy. Why'd you put the ketchup on the table?
Uh huh. So you'd say that was like that. And then the song, uh, uh, toxicity. He would
You go dude, what do you want in the reg?
Yeah, that's funny.
And it would just fucking kill me.
It would just kill me.
I used to, when I was super into Weird Al in grade school, like nine years old, I would
write parodies of the songs of the day.
My biggest hit, of course, being losing my pet pigeon.
Oh, boy.
I was nine.
Not bad.
Nine.
You would have a good dog.
If a nine year old was in here and now you'd be like, hey buddy, that's how young I was.
That's good.
All right, let's get to this movie corner.
I only have one for this week.
I want to talk folks about a movie I saw last night that I think is a fucking masterpiece.
And I guess I probably saw it years and years and years and years.
I must have seen it.
I know I saw it.
But it was like watching for the first time.
Owning Mahoney.
Phil Seymour Hoff.
Are you looking for it?
Oh, you're just off mic.
Like, okay, I thought it was a goddamn masterpiece.
And the best movie about gambling ever made.
People just, it's a rounders or whatever.
Rounders is one of the most unrealistic movies
about gambling ever made.
Yeah, it's almost all made by people
who don't understand the game.
Also too, I mean, look, I love Malcolm Vitch,
but Jesus Christ, he's absurd in rounders.
He's absurd, it's absurd after a while.
Have you seen Oning Mahoney, Joe?
No, I just heard it's so sad
I was like I don't I don't know if I can take it. Oh my God. I mean, it's depressing. It's hell
But it's the only true. I think it I think it got me off gambling
I've had a tremendous amount of luck with gambling
But I recognize in myself the potential to be a gambling addict to be a mohoney. I tell you
Well, it's it's one of those in our office best performances his girlfriend is many driver which
She's great at it as well.
She's in rounders too, isn't she?
She isn't rounders too.
I mean, the sequel to rounders, rounders too.
They've talked about making a sequel to rounders.
About what?
What would it even be about?
They're playing poker, but they're older now.
Anyway, if you haven't seen Oni Mahoney, it is certainly depressing and I don't know if
it's going to appeal to somebody who's not as into gambling as I am.
I was blown away to the extent that I looked up the screenwriter, the man's never done anything
since.
I looked up the director, never done anything since.
And I looked it up. They had a $10 million budget. It made less than a million dollars. So those guys are out of the business
But they made a fucking incredible
movie. It's so good and
I just why just I'm not even gonna talk about anymore watch the movie if you haven't seen it. It's a fantastic movie
My only one for this week is a little mini series called the Langle Lears
Wow, Stephen King's the Langle Lears watch all four hours of this thing. I watched all four hours
I saw it on TV back in the day when I was a kid
I bought a three -pack at Walmart when I was home over Christmas.
It's the stand.
Don't give Walmart money.
This is why.
Read an article.
I've read it.
Is there any store that's not your iPhone was made in a sweatshop?
It's like, what are you going to do?
Almost any store other than Walmart is going to be better for this country than Walmart.
Walmart employs a lot of people.
Joe, I can't get into this with you.
Well, what, what, what, what, what, what?
Well, tell me, school me on this, right?
Well, it is true.
They're in the news right now.
What do they do now for?
I almost sent you this article
because I was like, look at, look at, look at,
look at what they did so I know.
Well, tons of these employees,
they's great employees that you speak of
who make less than they would at any other store.
No health benefits, by the way.
They show up to their job and there's a closed sign
on the, they didn't tell me one.
They were closing it.
All right, all right.
You're making some good points.
Stuff happens all the time.
But Walmart, Walmart's business mission statement is move into an area where there's lots of small businesses doing well and crush them.
That's their model. Okay. All right. You convinced me. I won't buy anything at Walmart anymore. Please don't. I mean, I could I could talk for hours about Walmart.
They especially in Missouri. They I've never seen a Walmart in California. Maybe that's a second podcast.
Yes. Fuck, Walmart.
Listen, don't shout there, guys.
All right, sorry, whole year than thou.
That was to the guys, that wasn't to you.
I was at Target, OK, and I bought this three -packed of TV.
It was the stand, the Langoliers, and the Golden Years.
Golden Years, I haven't watched yet.
Why?
Someone I was a kid.
Don't remember anything about it.
Well, you might ask, why, Joe, why do you
watch the first two and not the third thing because guys the langleyers
this pains me to say because Tom Holland directed and I love Tom Holland
it was so fucking bad
it also starts bronson pinch show
there's two reasons for me like this movie right out of the gate to be a
roller
no okay
he plays the bad guy actually
uh... and this
it starts fairly interesting the premises you know
you know, these people pass out on the plane, they wake up and they're in an alternate
reality.
Everybody else has disappeared.
They don't know what's going on.
It's interesting, but I mean, my God Almighty, this thing just drags and drags and drags.
It's not very well acted.
It's not visually pleasing.
And it came out at that time when special effects on made for TV movies were just unacceptable.
Like, it's got like CGI monsters that come that are the Langle Lears and like, it just
looks so ridiculous that you can't, you can't care, it's just terrible special effect.
But I sat through it, not a good king adaptation and not one, quite frankly, not one I think
they should have even made.
I don't get why they pick this story as a, as a, as a, as a, as a, as a, to, to do a mini
series.
It's just not a good it's not a good enough story. It's an interesting idea short story, huh? I believe so
Tommy knockers
No, I've never seen the Tommy knockers. I thought I would either
But I will watch gold nears eventually, but that the Langoliers left such a stain on me
I was like I got to give this this set of break
And somebody one of the fans actually wrote to me and said why don't you do the Langoliers so somebody that you love from
and proper strangers in it.
Quincidentally, I got that just as I was watching this.
So yeah, it's not great.
All right, did you like the stand many series?
It's okay, it's good enough, I like it.
The story doesn't,
there's nothing wrong with the mini series.
I just don't find that story very captivating.
Like I've never been a big post -apocalyptic guy.
But for that story, it's good, it's well done.
You know what, Bronson Pincho is great in his risky business.
Who's he play?
Plays Tom Cruise's nerd friend.
He's great in a true romance.
He is great true romance, but like I assume risky business
would have been one of his first things.
He just like plays such a realistic like high school nerd
in a, no glasses, no tape on the pocket protector
and all that shit.
He's great in a, and when I was really blown away
by with risky business, which became one of my favorite movies. I had seen it 20 years
ago, but Tom Cruise, like, I don't know, there's ever been a better performance from Cruise
and he's like 20. Yeah, he's very good. He's so great in that movie and he's kind of playing
a dork, which is weird. He's a great actor, man. You know, we can all say what we will about
the Scientology stuff. He's just a good, but he's a great actor. Yeah. The guy he was meant
to be a movie star. And your favorite Mr. Beckon de Mourne completely nude. She's not my favorite,
but I'll take it. On one of the early episodes of the show, you talked about how you dreamed of
starting a life with Rebecca de Mourne. I don't think that's true. Well, we can go to the audio tape.
Let's go to the fans. Guys, if you know what Pat's talking about, send us the transcription. I know
they will know because I think they've talked about it and the thing, but I mean, she's a hot lady.
I just I wouldn't say she's my favorite you had like looked up to see who she was married to it got pretty deep
So you must know I do remember do that because she's in the stand made for TV move
I mean, I mean the the shining made for TV movie. Oh, okay, and I was like what happened to this lady
Well, she's fucking great and hand the rocks a cradle. I know that much. Yeah, she's fucking great in risky business
I was I was blown away by risky business. I saw some I'm gonna just only watch older movies from now on
I think it's a good movie. They're better. Well, yeah
a couple quick picks, trapped in paradise.
Do you wanna talk about an old movie
that is not a Harvey movie?
You know, I was buying up some Christmas movies
at like a dollar a pop on Amazon,
and I was like, I don't know if I ever saw this.
Harvey, Nicholas Cage, and John Lovitz.
That's good.
It's awful.
It was a huge box office bomb.
But folks, I bought it for $3.
It went out of print two weeks later,
And I sold it for $60.
I felt real good about that, but the movie is unwatchable.
It's terrible.
Don't check it out.
I saw Donald Cride, which is streaming on Netflix, great movie in the Chuck and Buck
Vane.
Okay.
Guy goes home, reconnects with an old friend.
He's very strange.
It's an uncomfortable comedy.
I liked it quite a bit.
I recommend it.
Get me Roger Stone, documentary about Trump's kind of key advisor, fascinating look at what
is going on in American politics and how they pulled off this win and it's it's so frustrated
because their whole strategy is like let's do things on the absolute line of legality
right and it completely worked like you watch it and you're like as much as I hate everything
this man stands for he's a genius okay it's depressing as well but I urge you to check
it out Valerian lost planet yeah somebody in the Facebook page referred to it as his favorite
movie of the year. Uh, folks, this is one of the worst things I've ever seen in my life.
Look terrible. Absolutely terrible. It looked terrible. And they keep giving that kid shots.
They keep giving the kid shots. Well, I guess Luke Passon finally came back with that Lucy movie,
but they keep giving Passon shots. I mean, Jesus Christ. It's like that kids, they just, they're like,
he's going to star in movies now. It's like, why? That lead couple in this move. I mean, I almost
don't remember watching it. I watched it three weeks ago. That's all I want to say about Valeria.
Don't watch it. I don't know if I talked about Coco on here. Beautiful movie. Beautiful
Pixar movie. I don't like cartoons. My era with stories. Sandler. You talked about that already.
Saw it out. Hounds of love. We're going to do that on this show or not. I don't know, but why don't
we cool it on the movie corner? Because you're barreling and I don't know. I'm getting confused as to
which you you've definitely mentioned. That's why I'm checking them off. I don't I don't remember if
If we did this one or not, but do you want to do
howons of love on the show as well?
I don't know what howons of love is.
I've never talked about it, but I did text you about it.
Should we do it for the show?
It's a sick horror movie that's on Hulu.
Oh, no, let's do it for the show.
All right.
Folks, if you got Hulu, watch howons of love.
It's also very disturbing, but we'll do that
in the near future.
Is it about dogs or something?
No.
It's about a couple in Australia who kidnaps
and tortures young girls.
Now let's not do that on the show. I need a I need a little breath from torturing it. All right
Well, that'll be my last one then. If you did you like it? I
Absolutely loved it and the guy that directed it will be directing I'd like to say great movies in the next few years
But let's be real he'll be directing fucking Marvel movies in the next few years because that's the the career path now for people with vision and talent
How's the love is based on a sad true story about a husband and wife in Australia who
would drive around because the wife was in the car.
They're like, yeah, I'll take a ride, you know, bring them back to the house.
They tie them to the bed there.
The husband, they seem to have an arrangement where if you're going to do something tour,
We both got to be there, but the husband keeps kind of slipping in on his own right you never you don't see anything
I want to make that clear because this movie will be very triggering for some it is a very upsetting
But they don't show you stuff really and
While it is very disturbing. I would put it on a on a par with like our movie from last week raw
It's very unsettling very disturbing, but at the end you're just like god damn like it's it's very exciting very suspenseful
All right, and for some reason it's on fucking Hulu, which Hulu I always view as being like a family place
Yeah, they throw some weird shit on there. It was it was a very depraved and excellent movie and and as far from a direction directing standpoint
I think really an interesting movie
All right, well, I'll check it out after I haven't seen so many like eating flesh and torture things recently
Sure
I don't have a scary stuff for this week unless you do now
Now let's get into our topic, Black Mirror season four, episodes one through three.
Let's go through them one by one.
The first one, most people know as basically the Star Trek one with Jesse Plemons, also
known as Fat Damon.
I mean, and now he goes shirtless in this thing.
But he makes them shoot him from like 30 miles away.
Yeah, but you do see that the man is a chubby man.
And he's...
him in briefs at his fattest in the Fargo show. And I mean, the guy's like, he's going
out with one of the most beautiful women that's ever walked the earth. They're married
and he's impregnated. There's, to me, there's no one more attractive than Dunst. And I admire
the man. I really, I saw him making out at drunk history party. I admire her for not being
all about, you know, for being about a normal dude. He's a good, a great actor. Look, not
everybody goes just by looks you know. Yeah but you do and you've said it repeatedly. It's not
true. No it's not true. This one is called USS Callister season four episode one. So yeah
Jesse Plemons plays basically a kind of disturbed VR designer who creates sort of a fantasy world where
he's basically the captain of the ship of his favorite Star Trek like show.
And in doing so, lines up kind of like trying to control and dominate the people in the thing,
including Mr. McPoyle from Always Sunny.
He was great in it.
And also Westworld, of course, Jimmy Simpson.
And Christina Miliotti who I really like.
She was great from Wolf of Wall Street and many other things.
It's a powerful Wall Street.
The Capriots' first one.
Oh, I didn't even realize that.
Oh, yeah.
She's great.
I thought this episode was fantastic.
I thought this was as good as Black Mirror does their thing.
Nearly a future film, really.
I liked it a lot.
It just had all the elements that I like about Black Mirror.
And some of these other episodes had the elements I don't
like about Black Mirror.
But this one had it.
It was fun. There was a twist. There was a social commentary. I like that in the beginning
you think plements is the good guy, then you realize he's the bad guy. I like the reveal
that these people that he's duplicating in a virtual setting actually have consciousness
in the other setting. And that's what makes him sadistic and you realize that's really what
he's all about. It's got a chilling ending. It was funny. They did really funny stuff with
Like, when he pauses the game and leaves to get the pizza at the door, everybody else is just there in the world like talking, like, you know, like they're at the water cooler at work.
I just thought it was great. And I also think it's always best on Black Mirror when they do slight near future.
And this was exactly that. So I thought it was just very, very well done. I like the whole episode. It was my favorite so far of the season.
it's the first one Joe out of the three I've seen it's my favorite so far the
season all right I thought you were like the guy who who called a show the
it called the show LA De Vegas the other day the worst show of the year
premiered like January 3rd I hear it's do you think I hear repeatedly that it's
terrible well the man who made it is a friend very nice man all right I'm sure
future episodes. I don't know what's the time. Look, I got nothing against your friends.
I don't put words in my mouth. I'm not putting words in your mouth. I got something
else I'd like to put in your mouth. Folks. Yeah, I think we're both big fans. I'm gonna
go B -plus on this one. Hogs up. Two hogs up. Please don't start doing that. Episode two,
arc angel I thought was a pretty dismal affair directed by Ms. Jody Foster. My
issue with this thing really was the two leads. The woman, where's her name?
Rosemary? I can't remember. Fuck. I liked her in almost everything and I just
didn't in this and I thought the girl who played her daughter was particularly not
great Rosemary DeWitt I just I get it you know parents being kind of over
protective and there were certain moments like where she's watching her daughter
get fucked basically where I'm like okay this is I'm disturbing well if you
haven't seen if the premises they put a chip in her daughter's head when she's
very young and it's basically a way that you can track your kids never lose them
And like most black mirror things, it starts out as this sort of promising technology ends
up going to the to a darker place as they always do.
And one of the things she can do with this technology is she can literally see what her
daughter's seeing.
Yeah.
So she stops using it at some point because it's basically fucked her daughter up because
it allows her to block traumatic visuals from her daughter.
So her daughter as a child gets to this point where she can't, she doesn't understand
what blood is like you know like she doesn't know anything because this is all
been blocked through this filter she shuts it off promises never use it again but
then when her daughter starts getting into a little bit of fun trouble in high
school she starts monitoring her daughter with it again because you can never
remove the chip and that's why she sees the daughter now at 17 or whatever
having sex for the first time or even you explaining it it sounds good like
That sounds like a great science fiction short story, but for me, really, this was a performance
issue.
I didn't like either of the actresses.
I don't know what to tell you, but I was bored by it, beyond belief, and I wanted it
to be over.
And then when it ended, I was like, huh?
It's look.
It was a very, now this is what I was saying about earlier.
This is where I start to not like things that Black Mirror does.
Great premise, great commentary.
I didn't mind the...
I thought the actors were all very good in it.
And I also thought that it was well directed,
because it's obviously it's Jody Frostre.
But Jody Frostre, the Baker, yes, yes, yeah, okay.
So anyway, so I liked all those elements of it,
but it did things that Black Mirror tends to do.
Everything is interconnected somehow,
it's way all up its own ass,
like this storyline exists
because this seed was planted there at the beginning.
It doesn't have to be all that, guys.
You could have did this thing in 28 minutes flat,
Twilight Zone style, and I always think
black mirrors should be Twilight Zone style.
I think they'd all be so much more effective
at a half hour, I can't even tell ya.
Yeah, so, and the ending quite frankly
didn't, it wasn't enough of a payoff for me.
It wasn't dark enough, it wasn't chilling enough,
it was just the daughter runs away,
and the mom finally really loses the daughter which is what she's trying to
prevent the whole time and I'm like I understand that point or that you know
what they're doing but it just it was just kind of a boring ending to a movie
about some crazy technological advancement right just seeing this daughter just
get on a public bus at the end and leaving yeah okay yeah yeah I mean black
Black Mirror as a whole, I, it's a show that I love while when I really look harder at
the seasons, I'm like, oh, wait, half of these kind of suck.
But I love thematically what they're doing.
And I just love that something like it exists, really.
You haven't seen other seasons, really, haven't you?
I've seen them, yeah.
People find it scary, which I don't understand.
Like, I know people that are like, I can't watch it before bed.
Wow, man.
It keeps me awake.
I'm like, what are you talking about?
I've never even been mildly scared by a black mirror.
Um, and then the third one,
least favorite could barely get through this fucking thing.
It was so boring.
I got to tell you for whatever reason
this was my favorite of the three.
Crocodile.
Dundee, right?
Yes.
Uh, that might have been my mistake.
I accidentally watched Crocodile today.
Um, not a lot of stuff about science,
but really funny.
Well, I learned what a knife was
wasn't what a knife wasn't. I'll tell you that. I thought that crocodile was fantastic. I thought
the actress who I had never seen before was a real villain like rough stuff. And I just loved it.
Would it with this have been better at a half hour? Absolutely. But the whole technology of like
smelling the beer and all that to recreate memories. For whatever reason I got into it. And the
the ruthlessness of this woman going through and killing anyone who might fuck her life
up.
And in that final reveal of the guinea pig at the end, and you know, the guinea pig's
gonna find her out and she killed a baby for no reason.
For some reason, that's the kind of like dark shit that I love when Black Mirror does.
That was like shit.
Oh, look, I like those elements of it, that it was ballsy and it was dark, but you know,
Now I just doesn't, I didn't buy for a second that the woman at the scene of the hit and
run at the top of the episode, who's insisting they call the authorities and report this.
Right.
And then her boyfriend is the one being like, you can't, I'll go to prison.
We're not mentioning this.
And then two years later, when he comes back and goes, I can't live with the guilt or whatever.
I've got to confess that she then is suddenly able to kill and cold blood.
I didn't buy that and I also didn't buy that there wasn't a simpler solution, which was, okay,
Remember when I wanted to turn you in because you did this so go turn yourself in just leave me out of it
problem -solved
Well, why does she have to get drug into it?
There's no way to prove she was there. Just go say that you fucking did it. Fine. I don't give a shit. Just leave me out of it
I had thought of that that would have worked
But it's not what happened here.
The stakes just weren't high enough for me.
I didn't care.
There was too much procedural content about how,
even though it was cool that the insurance company had
this advanced thing they could do,
the scene still felt like I was watching a movie
about an insurance agent in the 80s or something.
Like, I just, I really, really found it fucking boring.
Okay.
I was also quite frankly insulted for English people
that Netflix is like, we're going to do Black Mirror now. Suddenly the first two episodes
that are the big lead off ones, all American casts. And then they toss all the English actors
into the third mildly forgettable episode. Yeah. If you've seen the additional three
in the... Not yet. Okay. Well, we'll do those as a second part. Yeah. But it's weird. The show was
like such a crazy phenomenon. And then I haven't heard as much about this season, but
I thought it was as strong as the others. It had good and bad. It's a good show. I mean,
overall, it's good. They just need to tighten it up. I agree. I think I think they should
all be a half hour. Absolutely. Anyway, folks, that's our show. I'll be headlining Gotham Comedy
Club the week in February 16th. And after that, I'll be doing the Patrice O 'Neill benefit
in New York City. So if you're in New York for either of those things, please come out and
say hello and it's Joderosa comedy on Twitter and Instagram.
I'm at the Patrick Walsh at Twitter and Instagram.
Thank you all for your feedback, tweets, Facebook posts, et cetera.
I don't know if you've been in the Facebook page run by Emily, of course, but merch is coming,
lot of merch is coming, posters, beautiful artwork, et cetera, we're very excited and the
launches close at hand. Also, a quick shout out to the gentleman making funco versions
of me and Joe, little funco figurines. It's one of the coolest things I've seen. Maybe
because it involves me, but let me look up the guy's name.
I believe it's Brendan Gash doing that.
Well, I want to look up his handle.
Okay. Yeah, thank you. Those are awesome.
Oh yeah, so it's just Brandon .Gash.
Branding, yes. Sorry. Really, really cool shit. Thank you for doing that. And
Something that somehow I had missed. We have an Instagram page called
See You In Hell Pod that I don't think we've ever mentioned on this show. I didn't know we had an Instagram page.
It's new. I believe Emily started it. So follow us there for updates about, you know,
Merch and all that stuff. Yes. Just all one word See You In Hell Pod. Check it out.
Thanks guys, we'll see you next time, and we'll see you in hell.