Huff, puff, and spin the house down at Golden Nugget Online Casino.
Right now, new players can deposit just 5 bucks and get 500 total spins on Huff and
more puff.
The slot that's blowing players away.
Download the Golden Nugget Online Casino app and use promo code Nugget1.
That's code Nugget1 to enjoy 50 spins a day for your first 10 days.
All on our players favorite game of the summer.
Now's the time to score daily bonuses and spin for all the bacon on the game everyone's
hoffit about at Golden Nugget Online Casino.
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberler, please play responsibly, 21 and over, physically
president Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia only, void an Ontario.
New customers only, nonwithdrawable Casino spins issued as 50 spins per day for 10 days valid
for featured game only and expire each day after 24 hours, see terms at GoldenNuggetCasino .com
slashed promos ends at 11 .59 p .m. Eastern on August 31st, 2025.
The football season is full of guarantees.
And here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if your
football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Monthly 21 -plus, gambling problem called Winning 100 Gambler,
offer not available in all states, terms apply,
see Fanatic's fourth book app.
Hey, if you fucking people Christ, sorry, I was, I was, that was a pathetic intro.
I really enjoyed that.
I was sliding out trying to sit up better on the couch and failing.
It was a tough thing.
What does it mean when you apply pressure to your lower back and you feel almost like you
have a tumor in your throat when that happens?
it. I don't know, but it's probably not good. It's not great. It's not great. Uh, it's
we'll see you and hell party people. And this is where we talk about stuff usually about
horror sci -fi fantasy related film and television. Sometimes like today, we go a little bit
out of the box. And that's not a euphemism. Uh, today we're doing MI6, which for all intents
and purposes is a fantasy fantasy.
It's a little bit of a fantasy.
They're peeling off their faces at their various points in the movie.
It stars Tom was it Cruz?
It stars Tom Hanks, Tom Hanks, Penelope Cruz, Penelope Ann Miller, the guy in beddie lose
handbag Alex winter of freaked, yeah, Bill and Ted's ex you ever see Freaked?
Yeah.
No, I know.
I know.
He directed Freaked.
Yeah.
That was he was going to be a director and I think I love that movie. I heard it's great. Really funny scenes in it. Mr. T's in it
Alex Winter plays Bill in the Bill and Ted's excellent adventure. Yes. And Billy Baldwin is in this flick. Yeah
Not freaked MI6
Alec Baldwin's I know. I know that was why I said Alex was fucking up all the names. You got you got Billy Baldwin
ving rames. By the way, scream that ends. Let me take you there a little early. Oh, really?
They see ving rames in his own home. A neighbor calls police break in that like there's a big
black guy in the house next door. They they bust into ving rams his own home. Jesus Christ
to arrest him. And ving rames is like, I'm ving rames. This happened like two weeks ago. Are
Are you kidding?
Yeah.
Why would I make that?
That's fucking insane.
It would be a sick thing to make up, wouldn't it?
Yes.
It would be a sick thing.
I mean, I know you're not making it up.
I'm merely speaking and euphemistically.
It's in the news.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
Is he suing?
I would.
I don't think so, but he should.
What do you think the odds are that he went to his neighbor after and he said, now listen,
sometimes you're going to see me in a window and you're going to feel a sting in the
back your neck to call the cops, right? That's pride fucking with you. You're quoting
the Comedy Central roast of Bruce Willis. Yes. Because as far as I know that's only from
that roast, he never did that in a movie or anything. Right. Okay.
Think Rams, is he fat now? It's hard to tell when watching Mission Impossible. He wears
a lot of like soprano shirts, which usually means you're fat. Yeah. And his face looks weird.
He looks like a big muscular guy that that probably put on weight. Yeah. Yeah. Still enjoy him. I still
enjoy him very much. They didn't they'd always kind of cut away when Bing would start running. They'd be like,
let's let's see what we got in a two shot of Tom and then come back to Bing when the running has
stopped. Yeah. It's bad when it's bad when you're letting Simon Pegg get more action speaking of
of looks. Yeah. So, well, Simon Pegg, we're watching that man bald. I think from scene to
scene, we're watching him bald. I love Simon Pegg, but what is he 68? For Christ's, I
thought the guy wasn't that much older than we are. He looks like a 68 year old man. It's
what happens to all British actors. Like they, they look like newborns until they're 25 and
And they immediately look like they're 80 year old women.
Your face is going strong.
He still looks great.
If that British guys have it a little better, the pale, frail, light skinned, fair haired
British guys always want to look like old women.
I look, Hugh Grant looks like a 75 year old woman.
I never would have put money on the, on the, on, on Robbie Coltrane keeping it together
long.
That helps.
Did, uh, do you, now do you think he's hitting the sauce because he's got a real, he's
He's got a leathery face.
Pagma'd be hitting the sauce.
He's written movies about trying to beat the sauce.
That is true.
That world's in, which I really didn't care for.
I like the world's in.
Did he write that though?
I thought the other, I thought his buddy wrote it,
that directed it.
I thought it was the two of them, but I might maybe it was.
I don't know much.
But I know, I love you.
All right, well, you slid a segment in really, really.
You know, I thought that was a scary story.
Do you have any news stories?
Uh, new stories, uh, no, not this week.
That's that's that that did us just fine, uh,
but I do have something for scary stuff.
All right.
We didn't do scary stuff last week.
We didn't.
You know, we don't have to, we don't have to answer to you
every fucking week.
Uh, I'm in a CVS today.
Yep.
Stands four.
I believe it's a disease that causes cervical cancer.
Jesus.
All right.
HPV. Sorry, I'm getting my three letter things mixed up. I don't know. What's what the fuck the CVS ever? No clue. Certified, variable.
Nope.
Synthetics.
Uh,
CBS.
Yeah.
Buying, uh, I need to buy condoms because I like to make sure that I'm safe that I got some on hand. Yes.
Yes, I go into a section,
rubbers called personal intimacy.
Yeah, is the name of the section they keep them in now.
Wait, real quick pause.
Using this basic area as a setup,
give me a Woody Allen joke involving
the section personal intimacy.
And I need the voice as well, please.
It's an improv challenge.
Hold on a second.
I need you to repeat that because when you said pause,
I wasn't sure if you meant pause the recording.
No, no, no, I didn't. It's still going.
What I want is, so you're going into the section
of CVS personal intimacy,
and I want a Woody Allen joke and a Woody Allen voice.
Okay, off this premise.
They keep the condoms in the usually
in the personal intimacy section.
I often bind mine in the public intimacy section,
because I find if you can't share with anybody,
You should be ashamed of it.
Yeah.
Okay.
All right.
Anyway, personal literacy.
So they got the fucking condoms in this,
like, you know, locked case.
You can't just get them,
because I guess people are stealing condoms a lot.
Hey, they shouldn't have to steal them.
And they also shouldn't be $25.
Yeah.
To buy an 18 pack of condoms
when everybody's getting each other knocked up.
So there's a button.
Yeah.
It's just press for assistance.
Okay.
You press it.
Announcement through the whole fucking store.
We need a customer service wrap and family planning.
Wait, were you shopping in every 80's sitcom?
It was like out of the golden girls.
It was ridiculous.
Were you the one millionth customer perhaps?
I swear to God, that happened.
I mean, only one standing at the condom rack, we need a customer service rep to family
planning.
I'm sorry.
Were you shopping at porkeys to the revenge?
So that happened.
Yeah.
And I'm in line.
And I'm standing in front of this guy and I go, dude, I forgot to buy something.
Can you hold my place?
He goes, yeah, no problem, man.
Nice.
Just that is a victory.
It was a victory.
He goes, no problem.
go ahead. He's got a little bit of an accent. I realize he's a Mexican dude. That's why he's nice.
And he does this move that I had such respect for. Went into CVS for one reason, one reason only
to buy a handle of Bacardi, which beautiful. I can only assume he's making some delicious desert,
juice of the cacti drink with it, you know. Yeah. It was such a, it was such a classic move. I loved it.
I fucking loved it all right anyway, so that was my that was my day folks. Don't give me started on what yesterday was like
So I'm walking into a personal intimacy I see in the section and
You know, I realized that I can't buy anything in in personal intimacy because I've never experienced it
It's narration to Annie Hall to the revenge.
Um, Annie Hall to this time it's personal.
Annie Harder, uh, Army Hammer.
You like Army Hammer?
Uh, I think Army Hammer is fine.
You like, you like, you like Army Hammer?
I think he's fine, and I think he's,
Who was the actor I was just looking at and I was like, this is like, this guy is just
like Army Hammer where, you know, he, I feel like Army Hammer, it was supposed to be
real big.
Yeah.
And then it wasn't.
He put all his chips on the loan ranger.
I enjoyed the loan ranger.
Never saw, but I know a lot of people enjoy it.
And we've questioned Tarantino's opinions on films, Tarantino went on record saying
that was his the best movie of that year.
That's right.
But he's a fucking mad man. Matt Zola Sites, who is a great movie critic and a great critic,
especially to follow on Twitter. He always just has great film conversations going. But
he asked the other day, like, what are the 10 movies in the last 10 years that you would
say didn't get a fair shake. And the number one in his list was the loan rate?
It absolutely didn't get a fair shake. It was, it was every bit as enjoyable as the
Verbenzki Pirates of the Caribbean Pirate movies, you know, the fact that I love the
Verbenzki directed The Weatherman because that's so out of his, and it makes me wonder
if that's not what he wishes he was doing because he was, I love the movie so much.
I was wondered why Nicholas Cage battled a giant octopus at the end of that film.
I was, I thought that was out of play.
It seemed forced.
Yeah.
I love The Weatherman.
It's an awesome and very bleak fucking movie. Yeah, very bleak cage playing a depressing thing is great. Yeah, who's the dead Michael can't yeah, and he's just the whole time
Yeah, we're blue. Yes, son. They have that scene where they're trying to connect in the car while like a rock by Bob Seager is playing one of the most brutal scenes I've ever seen. I love that movie.
And just like how he's disgusted by his daughter, I always found so troubling.
Like you know, there are people who are disgusted by their kids, but you never really see
it.
I love when that makes a new movie.
It was crazy.
Yeah, like father of the year when Robin Williams just hates his son.
That movie is something special.
That's one of his best movies.
Yeah.
I enjoyed it. I watched it in one sitting. I thought to myself, here's what it reminded me of,
when I was like 10, I used to watch, I used to be excited on Friday nights because I could watch
Letterman and sometimes Carson mostly Lena. And Robin Williams was on Letterman and I was so excited.
This was like around Aladdin Mrs. Dalfire time
He comes on he does the thing where he's doing a bunch of improv and
Tweety bird. Oh, let me tell you. Oh, Tweety bird. Oh, and he's flying overhead and and an old man
Revelled and I was like, you know, this stuff makes me actively frowned now
Forget laugh, but when I was a kid, I was like this guy's amazing. He's a genius. You know, you don't have tastes when you're a kid
I dropped my phone on the ground.
So, it reminded me of the first time I saw
through the phoneiness and the bullshit
of the Hollywood system.
I watch him on Letterman, I'm like this guy's,
and no matter what day he throws
and he can spin it into a joke, he's crazy, so talented.
And then the very next night he was on Lennon
and he did the exact same bits for Badam
but in that, I'm improvving style.
Right.
And it really shook me up when I was a kid
because it just shown a light at how you know fake everything is right so I did I never liked his
riffing beyond age 10 or so I prefer to as a dramatic actor to a comedic actor by about a million
percent and his stand -up comedy is shit that said I mean you grow up with Rob Williams he's like
your dad. And honestly, it's very similar relationship. You're embarrassed by a lot that
he does. Your dad's always putting that dress on. Right. Funny voices. But the documentary
was fantastic. I loved it. I love. I can watch any documentary about anything but particularly
comedy to which I'll slide in a recommendation for CNN's The History of Comedy, which has
It's been a blast to watch. They're on season two.
Uh, I am not a huge fan of that scene and show.
But, uh, I like, well, some of it just makes me angry and I like feeling angry.
Like, when you see the people they have on, Pete Holt is actually one of the, I guess, he doesn't
make me angry, but I saw him and, uh, um, you know, they all discuss animation and everything
and they discuss.
I'm just sick of people talking about comedy.
They all talk about the comedy and a lot.
That's why I really didn't like the first half of the Robin Williams documentary because
it was all about his comedy and everybody being like, you know, it's all the shit you'd
expectively.
He was, he'd come into the room and he was a lightning rod and it was just a, you know,
yeah.
And they don't, they don't address the joke stealing at all in the document.
Not at all.
So that crap.
But once they get into him becoming the actor and like his personal life and who he was
was actually as a person.
Right.
I thought it was very touching and very sweet.
And it did make me miss him just being around.
So I like the documentary quite a bit.
Oh, great.
It was a good one.
I would like to discuss if I may a TV show that I think
is really great and really well written.
It is called Killing Eve.
OK.
And it's become kind of a cult show very quickly, but I washed it on the AMC app.
It actually airs on BBC America, so I don't know how those two synced up, but that's what's going on.
And it stars Sandra O, an actress I have routinely not liked very much,
and a bunch of other people I've never seen in anything before. It is by Phoebe Waller Briggs,
who was the voice of the robot in solo and also did the excellent BBC show Fleabag, which
a lot of people love.
I highly recommend six episodes.
Fleabag is the voice of that robot.
Yeah.
I didn't realize that.
That's a good show.
It's a very funny comedy show.
And this, this is like a spy show, a very intense thriller show, lots of twists and turns,
but also super funny.
And I absolutely loved it. I watched six in a row. I'm dying to see how it ends.
My first day at work, I was like, what do you guys watch that is good?
Everybody said killing Eve, went home. Got a hook. It's a great show.
All right. I recommend it with confidence. You'll like it.
All right. Very good. Even if you don't like Sandra.
Very good.
I'll do a TV show. Dickensine.
And I think you've discussed Dickensian on this show, at least to me, but go on.
I don't think I have on the show yet.
All right, Dickensian, it's on Amazon Prime currently, it was a BBC show, it's probably
about two years old at this point, they only did one season, but it was, you know, a lot
like Castle Rock, it is based on the works of Charles Dickens and it has all the different
characters from the Charles Dickens novels intersecting, crossing paths and everything
in London. Yeah. Uh, Mary old London. Mary old London. Yeah. Yeah. But I'll tell you
Pat, things aren't so merry because it opens with a murder. Okay. Uh, murder most file.
Modem. Yeah. All right. You got it. Have you seen this show? No, but the, uh, uh, it opens
with the, in episode, there's a little bit of a spoiler. Episode one is, it is the main plot
point is the murder of Jacob Marley. And that's how and everybody's sort of a suspect.
And it's a very fun, you know, is Fezzy Wigg a suspect fast patient.
Fezzy Wigg's dead at this point. Oh wow. He was young Scrooge. Okay. But Scrooge is
in there. Fuzzy Wigg alive. Only when the Muppets do it. Okay. Yeah. Also starting Michael
Okay, brings it back as Scrooge, yeah, Ebenezer Scrooge, but they're all in it, you know,
there's a lot of everybody from great expectations and, you know,
Miss Havishem.
Havishem's in it, she's not Havishem yet, though.
Okay, she's the future Miss Havishem, like a young, beautiful woman who hasn't turned yet.
She's, because Havishem's the one with the much older husband, right?
Oh, no, wait.
No, I'm sorry.
Miss Havishem is an old spencer like left to die in an attic.
I'm sorry.
Have a great expectation.
His young in this and her brother and her and she have just parted ways.
Okay.
I'm getting them names of people mixed up.
And her brother, that's the brother's pot line is he's actively trying to swindle her
out of the money.
You find out there's a, there's a very heavy indication that the brother is gay and that's
not acceptable at that time in society and that's why his father cut him out of the wheel.
So they take some nice liberties to justify why people don't like one another.
My favorite of which being Scrooge catches Cratchit essentially stealing because he needs
to because he's so fucking poor.
And that's when Scrooge is like, you're fucked man, like you're under my thumb from now on.
And that's why he treats Cratchit as badly as he does because he caught him basically stealing
from the company.
So I just thought it was cool that they were like, what if we justified why these people treated one another like this?
And then also what if the guy, you know, what if who's the guy from Oliver Twist, Fagan, the crook, Fagan also knew I portrayed Fagan, you did in the fourth grade Patrick Walsh's Fagan.
I told the story in this podcast. I'd say it is Fagan. I don't think Joven listens to me on this show.
You, well, I don't, but no, I didn't. In the fourth grade,
a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a
he does come into it at one point. And so is the artful Dodgers in there. They're all in there.
It's great. Well, I want to ask you about two movies and are we going to do them before I
discuss them? And those movies are Deadpool 2 and Jurassic World 2. I never want to see either of
those movies. All right. So you go for it. Then I would love to talk about Deadpool 2, which
which might be the best comedy I've seen this year, and I didn't even love it, by the
way. But it is a movie that just pops off joke after joke after joke. It is a huge improvement
on the original. It's a full on comedy. They don't even really, it felt to me like the closest
we're going to get to like a naked gun or a hot shots. It was so fun. And the percentage
of great jokes to duds were surprisingly high.
Well, am I making a mistake? Should I see it?
And then we do do it?
Or no?
Well, if I told you, I told you all this weeks ago.
I mean, I don't know if you're going to see it or not,
but we could do it when it comes out on Blu -ray.
I think it's coming out.
If you want to save this.
That's all right.
No, no, no.
I just felt like I wish every superhero movie was like this.
I know that would be your worst nightmare job,
but treating a subject this stupid with about the level of respect it deserves. I thought
it was very funny. Contain a great bit of narration where Ryan Reynolds who co -wrote this
one. And it's just a funny man, folks. It meant it. Yeah, Ryan Reynolds was really funny.
But he goes, anyway, we're heading into the third act now. This is usually the part of the
movie where the hero really falls upon his biggest struggle and biggest downfall in cool
runnings. It was when John Candy lost his beloved bobsled in human centipede. It was
when all those actors realized they'd agreed to do this movie. I was like, these are great
jokes. I was just enjoying the hell out of a cool running's reference. Rob Delaney of
Twitter fan, the funniest guy on Twitter now and forever outside of maybe George Wallace
and a very nice man.
But Rob Delaney is playing the, like a dad who gets recruited, so they do like this segment
where it's a very short part of the movement there, recruiting like a new ex force, like
an X -Men team.
And Rob Delaney just shows up because he saw the ad and he's just like a dad, like a 45 -year -old
paunchy dad and pleaded khakis. And then they all go on this mission together, including
Rob Delaney. The payoff of that scene comedically was a massive laugh, like a huge, like something
about Mary style theater laugh. All right. They, it's, it's great jokes. I was, I personally
was thrilled by it, considering as I was saying on the last episode, how shitty comedy has become,
Um, it's shit. It's very entertaining. All right. Great. All right. Well, I saw, uh, well,
this is a rewatch, which we get sometimes on these segments. Uh, I rewatched fences with
the great Denzel Washington and Viola Davis. Uh, when I first saw the movie, I said that
I thought it was great. I enjoyed it very much. Uh, upon rewatch, I have gone from saying
I think it's great to, I think it's a masterpiece.
Oh, look out.
I caught so much on first watch, I was like, well, this is a really good movie about family
and the struggles and this time period.
And all of a sudden, second watch was when I really picked up on what, what all of it was
truly about with the generations.
And how his dad is dense else playing this guy that basically is barely, you know, was living barely out of like almost slavery time. You know what I mean?
And was discriminated against so much fucking harder than his son is, even though his son is still discriminated against.
And that his father had it even harder than him and his father treated him like garbage.
and now he's kind of treating his son poorly but it's because he loves him and he's tried
to do his best, but he just doesn't know how to express it and he fucks up and makes
a lot of bad mistakes in the film and it's just a brilliant, brilliant depiction of what
the decades and the generations and the culture do to a family and how they are unable to relate
to one another because of it. But at the end of the day, what the person is doing is the best
they're able to give, even though that means potentially doing some very horrible things.
You know, it's not like you ever beats on them or anything like that. But you know,
it's this concept of, you know, you do your best. Nobody's perfect. And I just, I don't know.
I just thought it was a really, really, brilliantly written script. I'd love to see the actual place
sometime. I'd say it was about the fences between us. Well, that's, that's it, too.
Cause they actually say the line, some people build fences to keep people in. And
some people build fences to keep them out. Right. Uh, but when he has the final falling out with his
son, and he says, I can't taste anything anymore. And he's like, now it's just you and me, Mr.
death. Yeah. It's just you and me. I'm ready for you. Right. And that's where I'm at. Yeah.
That's where I'm at right now too. Quite frankly. But but it's just it's it's it's it's a guy
literally like destroyed. He's destroying all love in his life because he was never shown
in he loved and he doesn't all he knows is how to survive. Right. But he still he still
tends to his responsibilities. Like he makes sure his son is fed. He makes sure his wife is
taken care of, even though he fucks up royally. You know, so I don't know. It's just a great
fleck, man. It's one that I would actually purchase at this point and own. Maybe I'll
revisit it. I don't sell it at the once. And Denzel's just fucking awesome in it. Of course,
when the kid throws his helmet at him, yeah. And he's like, come here, come here. And he's
like, you're in the baddest box on. Yeah. You got one strike. Don't strike out. It's he's
She's so intense.
She's just awesome.
Yeah.
It was an awesome movie.
Vaila Davis crying up a storm.
She really emotes our remember.
Yeah, she emotes like nobody else out there.
She's fantastic.
I love it.
Great flick.
She's really in emote control, I would say.
I saw Jurassic World rise of the machines
it's a while back and my Lord, it was not good. I thought Jurassic World was fine. I was
like, if they're going to keep this franchise going, I guess this is barely enough. And
two is half as good as that. It's just ludicrous at the end. It's like a haunted house movie
with dinosaurs. They're in a mansion running around. I didn't even find that too stupid because at
this point they need to do something crazy like that. But somehow they just made it not fun and
boring and I didn't like any other. How did the dinosaurs get off the island? There's people who
bid on them like slaves because they want them to like study or hunt. So they have like auctions of
dinosaurs. They get off that way. Even after the events of the first film where they try
to kill everybody. That's correct. And there's no, at no point, the government doesn't come
in and say, you know, you can't do this anymore, guys. They try to, but it doesn't work. Chris
Pratt, there was a brief flash where I was like, this guy's going to be big. He's boring
me already. Uh, I'm, I'm so over it with Pratt. He's a talented guy, but it's just, you
know, he's the smart -ass good -looking kid, like, and it's very boring. I really hope, because
there's, you know, they're making this last Indiana Jones movie and then they're saying they
might pass them to torch to somebody else. And they were, they were throwing his name around
for a while and I really, really hope it's not him. I bet it's going to happen. So it's
not going to be Alden Heidenreich. Alden, who's that again?
Solo. The star. Oh, Solo. He would have been great. He'd be a great Indiana Jones. They're
not going to give it to. Well, they won't. They'd be throwing money on that.
That'd be crazy. What if he took over all his words parts? He won't. Ladies and gentlemen,
I've been working girl, 2020 during all the Hayden Reich, right, right, witness again.
Yeah.
Air Force two.
Am I right?
You're right.
Air Force one was great.
Saw it like a week after face off.
That was a great time for action movies.
That was a big time.
Yeah.
That was when he was like right in the middle of the clear and present danger.
Shit.
Yeah.
Yeah, fair presidential is awesome. Yeah, I like it better than patriarchy. It's significantly better than patriarchy
Do you have one more here? Are we moving on one more? Okay, I saw because I was on a Denzel kick
After I watch fences, so I went in and I watched a movie I'd never seen with him and I'm surprised
I've never seen it. You'll be surprised as well inside man
It's a bit tight. Love inside man. Awesome. I thought we had discussed that maybe not. I guess
awesome movie. Oh, inside man is the shit. And I'm sure you didn't know the twist because it's been
so long. I never knew the twist. Yeah, I never saw it. Never heard it. Or if you heard it, you forgot
it. No, I never heard it. Nobody ever told me the twist. That I mean, Spike Lee, I'm I'm always
glad when he comes back and I feel like he'll always come back until he's dead. I'm excited to see
black clansman, which did very, very well this weekend. He's one of our best directors.
And the lack of respect people give him is shocking. And he's made more great movies
than almost anyone. And inside man is like just him doing like a big commercial movie.
And it's awesome. There's so much extra shit in it, like beyond just being a good thriller.
Like, there's a lot to say. It's shot awesomely. There's great stuff in it. There's great dialogue
And a lot of twists and turns.
Yeah, a lot of interesting racial commentary.
That's that's right.
It's as you would expect from a Spike Lee movie,
but not necessarily in this type of Spike Lee movie.
Right, but it's very well done.
And it's woven into the plot seamlessly.
It's a great, it's a great flick.
And Denzel's, any time Denzel is
fighting anything, he's awesome.
But I particularly like when he is a hero
and sort of an anti hero at first,
where you're like,
I don't know if this guy's straight and narrow or what?
Willem DeFel,
Jody Foster, yeah, killing it, playing a bad guy.
She never plays a bad guy and she looks
stunning in the goddamn movie. Jesus, God. It's a great moment.
So, you know,
speaking of plot twists by the way, Pat. Yeah.
this episode is due for a twist because we're 32 minutes in and we technically haven't gotten on
with the show yet. Oh, you're right. You're right. Then let's just get on with the show and at the
same time on with the even Joe Blano butterflies. Very good, right? Very good. I thought
of one of the last second there. All right. I don't know how you keep coming up with
these damn things. Keep coming up with hits like every damn day.
We're a quick Joe scary stuff for you PlayStation 3 and Xbox 360 fanatics out there and any of you that like Star Wars.
I strongly suggest you revisit the Force Unleashed and the Force Unleashed 2 video games.
This is yet another thing like we're talking about the lone ranger. It's got such a bum rap when they came out.
Very lukewarm reviews.
people were complaining that they said it's ridiculous go go fucking police are
great great great video games they're stunningly beautiful they're they play
well you have the force and you do all kinds of crazy force shit it's fucking
awesome it's awesome action games I don't understand what you know it was just it
was cool to hate Star Wars then so I suggest you revisit those do yourself
of favor. I actually have one. I watched the scream factory Blu -ray of Tobay Hooper's life force.
I own it myself. Long -heard rumors about it just being completely insane. Those, it's
certainly lived up to those rumors. It's a crazy movie. It's crazy movie. It had, you know,
one of the most beautiful women I've ever seen in my life walking around completely naked for
90 of the 120 minutes, not exaggerating, seems like just a godsend to like kids surfing
HBO in the 80s and 90s, I'm definitely selling it.
It's not something I'm ever going to watch again, but it was fascinating and I really enjoyed
it.
Okay. You sort of did that, right? Well, it had special features. Yeah. So interview
with her where she said she was ashamed of it. Why was she ashamed of it? Because it's
like doing porn, basically. Because she's naked. Yeah. She doesn't have sex with anybody
in it. She has sex. Yes, she does. Yeah, but it wasn't like porn. You know, it was like
I think it's an awesome movie, amazing practical effects, one of the few good films that Canon put out and I don't mean good in an ironic way.
Most of Canon's films are ironically good. This is actually a good film, I think.
Toby Hubert's finest work outside of the Texas Chainsaw Massacre. It's not better than Poltergeist.
I mean, if you want to call that a Toby Oh shit. Well, he even came out that he even said
like, yeah, he was, yeah. Um, but, uh, you know, it's a fun flick. Um, it's got some good
gory in it if I remember. It does seem in a while. No, it was a cool movie. I mean, I was
excited as soon as in the opening credits, it says based on the novel space vampires,
there's the original title. Yeah. Yeah. I was like, all right. Well, that's that lets you know
where you're at. That's up there with hotel for dogs and that's right. Crazy rich Asians. That's
right. Not a lot of mystery in those titles. No. You're going to see crazy rich Asians. No. No.
I don't have an interest. People are saying it's a masterpiece. Look, I'll check it out. I'll see
with these Asians are up to, uh, these crazy, yeah, agents. Um, it's such a ridiculous
title, right? Like, but like people are saying it's very, very good and it's like it redefines
the, however he talks now though, they say it redefines the romcom. Uh -huh. We'll see. Um,
but, uh, you know, I'm not against it. It's just as you are against Asians. Only crazy
Oh, okay, this is this is, you know, crazy rich is a different story. Yeah. I'm kidding everybody before you I'm kidding for the block before you get your blog out.
Anyway, yes, let's get on to our movie of today. We're about approaching the 40 minute
mark. It's probably time. The film is called Mission Impossible, colon fallout. And this
This time around, they actually spelled the word colon out.
Right.
It was, I thought going to be taking place entirely in Tom Cruise's colon, like the inner space.
So I love this film, you know, it's what you go to these movies for.
One great big old action set piece after another.
You got five minutes of Tom Cruise running as fast as he can, that's just awesome.
Best of the series?
I don't know.
People calling it best action movie ever made?
No.
No, that's crazy.
But it sure is entertaining, and I can't imagine somebody who likes an action movie not liking
it.
Here's my one sentence review, Scientology, where do I sign up?
I know.
Oh, it's working for this guy.
Yeah.
I, uh, I was on cruise control.
Yeah. Right.
Uh, like speed two, like speed two.
I love the film as well.
Uh, it five is my favorite of the series.
Right.
They would have to do a lot to top five for me.
That's all the washing machine bit.
They're in like a giant washing machine.
Yeah.
When he's got a, yeah, it goes in reverse.
It's also the one where he hangs off the actual flying plane.
Right.
Well, he hung off a flying plane in this one too.
Yeah, he climbs a rope attached to a moving helicopter.
Yeah, it's real, but yeah, man, it's an awesome movie.
I mean, you got, first of all, you got, you got crews coming in with,
I mean, the guys, it's just charisma just dripping off of him.
Yeah.
Just, just coming in, doing this thing and, and just kick an ass and being great.
And just when you're like, you know, you're sitting there going,
I fully believe this man can do all of these things.
I believe it. Yeah. Who could be a match for this man? Right. They bring in God damn
Superman. cable. Yeah. Only time I've ever liked cable. And he comes in and it's the
same thing. Mustache helps him a lot. This guy does every fucking thing. I believe all
of it. Yeah. Mustache helps him out a lot. As you said, Ving Rames is back pegs back. Simon
Moana Hannah's back. Michelle Moana Hannah's back. Angela Bassett, a new addition.
Bassett enjoyed her very much as the sort of bold one. You know, the cold, they said
the bald one. I was like, she's not bald. No, you know, she's like the hard boiled director
of CIA. She's almost like, um, central television. The, uh, the lady in suicide squad that
Viola Davis, I can't remember the character's name now, but yeah, either can Viola, but
she's great.
Baldwin is, is, is, is a lot of fun.
Baldwin had some of my favorite lines in the movie.
Yeah.
Um, and I, I do like to that they, it, it, it's a continuation of five.
It's a direct continuation of five.
I don't think any of the other ones did that.
No.
But I still think you could follow without having even seen five everybody sees all these
but they're, they're not only beating the James Bond movies that their own game.
They're just significantly better and they leave them in the dust.
Now do you think this is the last one?
I don't.
Not at all.
Going into it, I didn't think it was going out of it.
I thought it was because it was very much about him.
Tom Ethan Hunt making a men's in his life, they, they go out of their way about four
times in the film to have him say the exact line, I'm so sorry.
Yeah.
Well, you know, Joe, that's so that they can say he said he'd never do it again, and then
he'd tie him on a bandana.
But you know, it's like we made too much money, you ever know how I would leave $10 in
the table?
No, no, no, no.
But I'm just saying like this did seem like a tie up all the loose ends, like they find
finally brought there's going to be spoilers here. They finally brought closure to the storyline
with his wife. Yep. The CIA and the miss the M .I .F. or whatever the fuck they're called
or IMF. They finally made amends. You know, he kind of did right by these finally with the
woman that he fell in love with in the last movie, you know, he stuck to his, to his
principles in the, in the, in the, in a time when it was the hardest for him to honor
his principles, he didn't betray him. It just seemed like it was kind of like, this
was it, but, but I don't know. They would have said the final mission impossible. You use
that in your marketing. If that's what it was going to be.
Yeah. So I mean, look, I'll keep seeing these things as long as they keep making them.
Of course.
They're just great.
And Macquarie, who really didn't do anything between usual suspects and like, we did
way of the gun and then kind of dropped out of Hollywood.
But I started seeing his name and things about five years ago.
And now he just makes the best action movies.
Jack Reacher was pretty awesome.
Is that how he got on to mission and must have been?
Okay.
Yeah, because Jack Reacher won was before MI5, right?
Yeah, I think.
I heard Jack Reacher's good.
I never saw it.
It's great.
I never saw the second one, but Jack Reacher's a lot of fun.
I heard the second one sucks.
That might be true.
I gotta see that.
I don't know why I've never seen it.
I mean, you know, with, it's a John Wick thing, right?
And it's basically.
Yeah, it's really good.
He comes out and beats people up.
Pretty much, yeah.
And Reacher's over and beats them up.
Jack Reacher, what was your favorite action sequence in MI6?
For me, it was that cruise running bit, it just pumped me up,
which one, which jumping from building to building?
Oh, the one, I like that, too, where he comes to the window.
Why'd you stop?
I'm at a window!
I thought there were some really funny parts in it, too.
I liked how they'd be in the middle doing some crazy secret spy shit
and like a, you know, and then a normal person would be there.
Right.
You know, like, I like when he had to go, he's chase,
he's being chased by the bad guys and he breaks up the funeral.
Right. Yeah.
Again, says, I'm so, so sorry.
Right.
Like they, they just, they were, there were some really funny bits in it like that.
But, um, yeah, cruise running was awesome.
I'm going to go with, I think the motorcycle thing might have been my favorite.
That was pretty cool, but that was the only time where, and I'm, I'm pretty confident.
but I think there was some digital work going on in there.
Well, they say that you can see and break his ankle
and he crashes on that bike and then gets up and starts running.
Yeah.
And he's hopping lightly on one of his feet and I'm like,
holy shit, I think that's when he broke his ankle.
Right.
But my favorite scene in the whole thing,
there's a great set up in the beginning of the film
where Angela Bassett says,
you're just a bunch of boys running around and masks.
Yeah.
Because they always cover their faces with the, you know.
And I love the when like they move the bad guy out or they move the Simon Pegg is the
fake bad guy out of custody and they leave the fake bat the real bad guy in Henry Cavill's
custody.
Yeah.
And then that's the scene where Cavill reveals to him, he reveals the audience that they're
in cahoots and he's actually a bad guy and then he goes, Cavill goes she's right, they
They are just a bunch of children running around in masks and realizes that Simon Pegg is
the one sitting there.
Right.
That part was awesome.
And then Baldwin comes up behind him with the gun and he goes, oh, I've ruined your
day.
Haven't I?
Yeah.
That whole, I love all that fucking shit.
I didn't like Wolf Blitzer being in it.
He wasn't.
It was Simon Pegg dressed as Wolf Blitzer.
Yeah.
I, uh, that was my only issue.
And then it's crazy that they still do the face peeling off. I mean, it's insane.
In a series of movies that are so based in reality, it's weird that they keep going back to it,
but it is mission impossible. I'll tell you this, it's even crazier that I'm still buying it.
Yeah, still going along with it. When they say I'm going to make a mask of his face and wear it,
I every time I'm like, oh, of course you are.
That's what you need to do right now.
Yeah, it was, it was a good flick.
I really enjoyed it.
That, that, those opening sequences get me revved up, man.
That whole thing, you know, when, yeah, the wolf blitz
are part where he walks in and then the four walls fall.
And you realize it's not a hospital.
He's in their facility and he goes, this, this goes, this goes
those as far as we say it goes or whatever the line is and it kicks into the fuse and
the music.
That's exciting stuff, man.
That's great, Joe.
That's exciting stuff.
I actually thought it would have been better.
Am I mean this?
If Wolf Blitzer was actually Wolf Blitzer, but a member of the IMF, you never said, never
see.
Like I thought that would have been funny.
It's crazy.
But I just thought it would have been funny.
for this whole time with blitzer was like a secret agent or something.
Do you think we'll get another Austin Powers?
I mean, if there's a God in heaven, we will.
I feel like there's zero chance.
Oh, come on, dude.
If Myers went to Netflix and said I want to do an Austin Powers, which might be what we'd
get, they'd do it.
If he wants to go theatrical, I don't know.
People would see it.
I'd see it.
I'll tell you that much.
Dude, anything's possible.
We've seen, we saw Star Wars with 75 -year -old Han Solo, like anything is possible.
It's true.
What about Wayne's world now?
Wayne's world three.
It would be, that would just be sad at this point.
I think that would be what's great about it.
Well that's what the Bill and Ted thing kind of is, is like that they have it.
Work's too was pretty sad as well.
There's a melancholy to it.
Well, it also is sad when, because they're, it's fine when those two guys are running,
like Dante runs the convenience store and Randall runs the video stuff.
That's fine.
Even if they're in their 40s or 50s or 60s.
Once you take those guys out of that and they have to work fast food together, that's when
it gets depressing.
Yeah.
I agree.
Yeah, you know, so clerks three not happening, but Jay and Silent Bob get rebooted is I'm very excited for that as a mine. I think it's going to be great. You know, it's an exact.
It's an exact.
It's so up its own ass. It's crazy. It's an exact remake of Jay and Silent Bob strike back.
What is the Jay and Silent Bob reboot movie?
what are you making that face for? I don't know what you're talking about. Kevin Smith
is, his next movie is Jay and Silent Bob get a reboot. Oh, okay. That's the movie. It's
a sequel to Jay and Silent Bob strike back. And they're making Jay and Silent Bob strike
back into a no. And the plot of it is is they're finding that Jay and Silent Bob find out Hollywood
wood is doing a reboot of Blunt Man and Chronic. Okay. And they have to go across country
again to stop it. So it's like, that's like the most self -referential thing I've ever
said. Yeah, I'm already confused. It's the same plot as the original, except now it's
their older and Hollywood is making another re a reboot of that first movie that they were
going to stop in the first film. You follow me? I follow you. What's that coming out?
So soon, I think like it's, it's definitely getting made. It's not like, did you like
Jay and Silent Bob strike back? Yeah, I loved it. That's my last. I love it. It's got
my favorite J. Laila's funny, and Lil Farrell is very funny. It's got my favorite J line
of all time when he's talking about the trolls on the internet and why it matters. And
Ben Affleck doesn't understand why they care so much. And J goes, just what if we meet some
hot chicks, and they're like, ooh, we want to suck you guys' dicks off. And then they
see what these fucking assholes are saying about us on the internet. That's a very
funny line to me. All right. All right. You know, sit up there on your high horse. Look,
I like a little more urbane went urban humor. You mean? Yes. Martin.
Shanae. Hey, folks, we have love talking to you. We're going to be back with what do you know,
Joe. I believe next month we'll start with Army of Darkness. Yes, we're going to get some
classics in. Get some classics in. Army of Darkness has been requested many times. I just watched
a new blu -ray of it and that's a movie. A lot of people have a lot of opinions on which cuts the
best and so on and so forth. Plugs, I'm on the Twitter and the Instagram at the Patrick Walsh.
this is the last episode of August, I believe it's this weekend that I will be at the Campbell's Resort of Washington there state, so come see me if you can.
and then red clay festival in September and in Atlanta.
And before we go, people, we've got your, I don't know if you heard, man, con just shook
real loud behind me there. I don't know if you heard that rattle. Anyway, we've got your
shout outs for the month of August. And here they are. Anthony V. Manito, AKA party
McFly, Chuck Egs, Chloe Paget, Brooke Adams, Michael Witt Zett, Zach Baldwin, Matthew
Russ, Daniel McLean, Scott Purchitt, Dennis Ormston, Travis Hines, just John Weisengruber,
Matthew McGuire, Angela Piccaro, James O 'Brien, Kamani Coldfielder, O 'Waggo, Matthew Moon,
with Jay Fischer, Sean Lyle, John Hollywood, Jake Mick Alvin, Meredith Mick Williams,
Gregory Hassel, Jesse, or excuse me, Jesse Janicki, Mike Greenwood, Brianna Alkire, I believe,
as always, people, apologies if I'm not saying your name right.
I'm trying my best here, and if I'm not saying it right, you can let us know.
And then we'll try to correct that.
But Chloe Rothiker, Matt, supportive guy, Martin Brandt. Oops, I said that last one wrong.
Scott Connor, Anthony Rodriguez, Chris Passmore, Casey Jones, Sinjie, Dermott, fuck you,
Blade Runner.
It was a great fucking movie. All right. Robert Haynes, Natalia Hatley, Will Pittman, Kevin
Kevin McNannie, Kevin Driscoll, Jen Wessels, Lewis Bell,
Heighten Davidson, Joe Hoffman, Scott Sweeney, J. Miller, Clayton Stamper,
Amanda Lancaster, Michael Bolas, Ethan Gamas, James Joe Rolamo,
Girolamo, one of the two, Derek Adams, Sean Hall,
Adam Lownsbury, Brett Franjella, Toby Bell. That's almost like Tobin Bell.
Vincent Frank's Natalie Hartline, Joseph Ragoza, Steve Burton,
Annie Demario, bow, Aaron Roberts, Scott John, Ben Medi, Kevin Eason,
Rich Tillman, Sarah Catherine, Paul Francis Merchee, Scott Sweeney,
Karak Konini, right? Joshua Taj Bozerman, Chuck Andrews, Neil Dolby, Tom
Lavorick, Tucker Rouch, John Smith, Edmund Agabbo, Andrew Brian Bowlarrier,
Will Helms, Jennifer Anna, Bryce Buckmaster, T. L. Monholin, or is that T .I.
Hi, Monholin. Melissa Alvarez, Jake Bullock, hashtag tangusreligion0foxstraut .com. You
fucks tangusreligion. Anyway, Matt Crawford, Jenis, Jenna, excuse me, Richard Deming, Brian
Calls, Tim Drain, Michael Madrigal, go to Mr. Suit Records when you're in Lancaster, Pennsylvania.
Richard Howanstein,
Bretton Fraser,
Sean Luke Fisziak,
Karen Kilgarif,
listen to our friend,
Karen's wonderful podcast,
my favorite murder.
Tyler Sanderson,
Joey Moller,
Shelby L,
Nathan Baskett,
Gary Myron,
Sairad,
Dylan Larr,
Phil Borrell,
Edmund Dillon,
the Blackmagic Ninja,
Scott Pauline Sirell,
Patrick Baxter,
Stephanie Kellogg,
Ryan Martz,
Tristan Avery,
Henry Hunk Masterson, Richard Ironman, Matthew J. Brown, Julie Aguyer, Charity Ferguson,
Hank Gustafson, Nick Walther, Alex C, Alexander Stein, Tyler Keatley, Emily Marvel, John
B. Wat, thank you John, good buddy of mine, more and go to John's Etsy shop, which I again
have forgotten the goddamn name of, I'm sorry John.
I don't know why I cannot remember it.
Mori Benjamin, Nicholas Burns, Alex Niel Nelson, Jeremy Cool, Derek Clark, Alex Shipley,
Sean Pinnock, Amanda Liebsen, Tom Timothy Letzo, Shane Nazarene, Smelly Bubbles, Samantha
Kiefer, I love you.
I wonder if that's Samantha writing that or somebody saying that to Samantha.
David Bellinger, Hunter McDonnell, Justin Boanger, Adam Benbenek, Mani Rios,
Damani O 'Rubio, Brandon Gash, Jake Farratt, Rob Lines,
didn't, Brandon's one of the artists, right?
You're Mike's not on.
Yes.
He did the little, uh, okay, thank you.
Thank you, Brandon, for the art.
Uh, Pat keeps talking to me when I was Mike's not on.
Jake Farratt, well, just a nod.
God, yes, you know, would have been fine.
Jake Ferret, Rob Lines, Jacob Barrett,
Jordan C. Maxwell, Ashcroft, Ryan Kohler,
Barb Allen, Jonathan Face, Rebecca Cohen,
Chris Pohen, Mike Gibbons,
Donnie Joyce, Michael Dawson, Jennifer Smith,
Connor Denahy, Steven Copa,
Kevin Swistowicz,
Anthony Jake Wohardo, Annie Johanna Sin,
Timmy Kay, Megan Lybrand, Scott Blikkins -Durford,
Alic Walker, Brett Werner, Tristan Carlson, Laura Sexton, Anthony Guajardo,
Western Thomas Veeed Hill, Jared Blair, Josh Smallridge, Richie Verdugo,
Chris Hopper, Emily Griffith, Emily Florence. Thank you, Emily, for all you do.
Sean Al, Dave Comerick, Abby Manuel, Kim DeAngelo, John Galat, Michael McBee,
Stephanie Power, Sterling Abringo,
Juron Sanderson, Diego Campos,
Stefan Masu, I always have trouble with that one.
Sorry, Stefan.
Zoe Blaskovic,
Aasley Kivinsland,
Dan McLeod, Lawrence Bunganiers,
Alejandro Salagato,
Puppas Mouss,
Tracer Reddington,
Sean Thomas, Amanda Alzamora,
Jason Wyble, my Corey Drew Spidler, Andrew Kovale, Sam Mitchell, Aaron Millinowski,
Scott Nolan, Jack Gertz, Ben Misty Zavar, Molly Russell's, Moly Russell's Wart, very
nice.
Dajne Wilford, Johnny Ferg, Matthew Matthias Pegui, now fuck, Matthias Paljo, sorry, all right,
you even put the pronunciation in there.
Michelle Gold, Danielle Doer, Eric Lemora, Steven Reese, Kevin Marseilleck, Lawrence Anderson, Jared Smolridge, Will Potorff, thank you Will for the art, Natalie Craig, Kyle Kinslin, Monty, just gonna leave it at Monty, sorry Monty, I remember you don't like us saying your name.
Ani Babaduk, Scott Patton, August Rydell, Paul Pickler,
Pick Earl, Paul Pickerel, Rage, Last Name, Sounds, Aegean,
Beth Gaston, Julie Bailey, Michael Aiello,
Reed, Estetic, and Max Unwraff.
Guys, we're overwhelmed by the amount of support.
Thank you so much.
So there was a hard seven minutes of eight,
almost eight minutes of shout outs.
Thank you so much.
We'll see you next time.
We'll see you in hell.
I'll see you when I know you're the one who I'll see you when I know you're the one who I'll see you when I know you're the one who I'll see you when I know you're the one who I'll see you when I know you're the one who I'll see you when I know you're the one who I'll see you when I know you're the one who I'll see you when I know you're the one who I'll see you when I know you're the one who I'll see you when I know you're the one who I'll see you when I know you're the one who I'll see you when I know you're the one who I'll see you when I know you're the one who I'll see you when I know you're the one who I'll see you when I know you're the one who I'll see you when I know you're the one who I'll see you when I'll see you when I know you're the one who I'll see you when I know you're the one who I'll