Summer is here, and Bet MGM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bet MGM Casino.
Spin on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Land, Raken
Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Bet MGM game sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal, durable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Monthly 21 -plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gambleer, offer not available in all states
terms apply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
This is a HeadGum podcast.
Hello everybody and welcome to a brand new episode of We'll see you in hell with myself Patrick Walsh and my dear dear friend Joe
Derosa and I guess all intros out of the way. We can get on with the show and while we're at it folks on
Who are the Joe I like that one. It was so dear dog. You didn't scare me. Just was like what's happening over there
It was a soul tree one. How are you wash? I'm doing good
Folks on today's show we're going to talk about the landmark Supreme Court case of Freddie versus Jason that changed the way
Mutants were perceived in society. Yes. Yes. Much like the X -Men films. Yes
You're doing well. I'm doing good, Joe. It's it's it's a nice day. I went I
But I decided, you know, I'm not gonna drink.
You decided the same thing, at least for a month.
Been off a week, it feels fine.
I haven't, you know, I don't have cravings or shakes
or anything like that.
I did find that my weed card was expiring yesterday.
And a little frantically, I called and I said,
if it expires on the 19th,
does that mean you can still take it on the 19th?
Like my voice, quivering with fear.
where she was like, yeah, you can still use it today.
I was in the car like smoke outline of my body
hanging in the air,
drove up to the old green wolf.
And I decided I'm just gonna like blow out
whatever's in my wallet on weed
and then not renew my thing.
Be done with weed forever.
I'll probably weasel my way back into some.
I'm not gonna take a joint to the party or something.
But yeah, just done maybe done with getting like the card.
It's too much access to weed and weed feels too good. I wish I felt that way
I I don't like it as much as you do and I
Really do I haven't smoked it once since the since sobriety. I could do it without drinking and be
Total I'd ride I'd take weed over drinking at this point. I really would that well then you got it figured out
Why do you want to get rid of it? Yeah, you're right because I tend I wind up doing like weed and drinking
Well, if you can just do the weed. I mean God bless you man
That's what I would I mean maybe but I bought a nice amount. I love the people over there at Green Wolf
I'm me too
Wonderful staff. They don't sponsor us, but we'll give them a plug the Green Wolf here in the plus field is area
They do great work. They always throw in a free joint
Yeah, and you know
The world the way it is. I'm not gonna go into this at all
You need it. You need something. I don't do any depressions, you know
I know that's that's my auntie to press and it works well. Yeah. Well, hey, mine was whiskey
and my wife was
frisky, yeah, I do want to say though
Several people because last week I said we know whatever two weeks ago
I said you never hear anyone say boy. I sure enjoy the political discourse on we'll see you in hell
So I got like ten tweets. Yeah, ten Facebook comments that I really enjoy the political discourse. I'm gonna see you know
then I also got this, folks.
I bristle at broad stroke statements like this
that helped get Trump elected.
I laugh out loud, it will see you in hell,
but fast forward through your armchair
political comments.
What are the broad statements
that helped get Trump elected?
Her name is Lynn.
Well, I said at this point,
if you support Trump, you're a racist.
I said it in so many words.
Okay.
On the pod, I think she's referring to,
I also had a tweet that said basically that.
And but she's against Trump yet she thinks you helped get him elected. She's very pro Trump. Oh, she's a little confusing. Oh, well
Lindsey, let's just sum it up now. Go fuck yourself. Fuck you. And if you don't like what we're saying, go fuck yourself. That's exactly right. You know, I did though
I wanted to offer you all of your money back that you've paid us for for doing the show for two years and all these
these episodes and literally days of entertainment.
And I really mean that, Lindsey.
Fuck you.
This isn't like a bantery funny podcast thing.
Go fuck yourself, you're a fucking idiot.
Yeah, I just, actually while Joe was talking there,
I realized you actually haven't given us a fucking dime
and it's our podcast that we do for free to entertain you
and we'll talk about whatever the fuck we want.
Yeah, and by the way, is it not balanced enough
when one of the hosts is going,
Well, I didn't see the clip of him saying denying to do not the KKK so I don't want to make an opinion on that yet
Right, is it not is that not balanced enough that that we're you got one guy saying this is what I saw
Is what I think you got another guy saying I'm only gonna speak as far as I'm educated. I'll tell you what Joe you know
We're doing a movie podcast. We don't have to be balanced to anything. No, we're not we're not CNN fake news
You fake news
We're a fucking movie pod. Yeah, we're talking about whatever the hell we want to
I was watching the golden free entertainment. Yeah, free entertainment. I was watching the golden girls today
Yeah, this is what Twitter has done. I'm so glad you brought that up because I didn't see that tweet
That this was just went to me. Okay, this is what Twitter has done. This is what social media in the internet has done
So he had two followers by the way.
These fucking morons that live in this goddamn country.
Other countries are using it to have a revolution.
This fucking idiotic country.
This is what people are using it for.
And this is the problem.
I'm watching the Golden Girls today, and they're talking about...
That's not like a problem to me.
Wow, it was wonderful.
They're talking about it's during the potential nuclear war crisis when Reagan was president.
Yeah.
Because this is the first time there's ever been talk of nukes.
So everybody freak out because it's never happened before you fucking baby children
Anyway
They're talking about the nukes and roses like I'm very upset. I know I'm very afraid of nuclear weapons
And they're like well, what are you gonna do? Like it's you know, it's hopefully nothing happens
But and then rosas I'm gonna write a letter to the president and dart these like you can't be serious rose, right?
Yeah, this is how much
people's brains.
That could not be on television today.
Yeah, there's so much people's brains have changed.
People now literally think, well, I'm gonna tweet it,
Trump and Tom, what I think, or I'm gonna tweet it,
no bottom of town, what I think.
Well, then they get blocked by them, they get all excited
and it's like, he did say it, and not just some advisor
who's combing through tweets.
It's just, it's so crazy.
It's like, it's, so, so.
What's like the guy who puts like, you know,
hey, hey, date me, you know, in the comments
of Rihanna's Instagram, we're like,
Eight million people are liking each photo exactly. He throws his hat in the ring or the guy who comments on porn
Exactly. What are you doing exactly stop it? Yeah, these you don't have to let people know you're watching porn these hard -on guys
That right to yourself that right to like they do it to like female comics a lot though like right to them and be like
I saw your act and I just want to say you are beautiful
Yeah, and I would marry you and then these these women have to write back and be like you fucking idiot
it. It's my goddamn stand -up. I'm not standing on the ledge of a building. Yeah.
But go fuck yourselves. Everybody can suck my dick. Yeah. They could. You know the
that that even existed. Or do you mean beyond the sea, the Kevin Spacey starring as Bobby
Darren biopic. Now did you see that flick? I saw 10 minutes of it. I couldn't believe
it was a shit show. Yeah. And I like Kevin Spacey with god damn it was bad. Okay, hold on.
He can he can do one thing great. And then when he goes outside of it, yikes. By the seaside
here it is. Never heard it. Where's this going? Folks, I'm sorry. Okay. So my new thing
now, because that's the, that ringtone is my alarm clock in the morning. Yeah. So that
That goes off and I wake up and immediately start singing to it, fuck the world, the world
can suck my fucking dick, fuck the world, the world can need to bag a shit, fuck the world
inside its ass, that's how the day starts.
So how much more time you got, you think?
On the planet?
Yeah.
I'm gonna outlast all these fucking pussy.
All right.
Everybody's freaking out, everybody's freaking out.
Sure.
I'm not happy was what's going on, but I'm not gonna freak out about it
I'm gonna be the guy with the sharpen stick in the dark. We know it all goes down
You're not gonna get me it's going down. It's going right down
But let's get off it for for Barbara whatever the fuck her name was let's get
Let's talk about what Barbara wants to talk about Barbara
We don't accept your letters. We don't even even Barbara. I don't know what it was
I don't remember what it was, but Barbara seems like a good name. She tweets it only us and Adam Karola
Somebody wrote to me, though, too, that was like, oh, blah, blah, blah, please get past the political
crowd. I saw a few of them. We shouldn't just be beating up on Barbara, who's not
definitely one of them. And this one was a guy. So this was a dumb dickhead. Yeah.
The dumb dick. Well, I guess a woman, anybody could be a dickhead these days.
I don't mean to gender discriminate. No, I mean, that's kind of the beautiful thing about America.
You can talk about whatever the fuck you want, and then you can also not listen to it.
These fucking people.
You can also just not listen to it.
This goddamn world we live in doesn't change my pocket book, Annie.
This goddamn world we live in, everything is just, everything is do it for me.
I'm talking to this lady at the bank today.
There's your first mistake.
Well, I because because I got a fraudulent alert. I got a fraud hold put on my debit card because I tried to take money out of an ATM in the city
I live in right so I call and I'm like lift the fraud alert. Why is it going off? What are you talking about? Yeah, and
And she goes and really sorry I'm going to file a complaint for you. I said thank you. It's very helpful and then like any time
You talked to somebody in customer service. She goes we're gonna send a survey if you could send it no
Oh, your boss's fucking job is to monitor what kind of work you do.
It's not my fucking job.
That's, I had never thought of it that way, but that's true.
God damn it.
I started down, I had a real helpful woman the other day
and I was like, yeah, I'll do this survey.
I'm talking five minutes later.
I'm on question 26, like, well now I'm out.
Just say, was she good?
Yes, no, I've got a life.
Yeah, it's crazy.
Trying to throw you a bone, but Jesus Christ. I'm giving these horrible lift drivers five stars just because I'm
Scared about them shooting back with a zero point zero. Oh, that's well. That's how they get you
It's black beer. It's black beer. You got a rating on you. I got one on me. Let's fucking deal
Yeah, that's the problem with politics. I got to get my bill passed. You got to get your bill passed
I hate you you hate me. Let's fucking deal
This world is bullshit, and it's
Inhabited by shit people that do nothing except spew and suck shit all day long. Yeah, and it's not my fault. I didn't do it
I didn't do it either. I didn't say you did. I'll tell you that much
I know con here the dog asleep just amassing
In I'm in a game stop level inventory of
video games at this point because I don't want to leave the fucking house anymore.
You don't have to leave the house, that's the beauty, that's the beauty, that is the true
beauty of America.
You don't have to leave the house.
Last day checked I couldn't bang my blu -ray player.
You probably could.
Paying on what you're working on.
be a sad state if your penis is sitting that little slot.
Folks, let's get to Pat's movie corner.
Let's get to Pat's movie corner.
I want to, again, kind of go to the past, I haven't really seen any new ones.
It's shine a light on an old romantic comedy called My Best Friend's Wedding.
It's really.
I watched it the other night.
I brought up at work the other day.
I remembered at the height of like Tarantino Mania, and I was so amped up about Jackie Brown
that year.
I saw it on Christmas Day, I remember.
And that night I think Quentin Tarantino was on Charlie Rose, and Charlie Rose asked him
what his favorite movie the year was
and he blurted back my best friend's wedding.
And he goes, I think that to me
and like maybe bringing up baby
are two of the finest romantic comedies I've ever made.
I think it immediately goes on.
And I remember this interview
and I was just talking about it for whatever reason.
So it was on TV, it's the 20th anniversary.
I watch it.
Everybody in this fucking movie is a sociopath.
Have you seen this movie?
No, right.
I mean, it plays like a no -laff track sign fell.
She, well, first off, she's 28.
She promised her best friend that if they weren't married by 28, they'd marry each other.
This is Julia Roberts.
Julia Roberts.
Is this the movie where the trailer ended with her in the ballpark going, I got moves.
You don't even know about holding the hot dog.
Oh, that's...
What is that?
Oh, something to talk about?
Oh, yeah, that's well that belongs in that movie. It's a little sassy. No
She's a complete hateful sociopath that you want to die throughout this movie. She's so awful and
So her friend, you know, does Dermot Moroni, and he comes in, and he's like, hey, I gotta tell you I am getting married
So she's like, oh fuck so the whole rest movie is her trying to destroy their engagement
And it's played by a 20 -year -old Cameron Diaz in her prime who was like really funny and really good and lovable in this movie
She's the only decent human being
Because behind her back this sweet girl has Robertson and Moroni like walking in on each other naked flirting kissing
Talking about all memories of their old sex life together on and on and on and me when we got old Cameron Diaz
He has just planted a wedding.
All excited to be getting married.
So Roberts is trying to sabotage it to the extent
that Camardia has a severe fear of karaoke.
She takes them to a karaoke bar.
She forces her to sing.
She has a horrific voice.
This is the best scene of the movie.
Camardia has plays it really well.
She's embarrassed and they're booing her.
But then she's so charming that she wins them over.
And Julia Roberts is like embarrassed
because now people only love her more.
It's a really good scene.
All right.
right? But then things get to a place where Julia Roberts is sending emails to German
Moroni's employers to fuck up his job situation. She's counseling, uh, can't, can't
me Diaz, as James Lipto would say, she's counseling her to give Moroni an ultimatum because
she knows that Moroni hates ultimatums. So he does this, she does this in front of Julia
Robert's who's like all but cackling in the corner as she shatters this beautiful young
couple's engagement. That's terrible. For her own benefit. That's terrible. It's sick. It's a sick
film. Yeah. It's when we made like $200 million. I saw it in theaters when it came out. Yeah.
I don't know how I thought any of this behavior was normal. Did you like it when it came out?
I did. I liked it a lot. I saw it in like a first date. Young girl with the last name of powderly.
Powerfully?
I don't think of Julia Roberts in like that,
she's the villain of it.
But she's the good guy though.
You're supposed to look at her as the good guy.
Or no.
Oh yeah, no.
I don't understand.
I think, why wouldn't they make,
I think under the lens of 1997 when it came out,
I think you were supposed to view her
as the hero would be on her side.
Why wouldn't they just make Cameron Diaz's
because Diaz wasn't big at the time?
But no, why wouldn't they make her unlikable?
So then you're rooting for Julia.
I don't understand why you're saying.
I mean, Diaz could sack up a little bit.
She's like willing to give up her life for her man
a little bit too much, whatever.
They give her some flaws.
But really, she's just a kind innocent person
who's just having her life walked all over
by this, frankly, a sociopath.
Well, who shows no remorse, no emotions.
There was three lines from a young Paul Giamatti.
Always great to see you in a 90s movie.
What, who did he play in it?
Some bell hop.
Oh, okay, yeah.
She's smoking in the hallway and he's like,
Yeah, she's not smoking all the way.
That's my Paul Juma and she's like,
you smoke and they share a nice cigarette moment together.
Okay.
But I think very next year he was a negotiator.
That's where I first remembered him
and then I saw him in private parts of course.
Yeah.
Private parts was same year, 97.
So yeah, same year he was pig vomit.
He was in that best friend's wedding if I'm not mistaken.
I'm a private part so much.
It's the greatest.
It's a really wonderful film.
It's the, it's the, it's the, well, the, the third act of G,
I wish the third act would, they may,
I wish they made a whole movie of the Geomatic character.
Yeah, oh, I agree.
I watched, I watched a weekly series of that.
Yeah, yeah, so I saw, I also shine a light on a movie
that I've already seen that I re -watched
and I just find it to be a wonderful film.
It did not get the credit.
I feel that it deserved, okay.
from critics, but the movie is God's pocket, say, oh, no, I didn't say it. Never saw it.
Starring the late Philip Seymour Hoffman, the great John Totoro, they play two, you know,
sort of knock around guys, hustlers, whatever. Philip Seymour Hoffman is married to the,
I can never remember any of them. Someone far more attractive than him, I'm sure. It's, it's, it's,
It's not even close, it's, it's, it's, it's the, like, the, like, in, uh, um, for the
devil knows your dad, where he's fucking Tomey at the beginning, Tomey in her prime,
him and his auntie, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's insane.
This is even crazier, because it's the lady from Mad Men, uh, Hendrix.
Yes.
Christina Hendrix.
Yeah.
Like the most striking woman to ever walk the planet, and who's also like 31 or 29 or something
when they shot this thing, he looks like he looks like he's pushing 60, but they're all
great in it.
What's his face is in it too.
Another guy whose name I always forget, the Bongo guy, the movie about the Bongo's were
nominated for the Oscar, the Bongo's, the drums, the movie about the where he played Whiplash.
No.
The guy that made the station agent, his father movie was about the guy that started Oh yeah
Richard Jenkins.
the visitor. Yeah, Richard Jenkins. Yeah. The visitor. Yeah, which is a terrifying name for a film
that's supposed to be that heartfelt. Right. It doesn't sound pleasant movie. Anyway, he's in it.
He plays a drunk that writes about the town God's pocket. It's based on a neighborhood in Philadelphia
called Devil's Pocket. But you know, super blue collar opening one of the opening lines of the movies,
these, the movie is the people of this town can forgive anything except for not being
from God's pocket. That, of course, plays a role significantly or ultimately. You know,
it's not a crazy story. Christina Hendrix sun dies if it's Philip Seymour Hoffman's step
sun. And you know, it kind of goes from there. And the sun is played by that kid on Twin Peaks
who I have never seen play a decent human being. The guy who like beats up the giant woman
in her trailer. No, the guy that's married to the girl from Mama Mia, who's like the
co -kid. I can't remember any of his names anymore. The girl from Mama Mia though, I mean,
oh, sea freed. Yeah. Amanda sea freed. Yes. Her husband. Okay. He's like the horrible,
hard co -kid. Yeah. It's him. He's also the brother and get out. Yes. Who I can't contain
his racism look enough to pull the scheme off track. Yeah. Yeah. I mean, he just plays a piece.
I gotta see the movie again. A piece of shit in this movie. Okay. Like, I'm talking makes,
makes the get out guy. Almost looked tolerable. All right. I'm gonna watch it. Like, you know,
let me see like an anti -semite. He's just, he's just a horrific racist drug addict. Okay.
horrible like waste of a human being in this movie. He's horrible. Okay. Um, I'll check.
So yeah, but, uh, but it's, it's a really great flick and, uh, critics kind of panned it,
but I thought it was really great. Uh, it's heartbreaking. It's also very, very funny many times.
And a friend of mine, Carmine is in it, uh, and he's very funny in it. And, uh, yeah. So check
that, uh, I'm going to watch it. And I think I got us advanced tickets to see it up at Warner Brothers.
Shut up.
I think we're gonna get in this week.
This week?
That's what it looks like.
Don't tease me.
I'm not confirming, but it could happen.
Don't tease me, baby.
You're saying this Mr. Mercedes show is pretty good.
Yeah, we talked, we touched on a little bit last week.
I had not read Mr. Mercedes,
I own it and haven't gotten around to it.
So I thought maybe I'd do the thing
like I did in high school where I tried to read the stand
before the CBS miniseries started right then just want to watching the movie
Movie almost almost as long as the book. I know yeah, so that's what I do with mr. Mercedes
I started it. I was into it and then I was like oh watch the movie, but Brendan Gleason is awesome in it
The guy whoever's playing the the killer is awesome in it, but this thing starts
with a guy who lives in his basement and is
Definitely like having an incestuous relationship with his mom
They're actually hooking up or he just wants to have sex.
He's like staring at her crotch.
They kiss.
Okay.
He jacks off after they have a conversation.
But you assume something has happened at some point.
You know, it's like it's like heat.
They show you his side.
They show you the cops side.
The cops retired.
Gleason is awesome.
I thought this was about a car salesman this show.
No.
Well, at the beginning, the reason for the title is he drives a Mercedes into a large
rally of people and I cannot believe that they didn't immediately in the
stand -age pull that show right off the air. Well usually that's what they do. I
can tell you I didn't just have to show I audition I didn't get it I auditioned
for it well over a year ago. Do you know what the part was? I auditioned to play the
boss at the electronics oh yeah well the guy who's in it is really good and they
told me I was too like flippant. Oh just how I thought it should be. Yeah you know
I thought it should be a prick and they're like bring it down a little bit and I did it
But I didn't think I don't know. Maybe it just wasn't right for it. Anyway
Stephen King himself said to me you're too flippant really no
Well, I thought maybe you got that far on the audition, brother. I don't think he is any part of the audition
Sometimes he's an AP on these projects. He wants to make sure they get it done, right?
Do you got anything else that you've seen?
Well, I
I guess, you know, I know we have a lot of crossover in our audience for this, but I've watched now all of Rick and Morty, and I just kind of don't know what I'm missing, but I know it's very smart.
It looks awesome, and that should be enough, but I think it had just been hyped to the extent where I'm just, I'm never laughing at it, I'm always saying, that's really clever, that's really smart. Have you seen the show?
know, I haven't, but I feel that way with every, I'm going to say something very controversial
right now.
I feel that way about every single animated adult comedy I have ever seen, including The
Simpsons.
I watch it.
I'll show you some substance.
Look, I'm not saying I've never laughed out loud in any of it, but I watch it.
I go, most of the time I go, that's a very well written joke.
That's interesting, but it does not engage me in a way.
it's never going to pull me in the way like trading places does where I'm so
into it and I'm laughing hysterically it's just I'm just not going to invest in it
the same and it's something about the animation I love dramatic animated stuff I
don't really like comedic animated stuff I can see that I guess other than
Simpsons and South Park I never really got into anything either but there I mean
there are 10 years of the Simpsons that I would put up with anything in comedy and I'm
I'm not saying, certainly the early days of South Park
before I got tired.
I'm not saying you're wrong.
Some of the episodes, how, at that fucking show.
Some of the episodes of South Park are some
of the most brilliant things I've ever seen,
but it's still never made me go,
well, I want to keep watching.
Okay, that's fair, that's fair.
I just don't like cartoons that much.
I agree with you on that.
I mean, I don't, even the Pixar as I'm always kind of like this.
Oh God, those could never be made again.
I wouldn't give a shit.
Yeah.
People really lose their shit over them.
Yeah, I know.
Let me tell you what they look they look amazing, but I'm always like I'm a one and done
I'm like that looked incredible. I'm glad I saw it whatever, but let me tell you about the day
I was in an office space in LA. Okay, and
Five grown people in their thirties
We're going. Oh my god. You saw inside out. Don't no spoilers. No spoilers
That's the town we live in
Anyway, well, let's get to the film at hand
Oh one more thing. Yeah, I don't really have anything else, but I will just a quick Joe scary stuff
I did receive the creep show double vinyl. I can't urge you enough to go buy it
It is fucking beautiful. They it is a stunning piece of work. All right every horror fan, especially if you're a fan of creep show
Two should own this. It's just a really really really beautifully produced piece of work
So check that out because I mentioned it last week, but I hadn't received it yet
And now yeah, I don't have anything for scary stuff. That's all right. Uh, movie at hand.
Freddie versus Jason. We both be at clawed hand. We've already watched it today. Yeah, we
I'm about to open something on my Blu -ray shelf,
my DVD shelf, especially in my Criterions.
I go, you know what, I better make sure
this thing hasn't gone out of print,
especially because Blu -rays,
I would say lightly endangered, you know, at this point.
So I have a big Blu -ray collection
and Joe goes, you wanna do Friday versus Jason,
I say, sure, I've got this,
thing I got for $50 at the Warner Brothers store,
collection of all the Jason movies
Plus the remake of Friday the 13th plus Freddie verse Jason plus a huge bonus disc with like documentaries and shit on it
Got it for like 50 bucks. So I grab it off the wall absom mindedly rip into it throw Freddie versus Jason into the thing
I've had this for like three years. Right. I know I'm not a big fan of the franchise frankly
And right after I do it something kind of just bothers me in my stomach. I hop online. I check it's going for $800
$400.
Oh, $800 new.
Oh, you hate to hear that.
I like new, it's, you know, $250, you hate to hear that.
I just, what I have gotten it, maybe not.
I just made it happen to me today.
I got a copy of the Colcheck, the Night Stalker,
and Night Strangler Double Feature DVD at Amoeba Records.
Yeah.
Now, granted it was used, but I got it for $18 .99
and starting price for it used online
was like $32 or something.
Hello.
So you're not not quite an eight -year -old Mr. Profit
But
Did you now just overall did you enjoy the film?
What film Freddie versus Jason Freddie versus
Jesus Christ
Well, we've talked about a lot of stuff on the show Joe. Look I
Didn't I mean it's not a good movie and in fact I would actually call it a bad
movie. Um, they keep them apart for most of the running time. And then basically the climax
is two of history's greatest monsters punching each other on a dock. I think that's the
climax of. I think you're over simplifying, but, but we can get into all this. All right.
I will say this. The first time I saw the film, I hated it. I love the nudity at the beginning.
What does it even do for a man who's dead inside anymore? I mean, it still gave me a little rush.
uh, little jolt. The uh, the, in my pants, I hated it. When I saw, I saw an opening day
in the theater with Big J. Oakerson. We were on the road together and we went to see it and
we said, we know this is going to suck. Yeah. But we love the film. We love these characters.
Yeah, I would have thought you'd be skipping into that theater. Like, yeah, well, here's the thing.
My hero. I half was. Here's the reason I was, was, uh, was very hesitant. Yes. Now, first of all,
You gotta remember this people, Freda versus Jason,
that was like insane that that happened.
Like that was a thing they talked about for years.
They, they, it was never gonna happen.
These, you know, nowadays properties are get traded
and you know, Spider -Man shows up in the Marvel movies,
owned by Disney even though he's owned by Sony
and all that shit.
The nutty professor pops up in the dark night.
It's like, what's going on?
Yeah, yeah.
You know, you got ready player one coming out
with like every fucking pop culture character ever in it.
Wreck at Ralph, for example.
I almost called it Wright said Fred.
Wright said Fred.
Uh, yeah.
So, so, but when this came out, this was like a pretty big deal.
And I said, I got to see this, I can't wait.
And then I saw an interview with Kelly Rowland from Destiny's Child, who's one of the stars
of the film.
Yeah.
And where were the only time I ever saw her in a film?
Maybe like an urban legends, too, or something.
Yeah, yeah.
her one quote in the interview was this was the sound bite you you're all
you're all gonna love this film it's amazing and I said okay and she went
there's a great scene we're Freddie and I get into a fight and it's hilarious
and I thought well there that's ruined it'll be the worst movie of all time well
you're not you're not too far off I mean not only do they fight but the fight starts
with Kelly Rowland referring to Freddie as the F homosexual slur that starts with F.
Oh, you're skipping a beat. I fell off the couch, frankly, to see a member of Destiny's
Child called Freddie Krueger, the most hateful gay slur there is. Before that, Freddie turns
to her and says, how sweet, dark meat.
Yeah.
So he's throwing a little race play her way.
Hits her with a racist joke.
Yeah.
She gets him with an anti -Semitic.
Then she does this whole analogy about how his claws
are making up for his dick.
Yeah.
And then she immediately contradicts.
She goes, Jason has this big old hatchet
and you have these tiny little butter knives.
Right.
And it's like, that doesn't make sense with the dick thing.
No.
The knives would be really long.
She's like, yeah, can I talk about the butter knives?
Can I talk about the butter knives?
Like, she's roasting Freddy.
Yeah, she really goes into like a Wendy William style
like dress down of Freddy.
It's terrible.
What kind of F?
Where's a Christmas sweater?
I bet that got a big laugh.
You see that in Philadelphia?
I bet that got a big laugh up in South Jersey.
Oh, okay.
It didn't get a big laugh.
We went to the 3 .30 p .m. showing.
There were about six of us in there.
Six people in sweatpants.
Now here's the thing.
So, I didn't like the film when I saw it in theater,
but then I bought it.
There were things I liked about the film initially
in the theater.
Now, right there, I didn't like when I saw it in theater,
but then I bought it.
Why would you buy it?
Because I'll tell you why.
There were some things I initially like
that I did like in the theater when I saw it.
They had a lot of nods to the Nightmare and Amstrey
franchise that I like.
I liked it.
They brought back the goats, the goats in the sheep
or the animals in part one and Tina's dream.
The snakes are part of the Freddie dreams in the first one.
the hip -na -cils from part three, the clinic, the kids are inners from part three.
The potato sack, they throw over Jason's head in the flashback, he wears the potato
sack in front of the 13th part two.
There were some really, really cool nods where I thought this guy kind of knows what he's
doing, like I don't know, maybe I'm missing this.
So eventually when I started really collecting DVDs and Blu -ray and whatnot, I had obtained
every Freddy movie including the remake which we'll get to and I said well
I'm not gonna not have Freddy versus Jason so I bought it it was like four bucks
right and the first thing I did when I came home was I watched the bonus
features and the first thing that the director said in the bonus features is I
wanted to do a throwback to a King Kong versus Godzilla the great monster fight
movies of the 1960s. And I said, okay, now I will rewatch it through that lens. And honestly,
it made it a lot better. I liked it more. All right. I liked it more. So now when I
want, I know it's not great, but there are, there are some great things. Look, first of all,
I love how reprehensible they make so many of the characters because they're all terrible.
You're cheering when they get killed. I mean, the one kid is going to try to fuck the girl when she's
unconscious. And he gets stabbed like through the, you're like cheering that Jason kills the guy,
you know, that rave was cracking me up that rave the mole of the cornfield. Yeah. Yeah.
It was like, come on guys. I enjoy that. Could somebody be drinking or I image look like
the most Disney channel rave. Oh, they were all drinking. They're all drinking beers and
it just seemed very tame. The kid even says this, this ever clears kick in my ass.
They're smoking weed. What are you talking about? It felt very tame to me. Well, it looked like a fake corn
I like it and blade when they go in and somebody's getting fisted in the corner
I like a club and then the sprinklers rain blood down. Yeah, exactly
I find that cornfield scene to I'm glad you brought it up
It is one of my favorite horror movies. It's my favorite. What's going on? Are you about to praise this is one of your favorite?
No, I'm just
I got to know it's here and I'm reading them.
That is my favorite Jason sequence I've ever seen.
Like, there's nothing better than,
I mean, for Christ's sakes, it starts with Jason
being lit on fire and a flaming Jason
walking through rows of corn, of the cornfield
and then just going crazy with a fucking hatchet
on people or machete.
It's an awesome setting for Jason.
All right.
For Jason movie.
So I like that.
I think the movie had some of the best Jason kills.
I thought the craftmatic bed folded in half with the kids folded inside of it was great
As our friend Jim Pinkstone pointed out to me recently when Jason is getting electrocuted
Yeah, and he just grabs a person next to him because his whole mentality is how do I just kill somebody immediately who's near me that's a great kill
That being said
Just some of the lowest points for Freddy's
I mean, I mean, I don't even know where to start.
For me, when the guy's standing in the blood,
kind of a cool scene when he sees his brother
who commits suicide in the blood in the bathtub,
kind of a cool scene.
You know, that's Scott Farcus from a Christmas story?
Yes, I did.
I'm gonna tell by on site.
And how sometimes he looks,
he plays the oldest kid in the Christmas story.
Suddenly, he looks like he's 29 still.
Yeah, yeah.
It's insane.
Anyway, sorry.
But Friday's entire like set piece for that room
is to have five like strands of blood
in circle his feet. That was one of the lamest things I've ever seen.
It would just be like worms or something. It was pathetic, Joe.
Well, it looked shitty. It was bad CG. There's a lot of bad CG.
Movies from like 83 in that franchise look better than this.
Yeah, because they use practical effects. They use a lot of bad CG in the movie.
I agree. My, here are my Freddie low points because I've got a list.
Okay. The pot worm. Oh, Joe.
I thought I was still higher from the night before watching that shit. That was embarrassing.
The pot worm is terrible. He breathes weed into the kids. I guess that somebody must have
said, look, who do you think's really going to a movie called Freddie verse Jason Stoners?
They want to see themselves on screen. Maybe. I guess that had to have been like a new line,
you know, sort of pitch. Dark meat we already mentioned. Opening monologue is great until
really goes being dead. It's one thing. But then they forgot about me. And that's a bitch.
Yeah. Come on, guys. Yeah. He's calling everybody a bitch in the movie. And it's kind
of a sunset boulevard story. He says bitch a lot, which is one of the funny jokes. Apparently
that again, Pinkstone told me about it that they did an episode of Rick and Morty with
because I went to Hollywood,
horror nights at Universal Studios,
and I went through the Freddie versus Jason Haunted House.
And at one point, you hear Freddie say,
welcome to my nightmare, bitch.
I'm like, they can't even stop him from saying it
in the Universal Studios Haunted House, right?
No, I need to say bitch.
Wait, oh, and then the lowest of all the scenes
in Freddie's entire career is him
crotch thrusting Jason around the boiler room as pinball noises are happening.
Yeah, I couldn't believe my eyes.
And then Jason falls and he goes, tilt, what the fuck?
And this is what made me so mad.
That was pretty, pretty nuts.
This is what made me tilt.
So mad when so many nightmare fans were like, that fucking remade sucked.
And it's like, did it suck?
They made Freddie kind of scary again.
Okay, it wasn't a great flick, but Jesus Christ, don't you prefer that to the pinball
gag. Anyway, do you like both the nightmare remake and the
Friday 13th remake, right? I like them both fine. I find them
entertaining. I know they're not as good as the originals, but
but you know, they're fine. You know, I've only seen Friday 13th
one and Freddie versus Jason. That's it. And I've seen all the
Fred is the Friday the 13th remake has the best Jason kill ever ever in it all right next to Jason
X Jason X there's a scene where he dumps a lady's head into liquid nitrogen her whole head freezes
then he smashes it on a table and it turns into blood slushy that's a pretty fantastic kill
uh and he wrote Jason X has like this big article going around for years about how he lives in his car
that was his one.
It's not a great movie.
Hey, it was one shot.
He's just like, it's cautionary tale.
But I did enjoy the film.
And then in Jason, in the Fred 13th remake,
right at the top, he put some kid in like a sleeping bag
and then just hangs it over a fire.
Okay. Good, pretty dark.
But there was a look.
Look, there was some amazing...
That was the other thing too with this.
Well, we're on Jason.
and uh, there's a, I went on Wikipedia to read about it, they recast Jason, it's not
Toby Hooper. Right. Well, it was never Toby Hooper. I mean, not sorry, it wasn't
Kane Hodder. Excuse me. It's Tobay Hooper. Where is the Tobay Hooper? But the directors' justification
for a needing, because there was a lot of backlash from fans. They're like, who line
blams on the director? The director blams it on new line. Yeah. Who's lying? They're all
line. They're all one. But the director's quote was, I wanted a slower Jason. Yeah.
Well, why don't you just tell K -100 to walk slow? A little slower. Yeah. Yeah. I will give
this to the actor that played Jason. It is the only Friday the 13th I've ever seen, where
I feel you feel sorry for Jason a little bit. He is. Oh, I was totally rooting for Jason.
Yeah. He's the King Kong of it. You know, he's the King Kong. You feel bad for him. So
And it does almost the same thing if I remember correctly as alien versus predator where it's like one has one but then the other one like shows like, no, I'm still here the what is it Freddie Winx?
You know, Jason's holding his head and Freddie Winx fucking ending. And then I think the ending of the first alien versus predator, which was almost unwatchable was that the alien had won but then the predator like
like shows that he's still alive.
I think they did the same exact thing.
I honestly don't remember.
But they never did Freddie Verse Jason too,
even though this made a ton of money,
why do you think that is?
Cause this was supposed to be the end.
This was supposed to be,
let's never stop them before.
I think this was really supposed to be the end.
After the final nightmare and the final Friday,
I think this really was supposed to be like,
you know, we're able to,
we've somehow worked this all out
and we're gonna do this once.
I mean, but here's the thing, it's like, I'm glad there wasn't a sequel and this is why
the wink pisses me off so much.
And this is why the fight at the end of the movie makes no fucking sense.
The fight makes sense when Jason's in Freddie's, when Freddie's in Jason's nightmare because
Freddie is all powerful in the dream world.
When Freddie gets pulled out into the real world, guess what?
He's just a regular guy.
So how was he able to go up against this superhuman guy?
Jason would kill him in two seconds flat.
Not to mention his body is decayed from being burned
To God knows what I yeah, so that bugs me it bugs me at the end that Freddie brings
Because Freddie's not immortal Freddie's immortal in after death. He's not immortal in the real world
The whole thing is you pull him in the real world. He dies
So that bothers me that they just kind of spit in the face of the of the
Logic if you will
Of the nightmare in Elm Street franchise
Guys, here's another thing that bothered me.
The Goddamn soundtrack.
Oh, yeah, well, that was a period of 10 years
where everything was like, ooh, uh, uh, uh.
That song was in every one of these fucking horror movies,
disturbed or the sickness or whatever it was.
Well, it's that stuff, it's the shitty metal songs,
but then it's also the fucking,
like, don't put a Goddamn John Williams orchestra
behind every like, suspenseful Freddy chase.
Yeah, it ruins it. Yeah, like leave some quiet. It's not scary when there's a fucking string section every three seconds, you know, yeah
That all being said I will give some nods to what I'd liked about the film
And tell me if you agree chose really going to the like book report mode with us thing. Well, I wanted to be prepared
Pros and cons
I thought there were some amazing amazing visuals in the film that were truly creepy the kids in the commas
The coma kids with their eyes covered that was really creepy
Flaming Jason Erdy mentioned I like to recommend the song coma girl by Joe Strummer and the mescaleros
That's my spit scary stuff coma girl. It's a great song. Joe Strummer lead singer of the clash
I also had a fine solo career not enough people know about check it out
The entire opening sequence is quite enjoyable except for the bitch line
It's fun seeing the the Freddy backstory and stuff. Yeah, it's very well shot. I like seeing all the like the best of hits
Have you seen like Maris is amazing yeah when he's like walking to that cabin dragging the body right and then he opens the door
And there's the body's floating that and then Freddie jumping out of the lake. That was cool looks really cool
And then they kind of made him look like Freddie from new nightmares
That was yet another nod to the series which I liked so that those were very very cool visuals
And then also the mouth -to -mouth scene is fantastic
Yeah, when Kelly Rollin, I was almost as if ripped out about the Jason. It's so disgusting. And then he just like
Yeah fucking comes awake and the van crashes. That's a really cool fun. See
What's up? I mean, no, no, nothing. It's
It is what it is. It's not great. Certainly. I think we're both agreeing Joe liked it more than I did
But neither of these franchises are ones I'm obsessed with you know I
Like them, but I went and looked up
Yeah, the cast of the film sure as you don't see them in a ton of other stuff
I looked up a few of them. It was a very busty collection. Uh, did you look up that lead actress Dina something? I sure did
I mean talk about ziggin when you should have zagged
It's a girl in a movie with oh no playing with she's a movie Jason Ritter plays the male lead in this movie. Yeah
Certainly a dashing fine young man
I'm sure this girl's fucking striking. She's a great actress. You know, she's got personality.
I'm sure she had more than a shot with Jason Ritter.
Didn't hook up with him apparently or at least as far as I know.
Followed this up with a film, Night of the Demon's Remake,
whereas Directive Video, I believe it came after Freddie versus Jason
and chose to get hunker down with Eddie Furlong.
Oh, she's married to Eddie Furlong.
Well, they were dating.
He was arrested three times for domestic abuse.
Oh boy.
And then I found an article that said,
she broke her own restraining order
to have lunch with Eddie Furlong
and there's all these pictures of them together.
And they both look like, they said in the article,
she's 34 years old, she looks like she's coming
around the bend of a 54 year old. Like she looks like Mickey work would have hit on her in bar
fly. I mean, it is rough stuff. Yeah. And I'm not trying to kick her when she's down, but like,
you think like, I realize that's kind of what I'm doing. She's like clearly. Yeah, there was it's
it was very sad because you're like, here's this girl. It was like had such a promising career.
And it's sad with any fur long too. It was really fucking talented, man. Yeah. And they both look like,
Yeah, they got the bags under the eyes like something something's going on there. Yeah, something's going on there here
Talk to I'll look up the picture. Keep talking. All right. What's your name Monica Keena? Oh, yeah, I thought it was what is he Zina?
I think he said Zina
They had a guy Lachlan Monroe everybody thought was gonna be the next big comedy star play the guy that plays the sheriff
You know, he was in like dead man on campus and said they really tried to force him as like a Ryan Reynolds for a few years
and it didn't quite materialize.
You got me.
Yeah, the dad trying to kiss her moment
was kind of effective, creepy.
You know, when Freddie and Habits were dead,
all the dad's stuff was kind of creepy.
Here we go, there's a picture.
All right, you can still hook up with that woman.
That's you would.
That's another, that's like another Nick Stall situation.
Yeah, where it's like it's sad, man, people this town a lot of people can't take it
Sometimes they had a snapshot of Eddie for like fixing your hand
All right, this is bringing me down. Yeah, that's my favorite wood
Where he's like come for something has happened. He's come for the year. He's he went too far
And he's in it during a diner by the way, right? So two of the two kids started it looks like
Look final scene of Buffalo 66
Yeah, in the end of the article, wait, wait a second, all that, in the end of the article,
they say, got somewhere to be, Eddie, because they have several shots of him racing from
the front door to his car, he's several shots of him running.
Yeah.
All right, all right, that was a lot, a lot for me to say.
Yeah, sorry.
Anyway, so that's Freddie versus Jason, you know, it was Eddie for long versus Freddie versus Jason pretty good in my book.
Not great. Very flawed, but a fun Saturday afternoon movie. That's my final, yeah, consensus.
I guess that now, Joe, before we leave, if you could have any two characters movie history, Duke it out, who would you pick?
I already had it. It was Batman versus Superman. Oh, Christ.
All right, I'm moving on.
No, what would yours be?
Oh, I don't know.
I'll tell you, I think it was Bruce,
was it Bruce Willis?
No, it wasn't Bruce Willis, it was Kurt Russell.
Okay.
Said recently he goes, you know,
I tried to pitch the Avengers in the 80s
with like action heroes.
Oh nice.
Where it would be like all of our characters.
And he, I guess basically would have been like,
like Snake Pliskin, the Terminator fucking Rocky or Rambo.
Yeah, Rambo, and I was like, that sounds fucking awesome.
Why don't they do that?
Well, that was kind of what the...
Expandable.
Expandables was.
Yeah, yeah.
But, but I don't know.
He was like, yeah, nobody thought anybody wanted
to see that crap.
Now it's huge, yeah, whatever.
Well, hopefully they get it on board.
When did he want to do this, like the 80s?
Yeah, like the late 80s.
And instead they all just got together and opened a planet Hollywood.
Yeah. Yeah. And John Balky's jacket from his set up.
Perfect strangers. Well, John Goodman and Dan Ackroy played the real
first brother. All right, folks. No, you didn't say he'd she'd do it
out? Or did you? Did I? Didn't I? I don't know. I hate questions like
this. You asked the question. I asked you. I would pick Kevin from
home alone and the devil from the devil's advocate, just Pacino screaming at Kevin from
home alone.
Okay.
It's not what I would pick, but I have to say something.
I would pick...
What do you like to see?
I wish you know screaming a child.
I would pick at his hammyest.
I would pick Anakin Skywalker pre -darth Vader.
Okay, but but evil. All right before he becomes the in the suit, I mean, so just just
uh, Jake Lloyd, or just Hayden Christians, but evil Hayden Christians in the end of
the third movie versus return of the Jedi Luke Skywalker. Okay, that'd be fun to see.
All right, very specific. Well, you asked the question, folks, that's our show.
Pat, are you plugging?
I am on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh,
and I really don't have anything else to plug, frankly.
I'm at Joe DeRosa Comedy on Twitter and Instagram.
Thank you all for listening.
I'll be in San Francisco with the punchline,
August 30th through September.
Third, I think it is, or second?
Also, real quick.
So, come on out and see me.
I'm headlining a bunch of shows up there.
Our Facebook page just crossed like 400 members, which is really fucking awesome.
Thank you, Emily, who runs it.
Thank you, Emily.
We'll see you in hell on Facebook.
I still love reading like the little recaps.
I send them to Joe.
We crack up over them.
It's awesome.
Thank you.
And another thing, we live in the Los Angeles area at the Egyptian theater on Hollywood Boulevard here in Los Angeles.
Friday night, they're doing Creep Show, Creep Show 2, and Kat's Eye.
Joe and I are discussing going schedule dependent, but whether we do or we
don't, a horror fan should want to be at that show. So maybe we'll see you there,
but I hope you go regardless. I had a perfect, it was yet a perfect, maybe we'll
see you there and maybe we'll see you in hell.