Tired of losing your sanity, looking for important work?
Dropbox Dash finds what you need fast across all your workouts,
so you can focus on what matters.
Dash means less time searching, more time creating.
Learn more at Dropbox .com -slash -
Get downtown the easy way of bored Amtrak,
with all the leg room and none of that middle seat stuff.
Driving just doesn't track.
Learn more at Amtrak .com.
Amtrak, retrain travel.
I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell
You know how we do it over here. It's a horror thing. It's a sci -fi thing. It's a fantasy thing. It's a comedy thing
It's a drama thing. It's an action thing. It's a movie thing. My name is Joe DeRosa
To my left
It's a movie thing
You wouldn't understand
Since you've seen those memes that should be our our new slogan to ensure that no one ever watches the show
What are those new memes?
It's a move.
We'll put in two of us one before.
It's a movie thing.
You wouldn't understand.
The latest horrid appropriation of black culture, because that's what that started as.
That's a phrase from like the late 80s, early 90s, it's a black thing, you wouldn't understand.
Just the latest thing that middle aged white women have fucking hijacked so they could use
it as a slogan for an hour on QVC.
Right, even though they would never actually speak to a black person. Yeah, it's, uh,
well, I don't get to be started today. Well, I'm in a mood. I didn't. You started talking
and now we're all unsettled. I'm in a mood. Uh, I too am in a mood. I have one week left
to work. That makes me feel very good. I woke up not panicking for the first time in a long
time and that felt great. Uh, it is a Sunday. It's me and Joe on the couch listening to who,
I guess an aspiring DJ spin beats that I would I would call not that sick downstairs neighbor nice guy real nice guy
But man he be clubbing down there. It's it's just constant dude. It's just constant
EDM going
And not not particularly good, you know that you have to really dig to find
worth while EDM, but we are on the way other end of the spectrum.
I mean, all I can hear is the bass thump.
Yeah, that's all I can.
So who knows?
It could be, he could be the next DJ mouse head.
Yeah.
It feels like, you know, the opening scene of a lot of those like 90s drug movies, like
spun is probably going on in there.
You remember that movie?
It does.
Yeah.
Like there's probably like a guy like walking around and really loose briefs.
It does feel like, yeah, if you know like rail thin.
And if he's not composing music, he is in a bad way
with some kind of substance down there.
There's a real substance abuse issue, yeah.
And, you know, look, on the one hand, I go,
I get annoyed hearing this coming through the floor.
On the other hand, I go, hey man,
we live in a building that was built in the 20s.
He's probably not even playing it that loudly.
Yeah, he should be right.
It's just coming through.
And then I go, you know what, man, this gives you,
this gives you car launch.
You can play anything as loud as you want whenever you feel like you can crank the Frazier, yeah, you know
But that's the problem if I'm listening to music I can't hear it if I'm watching TV
You hear it because what do you listen? What do you watch your TV that is a constant base?
He'll be down in his apartment
Yeah, it's trying to filter it like through the floor and he's freaking out every fucking day with this god damn
Frazier shit, either that guy is writing for Frazier or he's got a real drug problem.
Uh, I've been watching a little bit of some crane shots lately and enjoying it very much.
There was a weird period of time where they would bring in like very scantily clad strippers
on Frazier.
Yeah.
I saw like four in a row where there was just like a nearly naked woman like way beyond
what could ever air now. And I maybe it was to remind people that Fraser and Niles were straight.
I don't know, but I found it pretty jarring. There's a lot of, I'm a real prude. A lot of sex
talk on the show. Eventually, it gets to a point where it does become mildly disturbing. Yeah.
Yeah. Uh, it does get to a point where you're like,
Frazier might be some sort of sex addict. Yeah.
Roz, I think might have been molested as a child.
Roz, and she's looking to plug that whole, no pun intended. Uh,
but it, it, it gets dark with the characters like the people should
be having this much sex. I don't think I always felt that with, uh,
when I was writing for two brokers, I'd be like, so how many times has
the cat Denny's character been sexually assaulted.
How many times can we just settle on a number and how many times did her mom throw her down
a flight of stairs?
Oh boy.
You know?
This is a comedy.
Uh, it was, you know, it was, it was folks, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, uh, anyhow, uh, we're here
this week to kind of really just, it's a first one in a long time to not focus on a specific
movie or show we're gonna just be talking about the events the day the Oscars
were last week I guess Joe watched them even after vowing he wouldn't I watched
clips of things and I read everything I didn't really watch it but that's a
typical 2019 American willing to do a full discussion of something they've
watched a few clips from I will we want I wanted to do a recap because I want to
talk about the controversy surrounding it. I want to talk about Spike Lee. I love stomping out.
Well, now wait, I heard about Spike Lee stomping out, but that wasn't on the show itself, wasn't?
Apparently it was. I don't recall seeing that. Let's wait. Let's wait to get to it. We got a
couple segments to go through. We do. First off, before we get to those segments, I guess I'd love to,
if I may, just get on with the show. And at the same time on with the show knows baseball.
Joe knows football. Remember those, Bo Jackson. Yeah, Bo knows. Did they do, they did a bunch
of those, right? They did a bunch of those boats. Because he played two sports baseball and
football. Yeah. I don't remember enjoying that campaign because it was just another reminder that
I was faking an interest in sports to hang out with my friends. Was Spike?
Lee? No, that wasn't it. Spike Lee did the Nike ones with Jordan. That's right. Yes.
You know there's a pretty serious rumor that's gone on for years that Michael Jordan
and got his father killed due to his gambling debts?
I've heard that rumor.
I don't believe it.
It's not a fascinating rumor.
It's fascinating.
I don't think it has holds much water,
but I mean, I think we would have heard about,
let's put it this way,
had it gotten to that point with Michael Jordan's
financial status,
I feel like there would have been many other stories
about how broke he was.
And there really weren't.
So I feel like that was just a hair brain rumor floating around.
And you read about this Jesse Smollett business, the guy from Empire, I've already followed it to the last detail.
I mean, I had never seen, and still I've never seen Empire, I heard at least the first season was super entertaining,
but it's a Fox show, I'm on the Fox lot, you know, I've gotten to hear some different perspectives on this thing,
but I thought that the guy was like the twelfth lead on the show and he was getting screwed over,
because any actor who's not a lead in a show now gets paid nothing, kind of appalling what they'll
pay even like kind of big names. So basically this guy was number three. He was after Terence Howard
and Cookie. Who plays Cookie? I have no idea. I've never seen the show. I haven't seen it either. But
But, you know, oh, Taraji P. Henson, he was third built.
And I guess he thought he deserved that, you know, super lead that Terence Howard money.
And that's why he did all this, like that, it's shocking to me.
Not that I would have understood it more if he was like a twelfth lead who wanted to get
bumped up by gaining some notoriety, which is obviously sociopathic and insane.
But you'd understand it a little more, like it's actually a kind of a cool plot for like
like a thriller, like an actress who thinks some attack on herself so that she can move
up the rank.
It's kind of interesting.
I didn't imagine it would have been -
He was up the ranks.
I would imagine it would have been a good plot on Empire.
For sure.
For sure about the music business.
The struggle to the top.
I mean, this thing is, you know, it's, look, it's old news at this point.
It's so funny.
I saw Michael Rapper -Poor.
I was on a show with Michael Rapper -Poor who does stand up.
I don't know if he always did or if he just started.
It's pretty good at it.
I always liked it.
He's funny, but he talked about when you two are speaking to each other, do you have
to be eating hogis?
We never spoke.
Oh God.
I just said hi.
I'm glad to be on the show with you.
Just seem like you're two voices going at each other.
There would need to be a sandwich.
I want to be on his podcast so badly, and I want to be his friend so badly.
Kanye West just publicly threatened him on TMZ.
What did he want?
I'm like, why would Kanye West know who Michael Rappaport is?
Uh, he was real famous.
Yeah, he was, but I just made like why is he following him?
Oh, because because you're Kanye West.
Michael Raviport will, you know, he's a struggling actor at this point because he's,
he's very publicly, he very publicly and constantly shits on the Kardashians.
Has his Instagram become like a huge deal?
Yeah, he gets pretty big.
And he tells, he tells, and his podcast is really big.
And he tells that girl who's embroiled in that cheating thing with the Kardashians.
He basically publicly was like, take everybody the fuck down, take that whole fucking family down.
You can't say that.
And so Kanye went on the thing and he was like, when I see you Michael Rappaport, it ain't
going to be on some shaking hands, shit.
We're going to have an issue, you know, so it's like, it was a vaguely veiled threat.
But anyway, my point is, I don't know, I felt about that voice you just did, Joe.
I felt fine about it, you know, I was trying to do a Kanye
impression. It's, it's, it's, it's not, can we talk about that for a second?
Kanye? Well, let's not get into it. I was going to talk about when you do a voice.
Yeah. If you're doing, here's my take on it. And this is,
well, no, this is my take on it. If you're doing an impression of a guy, a specific guy,
Right didn't find if you like like if you know a guy from India and you're going this is you're doing an impression of that guy
You're doing an impression of that person. You're not saying this is what Indian people sound like isn't it funny
There's a difference isn't there? I think there's a there's a there's a difference however if you were doing an impression of
a poo from the Simpsons, and you're doing that Indian voice.
There's no difference, really.
Well, I'm seeing if it's genuinely going to pose
a whole nother back.
I'm not sure who does it, but I don't open that box.
I'm not opening that box.
Speaking of opening boxes, folks, why?
Anyway, he's set on stage.
Michael Ravport said, he was talking about Michael Cohen.
And he goes, can you, and here's what's really funny
about Michael Ravport is he's very liberal,
But he's also super Brooklyn. So in the same breath, he'll trash Trump and talk about how much he hates him
And then it'll be like Michael Cohen that fucking rat
It's a strange dynamic. Yeah, but uh, but anyway, he was like saying how like he's like can you believe like
Jesse Smont was a week ago. He's like that's old news now. Yeah, what the fuck is going on in this world?
It's too much for me.
I am oversaturated and I've had enough.
Now what you're saying about the voices is interesting.
I have a diverse writing staff on the show,
but we do table reads all the time of the episodes.
Each day at the end of the day, we read the episode,
which is extremely helpful for,
if you are an aspiring writer,
on putting the lines into, you know,
sayable things.
If we can't say them in the room,
the actors are gonna be able to say them.
Helps for that also helps you hear what jokes are landing and what aren't even though it is an impartial
Jury a partial jury. Excuse me. It's like if you're doing if you if you're talking I'm trying to think of like who's got like a
You know like Theo Vaughn's a buddy of mine. Yeah, very funny comic Southern is hell, right like when you know
So if I go I saw Theo and he's like he's like Joe man what the fuck head
but you know, the Southern is always okay.
And there's certain things that are always okay.
And maybe that's fair, maybe that isn't fair.
But here's the thing, the Southern thing usually,
if you did a general Southern impression, right?
And you talked like that.
The insinuation behind that impression has always been
they're dumb down there.
Sure.
Which is fucking insulting to a large group of people.
It's insulting, and yet that impression is fine.
No one would ever say stopping that Southern.
So my point is though, is like,
if I'm doing that, I'm not going,
this is what Southern or Southern,
I'm trying to sound like Theo
in the story. I agree. I was going to agree with you to some extent while
disagreeing with you on some other parts but basically when we're doing these
table reads as an example you know if we you know we have gay people in the
room if one of them is not present if one of them is not reading the Sid character
it's always this awkward thing of like do I just do it but at the end of the day
you're doing an impression of Leslie Jordan you have to excuse me you know we
all that's the most fun impression to do but you are impersonating a gay man and
And we all kind of wrestle with that a little bit because it feels weird because like if
you're doing David Allen Greer, it's like, well, you know, what's the line?
I you want to sell the character, but you know, it's something that I think writers are
in struggle with as well.
We could all judge on an individual basis what the line is.
We all know if you're sitting across from somebody to table read.
If you're doing your best David Allen Greer versus this guy is doing like a fucking Amos and
Sure, but I think at this time, people are very scared about accidentally crossing a line
Which no one would want to do and it's something we nervously joke about in the room
Meanwhile, meanwhile though hijack. It's a black thing. You wouldn't understand and not even bad a fucking eye
Not you guys
I was like I don't think we just mean the the the devil
The blue -eyed devil I hear you
but I got a few for the movie corner great um let's head on over I've got a few myself
can I start us off you can let me ask you real quick though have you ever seen Conan the barbarian
I own it on Blu -ray no I own it on VHS yes I have seen it can we do that I watched it for the first
time yesterday in the near future. I'm ready to do it whatever you are. Right. It's a real
romp of a film. Crazy. Boy did I have fun watching. Yeah. So it's a scene, man. I mean, if I'm
being real, I fucking loved it. Yeah. And I'm watching Carnival The Destroyer tonight. Uh, you're going
to be a little disappointed in that. But I know that it's got its moments. Yes. Okay. It's got its
moments. I'm going to start out with a documentary I watch called Not Such a Bad Guy Conversations
with Dabney Coleman. This is a new hour -long documentary. I'm very intrigued. I watched
it on Amazon Prime where it is streaming and it's just that. A guy sits down with Dabney
Coleman today for like you know and cuts together the conversations they have over the course
of this hour or whatever or edits it into it down to an hour. And it's just a front to back to
having Coleman talking about his entire career. And it's fucking great. Sounds awesome. He talks about
he talks about the the best part of the doc is when he gets into nine to nine to five and puts
he back to back. Yeah. And being like and being like these two things were, you know, these two
things were feminist pieces these had a voice these were important films and I was in both of the god damn
things you know and he's like so proud to have been a part of these things he's got a really great
relationship with Jane Fonda who put him in both that and on golden pond yeah he talks about
the big scene with Jane Fonda and gold on golden pond where she's like I want to be your friend to
her dad and then he's like you know that was the reason she wrote that movie was she it was a
a way for him to make amends with her father.
He starts crying at one point at how beautiful he thought it was.
Okay.
He talks about how troubled their relationship was,
but in classic old school gentleman form,
he goes, now let me be clear.
I do not say that to disparage Henry Fonda in any way.
He was a wonderful man and a hard worker,
but they had a complicated relationship.
Sure.
He's just a guy that doesn't exist anymore.
He's in his 80s. He's still. Yeah, I got to watch sharp as a tack. Like doesn't miss a beat. That's really my favorite area of Coleman late seven his early 80s. Yeah, he he's he's still whether he talks about war games. Yeah, love war games. Yeah, and he's like he's like, you know, I never.
My guy didn't see him as a bad guy. He's a guy doing his damn job. He's like, I'll tell you why they didn't like me because I'm smacking cute little broderick around. You can't smack around a kid that cute.
All right, I got a wonderful film.
Have you seen the documentary that I always considered turning on, but have not watched
called like character and it's all these character actors, Danny Coleman being one of them?
I saw the one that had where Jane Joan Kusek was in it a lot.
No, it wasn't called character.
The girl from the thing or whatever.
The one I saw, yeah, you're the face.
Yeah.
I recognize your face or whatever it's called.
No, I never saw character.
Okay.
I will watch that for sure. I watched, we want to talk about a documentary. Um, I'll match you, Joe, because I saw a picture called Ashby.
Ashby is a documentary, newly streaming on Amazon Prime as well. Um, I find Amazon Prime, you know, when they get a new movie, it's something I'm always interested in. Whereas Netflix, I'm like, how many movies just Nicholas Cage make a week?
And I think that their original content is potentially superior to Netflix, the Netflix
original content.
I ain't seen much, but I did love Red Oaks, and I liked transparent for a few seasons.
Okay, so Ashby is a documentary about the filmmaker Hal Ashby who died relatively young
and was just like a total hippie basically like a addicted to weed could only edit his movies
stoned out of his gourd and just was so crushed by the Hollywood system that eventually he
was just churning out like very average action movies that everybody hated and made no money
And it just killed him that he wasn't making personal movies anymore. And basically he
Just dropped out of the film business his last movies were unwatchable, but he did herald a mod. He did being there
with Peter Sellers
He did coming home which I fucking love with Jane Fonda and Bruce Dern, which is like it won Oscars and shit
But if you have I think a lot of people have not seen that movie and it's a very good movie
So I enjoyed it as just a story about a guy in the friend, a story about a guy who got
really fucked over repeatedly by the system, had movies taken away from him because they
were like, you're not doing it in a way that we've seen before and he's like, right, in
the past when I've done it differently, these things have been huge successes, so why would
you not trust me?
Right.
then the weed use that got him so sort of creatively tapped in that he made
these last detail with Jack Nicholson and Randy Quaid, another fantastic movie
that he directed. He would get on this like wavelength that people weren't on
and make these amazing projects, but then once they turned on them, they always
when they wanted to get the film back, they would say, well he's a drug addict
because he smoked all this weed that made him so creatively gifted in the
Tim Steele's movies away. It was kind of a heartbreaking story. But they talked to a lot of big people,
Alexander Payne, Judd Apatow, you know, a bunch of key comedy figures of the day, and people who
knew him back then. Great documentary. Right now when I think key comedy figures, I think Alexander
Payne. Look, man, he made a couple great fucking, he made a couple masterpieces. He did.
Abouchment, election sideways. That's three masterpieces. Sorry. I agree with that. I agree with that.
But what was his last, oh, that's like an end of it.
All right, I'm staying on the documentary tip,
filmage, a movie about the descendants in all.
If you're a fan of the descendants,
or if you're a fan of all.
The Alexander Pan movie?
No, the band, which if I was the band,
I would have sued Alexander Pan for naming that movie
anything, oh my God, I hate that movie.
Anyway, if you're a fan of the movie,
to it by the way. The band, the band of descendants, or the band all or both. You need to see this movie.
It's an amazing, you know, it's just a great capturing of their story and what it's like to be
a band that, you know, kind of never says die and the drummer from the descendants, what the fuck's
his name, Steven's Bill Stevens, I think,
I'm liking it his name.
But anyway, he's sort of the linchpin of the entire thing
and they talk about how he was the guy
that kind of kept the band going
and they interview all kinds of reputable musicians
from Dave Grohl to people from the punk scene to whoever
and they just get into like what the descendants meant
to people, what their take on Milo, the singer,
leaving the descendants was and descendants becoming all
with a new singer and it's changing the sound a bit and then all never really taking off.
Dave Grohl is a great quote where he goes, trust me, I know. It's really, really hard
to be in a famous band, a popular band and then go try to start another band. He's like,
it's very scary and you don't know what's going to happen. And now of course it all worked out perfectly
for Dave Grohl, but it seemed like it worked out great. But he went from descendants to what?
Who? Who are you talking about?
The band, the band, the descendants when their singer Milo left
to become like a bioengineer or something
after they had done like five albums. I thought he had gone on to do another band.
No, he was making the girl connection. He literally left to go be
like a scientist because he took that was a huge part of his life
and they wanted to keep playing music so they renamed
the band all and hired a new singer and started writing different music under the name all,
and it was always sort of the descendants with a different singer, but it wasn't really
and all really struggled to find their place and things. You know at times it's very hard breaking
and at times it's extremely uplifting, but overall it's a really cool positive story about following
your dream, and I like that they get into like the financial stuff and you know how like you know you
You see these bands that have 10 fucking records
in the slot at Amoeba, and get staff picked
and get a lot of FaceTime, whatever,
in different record stores you go to throughout,
you've been through throughout your life.
And then you realize like, oh no, they're just like me.
They're like almost paycheck to paycheck.
The grass is not always greener.
So it's weird too because I don't know
the descendants hardcore punk is not, I, I, when they're not, they're not really
hardcore. They're not. They're not. They're not. They're considered sort of the prototype
for pop punk. Yeah. Blink when 82, whatever. Yeah. I, I, just that scene, you know, I don't like,
I like melodic punk, pop punk, I don't go, you know, all the way over to like newfound glory
and shit like that. But it's a genre I liked for a while, especially in college. I own Milo
goes to college, just because I know that's an album you're supposed to own.
And I don't know really anything about the descendants or the scene.
So that should tell you, these guys should be rich, but due to, I guess, getting screwed
over by the labels or something, but everyone has, you know, anyone with even a passing interest
in 80s punk has that album.
It's not screwed over.
It's just the reality of, this is what you made when you put a record out independently
in the album.
It's way less.
Yeah.
It's just what that scene was and they sort of got to cash in a little bit on like now here's the
thing. I think they're reaping the benefits now because not all they play but most of what they
play now are you know like warp tour and shit like right so they do these big fucking festivals jam packed
with kids who are dying to see them so I feel like now they're probably finally getting some of that
coin. Yeah. I had a very erotic day at a warp tour when I was in college. Erotic? I did.
I went on as a date. It was very erotic. Do you hook up with the drummer from a perfect circle?
Like that? No. I like a perfect circle. They wouldn't be at the warp tour. I couldn't
they were the closest band I could think of off the top. It's a funny title. It's a funny name for
Joe. Yeah, I never really got in the tool, but that first perfect circle album I thought was kind of cool, I guess.
I hated perfect circle because it sounded like lesser tool to me. I get it.
But I was never hugely into tool either. No, me neither. And I think that guy dodged pretty serious sexual abuse
allegations last year, and I never heard anything about them beyond the initial whispers.
Our buddy Pinkstone said, sorry, I just got keen and distracted by the fucking...
Yeah, I mean, the rhythm's gonna get you.
Now, do you think, let me sidetrack.
Do you think I'm out of line if I text him
and I just go, hey buddy, no worries.
Could you just turn the bass down?
Listen to that.
Yeah, I mean, do what you want.
I get this, this stresses me out, dude.
Do what you want.
You might just be here in bass
because you live above guy listening to loud music.
Like, but if you turn the bass down,
I feel like that's all I'm hearing.
This isn't a distracted man. I'm distracted very easily. That's not bothering you. No, I'm just kind of fades into the background. All right far enough. I'm not going to text him.
What was I saying?
Oh, our friend James Pinkstone.
Yes, not James Keenan.
Yeah, I remember when that last tool record came out, I go, do you get the new tool? And he goes, no, I'm going to go, why?
and he goes, and he goes, I can only listen to so many two -minute fading in ambien base
intros.
Yeah.
He's like, I'm just done, dude.
I can't do this anymore.
And I was like, yeah, that's a very fair point to lose, but that one was kind of cool.
I know the piece is fit, but that one was kind of cool, but I was never a fan.
Stink fist.
I was always like, come on, guys.
Class it up.
Yeah.
You don't got to call songs Stink fist.
We know you're dark. I didn't I didn't mind that. Okay. I kind of like it was it was
It's it's some nice low -brow stuff, you know prison rape. What was that? It's what's called jail -sec prison prison sex
That's an awesome song
I
On the documentary tips for
generation wealth
Just the new film by Lauren Greenfield
Who was a photographer who became a documentarian?
I thought it was great.
This was also on Amazon Prime,
and it is kind of a visual history, you might say,
of how we became completely obsessed with wealth, fame,
looks, and just really exposes the shallow,
shallow underbelly of society today.
It's depressing as hell.
I bet it is, um, she did, what was that movie about the woman who kept building bigger
and bigger houses?
Remember that?
She like, eventually, I drove her family into Bank of New York.
No, she was insanely rich, um, and just kept building and building and building and building.
I'm gonna look it up.
No idea.
William Randolph Hurst, I think you mean?
No.
Well, this, once it comes up, I am to be taking several hours to load.
I will tell you that it was called the Queen of Versailles.
Oh, yeah, I remember that movie.
I never saw it though.
Fantastic documentary as well about five years back about the same thing, obsession with
wealth.
So this movie was good enough to get me to buy her latest photography book, Generation
Wealth, which I've been enjoying the hell out of.
And it's a, if you need like an unusual coffee table book that, you know, will serve the
the purpose of those books as they're supposed to be,
as a conversation starter, pick it up.
It's like 40 bucks for this big, thick,
beautiful photo album and it's like art,
you know, really great artistic photos.
You know what I just decided?
I'm in the market for a coffee table.
I want a coffee table.
I think you should have a coffee table.
I'm gonna get rid of this ottoman
and I'm just gonna have a coffee table.
All right, maybe get this book.
I hate this ottoman.
It's comfortable, but yeah, it's not exactly
striking. I'm tired of it. Get a nice coffee. I might get one today. I'm going to tell you where
you should go. Actually, if I remember, I'm going to do it as an advertisement for them because
they're great, great cheap furniture. I'm going to have to look them up because I forget their name.
But Generation Wealth, I recommend. It is funny, it's dark as hell, it is weird, it's interesting,
It's got a lot of jarring nudity that pops up in it. I couldn't recommend it more highly
All right, and weirdly not well reviewed
Because I think everyone loved Queen of Versailles so much and thought this was like a more scattered
And it is. It's not about one person. It's about a
Problem with society. So yeah, it's a little less focused
But that didn't bother me in the slightest. I really dug it all right check it out
And and I remember the name of that furniture place if you're in Los Angeles, it's called Nado
NAD, where is it EU NAD EU where is it to the one I used to go to is in West Hollywood
But I got this amazing old wooden desk
I got like some really great piece of furniture and they're like $200 and they're actual and are we gonna be anywhere near it today
Where we go to the eba we I'd have to I'd have to split up from you if you want to go on to this
You and I could go together. Okay. We could maybe do that. I could use your car to get my coffee table home. Oh
Well, so you want to use me for my vehicle. I want to use you for your body
The coffee tables of bonus. No, I can do it on me, but then I'm done today. I got I got the shit to do
Oh, well excuse me. Sorry. Fuck. Oh, sorry
Anyway, so that's my second. What's your third pick Joe?
I'll be quick with my third one, another punk documentary, the decline of Western civilization.
I had never seen the first one.
Oh, great one.
I own all three.
I'd only seen the second one.
The second one is the masterpiece of the three.
We watched the second one religiously when I played in bands in Philly.
We would go to the house we called the cat box.
We're a lot of my musician friends live together and we would do shows there and stuff.
But we would get real stone and watched the decline of Western Civilization part two and laugh our asses off
Part one is not funny at all. It's more about the true
Tried and true punks scene of the early 80s
It's pretty good. It gets in there. I liked it a lot
And it's funny to see how much that scene has changed over the years not too down
I'm not knocking for it for what it is now
But I mean, it was pretty fucking grimy back then and it's fun to see the footage of that
It's fun to see
Some bands that you still know are out there today in their early stages like X
Love X just saw my Christmas time
I mean, it was a cool way for me to find some new music of bands that I hadn't heard of you know those first four X albums are fucking masterpieces
But you know black flags in it and it's it's fun, man. I really liked it. So
So the drummer firm, the descendants, was also the drummer in Black Flag for a little while.
So there you go.
Everything connects.
Watch this movie if you're a fan of punk, even if you're just a fan of music and music
history, and you just want to learn about, you know, a time period, an era that took place.
It's worth a watch.
And I'm going to get us off documentaries from my last one, talk about a very underrated
comedy the two few people know called the wrong guy starring and written by co -written by
Dave Foley of the kids in the hall and also news radio fam co -written by Jay Kogan of
some of the best Simpson's ever and David Higgins who was just the big fat bearded guy from like
Ellen the Ellen show like you know him you've seen him in sitcoms and stuff yeah I know who he is
They wrote it
The three of them acting it this thing is like kind of like a live -action Simpsons episode
My buddy Rob Wisman on a great follow on Twitter
Recommended it the other day and I was like I own that movie and I've never seen it. I dusted it off and
Holy shit, there's some funny bits on this the most famous bit in it is almost like a usual suspects type spoof bit
where she goes what's your name and he like looks around and
and, you know, sees like Philips, right, you know,
tooth brushes and so he goes, Phillips.
And she goes, okay, what's your last name?
And then he looks up at the shelf and it's Enema Bag,
and it goes, Enema Bag Jones, Enema Bag Jones,
my name, whatever.
So this has been this famous bit I've heard about for years,
and I feel like the filmmaker David Steinberg,
who does a lot of curb.
I don't like David Steinberg too.
feel like he botched the bit, it cuts to, anyway, anyway, I think it cuts to it too quickly
and it also includes another name in the shot.
So unless you're thinking he's gonna pick the other name, I feel like they botched this
like simple classic bit, but so many people cited it as their favorite scene of the movie.
I would say, that's the joke is that he's too dumb that he doesn't even use the other name.
But if the other name had been Mark or something, I'd get it, but it was like another, he would
to make his name like Philips Jenkins or something.
It didn't make sense.
I'm saying maybe that's the joke that he's so bad
he can't take the obvious hint of Philips.
I guess.
And he panics he goes, and him a bag.
Something about the way it was shot didn't work for me.
I guess the way it had been described to me
over the years was funnier than when I saw it.
Which can happen.
I've never heard of the film, I've never seen it,
I will check it out.
There are no less than 30 laugh out loud jokes.
That is a hugely successful comedy.
Absolutely.
Day fully is unhinged in this movie.
I have never seen him like this,
even in all his years on those shows,
he was always so mild -mannered.
But the first 10 minutes of this thing,
he has this bit where he's screaming in his office
that is incredible.
Then he does a bit where he's sobbing in his office.
That is incredible.
Then he just runs around screaming for 15 minutes
and it's funny the entire time.
He's great in it.
But there's some great weird shit in it.
It's very surreal.
It felt kind of like those, you know, early Sandler movies where it's smart stupid, which
is a genre that is just never even attempted anymore.
But I think because people are too worried about being viewed as stupid.
So everybody's comedy is, I'm smarter than you, I'm so smart, but nobody's doing what I think
is harder and so much fun here, which is the smart dumb.
That's my favorite kind of comment. Right, right. I got you
Okay, that's what this is checking out
Little screaming in before we get into the Oscars
Emily Florence will be
One of the only people I know happy to hear this I can't remember where I read this if it was on
Bloody disgusting or movie web or what but
But this is the headline, and they had the audacity to write this with excitement, whoever
wrote it.
And even longer, three -hour, ultimate cut of Clive Barker's night breed is being put
together.
I saw that.
Does anybody fucking need this?
Does anybody need this?
There must have been an audience for the last one when it came out, because there wouldn't
be making it another one.
Oh my God, man.
This thing is like still never saying it. It's terrible. It do it. It's like watching
Like a bad Robert Altman movie except with monsters. It's just monsters talking to each other for hours
God damn it this movie sucks
Did you also see that they're a shutter?
Of course we love shutter is doing a
Critters television. Yes, is it a show or a new movie?
Shutter is doing a TV show sci -fi is doing a new movie. Okay. Um, I believe I've seen critters won
I have not seen the others. Critters is fun. I'd be more curious to see the new movie over the TV show
I don't know that I need you know
10 episodes of critters
But you know I own the four pack and I enjoy the films. They're fun. All right. They're fun like sort of monster B movie fun
You know what one is decaprio?
go in? Christ, I don't even remember Chris. He must be in like the fourth one. And I didn't even realize.
But, uh, but you remember a movie called Munchy? It was voiced by Dom Delewies. It was like
This little sort of troll thing I bet yeah, I don't I barely yeah
Terrified I mean when I was a kid it was supposed to be a child's comedy it terrified you horrified me
Well, you were also scared a little monsters. I was scared of little monsters the craziest thing I've ever heard sorry
I was very sheld
Let's get into this Oscars recap. Um
I mean look let's start with the elephant in the room. I
off the bat. Have you seen it? I haven't. Joe, don't you don't you feel you
should have seen it before launching into whatever you're about to launch? I'm
not criticizing that it won best picture. Okay, so no, it doesn't I don't want to
want it. Dude, it looks like I made for TV. It looks like a bad movie to me. It's
it's it's very in the driving Miss Daisy 90s mode, which I gotta tell you I
still enjoy driving Miss Daisy and I don't they are the only way you can get
it more than half the country to have any sort of discussion about race is through a movie
like this.
Is that fucked up?
Yes.
Is that cool?
No.
Are the movies themselves entertaining?
Sometimes.
Um, you know, I, I, do I feel either should have one best picture?
No.
Drive Ms. Daisy should not have won in a year where do the right thing was nominated.
That's insane.
All right.
The fair enough.
I do not understand.
Look.
It's not the first time the economy wasn't nominated.
to do the right thing. It has given best picture to something that I may or may not think sucks, right?
Yeah. But the point, that's not my point. I'm not worried about that. My thing is, is I do not
understand where we're at mentally right now where we are praising and celebrating and loving the
fact that the actor in Green Book, one best supporting actor, and stars in True Detective, and is doing
all this cool stuff and as being recognized as a black actor in Hollywood and being rewarded
for it.
And then we're also furious that Green Book One best picture.
It's very confusing to me, especially when you've got -
I completely agree.
People like -
I don't understand that at all.
Octavia Spencer is in it and it's like people are going, this movie shouldn't know what it's
like.
But what about the black people that were involved with it?
And my opinion is this, and I forget the actor's name, I apologize.
us, but that guy, that guy wins best supporting actor and then Green Book doesn't win best
picture. That guy's just another Marissa Tome at that point. It's like, yeah, or a highly
berry or whoever where they win best supporting actor for something that where the picture doesn't
get recognized. To me, strategically on the Academy's part, this is conspiracy theory, but
I think it's very possible. The Academy probably said, you know what? If we give Green Book
best picture and this guy best actor, another dude gets to, gets to make some real moves
in this business because it doesn't get lost in the shuffle at that point that he won
for this.
You know what I mean?
There's more of a discussion about that.
Now you're losing me.
I don't feel the Academy Awards just goes, let's pick whoever we want to win.
So it will look good.
You don't think there's, because I think they were well aware of the controversy surrounding
Green Book going into those things.
In a business, in a business, and you know this is true,
in a business riddled with awards being based completely
on campaigning, strategy, power plays, trade -offs,
whatever you want to call it, you don't think
that that's possible, that there was some sort of strategy
behind if we can get best picture for this
and best supporting actor for him,
then this guy has a better chance of being another Denzel.
I just think they actually count the fucking votes
at the Oscars. Call me old -fashioned. Call me, too, too.
Oh, no, no, no. I do think they count the votes. I think that could have been a motivation
behind the votes. That's what I'm saying. But I do think everyone in Hollywood knew that
Green Book was a very controversial film going into the voting. But I just think that with
most of the voting bodies still, even though they've updated it and upgraded it, is going
to be old white people. That's going to be most of the Oscar voters. And that this movie
is catnip to them because it lets them feel good about, hey, these movies are actually
generally teaching the message that even a racist and a black person can get along.
And while that is good, I guess, it's also like not great that you're the racist, you know,
they don't cure you from that.
But that's the reason these have a wider appeal because so many are racist.
They see themselves in these characters and say yes, I'm nice to the black guy at the hardware store
I'm just like this guy in green book and it does make people who are doing the absolute bare minimum of tolerance
sort of feel better about themselves. I think that's what's a little gross about these movies
But they're not going away and people love them
And I enjoyed this movie watching it with my dad. I agree with that
I do not think the and I also and you know and I've complained about it left and right and they talk about it in
hard new are, which is wonderful.
But they talk about the character of the magical Negro
that teaches the befuddled white man,
you know, the mystical ways or whatever.
So I do think that Green Book could be interpreted
as maybe having an element of that.
Like, well, it's that and it's also the white savior stereotype,
which is Matthew McConaughey comes in and saves all the slaves.
Right.
You know, that's not a great way to tell that story either.
So I get both, I get, I get, I get, I get the,
I get the some controversy, and I get some of the criticism.
When I don't get is, I think it's, by the way, you know I love black clansmen, boy
do I love black clansmen, I thought it should have gotten best picture without even seeing
the other pictures or not all of them at least.
I loved that movie so much.
I think it is ridiculous that Spike Lee stomped out of the theater, attempted to, and then
was told he had to return to his seat.
And then like a child having a tantrum had to return to his fucking seat.
I think it's ridiculous.
Spike, you're participating, you're there.
Why do you want the fucking thing so bad, if it's so fucked up and it's all bullshit?
Well, he said he wouldn't have stopped out if Roma had won, if other movies had won.
There was something about the Green Book that bothered him too much.
i i i think it's i think you it's silly i think it's a tantrum
and i think i think i think it's i admire anyone doing something like that because
otherwise this would have been on a night notorious for being boring
one of the most boring Oscars of all time isn't it just more interesting to not go
to the Oscars and then win the Oscar and not even be there like fuck you that's
that's interesting to me well i don't know you know it gave the thing a pulse i guess uh
and Spike Lee's good at that.
He's a provocateur or why we love him.
I guess, and I'm gonna double down on something here
with the green book thing,
because I got a lot of, not a lot,
but I got a little bit of shit from people
for our discussion we had about saying
a racial slur in context.
And if you're saying it in,
because of the, what's his face?
Who was the actor?
V. Joe Morns.
V. Joe Morns, you know what, guys?
Or V. Go, I don't know.
I'll say this to anybody and I'll stand by it.
If you think it's never okay to say any sort of offensive word in context,
if you think context doesn't apply, then it can never be said in a movie.
Then you can't say it in black clansmen playing the clan member.
That's context. That's what context means. It means what are the parameters around how the word
is being used? You don't watch black clansmen and go, it's terrible that the clansmen are using the
the end word in this movie.
So, the Vigo Mortisan is not the same kind of context,
but it's the context argument.
I think it is fucking insane
that we are losing sight of that.
That's all I wanna say.
That's it.
All right.
Anyway.
The, you got anything?
No.
About the Oscars?
Or no.
I didn't know if you were gonna add to the context thing.
No, you don't really agree with me.
But it's, but that's okay.
We can disagree.
No, I do think you have to make things historically accurate, but sure, you know,
So then but then when you're when a guy's having a discussion
Would I ever feel like no, I feel like context -wise. I'm in the clear to say it right now. I'll never have that feeling
No, I don't feel that way either. Yes, which is why I didn't say it
Right, but my point is is I think we can all take a breath and go a guy that's not even from here
trying to discuss historical accuracy in a movie
and using the word in that moment is not a guy being racist.
It's just like, I agree.
I agree, although you do wonder why
somebody doesn't have that filter to say,
I'm not going to say that here.
I think not being from this country
has got a lot to do with it.
Perhaps it does.
You know, I really do, but I don't know, whatever.
It doesn't matter.
It's an unwinnable debate.
It'll never, we're all gonna have different opinions.
I just wanted to say that I bring up something that's not going to be controversial at all and it's something we've suspected for several years
Rami Malik is completely fucking insane. Yeah, he's nuts if you saw him backstage with the champagne
Dead -eyed
Blasting reporters with a bottle of champagne and shaking it all over the place looking like fucking American psycho. Yeah, he's nuts
I mean, he's gonna he's going to kill someone he fell off the stage saying he fell off the stage
That that was the second craziest thing he did then he's released this video online where he's like I
Like oh my god wearing the clothes. I like to wear no
He goes I'm like dressing up for a fan. I'm like. Well he starts every sentence with I'm a fan of I'm a fan of yeah
Like he's a sharp right regardless of the occasion. Yeah, I'm a fan of foreign cultures. I'm a fan of
of Granny's chocolate chip cookies.
Uh -oh, this just in text from Vince Averill.
You still at the improv,
because I was at the improv last night.
But our old boy Vince might be sniffing around
for a little fun today.
I've always enjoyed fun.
Yeah, remember when we said we were gonna,
I'm gonna say you got a drink,
but I'm saying remember we were gonna hang out today,
and now you're going, I got into Miba and I got to go home.
I could maybe hang a little bit, you know?
I just can't do a an eight hour. We don't spend any goddamn time together anymore
But I'm gonna be off soon. I'll have whole days
But we need to line some up. We need to do like a nice summer day and record four of these
Shove it up just joylessly bang them out
That's how you refer to your women correct. Yeah, I did joyously bang them out
They awarded Grammy Malik everyone jumps to their feet standing ovation for him
This guy pretending he has no clue about Brian Singer in a movie that everyone also finds highly controversial, it's like it doesn't matter.
Just we'll give you a standing ovation, then by the time we've sat down, we'll be talking about how much we vehemently disagree with everything you stand for, and it's the grossest business in the history of time.
of these fucking people. Let me tell you something about enlightened people. Okay, all right because
that's who these people I'm using heavy quotes around enlightened because that's who these people
pretend to be this trash that fills up the the audience at an event like this. They pretend to be
progressive yet all they ever do when they disagree with somebody is shame them and try to ruin them.
You know what? You know what? Doesn't do that. Actual progressives. Martin Luther King
didn't shame people. Jesus didn't shame people. Monks and lighten monks don't shame people.
They say to people that they feel are in the dark, I want to teach you to get you out
of the dark. I've gone on a beautiful spiritual journey. I've grown. I want you to experience
that. Come out of the dark and come into the light with me. These people don't say that because
they've had no spiritual journey. They say what they need to say to keep their fucking bank account
in the goddamn black. That's all it is. I am so fucking tired of it. I am so fucking tired of
these hypocrites getting away with this, walking around going, I get it, I get it. It's like,
isn't it amazing? Isn't it amazing that you're exactly woke to the latest controversy? Isn't
that incredible? That everybody just happens to have their finger on the exact wokeness of like
like the John Wayne video that just came out
or whatever the fuck it is.
The latest thing, you're just on top of it.
You've already gone through this journey.
You get it?
Yet you're not teaching anybody how to see it your way.
You're just yelling at people and saying canceled.
I hate it.
I hate these fucking people.
I hate them.
They're hypocritical bastards.
Joe, I didn't hear much.
I disagreed with them.
And I really thought I was going to.
Usually when you reach that level of anger,
or I'm like, oh, okay, Joe's lost his mind.
Yeah, I'm polishing a gun.
Yeah.
Not another thing.
I'm discreetly dialing nine and one
and just waiting for the cue to hit the other one.
Joe, just put down the knife sharpener as you talk about this.
Well, it's a knife sharpener too,
like on the leather belt.
Yeah, just scraping it back and forth.
It's a disgusting two -faced hypocritical business.
You know, just people will just stab you in the best people will stab you in the front.
And just walk away from it, you know, it's a it's a six, six business.
It's a six society and the entertainment business is it turned up all the way.
It's yeah.
It's like a reality show.
It's like every day you're living in a form of a reality show.
It's on tilt, it's full tilt.
And the last thing about the Oscars real quick before we wrap up here.
So Spielberg now is launching a campaign.
Stephen?
Stephen.
Yes.
Yeah.
Barry Spielberg, the grip, is launching a campaign.
No, Steven Spielberg is launching a campaign against where he's, I guess, assembling other
directors and he's launching a campaign against Netflix so that they are barred from the Oscars.
The streaming services don't count.
Now, this story pisses me off.
This is one of these things where I don't even know where I fall
because I'm mad at everybody.
First of all, movie web runs this fucking article.
And I don't know when I'm going to learn my lesson
and stop going, I got to find a new movie website
because movie web pisses me off and I'm addicted to it.
Movie web's headline is Spielberg, you know,
I'm paraphrasing, lashes out against Netflix,
involvement in the Oscars, faces backlash, okay?
Okay, I read what he's doing, which is what I just explained.
I scroll down to see backlash.
One director, the director of Selma,
one director said, I don't agree with this,
and I disagree.
Right.
It was such a fucking bait and switch headline.
I was so fucking angry.
It's all they do.
After the dust settled on the story this weekend,
everybody was like, oh, so this wasn't a story at all.
The Twitter all weekend was let's flush this old son of a bitch out of the business. Sorry Steve the world's changing
Then it's like no stop. He he didn't say that yeah
Here's what he's saying and then everybody's like oh, yeah, sorry
I screamed that an old legendary director should die yesterday
Because he had an opinion about something it's insane
I mean, um, you know, I got a little annoyed with Spielberg, which is darker by the day, man.
That's I can't I don't know how you're still on it. That's I mean, it's uh, I don't know how you're still I'm on it way less than
I've ever been, but I you check in just to watch people just go nuts, just eat themselves alive all day.
Here's the thing I don't understand with Spielberg. Why does he give a shit? Why does he have a dog in this race?
The man is 75 years old, he very well could be the devil with the amount of success he's seen in this business.
I wouldn't be surprised if he was the actual devil.
You don't stay relevant for that long easily, that is tough work.
He can do any fucking thing he wants, he's got his awards, he's got his recognition.
I'm not quite sure why he cares so much.
I admire that he still cares that much.
Well, that's a good point. That's a good point. I don't know if I feel that Netflix should be barred from the Oscars
And I'm not a Netflix fan. Yeah, you know, but I got to say it's like
You know what bothers me should have at least been a discussion about it before it's like yeah, fine. Welcome aboard
Well, it did play in theaters. Did it not? Yeah, but he's he's saying that they should play three weeks in theaters or something like that
Which okay fair enough. I mean look here's the problem now people and nobody's gonna fucking jump on board
And I guess I'm sort of patting myself on the back a little bit.
I don't mean to do that, but I said it about fucking Twitter years ago.
This thing is going to turn on everybody.
You cannot put every waking thought that comes into your head online and document.
And sure enough, it's biting everybody in the ass.
And I'm saying it fucking now about Netflix.
They are trying to monopolize entertainment.
They somehow have some fucking limitless amount of money.
I don't know where they get it from to budget thing.
It ain't coming from a great place.
I can almost guarantee you of that.
They are the Donald Trump of entertainment.
They lie, okay, they come out with terrific numbers.
We had to read bird bucks, most loved movie.
And then people go, well, what can we see the numbers?
That is the most insane part of all this
that they don't have to report.
They won't.
Yeah, they won't.
And that's part of Spielberg's thing too.
Would you just tell us what you're doing?
Because we all have to compete in box office,
we have to compete in terms of all this shit.
Tell us how many people watch the stupid thing.
They don't turn over the documents, just like Trump.
Right.
Uh, they are trying to be an absolute one voice power,
just like Trump.
It's demigods, bullshit.
Everybody bought into that fucking marketing campaign,
Netflix and chill.
So guys, there are a million other streaming services that aren't trying to, it's a monopoly.
It's supposed to be illegal.
You're not supposed to be allowed to do it.
Netflix is trying to monopolize entertainment by buying up every fucking thing they can.
And they're trying to shut everybody else out.
And keep paying the extra dollar every six months so they can do it.
Stop, stop, walk away from this shit.
Why is everybody so fucking dependent on this stuff, dude?
It's like Apple. Is it that it's is a world without Apple that terrifying?
Well, what they're doing is that
The more and more people that do this and a lot of people I know in Missouri and should have pulled the cord as they say
And they just have Netflix because that's like okay, that's the entertainment now the more that happens
The more they're gonna fuck out all other avenues and I think that's on the way
But they're doing this and then when you have several people that do this
Then the only television shows people are talking about are
Netflix shows which requires then if you want to see these shows the people are talking about and that flex is only had two or three of these the true
Breakouts a stranger things a house of cards, right, but if everybody's talking about it, then everybody has to get it
So as that happens and as the other options are shut out then
Everybody's only talking about the same thing.
Everybody's only talking about bird box,
and that, to me, is the scariest part of all of this.
That everyone just watches one movie
that you're told to because the algorithm
puts it on the top of your thing.
Oh, Sandra Blocks in a Netflix movie I can get for free.
Okay, push.
Oh, that's weird, yeah.
It's almost like somebody in an immense position of power
telling us what we're supposed to think about things
and what the national opinion should be.
Sounds fucking familiar.
It's just crazy to me that in these places in day to day life where keep screaming at Trump
Guess what he's never gonna listen ever you're never gonna get through to him
But everybody wants to scream at him meanwhile in your day to day life
You've got like a corporation you could tell to go fuck itself by canceling your subscription and not contributing to the problem and people are just like no
No, I'm gonna keep doing that
It's like you'll scream about Walmart, but not Netflix
Well, not only that, but it's like LOL, did you all see glow or whatever, you know, because
people support it. People support the hell out of it. That has no way of being shut down.
Just like I think there's Trump machine has no way of being shut down. That's why, you know,
I caught up a little bit on this Cohen thing. I've been busy, but what's scaring people the most
is like, you can't turn around what he's done in the short time in office. Like, you can't
walk it back and Trump's not going to hand over this presidency peacefully. He's going
to blow shit up before he gets out of office. He's going to make it a hundred percent
certain that we are going to have to work years to undo what he has done. So him and his
friends keep getting rich. That's some terrifying shit. I guarantee you this. I guarantee this more
people cancel their subscriptions. It certainly slows their role a little bit in being able
to just run shit constantly.
I think that is possible.
I also think it's possible to see people cancel those.
Well, they won't.
They won't.
That's what I'm railing on about here.
You know, but I mean, you're talking, and just to see you guys know where this network stands,
you're dealing with a network that told Canada, sorry, bird box is already, and I've talked
about this, bird box has already been published to the streaming site.
We cannot take it down to remove the fucking train wreck tragedy footage from your country
that that we've exploited in our horror movie. Sorry, we can't do that. Meanwhile, the notebook hits Netflix
Europe, okay? And it's got a different ending on it because it would, they received a different
cut. Notebook fans freak out. This is, this is blasphemy. Where's the original one? Netflix responds,
sorry, we got the wrong cut. We didn't even know we're working on it. We love the notebook. They
The fans of the fucking notebook, then they did to people that died in a train wreck in
Canada.
Okay?
That's what you're fucking dealing with.
Be a part of it.
Enjoy yourself.
Have fun.
I got to ask you this.
Yeah.
Right.
You mentioned being very excited about, I hear you paint houses don't you?
The Irishman.
I'm usually excited about it.
You're not going to watch that movie.
I'm 100 % going to watch it, but I'm going to go to a theater and watch it.
Just a still Netflix.
Well, I also think it's Scorsese,
De Niro, a bunch of people that I love and respect
that I can say I'm supporting these people.
But look, I'm not a fucking lunatic.
I'll look over my sunglasses at Joe right now.
I'll say this much, I'm not a lunatic.
I never was a person that said,
Oh, Uber gave to Trump, never used them
under any circumstance ever.
I said, all right, if you wanna try to not use Uber, I get it.
But to say, to think that any part of your life
does not have some corporate interference is crazy and I know that that counts and I know that I can't
I can't fucking avoid these what am I supposed to do never watch a thing ever again
I you know I don't I cancel my subscription I'll see that in the theater. I'm gonna have to
Miss fucking stranger things three when it comes out, you know like but you know I don't know so maybe
Maybe I'm full of shit for going to a theater to see that I don't know to me that seems okay
but I go to a theater, the movie is put out by Netflix. I'm just saying where
where's the line and the line is not possible to draw. We're surrounded by the
shit all day every day. I hope we cheer you up this week. I hope you
made your life made your smile. Let's get over to that Amoeba. Trade some stuff.
We're going to Amoeba. Have a great day. Those of you hearing it on Himalaya.
Welcome aboard. Please check out the patreon. Please check out the hog house page at Etsy for a merch
Thank you Emily Florence for beautifully running that
Thank you to all the fans who send in fan art tell your friends about the show
We're getting new people in the Facebook group all the time who heard it from a friend who heard it from a friend who
who heard it from another me and Jobin messing around.
That's Arios Speedwagon.
A band my dad once basically claimed to have discovered
because he saw them a couple of times
early in their career, right?
You know, essentially pretended he managed them
on the first three albums.
Folks, cool kids, Fridays, Fox, it's also on Hulu.
I am on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh.
Joe, Joe DeRosa comedy on Instagram, I'll be in Vegas March 29th and 30th.
Bonkers presents comedy at Topgolf. So come on out for that. New story this month in
Penthouse entitled Menu Change in the March issue. Please listen carefully because our menu
options have changed? No. Uh, and then also, uh, uh, I didn't form his back. Bill
Burr and myself, patreon .com slash burr, five bucks a month to get two episodes. Thanks, folks!