I'm here for Bet Rivers online casino and sportsbook with poker icon Phil Helmuth.
And now thanks to the excitement of Bet Rivers, I'm also a slots icon.
That's great! And a same -game parlay icon. Cool, cool. A blackjack icon,
a money -line icon, a roulette. Take it from Phil Helmuth. If you love games,
Bet Rivers is the place to play in Bet. Bet Rivers. Games on.
Must be 21 plus in present in West Virginia. Void were prohibited. Terms in conditions apply.
gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberland.
Firestone Complete Auto Care's epic savings advantage is the sign you need to stop putting
off your car's maintenance and you can save up to $100 on tires and services while you're
Don't wait, call fires don't complete out of care for an appointment.
Howdy folks, Joe DeRosa welcoming you to we'll see you in hell.
Pat's here too.
It's not just me.
I thought surely that was some sort of like sound check.
It was such a bizarre intro to the show, spotty all over the place, no real theme or
throughline to it.
As an actor, Pat, I take chances and I say nothing's off the table.
So and sometimes chances don't work out I mean for every Nicholas Cage Mandy you
got a Nicholas Cage 2 -1 -1 or whatever the new movie on Netflix is like I got
area code as a title Nicholas Cage eating a sand which is the cover of the
box. Is it an action movie this one? I think it is. I follow this site
Instant Watcher which tells you what the top 50 movies are on Netflix and
Amazon each day. It's very helpful, you know, what came out. And 2 -1 -1 was on there. It had, you
know, a 3%. And Cage has a new movie on there nearly every Friday that you've never heard of.
And it always has a verb title, searching, looking, knowing. And then the weeks where he doesn't have one,
then there's Bruce Willis lazily holding a shotgun. And those are always called like Jupiter ascendant or
or something like that.
And those are always the ones where people are like,
you know that supposed to be death wish five, right?
Right.
But it wasn't good enough.
And there's always the one with that.
It's that that one actually was really good.
The one with him and 50 cent.
That was actually really good.
I'm not gonna watch it.
I'm glad you just said 50 cent.
Cause I was wondering how I was gonna bring this up.
But for some reason, I'm a fan of 50 cent as a rapper.
Sure.
I've never really filed a film closely.
But somehow on YouTube, I got into this rabbit hole with Get Rich or Dytron.
The movie?
Yeah, like just watching clips of it and stuff.
And then I was like, how did this do?
And I looked it up online and it did very poorly.
I didn't think it made money, but it was critically slammed.
And then I was like, I wonder what happened to the guy that directed Get Rich or Dytron?
It's the fucking guy that directed my left foot.
Jim Sheridan.
In the name of the father in America one of my favorite movies of all time isn't that's insane
I know and it was written by
Terrence winter who is
Arguably the best soprano's writer next to David Chase who did the whole thing
Um, and they made a joke about it on the sopranos. There's like a used DVD bend and some guys like I you couldn't pay me three dollars to watch this shit and it's
You know the movie like the guy who wrote the episode wrote
I think he hated it too
It came out like five years too late for 50 cents prime. I never saw it. I've never seen it
I know he's got a show on stars now where he jerks off on camera called like power power
I believe you see his dick and you see him he just it's the only scene I've seen of the show he jerks off
on camera and then he was all upset because they aired it
like as if they had told him, go ahead and jerk off, but we won't show your cock, which
I just don't believe.
So you literally see his hand on his dick and you see him jerking his dick, correct?
Not to climax, but yes.
It's not like it's a cutaway on his face the whole time.
No.
Oh, check his dick in the shot.
Ugh.
Sharon Stone also claims that she was not made aware she would be showing her, her beef
in base against him.
We don't know what these stories are.
me a fucking break. I think generally that that's the whole scene. She does it to it would have
had to be written that way. You would think you would think unless unless they were like we're in a
tight we're in a tight onesie here. Right. Chair. We're you know you put a shoulder up and you know
they would have done that I wouldn't put it past anybody. Let alone Paul Verhoeven. All right man who
to use the invisibility gimmick and holloman to have the lead character spy on and sexually
assault women.
That's how he chose to use being invisible.
That's the whole plot of holloman?
That's a lot of holloman.
It's him like watching people on dress.
I've never...
It's like zapped, but the horror move.
But not fun.
Right.
I never saw Hollow Man. That was in that Sturveco's period of bacon movies that I had no,
everybody started doing these thrillers. You know, I love Sturveco's. You know, I love wild things,
but yeah, no love for Hollow Man. But it was like, it was like when, what was that movie with,
I gotta hate this movie. Everybody's always says it's good.
That movie with Bill Paxton that came out, right? For Elty? Yeah.
Yeah, it's pretty sweet.
I just didn't like it.
That was a genre for a minute.
Where they had mainstream actors suddenly
started doing these thrillers.
They weren't quite horror films.
Yeah, there was a lot of that.
It was a real early 90s kind of thing.
Like, I just, I never got into it.
Or were mid or late 90s, actually.
But it's weird, the shifts.
I mean, the biggest thing in the early 90s
was thrillers, hand the rocks, the cradle, all that.
that all those really great popcorn type thrillers,
those are gone unless they're black films, basically.
They do like, win the bow, breaks,
or win the cradle falls and all that stuff.
Right.
And I've seen a few of them and they're kind of fun,
but I don't know, it's just strange how genres change.
It's always very baffling to me.
Then teen romance and teen horror were huge in the late 90s.
You can't find one of those now to save your life.
Yeah, like I know what you did last summer.
Yeah, it makes no sense.
Yeah, yeah, I wasn't into those either scream. You know scream is good
They hit me when I was in high school, you know 90 96 to 99 so I watched all of them. Some are better than others
A lot of those teen movies are underrated dropped Ed Gorgeous is very funny
Sugar and spice very funny. Well those aren't Josie and the pussy cats very those aren't thrillers though
Those are I just I said the team comedy. Oh you did
Not another team movie is very funny spoof of those movies. Okay, you did
say that. I believe. I didn't hear you. I'm sorry. That's all right. I'm sorry. I don't know.
Am I not, I mean, that's the beauty of this. We have the tape you can see who was writing. It was
wrong. Let's go to the tape, your honor. Pat, we got a lot, I think both to say today about
our movie this week, Tales from the Hood 2. Yeah. We recently discussed Tales from the Hood,
one that really surprised me and Joe. And I think was a very entertaining horror picture
with a lot on its mind and a lot to say oh and from the hood too we might have different views
and speaking of movies and tales where this is the official announcement of what we'll be discussing
at the live shows we will be discussing tales from Halloween or of Halloween tales of Halloween
on Netflix new to Netflix yeah we'll be discussing that like probably on the early show and then in
in the late show, we'll discuss the new Halloween.
Right, the new Danny McBride, David Gordon Green,
Halloween Remix.
So if you don't wanna have that movie spoiled for you,
you have basically 24 hours to see it.
You gotta see it Friday night or Saturday during the day.
Otherwise, we're probably gonna reveal plot points
and you know what Halloween is, so.
Yeah, so anyway, those are the,
we wanted to do two Halloween theme movies
for the live show and what better to than than those two that is very
apropos. You know you're going to be rolling into this live show. Couple drinks
deep. We're going to see the new Halloween. We're going to hit Amoeba. We're
going to roll in it with positive vibes and a lot of surprises for that live
show. Very excited. Very excited about it. Get ready. Very excited. And by the way
we'll be releasing both live shows. This is the most asked question I have seen
on the Facebook page. Both live shows will be released as Patreon episodes. So if you've
been debating, if you've been on the fence, now's the time to get that Patreon, we will
be broadcasting both live shows. Yeah, the first one will be October's bonus
up in the second one will be November's bonus up. Correct.
Wow, you're through that beer already. We open to beer at the beginning of the recording
and I look over just some faint suds
on the inside of Pat's bottle.
I, today I slept for like 10 hours.
I woke up like just weary.
I forced myself to exercise and then the spear hit my lips
and I was like, well, I better nip this in the bud
before I drank 800 beers tonight.
Nip, what in the bud?
Just, you know, I had a real tame weekend.
I didn't leave my house, I chilled at home
And then it's as they say in old school and once it touches your lips, you know, you want to do more.
Oh, oh, oh, you mean I better nip the exercising in the bud.
No, I mean, I'm a little hungry, I'm a little tired, I'm a little worn out, you know.
And then you drink and then the drink hits you twice as fast because you got no water in the tank.
Right.
And I was thinking I better nip it in the bud, meaning I don't want to be hung over for a full week of work starting tomorrow.
Right. Although we have discussed going out after this recording, and we may, I thought
you were saying drinking the beer fast was nipping it in the butt. That's that's the part I didn't
understand. Let's just pretend I didn't say nip it. I drank it so fast that I realized I need to
nip my alcoholism in the butt. I guess is what I meant. Because I would say drinking at that
fast is the opposite of what you're trying to recover. Yes. Because now you need another one.
Yes, I'll probably have another good news that my court is long enough that you can make it to that fridge for where you're sitting
I'll go
Anyway, we I want to I want to give us enough time to really talk about tales
From the hood too, so if if you want to take us down to the well first. Let's get on with the show
And at the same time on
With the Joe girls they want to have fun
Joe girls just want to have fun
Right yeah, I didn't get it at first, but then I remember she goes oh, yeah, now I get it
very nice and
The morning light my father says what you're gonna do with your life
who was the father, a famous wrestler, Captain Lou Albano.
Captain Lou Albano.
show, which was the show where they would show the Mario Brothers cartoon with live
wraparound segments in their like plumbing facility. And he played Mario.
And then once a week, they'd show a Zelda cartoon.
I remember that.
Yeah.
But yeah, I do remember that.
Yeah, and it starts with a rap song where they dance in and rap.
I don't remember that song.
I also remember the Mario Brothers movie.
It was a fascinating article released about the making of that pretty recently that I
I would look up like an oral history.
Terrible film.
I've watched many making of videos and it's just,
it's wild.
Like there's the whole thing where Leguizamo
crashes the car because they were drunk.
They were drinking while they were driving the vehicle.
Yeah, Leguizamo in the oral history says he realized
like a week in, he was like,
how was Habab Hoskins not going insane?
Cause these people suck so much, these directors.
And then he realized that Hoskins was just drinking
out of a bottle of bourbon all day. So then they started drinking together all day every day,
and then every scene in that movie said they're completely drunk, like black out drunk.
Wow. It's a different time. Yeah, it was a better time. It was. I'm going to my theme today
for the movie corner, and I can only get two, but I'll add a third as well, is movies involving
severed penises. Because I watched two such movies this weekend by mistake.
Okay. I watched a bunch. The yesterday I watched movies from about noon to
midnight was fantastic. I watched Game Over Man by the Workaholics crew. How was
that? I heard it wasn't very good. Yeah, I mean it's it's a mess. The one of
The grossest things I've ever seen was in an episode of Workaholics where they are
presented at a diner a skunk carcass, like as a meal, and it's got maggots and everything
on it.
And the effect was so gross that you couldn't have laughed if you wanted to, and started a trend
of Workaholics being like a really disgusting show to the point where you couldn't laugh.
So I stopped watching it, not necessarily for that reason, I thought it got kind of significantly
are gonna be less funny over time.
This movie, it's disgusting.
It's got like insanely graphic violence,
like beyond the point where you're allowed
to then still laugh at things.
I don't mind it if it's an action movie.
This has been open with a really gross thing.
The whole, this was a big day of watching movies
I had started months right now.
So I'm hazy on the beginning of the movie.
No, I think you told me it opens with like Adam masturbating
or something.
Oh, well, there's a 10 minute scene
where he just got his dick out
running around a hotel room. That's probably what it was. There is a scene where like a dog
explodes and then like the blood splashes all over the people at this party and so it's like
a Freddie got fingered style of comedy that I don't like. I don't get it. I don't like. I don't
think anybody liked. I was very disappointed in Freddie got fingered. Not one minute of fingering
in that film. That one is the closest I came during those days to a walkout, Freddie got fingered
But I knew that it wanted me to walk out so I would not give it the satisfaction
Game over man. It's one of my dear friends John Gabris. It's a hilarious man an improviser a
Big dude a burly. Yeah, 300 pound dude. It's kind of his claim to fame
Stoner is also his claim to fame. He does a lot of drugs
And I love the man
I'm watching game over man. I get about an hour in and
And the villain is harassing this like other guy at this party that he's got held hostage
Uh -huh, and he's like you're just mad at me and waving your gun around cuz I made you eat that stripper's ass hole
And you got crabs in your throat
It's a really gross joke. It's gross not funny. That's what I'm saying gross not funny joke
And then the guys like I'm gonna get revenge on you and he brings this fat guy over
And I realized that it is my dear friend John Gaperus who strangely had never told me he was in this film
Then the villain pulls down Gaperus's pants and underwear revealing his
bent over ass pushes him face down on a table and then forces this guy at the party to
tongue out my dear friend John Gaperus's ass
What the fuck and I'm just kind of sitting there like I'm too old for this, you know daddy Glover style
That's exactly right. Yeah, I got you feeling more like Danny Glover every day.
Um, I've got a decent sized list here, but you know what I just realized?
We got to record two episodes today, right? And then we have two on Saturday, right?
And your week's going to be nuts. We better save some movies for the movie corner on Saturday.
I'm going to have plenty. All right. I'm just looking out for you. I'm going to have time. I watched a ton.
I watched a film, a little film called, I mean, I wasn't done. Oh, you weren't done. Oh, so sorry.
I mean, I was just sort of listing things that happened. I thought that was the climax. I thought that was the closer to the story is the fat man getting his ass hole eaten out.
No, I mean, that could be the end of my review. I think you get what I'm saying.
It was real hard for laughter to sneak through. Although there were some shootouts, some action
sequences, some violent sequences that were really well done and kind of cool and fun,
not enough to recommend it. There were also a couple lines I enjoyed. For example, they find this
big pile of hand lotion. And the guy says, damn, this is like a buffalo bill went to Costco amount of
hand lotion. That's a funny joke. Yeah. But it's the kind of movie where those jokes make you go,
oh, that was weird. As opposed to there being a lot of funny jokes. Right. I can't recommend it.
I like the early years of Workaholics. I think those fellows are funny. I can't recommend it. Sorry.
Joe, go ahead. I watched a film called American Fable. What the hell's that? It's a movie that plays
like a fable. Draws its inspirations from ASOP. There's a little ASOP in there. There's
a little fairy tale quality. It's a thriller. There are a few moments where, well not a few
moments. For the first half of the movie, you're not sure if this is going to turn into some
sort of fantastic thing or whatever. But it's, who was ASOP? Is he an actual person? An old man?
What is it sign fell routine you're doing I want to know who I stop what I really do was he an actual person
Yeah, he wrote the fables he wrote the fables and like the 19 hundos the 17 hundos pet
I don't even know if he was an actual person let alone what year he penn these things, but yeah
I think yeah, all right. You're listening to a stop rock
You're listening a sap rocky. I've listened to both. Yeah thoughts on each it bothered me that a sap rocky was
basically took his name from ASAP rock.
I found that strange.
Yeah.
I do like all the ASAP Rocky albums.
I like ASAP rock, what I've heard fine.
And I like ASAP Ferd, who was also in the ASAP mob.
I like Fergie myself.
She pissed her pants once.
I know.
That's why I like her.
All right.
Uh, it's a, it's a, it's a, it's a marginally fun thriller.
or it's, where's it about, never even heard of this thing.
And it's about a, it's about a farm in the 1980s
and the farms are, the farm community is collapsing.
All the farms are being bought up by developers
and everybody's going broke and belly up and blah, blah, blah.
Yeah.
Well, it's good that you care about the common man.
It's about a farm in the 80s.
I mean, what takes place on the farm
and then the little girl finds a man inside of this old abandoned silo on her property.
Silo and I was young that the dad tells her to stay away from.
You ever heard that song?
Yeah.
Can I just get through this?
I just want to, I don't really want to talk about this movie long.
Shiloh by Neil Diamond.
I just always like, like your pick and move is now that like no one has heard of.
every week, you're like, yeah, I saw, you know, like deteriorating astronaut.
What, what do I, what do you get on our shoulder black?
You're going to marshal my movies?
I just, I don't know, I can't even join the conversation.
I got to start singing Shiloh.
You don't need to join.
You just, let me say the way if it was good or not, we could move on.
That's why I want to move on.
It wasn't a great movie.
I thought I maybe had discovered some fun little thriller.
All right, and it's, it was kind of boring.
But the plot is she finds this man locked in this silo. And again, you don't know if this is real or not, yeah, and
And then as the movie
Spoiler alert as the movie unfolds you realize he's a missing land developer who the dad has kidnapped and
Put into the silo
So he can't ruin any more farms
That sounds horrible.
Joe, we live in an age where like you're not going to like watch some random movie and
it'll be amazing.
You can look and there'll be a hundred people that have written about these unsung classic.
There's where I watched it.
The damn thing was on.
I think Amazon.
What's it called again?
American Fable.
Okay.
The title.
I was like, oh that's an interesting title.
Is this like a fantasy movie?
The thumbnail for the thing was like wicked queen on a horse in a corn field.
And I was like, oh, this looks like it's going to be like a horror movie.
Then read the description. It's like drawing its inspirations from fairy tales,
gothic horror. And I was like, oh, this sounds like it's going to be awesome.
And then I watch it, and I'm watching, and I'm watching it.
And then you get to the point where you go, well, now I can't turn back. I started.
And at that point, I started looking up reviews, which also the same thing.
It was, it was, it was, it was expertly directed for a first -time director, which it was, but the movie just isn't that interesting.
Alright, so, so there you go. There's your fucking American fable.
I watched The Package, which is another Netflix original.
And another, you think you'd learn from Game Overman, and you turn immediately to a movie where a guy gets his dick cut off.
But the package was surprisingly well -reviewed, and I saw some guy, I follow a lot of film guys on Twitter, and a lot of them really raved about it and said like it's a return to the American pie and the raunchy days or whatever.
Guys, pull your heads out of your fucking ass.
pull your heads out of your fucking asses the package was not good it was not
funny the cast was not particularly amusing or likable it was by the guy who
did Mike and Dave need wedding dates one of the more hotly contested titles on
this show yeah yeah you never even saw it's up there with tower heist you never even
It's all I refused to see it, but you certainly knew all I know is the wife from the great outdoors is in it
That's the only thing that makes me kind of want to see it. Yes, she is. She plays like the answer. So okay
Yeah, um, I
Don't know what to tell you. I thought that movie was funny as we all know
I just thought this wasn't it was a real long 90 minutes. I mean basically it's a guy accidentally cuts his dick off on a camping trip
There are 35 scenes in this fucking thing where they put the dick in a cooler.
They trip over a branch and the dick comes flying out of the cooler and slow motion.
They do it 35 times.
It's just a movie like that premise could have led to an amazing comedy, you know, whether
or not they show you the dick a million times as this one does or not could have been subtle,
could have been gross out.
but this movie just has no imagination to it.
They're trying to get the dick from A to B.
They fall into the same obstacles again and again
and again, which basically involves tripping
and dropping the dick.
It just did not work in any way.
I did some research on it.
It was the subject of a mass intense bidding war,
the script that Netflix won.
Just goes to show you, it's like in the TV pilot world,
There's a pilot every year called like fucking bitch
And then there's a big bidding war for it, right? And then you read it. And it's just a standard
sitcom pilot that's boring and has nothing to do. They decided I'll name it fucking bitch
So everyone can think it's edgy even though you can't call a show on network television fucking bitch
Right, and they buy it and they're like, oh, we can't do the edgy version of this and the show never gets made
People are just fooled by these flashy thing you read that movie about the guy who gets his dick cut off
Well, that sounds funny, and then everyone's bidding on it.
But at the end of the day, nobody cares.
Nobody wants to see it.
There's nothing original about it.
It's a sick business.
What's your next movie, Jim?
I'll close this out on a high note.
Are you going more than two?
Didn't you say?
Has movie corner involves three pictures each week?
Okay.
I thought at the beginning you said you had two.
I have tons, I said.
No, no, no.
Oh, I have two about people cutting the Dicks off.
And you go, I thought you meant, like, so those were the ones
the God damn it. I thought you said that you were okay spider. I rewatched the film Delirious
John Candy or I'm candy. Okay. I have always loved the movie. I loved it again. Yeah,
I hadn't seen it in years. I was worried that I actually put it on because I hadn't seen it
in so long. I thought, well, I love this as a kid. It probably doesn't hold up and it'll be easy
to fall asleep to, ended up staying up watching it front to fucking back, it's a fucking
really funny movie man and it just got panned. I haven't seen it since it came to video
when I was a boy and maybe I'll give it another shot. I don't remember liking it much then.
I put it with once upon a crime where I was very disappointed. I watched or tried to watch
once upon a crime based on my thrill of delirious and I couldn't even get through it and that's
It's quite a cast.
Levy.
Sort of is.
Levy directed it.
It's Richard Lewis.
Yeah.
It's like Richard Lewis.
Sean Young.
Yeah.
Jim Belushi.
Okay.
You haven't.
Uh, but uh, excuse me.
She, uh, that was when every movie poster was the cast in front of a, uh, police lineup.
Yeah.
They did that on like 800 movies.
Review.
I read on Ron Tomatoes of Once Upon a Crime was, uh, uh, uh, usually a movie.
movie, usually movies centering around the plot, usually movies whose plots center around
a stolen dog aren't very good.
This one has no exception.
Sure.
Well, John Wick blew that theory out of the water.
Well, this was a review written 20 years ago.
That's true.
But I bet they ate their words when they saw John Wick.
Yeah, sure.
Delirious was, I thought it was a lot of fun.
It's about a writer who who somehow wakes up after an accident in his own shitty soap opera that he writes right then he realizes that as he writes in that world, he can affect it okay, but there's a there's a jerk off.
You know, suit writer whatever hired by the network people that gets introduced earlier in the film and he realizes that that guy is still writing against him.
Played by him in the real world. Nobody famous. Okay. So he's so he can't just do anything
He's got a fight against this other guy's writing, but it's funny and there's a great line when
The guy that played sledgehammer. Which is name again David rash. Yeah
He's got a great line where he's a doctor and
Somebody needs the Heimlich maneuver and John candy does it so he can impress this woman
He writes it that he does it and the doctor doesn't know what to do
as the person's joking.
And after John Candy saves the person,
the doctor's all distraught and everybody's going,
shame on you, you're it, you know.
And he's like, I'm a doctor.
I know the Heimlich maneuver.
I do it all the time.
It's one of my favorite maneuvers.
All right, yeah, it's a funny movie.
I'll rewatch it.
I lately, when I've been revisiting things
that I remembered as not being great,
I'm proven correct.
I have a few of those for next week's
Movie corner. I'd like to close. I just finished the third season of HBO's in secure
Which I just think is a really good show that I have never spoken about on here before
It stars it's a ray who I found a little annoying and like the first couple of episodes
She was playing like aren't I a nerd a little too hard because she's a absolutely stunningly gorgeous person and that can be
difficult for true nerds to watch someone act like they're a nerd and they're gorgeous.
But she quickly, I think learned that that was not her strong suit and just played herself
as a woman who struggles with relationships and intimacy and dating.
It was kind of like a black sex in the city -ish, but much younger here in LA, so it's cool
to see all the places you've been and all the locations that you go to in different bars
and stuff. The haunts. The haunts. Yeah. But I just think it's a extremely well -written relationship
show way better than like divorce and the other recent attempts that HBO has had. Who feels
very truthful, feels very funny, some hot sex on it. It's a great show. There are three seasons
in, each seasons like eight episodes. I recommend it. Have you seen the trailer for this camping show?
what the fuck is camping? I know a guy who writes for it is a great guy I'm not
going to spit I haven't seen it but I'm just like how is this a show? My buddy
brilliant. I love Juliet Lewis. My buddy Bridget, Everett is in it. I love Bridget
Everett and I was happy to see that she was in a show and YouTube for some reason
like one night every video I watch they'd run a two -minute scene from that show.
Yeah I'm in the fucking thing is I'm just like what are they? This is like it's
like, there was a time. Now modern family say, right? Right.
Not a family is a good show, but it's also a good show for that for
net for ABC. You know what I mean? Like that to show ABC. But
you're like, given all the fucking boundaries that get put on
things on one of the three major networks, this is they did a
pretty good fucking job here. You expect one the other night
hadn't seen it in five years. I was laughing out loud.
Modern family has great characters and great jokes unquestionably.
I expect a little more out of HBO.
Of course.
There are no boundaries they can do whatever they want.
It's not TV.
It's HBO.
So to have this comedy where the jokes are very, you know, they're just, like, these characters
aren't very believable.
Right.
Juliet Lewis is playing this like, you know, it's funny, but it's kind of funny.
But, you know, that's when I realized I didn't need vitamins.
It's vital. They should read, you know, like one of these hippie fucking and it's like
I guess this character is sort of believable like, but I
Mean who I'm watching HBO. I don't a bit about vitamins being bad
I don't know. It's just boring. Well, you know when you go you see go see a comedian and to me
Seinfeld never went this way even though Seinfeld is one of the richest men in America I would imagine but
but you go see your comedian that you love,
and then at some point you realize their jokes
are just about like flying first class,
and like how you can't get a good reservation
at a five star restaurant or whatever,
and they start to kind of edge you out.
That is what HBO has completely become.
There's no eastbound and down anymore.
There's no show for the people.
It's just these shows for like people who think they're smart,
people who laugh too loud at a movie at an art house
to prove that they get the jokes.
I think John Oliver show is very smart and funny, but there's also this air of smugness
and superiority about it that always keeps me at a distance.
Well, make no, no, there are no two ways about it.
I am a fan of John Oliver and I enjoy his show whenever I catch it.
But that is a show for privileged white people.
I mean, that is a show for people with money, mostly white.
I mean, that is not a show for the people.
Well, it's the same thing like Bill Maher.
Bill Maher is talking to people in the Hamptons.
You know what I mean?
And I like Bill Maher too, but like it's just,
I don't like Bill Maher.
John Oliver is pretending he's not Bill Maher,
and to some degree, yes, I think he's better
and a better joke writer, but they are
to playing with the exact same people.
People have nothing to worry about.
And that to me is the network in a nutshell.
I have nothing to worry about except their worries.
where I like it is is in an insecure when they're showing you not a
huxedible diversion of black America, but they're showing you a very
different side of like Inglewood than you generally see in movies and TV, right?
And I think it's an awesome show and just that regard as like a sort of travel
log type show of lesser explored areas. That's right. That's why Friday was so
awesome. Ice Cube said. Absolutely. Ice Cube said. He was like, I just I wanted to see
a movie about the hood that was fun. Yeah. It's not all fucking awful shit like we had fun man.
Right. Yeah. So, um, but I think everything else on HBO, uh, can kind of fuck itself at this
point. I think Silicon Valley is a very snobby show. I think divorce isn't unwatchably snobby show.
I haven't seen divorce yet. Um, they're just movies for and about rich people or shows about
foreign about rich people. Yeah. Apparently they're doing a new dynamic bride, Adam Divine,
John Goodman show about televangelists. Oh, okay. I think that's going to be fucking great.
I would imagine. I liked vice principals, but like you can't have only dynamic bride holding up
the rest of America portion of your network. Like high maintenance is an awesome show and very
well written, but that too everybody in it is talking about, you know, the new, uh, what's
Never the fuck Indy film or whatever there's no like real people in it. Oh, that's the pot one. Yes
Yeah, no, that's that's I like the show quite a bit. I just good
But it caters to very specific personality types. I would say that's what I'm saying. That's all I'm saying all right. Well, look
I'll let you end it there great because we're at 35 minutes
Right, I mean Joe's a real time keeper folks. Well, I could talk all day
Joe says you guys don't deserve more than a strict hour. I died
Even after all you've done for us and I argue with them about it. I haven't written on the wall over the TV
So Pat doesn't forget
Well, I want to do a I want to get to a 24 -hour news psycho. Oh, please and I'll grab a beer while you're doing from screaming in
and ladies and gentlemen, much to my surprise,
I didn't know I'd be here this soon,
the Pet Cemetery trailer came out
for the new Pet Cemetery.
And to me, that's news for two reasons.
Number one, it's a movie that a lot of horror fans
are obviously looking forward to.
Number two, is it a Lithgow?
Yeah, okay.
Lithgow and Jason Clark, the guy that we keep talking about
that I can remember his name.
And the trailer is great, but oh, it's also news because the director announced the
same day, like this movie will definitely be rated R and his quote was, it's a fucked
up movie, right?
Real spooky imagery in the trailer, it looks to be well directed and well acted.
I don't know that you see Lith gal in it, but his voice is what's narrating the trailer.
I'm the fucking love Lith gal.
I do too.
I don't remember.
I mean, how long has it been since we've seen Lithgow and like a juicy big budget movie he's done such great work in TV
But rise the planet of the apes probably
He was in the first one. Yeah, he played the dad with he played James Franco's dad that had all assignments. Oh, okay
Yeah, he was great in that. Yeah, it's great. He always is. I love him
One weird thing. It's not a criticism. It was just something I wasn't ready for Lithgow does not play it with the new England accent
I'm disappointed
I thought I was too, but I understand why he didn't do it.
I was like, if he was doing, he as an actor was like,
if I do that accent, it's gonna sound like
I'm just parroting Fred Gwynn, and I'm like, he's right.
You can't be an older man and do that accent
and not sound like you're doing Fred Gwynn in that role.
So, the boys aren't gonna bury that kitty cat, are ya?
Up there on the top of Old Pet Cemetery Hill, rocking chair.
That's a beloved character I return to on Twitter a lot is me and a rocking chair on my porch and
Then all the teens gather around me to hear my
My wisdom right I use it a lot on Twitter and you do this on my I thought Twitter had
Had made a new rule that unless you were bitching about politics you weren't allowed to tweet
I tweet now once a month and then I get out as quickly as I came because I can't even stand it
Shutting that fucking thing down is a joyless hole I ever did. It is it is it is so out of my life
I took Instagram off my phone. Yeah, I never look at Facebook. I just love it. I should too Facebook
Just had another five million person leak. I'm like, what am I doing?
Yeah, I don't have any band it. Yeah
They band it. I was when I was over there. I was like, why did they ban Facebook and Google?
And they're like because they thought that when they were gonna sell our information to people right and I'm like they did yeah
Well, how does pet cemetery look?
It looks great.
It looks very atmospheric, very moody.
As I said, it looked...
It's a strange thing to say after you see the trailer,
but just from the trailer alone, I was like,
this looks like it was really well directed.
Who directed it?
I don't know.
Remember when we had this exact...
Who directed it?
I thought maybe you looked it up.
No.
I mean...
Are the animals what, CGI?
No.
People in animal costumes?
Yeah.
It's...
They're puppets.
Puppets, okay.
So there's a the Henson company did most of the work as far as I understand pet cemetery 2019 film. Yeah, I'll show you a picture of church the cat.
Do you like the original bad cemetery film? I love it. Yeah, do you like that cemetery too? No, it's a that's dog shit. Oh, also they announced that Zelda in this version will be true to the book. She'll be a 12 year old girl.
Okay, and they said it will still be very scary, but, you know, we don't know until we see a scene in Pets Elementary of the Ridge.
Kevin Colch and Dennis Widmer directed this film.
Kevin Colch also directed Starry Eyes.
Okay, I know people love that I never saw him.
He directed a segment in holidays.
It looks like those are the two standouts.
He the horror is a genre where you can make a jump to the big time real quick. Yeah
Anyway, it looks good go check out the trailer. I was gonna show you the picture of church the cat
We should do an episode where you and I watched like 15 new trailers. Oh
That'd be fun. You should do that soon
That'd be fun. There's a lot of Apple page or whatever
There's church back from the dead. Okay. Did you see the trailer for the Will Smith Aladdin?
Yeah, did you see what happened with the writers?
No, and I haven't seen the trailer either, but what's it all about the trailers musical
It's it's a teaser. It's it's the cave mouth opening and the voice being doing that rhyme
About the worthy one or whatever. Yeah, and the fucking writers of the or animated one came out and they were like
Hey, it's funny that the only dialogue in the new Aladdin trailer is stuff me and my writing partner wrote for the original movie and we haven't gotten a fucking dime
And he goes, and he goes, by the way, this is what Disney does with all of these remakes.
They don't pay anybody that worked on the original material.
Not a surprise.
Wow.
Disney's getting it.
Disney's, I mean, that's the thing.
You start throwing your dick all around, somebody's going to stick it to you, walking around
buying up everything.
Yeah.
You know?
They're buying Fox, like within three weeks, and I work at Fox, so every week, like people
look at their panicking for their lives.
Anyway, that was this new screen -in -ins.
Let's get to the flick.
All right.
Yeah.
Tales from the hood too.
It's now streaming on Netflix.
I had sort of read advance, not so great word,
but I was like, you know what?
Tales from the hood had its haters too,
and I really admired that movie.
The same creative team, Spike Lee returning as an EP, I thought, how can we go wrong?
And you got your, you'd hate to see Clarence Williams drop out, but then Keith David steps
in.
Right.
And you think, this is great.
This movie was fucking horrible from start to finish.
And even though it's hard is in the right place and it's got a decent message
I'm not gonna give this thing a fucking pass. This is a shit movie. Yes the shit the shit
How many times they go back to that joke so many every segment it's not funny anymore every segment
He would go back to that the shit then there's a button scene on the credits where or the last line whatever in the movie now
Now that's some shit, I'm like, stop it.
You didn't invent the word shit.
They do it, they call back to it like five times.
This movie sucked.
It looks as though it cost 1 -100th of the original movie
and those are 1995 dollars.
It appears to have been shot on like an iPhone,
edited in iMovie, it's cheap,
which okay low budget is fine, but these stories are so fucking preachy that at
times they forget they're even trying to tell you a story or be entertaining.
You're just watching like it's like a film designed for like a history of
racism course at like a community college. Yeah. There is no entertainment value in
it at all. Well, and it hits its point so obviously. And so like boringly that you don't
feel anything, you're certainly not scared. It does not work as a horror movie at all.
No, but really as social commentary, it's so lazy and obvious and shitty. I was kind of
appalled by it. A lot of that had to do with the one -dimensional villains. Yeah. Now in
In the first movie, the villains were not incredibly complex, but a one or two -dimensional
villain works when it's a racist cop.
You don't really need to know much more.
You know that racist cops exist, and you don't need to get much more across than that
in the story and the point you're trying to tell.
This fucking thing opens with a story about a 22 -year -old blonde girl who's obsessed with
like, Mammie dolls and shit like that.
And it's like, couldn't you have made it like believable?
Make it an older lady, like to do make it up,
like I'm sorry, like in this woke day and age,
I'm just not, but I'm not saying this person can't exist.
I'm just not buying it.
And then she's like, she wants this one doll so badly
because she goes, it looks like my first
that I ever got from my grandma.
And then she wants it so bad she breaks into the museum
him to steal it when the guy won't sell it to her.
I mean, it's fucking stupid.
It's just not supposed to believe there is a gorgeous,
like 16 year old girl who was obsessed
with the Mami culture and a little duck.
It's so stupid that you can't get on board with it.
And here's off the top of my head,
what would have been a very interesting segment.
Is that same girl, the same actress,
you have the same people,
But you go into the fetishization of black men or something like that where, you know, like then that is something that you can really hear two sides of the debate.
You can hear the pros and cons.
This just created its own thing.
It wanted to tell a story about Mammies and those dolls and found this way in that was so kind of embarrassing.
saying that a movie like Ghost World,
where Bishemmi is obsessed with that culture.
Honestly, dealt with this stuff
in a more sort of sensitive way, oddly enough.
Here's another grape I have with the film.
Are we done with that segment?
Because eventually she gives birth.
She gives birth to a bunch of men.
Well, then the doll comes to life,
which is just basically the third story of the last movie,
which they do call back to because the doll
from the Corbin Burnson story is in the place, but it's still the same premise.
This doll has been poisoned by racism and because of that it possesses the spirit of the
tortured souls that suffered through that time period.
It's the same fucking story, but instead of it being this cool, creepy little weird puppet
doll that comes to life, this thing comes to life and it's just a guy in a giant cloth costume.
It's ridiculous.
Looking honestly like a gingerbread man. It looked ridiculous. Yeah, it wasn't it wasn't
There was nothing
Moody or creepy or scary about it and then
Yeah, and then he fucks her and she gets pregnant because she wants to fuck the doll by the way
Yeah, she's like coming on to the doll because that's how much she loves
These dolls dolls of the old self like and then she gets pregnant and I'm not missing some commentary here either
I think that this was just really like a badly done story.
Here's where the movie went wrong to begin with.
Pat, what's the name of this movie?
Tales from the Hood 2.
Maybe one of the stories takes place in the hood.
That are very valid point literally not one story in the hood. I bear it
We barely saw the hood even even the story that connects the stories. So those those stories should those tales
Should be coming from the hood
And they're in a lab they're in a lab creating a robot like the country somewhere. Yeah
There is literally not what didn't even occur to me excellent point
No stories coming from the hood no tales from the hood by the way
Not only not only were the tales of taking place in the hood some of them revolved around white women that lived in mansions in the suburbs
Correct what how far away from this are we getting correct? So like let's go to the second story
There's a man that I thought was AJ Benza
But then realized it was the guy the gay closet guy from madman. Yeah, yeah
You watch like this like kind of fucked up prison sort of sequence and you know you accused the sky of
You know, in a sort of weirdly homophobic scene of like taking it in the ass in prison and then it's all very generic shit
They're shaking this guy down right who was a pimp right and they're shaking him down for money and the guy says
I'm not a pimp anymore. Yeah
I've cleaned up and they don't want to hear that and they get angry and they're beating him trying to get the money out of him again
This could have been in a sort of hood relative place
They're in a garage of nothing but $200 ,000 cars.
Yeah, like a warehouse.
Then cut to a TV.
So they kill them.
They kill them.
Cut to a TV psychic for the most boring five minutes of a film I've seen in a long time.
Then suddenly, this psychic starts performing the pimp through himself.
Well, this segment felt like, you know, as in like an all of me type scenario where the
ghost is coming through this white guy.
You're skipping a huge, you just made a big jump there.
The gang, first of all, it jumps to the psychic story.
I literally thought I had missed the end of the prior story, because it's such a hard
turn.
I'm like, what is happening?
Exactly.
And it seemed like a new story.
Yeah.
So I'm watching that.
And then I realize, oh, and then it cuts and you see that the gangster that killed the guy
is watching the psychic and then calls his buddies and says,
I know how we can find the money and their plan is,
they're gonna force the,
they're gonna break into the psychic's house
and at gunpoint make him summon the spirit of the dead pimp
to tell them where the money is.
And all of me, you are 100 % right.
That thing where he starts doing all the people they killed,
he's channeling all their spirits and like,
and one of them's a mobster,
like a mafia mobster and I swear to God the line is one of the gangsters going
Sammy the shark right I mean Jesus Christ those scenes if I'm not mistaken
because it was hard to tell what tone this was going for moment to moment were
played for comedy at the expense of a white guy doing a black voice if those
scenes weren't played for comedy and it was supposed to be scary I don't know
what to tell you. But I think that there was, they were in on the joke of that. But my
God was funny. Yeah, it wasn't funny though. It was terrible. And it felt again, sort
of like wrong to be watching in a way. It felt like more racist than the racism it was
calling out at times. And that story, yes. That story was far in a way the best story of
all four. That was the best story. I have a hard time declaring a winner because I hated
them all, but the joke is in there too, where he's like, where they're like, where he's
going to kill the gangsters now that killed him initially. And he goes, you know, and
the guy goes, we brought you back like, come on, man, look, you're in a mansion and you
can be this psychic guy and you're famous and whatever. Why would you be mad about that?
And the line is because I have a, I had a bigger dick. Yeah. It's terrible. It's just,
It's just hacky humor, it's terrible.
Yeah, it really sucked.
It reminded me so much of a course I took in college.
And I don't even remember the name of it,
but it was a sociology course.
And it was just learning about like the most obvious things.
Like it would be like, did you know like the Cosby Show
like introduced affluent black families
to white America or whatever and I'd be sitting there like,
well yeah, you'd look around and there were these kids like,
like, oh my God, like yeah.
It was like one of those classes where like 29 white people
were having their minds blown, you know,
and there was one black guy like seriously.
Yeah, are we really taking this class?
It was gross.
It was in Missouri.
I always felt gross in the class.
And weirdly, I thought gross watching this movie.
And to know it was made by an all black team.
I found the kind of bad.
I'm scratching my head.
The third story is just a me too story
and doesn't take place in the hood.
So now it's, it were twice removed.
Setters around an Asian woman and a black woman.
Yeah.
But now, and there are, once again, rich,
two rich women in the suburbs,
the kids going there to me to them are rich.
They're driving a fucking convertible.
This story offended the hell out of them.
It was five minutes long for starters.
They're already doing me too
in the fucking wraparound story
where the boss keeps grabbing her ass, so maybe we could have cut that out of the wrap -around
story if you're going to do its own story because it makes no sense and it honestly feels
cheap and gross to be using it in your fucking robot politician story that you're trying to do.
This one I was scratching my head because I literally would have this conversation over and over
in my head while I was watching. I was like, why are they doing a Me Too story? Oh well, Me Too
is a problem in the thing in the hood. Then why aren't they in the fucking hood?
And it just kept going back and I just right how does it affect the hood if you're going to do the hood story because we all know how it affects
You know people in affluent societies
This you know like this politician that they force this me to story on and the wraparound story
It he's doing enough you don't have to also give in that to hate the guy
Well, it's I mean about one -dimensional villains. It was it was it was like the guy is so careless that you're like oh come on right
but you know, but it's, by the way,
the wraparound story is just, that's the worst.
Oh, well, when the row, I think we should deal
with the robot turning on him at the end of the show.
Well, we will, but let's first get to the fourth story.
I'm not done with the Me Too, too.
So these women, and they have them in bras and panties
for the entire scene, which felt very gratuitous to me,
and a movie that's supposed to be making a point about Me Too,
But they're lying there drug these guys are talking about how they're going to fuck them
While they're unconscious and there are jokes between them
And I don't mean like they're joking like their characters are scummy
There are jokes that I believe we the audience are expected to laugh with like when he says
Like hey, I would never hit a woman like what's wrong with you now?
Let's fuck these women that we've knocked unconscious. That's like a multi -cam sitcom joke right where they're standing there
Basically dicks out ready to rape a couple of unconscious women. What is the tone of this fucking thing?
What is the tone of it then they become vampires the women do the women become vampires and punish these guys to like hell
It all takes like five minutes, and here's the big moral of this story
Date rape is bad raping an unconscious woman is bad. Hey, thanks tales from the hood, too
You don't have any more interesting spin than that
Well, they really thought it was clever that they were like the women are predators and
they prey on the men that are predators.
They really thought there was like a really clever twist because the women ended up eating
them and feeding them to a hungry vamp with some shit.
But the desk one too, I mean, I literally yelled this at the TV.
The second these two rich guys get to the house of the two rich women, yeah, that they're going to fuck
Or that they met on Tinder or whatever the fuck it is
The immediately the women are ready to have sex with them right after
Playing cards against humanity which clearly paid to have the game in the movie
Yeah, so then they play they they're like drinking all night. They're playing cards against humanity
They're laughing everything out of the women's mouth is a dick joke and how they want to have sex
They would have had sex with involuntarily and then the guy goes off and roofies them like it's just I'm not saying again
That that doesn't happen. I'm just saying it's bad writing make it that the guys make the guy more of a scumbag
Make it that the girl isn't going to fuck him and then he does that so I really hate hate him even fucking more
It's just write it write it put some tension or conflict into this thing. Yeah
It was it was very badly done. They were all very badly done and now I can't get this hoot thing out of my head
which I wasn't even thinking about because, of course, there's so much more to say 20 years later
about how the hood has evolved and what has changed since the original movie.
Yeah. Nothing. Not really not even a mention.
Nope. No story.
No, nothing. And the wrap around with this Trump guy that's basically supposed to be Donald Trump.
Not the only mention they make of his, of the effect of a guy like that on certain communities
in the country is when he makes a joke about his prisons that he owns being filled with
black people.
That's it.
Hey, here's an idea.
Maybe that's a fucking story you do.
Maybe you do a jail story.
Right.
Then they really introduced something interesting with immigration, which would also not be a
story from the hood, but he's like the robot comes out who's supposed to be cracking down
on crime.
Right away.
Don't get to the robot yet.
We're not there yet.
You're talking about the man.
I thought we were there.
I don't know, I'm just saying in this wrap around, which is leading us to the fourth
story.
All right.
I don't even remember the fourth story.
The fourth story is not only a mirror of the wrap around story, a white politician who's
corrupted dirty.
It's an, it's an identical retelling to the carbon burns and story, except the only
difference is is this, this one does flashbacks of the, Emmett Till, Emmett Till, who was,
He was attributed with starting the civil rights movement because he was beaten to death.
This one felt like something when you have a substitute, excuse me, a substitute teacher
in eighth grade that they would show you this story.
That's what it felt like to me.
This fucking story, and I rewound it and timed it, 33 minutes, 33 minutes this story.
Not one part of it is a tale, not one part of it is scary.
not one part of it is supposed to be horror.
It's literally just like like a bad twilight zone.
Yeah, and not even really like the ghosts of Emmett Till and Martin Luther King
and the four girls blown up in the church.
They all come and like talk to this guy to tell him like,
you know, you've got so much more freedom than we did.
You need to use it better than how you're using it.
Yeah, because he's working for the white,
It's called digital white politics in black man.
Corbin Birnsen, the black guys were working for him in that one, you know, and there's
the conflict of, you know, right, am I doing the wrong thing here, whatever.
But like, let me tell you this, of course, there's a billion things to say about Donald Trump
and the politics of today's society and how that affects black people and how that affects
minorities and how that affects immigrants and everyone.
one. This story at the end of the day, who is this for? Is it for Omarosa? Because what
other high level black person is working for Donald Trump? You're not, you're not even
calling out someone. This isn't a real problem. There are, you know, legitimate issues raised
in the movie, but to be going after some, a black person for supporting Trump, I think there
How many are there? I think it was not many.
Well, I think it was a shot at black Republicans.
Because that is a thing on YouTube.
We're like, is that a big enough issue?
Really? Black Republicans?
Well, that was his issue with it.
They're the writers issue.
That's why that's what it was about.
It was about like, how could you support this team
when they do this?
But again, there's a way to do that.
And there are black Republicans,
but it's certainly not the majority.
You know, like, what do you, here's a thing?
It's too small a target to build this 33 -minute segment around.
I think a 33 -minute segment was not needed.
I think there are better things that they could have had the ghost of Emmett Till come
back and yell at a guy for not appreciating.
And I also think once again, one dimensional, you got the guy that's running for governor
or the state and he's standing there and he's going, my colleague, his campaign manager
and he's going, he's got a beautiful white wife.
In the same breath that he's saying
we've gotten past racism and it's like guys,
there's a lot of dumb racist politicians out there.
How many of them are that fucking dumb?
That during a speech to voters, they're pointing that out.
They're putting an emphasis on the word white.
It's like just give it a little nuance for Christ's sake.
It's so much more interesting to watch a guy's swindle people and to watch a guy just say awful shit
And everybody just goes along with it inexplicably
And the stuff with his wife where she's gonna kill the baby and all that you know just
not none of it played
It's you're absolutely right that it was not any kind of horror movie. There was no no horror element to it and
There were big chunks of this especially like the field of dreams with
Black icons, Martin Luther King and Emmett Till and et cetera.
And it really was a field of dreams, like they're all ghosts standing there in front of them,
where they abandoned all pretense of horror, of storytelling, of anything, and it really
just became sort of an educational film strip.
And it makes no sense.
In an R -rated horror movie that's also going to like do big jokes and have girls running
around on their underwear.
where I found the whole thing to be an absolute disaster
and a mess.
The movie's terrible.
Now we haven't even gotten to the robot.
The end.
So this wraparound story is about this politician.
The reason that Sims is there telling stories to him
is because they've created an artificial intelligence
that will police society.
Right.
All Robocop.
He needs to tell, he needs Sims to tell him the robot story so the robot can learn what
crime it.
It's such a convoluted fucking plot.
Anyway, at the end, honestly, until the end, I didn't know what was going on in that story.
I didn't know idea what was going on in that story.
It's not.
So in the end, they do the big presentation like in Robocop.
The robot comes out like in Robocop.
It looks literally like something that would come in a happy meal.
Yeah, it's it's it's it's it look like Johnny five. It's horrible. Yeah, Johnny five looked
a hundred times better. This thing looked like a look like a man in a plastic suit. Look ridiculous. Right.
And then
the thing goes haywire and kills the candidate who's presenting the robot to the people.
Just like it's like fucking Robo cop right first is like
Six of you are illegal immigrants. They have six Hispanic people get up and like get captured by the robot
And I'm like all right then three of you are robbers and like three people who have robbed get up and you're like oh my god
Yeah, by the way, what illegal immigrant is going to the public rally that the racist politician is holding
Who's coming? I got to get over it.
Joe, it's an extremely valid question.
Then they ask the robot who you've neglected to mention, and I wrote it down here, is
named Robo Patriot.
Then Robo Patriot turns, and they're like, the Robo Patriot's job is to eliminate any threats
to America.
it turns on the politician and says the following quote robo patriot identifies
punk ass bitch yeah and it shoots the president and do you do you get the
why he says punk ass bitch do I get why he says it hold on a second keep keep
talking because I got to look this up well yeah then basically it ends with
Keith David, driving him to hell.
The one aspect of this movie I thought was cool was like the incredibly cheesy Tim Burton
ask opening credits with like floating skulls and shit.
Certainly not enough to recommend it.
It looked like a screensaver but I thought it was kind of neat and cute and old fashioned.
I was, see, I disagreed with you on that.
Even when that credit sequence started, I was like, we might be in trouble here, man.
this doesn't look good. Did you stick around for the ending sort of rap metal song that played over
the credits, which would have been outdated in 1994? Pat, I made a note of it. I haven't heard a song
that bad in years. I made a note of it. Again, this is Tales from the Hood. The movie ends with an
an industrial song with like a corny white guy rapping over it.
Yeah, industible.
What in the fuck is happening?
How do you not end this movie with a rap song?
Or an R &B song?
Or a rock, anything that it comes, one music,
the only music that didn't come from the hood
is industrial music.
It's the only music that didn't come from that neighborhood.
And by the way, I hate industrial music.
I think most people do, but industrial music hasn't been popular in 15 years, and even
my industrial music standards, this was bad.
This was worse than the norm, and I believe it was a white guy wrapping the song.
I looked it up and he, if I found the right guy, it wasn't white, dude, and look, nobody's
saying white people can't live in the hood, and nobody's saying that only black people
live in the hood.
but for Chris Sakes, guys, at least have an M &M song.
Have a rap song.
And for a franchise that was so,
like the original made so many great points
about black people hurting black people.
That it seemed to have forgotten all of those points
in this movie, you know?
Like why would you empower a white guy to rap
over the end credits of Tales of the Hood, too?
A bad rapper.
The robot calls him dumbass bitch, not punk ass bitch.
Oh, cuz yeah, the company's called name was dumbass.
No, no, no, his name is Dumas Beach.
Yeah.
That's the character's name.
That's why he goes, it fights crime better than it pronounces things or whatever that fucking
gag was.
Yeah.
But they literally name the character Dumas Beach just so they could do that gag, just so
they could do that gag.
He's standing at a podium that says dumbass in front of that in this movie that you're supposed
to be scared by. The genre is horror. They didn't even make, in my opinion, they made no attempt to
scare in this movie. Which, hey, you're going to really piss off the horror audience. But be like,
it's kind of your job here to make it scary. Or don't do a tale from the hood because this movie
We did not fit the franchise or the title.
No.
I 100 % agree.
Two hugs down.
Way down.
What's the original?
Please.
Man, we had an hour, eight minutes.
All right.
Talking about this movie.
I almost wish we would have went along into the game.
This could have been a two -parter.
Got me.
Got me worked up.
That's our show, folks.
I'll be in Philadelphia at the punchline, headlining Thanksgiving weekend, four shows, two
Friday, two Saturday.
they come on out when you got that belly full and take a big old shit in their bathroom
then come laugh your balls off. Yes. Our live shows are a week from tonight, you know,
a week from today. There's this week. They're listening to this Monday. They're on Saturday
night. This comes out tomorrow. Right. They're on Saturday, the 20th, 730 and 930. They are sold
out but you know see what you can do if you if you really want to come the movies are going to be
tales of Halloween which is on Netflix and the new Halloween with dynamic bride behind the camera.
My show is The Cool Kids Fox and Hulu. It is on Friday nights. It is doing well. Thank you for
watching. We got some great episodes coming up. I am on Twitter and Instagram at the
Patrick Walsh and what else? Our next one coming up is going to be the the new movie
to Netflix called event horizons the next one. No, it's not. Yes, it is.
The more I texted you and I said, so we'll do event horizon and tails from the hood too.
This week and you said, okay, cool. And I go, great, we can do a puzzle and people under
the stairs next week. No, I must have misread that. I'm not caught up. I've seen event
horizon. I have not seen a possible. So if that is the next episode, we can't record
it today. I thought you were 100 % on board watching a possible. You were like, can't
wait to watch. I am excited to watch the late start time. I am excited to watch. But then
I said, Hey, just thinking about this, should we do event horizon as one? And you said,
yeah, no, we should do it. And I had already watched event horizon again. I watched everything
I was supposed to accept event horizon.
Hey folks, who knows what's coming at you next week, but eventually two of these will
be event horizon and apostle.
So, state horizon apostle and people under the stairs are coming out.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey