Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer, or check out our
exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz, only available at Bed MDM
Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as non -mustrable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberer, offer not available in all
states, terms apply, see fanatic sportsbook app.
Welcome to the newest edition of We'll See You In Hell.
This is that podcast you listen to when you want to hear about horror movies and fantasy
films and sci -fi flicks.
You know how it goes, people.
I don't want to tell you why you're here.
You know why you're here.
And if you don't know why you're here, then you're a fucking moron.
My name's Joe DeRosa.
My name is Patrick Walsh.
I don't think you're a fucking mind if you don't know why you're here. I'm just happy to have you aboard and that's how we do it good cop bad cop
Right, we're both in very form fitting police officer uniforms right now very form fitting in Joe's case
Can you hear that can't a little wheezing in my I do yeah, what do you what do you think that is like cancer?
I am worried it's cancer because you have a cough
Well, it seems to be related to having a smoke to cigarette, some cigarettes, but it's
not going away.
I've never had that sort of wateriness.
Do you think you have like dormant cancer, and then when you hit it with cigarette smoke,
it's like, oh, hey.
No, but I mean, maybe I have, I don't know, is that bad when you have that, or is that just
like, you got a little shit in you?
Sounds like you might be able to have a little cold, Joe.
Okay, because I don't like the feeling of it, but I can't fight this feeling anymore.
I'm sure of it.
We kind of heavy -drinking ahead will help clear it out.
We're already off to a great start.
Before we get into what we did today, today's episode is brought to you by the Devil's Advocate
that is the film we will be discussing, and why are we discussing the Devil's Advocate
at this time?
Well, I think the significance is during this sort of times up in me, not sort of, but this
times up in me to movement. A lot of our favorite celebrities have been exposed for doing horrible
things and it's very disheartening. And as far back as I can remember, the first time this
ever happened to me was not part of this movement, but part of a child pornography ring raid that
happened where Jeffrey Jones never worked again. Yeah. And up until that point, he was one of my favorite
actors. Are you suggesting he was unjustly persecuted or what is your point here? Who the hell said
that? Who said anything on those slides? I just didn't follow the logic. What does that have to do
with me too? It's got everything to do with me too. I'm saying we're in the middle of a crisis right
now where celebrities are being exposed for having done foul stuff and gross stuff and I'm saying the
The first time I can ever remember that happening
to a celebrity that I was familiar with
in the public eye was Jeffrey Jones.
Oh, okay, now I see what you're saying.
So I'm saying it's his downfall
is relevant to what's happening in Hollywood right now.
But he didn't go down with me too.
He went down, they didn't have a name for it back then.
This was pre -Twitter.
It was basically just the cops saying
you can't have child porn in your house.
Right.
That was basically the beginning of it.
Did they get him on an acting on it?
How do we come back to this topic a lot? Did they get him acting on
Apparently he conducted
photo sessions. Oh, okay, apparently all right. That's what it says on the Wikipedia
That's a shame. It's a real shame. The guy was a powerhouse and you you know, yeah, it's
No more no more. I mean look. I'm sure the man don't look great. I don't think we'd be seeing him in the movies anymore
I don't I think you'd still that picture
I actually did would hired him after all that right and so did Burton in sleepy hollow so which is weird
I like if you google on what comes up as this photo of him and like a red corvette with his his long red hair blowing in the wind and he looks very
Coked out
That's the last I remember seeing him like an action
Where did you see this picture? It was just like one of those like gotcha like TMZ type deals. Oh
and he looked like he was driving coke down.
All right, well, that's our movie today.
It's The Devil's Advocate, which he's in.
That's why I said the whole thing.
Did you now, did you, maybe smoke a little?
No, I did not.
I never wanted before you came over here.
All right.
I believe in you.
I'm not sleeping.
Might have something to do with it.
And I've had a beer.
Hear the wheeze again?
You can hear it.
I hear the wheeze.
Everybody gets sick.
I don't feel sick.
doesn't have to be a big thing. Just calm down. Take it weezy. I guess we should go ahead
and get on with the show and also on with a be with you girl like being low. Hey,
Hey, hey, hey, like being Joe I
Can't tell if that just sent the meters way into the red and folks if if it gets in the pleasure meters
I think it did if it gets distorted please bear with us
We're working with this new recording. I should pull the mic back set up. Yeah, you'd think a guy that was in a was in a band for
Five years would understand how a microphone works
Well, we used to rock our audiences.
Sorry.
Sure.
Rock me, Dina.
Anyway, my point is, bear with us if the audio levels aren't perfect.
We're doing the best we can with this brand new equipment.
And also, we're on our goddamn own over here.
You know, we're flying without a fucking net at this point.
Absolutely. We've got no support, except for you guys, and you come through a week after week.
This has really become like a letterman when he was at NBC. Yeah, kind of a thing.
Little lower stakes here probably, but I was, I got into your elevator, the most vile smelling like
post -fart residue in the elevator. Yes, hope it wasn't you, but it was not me.
I sitting in there and I almost just jumped off and then the door shut and I was like fuck
Some beautiful woman's gonna be here on the third floor. Right. Get in and think it was me did not happen but there was a
normal looking woman
Who got on the elevator and I almost said something and then I was like even if you say something you look guilty
I wouldn't say a damn thing and
What do you care? It's her problem now
Now she's got to ride down with it saying I hope a gorgeous man doesn't get on here. Yeah, that's true
But it would have been great if the elevator hit the second floor and the doors opened and it was a
Team of women and bikinis
We saw we the Swedish bikini team. We just need to take the elevator. Yeah
Hoping to change in the elevator on the way down. Yeah, that's that would make it in and they're like
They all run out turns into like a mighty python like they're just
Projectile puking all over the place. Oh boy. You know what I mean? Well those brits. They do highbrow stuff, you know
That's not my style of humor the everyone's puking bit. I like it. I just don't agree with going at highbrow
I think it's right right. I mean my favorite joke
In all the Austin power films
is when he drinks the human shit.
Easily my least favorite joke,
because he thinks it's coffee.
Yeah, I hated that bit.
And he goes, this coffee tastes like shit,
and then Michael wishes to just goes,
it is shit, Austin.
Yeah.
It's a bit nutty.
That's my favorite bit.
I hate it.
Why?
It's not funny to me.
It's not funny that he drinks shit.
What is funny to you?
I like what that.
Like, you know, tell me what America means to you.
I like when the penis pump goes through,
and he keeps saying it's not his.
Right.
And he goes, that's not my bag, baby.
And they go on through the bag and they go,
one book called penis pumps.
This kind of thing is my bag, baby.
Written by Austin Powell's.
I mean, that, that's what I like.
I like a clever joke.
You like a clever penis pump joke?
I don't like, yeah.
I don't like a man drinking shit.
There's nothing.
There's no twist to that.
The twist is this coffee tastes like shit,
which is a thing people say.
And then Michael York says it is shit -austed.
Yeah, it's funny to me.
All right, I know what you're proud.
I take it back, though.
That's not my favorite thing ever in Austin Powers.
My favorite thing ever, ever, ever.
You like when he goes, he goes, yeah, baby, yeah.
I like that.
I also like when he goes, oh, be, hey.
I like that too.
But I'll tell you, no, this is a deep cut.
And nobody I would never hear it from you. I like when he asked people if they make some horny. Yeah, yeah, Randy
No, my favorite thing ever is the is fat bastard speech. Oh, it's great at the end of the first one happy because I and I eat because I'm a man
Yeah, I just the heavy breaths as the music starts. I can't stop eating. Yeah
It's it's like this Oprah Winfrey moment. It's perfect. It's so good
One and two are really, really funny and three's got a couple laughs and you know it does. I get plenty out of three. I get enough out of three. It all I need out of it, you know.
It was a good series. I'm glad I didn't do it again. Love guru. Not so great. So I married an expert or pretty funny. Fantastic.
Love guru was just kind of forgettable. I didn't think it was as bad as everybody said it was. Yeah, I might have just been expectations.
I remember I just moved L .A. and they were like he's doing his love guru character up at the UCB. He'll just pop in and do it.
I was like, all the time I go, that's the worst fucking improv show I've ever seen in my life.
Folks.
That movie seems like it was improvised.
What?
It was written, shoot the writer.
Which?
The love guru.
Oh, love great.
Yeah, not great, and then it's him age 50, Jessica Alba age 20, kind of a romance.
Well, look, that's not the most absurd romance, Michael Myers has set himself up with.
The most absurd was trying, I was trying to believe Beyonce would somehow fall for him.
Yeah, that's true.
That was outrageous.
That's true.
It was offended that they were proposing this to me.
yeah anyway oh we got to keep talking well I don't yeah yeah we're on let me
take you all right what's what's going on man let me take you over to Pats we
didn't you didn't tell the people we did today before we came over here all right we
went to uh amoeba yeah I purchased several albums a kind of a cool moment I was
going to tell Joe Joe said what's in your bag I was reaching over to pull out the
albums I had bought. And I was pulling out the first one, a squeeze album. I love the
band's squeeze and they had all their albums very cheap. I'm pulling it out. And the first
song on the album starts playing in the restaurant. Yeah, I was wild. And saying, you know, you
don't hear a lot of squeeze. That was wild stuff. That was weird and wild stuff. It's wild.
And I recommend the band's squeeze. No, the only squeeze song ever here is that fucking
tempted song and pulling muscles from a shell sometimes. Yeah, those aren't their best songs
but then what did we do? We went to pizza, barra. No, that's where the squeeze thing happened. So
the squeeze we went to out of the closet for Joe to get an AIDS test. I was thinking boy, I hope this
This thing doesn't come back positive, or I got a real unpleasant afternoon on deck.
Clean is a whistle, boys.
How do they test that fast, though?
It can't be happening.
Instant test.
Don't start saying shit like that.
Do you pay him?
No, you don't pay them.
It's free.
All right.
It's a charity.
It's nice.
That's why I donate all that stuff to them for free.
Why isn't everyone doing that?
Why is everybody's a fucking moron, you know, why isn't everybody not watching, you know,
What's a shitty TV show on right now the voice the voice, you know, I don't know
Yeah, you got an explanation for that. No, I don't
Yeah, there's no accounting for taste. Yeah, you know, but anyway clean clean boys clean so
You know good feeling good way to enter the weekend
It is. I didn't get tested.
Well, I'm very confident of my status.
I've got a big weekend of a, of unprotected sex ahead of me.
Sure.
With a lot of strangers.
Did they give you paperwork you can show to these ladies?
Uh, they didn't.
Uh, but I tap on it at the bar.
Uh, what I did do was, with my phone, I took a photo of the nurse just giving a thumbs up.
That'll work.
And then I'm gonna write clean, negative, whatever.
I'll doctor it up with my iPhone.
That's enough.
I don't need to carry paperwork or none.
I hooked up with a girl once who had paperwork.
That's, it's not making anybody feel better.
It didn't.
No.
Did I do it?
I sure did, but it, I was just kind of like, okay.
Why are you carrying that?
What is the date on it?
It was very not not a romantic way to start the evening. I once had a woman pull out paperwork
And she had to blow a sheet of dust off the top of it. So I said honey. What do you try into with Quill pen?
It says here you tested negative for John this
I think you can still get John this it says here you test the negative for scurvy
I think he can still get scary polio you can't get I don't know polio. Yeah, there's pat
Oh, he's got a one -up everybody. Just want your joke to be accurate. I say about those folks if they can't be funny at least they should be accurate
Folks, I'd love to know what you think about that last bonus episode that we released if you were one of the people that heard it on the site
People seem to really enjoy it. We did a commentary on Jeepers creepers three
not a great deal of discussion about the film as there as there never is but I
got to tell you at about the 40 -minute mark it becomes a real blur for me I
don't really remember much yeah it's the only one I haven't listened to I will
listen to it but we were I mean by the end of the thing I wasn't even sure if I was
making sense right and then Pat left and then I played my video game where
arcade cabinets by myself for hours. He had played your video games on Del Rey. There
you go. Still dating Axel Rose? Me? No. Not for months. Lana? No idea. She was. That's
a weird relationship as well. That is a weird relationship. But she likes the edge, you know, if
you look at a lyrics, then she should date him. Music is deceptively soft, but the lyrics
works are very that's on that what you said she likes the edges and then well then she
should date how yeah I got she's in she's in hot water with creep creep show with
creed creed with radio head yeah I haven't heard the song that's supposed to be a rip off
but I know radio head was sued because creep sounded like another song so it's very out
of they would do this but well her song sounds so much like creep okay I was laughing
as I listen to it, to the point where I was like,
clearly she didn't steal this.
She just, well, she's heard creep, Joe.
No, I know, but I don't think she was sat there
and was like, I'm gonna steal creep.
Somebody in her circle at some point should've probably said
this sounds like creep and she probably went,
I know, right?
Oh, well, I didn't think of it that way
and didn't think they'd call her on them.
She sucks anyway.
Didn't like her.
Well, I'm not saying her album sucks,
but she can't really sing in real life, right?
I saw her once in Coachella and nobody can sing in Coachella
It's a goddamn night. Well, she did it on SNL, too, though. Yeah, that was rough. Yeah, Brian Williams tweeting about it
What did Brian Williams? Brian Williams. What is what a joke? What a fucking joke. He was
Wait, then the news guy who lied about his past on the news and then he was tweeting about how bad Lana Del Rey was from the news desk
Everybody's like Brian. You're supposed to be like
Walter Cronkite. Yeah
Well, I'm maybe not coming too hard on them, but you can't lie about your past experiences
if you're going to be a news person.
Yeah.
I can't do it.
It's a shame.
I'd rather get my news from Alice and Williams for Christ's sake.
Yeah.
She seems nice.
Let me take you down.
They don't seem nice.
That's the illusion of, oh, I don't think she seems to be the source for it.
Oh, maybe she is.
Maybe she is.
Yeah.
The problem with living out here, you hear a thousand things about people and they're probably
not ultra. Uh -oh. I'm not saying Allison Williams even though I just said that directly off
of a mention of it.
Yeah. You know, gang, we're over at the movie corner. Come on in. Have a seat. I saw.
Well last night I went over to my buddy Rob's house and we were gonna watch a movie and we're
looking through film struck. Have you had the film struck app?
I had it for like three days and then I was like this is too much for me. It's a little
too artsy. Yeah, it's just it's a little too much in that, you know.
Yeah, I have a two week trial I'm gonna use. We're looking through and then I was like the
Yakuza, starring Robert Mitchum, directed by Sidney Pollock, written by Robert Towne who
wrote Chinatown and Paul Schrader, who wrote Taxi Driver and Raging Bull.
I look it up, the script sold for more money than any movie in history at that time.
I'm like, how do I not know what the fuck the Yakuza is?
I don't know what it is.
This thing starts up and I had my answer right away.
Holy cow, I mean, we were dying laughing watching this thing, but why why something went wrong
reshoots or something happened, Mitchum's visibly drunk in every scene of course, but he
like goes to Japan and he goes to meet this woman he used to date who's like a middle aged
gaysia, very homely woman terrible teeth, bad skin, no idea how she got cast in this role unless
She was fucking Mitchem.
Maybe that's a sexist thing to say, but she's not a good actress, she's bringing nothing
to the table.
Right.
So, he's walking through like Japan town to get over and talk to her.
And the sets look terrible, everything about it looks chancy.
And this guy who you met for like one second that greeted Robert Mitchem at the airport starts
narrating the history of Mitchem in this woman, this gaysian.
So, he talks for like three minutes in a very boring monotone voice about, oh, I remember
when Bobby met Choonlei, well, it was the summer of, he's narrating while you're just watching
Robert Mitchem walk, then they cut back to the bald guy who's just sitting there, but also
narrating the movie, but it's just a bald loser sitting in a chair, then back to Mitchem,
Then, Mitchem and the ladies start talking, and their voices drop out, and the man starts
narrating what they're talking about while we're watching them talk.
Okay.
And I don't know if this was trying to be some sort of French new wave thing.
It seemed like they just fucked up the movie.
Okay.
I've never seen anything like it.
There were five minute montages of just like different angles on two people having a conversation.
All right.
We turned it off for 45 minutes and it was terrible.
Okay, all right fair enough but worth a watch for the for the you know the room factor fair enough
I don't know why it's not discussed more is just a very bad movie Robert Mitchim going to Japan to fight
Well, why is it on film samurai? See, this is what annoys me and I've tweeted this about the criterion collection too
But in the criterion collection is is complete of completely available on film structure
You know, I've tweeted like are these guys fucking with me?
They'll put movies in that goddamn thing that are trash.
Yeah.
That are really bad movies that are poorly acted, poorly directed.
I'm like, what is this?
Why don't they, they're cultivating them, are they?
It's not like these are like the best movies, is it?
Is that their brand?
Point of the criterion collection.
Well, criterion.
Oh, you just, you're not talking about film structures.
No, I'm talking about the criterion.
Okay.
And I'm making a broader analysis here that there is something about film snuff.
Where they sometimes they take a real pile of shit, and then they try to tell you it's great.
They go, well, you don't get it.
It's like, no, I get it.
It sucks.
Yeah.
You know, anyway.
Speaking of gaysias, I saw an episode of Masters of Horror that was never...
I didn't know this existed.
It never aired.
That the Takashi Mikaewam?
Yeah, imprint.
Yeah.
Rough stuff.
I rented it from Netflix as a DVD back in the day that's how long ago and didn't refuse to watch it
I got to freaked out rough stuff. Yeah, Billy Draggo who you may know as Frank Nitty from the Untouchables. Okay
movie
he plays a
I guess it's
I don't know late 1800s. It's supposed to be whatever time period that is
He's made his way to Asia and to this place where Gaysha girls work because a woman he
fell in.
Like Gaysha, he fell in love with there.
He promised her he'd come back for her, and she's not there, he ends up bedding down.
Not bedding down.
He never sleeps with her, but spending the night with a different Gaysha who's got a severely
Deformed face where half of her face is twisted up until like a smile and the other half is a frown kind of
And she tells him the woman that you love is gone. She's dead and
Then you start to find out about this woman's history through flashbacks
And then you start to find out about how the other woman that he was in love with died and it is a lot of
brutal brutal
brutal, brutal shit.
And it's the main reason I don't like a lot of Asian -based horror films.
Like Superbrutal Violence or Emotion on you about torture.
Yeah, people go, oh, the audition, what a great movie.
I'm like, I'm sorry, I don't like it.
It's a woman like torturing a man.
Yeah, it's like this romantic comedy and then she tortures him.
I did love audition for some reason, but generally that would not be my bag.
And I know that's not all Asian -based horror,
But there's a lot of torture stuff and I just don't care for it
I think I've said it before on the show hostile was one of the only
Torture -based, you know
horror movies I like because it it does involve redemption and there is it because it's much more of a revenge story and a payback story
Then then just watching people have horrible shit under them. Right. This one is all out just
There's not one redeeming character in the whole fucking thing. It's it's brutal
it's brutal and it didn't air on showtime because it was too violent right.
Showtime, yes, it was too disturbing, which if you've seen Masters of Horror, it's you
know, it's not a show that holds back, you know, it's right, they do some pretty graphic
shit on it.
It's supposed to be Showtime's whole thing.
They look at the company.
I got it, because I was saying the same thing, I was kind of scoffing like, well, why would
you not air this?
It's cable and whatever.
Then the further and further I got into it, I was like, this is just a scene after
scene of women having horrible things done to them, and it's upsetting after a while.
It's always upsetting, but you know what I mean?
It seems so repetitive that there is the part of you that goes, what's the point of
this?
Right.
You know?
But the guy gets his in the end, I'll tell you that.
There is the just desserts, but rough stuff.
Rough stuff.
All right.
I think it's all I saw, really.
I think that's all I saw.
Well, I've been sitting in a dark room ever since.
Yeah, pretty much.
Well, Pat, I got something for Joe's scary stuff.
Take me there.
I'll take you there.
Da -da -da -da -da -da -da -da -da -da.
Just got this today, actually.
And it belongs in Joe's scary stuff,
because it involves rapper Cool Keith,
the inventor of horror core, rap.
For you hip -hop fans out there,
you know that when Cool Keith started
with the Ultramanagome Cs, he was the first horror core
rapper out there to rap about horror shit. Anyway, I'm at a Meebo Ren example. He was just
the first guy to be like, oh, you know, I'll fucking eat your brains and I'll, you know,
I would say like horror movie. Shit that a monster would say, I guess, you know. Anyway, he's
done a bunch of horror based characters since then. The most infamous being Dr. Octagon. That new
record comes out in April, the second record, and 20 or 30 years or something like, something
crazy like that, 20 years.
You know, he did the Dr. Doom character with Cutmaster Kurt, which was also a cannibalistic
rapper who would eat people and then rap about it.
Anyway, I'm in a meba today, I just for shits and giggles look in the cool Keith section.
and maybe there's some pre -single release
for the new Octagon album or something.
I find this record, title alone catches my eye.
Your mom is my wife, it's a great title.
That's Pat.
One of the best I've ever heard.
Yeah, your mom is my wife.
It's cool Keith and Cutmaster Kurt.
It says right across the front of the CD,
only 500 of these were pressed.
It's basically B -sides from the Doom Sessions, as far as I can tell.
It's all tracks from 96, 97.
So it's like the Dr. Doom Sessions, the Sextile Sessions, that Sextile is another album
they did together, the Matthew Sessions, that's the album they did together after Doom.
It's great.
It's truly, truly great.
And it was such a steal.
So I urge you, if you're a fan of Cool Keith, go and find this fucking thing.
because there's only 500 out there.
I only paid $18 .99 for it.
For a CD that's one of 500, I mean,
somebody a good deal to me, but go check it out.
He always delivered, not, well,
some of his albums are less favorable than others,
but this is, you know, if you're a fan of the stuff
I'm talking about, this is a real treasure trove
of stuff you didn't know even existed.
So, yeah, go get it.
It's probably on Spotify too.
Well, I want to own it yeah, no, I know and I do own it. I
Know cuz I bought it today no ownership anymore if you recommend some people they're probably going to
Spotify you don't own me. That's my new character. You don't own me. Yeah, it's a it's a guy
He just says it real sassy like that
You don't own me it's a song
You don't own me. Yeah, but I'm doing it like
like from the first wives club.
Picture John Mulaney saying it.
Maybe I'll pitch this to Mulaney.
You don't own me.
Sure, call him up.
It'd be a good character for him to do.
I like it.
You know, I don't know what else it would entail,
but it's all I got right now.
I have to look.
Let's say Johnny, we workshop at Johnny.
Right.
I got, you know, I have nothing for you.
I'm in a tough state today.
I don't know why I'm just saying I'm like hot. Yeah, it's warm
It's warm. Are you turning the air on? Oh, no, it's all right. All right. We got a big saint Patrick stay a weekend ahead
Let's get to the movie at hand. What do you say?
That line of conversation was shut down. Well, well, no, we do we I'm sorry. We do have a big
I didn't know yet anything that what did you want to say? I'm sorry nothing. That was it. Let's get to the movie
So the movie is devil's advocate
Yet, starring a very equally matched in terms of their acting ability, Al Pacino and Keanu
Reeves.
And Pacino just slaps Reeves around the screen with his dick for like two hours and
fifteen minutes.
Now their acting showdowns are the exact opposite of Danero and Pacino in heat.
Yes.
There's a clear winner that walks away.
Yes, I agree and I'm a fan of Keanu, but me too. I mean at this time he was much more of a joke, but
Yeah, this is a hell of a picture folks if you haven't seen it
It's a wonderful film at pun intended. It's it's a lot of fun. It's very creepy. It's very scary at times
It's weirdly funny at times. Yeah, it's it's just a great movie
Tremendous supporting cast you got Craig teen Nelson you got Charlize
their own frequently nude you've got in fact another guy that was in
Masters of Heart in my favorite episode called Sounds Like the guy that
plays the pedophile that Keanu Reeves is defending at the top of the movie is
that Proud Taylor Vance I can't remember his name but he was a weird eye he
He wasn't like, no, he wasn't like true blood
and he looks like Rob Cordray.
He looked like he could literally,
if you said he was Rob Cordray's brother,
he'd be like, oh yeah, okay, I don't know.
But he was in true blood.
He was also in the wire.
He played a detective on the wire
that got his throat slit.
Wanna say Paul something?
You've lost, man.
Well anyway, he's in it.
He's got a small park, but he's great.
as we said you know Jeffrey Jones tremendous actor disgusting human being but
but he's very good in the movie in fact my favorite line in the movie revolves
around his character let's hear it's been a while for me so his character's name
is Eddie Barzun which is one of the greatest movie names I've ever heard ever my
friend Chip and I used to you know sort of collect like the greatest movie names
Uh -huh. So Eddie Barzoon was number one Bobby Chiaro from Hauffa was another one. Okay.
Floyd Gandali from Boogie Knights. Sure. You know, anyway, but uh, when
When Pacino is gonna our field from Garfield to two kitties. Sure. John John
Who plays John in those was Jason Lee was it was Jason Lee and I think I thought it was Brecken Meyer and at least one of them
Think he took it over in the sequel. Yeah, you couldn't even get Jason Lee back
He's done all the Elven on the chipmunks unless well wait. No, then it that's what Jason Lee's in
He doesn't play John and Garfield. I think that's Breck and Meyer
Breck and Meyer plays John and Garfield
There's so they're partners in the movie or you know, they work in Pachino and
a barzun or colleagues and then Pacino's gonna turn on him and as Pacino's
turning on him and you're also starting to get the first glimpses that Pacino's
character might be the literal devil right it's it's Pacino ranting and
raving about Eddie Barzun as they cross cut it with Jeffrey Jones jogging and
like slowly starting to have a heart attack right and there's a line in there
where the climax of that speech, where Pacino goes,
Eddie Bovazone wants to fist fuck the world
and then lick his hands clean.
And I was like, that's a great way to describe a piece of shit.
That's a great way to describe this guy's got,
the guy that's got it coming to him.
You sold me.
Now, I saw in the theater,
I've probably seen it a couple of times since,
but it's been a while.
Well, I remember it being very liberal with the nudity, very liberal.
You see Charlene's boobs a couple times, and you see the really hot, there's like, you
know, remember there's like the two really hot wives in the building, yeah.
You see them, they're boobs a couple times, they make out a bunch, I think, if I remember
correctly.
It's a sexy picture.
It is, and it hit me at the right time.
I was it would have come out 96 96 you were 39
Porn hadn't overtaken the internet yet, you know that was still yeah, well, this is all I had exciting
I think the same year it was devil's advocate and then wild things maybe a year after oh jeez these were big pictures for me
Jesus, but
Yeah, I remember it being long
Funny well -directed well -written, but mostly what I remember is the new today
for whatever reason.
I think it's because Charlize was new to the game
at that time.
Didn't know who she was.
She Charlize there on.
This, this is, no, she was brand new.
This was like her breakout role.
She's tremendous in it.
But I mean, you know, nobody'd ever seen her.
And then all of a sudden she pops up in this movie
and you're like, who is this?
I would always, I'd describe her as a creature.
Yeah.
You know when they say that, who is this creature?
I don't think women like that though.
No, but like men will say that in movies like when they see somebody like stunning who is this enchanting creature?
Yeah, exactly. Yeah, that's usually while kissing her hand.
Yes, and when I met Charlie, you know what I like to do when I kiss a woman's hand?
What I kiss it and then I look up at her and kind of like maintain eye contact
and then when she looks away I slide her ring off with my mouth
and I pocket the ring. I do that too, but I'll swallow the ring just to not add the extra step.
And then I'll dig it out of my own feces days later. You don't have to do that. You can just hold it in your mouth
And then she goes do you want to drink and I go through
Yeah, spit it back into her face
But no, she came in and you're like this is the most gorgeous human being I've ever seen
It was something else and you get to see her naked which is pretty great. Yeah
Keanu at the not the top of his acting game at this time. He's doing a British accent that sounds
No, sorry a Boston
Southern he's southern in it. Yeah, he's southern, but there's hints at times of both Boston and British
He's doing a southern accent. Some of it's British
Here's what you're getting mixed up with he's doing a southern accent in Dracula. He does a British accent and the problem is
Indrackily sounds southern and in devil's navigate he sounds British. Yeah, that's right
The biggest laugh for me and Dracula will not there's a lot of laughs in it, but
It's when Dracula walks in with the giant bonds on his head and the gray hair and he's like
like the 400 -year -old Dracula and
Cano Reeves is like writing something with a quill pen and then he looks up and he goes oh
Dracula
like he's seeing, you know, a pillow for the first time.
He's never seen this man, he's like,
Dracula.
Unbelievable.
My biggest laugh is when the three vampire seductress women,
how it's saying as well.
When they eat, they're like, they eat the baby basically.
Right.
And you don't see them do it obviously,
but it just shows, can't, can't, can't.
Keanu reaves his reaction.
Yeah.
And it's just him on camera going yeah, yeah, yeah, it's supposed to be like a man going mad and it's you know
Yeah, he's only good in silent killer mode or comedy mode. I like to men, you know parenthood and stuff like that
Bill and Ted three. I'm there the day it opens. You think they'll do it? Yeah, they just released some
Yeah, apparently it's happening all right, but but what's it gonna say was um
Um, the uh, oh, his accent.
Yes, he's playing a Southern, oh, that's what I was gonna say.
Keanu, not at the top of his acting game in this film,
but physically, ha -cha, I mean, this is as good as it gets.
Keanu is, is, is top form in this fucking thing.
Wow, okay.
Top form.
They got him and all these goddamn Armani suits and shit.
I mean, you're like, this kid is made to set the world on fire.
Well, all right, never heard a negative word about Kiana.
I've heard he's a wonderful man.
I heard he's brilliant.
Like he's extremely well read.
Take it easy.
That's what I've heard.
I heard he's an expert marksman.
Okay.
They did a whole article in like the New York Times
or the LA Times, something, some publication,
about like ten reasons more to love Kiana Reeves.
And it was literally like he hangs out with homeless people and it was pictures that the paparazzi got of him
Like just like fucking like taking a nap next to a homeless guy
Sharing cigarettes like just hanging out talk like this guy just seems like a fucking good dude
Yeah, he's apparently very very well read all right
Well, I mean it doesn't sound sometimes it don't sound like you believe me. I mean sure
Maybe he just plays a lot of dumb dumbs. I don't know. I just watched a video interview with Pesci on
Letterman from like the early 90s. Wow. Pesci barely does movies anymore. Forget press or anything. Yeah. Well, it's but it's back when it was like
right for good fellows or whatever and
There's some really great moments in it like like letterman won't stop going. Do I find you funny? What about me?
What about me is funny to you? He keeps doing that to Pesci and finally Pesci
he goes, well, that's funny.
Your face is funny.
and he goes, he goes, you know, yeah, it was me, Bobby, Marlon, Michael, a bunch of kids.
No, I'm kidding. I'm kidding. Wow. Wow. I gotta check this out.
Peshy is killing in this fucking video. You're just like YouTube's peshy letterman?
I was looking up peshy. I can't remember why I was looking up peshy. Oh, because I was trying
to, for my pen house article, I was trying to get the exact wording of a line he has an
easy money. Okay. So I was trying to find the scene on YouTube. So I found the scene because I was
out when I was writing it. And I found the scene. And then, you know, one of the videos suggested
was it's just a peshy letterman goodfellas. And I was like, all right, I'll watch this. And it's him
just smoking the cigar just fucking crushing it. I gotta check it out. Yeah, it's, it's great.
It's really funny. And it's, it's, it's a, it's a, it's a talk show that, you know, it's like,
like it's the old talk show days where like you kind of felt still like anything could kind
of happen.
Right.
It was spontaneous and it's a lot of fun.
That talk show circuit now, holy lord, there's not a bright spot in there.
now who's your favorite day would you say Ellen I mean I watched an
Ellen the other day I wasn't for me no it was who is it for I by the way you
know people are home it might stepdad loves look baby I'm home every day I
I couldn't watch it.
An interesting thing they did was like, the sketch was like, tell me if you see it and
it was like, you know, they'd show you a picture of something and like, wait, do you
see it?
And the audience would laugh.
And one of them was like a logo for something that looked very much like a cock and balls and
the audience starts dying laughing and it's like spraying something at the end of it.
I was like, it's 3 p .m.
Ellen.
What the fuck are you doing?
She's on that late.
I thought she was on like 10 a .m.
Well, it's just syndicated, but she's on during the day regardless.
So I don't think look graphic, you know, I'm like, yeah, I see it Ellen Jesus Christ. Hey, folks knowing her persuasion
She thought it was a cock and balls. Okay, ladies and gentlemen. All right. They had Dana Carveo, which is why I was watching
All right. Well, that was my James Gandalfini as an insult comic. Okay. You would have been a good one in the 70s
I just saw an advertisement for James Gandalfini colon celebrity autopsy. Oh, it's like you know what?
Go fuck yourself leave it alone. Leave it alone. I'm not gonna watch that. The docher comes out of the operating
You know room whatever pulls the mask down
Diagnosis fat
Real fat. You really got to cut the guy open. Yeah
And cut to black for 59 minutes of the special.
What was this O .J. Simpson special they were showing the other night?
Was that film now or then?
It's like it's supposed to be his confession or something.
It was filmed then. It was when he was selling his book.
Okay, look.
If I did it.
I feel like...
I'm not saying I don't think the guy did it or not.
I always believe more that he was guilty than not guilty.
Right.
But, but they're taking this clip from an interview from 20 fucking years ago, and they're
going, is this the confession?
It's finally been unearthed.
An interview nobody ever saw, and it's like, guys, so nobody, nobody around, if this was
so inflammatory, nobody around was like, hey cops, I think OJ just confessed on camera.
We're not allowed to air it, but your cops.
So you could probably see it.
You know, it's just, come on.
It was also pitching a book called If I Did It,
where the whole premise was that he did it.
It could have been taken from any of those interviews, correct?
It was from those.
It was when he was promoting that book.
I mean, of course, I think the man did it, but.
But like they, see, it's, here's the tough thing too.
Tons of people watched it.
They cut it in a way where you don't,
this is what I hate.
This is what I hate about the media now.
Now, they cut everything in a way where you can't see the actual version.
You can't see it.
So that's cut in a way now where every time you watch a clip, it's just going to be him
going, I don't remember anything after I hit her with the pan.
You know what I mean?
You're like, wait a minute.
What's the lead up?
I want to see the setup.
They're not going to let you see it because that doesn't get anybody excited.
So it happened to me with a shy, I looked up a shy love buff thing
He took some hard shots at your boy Spielberg recently. What is that? Oh, he was just like, you know
The guys and that's what you call punching up. He goes the guy's not a director at this point
He's a fucking company and he goes I've done a ton of movies with him and he goes
You know, you're being told constantly you got to get this line out in 39 seconds
And you got to hit the mark here and then he goes after five years of that. You're like what do I suck?
And he just was like, I just can't work like that anymore.
I don't want to do that and whatever.
But, so I was reading the interview,
and then it said something about how he had gotten arrested.
And so I looked that up,
because it was on camera or whatever,
and it said he was arrested and he gave a racist tirade
toward a black police officer.
I remember watching, man.
So, every video I find, I finally found out
what he actually said.
Thank you to like Time Magazine or something,
doing an actual real story, but every fucking video you see, everything is
beeped, because by the way we're also all children who where adults can't hear
curse words on news stories, fucking ridiculous. Everything is beeped, you can't
hear anything you're saying, and then every article that goes along with the
video just says, he'd said race is stuff, and I'm screaming by the A -flink on Google.
What did he say?
I want to know what he said.
You don't just get to say he said a racist thing
and then not tell me what he said.
That's not responsible.
Tell me what he said.
So finally, like I said, a real magazine like time did
and they explained what he said.
I was like, thank you, time.
Okay.
What did he say?
He said at one point,
you're all going to hell to the cops.
And then he turned to the black one
and said, especially you.
And the other, the white cop said,
well, why, especially him?
And he goes because of his skin color.
Okay, and not great.
Yeah, so, and then the only part I could catch
of what he was like on the video where I couldn't understand
what he was saying was him, it was above in the back
of a police car.
And the black cop was like, the black cop was just being like,
I don't know what to tell you, dude.
Yeah, sure I was like, I'm not having a fucking conversation
with you, man.
All right, I asked you for a cigarette you said I didn't have one. I said word
How to fuck him? I racist like he's put on this real hard like hip -hop accent all of a sudden
I mean, yeah, he's imbalanced I think but he's a good actor. I'm
Yeah, he apologize for what he said. It was obviously very
Appropriate and and you know, he says he's sober now. I hope he pulls his shit together that Mac and Roe movie is getting fucking
and accolades.
He's playing John Mackerman.
Yeah, okay.
So I mean, I want to see that.
You got LaBuff playing an unstable John Mackin row.
I'm there.
I loved American Honey with LaBuff.
I didn't see it.
It was a great movie.
I think I talked about it on here.
It's just like, it's like a two and a half hour movie.
It was kind of like a Harmony Karin movie.
Kind of a spring breakers feel to it.
All right.
You know, just young people driving around,
having fun, ripping people off,
Fucking doing drugs. I enjoyed it. Yeah, like our childhoods. Yeah, exactly. Yeah. No, no
I actually just sat in a basement with people and watched MTV really because I swear if you put
a gun to my head you said Joe, would you do more of fucking driving or ripping people off? I wouldn't be
able to tell you buddy. I wouldn't be able to tell you. Yeah, I didn't do any of the above. I
That's right. What were supposed to go see the strangers pray at night today and we didn't wind up
getting over there. But also I learned Joe hasn't seen the original strangers. So maybe we'll try to
you own it, right? No. I've seen it here, I think. Then I bought it and I haven't watched it yet.
I bought it for five bucks. I watched it a second time this weekend. I thought it was great.
it. It's a good movie, but you have seen it. Again, I'm not into, like, I'm not as into
the, like, slashery, you know, Wolf Creek always upset me terribly because I'm just like,
yeah, it's just sucks. It's just like a good person getting abducted by the worst person
on earth. Right. You know, like it, yeah, I don't enjoy
though. It's like a bad news story, you know. But, um, but Devil's advocate, let's, let's,
tie the devil's advo convo up with this. What do you think of? Pat is now rubbing his
eyes like we're at the end of them trying to solve a murder case. It's one of the greatest
David Tell jokes of all time. He talks about when you shave your pubes and they start to
grow back. Yeah. And he's going, now it looks like your dick was up all night trying to
to solve a murder.
That's good.
What is your opinion on the end scene of the Devil's Advocate, very polarizing.
Some people get furious.
I think it's a fun little sort of tale from the crypti wink at the camera.
You'd have to give it to me because I don't recall it.
It cuts back to, so at the beginning of the movie, Keanu is defending a pedophile.
He knows the guy is guilty.
he still gets the guy off and that's what launches his career into New York and
with Pacino's firm and everything. You find out Pacino is the devil, you find
out Keanu is his son and he ends up betraying his father and killing the devil
at the end or destroying the devil and then it cuts back to the courtroom at
the beginning and you realize none of that happened. It was all this dream
sequence. While he was in the bathroom after he had found out this guy I'm
wrapping his guilty. So then he goes back to the table basically says I can't
rep this guy anymore does the right thing. And then another lawyer comes out and
says like hey you know you did great we're proud of you and we're big things for
you and you're like oh he's going to be rewarded for doing the right thing. Then as
he walks away, that lawyer morphs into Pacino, and he goes, I always get what I want.
Well, that's a ridiculous ending.
It's not that ridiculous.
It's very, like I said, it's very tails from the crib.
It's probably dug it at the time, but that sounds ridiculous.
It's a wink to camera.
And I think it's also the only way you can end that movie.
Right.
It's like, you know, you're like, what do you, so they probably ended it with the dream
sequence and then they were like, you got to add on something else here.
People hate this dream sequence.
Well, yeah, you can't what do you do to have a happy ending like you did the right thing and everybody walks away
Cheer you have a little so then is the idea that Pacino put the dream into his head or something?
They didn't explain that part of it. It's kind of falls apart when you think about it
Not really. It could be that he played to play devil's head
It could be that he puts the dream in his head to make him do the other thing
Yeah, then he can make it work the other he's just like I'll make it work anyway
way you can, or maybe he's like, no, he did have that vision on his own because he is
my son and he does, he does know, but I'm going to work at this angle now. You can't
beat me, I'm the devil. Right. That's what I took from it. Okay. Didn't mind the ending.
I don't mind a little wink to camera. You know, unless it's a literal wink to camera,
like at the end of Freddie versus Jason, when Freddie's decapitated, it had literally
wings to the camera. Do you think nudity has come away from movies because porn is so readily available?
I think it's that. Yeah, it doesn't it doesn't sell anymore. Yeah, it's a show. I mean because nudity
was gone well, well, well, well before any of the current movements has started. So it's not a result
of that, they only do comedy nudity now.
Barely.
A dick or something like that.
Yeah, well yeah, you see a lot more dick on camera, because it's still for some reason
funny to see a dick on camera, I'll always laugh at it, but I don't know, I can't remember
the last time I saw like boobs in a movie, it's been a long time, it was certainly never
your leading lady, if they do it.
Even that movie Nymphomaniac, which I was part of,
was largely on Trier as a deeply disturbed man.
I saw that whole thing. I kind of liked it with trial above.
Yeah. But I mean, even that wasn't like overloaded.
I saw some of it wasn't overloaded with nudity.
There were dicks of plenty. There were some boobs and butts.
But for a movie called Mymphomaniac, plus one and two, it's...
Sure. Yeah.
Joe you have anything to plug yeah go for it tour April okay all dates
joderosa info dot com starting in New Hampshire ending in Michigan check
that out if you can't hope to see you out there other than that joderosa
a comedy on Instagram and Twitter and the Penthouse column is you let me down.
Folks, I'm on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh.
Watch my show, Living Biblically Monday Night CBS 93830 Central.
Go to the Hoghouse page on Etsy, pick yourself up, our brand new t -shirts, we also have posters,
stickers, etc. Thank you very much to Emily Florence for handling all of that.
And of course, check out the Facebook page which is rapidly approaching if it didn't already cross it a thousand members, which is awesome.
Thank you all!
We'll see you next time and we will see you in hell.