Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Bet MGM game sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM dot com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and
West Virginia only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal, durable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
Gambling problem, call 1 -800 -Gambleer.
Firestone Complete Auto Care's epic savings advantage is the sign you need to stop putting off your car's maintenance.
And you can save up to $100 on tires and services while you're at it.
Don't wait, call Firestone Complete Auto Care for an appointment.
Welcome to we'll see you in hell the podcast where we discuss and sometimes comment on
Hard, sci -fi, fantasy films, I'm Joe DeRosa, to my right is Mr. Patrick Walsh, Pat.
Yeah, I guess I'll reintroduce you, now that you've already done it, and then we can
get on with the show, and on with a Jew.
That was a curveball.
Kind of like a Betty Boop one nice misdirection. How are you Pat? I'm great
Two infrequently mentioned on this podcast is our fantastic and catchy theme song. I'd like to remind you
It was written and performed song instruments everything by the great Joe D 'Arosa. Thank you
And with that respect, I would like to now play my buddy Eli Bradens cover of
That theme song. It's very cool
It's a different take on it. Eli writes songs for the Howard Stern show, and he's a tremendous
follow on Twitter. Give it a listen, here we go.
Yeah, here we go, I will.
Very cool, I like that.
Yeah, it's like a hair metal take on it.
Yeah.
And it is very stern show -ish.
Yeah, reminds me of a lot of the stern show songs.
Yeah, no, I loved it, I appreciated it.
Thank you, what was his name again?
Eli Brayden.
Thank you, Eli.
He's also a relentless joke machine,
very, very funny on Twitter.
Eli Brayden, that's a great name.
Yeah.
That sounds like an old, old,
Russell character.
Yeah, I was gonna say like an old sheriff right sheriff Eli Brad
Speaking of Kurt Russell our movie today is the 1982 version of the thing some would say it's the only version
I don't feel that way but I love the film yeah, but I do still have respect for the original
And I like the sequel quite a bit or the prequel, but you know this one is you mean the latest one?
Yeah, the thing oh Christ well when you rewatch the old one the 82 one
And then you watched the prequel again, they I thought did a very great job of like tying it up
Like it's very cool like how they recreated this
Swedish whatever those guys are the Turkish whatever to fuck their base and like the beginning
Oh, that's tough. I you know, I wish I had a little less CGI in it
But I thought it was a cool movie, but the more on that later. It's just a general catch up here. Sure
How are you Pat Pat and I've been booze -free for roughly two weeks now
Yeah, I'm fine. Everything is just very difficult, very stressful.
Give me that ball.
Cons all over Pat, because Pat's got the ball near him.
The green ball that my dog's obsessed with.
I'm going to put it up here for now.
This dog is going nuts for this ball.
Don't you wish you felt about a ball like that instead of whiskey?
like that. Huh? Which I felt about anything like that. Yeah. Um, that's his booze ain't going
to get no, ain't going to get no cirrhosis from a rubber ball. That's true. Um, so wait,
yeah, how's it going for you? It's going fine. You know, uh, it's trying to get the show popping,
you know, your TV show. Yes. Yes. It will. It'll get popping. I don't want you to worry about it.
I'm not. I just just want to start for Christ thing. It'll start. Yeah. All things start. They do.
One day you'll look back at this time. You'll go, remember the sweet time when I wanted it to start
When it was just it and it oh, I didn't know how good I had it. No, I got. I had it
You know, and then you want it to stop and then you'll say, remember when it was starting how great that was
I'm so on and so on and that's not dead by this point, but yeah, you can't be happy in life is the point absolutely not impossible
Um, are you enjoying the no drinking thing?
I mean, yes and no.
It, uh, it's sort of up my weed usage, um, which is, I guess is cheating, but I, you know, I, I, I, I didn't really have any adverse effects from drinking.
Speaking of which, do you want a little marriage you want us?
Yeah, yeah, I, uh, I got half a little joint in here that I ruled the other day.
I'm ashamed of what this podcast has become.
I mean, who cares?
Yeah.
It didn't up my weed usage.
It made me, I tried, I keep desperately trying to get back
into weed the way I was in college,
and it just makes me paranoid and crazy.
So let's see how this goes.
There's kind of already there.
Yeah, I mean, you know.
So, but you know, there's just nothing,
the amount of, in two weeks in this hard, hard city we live in,
Just a terrible city full of terrible people the amount of parties that have popped up that I've like last night performed at a house party
Yeah, at a house party
Not gonna enjoy and I work out of the boots in the center of the room incredible lineup on this thing
Nikki Glazer. Yeah, where's he Cooper men lover me Andy dick? Oh, Dino
I don't know.
Yeah, however the hell you say his last name.
Great fucking lineup.
People are having a blast.
There's free booze everywhere.
And I'm just like, beautiful women.
I'm like, I gotta get the fuck out of here.
I left.
I chain smoked three cigarettes on the balcony
and then I left.
I was like, I don't know how people do this sober.
What is fun about this?
I mean, I did not have sex until I had a drink.
And then I was like, oh, I understand how people have sex.
No, I didn't get it before.
Sober people doing shit, I mean, I don't understand.
Doesn't make any damn sense.
Use that as an asterisk.
People, our world is crumbling around us.
I think you think I don't know.
I talk to a friend the other day.
By the way, don't online harass that woman.
I referenced last week.
I saw somebody being like, you know,
Senator fuck you, it's just don't engage.
Yeah, don't do that.
We're not we're not trying to get you out after the woman. She's entitled to her opinion. We're entitled to ours
And it needs them there. That's all then what he needs to be, you know
What do you need to be wearing torches to people's doors via Twitter? No, I don't want to think I put hate out into the world
Especially time of so much hate. I'm more confused than ever
I talked to a staunch Republican friend of mine the other day who's not a fan of Trump, but is a devout Republican and
Her arguments for everything
thing. This is my problem. I used to have a bit about this. I hear both sides. I'm so
dumb that both sides just convince me all the time. Yeah. You know, like I used to have
a bit where I go. I watched Obama and not McCain. Um, who was the guy? No, the vice president
that shot his friend. Oh, Cheney. Yeah. I watch Cheney and the vice president that shot
his friend in the face and Obama debate Guantanamo Bay once yeah and Obama was like you know it's
disgraceful we need to get rid of it it's inhumane I was like he's right this is when are we
gonna grow as people and then Cheney's like they're terrorists what are we supposed to do and I
was like you got their fucking heads off I can't I can't pick a goddamn side it's getting easier though
though it's getting easier of course I just mean in general you can pretty much sway me on anything
think. Sure. Uh, which leads me to a debate Pat Walsh and I had yesterday about the
new Queens of the Stone Age record. Pat said, you know, he thought the record was pretty
good, but that, but that their best album by far was rated R. No, no, I didn't say it's
the best album by far. You, you said easily their best. Those, I will read you the text.
Rated R is easily their best you said.
I might, well, I do love it,
but I feel like I would have said easily one of the best
because I wasn't quite prepared to make that big a client.
Well, here's the thing.
Are you ready for this curve ball?
Yeah, and I disagree with it.
I got this fucking ridiculous stupid statement.
Rated R is an excellent, excellent album.
That's what it said.
No, no, I'll tell you what I said.
Here we go.
Okay.
Joe texted me, digging the new Queens.
I said, yes, it's my least favorite of theirs,
but it is good.
Joe says, least favorite, Walsh, Damott, I said it's easily their least good album, still
a solid B -plus.
Joe says, rated R is by far the worst album, listen to it many times, see it best.
I wrote, you're not smart.
Joe said, tell me when I see you, it makes that album good, and I will, tracks 1, 2, and 3
are great after that it's very hit or miss, and it's not.
I can freely discuss that.
Well, I just really revisioned history there.
So, let you say that?
Yeah.
Revised history.
I'm reading, I didn't say rated R as their best.
Well, in any case, in my head, that's what you said
and I relistened to rated R today for maybe the fifth time.
Yeah.
Loved it.
Finally clicked.
All right.
Coincidentally, finally clicked where I was like,
oh, now I get it.
And you know what I, you know what I,
we can do it.
America can do it.
And then I also uncompromise.
Re -listen to some of the new one which I love,
But I also got why somebody like you who's a diehard fan would think it's the worst of anything they've put out
But still good, but still good. It's definitely there
It's like I'm a devout fucking spoon fan. I get mad when people say
God, God, God, God, God's their best album like no, it's not that's the party album, right?
It's ten poppy beautiful sweet crunchy songs, but that is not the best album, right?
So I when I heard then re -heard the new album that I was like, oh, this is why like I get into arguments with spoon people
We're all say like I like kill the moonlight better than Gaga Gaga
And they're like, what are you talking about? And I'm like because it works better. It's it's a cohesive piece of work
Right, which is how I saw rated R today finally. Yeah, a lot of it is when you come to an album like I was a fan of theirs from pretty much the
jump that allowed a show I've ever seen. I think permanently damaged my hearing. But also great
and re -released pretty recently is their debut before rated on. I like that. I like that.
The pubic hair cover always may be a little uncomfortable. It makes me real comfortable.
The black crow's had to change. They had to change the cover of a morca because it showed pubes,
which is the best black crow's album. I love lullabies to paralyze.
I like that I'm quite a bit but I find that the first half is so far superior to the
second half that it's a bit of a downer.
All the...
I'd revisit them all.
I mean, their albums just grow and grow and grow and especially if you're going to get
high.
It's just a dream.
It was the song for the deaf is of course incredible.
Just a masterpiece really.
That's a great one.
They're all great.
I learned from doing a little research this weekend that Aeroville Geras was shot on by
critics, which I think is an amazing album.
I think that's my least favorite of all them I think it's good, but it's got too many
There's some dips in between the songs that I really love. I really would you
One of my favorite songs. That's a good tune. I think three's and seven's is one of the version seven's and three's fantastic
That's that's I used to play that on rock band and make you cry
Anything for a pet's movie corner this week.
Yeah, I'm about halfway through the Handmaid's Tale.
I want to quickly take a hard shot at Hulu, if I may.
You're so far inferior to your other services like the Netflix and so forth.
And I wish you better than what you're doing.
but at the end of each episode, the credits,
you can't see who wrote or directed any of the episodes.
They throw up a giant graphic
that covers wrote and directed.
That bothers me when they do that.
I mean, imagine you wrote or directed that show
like you're dream and no one ever sees it.
So that annoys me and I like to know
who wrote and directed shows.
Also, so I'm watching through the Handmaid's Tale.
So my girlfriend watched it without me, and then I'm watching it now.
With each episode, and I've watched six of them, it's hard to even explain.
It plays the last minute of the episode you're about to watch.
So you hit play and you're like, this is kind of a weird first scene.
Why does it do that?
You realize you're watching the end of that episode.
Because Hulu doesn't have their shit together.
Oh, it's like a flaw. They have a numerous flaws when you're trying to watch a show. So now I've seen six episodes of a show where I know how it ends
Point being handmaid's tail. Good show. I get where everybody likes it very entertaining
I haven't watched it yet, but I'd like to I just haven't gotten around to it
Like it. Did I see anything this week? I still haven't watched the copy of gross point blank that you went me
Oh, I will. Oh, I do have something for this. I
I started season two of ash versus evil dead.
I'm a big, big evil dead fan.
I was a really big fan of the first season of the show.
I'm excited to see what the second season has to bring.
It lost me a bit.
It's, I will say that season two.
They're going a little too on the nose already.
Sam Raimi was quoted as saying
that what he tried to do with evil dead
That was basically be like, I love the three stages and I loved horror, so what if you combine
the two?
And it's very, very well done in the first two films.
Army of darkness, I don't dislike, but I'm not a huge fan, I get a little too carried
away with the goofiness.
I felt...
Pretty funny though.
It is very funny.
I love the Evil Dead Remake, I like that they just did a raw horror version of it, I thought
that was cool.
And I thought that ash versus evil dead season one
Road the line pretty perfectly of what I liked about evil dead two in particular
Yeah, the second season the scene with him dropping all those light bulbs and then walking across them in the pilot
Yeah, it's one of the funny scenes in television
I rewind it over and over and over
Just so funny to me. Yeah, it's it can be very funny
And I like that but but what I don't like in season two is like
like, I don't need to see up when a pipe hits him in the head to see Ash go, why I oughta.
It's like, he doesn't literally need to talk like Mo.
The other thing I didn't like is, they're putting in like, just sitcom jokes that aren't
indicative of the characters and that bothers me a little bit.
And it's a funny joke when he goes, he goes, I don't got that memory for getting disease
whatever it's called and then the kid goes Alzheimer's and he goes Alzheimer's.
That's that memory for getting disease.
Why are you bringing that up?
That's a great joke.
That's a funny joke, but it's like,
ash isn't a fucking moron.
Correct.
You know what I mean?
He's got tool qualities, but at the end of the day
he's a badass and he gets, and I'm like,
maybe you don't give him in the Alzheimer's joke,
like he's like coming unglued,
yet he's somehow defeating all these.
So I hear that.
You know, it's just little things like that.
Like it happened on the later years of the Golden Girls,
which I've been rewatching season six and seven right now.
How are they? They're great. They're way better than I remembered them being because I was when I first saw them
I was comparing them to the first five seasons, right, but now we're watching I'm like, oh no, these are actually very funny
But it's it's the end and there are jokes in there where you're like
Blanche wouldn't say that that's not a blanche joke. That's a rose joke. Yeah, you know, so Joe angrily pacing around his apartment going
Blanche wouldn't say that. Yeah, you come over. There's six crumpled marble marble red soft packs on the table
Empty mountain of butts like a weird body pillow with room a clan of hands face on it covered in jizz in the corner. Yeah, I'm I'm yelling at it. Yeah, when you walk it
But I but that all being said I am I am still enjoying the second season and I do plan to stick with it
Oh, one other thing for pets.
That's pretty good.
Honestly, they've been sitting on my DVR since the show aired a year ago.
Watch the first season of Stan vs. Evil, which is very in the vein.
Dana Gould?
Yes.
Okay.
I enjoyed it.
All right.
I say this respectfully.
I wish the show looked a little bit better.
There is something about the production that makes it sort of look like if RL Stein did an adult
horror show.
Uh -huh.
Like, it's got a sort of Nickelodeon like fog over it.
I don't know what it is.
Maybe it's, I think it's just the cameras they use.
Other than that, the monsters look awesome.
It's funny.
I always love John McGinley, the woman who plays the daughter
who I'm unfamiliar with is really, really great.
Everybody's great.
The sheriff, you know, the deputy guy, it's a fun show.
And I'm glad they got a second season.
And I wish you well.
Dana Gould.
There you go.
Joe's scary stuff.
Really quick. Oh, sorry because you're gonna love this I watched
3d in my home
Titanic all four hours all three hours why
Because the best 3d I've ever seen in my life. It's it's a movie that was not shot in 3d and it looks better than when you go
See Dr. Strange 3d really it was incredible. I felt like I was folks. I felt like I was on the Titanic
It was like beautiful like I kept pausing it and calling Heather in and we'd like put on the glasses just be like look at it like art
Now would you say that this 3d restoration didn't sink? I would and it won't sink your pocket book
But yeah, it's on Amazon for like 15 bucks or something
I know everybody doesn't have the 3d TV and I think they're already pretty much out of fashion
But they that was the beta max of modern televisions. Yeah, they they went out quick, but I love mine and I watch 3d shit all the time and I love it
It's like a especially when they go back and do the old ones predator or whatever
But to me Titanic is the best I have ever seen 3d look I
Couldn't recommend it highly enough. I know they did a brief theatrical release of it and I know that now
they have Terminator 2 3D back in theaters which I am seeing a hundred percent.
I'm not saying this to shit on Terminator 2, which you know I like to do quite frequently.
I heard that it is not a good 3D restoration.
Really?
Yes.
Interesting.
Somebody wrote to me when I tweeted about Terminator 2 not liking it the other day.
Somebody wrote to me and said I love the movie but the 3D version is shit.
Oh no.
So I don't know.
I mean if a Cameron since he had done this would do a great job. I also hope he does the abyss 3d
I think that'd be sweet. I look anything's possible. I'm not saying that this guy's definitely right about it being
You know, I mean who knows you might know everybody on the internet is a hundred percent right
At all times. I got a thing for Joe's scary stuff
Well, I got two things actually the first one is
You heard me boast and and brag and
and just the vocabulary. And guys, this isn't the weed talking. It's just gone. And
we got it. Both of them bragging mean the same thing. It's just gone. I can't understand
what you're trying to say. I almost said sulk. That's the wrong word. Wallow, I don't
know. Anyway, the creep show two vinyl wax works my hats off to you. Fantastic job. Days
days after receiving the Creep Show 2 vinyl days yeah I go on the internet wax works has
now released the Creep Show 1 soundtrack wow vinyl I out loud I went you bastards because
I couldn't give me a second to get a breath but I ordered it it also comes in two versions
there's the lung head version which is based on the jury Jordy Varel story so you get a nice
blue and greenish smoke vinyl. And then the other is the death smog version or something,
death smoke, which is red, which confused me because I thought death smoke would be the
Ted Danson segment because that fog comes in with them. But I think it's based on maybe the
Jesus Christ, I think you've got that Alzheimer's old man type disease.
Yeah, I think it's based on maybe the Tasmanian devil one, yes, but there's no smoke in
that.
So maybe it's the first, there's no smoke in the first one either, but they do a lot
of red shots in those two segments.
So I don't know, I got the Judy Vera one.
That's my favorite creep show segment out of any of the movies.
I just love it.
I watched that and I think how the fuck did Stephen King not just be an actor, like the
The guy is really, really good in that segment, and it's just him, and he carries it.
Anyway, that's out.
I ordered mine.
I'm going to get it soon, I hope, and they did the same thing.
It's got the double gatefold thing, and you open it, and there's like a mini sort of
the comic.
The liner notes are all written like to look like a Creepshow comic book, very cool.
And I prefer the soundtrack to part one way, way over part two, because it's all that old
80s synth stuff.
and it's a much more consistent soundtrack
in the sense that it all sounds the same.
Whereas the two is like Steve Howe did a lot of the music
and then a different composer, I think,
did the title and so it kind of changes a bit.
But anyway, that's number one for Joe's scary stuff.
Number two, and this is the first people on this podcast,
I'm gonna do a negative scary stuff.
What?
I got to the damn game stop yesterday
to trade in my Street Fighter 2 for my Nintendo Switch,
because quite frankly, it sucks.
It's revamped graphics.
They won't let you do a full screen of the original graphics.
There are these annoying, distracting borders
that you can't change on the original graphics.
It's not hyper -fighting.
They don't allow the turbo speed.
It's just, it just let me down.
So I said, I'm just gonna take this back
get something else. So I take it back. I enjoy GameStop. I know a lot of you video game enthusiasts
don't, but I, you know, I think it's a convenient store. It's the Walmart of video game stores. I
go in. They were very nice. Why don't the haters like GameStop? I think because it's like the,
I think they intrigued their employees bad. I've heard a lot of that online. But every time I go in,
the employees are very friendly and nice and helpful and they seem like they're in good moods. So
Walk out and they get electrodes to their genitals. Yeah, which can and has happened
Remember that caddie check to yes now you might be the only funny joke in the entire movie
It's a bad bad is Dan Acquired doing that yeah, yeah
Anyway, I
Said what do I get? Oh, well, here's this game the binding of Isaac after birth that everybody says is so fucking great
Oh, it's a Zelda clone, they say you're gonna love it dungeon crawler heavy action. It's a Zelda clone
I go okay great a customer goes. I love that fucking game
500 hours clocked. I'm like this is perfect not drinking not not doing anything fun
Let me sink into my bed at night and get into the world of Isaac and explore his world. Oh, and it's hard themed awesome. I
buy the thing
this game
fucking sucks. Every time you die it starts you over again so you'll be in the
second dungeon and you die and then you have to go back and redo a first dungeon
again. Now granted they change as you you know with I don't think you ever get
the same one exactly twice but it's like fuck you I this isn't a Zelda clone just
because it's a top -down dungeon crawler doesn't make it a goddamn Zelda clone
There's no like exploring the world and finding things you need and if there is it's
You lost me. I got like three you were holding it up to
The standards of Zelda when it's its own thing
They the the guy that made it said I wanted to do a Zelda clone kind of thing
So where the village is where's talking to the townspeople? Where's searching around? Where's your save points?
Where's searching around?
Because that's part of Zelda you got to go find the flute so you can move the rock and then you know all that shit
I haven't played a video game since paper boy original Nintendo
I just did not enjoy this game aforementioned rock band and I again
I'll give it not the game stop God bless the guy behind the counter goes want to use copying case. You don't like it
Yeah, yes
I do and that is getting returned within my seven -day window and I'm getting what I originally wanted which was shovel night
night. Shovel night. Yes, I want it shovel night. So couldn't you go home completely
beat a game in seven days and then bring it back and get it up game. They don't care.
You have seven days. If you buy a usual, you can't do that with a new game, but if you
buy a used game, you have seven days, as long as you bring it back and it's not like all
fucked up, you know, but I mean, I got to tell you, most video games these days, even these
that are sort of nods to Nintendo and Super Nintendo.
Even those, I think a lot of them,
you'd be pretty fucking hard pressed to beat them
in seven days unless you're doing nothing but that.
Yeah, that's how I beat Mario Wii,
which is my favorite game of all time.
The Super Mario?
Yeah, yeah, that's a great one, buddy.
Did it in like a week and then hugged each other
and went to bed.
That's a great game.
Yeah, all right.
So I guess I have played a game in the last 10 years,
but that was it.
Well, no, that's almost, you're pushing 10 years.
Yeah, 10 years.
Yeah.
Anyway, our movie did it.
And I had one, two, one day.
Oh, you do?
I'm sorry.
Well, it's not scary at all,
but did you use my birthday gift,
the Onzao Zero Dust Stylus cleaner?
I did.
Did it drastically improve your sound?
It didn't, but I realized, because here's why.
I realized how clean I've been keeping my needle
and I didn't realize it.
I frequently am pulling the dust off of it.
Yeah.
So it wasn't like it sounded better because it got the little pieces that I can't get to but it's a great thing
And I'm glad to have it and I don't now. I no longer have to potentially damage my needle by putting my fingers on it
But I loved it and the three records I got from you
Candia well no Vince ended up so Pat brought over six albums and said you and Vince it's your birthday. You each take three
Three of them were cars records heartbeat city candy. Oh in the first one. Yeah correct heartbeat city the not the first one
Oh, and the first one. Yeah, there's three. Yeah, and then the other three were radio
head, okay, computer, an oba record much to everybody's surprise, their best record arrival.
And then big fan of all, a John Lennon. Oh, Yoko. Yeah, these were records I had bought
twice, either by accident or because a new version came up. So in any case, I originally
wanted all three cars albums, but I Vince was in here. So I didn't feel fair doing that.
So Vince came over, I said, look, I'm prone to the car's albums, but the one I really want is heartbeat city
He said, we'll take this one too. I'll just take candy out. I said great. He took Lenin
I said, thank you for getting that guy off my plate because I'm not a fan and then he took the Abba album, which I was also grateful for
Yes, and I so I got the first cars record yeah, and I already knew okay computer, but I got to tell you these two albums are phenomenal
Harpeats City. Harpeats City is superior, but the two albums are phenomenal records.
I think the cars had an amazing run. Really, really good stuff.
I have their box that I'm vinyl. Each one's a different color. It gets a lot of
play on my house. The first one, it's like the first three or four songs are
singles. You're like Jesus Christ. Yeah. Well, yeah, anyway, I'm gonna ask Vince
what it did for his record player as well. Well, his record player is broken, so he
It's probably not gonna check, test it yet.
So if you want to listen to this Creep Show vinyl,
perhaps I'll tie it into yours.
It's called the OnZao Zero Dust Stylus Cleaner.
It's about 30 bucks on Amazon.
It made my home setup.
I have like a nice kind of higher end turn table
that I love.
I thought I was taking care of this thing.
I dipped it in this OnZao five seconds.
like the sound, I would say it almost went back to better than the day I bought it.
It was, I was anger at myself for having lost like a year to this subpar sound, it was
such a huge difference.
Did I not hold it in enough?
I just kind of went, it's all it really takes.
The instructions are Japanese people trying their best to speak English, so it's hard to
follow.
Racist to pan.
Racist.
Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. Nationalist. National
And he was like, yeah, I'm a big believer in transgender rights and all these things.
And he goes, we need to stand up for these people.
And the other person who's, you know, the brother or whoever it was, he goes, he was
he or she.
It doesn't matter.
He goes, uh, that's ableist.
You shouldn't say that.
And he's like, what?
And he's like, what did you just say?
And he goes, we should stand up for these, right?
And he goes, don't say that.
And he was like, I don't understand what I said that's wrong.
And the person goes, that's ableist.
Not everybody can stand.
and try to think about that,
that some people are crippled and you're,
this isn't real.
It was, he told me this is a hundred and a real.
I almost, he saw flames come into my eyes
like at the end of Witches of Eastwick.
Okay, all right.
Like, and he was just like,
he just started laughing, he's like, I know, I know.
And there was a split second where I was scared
that he was gonna be like, you know,
and I just had never thought about that.
Yeah, right.
But he was like I know fucking crazy right that's nuts. Yeah, so that really whoo truly nuts, whoo
Got a lot of heat about my gum chewing on last week's episode. Oh, yeah, they were after you
I apologize and what's weird is that the week where I was like I hope I'm not chomping gum in these people's ears
I wasn't and the week I didn't even think about it. I was
Ain't that ain't that the way she goes
Ain't that the way she goes, do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
uh...
i was here about this movie at a very young age from my best friend growing up
mr. ryan huntsle
ryan shout out probably not listening
uh... he used to be like
pat
this i didn't like scary movies
at the time i was a kid was ten and also couldn't see our rate of movies
he was like when it comes to suspense
nothing beats
the thing
and he would always say the thing
So then finally I was he was what was he southern trash. Yeah, well, yeah, kind of we all were
it's Missouri. Nothing beats the thing. This was a guy whose younger brother wants a quick
funny side story before we even finish the intro to the thing. I mean, I'm already break off. But his
little brother we had a scary movie night and we were holding up like flashlights and we'd go
around until scary stories till we made the other ones like freak out you did
live in Missouri not a lot to do so I tell a story and perhaps this is where
I got my gift for storytelling but I'm shining the flashlight under my face
we're all sitting in a circle and I'm telling the story about like a demonic
clown or something and finally everybody's like you know made everybody jump pass
it on everyone goes around then it gets to Caleb Ryan's little brother and he
He shines a flash under his face and he goes,
once upon a time, there was a house just sitting there.
And it's the thing, it might be the hardest
I've ever left in my life.
I was the right age.
He thought he was like trying to impress us
with his storytelling, once upon a time,
there was a house just sitting there
with a flashlight underneath to make it extra spooky.
Man, it was funny.
I'll tell you what's weird is every Halloween my circle jerk group. That's how they make us do it
You hold the flashlight into your nads. Okay, and then do you jerk on to the flashlight?
No, it just illuminates the spray as it goes up
Have you used a flashlight? But you do have to tell a scary story as you do it. Okay. Yeah, I don't know if I could do both
Have I used a flashlight? Yeah, no, but a very funny flashlight line was from and we talked about Dana earlier
when I did Danny Gould's podcast, we were talking about like when you do comedy festivals,
yeah, how they always give you a gift bag. And he talked about a festival they did. He did
where he goes, he goes, in the gift bag is a flesh line. And he goes, you know, you don't have
to underline the fact that I'm alone. Yeah. Uh, Roy Scroville must have been at that same festival
because he did a bit about, it's, it was getting a flesh line in the gift bag. It's, it's the,
It's the moon tower festival in Austin, I believe.
It's a fantastic festival.
It's one of my favorite festivals ever to do.
But I remember they did give you fleshlites in the back
because Dudley and Bob, the radio show down there,
they gave me a fleshlight before.
It's something that is going on with Austin, the fleshlites.
But I remember the music.
The owner of the club drove me a radio
and then they gave me a fleshlight
and I was like, well, I guess maybe I'll try this out.
Sure.
And then we were leaving, me and the owner,
and she was gonna drive back to the hotel,
and I was like, you know what?
I'm gonna hang downtown.
She's like, okay, cool.
And I go, hey, can you take this for me?
Uh -huh.
And I'll get it from you later, and she just goes, no.
So I just threw it away.
Yeah.
That's a shame.
Well, I wasn't gonna carry a fake vagina around the whole day.
I had a buddy of mine do some sort of like,
sort of like blog or vice piece or something.
on the flush light company and got a bunch of free ones.
So I do have one and have used it.
But I don't, I don't go to it often.
How's it feel on your nuts?
It's, it feels great.
I'm not gonna lie.
But it's not, it's not like it simulates sex
and it's too much of a hassle to not just jerk it.
You know?
It sounds also like the status cleanup.
That's what it's gonna say.
You know, it's, it's gotta be the status cleanup of all time.
It's a lot. It's shoving your fingers in the flesh like to scrape out your own jizz. Yeah, you know, I mean
It's not ideal. Where do you wash that? That's like when you got to get rid of paint
Where do you you don't want to dump it in the kitchen sink? Where do you what do you do with it?
You know, you just soap and water it up. Well, what sink do you use? You're not using your dish sponge on that
I use the bathroom sink, Joe. All right. What kind of soap? I mean, I imagine you got a antibacterial. They have explicit specific instructions
I mean, I've had this thing three years.
I probably used it four times, but you know, I can't not recommend it, especially if
you live alone.
I certainly would have used it back when I wasn't having intercourse.
I thought you were going to do the same thing where you say you have it this amount of time
and then you say you used it more times than it.
What's that?
I thought you were going to do the joke where you say I've had it for three years and I've
I've only used it for a million times.
Yeah, yeah, something like that.
Sorry.
I said a bit about old Navy.
That's a bunching up my personal anecdote.
When you're my old Navy bit,
I'll bring back another old bit.
All right, you know, everything is cheap at old Navy,
but the problem is you get,
you go in there for the one thing you want
and then on the way to the register,
there's 8 ,000 things that you just end up picking up
because it's so cheap.
Uh -huh.
But then you get to the register and let it goes,
that'll be you get a $200.
And you're like, $200 is ridiculous.
How many things do I have?
It's 300.
All right.
Look, I didn't say it was a great joke.
It's all right.
It's just an old bet I used to do.
You spent it.
I like stuff like that.
All right.
Anyway.
Send us your votes on the old Navy joke.
I am curious to hear what you think.
we have yet to talk about the thing we're a cool 40 minutes into this podcast but look folks
you've been asking us to do this one for a while it almost seems like we had but we hadn't
I rewatched this thing last night, the new screen factory 2K restoration, whatever, I mean,
it just looks absolutely fucking incredible, and they don't scrub it of all the grain,
it feels very just perfect to me when they do these old movies.
It doesn't look like you're suddenly looking at like a live sitcom version of, yeah, exactly.
Okay, good.
I mean, the thing is, just, I guess I respect it more every time I watch it, you know, when
When I was a kid, watched the thing, it was really terrible.
It was suspenseful, it was very terrifying, but I was also super grossed out and disturbed
by the effects, the dog bursting and the face is bursting and all that.
It's still kind of unparalleled and underrated effects work in that movie.
I remember as a kid, we had a cable channel called Prism, which I think was only on the East
Coast or something.
thing. But I remember the ad. Prism was the, there was showtime HP on prison. We had
all three. And prison was the one that would show actual like porn after like 12.
All right. So they were the edge of your station. And I remember the ad phrase. I can't remember
but I remember like there was a strict rule of like I was not allowed to turn on prison
after a certain time. Right. You ever sneak it? No, it was too scared. And then by the time
I did get the balls to sneak. We didn't have prison anymore. We just had showtime and it was just stuff like lady chatted at a
Lee's lover stuff like a shoe diaries. Yeah. So anyway, prison would run ads for the thing and I remember in the ads would be
Almost every horrific
Visual from this fucking movie. Yeah, and I remember just being so
Disturbed and frightened of it and now I love it, but you know that was my first exposure to this film
It's the best, I mean, I don't know what to tell you folks, if you haven't seen it making
a priority, Kurt Russell is awesome in it, there's never, it's just so refreshing to
see a movie that's like kind of funny in spots that like doesn't even attempt to be funny
at all.
Like in such a joky time for movies, like the only, and Heather was watching it with me, she
had never seen it.
we were wound back she laughs so hard at this part when Donald Muffat the older guy when he's like
I don't want to spend this when I tied does this fucking couch we start screaming them I mean we're
dying because it's like that's a real genuine character comedy moment in a movie that's been like
deadly serious and it works it's really funny if every line in a movie is a joke suddenly you're not
so scared anymore or suddenly you're not enjoying this superhero movie I'll tell you the line that made
me laugh very much and it's not even supposed to be funny is when uh uh who plays like what's
the actor's name that plays the guy that makes it to the end besides Kurt Russell Keith David.
Yeah um not to be confused with David Keith who was also an actor true story Keith David when
he goes uh when he goes duck do you believe any of this hocus pocus mumbo jumbo yeah I love I
I just love that he's referring to alien life forms
as focus, focus.
Yeah.
Yeah, it also made me laugh really hard
when he would test the blood,
which is like such a great, great scene.
Amazing.
Goes through and tests the needle on the blood
and then how each new person is now untied
from their chair and like standing with him.
It's just, there's something so funny
by the way that was cut.
Right.
It was Dean Kundy, the guy who shot like back
to the future and shit.
Like it's an amazing looking movie see the deep here the editor D .P
Amazingly shot. Did I say editor?
Well, you were just saying the way it was cut so I didn't know if you man. Oh, I'm saying two different things
The uh, I love that scene and that to me is one of the best twists in the entire movie
When you realize Kurt Russell has killed two men that are innocent. Yeah, and we're not infected right
But it's because everybody's losing their shit my friend Dan
and pointed out a really great point about the prequel,
which I mentioned earlier, which again,
it's inferior, but it's an enjoyable film.
It deserves more than a 33%.
I think.
All right.
On Ron Tomatoes.
But he said one of the things he didn't like about it
was that it wasn't an all -male cast.
And he said because one of the unspoken,
well, he didn't mean it that way.
He said one of the unspoken qualities of the first film
is that you've got nine guys
cooped up for a year
in this snow -ridden fucking whatever.
And he's like, the sexual tension in there
must be just off the fucking charts
because they don't even have a hope of seeing a woman.
There's no TV, he's nothing.
And he was like, to me that added to
why it escalates so quickly
and why they're all so fucking reactionary.
Yeah, that's fair.
So I thought that was an interesting point.
I mean, but, you know, you gotta, you gotta diversify.
You can't just make the same fucking movie again.
So I think, you know, they reacted pretty reasonably
to what was happening.
In the thing?
Well, they react fairly reasonably.
My point is is it escalates pretty goddamn quick though.
You know, that's why we got out in hour 40.
Everybody's on edge because, you know,
like Kurt Russell before anything even starts going down.
He's just like, I just wanna go to my damn bunk
and get drunk, you know what I mean?
like everybody's kind of had a lot of joy it's been smoked huh a lot of
joints being smoked can in joints yeah how do they say fluid the government
let them fly the weed up there Joe he hit it he hit it in his bank um it was a
simpler time folks I went to the Hollywood Bowl last night and saw Brian Ferry of
Roxy Music fame and I'm glad I saw him because I love Roxy Music but you know
It was it's a past is prime kind of kind of evening play with the orchestra. That was cool and
Are you already digressing from the movie again? Yeah
No, but I was gonna come back to it. Sorry, you know, go ahead. I just wanted to ask if that's what was happening
Well, what were we talking about thing? Talk about the brain fairy thing if you want
I don't even remember what my point was
Oh, I know what it was so we were going into the bowl and
My buddy's got all this weed paraphernalia and he just puts it in the side pocket of his bag
And they're checking his back the visible on the outside side pocket of his bag, right
And he goes no, they don't check side pockets. You can put a fucking handgun on the side pocket
I go that's crazy. Of course, they're gonna open it. They're searching bags
They do one single zip and then a single zip back up right through so if you if you live here
You want to get anything into the bowl at all? You want to kill people take it easy take it easy
You can't you're not about to suggest that I mean, it's just crazy
You're being just you got to say that you're being funny right now folks
Folks, you know, I'm not saying to go blow up the Hollywood bowl
But I'm saying for kill people or hurt people of course not
In this day and age you got to say that of course not
But yeah, you can get whatever you want in the bowl was my plan. We're gonna have a god damn Kathy Griffin situation on our hands with this podcast
Cut to wash crying on CNN
That I mean you want to talk about things escalating quickly. Jesus Christ. Um, I
Back to the thing. Yeah
One of the really most astounding aspects of this film. Oh, you know what we got off of that because you were talking about
How did he get driving up the weeda well the movie doesn't take place in the Hollywood Bowl Pat
Or does it maybe it's a metaphor for the Hollywood Bowl. Yes
I
Think one of the most astounding and fascinating aspects of this film when you watch it now
Yeah, is not just how well the script holds up not just how well perfect direct the tight tight script
Not just how it still seems somehow timeless. Yeah
Yeah, they put these guys in a situation where they have no radio signal or anything so you can even think to yourself
They have cell phones, but clearly they don't work right
The effects
They hold up so well, and I am not you know a practical effect like
Absolutist, you know, I like practical effects quite a bit
But I understand why computer effects sometimes help or sometimes work these were these were all amazing and it's
They're disgusting.
The dog one, real gross.
Whoever figured out whether it was carpenter
or whoever, whoever figured out like
everything should wiggle.
Yeah.
Whenever you see this alien, things have to be wiggling.
There's something about that that's so disturbing.
I don't know if it's because it makes me think of like
when a guy gets, like if a guy gets shot in his body
is like twitching, like that's very disturbing to me.
So I don't know if that's what it is or what.
but like it's just the wiggling yeah and then each one kind of had its own
usually in these movies when when the alien kills somebody it's kind of in the same way
every one of these kills was like completely different and strange
their heads were like oozing off in some cases it was just crazy shit
I'll add too awesome it's not every day you see Richard Mauser and Wilford Brimley
That's true. And a disgusting harbory.
Wimley kills it as always. Yeah, I think it's the only well the firm
He was in he was a bad guy too, but I talked about him on this podcast on the firm
He has one he has one of my favorite lines which was
When he's showing Tom Cruise the photos of him cheating on his wife that they're gonna use the blackmail him
Then he's like
This isn't just missionary stuff either
these are the more intimate acts oral and such that a young bride won't likely forgive it's like
one of my favorite lines in history and he looks he makes eye contact with Tom Cruise when he says
oral and such which is just an amazing delivery. My other favorite, Brimley is the film in and out which
which is a very underrated comedy.
I love that, my joke, you sack.
And really one of the first mainstream things
to get into homosexuality.
Half the theater walked out when I saw it
because Tom Sellett kissed Kevin Klein.
I love the theater walked out of Missouri.
But they're watching on the Oscars.
Matt Dillon wins.
It's this spoof of Tom Hanks winning
and kind of like outing his old drama teacher.
So Matt Dillon's like,
and I just want to thank my high school teacher,
Mr. Sush and such, and he's gay.
And the guy's engaged and like everybody freaks out.
So then they cut over to Bremley,
who's watching Matt Dillon on the Oscars,
and he goes, he mowed my lawn once.
Never again.
Man, when he's winning an Academy Awards in Los Angeles,
he's not going to allow him to mow his lawn again.
Just a funny man.
Yeah, the one downside to in and out is Bob Newhart plays is ultimately a bad guy. Yeah, and it's it bums me out to see Bob Newhart not completely likable. But wait, what did Newhart do in that movie who is the principal?
He's the principal that eventually like fires him and stuff. And like, you know, he's funny. He's funny in the beginning. They get like a lot of funny out of Bob Newhart, but then there is the turn where you like don't like the character anymore.
Um, just a stacked cast, Joan Kusak.
It's a great flick in that movie.
It's a great flick.
Uh, it, it, um, but, but, but
brimley and gross point blank as well.
She's great in them.
I, I love her in everything I've ever seen.
Yeah, brimley, um, here's my question.
How the hell when the firm was like the biggest movie ever when that came out,
and everybody loved it.
How the hell were they're not like brimley oatmeal?
sketches on SNL that were like mixing the firm with Brimley being an oatmeal guy.
They did, when they would spoof Brimley, I think it was Will Ferrell but it would just
be the diabetes stuff.
Yeah, well that's it.
I have diabetes.
But I mean a specific firm.
Yeah, I don't know.
It was right there for them.
It's right there.
Ever tell you my dream SNL sketch that I can never do?
No.
Well, it's so outdated now.
I wanted to do Welcome Back Potter, Harry.
Yeah, and it's about, it's basically Welcome Back Potter,
except Harry has to go back.
Old Harry goes back to teach at Hogwarts.
And then all the new wizard kids are like the sweat out.
They can absolutely still do that.
That's what that's great idea.
Surprise they didn't.
Yeah, that's another one.
Travolta's hosted that goddamn show 800 fucking times.
Do the Welcome Back Potter.
They did they did a welcome back codder with pulp fiction. I remember that that was pretty stupid
I remember that but I did laugh really hard and I can't remember who did it
But the guy that comes in as as the angry principal. Yeah, codder
The heck is going on in here. I think I came up with this on this podcast and we riffed on it for a little bit
But I want to do a sketch
with
Actual little kids roasting vegetables. Yeah, I think that's very funny
and it'd be so easy and fun to shoot.
Would it be dirty?
It could be.
Does I think it should be?
Well, you know, it'd probably eventually get dirty.
It'd be funny if it was really cute and funny.
Yeah.
And then like the fourth guy is like the Pat Cooper
that comes up.
Yeah.
You pussy -faced weasel.
Yeah, and then like reaction shots of the other.
One of my favorite looking shots.
But Rose jokes of all time is on the Drew Carrey roast when Pat Cooper closes it.
Pat Copa proceeds to trash everybody in the room that he's a better comedian and they're
all bigger than he is.
And then talks about meeting Drew Carrey for the first time that night he goes, and he
talks about how he's shaking his hand and he goes, this fat son of a bitch has his own
TV show and a hand like a bag of clams. The utter disgust that he doesn't have a firm
handshake is so funny. Yeah. What else can we say about the thing? You know, look, this
is also another important thing about this film. I mean, if you haven't seen it, we've ruined
a lot of it for you already, but you probably, if you're listening to this show, you've probably
see it by now. You should have seen it. And if you haven't, you haven't seen the new
Blu -ray. This is the Kurt Russell. I mean, this, right? This is pre -escape from New York.
Yes. This is kind of, I feel like maybe year after, maybe year after. If this is not the movie,
to me, this is the, you know, one of the seminal movies that really launches and makes Kurt Russell
Kurt Russell, right? Yeah. He's doing like no -wise cracking. No. That he would later start doing a lot.
It's the best it's the Kurt Russell. You always want it's yeah in my opinion. I prefer the sort of Harrison 40 Indiana Jones Kurt Russell
Right to the wise cracky big trouble little China Kurt Russell cap and Ron Kurt Russell. Where does he fall?
He's not even in it. I got to be honest with you
This film was got some laughs
Not sure I refuse to believe it Martin short
Yeah, I mean I want to say yeah
But I mean the movie just looks so bad do you ever see pure luck with Marty short and Danny Glover?
No, that's a really fucking funny movie. It is. It's very funny. All right. I'll check it out
Maybe I'll buy today pat and I grow in DVD shopping after this. He gets stung way of beads for I guess they use it in the trailer
But he like blows up to like
You know, like almost like Norbit style levels and he's he doesn't realize it
So he's sitting in the back of this plane and they turn around and look at him
He's like, he's basically looks like Jimmy Glick before he was doing it. He's like, what's going on?
Just it's it's pure short. It's like his
Who's Harry Crom kind of all right? I'll check it out. I kind of want to buy the movie where he's the little kid
That's a real weird one. I own Clifford. It's one of the funnest movies. I've got him in Grotein. I mean, it's Clifford has some big big laughs
Really on PC film what I've seen. Yeah, and I really like it's crazy and I love Grote
Uh, Grodon's the best Beethoven, not my shoes, Beethoven.
No, uh, Grodon's best, uh, Beethoven, not on the rock, Beethoven.
Oh, do you ever see the original heartbreak kid with Beethoven with, I mean, with Grodon.
Yeah.
I fucking loved it.
How was there not an SNL sketch where they had Beethoven and the heartbreak kid, the heartbreak
kid with Grodon was incredible.
Uh, yeah.
He's incredible movie.
He is fantastic.
Yeah, so much better than the stiller remake.
Yes, I would say certainly so,
with Carlos Mancilla in a key role.
Oh, God.
The thing, I wanted to bring this up,
was written by a gentleman named Bill Lancaster.
He wrote the screenplay.
The story was the other guy's name was escaping me,
giving me one second.
Original story is by,
and it's not here,
but the guy that wrote the film, the first film, okay?
But Bill Lancaster, very interesting, died at 49 from a heart attack.
These fuckers lived hard, man.
He was an actor, the only picture of him from his acting roles on Wikipedia is him in the
big valley.
So he was, you know, he was one of these goddamn western guys or whatever.
This guy's lived really hard, but doesn't have many film credits.
Only three.
he's written the screenplays for the thing and the sequel to the movie I'm about to mention
but he also wrote the bad news bears which is a masterpiece yeah what a what a run yeah the bad
news bears and the thing yeah and he also wrote bad news bears go to Japan genius which I don't
fault him for because the first ones ahead maybe he thought they could strike gold again
I only remember breaking training I don't know if I ever saw Japan
I never saw him training. Oh, no, this is the third one he wrote the second one. I guess is breaking training. Okay
Jesus Christ. Did you know this?
Regis Philbin is one of the stars of the bad news bears three. That's why I probably didn't see that one
But yet died at age 49 on his wife's 48th birthday. Oh, that's tough. That is terrible
I actually really love the bad news bears remake with Billy Bob Thornton. I thought it was great
I mean, people were angry about it.
I'm kind of like, what more could you want?
It's like they put, you know, Jamie Kennedy in it
or something, like, Billy Balfourin is fucking hilarious.
I scoffed when they first, when I first heard about it
and then I watched it and I really liked it.
And I was like, you know what?
They were, they were very true to the original.
They left out one or two jokes just out of the fact
that like, we just can't do this joke now
at times of change too much.
But they also added in shit that's not in the first one.
And I love that Billy Bob Thornton fucks the Marsha gay harden, you know, is the head
of the little league, you know, whatever it's called, corporation, or that'd be the,
the little, because you want to say the league, but then you say the little league league.
And it does organization.
Yeah.
There you go.
I like when he has all the kids sing cocaine, puts it on the jukebox and has all the kids
sing along to cocaine.
Yeah.
That's real funny.
Yeah, it's great, what else was it oh also about the thing any Omar Cone did the score. Yeah, it's a fantastic score
I was surprised to see it wasn't Carpenter, but yeah, I love the music and the thing well did Carpenter to do the title track at least?
I don't think he did
Have you seen the thing from another world in 1951? I've never seen the original. I
Have respect for it out of you know that it spawned all this other stuff. I like but I've never seen it
It's pretty decent.
I'd recommend it.
That's all it was, young.
It's a little, man, it's right in a pocket
of horror movies that I'm not.
Those early 50s ones, man, they're very like,
that's a lot of like invaders from the other planet type shit.
You know, and I don't get into like a twilight zone or something.
That's good.
All right, well, I'll check it out.
Well, I mean, because I bought the box set of,
And please, listeners out there, tell me what I'm missing.
If you know, or maybe you agree with me,
I bought the complete box out of the outer limits.
And I hadn't seen that as a kid.
I'd seen the Twilight Zone before I purchased all those
and everything, but I'd never really seen the outer limits
and I bought it on reputation alone
and I didn't pay a lot for it.
I can't get into it.
I just don't, it's something about it.
Maybe it's because the episodes are an hour long
each instead of 30 minutes.
But I don't know what it is.
And I've watched the Harlan Analysts in episodes which are deemed some of the best
Science fiction television episodes of all time
They're not it's not bad. I just do not find myself riveted by it
So give me your thoughts on that if you have any
Never seen any of them and actually I haven't seen all the twilight zone. I've only seen the first season
Oh god, dude, do yourself I know I know that show I'm working my way through it
that show hits from start to finish it dips a little bit in the fourth season
because they go to an hour long format so it's less episodes and it doesn't
work as well like they should be a half hour but other than that I mean I
can't I can't say enough good stuff about that show all right anything else on
the thing it's a great movie I mean it's hard to have a discussion about it I mean
to to me I can honestly say every time I've watched I've liked it more like I was
just like there's almost nothing to change about it well it's a near perfect
movie. That's actually something I wanted to say was like it is a very layered film you will find
and it's great it's part of I didn't know this either it's part of John Carpenter's what it
is called the apocalypse trilogy so this is the first film Prince of Darkness is the second film
in the mouth of madness is the third film and they're just about different apocalyptic events or
events that could lead to the apocalypse have you seen my hip hop clips trilogy I have not have
a series of rap videos that I made with my friends.
Literally think that's an actual movie with Coolio in it.
Hip -hop clips?
Would you be surprised?
It's not on the slides.
This is the man that was in Fat Beach.
PA.
Which I don't even know if that's a play on Fat Bitch.
Or what?
I never thought of it as such.
It's a pretty hot and tempting fat.
Like that girl's fat.
But I'll say this about the apocalypse trilogy.
I haven't been so far a huge fan of the prince of darkness. I am going now give it another shot because I didn't know this was considered a trilogy in any way, and in the mouth of madness is in my top carpenter films ever.
Like I love that fucking movie. Not a big fan. So I'm curious. I'm curious.
I, uh, and then, uh, so this is a very, oh, this one's gonna say, this is a very layered
and nuanced film.
Uh, it's not, everything Carpenter does for the most part is great, but this is certainly
I think a little less straightforward than some of the other stuff he's done.
And I think you get something new out of it every time you watch it.
Uh, and the ending is just tremendous.
I love not knowing could, could, uh, Keith David be infected, do we not know?
And just kind of knowing they're all dead regardless. Yeah, he'd still be alive. The last shot of Kurt Russell
It looks like he might have died, but it's not clear like it's just a really really tremendous movie. It is
We loved it. Go see it. And also a shout out to horror great
Mr. Tobay Hooper
Which I have been told I am mispronouncing and have been since I was a young boy somebody said today that he died
because he heard the way you said his name.
I doubt that's true.
Jack thought it was a little much.
I don't love that like three weeks before his death,
they break the official news story
that he did not really direct poltergeist.
Like, maybe we didn't need to kick an old man, you know?
What did he die for?
They still didn't announce what he died for him.
He was young.
Yeah, 76.
Oh, yeah, that's pretty, huh?
Yeah.
Favorite tobe?
Mine, of course, is poltergeist.
If we're saying he didn't direct,
that I guess I gotta go, Texas Chainsaw.
I think it's Texas Chainsaw far and away.
I feel that the film is groundbreaking,
and I love Poltergeist, but Texas Chainsaw
really reshaped our in many ways,
and it is a terrifying movie.
It is.
It's great.
Yeah, R .I .P. Tobay.
And Selom's, I like Selom's lock quite a bit.
But not as much as Poltergeist or Texas Chains.
Anyway.
Plugs, Jotaro's a comedy on Twitter and Instagram, if you're hearing this now, the next gig is DC, DC Drafthouse in September.
I think it's this, I don't know, it's early in September, go to their website and find some tickets and come on out.
I am Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh.
That's all I got folks, we will see you next time, thanks to Eli Braden for his re -recording
of the theme.
Yes, one more plug, Penthouse column, you let me down, it's out now, every month in Penthouse
digital or hard copies are available, go check it out, I enjoy writing it.
And check out Joe's other podcast, Emotional Hangs with Mr. Kurt Brommerler.
All right.
That was a hit gun podcast.
You