In business, every dollar counts.
So Comcast Business is giving you a year of mobile on us with your internet service.
Save hundreds with the fastest mobile service with 5G cellular and Wi -Fi hotspots.
Get mobile on us and get one year on us.
Comcast Business, Powering Possibilities
NS9 -2225, Resurrections Apply.
New mobile customers only with internet standards service were above.
Limited to value of one unlimited interline apply via 12 -month internet bill credits.
One discount per account.
Fastest mobile based on mobile Wi -Fi and cellular data in service areas.
UCL Speed Test Intelligence 2H24.
Talk about stepping up.
It's time to level up your game.
Introducing the all -new ESPN app.
All of ESPN, all in one place.
Your home for the most life sports and the best championship moment.
The electricity is palpable.
Step up your game with no annual contract required.
It's the ultimate fan experience.
Level up for more on the ESPN app or extreme .esPN .com.
Sign up now.
Well, hello, and how do you do from the good people that will see you in hell?
Your favorite podcast about horror, sci -fi, and fantasy films.
And once in a while, a little comedy, drama, action, and adventure.
I'm Joe DeRosa.
I'm Patrick Walsh, tonight we're going to be folks, folks, a sing on a man who brought a lot of comedy to the world.
Veering away from horror a bit.
Mr. John Candy, one of our all -time favorites.
That was a Twitter suggestion and a great one.
It's the 25th anniversary of his death.
And we'd like to celebrate the man's life.
Also a thanks, if I may, to Liz Sheldon for suggesting that we do this episode.
Thank you, Liz.
Appreciate it.
And I'm looking forward to it.
And I look forward to talking about the life, the work, the breath, the experience of John Candy.
You said the breath, the breath.
Oh, okay.
I was like, is it like we use bad jokes after his man's death?
Is it breath with a deep breath?
Breath, breath of work.
Yeah.
It's I have a hard time saying that word.
Folks, Joe answered the door today.
Harvey Weinstein style in a loose towel.
Mastering into a bush.
Shirtless with a loose towel.
It was alarming.
I was two minutes early.
And folks, I'm real glad I wasn't four minutes early.
If you catch my drift.
Glad we had that two minutes for towel tying.
And there was a hell of a drift coming up that towel.
If you catch my meaning.
Yes.
And a hell of a meaning coming up the towel.
Wow.
It's raining like hell.
Well, we weren't supposed to record today.
And then Pat somehow got out of his job early, which I've never seen happen.
And I had a little time before I go off to a show tonight where I will be singing the song Santoria.
You know, practice Santoria.
What do you do at karaoke or with a band?
With a band, my friend Brian Cook has a show called Guilty Treasures.
In fact, our dear friend Karen Colgareff will be on the show as well tonight.
If you're hearing this, don't go running over to the show.
It already happened.
Right.
Unless you've got a Delorean of some kind.
Oh, speaking of which, the man who made the Delorean or whatever it's called is coming out.
I believe John Delorean, isn't it?
Starring Alec Baldwin as John Delorean.
Yeah, I guess he was a spy or something, too.
It might be an interesting story.
It's called the Man Who Framed Delorean.
That's what it's called.
Okay.
I believe.
Anyway, you do a set and then you talk about a song you love that you're kind of embarrassed that you love.
Sure.
And then you sing the song.
And I chose Santoria by sublime.
I don't think there should be guilty pleasures.
I think you should like what you like.
But if I had to pick a couple off hand, I'd go Selena Gomez's song, Same Old Love.
I don't know.
But much more embarrassing than sublime.
And I also love the music of Carly Rae Gypsen, particularly the song Cut to the Feeling.
Those are two pop classics.
And now I'm going to sing them both in full.
I had to look up the lyrics to Santoria because I didn't know all of them.
I definitely know the lyrics.
I thought I did.
And I kind of did.
But you know, there were little words here and there.
I was like, what exactly did you say?
And now I got to do this.
I got to give this disclaimer speech before I sing the song because he talks about smacking a woman to the ground.
Sure.
But I don't think he's saying it as him.
I think he's saying about a character, a guy who would do...
I don't know.
I'd pop a cap and...
Sancho, yeah, slap her down.
Yeah, I don't think Brad is from sublime was popping caps in people.
Sancho's a woman.
Sancho is...
I looked at all the words.
I looked up what Santoria is.
It's an African -American religion that I think has Cuban roots.
I knew Santoria.
I think as voodoo elements to it, sort of like animal sacrifice and stuff.
And then...
Also a great push a T song from the latest album, Santoria.
A Sancho is a guy who like steals your lady, I think.
Okay.
And Hina is a term for girlfriend.
Well, if you're slapping down Sancho...
No, he goes, I'm gonna pop a cap in Sancho and I'll slap her down.
Okay.
I mean, it's ultimately worse for Sancho.
He's getting murdered.
Right.
But, you know, still, you don't want to condone anything like that.
So I got a whole spiel worked out to hopefully let the crowd feel okay with it as I sing the song.
You should say, hey, just be glad I'm not singing smack my bitch up.
Could have been doing that because that he died, he did die.
And people like had lovely tales about him.
I guess it was a sweet man.
Same with Luke Perry.
All these stories come out and you're like, not only is it cool that Luke Perry was a cool dude
but it's cool that like I didn't know that because he didn't go around talking about how nice he was.
What do you think took Perry out and King Kong Bundy?
God, man, it was a lousy week.
What do you think took Perry out?
I mean, the guy was in great shape.
Perry had a stroke.
No, I know, but I mean, like do you think he had a pre -existing condition?
Do you think he, you know, was a heavy smoker?
I mean, look, if you look at his skin, he looked like a guy that lived kind of hard.
Yeah, there was drink in his song.
I mean, he, to be that wrinkled, let's call it what it is at 52 is a little weird.
He was leathery.
Leathery.
I don't know when it happened.
I mean, of course, I'm sad when people die but I had no real effect on me because I don't think I've ever seen Luke Perry in anything.
I've never seen an episode of 902.
I'll feed a vampire slayer.
The movie.
The film?
Yes, fair enough.
I've seen Buffett the Vampire Slayer.
You were a big.
I love Buffett the Vampire Slayer.
You were a big Riverdale fan.
You wrote a lot of Riverdale fan fiction.
Never seen Riverdale.
I will give you that.
Let me look him up.
I'll tell you why I bummed me out.
He's one of those guys that, you know, it's like, it's like, it's like, when Joni died.
From happy days.
You know, you're like, that's Joni.
You know, so Luke Perry.
It's like, that's Luke Perry.
So, bum me out.
And then also too, I was excited for him to eat a part in the new Tarantino movie.
And I'm like, look at this guy.
Like, he's going to make a comeback.
You know, had he shot it already?
Yeah, it's already shot.
Well, that's good.
But I just, you know, you feel bad.
You're like, this guy had a big moment.
He was probably really excited, you know.
It's a shame.
I have also seen Luke Perry because I've seen every episode of one of the worst television shows
ever made.
Jon from Cincinnati.
Which got a post -Supranos premiere on HBO.
It was like Low Winter Sun when he came on after Breaking Bad.
And everybody was like, what the fuck is this?
Wasn't it the same creators?
Supranos?
No.
It was Milch, the guy who did Deadwood.
Oh, okay.
Milch.
Oh, I thought you meant that show on Show's time.
Where the single mom is always going around complaining.
People want to have sex with her or whatever.
That's smilf.
Single mom, I'd like to find out.
Could you imagine writing a show?
Let's just be honest for a second here.
I don't know the woman.
I have nothing against her.
Could you imagine though, the writing a script about yourself,
where you refer to yourself in the title as somebody people want to fuck?
Could you imagine having that level of confidence in ego?
No.
Absolutely not.
And it's not even like a joke.
It's not even like, she thinks she's sexy, but she's a hot mess.
It's like, no, she's supposed to be, and she is.
She's hot.
But I mean, it's just kind of weird.
Rosie O'Donnell as her mom.
I saw the first one, the first episode was very dawn heavy.
It didn't bring me back, but I don't know enough to speak ill of it.
She's a, I can't speak ill of the show.
I just, just the title of, I'm going to make a show about my life.
Also, she's a big, big middle -ditch fan.
Who is?
The woman that created and stars in that show.
How do you know that the lead of Smilf, a show you've never seen,
is a big Thomas middle -ditch?
Because I auditioned for her show once.
Okay.
And I had to watch the show, it was before us out.
I had to watch the short films.
Oh, I've seen the short film.
And he was in it.
And then the other day, I ended up on her Twitter because she's in Jay and Silent Bob,
get reboot, get the reboot, whatever it's called.
And I didn't know who she was in the picture.
So I clicked the link and it went to her feed.
And I was like, oh, that's the lady from Smilf.
And then her first tweet was like something along the lines of like,
ten years ago, this beautiful man started my short film.
Okay.
It's like one of those things.
Yeah.
Uh, and Thomas middle -ditch, I've never met yet.
I can't stand.
Um, yeah.
I mean, look, the guy, the guy's commercials have, uh, really,
I never cared for Montsilicon Valley, but these commercials are something else, man.
They're something else.
I liked them on Silicon Valley.
The Verizon things put me, I'm just like, yeah.
Oh my God.
Eddie Pepitone does a tremendous amount of tweets about how much he hates middle -ditch,
and they're always fucking hilarious.
I saw Eddie Pepitone here in town recently.
God, it was funny.
I saw him the other night.
He was very funny.
Yeah.
Um, yeah.
I looked up Perry.
I looked through his whole illustrious career.
Truly, the only things I've seen, John from Cincinnati, both of the vampires there.
But RIP, I couldn't pick King Kong Bundy out of a lineup that just was not my era of wrestling.
Uh, King Kong Bundy is, you know, he's one of the classics, man.
And he was really funny, too.
Yeah.
He started to do stand -up, I think, after he quit wrestling.
Okay.
Which I'm always skeptical about.
I just, you know, our friend Stormy Daniels now is doing stand -up.
Yeah.
At the joke joint.
I said to my friend, I go, I'd be less embarrassed to be headlining the strip club in that city
than the joke joint.
Folks.
Uh, but, you know, I'm always skeptical when somebody leaves their other thing and does stand -up.
Yeah.
And, uh, but, and I never saw a stand -up.
So I might have been terrible.
But in interviews, he was really funny.
Uh, and he would say like very edgy stuff.
And I thought I liked it.
I enjoyed it.
But, uh, you know, what do you say?
Let's, let's throw this out to the fans.
Let's put out a thousand dollar Patreon level.
Okay.
Patreon level.
It's thousand dollars.
We, we'll put it up there.
You get it.
The three of us, whoever gives the money to you and me, fly down to Houston, Texas.
Yeah.
For the Stormy Daniels stand -up show.
Now, do that, do they give us a thousand dollars?
Do we split it?
If you, if we buy three tickets with the thousand dollars, we need two thousand dollars.
We need more to be hotel money and stuff, too.
Yeah.
But yeah, but we pay, we'll buy the whole package.
We'll fly you from where you are.
I'll do that.
Two thousand dollars.
I am two days away from being out.
Oh, work.
I don't know what's next and folks.
I don't care.
I'm gonna relax.
You put your time in, baby.
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, I would, I would go do that.
So if any of you want to contribute two thousand dollars, we'll meet you in Houston for a Stormy.
Speaking of Stormy, it's raining like hell out there right now.
I'm enjoying it.
Are you though?
I mean, it doesn't rain 364 days out of the year, usually in Los Angeles.
We've had about a month of pretty steady rain.
I'm loving every minute of it.
Every minute of it?
Every single minute of it.
God, never, never getting enough.
No, I hate Los Angeles weather and this doesn't feel like Los Angeles weather.
So I love it.
All right.
Now, folks, if I may, yeah.
Let's get on with the show.
And at the same time, on with the Jewel.
All right.
There it is.
Take two of the arm with the Joe.
Uh, we had to redo the arm with the Joe.
Well, no, Joe had a call.
Pat wasn't happy with the reason.
I said, hey, if you're taking a call, let's get out my shitty arm with the Joe and replace it with a slightly very slightly less shitty arm with the Joe.
Um, folks, let me take you if I may over to Pat's movie corner.
I saw a picture, believe on stars, I want to say, called ideal home.
Uh, I was intrigued for three reasons, two at stars, Paul Rudd, who's always fun.
And the great Steve Cougan, who plays one of my favorite characters of all time, Alan Partridge, who has a new show on the BBC that I am dying to see.
Is it the talk show again?
It's the talk show again.
Wow.
I cannot wait.
My favorite Alan Partridge is the post talk show, like chronicling his life falling apart.
Yeah, the one where it's like the office version of Alan Partridge is one of the funniest things you've ever seen.
Yes, but I'm still very excited for this.
And I've heard that it's great.
Anyway, Steve Cougan and Paul Rudd as a homosexual couple who wind up in, you know, raising a young boy.
The movie was directed by Andrew Fleming, who was a writer director.
I like a lot.
He did the craft, which we covered on this show, but I prefer his comedies.
He did Dick, which I liked a lot.
He did Hamlet II with Steve Cougan, which is really a funny movie if you have not seen it very underrated.
And this is just basically a love story about kind of a bitchy gay couple trying to raise this kid.
And it played like an average sitcom for about its entire running time.
There are like a couple decent jokes.
It's all very pleasant.
It's just not something I would say you got to rush out and see.
It's elevated by the performances.
Just in my opinion, Andrew Fleming is usually a much sharper writer director, and this felt just kind of, you know, barely hung together.
However, there's so many generic romantic comedies that come out all the time.
I liked having the gay twist on it, you know, that they should have their generic romantic comedies too.
And that's what this was.
At the end, they show a lot of photos of actual gay couples and their actual children as kind of a montage over the credits.
That was fantastic and very cool to see.
I just sort of felt like I'm not sure you earned this loving montage, you know, like with what came before it.
All in all, an average film.
If it's on TV, you're not going to hate yourself for watching it.
But there it is.
Sounds like a boring movie.
Like when you were describing it, I was like, what is this like a one of Rudd's first films?
This is like a newer thing.
Yeah, like Rudd was cast as gay for about five years there.
No, but I'm saying though, like this is a newer picture.
Yeah, it feels exactly like a 98, like object of my affection type movie.
And that's about the level it's at.
It's fine.
Would you say that I'm the object of your affection?
No.
Especially after that towel encounter.
I see now, you know what that says to me, people?
He wants it.
He wants it and he can't have it, sister.
I watched a documentary.
I can't remember if I talked about this on the show before because it was the second time I watched it.
But I watched a documentary called Adjust Your Tracking, which is about VHS collectors.
And I really enjoyed it.
I find it.
I found it on Amazon.
No, I think I saw it on Toobie.
Jesus, with this Toobie.
It's a great app.
You're going to be recommending all stuff, no one has any idea what you're talking about.
Well, the first time I saw it wasn't on Toobie.
Toobie originals.
There was a time when they said this about AMC pet.
Keep that in mind.
I watched Adjust Your Tracking.
It's a fun documentary.
It's guys with these end gals.
But it is mostly dudes with these insane VHS collections.
They're just pretty cool dudes.
They seem nice enough.
There's one guy that has a video store in his basement.
He converted his basement into an actual video store.
They talk about renting VHS.
And people still come by and rent them.
I couldn't tell if he was open to the public or if he just as a goof,
he turned his basement into a video store.
But he had like a cash register and everything down there.
So that was hard to tell.
But they get into blockbuster and the fall of the mom and pop video store
and how that all worked and what happened and went wrong.
This sort of thing.
And I just enjoy watching anything about collectors usually,
especially collectors that collect things that I'm interested in.
And then I'm not a huge VHS collector.
But I have a modest amount over there.
And I have a decent sized movie collection.
So I just enjoyed the film.
And my favorite part is when they get into the rarities in the VHS field.
And like these movies that look like a guy shot it on a camcorder in 1983.
But it's so rare.
It sells for like $700 new if you can find a copy of the movie.
I had a very extensive VHS collection covering a whole wall of my basement
when I was well till I left my parents house.
I think one day my dad just sold them all for a dollar probably.
But I had a very extensive collection including Rad, the BMX biking movie,
which I sold for $500.
A used copy that I stole from blockbuster video,
which was an evil corporation and I felt I was owed it.
And the other that I sold for quite a bit of money was a VHS of Gatorbait,
which was like a deliverance type movie,
but with a Playboy model.
And I never opened it.
It was like a gag gift.
And I was like Gatorbait.
But years later I was like, oh, I never opened this.
Looked it up online worth like $500 new.
You can do some funds for losers.
Especially if something never came out on DVD,
which is the case of both of those movies.
The last blockbuster just closed.
It was Australia.
Alaska, right?
I think it was Australia.
It was a place that started and ended with an A.
Well, John Oliver talks about this on his HBO program and I believe it was Alaska.
How does he talk about it at the top of his lungs?
In a Muppet voice screened at the top of his lungs.
Blockbuster video still has stores open in Alaska.
Thank you.
Oh, so the last one didn't close.
Well, if it did, it was in Alaska.
Okay.
So YouTube has been splicing John Oliver rants about Brexit in as ads for some reason.
I guess, I mean, you know, people, it's like, what fucking world are we?
We got an entertainment show that has paid ads about its take on Brexit.
You think your voice matters in this fucking, just please.
Anyway, John, I mean, it couldn't be more corporate meets pot.
It's just crazy.
But anyway, it's this thing.
I go to sleep to a lot to YouTube.
I'll go to sleep to collector videos and video game reviews and stuff like that.
I find them very soothing.
Okay.
And the middle of a soothing thing where guys like the problem with the burger time port on the Atari is,
you know, it doesn't control as well.
Brexit.
But it is madness.
Do you believe it?
And I'm like, what the fuck is happening right now?
Yeah.
I have to like roll it and it goes on for like five minutes.
That makes no sense.
That's not an ad at all.
I don't know what that is.
It's literally a rant about Brexit from the desk.
And when you're going to bed, you just let your laptop sit there all night playing.
I have my iPad and I play like a playlist or something on YouTube.
But those still have ads in them.
John Oliver show.
And I think I've seen every episode of it.
I can't do Trevor Noah.
It's just deadly.
But I mean, I like the one chest deadly.
Once a week like John Oliver, when he'd go into an issue like he's like all this week,
we are talking to you about teacher salaries or whatever it may be.
And they do kind of a probing in -depth look.
I like that.
When it's him now just like, whoa, Trumpy, fuck a Trumpy, you fucking orange piece of shit Trump.
It's like I can find this anywhere else.
This isn't very interesting.
The screaming you're dead on.
It's just like stop screaming.
I have to always turn down the TV like to it almost unlistenable point because you never know when he's going to start screaming.
The voice is a lot.
The persona's a lot.
I don't find him particularly funny.
I watch it really as kind of a news source.
A once a week collection of stories of the day presented sometimes entertainingly.
But I'll be damned if that guy doesn't grate my cheese sometimes.
I don't even think it's a good collection of news stories.
I feel like it's a few stories.
And then 15 minutes are like peanut farmers.
Where he's like tweet at your local senator to tell him he's a peanut head.
If he doesn't vote for this bill.
You're this angry about this.
And then the other thing is he'll be like, fuck you, fuck 800 fucks in a sentence because he's on HBO.
And it's like, look man, I'm no prude.
But you don't have to say fuck all the time because you're on HBO.
Then they'll do the news story because I tried to finger you earlier and you said no.
Well, I don't like being fingered.
I like other things that we can discuss after the show.
But basically he drives me nuts with that shit.
And when he really drives me nuts.
And this is something John Stewart and others used to do.
But at least you could usually believe John Stewart meant it is when he does the fake like really sincere bit.
And I'll show you a clip of like some so, you know, a clip of a man getting eaten by a bear or something and everybody goes, oh my god.
Oh my god, you see that?
And then 10 seconds later it's a clip of like a little girl, you know, having someone call her a racial slur.
And I'll come back and go like, fucks.
Can you believe what you've just seen?
Like voice quivering and it's like pick a tone.
And what are you doing?
This is my impression of the old daily show with the two of them, ready?
This is Stewart and Oliver.
So, you know, I'm Trump, maybe just maybe you know.
Maybe you know.
He's an idiot.
Yeah.
John, the man is a damn fool.
And Mike Pence.
Yeah, maybe.
You know, a Stewart fan as well.
And Mike Pence.
Maybe you know.
No, I just thought it would be fun to do this.
Oh.
Thanks for just stepping right on the bit though.
I mean, I didn't know how long it was going to go.
As long as I've got damn wanted it too.
John Stewart, I always enjoy it.
No, yes and kind of guy.
But I like John Oliver in a in that role of coming on for a segment.
A half hours a lot.
I like John Stewart.
I'm just pointing out how polar opposite it is that this show was a daily show clone.
Yes.
And Stewart was like, was like, I just have a baby, you know what I mean?
You know, it was all very just like understatus.
Shrugging the shoulders, making that face.
You know, sure.
And, you know, Christy, Oliver sounds like he's going to start throwing like lawn darts at the camera.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
Uh, I saw super troopers too.
How was it?
You know.
I believe it's on one of the networks HBO maybe.
How was it?
It is funny, you know.
It's like, I looked it up and terribly reviewed.
Then everybody who gave it terrible reviews the first time when it was just super troopers.
It's like nowhere near as good as the brilliance of super troopers because now everyone likes super troopers.
So everyone pretends they liked it when it came out.
Not all these critics, you look up their reviews like, no, you hated it.
Yeah.
I mean, it's just sick.
But, uh, super troopers too is stupid, but it's really funny.
And honestly, jarring to see a movie with jokes, a comedy with jokes.
And that's sad and scary to say, but it is a comedy with a ton of jokes and they don't all
work.
And some of them are real stupid, some of them are real gross, but it starts with a really funny scene.
And it just kind of goes from there.
Fred Savage turns up.
Great little cameo.
There's funny shit in it.
Will Sassos, great net.
There's great little bit parts for people.
And I think those guys are good.
I thought beer fest was maybe their crowning achievement.
I never think they're at some sort of A level, but in terms of your second tier comedy they know how to land a joke.
I like what they do.
All right.
What do you think of the broken lizard guys?
Uh, you know, they're funny.
You know, they're, they're, it's, it's hit and miss like any one of those troops.
Yeah.
You know, it's their, they're funny.
Uh, and then they're, and then I'm like, well, whatever.
And then they're funny again.
And then I'm like, yeah, whatever.
Uh, speaking of which, I watched, ooh, I'm going to get shit for this, but I wasn't even going to bring this up.
But you brought up broken lizard.
I watched a retrospective show about mighty, Monty Python.
Yeah.
Uh, I can't even remember the name of it, but it's, you know, something something the best of Python.
And then it's like all these actors and comedians setting up their favorite sketches.
Right.
One of which is Jim Carrey, and yet another just a born appearance on camera of him explaining to you what brilliance is.
Uh -huh.
Uh, people.
These fucking guys are not funny, Monty Python.
It is not funny at all.
It is not, it's, it's not funny.
Watch these sketches and tell me they're funny.
It's literally like every sketch is like, Jim Carrey will be like, I love the one where Terry Gilliam sees double.
Uh -huh.
But he's a mountain climber.
And then Eric, and then the sketch comes in and Terry Gilliam's body does.
And Eric Idle comes in and Eric Idle's like, and Terry Gilliam will be like, uh, now the two of you there.
And Eric Idle will be like, so there's just one of me here.
Okay.
Then both of you get right and it's just killing applause breaks.
And, and that's the whole sketch just over and over.
So, so you say there's just one of you then, huh? Yeah.
Well, then how come I see two of you?
So, there's only one of me could have a trouble climbing up that mountain with the two of you together.
So, there's one of me.
We might have, it's, that's it.
That's, that's the whole fucking sketch over and over and over and over and over.
My parents not dead.
Your parents dead.
That parent is alive.
Don't you see?
It's a lot, it's not alive.
It's dead.
It's not dead.
It's over and over and over.
And fucking nausea.
Did you enjoy Monty Python on the Holy Grail?
Some of it.
I thought the meaning of life was funny.
Meaning of life is funny.
I think portions of the movies are funny because there's like at least a character thing to latch on to.
Sure.
I have seen, I own the box set of Monty Python and I have not opened it.
Of course you have it.
I have seen some of the sketches.
I do feel like their sketches are probably more of their time.
I think it's like watching early SNL.
Super groundbreaking then.
You watch it now.
You're like, what the fuck?
Monty Python, I feel like would be less dated because they're more silly and surreal as opposed to political.
I'll go a step further with this just so you think I'm not bashing on our friends across the pond there.
Sure.
SNL was never funny.
People go, people go, oh the glory days of SNL.
You go back and watch these early, the once in the 70s you're talking about where people were like,
yeah.
This was a wild show.
It was wild because they are bombing from front to fucking back on this thing and the whole country.
And they're so high they don't know.
Yeah, the whole country was so coked up and stoned.
That's true.
It was like, fun to watch.
Those sketches stink.
Jean Bagger, Jean Bagger, Jean Bagger.
Jean Bagger, Jean Bagger, Jean Bagger, Jean Bagger.
There is a reason that whenever they do a retrospective and they do them all the time, they show the same 12 sketches.
So it's like, and who could forget?
And it's like, don't tell me you're going to show the shark knocking on the door again.
And they do.
And Rosanne, Rosanna, and all this stuff.
And I do think you can cut together a super funny two to three hour collection of SNL sketches in the 70s.
But yeah, when I actually sat down and I was like, as a student of comedy, I'm going to watch all of them when they actually put them on DVD.
I watched like all the 75 episodes.
Who there's some dog shit in there?
And when they don't have a funny host, man.
Yeah.
And they almost never have a funny host back then because they didn't understand you can't build a book like Milton Burrell.
That's like, that's like being like, you know what?
We're doing a comedy festival in the dingy as bars in Echo Park.
We've got rich little coming down to host it.
Like they didn't understand that this doesn't work tonally together.
But dude.
And then what when it wasn't him would be Buck Henry.
Oh my god.
You want to talk about a guy who's not funny who was just on there for years.
Mine.
My glory days for man wrote the graduate.
Don't get me wrong.
Of SNL.
My glory days for you SNL are the Farley cast.
That is the funniest time when the old guard was going out and the new guard was coming in.
But I'll tell you this.
You even you watch those dead.
Miller was my favorite Hollywood.
I mean, what the hell the fuck is it called?
We can't update.
Never liked that guy.
Always a norm man.
I love norm too.
But norm was sort of at the tail end of this stuff.
Right.
You know, this all kind of bridges over.
But that phase.
Yeah.
Was my favorite.
That was the classic time.
Spade was in there.
So you go back and watch those full episodes.
They suck.
It's the same thing when they show you the highlights of those seasons.
It's the same.
God damn 20 sketches.
But whenever Farley's popping up in something or Hartman or.
Yeah, there's plenty.
There are.
There's plenty.
They pop up in that doesn't work.
That's that one sketch where it's them like in the newsroom.
What are you trying to say?
I'm fired.
You're fired.
You're gone.
That's a very funny sketch.
It's gets.
Zero left.
Him and love it.
They start laughing about halfway through.
We watched that in the room.
Because love.
It's just today.
A cool kid.
And we.
It's fun.
I'm fans of all.
And I'm fans of the people that were in the cast of us.
I know.
And I'm fans of.
I love.
Like when I see John Cleese popping up, I get very excited.
Like I like these people.
John Cleese is a fucking hilarious man and faulty towers is a fucking hilarious show.
I like.
I just proof that it's not.
Which is proof that what we're talking about doesn't mean because it's of the time.
There's plenty of the time that's still funny.
Yeah.
You still laugh at Caddy Shack.
That's true.
You still laugh at the Monty Python movies.
I'm talking.
These shows as sketch shows are not fucking funny.
I'm sorry.
It's.
And Jim Carrick can sit there only once in a multi colored rayon shirt telling me that it's.
They've captured madness man.
Yeah.
That it's madness man.
Oh god.
He fucking sucks.
Whoo.
All right.
That's all right.
You're doing a lot of screaming on today's show.
I had a lot of fun doing my reenactments of Mighty Python.
I'd like to say for the record.
I haven't seen Monty Python in the Holy Grail in a while.
But the movie I always found to be a just joke dense hilarious film.
A lot of jokes.
Meaning of life is very funny.
And life of Brian was kind of lost on me as a kid.
But I liked it more as an adult.
I like meeting a life because it was dark.
I like that they did some gross out humor in it.
And Mr. Creosote never sat right with me.
I never found that funny.
The fact I.
Yeah.
Why?
The puking.
I never enjoyed puking.
It gets a disgusting sketch.
Yeah.
But I liked it.
And it had some to say, you know, about the rich and they just keep eating and they're blah, blah.
I get it.
I liked them.
I like scattered SNL.
I do think you hold up aside from this recent millennia episode, which was really just a wall to wall.
Very fun.
GM.
And they're best in five years.
If you hold up any of the past five years of SNL, to almost any other time in its history,
we're at the worst phase of the show.
I don't think you could tie together a highlight reel of the past five seasons.
And I don't think they've had a breakout character in the last five seasons.
It's not a show that lives on that.
It's not a cultural commentary anymore.
It's just jokes for millennials.
Almost just jokes for millennials.
It is.
Like, I really, I liked this week's episode.
I hated that fucking scream sketch.
It was just like...
Yeah.
No, it wasn't great.
It's just like, we get it.
Nothing phases.
Well, it's like, it's the same note over it.
And like, so many of like, when they'll do celebrity things now, it's like, who gets this besides somebody who's 22 or younger?
Sure.
Like, who's this into...
Like, the fact that Ariana Grande gave that show relevance again because she was dating somebody on it?
Yeah.
That says it all right there.
You know, anybody over 24 that listens to Ariana Grande?
I do.
I don't listen to her, but I have seen every episode of SNL since I have been alive, I would say, since I was five,
except for the ones my dad made me go to bed early.
It's a show I've really watched the progression of, and I think we're at probably its darkest time.
Joe, what's your number two pick?
That was my number two.
It was this money python.
Yeah.
Okay.
My number three, and remind me to read a Peter Travers tweet, the worst movie critic in America.
My number three is...
You know what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna talk about something that at unquestionably folks, the most relentlessly grim, like six month period of my life,
this thing brought me such joy.
I watched the last one the other night, and it is the six round the world with Conan O 'Brien specials that are on Netflix, fairly new to Netflix.
And in each one, he goes to a different part of the globe, Haiti, Italy, whatever, Israel.
And I think a big part of it is that I used to watch Conan every single night, even when I was a kid,
I would stay up till 1230 and watch him.
I worked to Conan briefly, but eventually got kind of burned out.
I watched all his run when he was in the Leno spot, and then I kind of gave up when he went to TBS.
But my god, as he's still funny, and these shows are so fucking funny.
They're relentlessly joke -packed.
They're edited very well.
They all clock in at like 45 minutes, and they all have moments of heart and sweetness and genuine learning about other cultures.
I thought they were so good that when I watched the first one, I immediately watched the second, and then I said,
no, no, no, save these in the chamber for a rainy day.
I did it just nice, where I was just like, oh, fuck, I'm in a bad mood.
I would sit down and start laughing.
I can't recommend them highly enough. They're fantastic.
Last on my list is the 1941 version of Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde,
which I had never seen.
Spencer Tracy plays Jekyll and Hyde.
I was a little more interested in seeing the 1931 version with Frederick March that this was a remake of.
Both were supposed to be on the disc, the 31 version wasn't on the disc, sadly, and disappointingly.
But I watched the 1941 version, and it is no slouch.
It's a very, very good film, excellent direction, very daring too, very edgy imagery for that time, for that time period.
Really, there's a scene when he first takes the potion, and the director does this whole craze leak, like montage of images, like crazy images.
And one of the things he starts, he sees himself on like whipping a pack of wild horses, like a madman, and then the horses turn into the women that he wants to fuck.
Like it's wild shit. It's pretty edgy for that time and place, because the ratings code was a pretty new thing then.
And I'm surprised they got away with what they got away with in this, but it's a great flick.
It's a classic. I have it on a four pack of Turner Classic movie, greatest hits.
That freaks the haunting, and I forget what so far you're three from four. I haven't seen this one.
The fourth one is, how am I blanking on this? The fourth one is House of Wax.
Oh, good movies all. Yeah, so it's a nice little pack and get it for like six bucks on Amazon.
I would recommend really looking into those. I bought so many of those four movies in one little set thing for five bucks.
And, you know, they're nice to have. They're not always the best quality. You got to read the reviews.
Sometimes they try to put like four movies on one disc and then everything looks worse than VHS.
But you can find some good deals if you look those up. I'm going to read you this tweet from a man who has made me angry for decades, the worst critic in the business, Peter Travers.
Now, just a shameful quote, or he uses words like roll a king and stuff, just so he can get put on a poster.
But this one was one of my recent favorites. And it's about, I didn't send this to you.
No, it's about what's the movie called Marvel girl.
Captain Marvel. Oh, she's Captain Marvel. She's Captain Marvel. It's been met with lukewarm reviews, which makes me very happy.
Because finally people are calling bullshit on Marvel and saying stop showing us the same goddamn movie over and over again.
It is strange that they're doing it to the woman one, but clearly Peter Travers was like, I didn't like this.
But it's about women. So I better say I did AV club didn't give it a good reason. I was like this must really not be a good movie.
Right. Yeah, they'll usually lie about anything. Here's Travers.
You could ding it for convoluted plotting and a retro style that flattens the usual Marvel fireworks.
But a dynamite Brylarson gives hell to cosmic villains and sexist trolls. And an orange feline named Goose is the best movie cat ever.
Exclamation point four out of five stars unbelievable folks.
He says two really bad things about the movie. Then just simply states what Brylarson does.
She gives hell to villains and trolls. Then talks about a cat being cute early reviews it for stars early reviews of the movie.
We're saying this cat the cat steals the show. I mean, what are we dealing with here? We're talking about a fucking cat stealing the show.
It's a cute and this cat looking on my finger. I hate cats. Oh, so you just try to show Joe a picture of my cat.
Your cat's cute, but I'm not a cat. I can't touch the things. I'm allergic. But I mean, people are talking about this goddamn cat.
It's like guys, we're already adults talking about a movie where people are wearing tights and flying around.
Now we've reduced that movie to just talking about the cat in it. These aren't good movies.
Can we stop pretending like these aren't these the reason that people think these are good is because we haven't we have an infirm a lust for information.
We can't get enough stimulation out of our devices out of our everything has to be now, now, now. And people are watching people are literally binge watching Marvel movies at this point.
It's like a TV show. You're watching Marvel movies at the clip you would watch a TV show in the 80s because they get released that quickly.
And TV shows are like watching commercials now because you can just blaze through the whole season in one city.
So it's like I couldn't even have met when I saw that like we're showing all the Marvel movies over a 24 hour period at AMC theaters.
I would die. I would absolutely die. There's not enough money.
Imagine just every movie with the exact hitting the exact same beats and the exact same noise.
Dude, they're in phase three. Think about how long ago Avengers won the first one.
People hate when we go off on super house. Avengers part one ended phase one of Marvel.
Only those movies were phase one. Think about how many movies that was.
During that phase, I was like, what was this getting a little silly, but all right.
How many phases are they doing? They're in phase three.
But is there a limit? No. They've already got phase four planned, I think.
Dude, it's just like who gives a shit, man. God almighty. How many times can you watch this fucking shit? It's so boring.
By the way, guys, this is the shit we all trashed in the 80s.
This stupid fucking brainless machismo horse shit that started off as really, really cool story -built action movies like First Blood.
And then you ended up with Rambo 3. And everybody was like, what the fuck happened to the genre?
They killed the goose. They put too much of it out. These movies are terrible.
They all rely on bad one -liners, stupid gags, and dumb machismo.
And that's all these fucking Marvel movies are. And everybody was like, no, no, no, no, great.
Shut up. If I hear one more fucking person go, the reason they're good is because of the joke.
Is it? Is it? That's literally like being the reason Ghostbusters 1 was good was because of the ghosts.
Do you know what I mean? I do. Fucking morons, man.
All right, sorry. I'm all worked up today. It's going to be a hot show tonight, Joe.
Joe's heading to a stand -up show. I might go on stage and do the money by that was never funny. Go for it. See if it works.
Let's get into our topic of the day. I'll say you need to tone down the anger and tone up the love for what do you say we sweeten it up with a little bit of candy.
Got it. Got it.
That's why we don't work in a writer's room together.
One of thousands of.
Yeah, in the middle of breaking a script, I'm pacing around the room.
John Candy to me. Easily one of my biggest comedy heroes, both in stature and in talent.
And it was immediate for like one of my earliest memories of childhood was a love of John Candy.
When you look up like when my dad was moving out of his house, he had all these boxes and I was looking through like old papers I had and it was like kindergarten.
Favorite movie star, John Candy, like that early.
And when John Candy passed away in 1994, March of 1994, I would have been about 13 and I remember.
Going on 30 because it was a tough childhood.
My mother told me about John Candy's death in the same way you would tell a kid that their grandfather had died.
And I took it every bit as hard. I refused to believe it.
I think it happened maybe a couple of months prior to Hartman, which hit me as well.
But you know, John Candy to me was like, I think my mom was like, I know you need to be alone or I went to my room.
I think I was crying. I mean, just just the funniest and he had something that most comedy stars don't, which is just you love him.
Everybody loved him. Farley had it certainly to some extent, but picked a lot of the wrong projects and was alive a lot shorter.
John Candy also had difficulty picking projects.
You certainly find yourself wishing he had more movies that were up to his talents.
But when you did find a movie that met him at his level, a plan strides on automobiles or an uncle buck or several others that we'll discuss here.
The man was fearless.
Candy didn't hit it. Candy didn't. This is what a lot of people don't realize. Candy didn't hit his stride in candy movies until the midpoint.
He got off to a slow start, you know.
There's a lot of stuff he did in Canada that were Canadian only movies that are very forgettable going berserk.
And even one of his earlier films, which we've talked about here, some are rental is not a funny movie.
It's got big laughs, but a terrible last half hour.
It's charming, but farley on the other hand, it was the exact opposite. He came out swinging.
And then he had a bunch of duds, and I feel like Farley had a chance at the same resurgence or finding his stride finally.
Farley was going to do an Oliver Stone biopic of fatty arbuckle.
That would have been awesome.
You know, that candy had also toyed with yours prior, but you are right now your 42, 41, 41.
John Candy died at 43.
It was like 56. It's because we were kids, yeah.
But I mean, even look at that picture. If you met him and he goes, I'm 43, you'd be like, what?
Yeah.
I mean, I would like to A, I was a massive SCTV fan from a very young age.
SCTV, you put that on now, you want to talk about holding up.
That is comedy now. SCTV now is what everyone is pretending is like the new comedy.
Everyone's like, oh, have you seen this?
It really is all that shits Creek is SCTV.
Right, right.
And it's not just because it's got O 'Hara and Guest.
I mean, it's slightly larger than life characters, but always performed fairly realistically.
That show is so much smarter and funnier and more timeless than SNL.
And the parodies of things, like I don't know who, like Brenda Vicaro is for example.
I believe she was in Saturday Night Fever.
But when Andrea Martin does Brenda Vicaro, her impression is so funny that it doesn't matter.
She doesn't have the impression where she's going, like taking these weird breaths.
And I'm like, I love this character, even though I don't know who she's impersonating.
One of the hardest, let me name a couple that I laughed real hard at.
But well, my favorite SCTV thing arguably thing ever is the, what's his face from Ghost Busters?
Rick Moranis would do Merv Griffin.
Sure.
And I remember the first sketch you ever did it on.
It's him and a piano and it's a promo for the Merv Griffin show that week.
Yes.
And he's looking into camera and he's going, on the radio.
And I lose my fucking mind when I see that.
Again, if you don't know Merv Griffin, it's just funny because you're like, who is this guy?
Right.
What would this show be like?
Also, Johnny LaRue is always great.
Johnny LaRue is incredible.
Five neat guys, which is the barbershop quartet, with candy, levy Moranis, Dave Thomas,
and Flaherty.
One of my favorites.
Yellow belly, the coward that John Candy played, who shoots a woman in the back, and then shoots
a child to avoid mild conflicts.
He's going to Western, but his name is yellow belly.
Candy did some great stuff on there.
The half -wits, which it was completely ripped off by SNL for the Trebek Jeopardy sketches.
Who's the character Levy would play?
Levy would play the like Stallone actor?
That would be like, yeah, he would do that laugh.
I know who you're talking about.
I do not remember his name.
But I know.
Candy, I mean, let's go through it.
So SETV is a great place to start.
And every episode of it is available on DVD.
You can get whole seasons for pretty cheap on Amazon unless they've gone out of print.
But where, I guess most people saw him in terms of movies, was 1941.
Wait, I'm going to show it.
You know, a notorious Spielberg bomb, a huge money loser.
It's Belushi, it's Acroid, it's in World War II.
I think it's pretty fun movie.
And not everything works in it, but it's got a lot of great stuff.
But Candy really came into his own, I would say.
And, you know, to me, this is a classic movie.
People either love it or hate it.
Blues Brothers.
And his character, the cop in there, and his immortal line, orange whip, orange whip, three orange whips.
I mean, John Candy is fucking incredible in that.
And John Candy's style of comedy, from the jump, was ahead of its time.
Nobody was doing that kind of comedy.
It was all very much him.
And all that comedy now, the awkwardness that people do, you know, that's in all, especially all cable comedy,
and everything's awkward, and everything's uncomfortable.
That was Candy in a nutshell, man.
Like, that was his whole thing, but he had a broader appeal with it.
And that speaks to some of the issues that Farley had with his movies, was they took him
and put him, the first thing he was in, he was the main guy.
Right.
You know, like, oh, he had a small part in the world, and yeah.
Billy Madison, he was hilarious.
But, you know, it's like, he popped up.
Candy was the second fiddle, third fiddle, fourth fiddle for a long time.
I mean, you get up to splash, he still isn't the star of this thing.
Blues Brothers 80, Stripes 81, he's hilarious and striped.
Again.
There are a movie on this flight.
Yeah.
And then National Ampune's vacation.
Small parts.
He's great in it.
Vacation as the guard, super memorable splash.
He steals that movie easily.
And then Brewster's Millions is kind of his first lead with prior.
Brewster's Millions, I remember loving as a kid.
Wait, Brewster's Millions was before Summer rental?
Well, same year.
Okay.
Well, even Brewster's, it's prior's movie.
Yeah.
Still, it's still not his movie is what I'm getting at.
You know what I mean?
In 85, the man made Brewster's Millions, which I loved as a kid, watched recently, it's not good.
And John Candy doesn't have many great bits in it.
I remember even as a kid being like, I wanted more from you.
It's a great premise and they don't do much with it.
He also was in Follow That Bird, which is one of the first movies I saw on the theater.
It was a porno film, correct?
No.
But Candy's funny in that.
Summer rental.
These are all 1985.
That was kind of his first lead, a call, a random movie.
Summer rental to me has big laughs and then just death.
You know, like real shit.
Yeah.
It's, yeah.
It's rough.
But it's very worth seeing to me.
Volunteers with Tom Hanks, his now wife Rita Wilson and John Candy.
You know, there's a reason that nobody has seen a movie starring Tom Hanks and John Candy that's not splash.
It's not very good either.
It's got its moments, but not many of them.
I also remember never wanting to see a movie at that age where Tom Hanks was doing an English accent.
Is he English?
No.
He does like a weird accent.
Yeah.
I remember being like, that's not Tom Hanks.
No, that's all he does.
Yeah.
Armed and dangerous.
I think you like more than I, but I need to see it again.
I'm a big fan of Armed and Dangerous.
You got Levy.
You got Lojiya.
You got Ryan.
What else do you need?
Yeah, Meg Ryan.
I mean, this is...
I might watch Armed and Dangerous tonight because I don't, that was one as a kid.
As much as I loved him, it was, it didn't get a lot of repeat spins.
Then we got Little Shopper Horrors, Discuss last week.
Spaceballs.
I imagine you also like more than me, but I like it.
I'm a big fan.
And in the same year as Spaceballs, you got Planes Trends.
Like, that's kind of the thing though.
He's playing Mog in Spaceballs.
In the same year, he turns in one of the greatest comedic performances of all time in Planes Trends.
Like, the guy would just be like, sure.
If the money is right, I'll be there.
Well, I don't know if it's if the money was right.
I think, you know, well, he wasn't in Ghostbusters because of money.
I think he just kind of...
Well, well, lack of money, fine.
But I mean, my point is, Spaceballs is a funny movie.
And I get to play a dog.
That's funny.
Yes.
Fair enough.
Not that different from the character he plays than from Dale Griffith.
Mog.
Yeah, you're...
Planes Trends.
You know, we've discussed so much in the show.
There's no point.
But that is...
We did an episode about it.
That is the pinnacle for me of Candy's career.
Oh, no.
The pinnacle's coming up, baby.
Next year was Great Outdoors.
Which is also discussed.
Super funny.
Then, let's not forget he was the voice of the horse and hot to drop.
Forgettable, Miss Fire.
Maybe never saw a hot to drop.
Who's Harry Crumb?
There's the pinnacle, baby.
Now, you put...
Who's Harry Crumb above?
I love who's Harry Crumb.
Obviously, I know that Planes Trends and Automobiles is a 20 ,000 times better movie than who's Harry Crumb.
Yeah.
I just have such a soft spot for that goddamn movie.
I am angry that we didn't get a couple, Harry Crumb sequels.
That should have been the new pink Panther franchise.
It was supposed to be his...
It was supposed to be like his...
Austin Powers.
Yeah.
I think, you know, he had a little more creative involvement in that one and really wanted it to pop.
Didn't pop.
This one's gonna get ugly, boys.
Throwing the bow around his neck.
Speedzone is terrible.
It was like sort of the third cannibal run film.
Speedzone is unquestionably bad.
And then Uncle Buck.
Now, Uncle Buck, I remember everything about the day I saw Uncle Buck.
I begged my mom and begged and begged.
It was PG, so I knew I'd get to see it, but we didn't have a lot of money.
So we go to Uncle Buck at the AMC Regency 8 Cinema.
We play in the arcade beforehand.
We go in, and that movie starts off.
My parents were so strict with fucking movies.
And it starts off and McCulloch Holkins, like, your nails are digging into my arm.
God damn it.
My mom's like, what?
And it is insane the amount that those two kids cost at the beginning of Uncle Buck.
Right.
In a PG movie.
And I thought I was getting yanked out of there.
I started sweating.
I remember everything about it because I was like, I'm not gonna be able to see this.
I wanna die.
Why are you that white cussing?
Stop cussing.
Please.
Right.
And sure enough, I looked over my mom at the end of Uncle Buck.
She had tears in her eyes when the mom comes home.
You know, it's not as as moving as plans trans.
But the end of Uncle Buck is very sweet.
Let alone both movies end with a loving freeze frame of John Candy.
Yeah.
Which makes them even more...
It's a wonderful movie.
Poignant now.
Poignant?
Poignant.
It's a wonderful movie.
Now, after this, we're gonna start getting into some of the dark times.
Well, with a quick stop at a great time, home alone and one of the funniest cameos of the history.
Voice and the rescuers down under, which I saw opening day because John Candy was a voice.
I had never even seen the rescuers.
And now we hit nothing but trouble.
Which is the one most appropriate for this podcast.
I wanna watch it again.
No, you don't.
But I have seen nothing but trouble.
No fewer than ten times.
Yeah.
Because I loved everybody in it.
And I was just like...
It was kind of like taking a pill.
I didn't really want to swallow.
But there is something fascinating about that movie.
That ended all of their career.
Yes.
In one fell swoop.
Demi Moore.
Yeah.
Heavy Chase.
John Candy.
Dan Acroyd.
Just a three stooge's slap across their faces with one movie.
That is...
I've never seen anything like it in my life.
I've never seen anything.
And I wanted to see it because at that age I didn't have much interest in comedy anymore.
I was very into rap music and all I wanted to watch were like boys in the hood and stuff like that.
Yeah.
And I wanted to see it because digital underground was in the movie.
Right.
I couldn't wait to see digital underground into movie.
I was already a fan.
Tupac is in nothing but trouble.
Which is movie premiere.
Think about that people.
Tupac's introduction.
To the world.
It's in the movie.
Let's be real.
Nothing but trouble.
Yeah.
It makes no sense.
It truly doesn't.
The movie is off the rails.
It's ugly.
The characters are ugly.
It is horror really at times.
I remember being scared by it.
I am going to watch it again very soon because I need to know what I think as an adult man.
Very funny cameo in John Hughes written film called career opportunities.
Wait a minute.
We're already done.
I guess there's nothing much more to say about nothing but true.
What do we got to say?
It's candy and a dual role including a woman.
Yeah.
Woman in a cop.
And then Acroid playing twin like globs.
And also a judge with a dick nose.
Yes.
You know, like all the makeup is just disgusting.
Acroid.
Like, you know, that's a weird guy.
Let's just be real.
That movie came from his mind.
And everything he writes, like the original draft of Blues Brothers was supposed to be like 400 pages.
Original draft of Ghostbusters.
400 pages.
Like, he's not well.
But when you hone down his genius or param with a ramester somebody, he's great.
I look forward to seeing him play Ray again in the new Ghostbusters.
He makes crystal skull vodka.
You know, I look forward to seeing him be funny again.
I haven't seen him be funny a long time.
You really want to see him in that brown jump?
So you think that's going to be funny?
Remember his cameo in the new Ghostbusters?
The new Ghostbusters was shit.
And remember, what was his line?
It was like...
I ain't afraid no ghost.
Yeah.
It was terrible.
I am afraid of a ghost or something like that.
No, I like that.
I like, I think as Ray, he's always very funny and he will be funny in that case.
He's good in that type of, and drag, not of course.
To me, if I'm singling out one of his more underrated gems,
I got to talk about only the lonely.
Beautiful film.
Candy and Shiti, it's one of his rare, rare romantic movies.
He and Shiti are adorable together.
It's a Chris Columbus movie who, you know, before Harry Potter I think made a lot of great comedies.
He was a protégé of Hughes.
It's a beautiful film.
Only lonely is super entertaining.
Marina Hara is fantastic in it.
It's just a very sweet and at times fun.
And also Anthony Quinn.
Yes, exactly.
Yeah, that's a very sweet.
You could never get away with it now in a movie because everybody's a fucking asshole.
That's a very sweet dynamic that the two of them have through the whole movie,
where he hits on her, you know, like it's a little over the top the way he's hitting on her.
And then her, her retort to it is like, you're disgusting, you greek.
You know, and they have like that.
You talk about Quinnon over it.
Yeah, that weird, like sort of chauvinistic, ethnic rivalry kind of thing.
Yeah.
And then at the end, you realize he, he really is just a sweet guy.
And she actually does kind of feel charmed by it.
And they, they go in the house together.
It's, it's such a cute little.
It reminds me of like the way people like it a nursing home would get together or something.
Yeah, it's a, it's, it's got like a Marty vibe.
If you know the Ernie Borg nine picture, Marty was very inspired by Marty.
Yeah, Marty's one of my favorite love.
The following year, well, the same year.
Actually, in the same year, this is what candy.
I mean, this man worked.
Nothing but trouble, career opportunities, just a cameo.
Only the lonely, Delirious and JFK.
Also a cameo.
That's one year.
Delirious, in my opinion, is one of his funniest.
And people, people hate it, man.
I'm trashed.
I now own the Blu -ray of Delirious.
I have seen it once in 1991.
Watch that overall watch.
I'm watching it tonight.
I would.
And his pro, his cameo and JFK is fantastic as the sweaty New Orleans guy.
A little hammy, but it's very funny.
Yeah.
Funny.
Funny, funny.
It's, it's funny.
It's dark.
It's, it's, it's, it's, for me, it's a lighter moment in JFK.
Oh, I don't find it funny.
Just him and the white suit and sweating.
To me makes me laugh.
But he's great in the park.
Yeah.
I like it in the park.
The accent's a little heavy.
Yeah.
Once upon a crime is terrible.
Terrible.
Richard Lewis in them.
Rookie of the year.
He's funny as the announcer.
Cool runnings.
Look, I loved it just as much as you did when I was a kid.
I tried 15 minutes the other night.
Bailed.
But maybe I'll get through it.
Wagon Z.
Star remember just being just depressed.
Yeah.
And Canadian bacon.
I was like, come on, man.
So he ended in a bad spot.
Canadian bacon is far more passable than Wagon's East.
But Wagon's East is just terrible.
I strangely, right?
His, he died during the filming of Wagon's East.
Yeah.
Strangely, Farley's last movie.
Almost here.
Almost heroes.
Same exact thing.
Yeah.
Like, Prissy Frontierman needs a rugged drunk wild outdoorsman to show him how to make this
trick.
Yeah.
And directed by Christopher Guest, weirdly almost heroes.
But who directed East?
Wagon's East.
I don't, I could look it up.
Yeah.
Maybe there was something to that.
Like, they both, they were either so far away from home that it made them just constantly start smoking and drinking.
Or just being outside and doing physical activities was bad on the heart.
I don't know.
But there is something odd that both those movies followed that trajectory.
Do you, I know a few people who work around the clock who don't have some sort of addiction they feed into.
Yeah.
It's not always, you know, the cliché is cocaine.
But it's not always that, it's like, dude, when you, when you work that much and you're that much out of your house
and you have to keep going and going and going and it's essentially starts to become all work in no play.
You start to pull play into work.
Yeah.
Because you're like, I got to just get through this, dude.
Like, you know, like this is a lot right now and I'm going to freak the fuck out.
You know, I never think it's weird when I go into somebody's office and they have a little bar set up.
I got a little bar set up.
I'm not going to lie.
Yeah, it's, it's tricky to not go to it all the time.
But yeah, it's candy apparently had a big weed thing, loved weed.
Remember hearing a story about how we baked a Thanksgiving turkey with weed or something like that and brought it to a potluck.
Jesus Christ.
What?
Pat, you were the worst at taking a symbol.
I was pointing at the clock like I have to go.
Oh, okay.
Which was supposed to be silent.
That's why I didn't say pat I have to go.
I mean, I don't know what's stopping you from saying I have to go because I didn't want to because when I say that on the pod, you go,
let's go back and cut that out.
And I was just trying.
I was just trying to give you a thing like, hey, dude, I got to go.
We got to give me the red light, you know.
Pat, what?
Worst guy to have you get caught cheating on your wife.
Why isn't with another woman?
Yeah.
We love John candy that little walk through his career was fun.
I'm sure there's a lot of movies of his, especially for the younger people that you just don't know.
And they're all readily available.
Yes.
The man could truly polish a turd.
Like, and bad shit, he's funny.
In good shit, he's funny.
In great shit, he's the best there was.
I mean, I love the man.
25th anniversary of his passing.
His memory lives on for us all.
Yes.
Well said, Patrick.
Joe DeRosa comedy on Instagram.
This end of this month, March 29th, the 30th.
I am at the top golf casino, or we're building a resort, whatever the hell it's called.
Doing bonkers presents comedy there.
Two shows, one each night.
I will also have a new story in Penthouse this month for the March April issue.
It is called Menu Change.
It's a fun little spooky kind of ditty.
And April dates coming up.
I have got dates in, I believe, Minnesota, Minneapolis, Minnesota, Pennsylvania, Austin, Texas.
And I think that's it for April, but details to come on that.
The Patrick Walsh Twitter and Instagram.
Cool kids on Hulu and Fox Friday night.
Folks, we will see you next time.
And we will see you.
And now.
A podcast network.