Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as an almost durable site credit slash bonus bet unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning, or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 -plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gampler, offer not available in all states
terms apply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
Joe, I just found an article here on Facebook that I thought you'd particularly enjoy.
Its title is, This Gen Xer's heartwarming advice to millennials has Twitter users in tears.
And who's the Gen Xer?
I don't know, Joe.
I just thought that sounded like something you might want to read and it might warm your
heart.
Well, Pat, it took everything I had in me to not spit on you as you were saying the title.
so yeah now friend of mine shared it I mean I say let's just get on with the show no I say let's
Let's get on with the show.
and don't, with Joe, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho,
Pat and I had a lovely day today so far we started it off at the cheese cake factory a couple stiff
skinny cocktails over there. I had the red sangria joe the long island iced tea yeah like a woman
looking for a man 14 years her junior to take her out to his Toyota Prius maybe go up to the seventh floor
the parking garage where no one else is and orally pleasure her in a little game. I like to call
how Joey got his groove back. Yeah. Then we went to see Alien Covenant, the subject of today's
episode. I thought it was Covenant of ants. I read that wrong and that's I think that's why I was
let down. How long have you been sitting on that? I was expecting, you know, ants around a cauldron
stirring and how long have you been sitting on that beyond it? It just came to me. Bullshit. Covenant.
out of it. It's not a good joke, Joy. I didn't put a lot of time in it. Uh, we also then after
went to Shake Shack, Pat got some sort of a, if you see a faded sign at the side of the road
that says 15 miles to the Shake Shack. That's right. That's right. So it was good. Oh, the lady last
night she was telling me that she was at a bar recently with Fred Durst and I, oh, I got it, I got
it mixed up. I thought she meant the guy from the B -52s. Oh, Fred Schneider. I was like,
what were you doing with that guy? What was she doing with Fred Durst? Uh, she was somebody
she always works with him or something. I forgot. Works with him. Something like that.
Stay farm insurance. Stop it. Be nice. Now to Fred Durst. I saw Fred Durst the other day
at Coral's Jr. He gave me an extra pack of fries. So that was cool. Yeah, right? That's
Did I ever see the first joke I ever wrote?
Probably.
These were the first two jokes I ever wrote in stand -up ever ready.
I was out in LA recently.
I saw Danny Glover in a Denny's and after he took my order,
I told him how much I liked that last lethal weapon film.
That was the first joke I ever wrote.
And the second one was terrible.
The second one I wrote was I caught my parents having sex again.
I would do I put a pause before the again and I go
Never gets less embarrassing. They're mortified. I caught them. I'm a shame because they can see my erection
That was the second joke I wrote. It's good. Yeah, it's it's cheap stuff, but it works good. I don't mind cheap
I know
Anyway, folks, what's going on
And as we told you the show's picked up,
I was in New York this week for the upfronts,
where they announced their upcoming schedules.
It's exciting.
I met the president of CBS, I pumped the hands,
I shook the babies, and then I came home.
It's fun.
Did you kiss anything?
No, I didn't.
You should have kissed something.
I should have.
Nobody was interested.
All right, fair enough.
Joe, what's been going on with you?
Not really a lot, Pat, I've sort of been living vicariously through your show pickup.
Right.
I've been telling people around town that it's my show.
Well, technically that's true.
So look, what is going on?
I don't know.
I started writing a column for a magazine and it's official and it's happening and it'll
be monthly.
I'm not allowed to talk about it yet because the ink ain't dry.
But but I wrote my first column. So I'm excited to be doing that a humorous opinions column. All right
and I
Been out in a date
Good
That was nice
Had a friend in town Wednesday when you were gone
He and I had a great time good tore up the town
Good with our pals Vince and Georgia and Jesse pop sure
It's about it Pat twin peaks starts tonight. I got the showtime add -on so I can watch it
I'm really excited. I mean, I think the reason I'm so excited is because
It's not trying to match something amazing. It's trying to match something that was briefly amazing then nearly unwatchable and
I think we're gonna get probably something
in between. I read the spoiler free reviews. Okay. And they all said they all gave it a claim.
They said this new show will entice in rage, mystifying whatever Twin Peaks fans, which is what
TV needs right now. True. They said it is not an nostalgia run at all. It feels way more like
Lynch like celebrating like his what he does best. Yeah, and he's sort of back with a pallet where he's allowed to create and have fun
But yeah, everybody said it's great and it's dark and it's weird
Right one critic said there is something in the first
Episode or the second episode that is quote the scariest thing he had ever seen on television
All right, I love that. I mean, I don't put it past Lynch
I know he's capable of it. I love it. I love it your friend
I love it. I remember that from swimming in raw sewage. I love it. The star of my
show and yours, Joe, is our mutual shared love friend, J .R. Ferguson. J .R.
Ferg and he will be appearing in the Twin Peaks reboot. Do you know how big
as part is in it? He said he only saw his pages. He had no idea how he relates to
anything. He's not allowed to talk about it. That's often what it's like when I do
you saw, they should have flying me in in the dead of night.
And the helicopter better called soul.
Yeah, they, you thought we'd all know soul.
Well, what other show has never had the word soul?
Johnny Carson.
I had a friend in college that would do that.
He would, he would talk about like actors he liked,
but he'd only refer to them by their last names.
Sure.
So he'd be like, he'd be like, that's the great thing about Mathau.
Mathau knows how to, you know, and you'd be like,
stop you don't know him you do you're a theater minor at a state school bobby
deniro anyway I was just making a joke about how secretive it always is right I
do better also and I was painting a picture and then you cut it off but that's
fine I mean I well you it's not like you said Saul like you were in the
Saul franchise oh Saul yeah but I know now that you meant
Saul better call Saul okay anyway I was just saying they forget it it's very
You got anything for the movie round up?
Yeah.
For once I did watch a few movies on the aeroplane at a first class seat for the first time
in my life.
It was very exciting.
I got this five star service, you know, they pick you up at the gate.
I got driven to the airport, they pick you up at the curb.
Some lady walks you past security.
Huge bar, but when I say open bar, I mean, all the bottles are just there with glasses and
ice and garnishes and mixers.
So it's just like, help yourself.
It's just like your own home bar.
It was amazing.
Layed down.
I love it.
So anyway, on the plane between two and there, I watched three movies, which was more than
I've watched in months and here I watched the founder starring Michael Keaton about Roy
Croc.
That's the movie I watched.
I'll be damned.
Yeah.
Did you like it?
I loved it.
I loved it myself.
It moved at its own pace.
It was a little slow at times.
It was very dark.
I loved it.
Gave me tremendous guilt about eating at McDonald's ever again.
Yeah, well luckily I haven't in a decade, but it's, uh, I don't know how they authorized
it.
Really?
I guess it's just a true story.
They can do whatever they want but I was at a McDonald's two days later. Yeah, that was about as long as I could wait
But Roy Crox, you know, basically steals these two sweet brothers had the McDonald's franchise their vision
The the arches the whole system of making food everything was theirs
Roy Crox slid in and just completely bent them over the grill and but fucked them
And at first it seems like he means well
He's trying to just help these guys build this franchise or this this this uh
this, I was gonna say metropolis, that's the wrong word,
but this, you know, this iconic, yeah, whatever,
but then by the end he goes dirty,
here's the spoiler alert,
and this is the part I was on Doug Love's movies last week
and we talked about the founder,
and this is the part in the movie that I found hilarious,
where you're like, because everybody,
when you say, I saw the founder,
I feel guilty about eating McDonald's,
Somebody will inevitably go, well, I mean,
is it that bad or did he just kind of like,
make more money than he should have?
And it's like, no, no, no, no.
That's how you feel the whole time until,
at the end of the movie, he makes a handshake deal
with the McDonald brothers.
I couldn't believe this shook it.
Yeah, that's kind of on them.
That they'll get 1 % of profits for the rest of time.
Yeah.
Then it shows the original McDonald's
that they opened their dream, their life, everything,
they have to change the name of it.
They're not allowed to call it McDonald's anymore.
So they change the name of it to Ames,
which is a real slap in the face.
And then their name, not Roy Croxman.
Then Croc opens a McDonald's directly
across the street from it, puts it out of business.
That was insane.
And then never gives them the 1 % profits.
It's no, they each get a check for like a million dollars
for to cover all their expenses for giving up McDonald's.
And then at the end of the movie, it's like they should have made
100 million dollars per year.
And then the last slap in the face is it says that when Roy Croc died,
his wife gave their entire fortune to charity.
Yeah. Well, we give some of it back to the family.
Yeah.
Jesus!
Then he's Laura Dern is one of my favorite actresses she had very little to do in it but she's
supportive of him the entire time you know all through his crack pot schemes and dreams
she's right by his side and he starts making money throwing food in his mouth that she made
a dinner and he goes hey I buy one of the vores yeah yeah crazy but he does go after one of my favorite
ladies on earth. Who's that? Uh, the woman that he dumps his wife for is the girl from
Patrick Wilson's wife, right? She's a girl from Freaks and Geeks. She was a cartilain.
Bloodline. Linda Cartilain. Yeah. She's not married to Patrick Wilson. She's great. And the reason
in the movie she was. Oh, in the movie she was. Yeah. She played Thelma in the Scooby -Doo film. Yeah.
I actually, I kept thinking, she looks so familiar. Who is she? Who is she? That is of course,
who it is. But I've never seen her with blonde hair. So I was confused. It was clearly a wig she was
wearing. Right. So it look, it's like any other biopic, it has those moments where like, you know,
I like the, the opening scenes is like him trying to sell milkshake machines to drive through
burger joints. And you know, they, they really go out of their way to show him multiple times waiting
for his food. Like, come on. Yeah. Why is it taking so long? Yeah. Very often they would,
I've seen that could have been 20 seconds would have been four minutes, right?
They did that a lot at the beginning of the movie. That's fine. I liked it. I liked it too.
Uh, I saw why him. Oh, God.
Sorry, Brian Kranson and James Franco. Two actors I like. I like the both two and I like
Malalee and I like Keegan Michael Key. Mm -hmm. And I like Cedric, the entertainer. I mean,
the cast is all really funny. You're saying all the right names?
so they keep it barely afloat if I wasn't on a plane I don't know if I would have
finished it but like it they keep the balls in the air just long enough you're
like that was all right you know it's if you watch it on cable you wouldn't
hate yourself there's a couple of chuckles fair enough I also watched office
Christmas party. Why do you do this to yourself? I'm on a plane, Joe. Yeah, but you have other options.
Well, I hadn't watched a movie. These were the movies I hadn't seen.
All right, tell me about office Christmas party. Office Christmas party. By the way, if I can just interject.
Laziest, you know, I like to bring this up a lot. Laziest movie title of all time. Yeah, I agree.
It's up there with hotel for dogs and as we discuss the other day, a hologram for the king.
Well, that's that's not a lazy title. That's the worst title ever. That's why that movie made no money
Anyway, by the way you were right because I we brought up a hologram or the reason we were talking about a hologram for the king is
We were coming out of the movie theater and I said do you think that new Tom Hanks the circle movie is gonna be any good?
Pat said no fucking way and I he goes to see that last one and we started talking about a hologram for the king
So then a week later I went on rotten tomatoes to see 13 % oh god, and it's got Emma. What's her face in it?
It's got Tom Hanks in it.
Tom Hanks, but it's got the Harry Potter girl
who's like all the rage.
It's like, how was it possible that she's in a 13 % move?
I don't even understand.
Okay, Tom Hanks is doing it.
I'll do it.
Anyway, go ahead.
So office crystal party is exactly what you'd expect.
It's an office crystal party that gets a little out of hand.
Much in the same way of why him, I would say,
on an almost no plot, it keeps things moving okay.
Okay, and all the laughs come from the guest stars, like Fortune Feemster has a really funny
bit in the car.
You know, stuff like that is funny.
There's funny little bits, but, you know, on the whole, you could take or leave it.
That's when a great comedy and forever, you know.
This, this, this new one coming out, and I'm sorry, I know it's an all ladies thing.
This is not sexism talking.
This is, this is me saying I'm to do something different.
That fucking movie coming out with Scarlett Johansson.
Oh, see that one might be funny.
It's from the Broad City people.
Stop it.
From the Broad City people.
It's this, it's another movie about a Bachelorette party
that goes wild.
Yes.
They had two, literally two of those, two years ago.
There were two of those movies.
Yeah.
So now here's a third one.
Well, this one is very bad things.
I don't know how they get away with not paying them to remake very bad things.
They murder somebody. They kill the male stripper, yeah, by accident.
And it's not a remake of very bad things. That's what I'm saying to you.
Yes. I don't understand. Very bad things depresses me too much. I can't take it.
It's a dark film. Yeah, Cameron Diaz is turned. I think everybody sees that maybe their friends could do
have something like that take place. She should have got her an Oscar for that movie.
She's great in it. Yeah, I haven't seen her in a movie in five years. She all right, Cammy. Cammy
You know Cammy's around all right. I see her down the dog park and okay, you know, we we swap recipes and things
I'm sure sure she lost them
What is that skirt with your answer movie? It's called like shit show or something. It's already changed the name a couple times
It's called like hot mess or something like that. Yeah, or something night wild night or something. I don't know shame night
yeah walk of shame night oh good night shame long it looks terrible anyway what
else is up we're talking today that's all I've seen do you see anything other
than the founder no but I feel like now I need to make fun of equally a male
movie that I think looks stupid well I am about to but the trailers we fucking
saw today about the dog of Val that was a female lead film what what else do we
She got to watch this fucking trailer.
It's about a woman who's alive is saved by a dog in Afghanistan.
She is like running and crying
in every scene of this movie.
Like, he saved my life about a dog.
There's like choppers going overhead.
It's like the president is pounding on his desk
and it's all about a dog.
Yeah, she like somehow gets the right
to adopt a military dog
and like she's changed the course of history or something.
Yeah, it's like you know, there was a guy that has no legs, right? Yeah, not to mention it's a German Shepherd. Not even an American Shepherd.
I did watch the new nor McDonald's special. I loved it. I saw it live and I saw it on Netflix. I liked it
I liked the last one better, but it had some very funny moments.
What other stupid movie trailers did we see today?
We saw what was the what was the really bad guy to tell you man. I'm a fan of the guy, but would he
Arrelson is pulling me out of the planet of the apes. He's pulling me out. It's I always like him
He's not right for this part. It will be a planet of apes. It sounds ridiculous
It really does and I had heard recently that he stopped smoking weed and I wonder if his acting isn't gonna suffer because of it
It sounds big and I'm sorry. I don't understand. I what is the difference between this planet of the apes and the last one the last one was the big battle
for dominance, and now it's another battle
for the planet of the apes.
Well, they are.
That's, they're always gonna be battles
for the planet of the apes.
The, the original ones aren't here.
Watch that original five film.
I've only seen the first planet of the apes,
and then I saw Burton's.
Oh, well, dude.
And I saw the remakes.
Do yourself a favor.
I own them.
I've never seen them.
Watch beneath.
That's gonna fuck your world up.
You know, that, that goes in a direction
that you have no clue.
All right.
I'm intrigued.
It's it didn't I don't know it looks okay. I'll go see it
It looks more like here here. We go and this is this is good ready. Yeah, it looks more like like some more dumb man shit
Yeah, so there you go, and I'm not just saying that to balance the scales
It looks more like man. How many more fucking like macho trailers are they gonna have where it goes?
Where they'll where they do this trick at the end? I
Didn't come here to start this
Yeah, silence black screen, but I will end it. Yeah title. May. Yeah,
timpani drums boom, boom, boom, boom. How many times are gonna do that? It's stupid.
Of course, of course it is stupid. The other trailer today, it starts up. Looks kind
of cool. There's like a kind of well -written narration and then it's Anthony
Hopkins oh god like since the door of time
We've dealt with the robots. I'm like the robots. What are we and I realize it's another fucking Transformers movie
Markey mark do it in that one too at the end. Yeah, they did Optimus Prime goes for my world to survive. Yeah
Yours must end boom boom boom boom boom boom
Transformers the last night Anthony Hopkins will do anything really will and I thought he had retired from acting
But apparently not yeah, at one point marky mark is running and he's like
Just like hold steady optimists
I was like how do you how do you look in the mirror in the in the greatest in the greatest
Suspension of disbelief of all time. Yeah, or expectation of a suspension of disbelief marky mark
Mark, Mark Wahlberg ladies and gentlemen,
if you didn't see the last Transformers movie,
was cast as a robotics expert.
Well, he was a fucking scientist
in that Shyamalan one, and he's even worse than that.
Yeah.
And he's, he's, he's like, it's a Transformer.
It's a Transformer, I know robots, it's a Transformer.
He sounds like a fucking idiot.
And I like, I can't like, Marky, Mark, I guess,
I don't know, maybe I don't like it.
I can't like it.
In comedies, I tend to like,
But we're burying the lead here because transformers
Five or six or whatever the fuck it is takes place in nights days
The days of nights some of it does what's called what circle of nights. It's called the last night
I mean
It didn't learn your lesson from Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles 3 when they went back into samurai times
Why are they going back in time?
Transformers can't time travel.
Because I don't think they're time traveling.
I think they're showing the existence of the transformers
here through many centuries.
Oh, blow me.
And talk about more of the same bullshit.
They got five kids running around on the thing
and you're like, oh, so clearly you've shoehorned
in a stranger things plot now.
Oh, for God's sake, everything is shaking.
You know what people seem to be liking?
Strange things.
Everything is shit. Can we never have a stranger thing's cat in the new transformers?
And and then they have that that lady in it who's like the hottest woman on earth, but she's a scientist. Yeah
Can you put some believable looking people in this please?
Mark Wahlberg and this fucking
runway model or the scientists in this film. Yeah, give me a fucking break. Denise Richards played a
nuclear physicist in that one James Bond movie
What film was that the world I think the world is not enough
And then at the end she wants to have sex with her her name was like Jenny Christmas or something at the end
He's about to have sex with her and he goes. I thought Chris. I only came once a year. Oh, last line of the movie
Cradits. There's a there's a franchise where if they never made another one I wouldn't notice. I'm never excited
They've ever a couple of I mean one or two of the crags were cool
What two of the other crags were cool the others just sucked every other one
Did I just I don't care? It's not my thing. You know he's gonna live
Yeah, he's gonna live and it's it's it's just actually never quite good enough the plots never quite good enough the characters aren't good enough
But you guys keep going back to pursue the the the one where Sean Connery comes back. Yeah, never say never again
And it's Rowan Atkinson's film debut and they have him in there as like a bumbling comedic detective
Really? Yeah, and he's like running through a market and he's going, Mr. Bond, Mr. Bond
And then he finally comes up and he goes, I've been sent here discreetly to and he goes discreetly
So I got my name through it like it's like literally supposed to be like this bumbling. Yeah, I see this thing. It's ridiculous
What was the other there was one other to preview after the the army dog one that looked somehow
even worse. Oh, it was the the shark movie with Mandy Moore. Oh, boy. It's like a neon shot
shark movie starring Mandy Moore. How many fucking movies are they going to make about
somebody being threatened by a shark and they can't get up. They did god damn. They did
god damn. Oh, jaws. Then they did deep water. Jaws up through four. They did the shallows.
The shit, and what's the one with the Blake, Blake lively in it?
Is that the shallows?
Yeah, this one, the twist on this one is they're trapped in the cage under the water.
Yeah, but why do you go into an underwater cage and shark -infested waters, you idiot?
People do that to, to shark -watch.
Well, don't do it.
It's just, there's a tip.
It's just stupid.
The cord breaks and then the tank, the cage sinks.
Yeah.
It's just dumb.
And it's not, the point of this gun on my head and pull the trigger and then I want to back
like killing myself. It's also not accurate. A shark wouldn't just hang around. No, like it's not
that's not the way it works. No, it's just fucking stupid. It's just stupid. That movie looks terrible.
It did.
Let's get out with the movie of the day, it's a little picture called Alien, Coven
of Ants, made by Ridley Scott who was pushing 80 years of age, he can't, I mean the man
puts together a great looking movie every time, he's got a style, it was very well -paid
Very like tonally cool, you know, it's a very similar style to Prometheus
But at the end of the day I really like the score
But I mean I got to tell you folks. I'm noticing the score on a first viewing it means the movie's probably not working
But it had a great score. It's boring as fuck for a full hour
boring as fuck. I fell asleep. Thank you. And
Then once the action kicks in there's a few good kills, but it really is just straight up
almost like a Friday the 13th you know it's just kind of one after the
other the alien has a new design that is not really an improvement over the
other it's like a white tiny alien that's almost so small you're not scared of
it. Well at first this is gonna be very spoiler heavy. That's fine. I'll say this
and by the way we should give a little synopsis. This is the sequel to
Prometheus, it takes place 10 years after Prometheus, it's about what happened to the ship
in Prometheus, it's about this other crew discovering that ship, and then the birth
of the alien as we know it.
That's basically it.
So here's the thing.
You people already know how I feel about the alien franchise.
I think there is one good movie in the alien franchise, stupid, and that's alien one.
I think two is a passable is a passable fun action movie, but that's about it one of the best action movies ever made
And maybe the best action movie and I think that this movie falls in that same tradition
It's not it's not scary. It's not horror. It's an action movie
It's a it's a fucking shoot them up and it's boring because if you're gonna do that
There's got to at least to be suspense and there was never in my opinion a minute of suspense
I thought Danny McBride was terrific. I thought the lead female actor was terrific. I don't know, but I didn't like I liked her quite a bit
I thought everybody else in the movie was you know Billy Cretup was fine
I thought Michael fastbender was good. Yeah, although he was he's just doing like a spock impression
Yeah, that is a magical hell from a two one thousand not not to you know 2001
How many shots though were there and I'm messing I'm betting it was
was 50, where a character would be in the foreground
and the alien appears in the background.
They did it again and again and again and again.
And then sometimes it wouldn't be the alien
to be a guy with a gun.
But then most of the time, it'd be an alien.
I'll tell you my biggest gripe with the goddamn movie.
All right.
Too much CGI.
Why was the fucking alien CGI in every scene?
Yeah.
That was the big, that was the big question.
It was worse than it did in 1979, you know?
That was the big criticism when alien resurrection came out.
People were like, I don't like how the aliens are CGI.
I know it doesn't look as cool right and then in this every single shot of the alien was fake every single shot
It didn't have any the texture any the weight my dear friend my courier and avid listener of the podcast sent me a picture reminding me of the the
Burned like copper alien face skull at the end of three one of the worst effects ever in a big budget movie
Well, that's cuz three sucks three sucks. I mean let's lay it out
But I go to one, it's just a stupid statement, but you know, I think with ease, I go to one.
It's not close.
You with what?
And it's not close, you're an idiot.
I go to one, three, Prometheus, Covenant, I guess, Resurrection, and then at the very end
of your alien versus predators.
I'll tell you this.
I'll take the alien versus predators over over Prometheus. I'll take them over alien covenant
Because at least you got real animatronic effects and stuff like that and at least I don't know
Like do those are just their video games there. They truly have nothing to them
I thought this was sort of a video game and by the way, why is the fucking alien franchise
About a goddamn robot manipulating everybody. Yeah, I don't know what like
Like, I think there's an interesting element to the fact that this artificial intelligent
life that was created by man is now destroying man with the creation of the aliens.
Like he is playing God, something artificially intelligent could in theory be like God where
it never dies, it never ages, or whatever.
But I mean, the David robot from the first film comes out, when you first meet him in this
thing, he's got a long hair.
Why does a robot have a long hair?
Yeah, and then cuts it. Well, I guess yeah, do they grow it out robots have growing it doesn't make any goddamn sense to me
Well, I mean, I guess you could program anything with a robot. So then but then that means it can age. I
Don't know. I'll tell you what I what I didn't need was
Seven -minute scene of fast -bender
Teaching another fast -bender how to play the flute
I was like what the fuck am I watching a lot of flute a lot of
Flu business in this film that they also kiss on the lips at one point, which I don't I that was a big
It was very clear that Ridley Scott was like well, we'll we'll blow their minds mate with how we have fast bend to do things to fast
Bend, uh, yeah, I know that's not what he truly sounds like but in my head that's how he's not the Rocket Islander
RIP. And also RIP, Mr. Chris Cornell, if I may, just one of the greatest voices of my
or any other generation. And it's a damn shame. And folks, if you're feeling down, if you're
feeling depressed or feeling sad, get help. Talk to a friend. It was all the dead at age
52. It's crazy. It was all the suicide is wife. It was all the suicide. That's why I'm saying
this. Can I say this? Every time a guy hangs himself, people go, I mean, you said this
too. I said, was he jacking up? You said, well, I hope not. Yeah. See, that's always
the notion when somebody hangs it. People think, because you'll hear people make, you
know, they'll talk about this. Let's say if you catch a guy jerking off and he died hanging
because he was trying to choke himself, you got to clean it up and make it look like he just
hung himself. I see you go the other way. You find a guy just hung himself, make it look
like he was jerking off and he died by accident. He'd come on the floor. He was just, he was having
fun. He was in a good place. He just had something bad happened. Now, what happens if they see
the come on the floor and then when they're doing the autopsy they test the come and realize
it was your problem.
Well, the problem is that they're going to think you were fucking him and hung him.
The problem is is when the when the when the detective comes in and dips his pan in the
semen and then tastes it as they always do and then and then knows it's not the guys come.
Yeah.
But I mean, maybe he didn't come yet.
Maybe he just choked himself before.
Maybe he just has a soft.
I know.
I mean, the truth is, if I were going to hang myself and I won't, why not go for the
orgasm to round it out?
I'll tell you right now, if I ever kill myself, that's how I'm going to go out as just one
last fuck you to the world.
Clean this up, you pigs.
Thanks for nothing.
Well, this got away from us, but I love Chris Cornell and I wish him and his family the best.
I do too. That's a bummer. Well, just a hell of a singer hell of a singer and songwriter
I think the down on the upside album is a masterpiece. It's my favorite of theirs and my favorite song of theirs
I believe blow up the outside world my favorite song is still a pretty noose pretty noose is awesome. It's a great tune
I love Thai cop
Yeah quick little punk number. What's this what's track two on that album the one that starts where he goes
That's almost like there's like zeppelin album or something. Yeah, yeah, that's my favorite of those. It's a great record. 16 tracks. I kind of want to get that on vinyl. I have it on vinyl. Yeah, sounds great. It's worth the squeeze. Yeah. All right. Fair enough. Anyway, back to Prometheus. Now what we have now in the Alien franchise. I mean, sorry, Alien Covenant. What we have now in the Alien franchise is in my opinion, one very well well made film, one fairly fun film. And then
and even Ridley Scott, and this is my problem with it.
Even Ridley Scott now, himself is mimicking Cameron's aliens
and not his original thing.
And I don't understand why everybody is,
there was no threat in this film.
I never once felt scared about the alien.
No, that's true.
I never once felt that it would,
it also, they also were breaking a lot of like logic rules
were like the face hugger jumped on. Again, guys, this is a lot of spoilers. The
face hugger jumps on, Billy crud up and immediately he births the alien from
his stomach. Yeah. It jumps on the other guy and that guy, it's it's it's 10
fucking hours later that the alien comes out. The guys in the beginning get the
spores up their nose and then immediately these white pseudo aliens jump out of them and it's like
it just was like I just kind of didn't get it like it didn't it didn't make a lot of I know it's
a fake movie it's crazy fiction but there's got to be some logic to it and it didn't make logical
sense to me. I agree and there's something I just checked here it made 36 million dollars this weekend
which is bad. Probably cost 140 or something. I think people are kind of not that end
aliens. The new Independence Day bomb, they're over it I think. I don't know what
they're looking for, but it's not aliens anymore. There's also too much going on.
Yeah. Why is there in Prometheus? Why does it have to be that there's... I hate
it Prometheus because it's an aliens movie with no aliens in the fucking thing.
Right, but I like that it was some different. I like it. I don't mind that it was
something different and I think Ridley Scott was trying to be artistic and say like I want to do
something different that will serve as sort of a prequel to Alien right and then when everybody went
to put there were no aliens and I didn't I didn't like this then all of a sudden it's like oh we're
jumping back in this one's called Alien Covenant and there's gonna be aliens anyway what's your favorite
Ridley Scott joint I've never been passionate about a Ridley Scott joint I must say what's my favorite
You know, I know he's a good director. I've never been like my favorite movie by him is hands -down matchtick man
I do love matchtick man. I love it. Yeah, I love it Sam Rockwell at his finest Nicholas Cage at his finest. Yeah, that was a great move
and
I've ever Tony Scott is easily true romance. What's her name is wonderful in it? Well, no, my favorite
Rapids are her movie as alien.
I might like magic men better than alien.
Holy shit.
What you talk about alien is if it's an all -time masterpiece.
I think alien is a wonderful film.
I'm just saying based on like,
what do I feel like watching more frequently?
Because it's probably because it's lighter
I'll throw magic men on.
No, maybe I like.
What's her name?
The girl that was in my friend Flicka.
The girl, Alison Loman.
and she's wonderful in that film.
What happened to her?
Where's she been?
She looked too much like so many other actresses,
I think was her problem.
There was a time in the early 2000s
where it was all these blonde girls
who looked identical to each other.
She wasn't blonde though, she's Brunette.
Alison Lohman?
Yeah, she's blonde a matchtick man.
No, she changes her hair because it turns out
that she's not, she's posing as a 14 -year -old
and then she comes back.
She's like 25.
I got you.
Spoiler alert on that one.
Yeah, I don't know. I don't really have much more of an appetite for this franchise.
There was never a point where I was really excited about seeing this, but then again, I'm not
excited about much that's coming out, to be honest. It's pretty dismal. Things are bad.
I'm excited for Wonder Woman. Not cool. I might not see it. It certainly won't see the fucking
pirates of the Caribbean. It's getting... I want to do pirates for this podcast.
Oh, I'll do that, but it's gonna be three hours.
The last one was three hours.
I didn't like the last one.
It was one of the worst ones I've ever seen.
Haviar Bardam's in this one.
And I thought the trailer was the last one.
No, he's the new bad guy.
I thought the trailer looked great.
I didn't care, then I watched the trailer
and I was like, you know what,
that's really a good trailer.
I think this looks good.
I actually don't think I'll see it.
If it's longer than two hours, I won't see it.
How did you know like the first one?
The first one is the best, but I was still bored by it. I don't like pirates. It's fucking stupid. Alright, fair enough. Stay on a boat, take a vacation, don't mess other people's good time up.
Nothing. I'm excited for Wonder Woman, good early reviews on that. I'm actually not going to see Wonder Woman.
Alright, well, listen. I'm excited for Justice League.
I'm excited for the last Jedi.
Yeah, I'll see that so those are three
Some like putty right now. Yeah, I'll see that
Feels like an Arby's night
The hardest I ever laughed in my life was feels like an Arby's night when she asked him where he wants to go to dinner
I fell off my couch. I was like rolling on the floor. I missed the whole end of the episode
It just took me by surprise. That's the that's my favorite episode
That's the one where he's got the religious stations on his yeah, and his radio. That's the burning. Yeah
Yeah, that's a that's a magnificent episode feels like an Arby's night. Yeah, that's the
episode with that's it for me. Yeah, I'm done. Yeah, it's so great. Uh, what was I going
to say? When else is coming out this year? I don't know, but see, don't isn't it sad
to you that everything you're mentioning is like the 18th sequel to something? Look, you ain't
never going to or ain't never going to see me be sad about a new Star Wars sequel. I know.
But what's there's never been a Wonder Woman movie there was a Wonder Woman TV show that was the same old shit
It's not the same old shit. It fucking is there's actually a movie coming out called so -and -so in the Wonder Woman
That's about the guy that created Wonder Woman, okay, and and
What's her face is in it
The lady that was
God damn, what is wrong with my brain today?
The, she's in the prestige.
She plays Christian Bale's wife in the prestige.
Rachel Voss.
No, no.
She was in Christine.
She was just in that movie.
You're mad at me for not knowing what the hell you're talking about.
We're back a English actor.
We're back a whole, right?
We're back a whole, isn't it?
Yeah, and I, so I'd like to see it,
because I like her work quite a bit.
All right, well I was Christine, I didn't see that.
I want to see it.
I haven't seen it, I heard it's phenomenal.
Do you know what it's about?
Yes, I do.
It was on the plan as well, and I wanted to watch it,
but I was already in a bad mood.
I found the actual clip of the lady
that shot herself on the air.
Oh, that's nice.
And it's not great.
Like a face of death.
It's just really grainy, like, and, but yeah,
it's that's who she plays in the movie.
Is that lady?
Well, check it out, Joe.
Yeah, but there's not much coming out this year. I agree.
No, maybe maybe something's waiting down the pike. I don't know, but folks, thanks for
tuning in.
Well, geez, what do you know? What do you just call in the shots over here?
We've got to get somewhere at four.
So I know, but it's how long have we been doing? 43 minutes, so yeah, let's keep it all right.
Do you have anything for Joe's scary stuff?
Not a goddamn thing.
All right.
It's been a slow week.
I don't know why I just can't think of what happened this week
All right, well gang gang thanks for coming out again
You know, I just something to put on your radar this probably won't be next week
But it'll be soon we saw trailer today for the new Kingsman and I turned my friend Joe here
I said, oh I'm excited about that the first one was fucking awesome and Joe because I've never seen it
So maybe that'll be one that comes up
Well, maybe Joe and I will watch that.
But does it fall into fantasy sci -fi?
It absolutely does.
Okay, all right.
The Kingsman in the Queen's Secret Service.
Yeah, you know what?
Actually, it's probably better for us to pair them.
So maybe we'll do Kingsman one and two.
But you know, if you haven't seen that,
those movies check them out.
I like Colin Firth, quite a bit.
Yeah, I'm down with Firth.
Yeah.
You know, this new one's got Channing Tatum.
Yeah, it does.
Yep.
I always say about Channing Tatum, both of his
name sound like a thing you'd call your taint. Yeah. Yeah. I always thought that about that guy. I don't hate
Channing Tatum. I don't hate him either. I'm saying I like him in a lighter role, a 21 jump. Do you
like him in Jupiter rising? That was one of the worst miseries ever. We played a half -dolls, half -man
who thought so. They lost their mind. Yeah. I called foul. Not because of the trans thing. They lost
their creative way. I called foul after the first matrix when everybody's gone. These guys are geniuses. I'm
Like, everybody just calmed down.
Everybody just calmed down.
I mean, the first time, these are great fucking movies.
Matrix two has an amazing car chase.
The rest is unwatchable.
Matrix three, pretty much all unwatchable.
Never saw the third one.
Cloud Atlas, guys, horrifically bad.
What was your favorite speed racer?
One of the worst things I've ever seen in my life.
I think John Goodman in there, I was like,
what are you doing?
I haven't seen Sense Eight, the show that they do.
I never saw Sense Eight.
It's got a lot of fucking.
him. I never saw a bound. Well, bound is great. I never saw a cloud at
less. Did you see that? Joe, I just went through these movies. Is
this a joke? No. You don't listen to me. I do listen. I'm just a
little fried today. Holy shit, folks. I just went through all these
movies. Then Joe went through them again. This you see why I don't
even I don't even really have a friend here. I'm just talking to
the. All right. Well, I clearly I don't remember what you said
about cloud Atlas. Did you say it was embarrassing? It's like 40 embarrassing stories. It's
sewn together. It truly is. It is like a bat shit pulp fiction. Yeah. Like what is going on?
It was terrible. Who cares about any of this? Uh, yeah, that, I don't know why we got off
in the Michalis, but yeah, I mean, they need to do something good again at some point. They
should really go back to like bound, like make just a little character driven thriller.
I thought V for Vendetta was okay, but did they did direct okay or they just produced it, but yeah, it was okay
Folks thanks for coming out I am on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh our Facebook page is really pumping along
Every time I check in I get some good laughs. Just search. We'll see you in hell
Emily does a great job running it. Thank you Emily. Emerge and dies is on the way
I feel free to tweet at us whatever you got to do
Joe any plugs anything like that?
Yeah, Joe Dorosacomedy on Twitter and Instagram.
I need to thank, thank, thank, thank the listeners of this show.
As you know for quite some time now I've been asking people
to go and help me fix my trolled album ratings
on iTunes and Amazon.
That were at one point down to one star
because of an army of trolls.
And guys they're up to like three and a half stars.
So you're clearly putting the reviews in.
so thank you for helping me write the wrong course of that ship. If you have it in you to go do it
again or leave some more. I'm not asking for fake reviews, but if you have it in you to say more
nice things, I'd appreciate it. It is helping. It is, it is again writing the wrong. So thank you for
that sincerely. And as far as plugs go, yeah, I'll be in San Francisco for cluster fest in June.
and third and fourth and performing there.
And I'm doing stand up at a most also hosting
the Paddy's pub trivia day or something.
So come out.
Thank you very much everybody.
We will see you next weekend.
We'll see you in a help.
That was a hit gun podcast.