Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM game sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal, durable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Monthly 21 -plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gampler, offer not available in all states,
term -supply, see Fanatic Sports Book App.
This is a headgun podcast.
Welcome to the show everybody.
It's another delicious,
delectable, nutritious,
booty, delicious.
Yeah, episode of We'll see you in hell.
Pat, why don't you kick us off here?
Sure, I will.
I guess we'll just jump right into it
and get on with the show.
And while we're doing so,
on with the Joe, on with the Joe,
Oh, if you think you're gonna leave, then you better say so.
What is that song?
Tom Petty, R -I -P, Tom Petty.
I need to know.
Oh yeah, you're right.
He played it when we saw him at the Hollywood Bowl
days before his untimely death, which I have not been doing well
with, like it's affected me more than maybe any celebrity death
in my life since like the John Candy Chris Farley days.
It's gonna be honest, it's affected me more than deaths
in my own family. Yeah, I mean, especially having that really magical night at the
bowl where he not only sounded incredible and played like 90 hits. Yeah, but he seemed
very healthy and looked, I mean, look, the man was never attractive. He looks like a
possum, but he was, you know, he looked like he always looked and he seemed very stoned.
He seemed to be the most stoned man of all time, but I love that because I was at the
I was at our favorite local bar, the Roost, the other night, and I said another sponsor of the show.
Not, just we love the place.
I was talking to the bartender, telling her about the shows before he died.
And she's like, oh, how was it?
And I go, he was so high, but it was awesome.
I was like, he's just clearly from a different time.
I'm like, I wish I could be like that.
He's just up there like, hey, everybody all right, man.
You know what I'm like?
I just am not wired that way like everything is stress and panic and he's just a child of the 60s or the 50
I don't know I think that is what he was 66 which is older than I thought he was but that's what a kind of
Effects it so much that he seems you know stress as a killer as they say so you imagine these people who are super stressed out
Is the ones who die young and he seemed really chill the other heroin issue late in life
he did obviously do a lot of cocaine,
but it was the seven days.
Well, that's the only piece of mind I can get out of this,
is that I don't hope anything.
I would like to think that there was a reason.
You hate to think a guy like this just dies for no reason.
Maybe it was hard partying or something
and it caught up with him years later or something
or maybe he had a hard issue.
I don't know, but what's the saddest to me
as the idea that Tom Petty just died for no reason other than his heart was like, yeah,
I'm just gonna do this.
Sam, I had seen him at a festival in Pasadena and it was a, I had seen him at many times
of my life, but it was a real miserable experience because we wanted to like push against a fence
with security guard shining a light in our face as the entire time.
And when my buddy asked me to go see him at the bowl, I was like, you know, they were expensive
seats.
I kind of went to bed I was like I just saw him but I couldn't be more glad that I went because I would have
Hated to have that other one be the last night. I almost didn't go yeah
I would have been kicking myself. Yeah, I almost didn't go because I was like, I don't know man
It's kind of a busy week and shit. I mean, I don't maybe next time I'll catch him or whatever like I almost didn't fucking go and
I gotta go and once I was there was so happy I was there as soon as you started playing
I was like, I can't believe I even considered missing this.
And then he died like three days later.
So, I mean, Jesus Christ, he died the day after,
I think, right?
The final night of this tour
of his 40th anniversary tour.
Yeah, makes you wonder if he, I mean,
obviously he didn't kill himself,
but it makes you wonder if he wasn't kind of like,
had maybe gotten a little troubling health news
and decided to go out for one last.
Who knows?
I don't know, I don't know.
And while we're talking about people
will take from us too soon. Ralphie May, buddy, very, very sad about your passing and the
whole comedy community is and just very, very fucking sad man. Ralphie was a great dude,
hilarious comic, fucking just, just a golden soul on that guy, just a nice, supportive,
great dude and I'm really really sad that he that he has passed and his again
it was another thing he did a show on Thursday night at Harris in Vegas and
he was dead Friday yeah he like it was like business as usual yeah I'm like
Jesus Christ man I never met the man he's very funny obviously great dude really
great dude I mean there it's a little less of it of a shock but still I mean
and he was a young man.
Yeah, it's unfortunate.
He was healthy, but not in great health, obviously,
or at least not in great physical condition.
I can't speak to what his health for us,
but I think I've heard that he had been battling pneumonia
or something, and I think sadly,
when you're at that kind of weight,
something like pneumonia is really gonna,
yeah, is really gonna potentially trigger
some other much more crucial stuff, you know,
or vital stuff and yeah, it's just a bummer, man, he was a friend and you know, he was the kind of guy like when I would post tweets about like, you know, fuck you American Airlines, you know, he's like the guy that would retweet you because he had significantly more followers and then be like, American Airlines, you know, who you fucking with?
that's Jonah Rosa right there, you know, and I'm sure that because he did that, it led to me getting
several. A free beverage vouchers from American Airlines for free flights. But he was just a good
dude, man. He was just a really, really good dude. I don't doubt it. Anyway, rest in peace to both of you,
Tom and Ralphie. And uh, and that brings us to Pat's movie. Hey, that's for that great, great warm -up.
Yeah, yeah, I like to get the audience hot sure before we go into your segment. I've seen a couple items
I watched
The HBO's Spielberg documentary. Here it's great. It's fantastic. It's it's two and a half hours
I could have gone for another two and a half
Because they left out a lot of movies. I mean it's not some with good reason and some without but
And Joe, can you turn that iTunes thing off?
I have OCD about it.
The what?
It's a problem.
The icon keeps bouncing down at the bottom.
The iTunes icon is bouncing.
It's, of course, it stopped the second icon.
I commented on it.
Doesn't look like anything.
Make a bounce.
Are you guys sliding me right now?
I don't see anything bouncing.
It was bouncing.
All right.
I don't even see a damn iTunes icon down there.
You see the icon.
I mean, I'm kidding.
I'm not even looking at a screen.
You can't.
you can't cover it.
It's in the toolbar.
I guess it'll just keep doing it, but that's fine.
Yeah, the Spielberg documentary.
So they, they didn't mention several movies, but I was kind of, they also start with
jaws, then go to the beginning, kind of jumps around in a very weird way.
Sure. But it was fascinating, especially how much daddy issues the man has.
And they really go into it because when they start showing back to back to back,
all these movies where he deals with daddy issues and the last crusade and even like frivolous stuff
even close encounters close to count that's and it that's probably the biggest one yeah ET
all this stuff missing father's abs and fathers catch me if you can
wore the worlds was about like they're all about them yeah and then you learn the story of
Chandler's list yes right you learn about his parents and that that stuff was all very interesting to
me. And the one thing I did have a problem with was they'd show these clip packages and
it would be like close and cause the third kind. Like I these iconic scenes, poltergeist,
ET, Jurassic Park, Schindler's list, War Horse.
War Horse, one Oscars. What for sound or something? No, no, that was a big movie man.
Maybe nominated for ship but when you made it into a fucking oh no it was a play first
When you see that stupid warhorse galloping around you're like don't start pretending that that's up in this cow
Then they shit on the color purple, which is a shit on I think it's a beautiful movie. Everybody does. Why did they shit on it?
The only mention that it gets is great. They shit on it or they don't they shit on it
And it was that was nominated for 12 Oscars
So basically, it starts out with a, they talked to a couple critics throughout and this guy's like,
I mean, maybe you don't treat this topic where every shot looks so beautiful, like this was him and it's absolute worst.
There's an documentary about Steven Spielberg.
Then, uh, why?
Everyone was upset, which I did, of course, I didn't know about this controversy.
I was four years old, but the book had a heavy lesbian plot and in the movie, they do what
Big Old Bird does kiss that woman pretty passionately and they go away from it.
It's a PG -13 movie, and things weren't handled that explicitly back then.
And people were apparently furious with Steven Spielberg and he discusses this in the documentary.
There's a scene in the book where she makes Woopy Goldberg look at her vagina in a mirror.
Like look at it.
That's your special, you know, that kind of thing.
And Spielberg was like, sorry, I did not feel I was the right man to include that moment.
And it made me uncomfortable.
I thought it was weird, but that's really all they say
about the color purple, like he didn't have the guts
to show you whoopee Goldberg's badge.
So suddenly it's a bad movie, like,
right, does it, does it show like as graphically
as Schindler's list does, you know,
what that girl went through?
No, but not every movie has to be that explicit.
What it reminded me of, there's 30 minutes in it basically
of Schindler's list.
and I think that's an all -time top 10 for me.
It's a classic film. I mean, it's, you know, it's a beautiful movie. They're both beautiful films.
Both of those films are beautiful films.
Yeah.
I'm going to say it. Steven Spielberg is a talented director.
Oh, I wouldn't go that far.
Not kidding.
We'll mention of the terminal.
Yeah, they just glaze over the terminal.
Four, five shots from the BFG made the cut.
but he directed that?
Yeah, he did.
I didn't see BFG, but also they like hook.
I think hooks pretty lame,
but like people really fucking love that movie
and it made a tremendous amount of money.
You see one shot of hook like flash by.
That's I'm happy to hear that.
I think hook is a, is a fucking schmaltz.
It's a bad movie.
But people, especially people in my age, love it.
My age.
What else have you seen?
You know what I mean?
All my people in my age.
No, people in my age.
Yeah, yeah, what what else um I want I'll do one then you do another right
Uh, I tried to watch the bad batch
Uh, heard things as was it NC 17 or something? I don't even know it was I was on Netflix. I put it on I
Think I made it about 30 minutes before I started fast forwarding. I was just like you know
It's another one of these movies and it's it's the same problem. I have with the drive guy
I, you know, with some of his work, the later world.
Oh, Ratham.
I thought you were talking about a movie called The Drive Guy.
No.
No, no, no.
The director.
It's the problems I have with everything he's been doing since Bronson, and it's the
same thing.
I forget the lady's name, and she directed a girl walks home alone at night.
I think it was called Iranian director.
Yeah.
She's very talented, obviously, but it's this crew of directors that's like, it's, it's
It's just a, it's a music video.
It's a big fucking music video.
It's a lot of scenic shots.
It's a lot of landscapes.
There's no dialogue.
It's very slow.
It's like, it's not enough.
The picture quality is not enough for me.
All right.
I found it extremely boring.
And then also Jim Carey with his like recent horse shit
where in every interview he's like,
there is no Jim Carey.
There is only the world's impression of Jim Carrey.
None of us are here, none of this is real.
It's like, well, really, Jim, then go live in a cabin
and stop producing things and making movies and making...
Nice that you figured this out as you make millions of dollars.
What, how does this tie into the bad bench?
He's got a cameo.
Well, he's got a small part in it and it's just...
You had snapped for a minute.
No, just the sight of him and it annoyed me.
And then, like Jason MoMA, you know, he's fine in it.
You know, it's like, it's just not the main girl,
I can't remember her name because I didn't know who she was
before I saw this, but she was good.
Like, it's like, nobody's bad in it or anything.
It's just an interest, man.
It's just that it's just fucking boring.
It's like, I don't care about this.
I just don't care.
Like, depravity in the wasteland is not enough
to make a movie interesting.
It's not enough for me.
Like, they cut her arm off in the first five minutes.
And then they're lagging the first seven minutes.
It's like, I don't fucking care.
Like, it's not enough.
That's not a story to me. So and I didn't really see I didn't really find it to be you know movie like THX
1132 whatever the fuck it's called the George Lucas first movie
It's stark and it's slow, but there's an interesting social commentary to it
It's about consumerism in the 70s and and materialism and all these things and I didn't see that commentary in this film
If I missed it, let me know. I apologize, but I didn't see the commentary. So I just thought it was just kind of a
much much much much more boring version of like a Mad Max movie. Okay, it's like you better throw some goddamn flaming
car chases into this thing with a guy playing electric guitar or that's my note on every movie anyway. That's my that's the
first one for me. Okay. I watched this morning, a movie I hadn't seen in 15 years. I saw
it at the theater in Missouri called Orange County. Yes. Colin Hanks, who is an acquaintance
of mine, a nice man. I like that Colin Hanks. Very nice man. Good face. Yes. Nice guy face. Yes.
Who plays the mom in Orange County? Catherine O 'Hara. Yeah, that's wonderful. Jack Black.
Yeah, Jack Black's real funny in it. It's a good cast Harold Ramos. There you go
Yeah, it's great great cast
For you know never like screamingly funny, but just like a very likable funny comedy with a good soundtrack
And the kind of film dare I say they don't make much anymore. It's likable and enjoyable in the way that like stripes is
Mm -hmm. I never found stripes like gut -busting funny, but it's a very enjoyable film and it makes you laugh
Tell us. Um, all right. Uh, I'm three episodes deep because all they were
released are three episodes of the season four of Gotham. I gotta tell you
folks, this show has found its footing. It is fucking awesome. Took about a
season and a half for them to kind of figure it out. First season, second
season, there were, there was a lot of bumpiness. It was kind of like, well,
Wait, why are they doing it that way?
And what is this, whatever?
Third season, they came out swinging
and kind of, they figured it out.
They were like, okay, we know what you guys want.
You guys want the villains to be the villains
and you want Bruce Wayne to become Batman.
Bruce Wayne at like 16 years old
and this thing is already going out in like a suit,
not the bat suit, but a version of it.
He's not Batman yet.
And fighting crime in the shadows.
Who's Batman, the kid from the OC?
see. I don't know what else he was ever in. This is the first thing I ever saw. Maybe he's
Commissioner Gordon. Uh, I think that yeah, it's like a sexy Commissioner Gordon. He's
like rugged. It's, you know, I wouldn't say it looked like a young Russell Crowe. Yes. That's
the guy from the outside. Uh, he's great. Um, Donald Lowe is just great as a Harvey Bullock. Um,
you find his kid, Donald Lowe. Oh, Jesus. I don't know. Didn't hear how that ended. I hope it's
All right, I hope so.
It's terrible.
Yeah, I forgot about that.
I hope the situation is all right.
Yeah.
You know, Penguin, I can't remember any of the outer names,
but Penguin is fucking awesome.
Riddler, they got scarecrow in it now.
Last late last season, they brought in like the beginning
of the Joker and they're doing like the detective comics,
fucking Dalmaker Joker, where he has his face cut off
and then he has it reattached like it's fucking awesome.
Is Jada Pinkett, Catwoman?
She's dead. She was she was a character they made up named Fish Mooney, which she was she was great in it
But I think that was one of the things that was confusing in the beginning
It's like why are you making up a new character? Like have her play somebody from the comics, right?
No, a young very young girl is catwoman. Who's got excited about that name Fish Mooney. Yeah, it's a great name
But they they've just brought in every young girl a camera. Remember name. She's catwoman. She's great
She's she's pretty much in full swing now is catwoman
I mean, uh, ratio.
Goal is entered the picture.
It's fucking awesome.
It moves like a fucking detective comics.
It's dark.
It's, it's great.
It's great.
I'm very, very happy.
And, uh, now speaking of, uh, Batman, I, I didn't get a response.
That's not on my text about the Justice League trailer.
I didn't quite understand why you were so wound up about this one stupid joke in the thing.
Well, you always complain about stupid jokes being in these movies.
But I thought it was a stupid joke and a harmful joke and it pissed me off and I was sitting and watching this
Trash preview. Oh stop it. I'm like all right. I'm not gonna. I'm not gonna see this
I had made it my mind and then at the end some guys in the in the Batmobile or whatever with Batman Bruce Wayne
And they go so what's your superpower?
It was unrich
He doesn't say I got the first of all he does. He says it's smugly
He this is why that's a kid's like Batman so then it's like oh, this is why that's gonna be a Batman
I got to accumulate wealth and then we're gonna wind up with a bunch of Republicans again. This is why that's that's not what's gonna
Happen. I think you're drawing really jumping to hard and hit me in a bad place. I'm sick of those movies a and b
Batman gloating about being rich not my bad. He's not gloating. Not my Batman. Listen
It was never about gloating from my
He might see you down at a long table in there
You might you might not be able to hear him down the table while you're trying to eat dinner, but he wasn't show off
Yeah, so I always wondered why you didn't bring basing his chair over you didn't think it was you didn't think it was weird when he goes
Give this guy a grant Alfred that
Fucking you know, I've never been in this room before no that stuff
Give this guy a grant sounds like charity to me is what it sounds like it was Robert Wohl's reporter character
who was a snooping sleaze.
Well, hopefully you pay them to not appear
in any future Batman movies
because it's hard to look at them.
Listen to that guy.
The reason that joke is in the trailer
is because that is a running Batman joke
that has never been addressed.
And that's them nodding to the fans.
Like, we're finally gonna put the thing in
where somebody's like, what do you do?
And he's just like, I have a lot of money
and I can buy these things.
Pete has a joke about it.
Give me a lunatic with a billion dollars.
That's a superhero.
Like, it's a joke.
It's like a common joke amongst Batman fans. So it's like that that's in there is a nod to the fans
That is not them being like isn't it cool that he's rich, but how's the kid gonna differentiate it?
Jesus fucking crazy. We're gonna children here. You're right
And the kid shouldn't have been allowed to watch beevison but had it was their fault
You know it's it's the pair it's your pretty we we and then we got to watch what kids think you know god damn movie
I just know my Batman was a lot cooler and a lot no I'm gonna say this you don't get to have a Batman with all the
The foul shit you've been saying around this podcast about him lately, you don't get
a bad man.
Oh, my bad man is, is Mike Keaton.
Well, I, I, I hate to break it to you.
My Joker is a Jackie Knicks.
You're insane.
There are better jokers than Jackie Knicks.
My penguin is a Danny DeVete.
That's nuts.
Oswald Cobblepon.
The only penguin is so far in film is a Burgess Meredith.
So far in film.
The TV show Penguin is they should have had him do the Burton movie is a second age 109 that
Data David is a great actor and he's great in that part. He's not the penguin that is not the character
You've seen a better let's see. I never you know. I never care about that the penguin is not about what's entertaining
You do care about it because we talked about it with it the penguin is not a mutant that lives in a sewer
With with it's crazy and about five for
Fiverr was great, so DeVito was great.
I just didn't like what the direction they took the character in.
Nicholson was a great Joker, but as any Batman fan, I'll tell you, Schwarzenegger was
a great free.
Oh God.
The best Joker is Mark Hamill's Joker on the Batman animated series and the second best
is Heath Ledger.
I have a terrible life connotation to Batman the Batman series, so I hate it.
I used to love it.
I stopped watching.
I just picked up.
you know how much we like that Americana at the Glendale, Galeria.
Sure. I went over to the Barney and Grove.
Yeah. The Barnes and Noble that we love so much over there, shopped for DVDs the other day,
got seasons two and four of the Batman Animated Series, 10 bucks each.
Nice. Also got a copy of The Witches, which is a really fun.
Angelica Houston. Yeah. So I saw that for the first time.
Six ninety nine. Also walked out of there with a copy of the Blu -ray of legend,
and starring Tom Cruise.
You know, I have the Blu -ray of legend,
and I have never seen the movie.
Director's cut.
Much better than the original cut.
Oh, good.
Both are good.
I went one night, they had a night in the cemetery.
I don't do this anymore, but you go.
Everyone always has like eight bottles of wine
for three people.
Weeds, always being passed around.
And I was so excited to go.
It was labyrinth starting at 10 p .m.
All right.
Legend at midnight and like the Princess bride at two
And I was like what a great night is gonna be and I'm out. I have a pillow and a blanket whatever
Why and starts flowing the joint starts flowing. I'm asleep before David Bowie's bull genders the
I saw maybe ten minutes of puppets and labrath and I was out
Actually if I it was my first time seeing labrath, I would have thought I was a movie about Jennifer Connelly babysitting
Yes, I wouldn't have known about the labyrinth aspect of that wraps up me for the movie corner. You got anything else?
No, I'm good. I'm good. Let me do a quick scary stuff. Okay. I got well
No, my you know what I should have done with save Spielberg for scary stuff. God damn it. It doesn't make sense for scary stuff
It does it's a thing about he makes horror movies. Jesus Christ. I really thought I had this one. I don't understand
and again, but he makes scary movies.
It doesn't, that's not what this is about.
Scary stuff is about a product that is horror related
that you can purchase.
You can purchase a Spielberg on iTunes, so.
But you're not, there's no physical,
there's no physical product to review.
So, there is a physical product.
It's a documentary called Spielberg and I'm reviewing.
You can't, here's what we're making a scary stuff.
Do you want to stop? You want to listen and try to learn how to fucking do this for once.
Here's what would make it a scary stuff. If you said, so criterion finally released
the Spielberg documentary on Blu -ray, it's beautiful packaging. It's got all these bonus
features. Go out and get it. All right. Watch how you do it. Ready? Folks, universal monsters,
the essential collection. Blu -ray. I've got it, but with a different
cover I've had it for years. The Blu -ray set, if you don't have this, go out and grab it.
You can get it on Amazon for a reasonable price.
It's not cheap, but it's probably around 75 bucks
or something.
You can get it cheaper.
If yours come with the 3D glasses
to watch Creature from the Black Lagoon?
No, mine is 2D.
So you can get this thing on Amazon.
It's very great.
I suggest you go buy it for your Halloween viewing pleasure.
It's all eight of the original Universal Monsters.
You've got the Mummy, the Wolfman.
and creature from the Black Lagoon,
the invisible man, Dracula, Frankenstein,
bride of Frankenstein.
Does it have Blackula?
And Phantom of the Opera.
No, because he's not one of the original Universal Monsters.
But these restorations are stunning.
They're just happening.
The Dracula, the vampire who drew off my victims.
I'm not in the mood.
I got to be honest with you.
I'm tired.
I just want to get to the damn movie review.
You're supposed to have a spirited debate.
It's, uh, doesn't have the Scott Bakula.
Maybe this is why you don't know how to do the segment because you're always busy
horse and off.
Well, whenever you get going on Zelda or whatever the fuck I tune out.
I don't have any interest in the movie, but go buy this usually at this point you're
talking about Zelda.
The version I got came with a bunch of postcards for each movie.
Very cool.
Very cool set.
So go buy that.
Notice how I'm not reviewing the movies themselves.
I'm just saying, this is a great set. Go buy it. Do you see? Do you see now? I do. All right.
Unfortunately, I didn't buy anything spooky this week. Well, that's fine. You don't have to do it.
I got to be honest with you, bet. I wouldn't care if you never partook in this statement segment again.
I have no problem. I'm not sure I ever had to be honest. I'm usually wrong.
Let's get to our movie this week. We forgot to even announce it at the top. Gerald's game.
We did new to Netflix. Oh, no, we didn't announce it. We did forget. Yeah. Okay. Yeah.
Gerald's game. Gerald's game. I was real in the Stephen King when I was a boy and my
mom pretty much had had the rule of as long as you're reading, you can read whatever you want,
which was kind of a good way to get me to read. And I love to read. But then Gerald's game came
along. I remember there were two books. One was American Psycho. My mom like slid it across
the table like this is disgusting yeah that's never seen her do that um and she would not allow me
to read that and then the other one was Gerald's game and I was like bummed out because it's Stephen
King I was probably 14 and then I read what it was about chaining it was in the book she's completely
naked chaining a naked woman to a bed and then the husband dies on top of her basically and then
that you know dogs and all sorts of things she's trapped in a room for the whole book chain to a bed
naked. So I snuck it every time I could get a moment with it, I would sneak the book, pleasure
myself to it, but also be scared by it. You'd pleasure yourself to the book. That was at an age
where just the sex scene before the death of the husband was enough. Needful things had a little
fantasy paragraph. Out of that thousand page book, there's one paragraph where the kid imagines
he's naked writing on the chalkboard and a teacher comes up behind him and jerks him off.
Okay.
And that paragraph kept me going for probably six years.
The naked young boy, that was all you needed to read.
Well, it was my age.
No, I know.
So yeah, the teacher would jack him up.
Pet Cemetery has a scene where the wife goes in with the oven mitt and jerks him off in
the bathtub.
Really?
And when you're a kid and porn isn't readily available, meaning I had no possible way
have seen porn, or really a sports illustrated swimsuit edition with my parents, I had to get
it where I could. So things like that. There was a Christopher Pike book called Monster
where there was a hot tub sex scene. It was a young adult novel. So it was probably three
sentences of this couple having sex in a hot tub. Yeah, I jerked off of this thing for a year.
Yeah, I remember there was a scene in the movie Fall Time starring Steven Baldwin and Mickey
you work. Sure. Where they have like a, I guess they have, I can't remember. I haven't
seen it in a while, but they compare dick sizes and you jacked off to it. Yes. They rob
a bank and there's a ball time. And then the points of his pants. Yeah. They rob a bank.
They, they've, they think two hostages, ones like a, a young woman. Oh no, no, that's right.
They take like a teller hostage and she's like a hot like girl in her 20s. And then there's
like a young kid on the team and like she seduces the kid and like jerks him
like reaches her hand in his pants and like jerks him off he's a whack off to
that all the time. Yeah. Um, crazy how how destroyed our
imaginations have become over time. Yeah, it's terrible. Like could you have
you I could do it. But how long has it been since you sat down and jerked off
with your imagination? It's been a while and I and I have to really let it
back up. I got to really just be in a real prison state of
things where I'm like, I'm going to explode if I don't do
this. Sure. Not to use such colorful language, but that's
you were big on jerking off it like at a plant at a restaurant
or something like that. What's that? You just release yourself
when you feel it. Yeah. Like Mr. Harvey Weinstein. What is a
planet? The rest story that came out last night that he jerked
Stuffed up a plant in a restaurant.
He was alone with this woman, a woman I have met
in a very lovely woman.
And she came out with a story,
and as all these stories are true,
because Harvard Weinstein has been a notorious monster
for decades, but he was like,
hey, what do you think you wanna come back to my room
and she's like, no, they're in a restaurant.
Like people are in the restaurant.
Right.
She goes, no, I'm sorry.
I didn't think that's what this is about, et cetera.
And he goes, just shut your mouth then, takes his dick out, yanks it like six times,
it jackulates into a potted plant, puts his dick away and goes back into the restaurant.
Where is the plant outside in the restaurant?
Nobody sees this.
They're in the back, like between the bathrooms and the whatever, you know.
All right.
And I mean, these stories are just going to keep coming and coming and coming, forgive me
with using the word.
Honestly did not mean to make the pun. What do you think of his claim that he made that he
Rited these things as best he could in the past and now and now I think it's absurd. I mean the man's like look
I came up in the in the 60. Oh, is that what he's saying? That is in his apology letter
He's like I came up in the 60 okay, you could jerk off in a plant in front of a woman if you want it
But it's not good and what's troubling to me is that Rose McGowan
And let's look to connect this to horror.
Man, man, it's produced a lot of horror.
The Scream franchise.
It's produced almost every Tarantino movie.
Also in the Scream franchise, Rose McGowan.
And this is apparently where it started to happen.
But Harvey Weinstein raped Rose McGowan.
She's been talking about it for years on Twitter
and whenever anyone has ever seen it.
Well, she's accusing him of it.
Let's not, let's not sentence the man here.
I'm not saying he's not guilty.
I'm just saying we should be careful.
Let's not say that it definitely happened because you know, I don't think there's so in this podcast, but but I'm just saying do
Process is a thing that we all need to remember is part of our judicial system. That's all
Sure, that's you know, that's fair. He did a lot. I'm not saying he didn't look I've heard many many decades at the end of
At the end of
What's it called
over night, which is my favorite documentary ever, folks, I bet many of you have not seen
the documentary overnight. I own it. You can buy it for 10 bucks on Amazon, whatever.
I think that might be the only way to see it. It's one of the best documentaries ever.
It's about the guy who made the Boondocks Saints, which is like every frat douche his favorite
movie. Well, the guy who made it is the ultimate frat douche. And at the end of that, he claims
that Harvey Weinstein tried to have him killed by sending a card or run him off the road.
Right.
So I mean, look, I never thought Harvey Weinstein seemed like a great guy.
I am not would not be surprised if any or all of this was true.
You ever read down on dirty pictures, but you know, it's, it's, you know, I'm also not
going to say, well, he's definitely guilty.
That's not my place to say it, you know.
I will.
I'll say he's definitely guilty.
All right.
Have you read down in dirty pictures about like the rise of the indie movies, mostly
dealing with a lot of Maramax Harvey Weinstein's ship?
It's an amazing book.
No.
It's basically the indie version of like Easy Writers Raging Bulls, you ever read that book?
You have to read both of these books.
Why?
The two of the best books ever written in my opinion, in terms of nonfiction, certainly nonfiction
entertainment industry related.
I don't care. I don't give a shit about that stuff. You don't care about like how all the 70s directors came to be Scorsese and
What would I what do I need to know they made they went to film the school
Coked out movie sets taxi driver. I guess. I mean, I don't know. I don't think I was amazing stories in both those books
I'm sure there are that those aren't the things I like to read though. I like to read fiction
I don't wait to read not they did make easy -rights raising bulls into a documentary that I would watch and that's great
That I also made a documentary about the 70s director speaking of books. Yeah, Gerald's game
Let me say this. Can I say this?
One of the best Stephen King adaptations I have ever seen. I thought it was a phenomenal film
It took a seemingly impossible to film book and made a really neat movie out of it. I liked it a lot myself
I thought it was fantastic
It's getting not none but about a tenth of the shine that this horseshit fucking it adaptation is getting you know
What that's probably why I like to even more it probably it cost one one hundredth of it
And it's scarier than it and it's better than it
Intense flick. Yeah really intense flick
To to the point where there were parts where I was like I don't know if I need to see that
Well, but that's what made it good
I'm going to do a quick spoiler, actually I'm not, but I'll just say the hand scene was
one of the craziest things I've ever seen.
So as I was telling Heather and I, she was asking if she should watch it and she was the only
time in my entire life that I've ever audibly screamed at a movie was auditioned.
the Japanese to cash him a K when that when the bag moves the big man in the bag or I screamed.
It was, you know, 15 years ago, I screamed in my house, I woke my roommate up and in that
hand scene.
What does it sound like when you scream and something?
It's not.
It's not a masculine scream.
But I watching that hand scene and if you've seen it, you know what I'm talking about?
If you've not, I won't go into any more detail.
Well, holy shit, that was one of the most intense things I've ever seen in my life.
There were two scenes where I live alone, as you know, and I just mean the dog here.
I made audible gasps at two scenes in the film to nobody but myself.
Fucking dog doesn't know what I'm doing, he's an idiot.
it. A lot of the gaps. And I was over here preparing food as I was watching it for both
scenes. The hand scene was one and then the other without spoiling anything. The Henry
Thomas dad scene, which I was just like, whoo, shiver me timbers. But the movie's fantastic.
Really both actors are really really tremendous in it that the guy that plays the the jewelry man with the moonlight man
That's the guy from Twin Peaks right isn't that the giant from Twin Peaks in makeup? Oh
Maybe I figured it was somebody with some sort of disfiguration. Yeah, I think it's actually I think it's just the giant from oh, okay
Twin Peaks looks just like him except with makeup on that's crazy make up on I didn't
Um. You like that ending? Um, kind of stupid. I don't know. I, you know, I, apparently
when the book came out, that ending was extremely polarizing too. It's like the last 40 pages
of the book or something. I didn't think we needed it. I felt like when she, well, look,
there's going to be spoilers now because I don't, we can't, you can't talk about this without
spoiling anything. I really thought the ending was gonna be and it would have been enough for me
was her stumbling out of that house and you see her, you know, the last shot is you see her like
pulling into the emergency room or something and it fades to black and it's, to me that was enough
of she did it. She overcame the demons that were literally in her life and emotionally in her life
for whatever. That would, that was enough of a triumph of the spirit for me or would have been.
Yeah. Uh, I didn't need a literal scene at the end where you realize, oh, the moonlight
man is actually real. And then she turns her back on him in the courtroom and here's what really
bothered me about the end. No fucking courtroom on planet earth is going to let somebody just
just waltz in and just go through those gates.
And they just know what even says, like, stop.
Yeah, nobody says anything.
They did, I don't know.
There's nobody guarding the door.
Then the moonlight man breaks the handcuffs
and you're like, what, wait, what?
How could he break the handcuffs?
This is a diseased man.
He's sick.
So there were elements of that.
It was, it's very on the nose for her to turn her back
and go, you're much smaller than I remember.
I'm not trying to shit on bloody disgusting, I do like the website, but they've been writing
some stuff lately that's been driving me fucking crazy.
One of the things was why the last 15 minutes of this movie was so important.
And it's literally like an analysis where it's like, you mean in like today's society
is that the job?
Just not so much that, just like this is why it's necessary, this is why you should love
the ending.
And it was like, the writer was like, when she turns her back, that's literally her turning
her back on her past, it's like, yeah, no shit, everybody understands that.
Like nobody's confused by what it's supposed to mean.
Yeah, I really got that idea.
It's just, I felt like it just didn't need to be there.
I liked the idea that like, you didn't know whether or not the moonlight man was real.
I liked that she drops her wedding ring into his jewelry box at the end.
and that's kind of where she says goodbye to her past.
Like, I didn't need a literal explanation
of why that guy was there.
Agreed.
I did think the one cool detail in there
was that the mutilation of her husband's body
was mostly from that guy and not the dog.
Right.
I thought that was pretty cool, but you know,
that being said, it didn't ruin the movie for me or anything.
It wasn't like, I was like, fuck this movie.
No.
I'm Gugino's great nut who Carla Gugino
She's great. She's really great in the the the Emma said the dad's name
The guy Bruce Greenwood who's in everything. I know I'm best from Star Trek
portrayed the press it always plays the president but recently he played the president in
Kingsman 2 which I discussed last week. Yeah, he played the president in 13 days and all kinds of different movies
gotta see that damn King's man one and two still so overall big thumbs up for
me for this flick I really enjoyed it I agree I agree with the thumbs up you
know but not a rave and not just because of the ending it was a
Yeah, it was a tense kind of involving movie, but it felt a little, it felt like the
best lifetime movie ever made in a way to make.
Look, anything, I think anything made for Netflix has yet to escape the made for TV movie
feeling.
Sure.
So there were times where I was like, yeah, this feels like an awesome mini series.
Yeah, I agree.
But I'll tell you this, if it ever gets released, I'll buy it.
It's one I would have for the collection without without without a doubt I would put it in
the collection reminded me a lot of misery and the things I loved about misery. The suspense
was great. The simplicity of the story and the one location and all that was great.
And the way the puzzle unfolded about the significance of the glass of water and why nobody could hear
her screaming and why they were there, it was all very, very well done. Because the source material
was obviously very good. So I loved it. Pat liked it. There you have it.
Patty, Joey, um, what are you, Joe? Why don't you, why don't you tell them about our, our Patreon?
Folks, we finally got off our large asses and got this Patreon up and running. Thank God, Jesus Christ.
it's up. You can go to it patreon .com slash W S I Y H those are the initials for
we'll see you in hell obviously pod P O D W S Y H P O D go to it we've got three
tiers for donations there's a dollar tier that's just a kindness donation if you
love the show and just want to maybe show us your gratitude of course through
through money because that's the only way to show gratitude in my opinion. You
can donate a buck or two. There's a $5 tier. If you want to donate five bucks, you
will get a shout out on the podcast and that's for every donation. They're monthly
donations. So if you donate five bucks every month every month we will give you a
shout out every time you do. And last but not least, there's a $10 tier and the $10 tier will
get you an exclusive mini -sode, which means you will not get just four episodes in the month.
You'll get a fifth one for free. Well, for ten bucks. And every month you donate to ten bucks,
you know, the people, those people will get the mini -sode plus this plus the shout out, I think,
to. We should probably you should get both. Even though it doesn't say that, you'll
get both. All right. You know, and I think it's safe to say these many soads will be roughly
the length of an episode of the shit. Yeah. And we'll do something different. A lot of
it. It's not deceiving. It sounds like it's five minutes long. Yeah. No. A lot of it will
be, you know, maybe, you know what? We'll go on and change it just to you'll get an extra
episode. You get an extra. And we'll do something different where it's like a top 10.
Yeah, we've talked about doing like each of us say our top five horror movies five to one etcetera. Yeah, or maybe we'll even do an interview with a guest or something like that. Yeah, but it'll be something different than the regular show so.
So that's it, the Patreon's out there, Patreon .com slash WSYIHPOD, you can follow me on Instagram,
please.
I'm only posting to Twitter now through my Instagram, it's Joe DeRosa Comedy, come
follow me over there, and this comes out, I'll be in Pittsburgh at the improv, the weekend
of October 19th, so if you want to check it out, come, I'll check it out, folks, you can
follow me on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh. You can hear me this Wednesday
on Los Felis the podcast. I know that's a little niche. And if you're out of the Los Angeles
area, it probably won't interest you. But it's with my old friend Morgan Murphy and my
new friend Rob and sure. And we talk about the neighborhood in which I and you could say Joe
and Morgan and those two and a lot of my friends live in Los Felis. It's a funny podcast
about the neighborhood. It's a very cool thing they're doing like a little community podcast. I like it and it's but it's funny. It's good and the other thing is my show has changed its name back to living biblically.
It was market tested. They were like living biblically. We don't like it. We're going to buy the book. Then two days ago they were like, hey, we tested it again.
and people prefer living biblically.
I said, you do whatever you want.
As long as it's not some stupid pun.
Now, is there any chance in these tests?
They say, we made a mistake.
Joe DeRosa back in the show.
I am going to bring it up at the next one.
Yes.
Yeah.
But the show, which for fans of the podcast,
is really going to be a treat because
not only did I write and create the fucking show,
but Joe DeRosa says, I've told you many times,
steals the fucking show.
He's amazing in it.
Well, that's not be if I stole it. I'd still be in the goddamn thing, but
In the pilot he's he well, he's awesome in it and it starts I still don't know but it's looking like January
I just wanted to tell you the name went back. So if you are you know, you talk to your parents back home
You want to tell them you listen to her show you watch for this television show the title is back to living biblical
All right folks. That's our show. We'll see you next time
and we'll see you in hell.