Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer, or check out
our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz, only available at Bed
MDM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bed MDM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bed MDM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Bed MDM in game sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
BedMGM .com for tees and seeds, 21 plus to wager.
Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia only, games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal, durable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
Gamling problem, call 1 -800 -Gambleer.
Firestone Complete Auto Care's epic savings advantage is the sign you need to stop putting
off your car's maintenance.
And you can save up to $100 on tires and services while you're at it.
Don't wait, call Firestone Complete Auto Care for an appointment.
There's a new podcast app that delivers chilling true crime stories straight to your mobile
device every day.
They release a new episode that investigates the gruesome true acts of America's war
serial killers and you can explore into the minds of psychopaths and murderers.
To get started, find and download Murder Minute from the App Store or visit murderminute .com.
That's m -u -r -d -e -r -m -i -n -u -t -e .com to get your daily dose of true crime, creepiness delivered
straight to your mobile device.
Hi there everybody, welcome to We'll See You In Hell with a podcast where you listen
to us talk about the movies that you like, about the horror and sci -fi and sneezing.
All your favorite sneezes represented.
And expanding the genre is quite frankly, moving into other territories.
Last week we covered, or two weeks ago we covered Love Actually.
Caused someone to walk out of the Facebook group, said, love actually, I'm done, walked
out.
Really?
I remember it was like, later, a walk out.
Yeah, I don't even remember the gentleman's name, I just chuckled to myself, God, people
are miserable.
Yeah, hey, I get it, but yeah, it's like anyone turning to us for like probing discussions
of the horror genre.
You might catch that now and again, but I would hope you're just here for the boys
at this point.
And if you're not, you know, go do something else, I don't care.
That's a real strange deal breaker, yeah.
I'm done.
It's a fucking thing that you download, maybe you don't like some of them.
Who cares?
Yeah.
You're not buying it.
Who gets a shit?
Now Joe, why did you tell Kevin Hart to tweet what he did?
Look, it was a 10 years ago and I was a different man back then, you know, what could I say?
Now what's your take on this?
Oh, this will be a real easy conversation to have.
My take on it is, is I don't know the man well, I know him a little bit, I do not believe
him to be a hateful man.
I do not believe he meant anything by those tweets other than he was trying to be funny.
He has addressed them several times and apologized several times and said, I'm evolving as a human
being.
And, you know, and we make mistakes or what we're have refraised it.
I respected what he did with stepping down from the Oscars and not kissing the ring but
then also independently of that saying, if I offended anybody in this community, I'm sorry.
I thought that was a real class move.
And you know, what pisses me off is, you know, when I wake up and go on Instagram and see
a thing from vice saying, here are the tweets Kevin Hart doesn't feel sorry about.
And it's like, well, number one, that's not true.
And number two, vice, you want to start fucking digging through the past?
Sure.
Because I can think of a lot of questionable shit you guys ran in that magazine.
But this is Kevin McGinnis, if I'm not mistaken, correct?
Well, Gavin left, the original, the only original person, there was three founders and
the only original guy, there's only one of the three original guys there.
Apparently there's a real nasty falling out between the three of them.
But it's like, dude, you go back to like the earlier, not even earlier issues of vice
magazine back when they were like this punk rock hipster thing.
Yeah.
You guys got a lot of skeletons in that closet.
I mean, you were exploiting homeless people, there's tons of fat jokes.
Fuck off, vice.
You know, now that you suddenly, you think you're the new like investigative new shut up.
Jesus Christ, shut up.
Yeah, I mean, the, what I saw was a bunch of like him calling people, the F slur,
in response to shitty things people tweeted at him.
And those are kind of hard to parlay as jokes, but you know, I didn't see those.
I didn't even really see what the jokes were.
In terms of, I'd kill my son if he was gay.
You know, Tracy Morgan did almost exactly the same bit a few years back.
Everybody still loves Tracy Morgan.
I think because Tracy Morgan gives the suggestion that he might not be all there,
even though I think he's very much all there as is Kevin Hart.
But it's very much picking and choosing.
I mean, Kevin Hart, they don't respect artistically because his movies aren't cool to the
critical community.
And Tracy Morgan was on 30 rock for eight years, the most critically acclaimed comedy of
our times.
Well, they just give him a pass.
And I don't think any of it's cool.
I just don't understand who, who gets to decide and, and why they decide when they decide.
And I understand why Kevin Hart set down because he's probably like, look, if this is day
one of taking this job, fuck off.
I don't need this.
Well, he doesn't need it.
I do like that he said publicly.
He's like, look, the reason I'm not apologizing is because I've addressed this many, many times
publicly.
Like this is not a new story, and, you know, what, how many times can I say, like, all right,
I fucked up.
Like, you know, I made a mistake.
Look, there's a lot of words, unfortunately, that we all used to use that, I mean, you
far in using that slow on my latest record.
This is a guy on this first two albums, first three albums, four albums, pride it himself
on using the word just to piss people off and was winning Grammys and still became immensely
famous.
Saying I'd do it with Elton John.
Yeah, exactly.
Elton John stuck up for him.
It's like, and now it's a different time and now even you have a guy like Eminem going,
I shouldn't have used that word on the new record.
I'm sorry about that.
Like, I went too far.
So, it's like people were evolving.
Nobody saying that anybody should not feel hurt by things.
Nobody saying that anybody shouldn't be upset by things.
But we have to also understand that we're evolving as people.
And there are a lot of words, slurs and not that we used to throw around, Willie Nilly retarded
being one of them, you know, and it's like, we're evolving.
We're learning how to speak differently and what's not okay.
But, you know, I just can't believe we're at a stage now where I've said this before on
the show, but where the so -called, you know, artistic, you know, progressive side of the political
divide are now acting like the Christians who Jesus had to say, you know, he without sinned
cast the first stone or whatever.
It's like, what the fuck is going on right now?
Yeah.
Like, we've all fucked up people, you know?
Things have changed, you know, at an extremely accelerated rate.
It used to be, it would take 50 years for people to go, yeah, Mickey Rooney probably shouldn't
have played this Asian character in breakfast at Tiffany's.
Right.
This is horrific to watch.
Now, you know, people will watch a movie from two years ago.
And can you believe that we let this slide and things like that?
It's like, well, yeah, because the culture changes.
It wasn't cool then.
It's not cool now, but, I mean, there are people who, it appears their entire life is just
simply giving people and movies and music and television shit for things they deem inappropriate.
And it's honestly...
I also can't, I just can't...
The double standard that the average person has, I remember getting into it with a bunch
of cyclists.
Sure.
Because it's something, I made a joke on one of my other podcasts about, about the, hitting
the cyclists with the door and being like, it's not my problem.
Look where you're going.
I didn't actually do it.
I was just making a fucking joke about it.
And then I actually did apologize, I guess it is kind of dangerous out there, like, you
know.
And this one guy that came after me real hard, I'm like, well, let's see what an ethical
moral guy this guy really is.
And I started looking up his stuff.
I found a story he did on the moth where he talked about getting so annoyed with a car
honking its horn in traffic outside of his apartment that he got eggs and started throwing
them from his window at the car.
And I'm like, I'm sorry, are you bragging about vandalism right now?
But my thing is not, my joke is not a pro.
These people are fucking nuts, man.
They're nuts.
And there's a lot of double standards going on and it's just everybody needs to chill out.
And everybody needs to get the fuck off the internet.
I was talking about this last time I swear.
That's for damn sure.
My friend Dee.
I was like, you've got a generation of people that have been raised digitally.
And they don't understand that when you are on the internet, if you don't like what somebody
is saying or doing, you can literally eliminate their existence.
You can, you can, you block them.
They are gone.
They no longer exist.
And you have people growing up like that.
And then they go out into the real world and think, well, I should be able to do this in
real life too.
And it's like, let's all take a fucking breath here, man.
You know?
You're playing with motherfuckers lives as M &M once said.
Yeah.
So, you know, anyway, I didn't think we were going to start like that today.
I mean, it's, it's all, I've been able to see or read or hear about for three days now.
Two things I don't care about, Kevin Hart and the Oscars and everyone is talking about
it.
That's the other thing is these people who like, okay, Kevin Hart is a pretty funny man.
I've liked him in certain things.
But no one should really ever be thinking about Kevin Hart.
You know, he's an entertainer.
It's just, he's, he's there.
He makes a movie.
You go see a stuff if you like him or you don't.
But now everyone talks about Kevin Hart 247 for a week.
And then in a week, he's back to nothing and nobody cares when we move on.
It's just exhausting.
Well, that's why that Michael Rapp report video I sent you was so great where he talks about
like, where he's like, I woke up today, the headline in my news feed, Cardi B, has a new
boy, who gives a fuck?
Yeah.
I mean, that whole thing that when he, when he goes after our grand day, he's like, people
are tweeting me saying, I should be scared because your fans will attack me.
She better go bat her fucking eyes and somebody else.
I liked my rap part.
David said, I love Pete, he's my friend, but it was funny that he was trashing a Pete was
really funny.
Like, he's, but he's right.
He's like, why is this news?
It's not.
Why is this news?
Why are we discussing these things?
It's also the actual news, which is that our president is supposed to be finally going down.
This has been the news now every day for two years.
Today's the day.
Today's the day, everybody's like, no, today's really the day.
Is it, though?
Is it?
It's not.
It seems like he's going to, you know, he's a tough one, Don.
Yeah.
I think this guy's going to cruise for a cool eight.
Absolutely.
Everybody's, you know, my dad wrote me today, he was like, can't wait to see Trump drown in
a toilet, fill of his own shit.
I was like, dad?
How about a hello?
Oh, happy holidays.
I'm just, everyone is just losing their fucking mind.
That's how I wake up.
Jesus Christ.
I just, I just want to get home for Christmas.
I want to, I don't even know if I do.
I want to stay in my mom and dad's spare bedroom.
I don't want to talk to anybody.
Sure.
I, I mean, I'm at a point, your parents have a spare bedroom.
Yeah.
That's nice.
I'm staying at the casino hotel myself with my wife.
I'm out.
I've got some vouchers.
Don't act like you didn't want to stay at that fucking casino.
No, I'll stay at the casino.
Yeah.
No, I'm staying in the spare bedroom with my mommy and daddies.
And I'll tell you, dude, I'm regressing, I might ask for toys for Christmas.
I just want to get, I want to get back to an age of innocence right now.
Yeah.
I can't deal with this.
I'm not going to do it now because it's too much up top.
We'll do it on the next one we record.
But I, way beyond Kevin Hart, I got to talk about Miss Lena Dunham.
And I'm going to bring that into the next podcast we record.
Which, well, here's the thing you've been keeping up.
No, I, I stopped keeping up.
I'm going to have you watch a brief video with me before the next podcast and we can get
going on that.
Here's my question though.
Yeah.
For the sake of the fans.
And we love you fans.
We really do.
What do you do?
Do you get it all out in this one and then give them a lighter overall pod on the next one
or do you split up?
I want to bring some fire into the next one.
Okay.
Usually by the second we record, we're like, the floors looking clean, Joe.
Oh, God.
Lena Dunham.
We had a request to get away from the songs and I'm happy too because I can't think of
one.
So let's get on with the show.
And on.
Very good.
I miss those ones.
I miss the simple ones.
You just got it.
So you don't miss it anymore.
Ooh.
Kitty got claws today.
Let me take you over, if I may, to Pat's movie corner.
I've still seen just a tremendous amount of stuff due to a really depressed Thanksgiving
break that I had where I just didn't sleep and just watched things for four days straight.
So I'll never really catch up, which is good, but at least I'm not lacking for any.
I saw the new picture.
I see it there in your screener pile.
Maybe you've watched it.
Nope.
Okay.
A little film called Boy Erased.
A lot of boy movies this year, a lot of boy movies, a lot of young drug addict movies.
They all start Lucas hedges.
Remember when they all started Lucas Haas?
I do.
Remember when he was the hot young thing in Hollywood?
He's still acts now.
He might have been in that, that first man, I think he was in, he's in something like that.
Boy Erased is a movie set in, I want to say the early 2000s, they don't really make it clear,
but it's about gay conversion, which is very timely because, of course, if Mike Pence takes over
the hot seat, which I don't believe he will, I think he'll go down with a ship, but he
strongly wants there to be gay conversion therapy.
And that's really cool, that a guy that thinks that is the second in command to our nation.
But Boy Erased is a well -performed and extremely depressing little film that really, these kinds
of movies used to be called Movie of the Weeks.
They used to start John Ritter, like you've never seen him before.
They used to start Judith Light a long way away from who's the boss, whatever.
But now they're making it to theaters, they're Oscar bait.
We can talk about the Golden Globes, too, if you want.
The movies that are getting nominated for Best Picture are fucking hilarious at this point.
My only frustration about nominees are that I can't believe that Fred Armas and special
got nominated.
Nothing against Fred Armas and I think he's a talented dude.
That special was like, that literally came off like he rolled out of bed and walked down
the street to the nearest coffee house and just said whatever popped into his head.
And this fucking thing is nominated for special comedy special of the year.
What a nannette I assume.
No.
No?
No, no.
No, no, nannette.
I honestly, I didn't even think of that.
He just said that.
I can't believe that didn't get nominated.
It must have, Joe.
Whatever I saw that was nominated, maybe it's just like the top specials on Spotify.
Maybe that's what I saw.
You're not getting out of a Golden Globes without nominating the net.
It was not now.
It was Gaffigan.
It was Armason.
It was Pat Noswald.
It was Chris Rock and it was Chapelle.
All right.
Maybe she didn't get nominated.
But maybe I was looking at a wrong thing.
I don't know.
I would have.
Sorry.
Go ahead.
Boyer Ray stars.
Of course, Lucas Hedges.
Lucas Hedges is the son of Peter Hedges, who wrote my all -time favorite book, What's Eating
Gilbert Grave, which became a pretty great movie as well, starring Johnny Depp.
He also wrote.
I didn't like the sequel much.
What are those grapes, Gilbert's eating?
Yeah.
I didn't think it had the weight of the first one.
I couldn't agree more than the mom, you know, ate more of the grapes.
It's basically a movie about grapes.
The book about grapes.
Yes.
His parents are played by Nicole Kidman in a small, desperate plea for an Oscar.
You might as well be like that Wayne's World scene where they flash Oscar clip over it while it's playing.
Right.
I thought she did not ring true in this role as kind of an uptight turning the other way, religious
mother.
And Russell Crowe, twice the size he was in gladiator, bigger than he was even in what's that movie,
The Nice Guys, playing like a pastor.
He really put on some unnecessary weight for this role.
No, he didn't put it off for the role.
They show you the guy and he's kind of heavy, but it's kind of like when Jonah Hill played that normal guy.
And it's like, oh, so you didn't put on weight to play this guy.
He's about half your size.
But I just, I ordinarily wouldn't care.
And I thought Russell Crowe was really good in this movie.
Kind of the best I've seen him in a while.
But it just occurred to me, if Nicole Kidman put on Russell Crowe's weight,
Nicole Kidman wouldn't act.
No.
That wouldn't happen.
No, that's a fair observation.
You know, as much as we want to pretend everything's changed and there's no double standard,
give me a fucking break.
Any actress puts on Russell Crowe's weight, then she becomes into like a character,
a character, a character, like a Kathy Bates.
She's not a leading man anymore, leading woman.
Boyer race, let's get to the point.
It is him and a gay conversion thing.
He's there nine to five.
The guy running it is played by Joel Edgerton, who was a good actor,
who also directed.
And it's well done.
You know, it's about the hypocrisy of these places.
It's about, you know, at the end, there's really moving stuff where it's like,
I'm not going to change.
I can't change.
This is who I am.
You have to change or else we're done.
Right.
You have to change because I can't.
And if you won't, cool, I don't need to see you anymore.
Right.
And I found that to be a very kind of refreshing.
I found people give too much of a shit about their parents, basically.
I like whenever in a movie somebody's like, great, then we'll just go our separate way.
Sure.
People act like you can't do that.
You can do it.
Pretty easy.
Sure.
I thought there was a lot to like.
It was well acted.
But it's super depressing.
And it goes to even darker places than you might be thinking.
But check it out.
All right.
I haven't watched any of my screeners.
That is a huge pile of screeners over there.
Actually, I watch one.
I watch it one.
And I will tell you what it is.
It is a little picture called Deadpool 2.
Okay.
I cracked and I watched it.
I have to say I was wrong.
For not seeing it initially, it's very, very funny.
It's so funny.
It's really, really funny.
The action sequences are awesome.
Yeah.
I love that it's relentlessly violent and unapologetic in that sense.
And it's just fucking funny.
It's just like it just really hits the tone of humor that really works for me.
Where it's edgy, but it's not like trying to offend you.
Yeah.
And you know, it's, it's, it's just great.
It's just, it's a really, really fun movie.
My favorite line is when he, when he's like behind the bar and she's like,
can I get you anything as a, you know, as a joke during like that shootout.
And he's like, yes, I'd love a cranberry orange vodka.
I believe it's called a baby's.
Please don't make me say it.
Reynolds is a really, really funny dude.
It's funny.
He co -wrote this one.
This one seemed to be stretching a lot less for the aren't we shocking bits.
It just kind of nailed its tone.
I think better than the original one did.
I've talked about it on here before.
I think it's one of the best comedies of the year.
I guess that's why they sent it out to try to be nominated for best comedy or something.
I don't know.
Now they did this PG -13 cut called a very Deadpool Christmas.
Freddie Savage has been directing the last few episodes of my show and he was doing a lot of advertising for it.
I don't understand how it's possible to make a PG -13 cut of this movie.
I also don't get the point.
I guess there are kids out there that want to see Deadpool.
But I mean, they reshoot the fucking movie.
I think they have some new scenes.
It's getting a theatrical release.
I think this Fred Savage bit where he's doing the McCulloch in an Uncle Buck thing,
and he's doing the Princess Bride thing.
I think those clips might be in the movie.
I guess it's probably an experiment and they'll see how it goes.
But I know from when I saw Deadpool and Deadpool 2, the audience was half kids.
I don't think anybody gives a shit about the rating system.
I mean, this is a tough one to bring your kids into.
I mean, I don't think I'd bring a young kid in to see this flick.
I guess so.
Especially since I don't have a young kid.
I could really get trouble for that.
I think parents only care about sex and nudity, and there wasn't much in there.
There was a long sex scene in Deadpool 1.
I don't recall any sex in Deadpool 2.
My parents anyway only cared about sex.
Yeah, I guess so.
I mean, there's a lot of like, guy gets shot in the head.
Sure.
Anyway, whatever.
What I loved about it is that Deadpool 1 eventually went that same way
of every one of these movies with like a 45 -minute climax of them fighting the villain.
Jokeless.
Right.
And Deadpool 2, they kept it real brief and it was still funny.
They kept all the action stuff still funny.
I don't know.
I was a big fan.
I had a dream that I watched this with my mom the other night.
Like I rewatched it with her.
And the whole time we couldn't focus on the movie because she kept going,
Wolverine, he's the one with the claws, right?
She just kept asking me that.
Uh -huh.
We couldn't get anywhere.
Anyway, good flick.
Sounds annoying.
I watched a movie really based off of the Facebook page and like 90 people saying that it was
everything from cute to really good to really funny.
Folks, I didn't feel it was any of those things.
It was called The Christmas Chronicles.
Starring Kurt Russell is.
That looks pretty stupid.
Johnny Old St. Nicholas.
But, you know, Heather and I are like, let's watch a Christmas movie.
And we're trying to pick between all these old classics.
And I'm like, let's try to watch a new one.
And, you know, we sat down and honestly, ruined a night.
Burned one of the few nights we had to spend together.
I was just like, this sucks.
It's lame.
It seems to be made for very small children.
There's a scene where he sings an Elvis song in a jail cell and he's got like
Bruce Springsteen's East Street band with him but not Bruce Springsteen.
And they're all in jail with him and they get up and play a song.
I was like, this is fucking stupid.
Yeah.
When I first saw the advertisement for it, you know, whatever website I was on, it was like
it was like Kurt Russell plays the coolest Santa ever in the Christmas Chronicles.
And the look of him in that outfit made me laugh.
And it wasn't what I thought it was going to be.
Which made me think they should make a movie like this.
This is my idea.
I'm saying it here.
So this is copyrighted.
Okay.
It's not, but go ahead.
Well, yeah, but I say it.
You can't say I have proof that this is a dated recording.
Someone could go, I never listened to this stupid podcast.
Well, whatever.
Here's my idea.
It's like, I wanted it to be, I'm not bad Santa.
Right.
But I thought it'd be funny to do like a Hancock version of Santa.
Where he does the right thing.
He delivers the gifts, but he's got a grump, you know?
And it's a lot of like son of a bitch.
God damn it.
You know what I mean?
Like he's hitting little hit.
And I kind of thought that's what this was going to be.
And it's not.
It's, it's just him playing Santa Claus.
It really, anytime it starts to do something interesting,
they yank the reins back and don't do it.
But like he's, you know, he keeps seeing himself in like storefronts and on billboards.
He's like, I'm not that fat.
I cut out carbs.
I cut out carbs, whatever.
And you're like, okay, you're circling a funny area.
But you have to then go forward into it and do something with it.
It just felt lazy to me.
It was produced by Chris Columbus, who has made many, many,
much more entertaining films in this vein.
Well, in many much worse films to be honest.
I mean, I don't need to, I don't need to put this next to bicentennial man to say that.
It's okay.
I said, no man's one of the worst movies ever.
But it tried to be in the spirit of like an adventures in babysitting or all, you know,
home alone or grandma or rent, right?
His, his film version of rent.
Rent is a nut.
Yeah, he's mad about it.
Similar echoes.
But the guy used to really thrive on kind of like edger family entertainment.
And I was happy just seeing his name even though he's just a producer on it.
But it's kind of a bummer.
The kids are sort of cute, but not, you know, like kids never get to be,
have any edge to them at all in movies anymore.
Kids used to be like, they'd cuss.
You know, they were like real kids and now kids are just scrubbed clean.
Well, the problem is, is now when they do that, it's like the big zany hook.
Yeah.
Like they did it in the new Halloween.
Right.
And it's like a bunch of normal kid, not normal, but like, you know, milk toast kids that you don't care about.
And then they have the one kid that's like, you better shut your fucking mouth, you crazy bitch.
The only kid I care about, yes.
Yeah, everybody's howling laughing, you know, like like it used to be that you had kid,
you had a bunch of kids that were just like that.
They acted like kids.
This kid looks like Joey Lawrence, the older brother, and it starts with him stealing a car.
And you're like, no, no, no.
What?
Oh, he's stealing a car.
I like that he's stealing a car.
It's not you wouldn't if you saw it.
It's like the most g -rated stealing of a car ever.
Sure.
You know, just I don't know.
I didn't like the movie.
Many did.
It's cute.
Maybe if you watch it with kids, it's a different experience.
But it starts out with this kind of cool concept that they see.
She's watching an old video of her dad who died in a fire.
And she sees this like hand come through right as the video ends.
They're going up to bed.
And she's like, it's Santa.
He's real.
And just again, that's kind of like, oh, cool.
They caught a little proof of him on tape.
This must be where this is going or what?
And just anytime something interesting would be started,
it would immediately be killed.
Well, I never understand what these kids focused Santa Claus movies is.
There's always the debate about whether he's real or not.
And I'm like, what do you do when you're four -year -old or five -year -old
who undoubtedly believes in Santa Claus watches this fucking thing?
Yeah.
And goes like, wait, what do you mean?
Is he real?
Well, they debate it in this one.
And I felt the same way.
But then again, I'm like, well, Santa's in the whole movie.
So it must not be.
Yeah.
They must not care because he's here.
But yeah, it sucks.
Little surprise for the movie corner this week, Pat.
Go ahead.
I'm going to go ahead and talk about the cool kids.
Oh.
I've caught up on the show as far as I know.
At least as far as Hulu has let me.
Yes.
I've rewatched several episodes.
I'm very, very, very much enjoying the show.
I find it very charming.
I find it very funny.
I'm not just saying that because you're my friend.
My favorite episode so far was the latest,
which featured a storyline of David Allen Greer
dating a much younger woman.
Yes.
And the investigation led by Vicki Lawrence
to see if she was a gold digger or not.
I can't believe a young attractive woman would like Hank.
Yes.
Yeah.
It's called Hank Rob's The Cradle.
For some reason Hulu chose a thumbnail of
little children at a roller skating rant to be the picture
for the episode, which that was a mistake.
Yeah.
Although I think sometimes they change the algorithm
to appeal to what the viewer wants.
Right.
Yeah.
They might have thought you wanted a little girl's
roller skating party.
Right.
Very funny scenes though with Sid and the little girls.
I like those scenes a lot.
They're great.
Yeah.
It's great.
I love the thing with Sid where he's like,
I ain't saying she's a gold digger,
but she ain't messing with no.
Well, you all know the song.
Yeah.
It was really funny.
I really enjoyed the show.
And I look forward.
Is there going to be a Christmas episode?
There's not just because of the nature of Fox.
Fox gets preempted by football a lot.
So they were just like, don't even worry about it.
We did a Thanksgiving episode.
And we will in the future if we get another season,
which, you know, we came back.
We yet we have yet to slip our lead -in slips in the ratings
and we don't slip.
So I think we have our own fan base.
We're doing well.
I.
Not that I wasn't from the jump,
but I really enjoy the cast now.
We get along great.
And I'm having a blast.
I hope it lasts a long time.
And I appreciate you saying that.
This morning, I noticed on Twitter,
it's got Brett White at Decider,
which is a great entertainment website.
I've spent the last few months cackling with the light every Friday
with the cast of the Cool Kids.
So of course, they made my best of 2018 list over at Decider.
This is such a weird, wonderful show.
Oh, great.
Probably the only top 10 list we'll make,
but I urge you to check it out.
I think we're hitting our stride.
And my favorite episode of all,
the Zodiac Killer,
with Ed Bagley Jr. airs this coming Friday.
Although, wait, we're airing...
Are we caught up?
Is this airing tomorrow or next week?
No, next week.
So then at aired Friday,
you missed it,
but watch it on Hulu.
Margaret dates the Zodiac Killer.
I think it's where we really hit our stride,
and all the ones still to come get even better.
So check it out.
I appreciate that, Joseph.
Of course.
I saw a picture called,
Can You Ever Forgive Me,
starring Melissa McCarthy?
Here, it's very good.
Another Oscar screener.
It's really entertaining.
I mean, I guess it says a lot about me
that I almost always like a movie or show
where the lead character is a raging drunk.
Melissa McCarthy in every scene
is just drinking from a large tumbler of straight whiskey.
I heard somebody told me
it's a film reminiscent
of the earlier works of Woody Allen.
Yeah. Well, I mean,
it's New York and, you know,
it's not, you know,
certainly from a language and content standpoint,
it's a lot rougher than Woody Allen.
I was, yeah, it looks a lot darker.
But I think you just see Manhattan
and people in sweaters
and you think of Woody Allen.
You know, New York in the fall.
Gotcha.
Melissa McCarthy is obviously
a very gifted comedic actress.
I have written a sort of drama action thing
that I would love her to do at some point.
Because I always sense she had more inner
and she's an incredible dramatic actress.
She is so good in this movie.
And Richard E. Grant,
who you definitely recognize,
but he was in With Nail and I.
He was in The Adventures of Ford Fairline.
Who's he playing there?
He's the old British guy with like the Big Teeth.
Wasn't he in Ford Fairline?
In The Adventures of Ford.
Richard E. Grant was big in 80s movies.
I remember there being a British guy with Big Teeth.
And for I think you think of the Wayne Newton character.
I know the difference between Richard E. Grant and Wayne Newton.
Thank you very much.
All right.
But he, I think,
should probably be up for Best Supporting Actor.
They make an amazing team.
I was, I was thinking of Wayne Newton.
Yeah, Wayne Newton.
No, he was, he's been in a ton,
but he was in Logan recently.
But he playing Logan.
He was in Hudson Hawk.
Who's he playing Logan?
I think he's the villain in Hudson Hawk.
Logan, he played...
Striker?
No, that was...
Doctor Rice.
I don't remember characters from Logan.
I'm sorry.
But yeah, you know him from Hudson Hawk
or you should.
Everybody loves that film.
He was in Garfield, a tale of two kiddies.
And now there's a classic.
But he is great in it.
It's...
He's been around.
He's been a character actor for years.
I know and love him from With Nell and I,
which is a very funny comedy, British comedy.
I played Dr. Jack Seward in Bram Stoker's Dracula.
LA Story.
Oh, he's the main doctor in Dracula.
Yes.
That like Renfield bites eventually.
Okay.
The guy is going to get nominated.
He's very good in this.
But basically it's about a woman who's very lonely.
Lizard their cat.
Very difficult around people.
Not a people person.
Big drunk.
Her agent is Jane Curtin who looks better than she did on Saturday Night Live.
40 years ago.
She looked incredible.
Jane Curtin is her agent and she's like,
I can't get you work.
You won't play the game.
You're...
You know, you won't go out and shake hands.
You won't be nice.
I can't get you work.
And she starts selling to make money for cat medicine.
Forgered documents, like forgered letters from famous authors.
And it's a very interesting story.
Really that aspect of it, even though that is the plot.
It was not super interesting to me.
It was just kind of watching this really,
these two very difficult people hang out with one another.
Richard E. Grant and Melissa McCarthy.
I really enjoyed it.
And I will close us out with a documentary I watched called
The Power of Grace Gole.
And this is a documentary.
It is the complete comprehensive history of He -Man.
It covers the toys.
It covers the cartoons.
It covers Shira.
It covers the live -action movie starring Doth Lungrin.
And Frank Langella.
It covers the reboots.
It takes you all the way through He -Man.
All of it.
It's made by huge fans of the brand.
The interviews are awesome.
It's really fun getting to hear Frank Langella talk about
doing playing Skeletor and talking about how it was one of his favorite things
he ever did, even the movie bombed.
If you're a fan in any way, shape, or form of He -Man,
it's very nostalgic, very fun, brings you back.
Very, very enjoyable documentary.
And it's just the movie or the whole phenomenon.
No, no, no.
It's, as I said, ten seconds ago.
It covers everything from the cartoon to the toys.
Well, then he said Frank Langella.
I was like, okay, you know.
Well, that's part of it.
And part of when they talk about the movie,
they interview Frank Langella.
Okay.
And then at other parts they interview other people.
Do they interview Orko?
Orko's not in it.
He apparently got me, too.
Oh, no.
Yeah.
He was going up to the woman who played evil in on set
and saying, you want to see what's really under this little cape?
Yeah.
And I believe he asked her to be his Orko at one point.
He did do that.
He kept referring to them as magic dicks.
Oh, no.
It was a mess.
Anyway.
But check it out.
It's a fun nostalgic ride.
I got a quick scary stuff for us.
Sure.
If you don't have these box sets,
you need to go get them.
They've been out for a long time.
It's nothing new.
But a slept on rendition of the Twilight Zone,
often as the 80s reboot.
It's an awesome reboot of the show.
There were three seasons.
The box sets are beautifully crafted,
very comprehensive stuff on them.
I mean, not a ton of bonus features,
but everything you could need.
There's commentaries from Harlan Ellison,
and one of them talking about how he punched the director
in the face for ruining the story.
Wes Craven directed a bunch of these.
The cast are awesome.
There's a great one with Robert Klein.
There's a lot of great ones.
Season one, front to back,
I could vouch for as a very good solid season.
Seasons two and three come together in the same pack,
and you're going to have to scavenge a bit more
through those to find the good ones.
But they do exist and they are worth owning.
But it's just a rendition of the Twilight Zone.
I don't hear people talk about very often.
And the sets, as I said, are beautifully crafted,
and there are a lot of fun to watch,
especially on a sort of a rainy day,
you know, when you can sit in front of the TV
and watch a good spooker as my dad used to say.
Spooker sounds like a word you're not supposed to say,
but I guess I'll allow it.
He was referring to horror movies.
No, I know, but it just,
don't you think it sounds like something
from Mississippi burning?
It didn't feel great coming out of my mouth.
I don't have anything,
but I've never seen any of the new Twilight Zone.
They're worth seeing.
All right.
Pat, let's get to our movie, I guess, right?
Sure.
Now, did you watch it as I strongly urged you to
with the Joe Bob Briggs commentary?
No.
Oh, no, I'm sorry.
I was watching other shit for the goddamn movie corner,
and I said, I can't rewatch your movie.
I've already seen that we're going to review.
I don't have time.
All right.
You could have watched just the Briggs segments.
I know.
I got to be honest with you.
I don't remember you urging me to do that.
I did.
I was on Thanksgiving.
Thanksgiving.
Thanksgiving day.
I wasn't with you on Thanksgiving night.
Thanksgiving night.
I was texting you.
I'm watching it.
The first movie is Texas, Chancellor.
I watched this.
You were like, I will.
No, it's really great.
You should check.
I thought you were just saying the marathon you should watch.
I didn't think you were saying this specifically.
I mean, not look.
I could go back to the texts.
I'm not going to.
I miss Reddit is my point.
Joe Bob.
This is his favorite, not only favorite horror movie,
but favorite movie of all time.
And he's never been able to share it
because it's still on some band lists.
The Texas chance I'm asking.
So like he was like TNT wouldn't let me show at this place.
We couldn't get the rights, whatever.
So this is the first time he's had the rights to it.
This night on shutter was called like dinners of death.
And it was Texas Chainsaw.
The original Hills have eyes, which I did not enjoy.
I think I prefer the remake.
It had blood rage, which we discussed.
And I watched.
And was insane.
And then dead alive to Kashi Miike,
which was also insane.
I'll save those for future movie corners.
But I have now watched both marathons in full.
The original one was 13 movies.
The second one was only four.
And there's another four movie marathon coming up on Christmas,
which I have to hope will have your silent night,
deadly night, you're, you know, all that kind of stuff.
Speaking of silent night, deadly night, Emily Florence Simpson texted me
and let me know that she met the actor who played the killer
in the first film.
No, no.
Talk to him about the podcast.
Yes.
Gave him our info.
And she said that he did show some interest in potentially coming on.
So we'll see if we hear from him.
That would be awesome.
I've only seen the original, but I loved it.
And I want to see the others who have seen all of them.
Texas Chainsaw, you could tell Joe Bob,
you could tell it was his favorite movie.
He talked, he made the movie almost three hours long with his jump -ins.
And for me, especially watching alone,
I like Joe Bob interrupting at times.
I'm a pussy.
If you can still say pussy.
And I enjoyed it.
I enjoyed the hell out of here in the anecdotes about the set.
Some of them you knew, some of them were new.
Some of them were about Toby Hooper.
Tobes.
But the best is he goes on for about 20 minutes about how Toby Hooper got such a rough,
rough, rough deal in Hollywood.
He was obviously a gifted director, but this movie made everyone think he was insane
because who else but an insane person would make this movie.
And then when he finally got his big break on poltergeist,
he said everything you have heard about Spielberg directing this movie as a lie.
Joe Bob had tears in his eyes at various points,
because it was clearly very close with Toby Hooper.
And basically a guy from the LA Times dropped by the set while Toby was finishing up
the shot with the tree crashing through the window.
And it was a very difficult shot.
And then up front doing a little second unit stuff,
that's in a round was Spielberg, because he was by the set.
Right.
They write this article that Spielberg's directing the movie.
Toby is troubled by this.
He takes out an ad in variety and he's like, this is a fucking lie.
Right.
Spielberg, I'm directing the movie. It's my movie. He's a producer.
Of course he's on set.
Right.
Spielberg got pissed at him because he said,
I'm supposed to be producing a couple of movies right now.
And if they see that I'm on your set and busy,
and they think I'm directing, then it looks like I'm not
in being involved in my other projects.
Can you just be quiet about this?
Let's not call any attention to it.
And the more I learn about this Spielberg.
I know.
Not a great guy.
All right, I'll drop it.
Then years and years later when the coach was clear,
Spielberg comes forward and he's like, just so you know,
I didn't direct it, but it was kind of too little too late.
And Toby Hooper's career was resigned to like a Masters of Horror episode here and there.
That's a shame, man.
That's a great shame.
It was, you know, tragic but a fascinating story.
He goes on about it for about 20 minutes.
If you're a fan of Poltergeist as I am,
it's definitely worth checking out.
Well, I think the Spielberg influence on that movie is that he wrote it.
Like Spielberg doesn't usually write.
He wrote Poltergeist.
Sure.
So of course it feels like one of his movies.
And he's owed a lot of its success.
But it's also way more vicious than most of your Spielbergs.
And that's where Hooper comes in.
I agree.
Texas Chan saw Joe, this isn't one of my favorites.
I think it's a very effective movie.
But I think you love it a lot more than I.
What are your thoughts on it?
I find the film to be a masterpiece in horror.
I also thought Toby Hooper was a lunatic until I saw he did other things.
Right.
When I first saw this film,
the best assessment of it I've ever heard is the reason the movie is so effective
is because it feels like you're watching a documentary.
Yeah.
It feels real.
It's one of those movies where you can't imagine seeing an interview with any one of the actors.
Yeah.
You're like, there's no way these are regular people.
They're all nuts.
There's no way.
They went through an asylum and got people to do this, you know.
I forgot how deeply annoying the big guy in the wheelchair is.
I mean, just almost impossible to watch.
And he stresses me out.
That thing where he's going.
The gun it goes.
Boom.
Chuck.
Yeah.
Boom.
Chuck.
And he just keeps doing it over and over.
I love the film.
It's one of the most disturbing and frightening films I've ever seen.
But it's horror at its best.
My opinion on Good Horror has always been.
If it good horror is constituted by one element, you can't escape.
That's what makes a good horror movie.
The second you can say during a horror movie, well, why don't they just do this?
They just go over there and then it'd be done.
Yeah.
Then it's not scary anymore because then it's not believable.
But anytime the setting is, you can't escape.
And in this town, that is done, or in this film, excuse me, that is done by the reveal
that the family basically is running this town.
Right.
And as sabotaged these kids and they have nowhere to run and nowhere to hide,
they can't get away from this thing unless it's just by pure luck,
which is how the lone survivor at the end finally gets away.
It's just a brilliant film.
And it's incredibly, incredibly frightening.
I love it.
I love Texas Chainsaw Massacre 2 for very different reasons.
It's a very different film, but I think it's great.
Let's do that on here, too, because we should do 3, too, because 3 is awesome in its own way.
Never seen 3, and 2, I only saw when I was 10, and it rattled me up so much that
even though I own it and have owned it for a while, I cannot bring myself to watch it.
It messed me up.
If you just sat through 1, I don't think 2 is going to give you much problem.
That's true.
I've seen one probably every 5 years I'll watch it once.
It's just not one I feel I need to revisit, because it is so disturbing.
I like it very much.
I understand how unbelievably innovative and terrifying it must have been seeing it in 1970 or whatever.
But yeah, there's an extra element to it that makes it uncomfortable, like all the stuff in the van at the beginning,
when the guy is cutting his hand and all that, just like there's an evil that comes off the screen.
The ending with leather face chasing, and then at the end dancing around in the sun with the Chainsaw is just fucking awesome.
The stuff where they're trying to bash her head and he keeps dropping the wrench to hammer into the bucket.
Yeah, that's upsetting.
I mean, my god, that stuff's just not fun.
And you realize the grandfather is still alive.
Yeah, you think he's just a corpse they're keeping around, like Norman Bates style.
And then in that scene, you realize he's still alive somehow, just barely hanging on.
It's rough stuff, but obviously, you know, the movie has earned its spot near the top of the horror pile.
I just prefer to watch an exorcist, a poltergeist, a Halloween, whatever, because there's more fun to them.
You find there's more fun to the exorcist for some reason I do.
The exorcist scares me on a visceral, like organic level.
It gets in my bones.
Texas Chainsaw, I find frightening and alarming, but I can sleep after I watch it.
The exorcist will get in my head.
I hear you.
I guess because I don't believe in demonic possession and I do believe in crazy freaks by the side of the road waiting to murder people.
Texas Chainsaw affects me more.
You know, one of the sort of basic rules of filmmaking is you want to have a good opening shot.
You want your opening shot to be interesting.
Yeah.
First shot in the movie.
And Texas Chainsaw nails it because first you get that scroll.
The text scroll.
The John Lara cat is narrating.
John Lara cat.
And it's very disturbing.
And then that goes right to the shot of the rotting cow head on the post.
Yeah.
And the camera pulls out from there is the report plays of like the grave robberies or whatever it is.
Right.
Just a fucking awesome movie, man.
Just a masterpiece in horror.
And that is why Tobay was one of the masters of horror.
He was.
It was.
I watched his life force, which is thought to be his like lost classic.
And I just thought it was real stupid.
I love life.
The nudity, of course, was great.
And I had some fun with it.
Well, you're all boy.
What is the matter?
The nudity was good.
I don't know.
I'm certainly never going to hit a point where I feel I need to apologize for enjoying nudity.
I just don't.
I'm not saying I know society wants me to.
It's not offensive.
I just mean like in a world where porn is falling out of the trees.
How do you still get this excited about boobs in a movie?
There's something about it that feels different.
It feels naughty or somehow.
Oh, right.
Because porn has become so mainstream.
Now you go to the theater to see any movie.
You almost never get nudity.
It doesn't happen.
What you're seeing now more often than not is dicks if you're seeing any nudity.
Because everyone's all excited now that you can show dicks.
But you certainly not seeing your a list actresses naked,
which used to be a real thrill of going to the movies.
I like that the lady and cam showed her boobs.
I like that too.
You remember in the MTV movie awards.
They went up and did five minutes with Travolta and Hugh Jackman.
Where they all talked about how excited they were that Halle Berry was going to show her boobs and swordfish.
She's up there with them.
And she's like in just three days you'll be able to see my boobs.
This was a different time.
And it wasn't that long ago.
But that was the selling point for swordfish.
Everybody there opening night was there to see those boobs.
There was a stretch of Halle Berry pictures where that was like the treat of all treats.
She just was taking it off and everything.
She was the hottest woman on earth.
Absolutely.
What's she doing these days?
She still is.
I mean she looks exactly the same.
What's she doing now?
She doesn't get a lot of acting work.
She had a network TV pilot a few years back.
It didn't really connect.
And she's in the occasional movie that doesn't really go anywhere.
She was never the strongest actress.
I mean I think she might have won for Monsters Ball.
But I'm not sure that was deserved.
I think it was.
You take that away from her.
I've always liked her.
She's great in that.
But all I remember is the sex.
I don't remember anything else about her performance.
I was real jealous of Billy Bob watching that.
Sure.
Christ.
Billy Bob and another life should have been a gas station attendant.
I mean, you know, Billy Bob has been with the...
I mean, I know that was just...
Angelina Jolie for years.
Jesus Christ.
She wears blood around her neck.
I mean, clearly she's got some sort of hick thing or something.
I mean, Pitt's more of a hick than he likes to let on nowadays.
Pitt's from Missouri, baby.
He's trash.
Yeah, Pitt.
It's funny.
I was watching a little of interview with the vampire the other night.
And it's almost funny now going back and seeing Pitt play that character.
Yeah.
He's good in it, but like...
He's blind.
Seeing him be like the guy that's like,
I was one subman.
Yeah.
You're like, you're like,
now it makes way more sense when you're guy being like,
gentlemen, and I want my scalps.
Yeah.
Well, I think the closest to Pitt for a long time,
now he's a little different.
But the closest we got to him on screen, I think,
was the true romance character.
Yes.
Because I had long heard that him and Aniston were just raging potheds together.
And they're back together.
They're not.
Yeah.
Did they just get...
Are they?
I think they just got remarried or something.
No way.
They're back together.
That would be the biggest news story in America.
It's in all the like us weeklies and all that shit.
It's on the cover.
Then if it was real, we would have heard.
We have heard.
It's in the magazines.
It's in us weekly.
It's like they're back.
They're dating.
They're dating again.
I'm going to look this up.
I'm telling you, they're dating again.
Pitt, Aniston.
Look it up.
It's not happening.
She made a statement about her relationship with him recently.
I believe that they are dating again.
Wait, she's reportedly pregnant with Brad Pitt's baby.
Yes.
There you go.
It says YouTube.
Dude, I'm telling you, they're dating again.
Look, say what you will about us weekly.
It's always right.
They've never seen an inaccurate thing in there once.
It can't be true.
With the news that his bitter divorce battle has gone
from nasty to downright ugly.
Brad Pitt is seeking solace and a romantic trip to Italy
with Jennifer Aniston.
And he's bringing along his daughter, Shylo too.
All right.
Maybe that happened.
There you go.
You delivered that in almost Dennis Miller style.
Dennis Farina.
No, it sounded like Dennis Miller.
All right.
I just thought this would be bigger news.
I just can't buy them.
American doesn't care about Aniston and Pitt together again.
I just saw Miller on a camel.
And they played a clip from his new special.
Not a fan.
I know you're not.
But the joke made me laugh.
Because Kimmel is like, I hosted the Oscars.
He did this joke.
He goes, didn't watch the Oscars this year.
Instead decided to take a solo canoe across the Atlantic
with a rabid fucking wood chuck in it.
He makes me laugh.
I'm sorry.
Anyway, folks, that's our show.
I'm your Joe.
What can I say?
It's a pleasure to be here.
I'll be in New York.
January.
I believe it's 5th, 6th, 7th.
It might just be the sick.
Whatever that Friday Saturday is.
I think it's Thursday too.
It might just be Friday Saturday.
It's Saturday.
I got them comedy club doing shows.
In March, I'm headlining Vegas at a bonkers.
Tush.
It's called bonkers.
Where's bonkers?
I forget where it is.
But I'll get more details.
Is it after I wrap at my job?
Because I'll be right out there with it in March.
You're right.
Later early March.
I'm done late.
I'm done March 10th.
I think.
And I'll be also returning.
Yeah, it's after March 10th.
Right.
And then I'll be returning to the Moon Tower Comedy Festival in Austin, Texas, shortly after
Vegas.
All kinds of new shit coming up in the new year.
I got other announcements to make, but I can't make them yet.
So that's it for me.
Joderos, a comedy on Instagram.
I'm at the Patrick Walsh on Twitter and Instagram.
Watch the cool kids on Friday nights.
You're going to love Margaret Date's Zodiac killer.
It's got a horror bent to it.
Check it out.
We're on Fridays at 738, 30 Central or whatever the fuck that is.
And Hulu.
Next week, Joe, we're doing...
Well, let's not announce it.
Okay.
Fine.
Thanks, all.
Enjoy your holiday seasons.
We'll talk to you next time.
We'll talk to you in L.