I'm here for Bet Rivers Online Casino and Sportsbook with poker icon Phil Helmiut.
And now thanks to the excitement of Bet Rivers, I'm also a Slots icon.
That's great! And a same game, Parley icon.
Cool, cool. A Blackjack icon, a Moneyline icon.
A roulette. Take it from Phil Helmiut.
If you love games, Bet Rivers is the place to play in Bet.
Bet Rivers.
Games on.
Must be 21 plus in present at West Virginia.
Void were prohibited. Terms in conditions apply.
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gambling.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 -plus gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberler offer not available in all states
terms apply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
This is a Headgun podcast.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to a new episode of We'll See You In Hell.
Anyway, yeah, I guess it's time to get on with the show and in doing so on.
Now, I'll tell you, folks, that was the best one of the day, and it was the third one,
because this...
That was more controlled.
It was a more controlled vocal performance.
This fucking whore equipment that I have keeps fucking up, but anyway, it's like our fourth
time restarting the podcast.
Yes, the previous two, I would say were more raw emotionally, but they were a little
a little pitchy dog.
I got to be honest.
A little pitchy dog.
That one was just beautiful.
I think we can all agree.
All right.
Let's just get into this movie.
We're doing the boba duck.
It's on Netflix.
Pause if you need to get it set up if you want to do this with us.
We're at 133 .45 something like that 46 literally right at the beginning. Let's do it. One two three play. One two three play. All right. The movie is
F .C. The Baba Duck, Duk, Baba Duk, Baba Duk, Duk, Duk, Duk, Duk.
What was that song originally?
Shoopy Duk.
Oh yeah, Shoop.
Shoop by the salt and the pep.
Shoop was number one on the hot 9 at 9 in St. Louis for a record breaking like 40 weeks every
Monday that did a hot, or no every night that did a hot 9 at 9.
It was the number one for like 40 weeks until finally if I'm not mistaken it was knocked
knocked out by everything I do, I do it for you by Brian Adams.
Might have gone the other way.
Oh, so it wasn't like number one on a rap station.
It was just number one.
It was my local pop, you know, hot music station.
Yeah, when I was like 10, 11.
My station's growing up.
Didn't mix musical genres at all.
It was always just like, there was the rap station,
there was the rock station.
There was like the bullshit pop dance station.
My big, like the big hot night and ninth station,
and you know, it would go from like,
loser by back would be a huge song for a while,
and then it would go into like more like a TLC type thing.
It was pretty all over the map.
That's jerking me around too much.
Yeah.
I like a lot of variety, I'm sorry.
I don't dislike it, but you know,
I don't need it every other song.
I understand, you know.
Here's the reason we're doing the boba duck today.
Okay, number one, consider it a new classic, I would say, in the horror.
It is.
Field.
Number two, it's a very well -reviewed and recognized film.
And most importantly, number three, it's a cool 90 minutes, so we're getting right in
there.
We're going to do the evil within, which was recommended to us by our still friend and
ex -producer, Ken Hanley, but we were having problems with Amazon Prime, streaming, and whatever.
So here we are now, back on Netflix, doing the old bobbidook.
And we have both seen the bobbidook.
I saw it when it came out and liked it quite a bit, although it wasn't passionate about
it.
And Joe, it seems like you did not like it.
No, I think it's a good film.
I think it's very well crafted, but I didn't like it.
I don't like any of the spoiler alert if you haven't seen this I don't like any of these movies where in the end
It's like it was just on her head. I don't I'm never a fan when that's the explanation of everything
You like it to actually be a
Boba Duke from another realm. Yeah, okay. Yeah, well the goddamn movies called the Boba Duck like make the fucking thing or
Thing it's real make it is Boba Duck an actual thing like a leprechaun was invented for this movie
I think it's made up for the film. I don't know. If you feel like looking it up, I won't. I can look it up. Hold on. I got my phone. All right, my computer right here. All right. Let me look it up.
History of the bomb. But my money is on that it was made up for this film because the children's books they probably made it up. That's true. Yeah, like she gets the mysterious children's book on her porch. Right.
right. And then it turns out she just wrote it. Right. But you know, I mean, I keep hearing
good things about Annabelle creation. Maybe we should go see that and talk about it.
I would very much like to see that it's supposed to be great. People I really like, we're
saying on Facebook and such that it's like unbearably scary. Really? Yeah. I saw Annabelle.
It sucks. Okay. I mean, I've heard it sucks. Yeah. The original Annabelle is, it's, you
good. But I think what I'm hearing is they did with this, what they did with Weija origin
of evil, which was to call them, or they, they took, they kind of learned from the mistakes
of the first one and said, okay, let's do a prequel and make this right. I tell you folks,
they say there's no original ideas in Hollywood, but we got an origin story for a board game.
Yeah, you know, just one year ago, the Babadook. Now here's an article that came up. The Babadook
is a frightening, fabulous new gay icon. Yeah, what is it? This is from the New Yorker.
Fears perhaps, the greatest compliment that Twitter's gay conglomerate could ever confer is
is that an adjective as any for the internet's unlikely new queer icon of Babadook. I think
I think on RuPaul's Drag Race, one of the drag queens was like a Babadook inspired, but
it was post movie Babadook.
Oh, I see.
Okay.
It's not like the director of the Babadook was inspired by RuPaul's Drag Race.
So they're not saying the actual demon, no, is again, no, all right, let me make you a little
more sense.
Folks, to kind of time stamp this week's episode, and I know how much you all love when we
get into politics here, but we are kind of
that sweet spot between maybe heading into nuclear war in the next week but also maybe returning to
the time of the Nazis. It'll, but it will be probably one or the other. I do want to say this, folks.
If you are a Trump supporter at this point and I wouldn't have always said this in the beginning,
although let's be honest, I kind of would have. You are a racist. You are supporting racism if you
support Donald Trump. That's simply true. The man has been asked point blank. Do you renounce
the KKK and he refuses to answer the question. So you see, is his that actually happened? That's
true. I can show you several videos where people are like, Mr. Trump, though, surely you don't support
white supremacy and the clue close clan. Right. And he refuses to answer the question. He's like, I
don't know what that is. I'll look into what these groups are and I'll get back to you. And then
And yesterday they're all asking him and he pretends like he can't get out of a room
essentially.
Oh boy.
But he won't answer the question because he knows that his bread is kind of buttered
by these types of people.
Oh boy.
So before in the early days you could have said, Hey, I like Donald Trump because of money
or jobs or whatever it is and you would have been wrong there too.
But there was a lot of anger like, Hey, we're not racist just because we support Donald Trump.
Now however you are.
So, you have to make that decision and I'd like you to make it quickly because it seems
as though we're headed for an end of the world type scenario.
It's enough.
I mean, we're flying closer to the sun than I thought we would and quicker than I thought
would.
Yeah, yeah.
It's a bit of a messy situation, a car drives into people who are protesting Nazis and
Donald Trump goes, Hey, you know, people are people are full of hate on many sides here.
Well, I hear this was my takeaway from that, um, and you'll disagree with this.
Now, step, step lightly, Joe, what do you got? No, no, no, I'm going to step.
When he said there's hatred on many sides, I, I interpreted that as him saying, look,
there are many groups that are doing terrible things and we need to stop it because there's
Antifa on the left. I think that's the name of it, right? The far hardcore left organization.
That isn't what he meant though, and he said that my point is he said this isn't about Donald Trump or Barack Obama
No one thinks this is about Barack Obama. That's how he starts his speech. I thought he didn't he didn't say it that that
Clearly he went like this. He just goes. It's been going on a long time long time. Not Donald Trump
Not Barack Obama. It didn't even make sense. No, he just was saying words. Yeah, and that's how he kicked it off
But so anyway, I think what he didn't say at any point was I
Disapprove of not season white supremacy because you can't and that's terrifying
I think that well that in combination with what you're telling me now. That's very very upsetting
They I mean they they let me answer it but upon my initial review or just watching that I was like
Oh, he's just saying like there's a lot of hate groups and that's never good. I get that
I think he just he won't he won't lose one vote like he won't
upset anyone who's like if you supported him from the beginning
Whatever you've ever done in your life whether you're a Nazi or not. He loves you because you think he's the best and he agrees with you
Now what is now what about the daughter came out and said
Evac's
And said white supremacists and Nazis have no place here now here's this is what upsets me a little bit instead of people saying
to her. Thank you, Ivanka. Thank you for hearing us. Thank you for saying something your
dad wouldn't. Everybody just takes this flip and like, hey, tell it to your father, dumbass.
Yeah. And it's like, well, how do we make any progress that way? You've got somebody on
their team that's like trying to recognize and assimilate with what the opposition is saying.
And then the opposition just like pisses on her. I hadn't seen it that way. But I do agree with
what you're saying. She is at least trying to differentiate herself from her father.
But at the same time, all these Republican senators and such who are like, Hey, I don't
agree with this. There's an element of covering their ass to it as well. She's married to
Jared Kushner. Right. You know, I mean, if anyone's ever looked like a Nazi, like, I mean,
he screams Nazi. She's covering her ass because she's hot and she can work forever because she's
the hot blonde, she'll go to Fox News and do whatever she needs to do.
But Ivanka keeps trying to play it on both sides, like she's real progressive and understanding
and it's, but she's not.
And that's fine.
But I agree that when she says, hey, I don't think Nazis are good, we shouldn't then say
fuck you.
Well, you know, my friend Steve Bern had a really great post on Instagram where he said it's,
it's, it's uplifting to see people from all sides condemning what's right to condemn. And it was,
it was Ben Shapiro, who I'm not a fan of, it was Bernie Sanders, it was Obama, it was,
I don't know, Bill O 'Reilly or somebody like that. But it was, I don't think it was, Bill O 'Reilly,
but my point is is like, he found people that you would say are extremely on one side or the other.
Right. All saying the same thing, which I thought was nice and I thought was a moment of like, yeah, we need a little more of that
We need a little more of trying to hear one another
Especially if we think our president is is a in any way a white supremacist or Nazi sympathizer
He is, you know, so but I'm I'm not saying he's not I'm just saying right we need to under I'm saying if you even think there's an
Enkling of that right
You need you both sides need to be listening to one another
there a little more, you know?
Great.
So, you know, it's just a mess of a time, folks.
We're not here to talk politics.
No, we should get off it.
No one's, I don't think as ever said,
I really enjoyed the political discourse
on this week's episode.
Never not once.
But I mean, to bury your head in the sand
is not helpful either.
But we're just trying to bring you some laughs,
so we'll get off it.
I mean, I don't know.
I kind of just feel checked out from people,
but I've always felt checked out from people.
Sure.
Why could you not?
So I mean, you know, that's what upsets me the greatest.
I've had, and I'm saying this with all honesty, and this is for the people that are now
saying that we're swinging too hard for one political team or not, because we're not.
We're just recognizing bullshit and calling it.
I've had equal fear of saying things publicly from either, from both sides.
I've had equal fear, and this is coming from somebody by the way, not that I ever like
to just brag about my stripes.
I've earned my stripes in this,
I've been attacked by online mobs
right of super, super hardcore conservative people
that were trying to get me fired from gigs and whatnot.
So I've been down the fucking road, all right, you know,
and I still didn't say,
fuck Donald Trump when the election came around
after experiencing something like that.
So I feel like I'm pretty up the middle as you can get
And I just think it's a shame that people feel scared to voice their opinion because of backlash from either side
I think that sucks and again, it's because nobody is talking nobody's discussing everybody's just attacking
Yeah, all the time and when you do that folks, you know better than the bobbah duck
You know better than the goddamn bobbah duck and that's what brings us back home
I just got Google Jared Kushner, by the way, and surprisingly found out the hottest new
gay icon really, Jared, I mean, I could see it in a hate fuck scenario for sure.
I'm kidding. Same with Ivanka. I mean, really, what more delicious hate fuck than Ivanka
Trump, because she is lovely, but she is so horrible as well.
I don't, she doesn't do it for me.
She's too like symmetrically hot.
Yeah, I get that.
When, when a girl's too like, superfically like hot,
I'm not like, don't like a gal with a broken nose.
Yeah, maybe missing one of the front teeth.
And between us, folks, he likes giving her that broken nose.
But that's between them and the friends don't ask questions.
That's not true.
I feel like I need to say that at this day and age. That's true.
Let me let me take us into a past movie corner because I feel like I've seen some things real quick before you do
Let's give an update on where we're at in the film. Yeah, because we really have not paid any attention
I don't know at this point. It could be porkeys. I wouldn't even know. I haven't even
No, it was porgy. There wouldn't be talk, but she has I be caught up in the plot of porkeys the mom has gotten the Bob a duck book
The Bob a book. Yeah, and it is
Uh, unfinished. The story's not complete. There's blank pages in it. And then as the movie
goes, the pages get filled in. She doesn't know how it's happening. Um, so that's where
we're at right now. She's gonna, she just pulled out a vibrator and she's gonna have vibrator
sex. It looks like a phone in the bed. Well, maybe she's got a huge vagina. I don't know.
You want a vagina? Uh, who the hell knows? That is a hell of a vibrator buzzing. Uh, or maybe
Maybe she's just got a truly, like a great elasticity
to her vagina, where she can take in something
that looks like an ivory tusk.
Her vagina is like the blob.
Just kind of a, you know, things kind of ooze into it.
And by that we mean it eats men alive.
Oh, I've never seen the remake of the blob.
I own it, I love it.
I own it, I haven't seen it and I will watch it
and maybe we'll do it sometime soon.
Truly a great remake written by Darabont, right? I believe so and your boy Kevin Dillon is the star. Kevin Dillon
Is not my boy, but yes, you were big. He was your favorite entourage member, right?
There was a turtle man myself. I mean, honestly, like it's hard to pick
There's no one has less charisma than E
Right, no one is less like engaging than E except perhaps for Adrian Grenier, right?
At least Dylan brought something which was the Joey from Friends rip off dumbness.
Right.
He had at least had a character.
Turtle's character was like he was slightly overweight and they all called him fat.
Then he got skinny and then lost even that tiny thing that set him apart.
I'll tell you man, and this is a hard shot across the bout at Grenier, whoever the hell you
say is.
Grenier.
I got nothing against the guy but when you're that good looking and you're on a show
that's was that popular and you're not working for as far as I can tell that's right you must really
not be that great I mean that guy that guy should have been a fucking movie star right look like
goddamn Marlon Brando I had a girl I dated for a bit years ago was a stand -in on entourage and all
the guys on entourage were so short that they had stand -ins that were female so they were all just
It's like super short, except for Dylan,
so and Piven as well, super short.
So here are the stories I heard.
I met Piven once.
Yeah.
Yeah, he's smoking a big cigar and drinking brandy.
I met him once.
That's him to a tee.
Yeah.
I watch Gross Point Blank this weekend,
which I'll get to.
And he's so great in that.
I used to love him as a character actor
and then it just kinda went nuts.
It's too much when he's the main thing.
Yeah.
I want him as the pharmacist in singles.
That's exactly right.
He's great in that.
Yeah.
Yeah, you know, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I, and I
This is allegedly, folks, but, you know, yeah, now you said to me, tread lightly earlier,
tread, tread lightly here, you're, you're, you're potentially allegedly, all right,
Kerenye, they were warned, Kerenye is going to try to hook up with you, but beware, he only
does it in the body.
and he stinks. And he like smells. He has bill. I've heard this about Robert Pattinson as well.
These are all Hollywood alleged rumors, folks. Oh my God. I didn't know I was doing a podcast with
Kathy Griffin over here. Harvey Levins in the couch this week. No, I generally don't do that,
but entourage, I think, did as much bad for our country as the alt -right is doing now, frankly.
It's, it's, look, look, and that's the sad thing about right now.
Everybody's scratching their head going, how could this happen? How could this happen?
I was talking to my friend Keith about it today. You, you, you, you fucking watched Jerry Springer.
You know, you watched reality TV. You watched flavor of love. You celebrated a culture
that prays the Almighty dollar and that left no decency or humanity or dignity to anybody in print
or on television or whatever. This is what it led to. It led to this. Here we are. Here we are.
It's a fucking sad truth, but here we are. You know, as much as it sucks, I'm like, the country
kind of fucking brought it on themselves, man.
Sure.
So what I've enjoyed about this time, the most,
is just kind of an embrace of death.
And if it comes, it comes.
I've always been a fan of the apocalypse.
I've always, I have.
I always think, I always thought hitting the reset,
but would be nice.
I would like to wake up every day
and my only concern be, I gotta go scavenge.
I gotta find dinner.
Sure.
I wouldn't mind if that was my only thing.
No, yeah.
Let's get out of this bullshit rat race for us.
It simplifies your life immensely.
That's why I get Jeremiah Johnson,
you ever see that movie?
Robert Redford?
No.
You know, he goes out into the woods
and he's like, I'm just gonna live in the woods for a while.
What do you hear else, and did it?
And he went through Hawaii and grew his own fruit.
Yeah.
And just was like, I'm just gonna live here
and grow my own food.
Sounds incredible.
The, I mean, what is this rat race we're doing?
Like he lived like the goddamn
character he played and planted the apes like for real. Yeah, you know, so I
Don't know. I just you know. I wouldn't mind
I wouldn't mind living in a culture where you could murder somebody
I tell you we're pretty close
show your white
Murder whoever you want. I'm not white
You're close enough. I'm I pass as they say which I find it I can race this to her
I thought that's racist to say that.
You pass.
That's a racist thing to say.
No, not to mean that if you're not white, you fail.
I mean, you pass.
No, but I remember in the 90s,
there were those commercials on MTV
where it'd be like a black lady who was light skin
and she'd say like, she'd say, yeah, people come to me
and go, well, you don't look black.
She's like, what does that mean?
I feel like that's the same thing when somebody goes,
will you pass for white?
It's like, yeah, that was considered really fucked up
like 30 years ago.
All right, you know, so I'm not saying I'm not mad at you. I'm just saying like I'm just making fun of the statement
But the I wouldn't mind. What do you check on us on a census other other? Okay. I always check other all right fuck them
That's what I say, you don't need to know
But I'd say I I wouldn't mind a world where it's there's a tribe over there. We don't like them very much
If you want to, sure.
What is this tribe you're speaking of?
I'm just saying my tribe is my tribe,
and then there's another tribe that maybe I don't like.
Okay.
Or a guy's a dickhead, or, you know, trying to take my shit.
The tribe is another name for the Jewish people.
Oh, I'm asking you to clarify.
That's not what I'm saying.
I know you're not, but I'm asking you
for your benefit to clarify.
I'm not, no, but I'm non -denominational tribe.
I'm just saying, I'm saying in the apocalypse of world,
when you break down into tribe living right and you're saying you want to kill the members of
Tribe called for us who I got to see live they were fantastic just a couple weeks ago how much
of the old stuff how much of the new stuff give it to me baby you know it was a very good mix I
think the new album hangs with the old I mean I love the new album so the new album is in my opinion
in the true fourth album.
I felt like the Love Movement and Beats Rhymes in life
had their moments, but sounded like Beats Rhymes in life.
It sounded, but it wasn't them to me.
It wasn't them.
It sounded like a collection of stuff
that they would have used on other albums.
Sure.
And the Love Movement, the same.
I feel like that new album to me is the true fourth album.
It's what should have came after Midnight Marauders.
It's really fantastic.
I mean, it's so rare in this day and age now to get like that.
Oh my God, an album is releasing.
I'm gonna sit and listen to it.
Like, you know, I I think of like the one one great when I had recently was when the new deaf punk came out
And I was an amp sure damn and I like got stoned and listen to it on a bathtub when it came out. I hate that album
I love it. I hate it loved it and still love it
But I'm a deaf punk album and then I found out why okay, and I'll ruin the I'll ruin deaf punk for you go ahead
So I found a YouTube video allegedly no, this is true
This is this is absolutely true. I found a YouTube video that was like basically like here's why deaf punks
Not so great and it would play the deaf punk song and then it would just play the song they sampled and you would slowly start to realize like
Literally all they did was take like a good loop and just put a drum beat behind it. Okay
Then all of a sudden they come up with this new album and I like to get
I did it and I'm like well, this doesn't sound like deaf punk to me
Yeah, why are they doing this and then I find out oh because they hired a guy like a guitar player songwriter
Who's in the band so they hired a ringer who essentially and very obviously in my opinion wrote the goddamn album
And then this not you tell my guy from a chic
Well whoever that guy was they brought in they had a bunch of guests and stuff
Yeah, no, but like if you look at the like liner notes for the actual songs not like the featuring Julian cats a blanket shit
the real liner notes. They brought like another dude in to the fray and like suddenly they have
this whole new sound that's based on like live music versus samples and it's like, well why is
that suddenly happening? Oh, this guy did it for you. So now you can play these things as you
stand up there in your robot helmets. Well, look, it's getting on everybody. Yeah, punk album, but I think
as far as like pop music goes, it's great. And especially if you're stoned in a bathtub and Amsterdam.
Sure. Sure. I was just in Amsterdam. I know you were. Yeah, but yeah, that big kind of like exciting record release thing
It happened so infrequently now and especially where it's good and I think that's not just because good music isn't coming out
But because we're just getting older and we care about less and less
But what what what what we're even talking about the guys on this subject
Deaf punk before deaf punk
Oh, Tribe Called, Tribe Called, that was an album where it was like the night it came out.
I like cranked it and was like, this is fucking great.
Yeah, it's a great album.
I would rank it amongst their best.
I think it's actually a better than Midnight Marauders.
I'd put it quality wise next to the first two, but I also think Midnight Marauders is a great
record.
I also saw folks missy misdemeanor Elliott at FYF, which was actually she's still going
by misdemeanor.
Well, I mean, I don't think she said misdemeanor, but it's in some of the song, but you were
yelling it.
You were yelling it.
Well, that's just because somebody was robbing me at the time and I was yelling at a placement.
But it was very good.
I was very good.
I was hoping Tim Belan would come out.
I was hoping Ludacris would come out.
My favorite guest verse of all time is Ludacris on gossip folks and not far behind
is Ludacris on one minute man.
We didn't get that and there was a lot of periods of time where Missy would leave the stage
for like five minutes.
I think she has some health issues.
She does?
She's 46 which is very, I wasn't expecting.
Is she in good shape?
Because she lost all that weight.
She's in great shape.
She couldn't have been more delightful, more charming, more funny.
But she's got it.
What are her health?
She had an amazing choreography.
I'm gonna look it up, but she had health issues
because she would leave the stage
and they'd show like clip packages of her career and stuff.
And you'd be kind of like,
there's an hour long set, Missy, like we wanted to see you.
But all in all, it was a great show.
So you're sick shaming her right now.
I'm not sick shaming.
I'm gonna look up what she had.
But this is, honestly it was my highlight
of the three -day festival.
This is gonna be the theme of this episode.
It's just constantly reiterating and clarifying
what we're actually saying.
Yeah, well you have to know she has Graves disease. Oh, it's no good. That sucks. Do you know what that is?
No, I just know it's not good. I would hate to have my disease have the word grave in it
Graves disease. You've got the end is near syndrome
Graves disease happen. You've got a case of the headstones
Graves disease happens when too much thyroid hormone is produced a condition called
hyperthyroidism. This higher thyroxene level can greatly increase your body's metabolic
rate, which may affect weight, mood and energy. Rapid heart rate, tremors, double vision
and somnia, enlarged breasts, muscle weakness. Hey, ho, stop right there. I'll take it, Doc.
Okay, but you won't die from it, right? President George HW Bush and First Lady Barber Bush,
also suffer from great disease. Maybe they got it at the same party. They all shit at the same
cake or something like that. But you won't, it's not like you're gonna die from it. It's just
gonna make your life. I just saw her perform live. She's fine, but I think it flares up at times.
Sounds to me like a Lyme's or a Crohn's. Crohn's. Well, I think you can die from those though. Crohn's
I think is a shitting disease and Lyme's I think is a tick disease. I only know about it from the
a lady from the real world.
I only know about Crohn's disease
from the lady who's law and I used to know
who always talked to me about how she had Crohn's disease.
And she was on the real world?
No, two different women.
Two different women.
I'm gonna go back quick here to the film.
Yeah.
I don't even remember this Barbie party.
Jesus Christ.
No, I remember this part.
It's not a Barbie party.
It's a birthday party for a little girl
that the kid is kind of friends with.
And this is the scene where all the other moms who are well put together, and this
mom is like run ragged, that's part of the idea of the character.
She's there all disheveled and all the other moms are kind of being like, oh it's up
with your weird kid.
This is when she's like, oh I have nobody in this world except my child and my child kind
of hates me.
He also does walk around in part of the movie with a sequence gold cape on which I don't quite
understand why and they might have explained it and we talked right over the goddamn thing but
I mean from my experience with kids a lot of them just wear capes and shit sometimes it's like
their kids. This is a gold sequence cape. It's very like James Brown. It's a very ripped tailor. Yeah it's
I keep choice.
So, let me take you into Pat's movie corner, why don't you come on inside with me.
I saw Atomic Blonde.
How was it?
Charlize Theron.
Well, it's essentially 12 music videos end to end.
It has an incredible soundtrack featuring some of my favorite music, New Order, Depeche
mode, Bowie, Queen, etc. It's the soundtrack is impeccable. The action is fun. It's very
John Wickish, but with a lady. Okay. And I love John Wick. All right. And I was entertained
throughout. And still I have to give you a butt, folks. It's not good. Well, neither is
John Wick. That's right. There's John Wick. It's just fun to watch. John Wick's kind of like
a trash classic. Atomic Blom was along the lines of a John Wick too. It was very entertaining,
and it was basically just Charlize Theron being a shed out of people with an amazing soundtrack
which is enough for me these days. And there was an amazing lesbian sex scene between Charlize
and some other woman. Really? That I just absolutely loved. And that's why you, Pat, was arrested
for jagging off in the movie theater. I wasn't the guy who jagged off
in the emoji movie, but I did an atomic block.
Yeah, yeah.
What else have you seen?
When I say jagged off, I mean,
I was watching an episode of the David James Elliott
maritime drama Jag on my phone while I watched.
You remember Jag?
Yes.
Yeah, I do.
I never watched it.
Terrible show.
I have a, when it's, when you're done, I have a...
How about that David James Elliott pull?
There was an argument against the effects of weed
that I just pulled that David James Elliott played Jag.
I have, when you're done, I'm gonna read this list
because I wanna...
When I'm done?
When you're done talking about your movies that you've seen.
Oh, what is your list?
I'll tell you when you're done.
Do you do your thing first?
It's how long it was fun.
This Boba Duke kid's really screaming.
And his mom is screaming,
as the kid is screaming, the mom is screaming,
just be normal.
The Onion AV Club, which is a side I always enjoy, sometimes their TV reviews drive me insane
because they say like a middling episode of such and such, or a substandard episode of such
and such, and they give it an A -. And it shouldn't upset me, but it does. They have like blinders
on for certain shows. Sometimes these are bad shows and they won't back off. The AV Club is all
that's kept me in Twin Peaks at this point, okay, because they keep giving good reviews
to the episode.
Yeah, they're really great at that recap ship, but sometimes man, like what they decide
to give everything an A2 drives me insane.
But that's neither here nor there.
They just released, because it's the 20th anniversary, unless always do huge on these sites, toward
the 20th anniversary of 1997, they did their top 20 movies of 97.
but on this list, much to my shock, frankly,
and much to the commenter's shock was number one,
Jackie Brown.
Oh, that's great.
And it honestly made me a little mad
because I think of that as kind of my own personal.
But we've talked about on the show many times.
That and like about Schmidt or ones that I hold very dear,
a simple plan, as like the world hasn't caught on.
So to give it a number one, I appreciated it,
but they also had on the list as number two face -off.
Oh, for Christ's sakes.
So I've always loved face -off,
but I hadn't seen it in 10 years,
and last night I was like,
they're gonna call this number two,
like let me watch this thing.
That's a fucking insult to Jackie Brown.
I'm halfway through face -off,
and of course I'm loving it
because it's undeniably entertaining,
but it's real stupid.
Yeah, real face. Yeah, off. I will say
Travolta is awesome in it. Yeah, and cage is unhinged in it great
But Travolta does a perfect cage and cage does
Travolta just as insane as he's been doing cage. He does everything insane in the movie right
And that's not right Nick. It's not right. You can't always be insane. You know, I love you
but I'm halfway through it and loving it,
but number two seems excessive.
They put also, boogie nights at number four.
I mean, what are we doing here?
Boogie nights should mean man to be higher.
You're making me mad now.
Now boogie nights should be two.
Yeah, of course, of course.
I saw, also on this list,
at number 18 was Gross Point Blank.
Another big favorite of mine through the years.
and watch that again, it holds up incredibly well.
You talk about an amazing soundtrack as well.
My dream project is to remake that film with Joan Kusek.
She's in it.
She's great.
But I want to make her the lead.
I would watch that.
Yeah, yeah.
I want to remake every John Kusek movie
with Joan Kusek as well.
Okay.
All right.
I want to see her holding that boom box up on the lawn.
Do it up.
Gross point of blank.
You've seen it, Isa.
No.
Seriously.
I've never, I never saw it.
You would love it.
Why?
Cause it's good, we're gonna do a simple plan,
gross point blank double feature at my house.
All right, you'll be pacing by the end of it.
I want to see, I do want to see a simple plan.
Gross point, I don't not want to see it.
I just kind of don't care.
Not, it's so great.
And what I, what this viewing showed me
that I had not really noticed before was how amazing
Dan Ackroyd is in gross point blank.
You're, listen, you're not reeling me in and be closer
He plays like his, his nemesis in the hitman world and he's fucking great in the movie.
All right.
Okay.
There's no way you don't like gross point of blank and there's certainly no way you
don't like civil plan.
That's a guarantee.
All right.
I believe you.
It's a, I'm just saying a big, a great sales line isn't, you got to see Dan Acroid in
this movie.
That's all I'm saying.
Well, I love Dan Acroid, but I used to.
It's his best performance other than maybe like a blues brothers that I've ever sent.
it. Ghostbusters is his best. Sure. All right. The original. Yeah. How hard does it get blown
by a ghost? No, but he's he's I really believe when I watched the first ghost. I really believe
he is that guy. Yeah, I'm like, I agree. This is a smart nerd that's excited about ghosts. He's great.
Only nominated once for driving Miss Daisy where he was not great. He's in driving Miss Daisy.
He plays her son nominated for an Oscar. Yeah. He had like a giant ass at the time like he was
I was like super heavy, but it all went to his ass.
Yeah.
And he's in like pleated khakis with suspenders.
So he looks like a ouzi.
He looks like Humpty Dumpty.
Yeah, exactly.
And then he's kind of like thinner by Gross Point Blank.
What is the thing in that is, he's like at the racist son
that doesn't approve of Morgan Freeman
or something like that?
He's a little more understanding than most.
But I can tell you, I watched him as Daisy
when I was nine or something, and of course, I liked it.
But it always got kind of a bad rap
because it'd be like do the right thing and significantly better films right about racism like do the
right thing is for me like a top five of all time but I watch drive Miss Daisy on a plane
it's good I'm sure it's good I really enjoyed it it was a really sweet movie like there's just
something I liked about it sure and folks another hilarious podcast called Hollywood handbook
I've been on it twice, but if you look up my first appearance I discuss in depth and it's made up of course how when I was nine years old I
directed a remake
of
Driving Miss Daisy for the hallmark Hall of Fame production company on CBS and it starred
Candy Bergen and Ken Griffey June and I described the plot at length and
And that show forces you in, like immediately out of your comfort zone into like heavy improv.
Right.
And I was really happy with it at the end.
I just kind of started pitching this movie and I was happy with it.
Sometimes improv goes to a place where you hope no one ever hears it.
That's one instance I hope you hear it.
When I did it.
And it's a funny podcast.
My buddy Sean Clements and Hayes Davenport who are two of the funniest guys in the world.
When I did Doug Benson's pitch off show.
Yeah, which is a show where you have to go in and pitch he pretends to be a movie exact and you have to pitch in movies. Yes
He the final pitch is he gives you like
He's like we just got a call here's here's what you got you got a motorcycle you got Sam Elliott you got
Chris or
God damn it my brain anymore Jesus Christ the guy from rush hour
Chris Tucker Chris Tucker and so go you got five minutes come up with a pitch
so I pitched that they remake mask. I think you've told me about Chris Tucker as
the kid. Right I'd watch that. Yeah and he just keeps yelling at Sam Elliott.
All right man look at my big ass head. That was wrong with you. Do you understand the words that are coming out of
I saw a trailer not long ago, they're doing a movie that's basically a mask with the kid from room, yeah, with the kid Julia Roberts. Yeah, it looks. I don't know what
match. Yeah. But yeah, the Owen, Owen Wilson is the dad. I just want to see the face of my son.
Yeah. You know, uh, I don't know why is that a crime. Um, which the movie looks terrible. It
looks like the sappy as fucking thing of all the little rough. And then there's the line where the
kid goes, the kid goes, it takes a lot of work to look this good and like runs his hand through his
It's, I mean, it looks terrible.
I feel bad for the, well, I don't feel bad for the kick
because it's not a real kid, he doesn't really have that thing.
You know, I feel bad for a kid that does have that condition,
but the movie looks like dog shit.
I hear you.
Yeah, it looks bad.
Other than that, I've watched most of this new season
of the Netflix drama Ozark.
I'm really enjoying it.
I used to spend every summer at the lake of the Ozarks
where my dad would lose his job right before we all were supposed to go to Disney World,
then we would cancel the vacation and go to the lake of the Ozarks. It's happened like three
different times. Very sad. But I was like, this doesn't look like the Ozarks I remember.
And the people playing the hillbillies in it are the weakest link because they're clearly LA,
douchebags playing hillbillies. It's not like that true scary hillbilly vibe. That's my only grievance
about the show. I think Bateman is awesome in it. And I think it's well -written. But I kept
thinking like, well, this doesn't really capture the Ozarks and I look it up. They filmed
almost none of it at the lake of the Ozarks. Well, of course they didn't. The show's called
Ozarks, but it just drives me nuts. Well, they never that. They filmed New York at Toronto
was New York all the time. Yeah, they always go. Everything's in Toronto now.
I was on a plane. What did I see? Well, first of all, I watched some WC Fields films. Sure.
You got a favor we don't know about?
Uh, I really enjoyed most of what I've watched on this WC fields comedy favorites collection
that I bought, but I really enjoyed the bank dick most because that dick is incredible.
That's the classic.
Yeah.
That's toward the end of his life.
That was my dad's favorite.
Really overweight.
Yeah.
He's just a goddamn drunk through the whole thing.
I don't have to doubt my mind that he's actually drinking for the entire production.
They surround him with annoying kids, annoying dogs, yeah.
There's a magnificent scene at the top of the bank dick where he comes down from his
bedroom.
He's up there like smoking and drinking or whatever.
And his six -year -old daughter stomps on his foot and he turns and punches her in the skull.
and then she throws, she throws like a vase at him and it hits him like in the
nape of the neck and he goes outside and picks up a potted plant like it's
literally so big it would it would murder the child yeah and he's gonna throw
it on her head I remember I remember the whole thing yeah don't you dare strike that
child yeah it's it's really funny you couldn't do it now you couldn't know so I
I saw that. I loved it. You know, I've watched a few of these WC fields films over the last
whatever. And I've enjoyed them. I watched, you know, like easy money is a very WC field type.
That's exactly what I was thinking. Yeah. Easy money is my favorite danger field movie really hands
down. Now, I do like easy money. Don't get me wrong. Catty Shack is the best use of danger.
But that's not a danger field movie. He's in it. That's not his movie though. To me, it's his
movie. I love everybody in that movie. Well, yeah, that movie's awesome. I mean, the dude
for Ted Knight for Christ's second cat. It's unbelievable. It's magnificent. I don't even
know if you ever did another movie. It's well, apparently he hated Dangerfield in real life.
Yeah. And like, they put him in headlocks and stuff. Yeah. Yeah. But I would take back to
school over his money very slightly. I would accept the argument very slightly. I like easy money better.
Yeah, but I was when I was watching the bank dick
I was like my god like this is the danger field movie right the mother -in -law hates him
Yeah, yeah, she thinks he's reformed at the end, but he's not he's still a scumbag
I
Watch the disappointment room
No, what's that? I've heard a hard move with Kate Beckins. Oh, yeah, how was that? Well Pat?
Let me tell you I felt like the disappointment room was my living room
I did not like it, it was boring, I didn't like it.
Woo!
Yep.
I didn't care for it.
I watched, I started watching the boy,
it started really, what is it about?
Tell me anything about the disappointment room.
Oh, what is it about?
Here's what it is, it's about a,
it's a hard movie, it's about Kate Beckinsale
and her husband and kid, they move into this house.
This old Victorian house, as always, there's a room she can't find the key for.
It's locked.
It's up in the attic, whatever.
She finally gets it, so gets it open.
She starts seeing these sort of ghostly visions of these 18th century people in there.
Just know what's going on.
Luckily, there's a town historian that can explain everything to her.
Who put her head to the town of the story?
Some more?
C .C.
Edgebounder?
No, no.
for once it was not a they didn't it wasn't a black lady for once so it was um it was uh some old lady
and then she's like you have a disappointments room and came back as I was like what is that she's
like you know in the 1890s or whatever the fuck it is they would send if they had a kid that they were
embarrassed by because it was deformed or something they put it in the disappointments room they'd lock
it away in there. Okay. So basically any kid that had any abnormality, they put it in there.
But here's the thing, because the movie is so scared to actually depict what kids they really
would have put into this room, which unfortunately would be like kids with like mental retardation
and stuff like that. Every kid in the history book that she reads has a giant growth on his face.
That's every kid. So apparently that is disappointing. There's this huge
just just just just rush of kids with giant tumor faces being born. They're all putting
them into this room. Goaters. Yeah. And so, um, so, so, so, so it sounds great. So a
discipline, a kid was in the disappointments room. He died. And by the hands of the evil father,
dig this. All right. Let me grab myself. Let me grab myself. The evil father.
Yes. Major dad. I'm not going to be scared. Gerald McGranny. Yeah. I'm not scared of
major dad? No, it's major dad. Yeah. So which by the way, where the hell did they find?
Can I tell you something? Well, there's always these weird connections in the show, but in
that lengthy improv I did about the drive Miss Daisy project, it involves major arguments
because at the time I I elude to a romantic entanglement with Delta Burke and then it led to a lot of
fighting with her husband, Gerald McRainey, on the set.
Okay.
Crazy.
Who has the romantic entanglement with her?
Me.
I was age nine.
Oh, at age nine.
And Delta Burke and then Gerald McRainey wants to shut it down because he loves her.
It's his wife, obviously.
I see.
All right.
Crazy.
He was also great on Deadwood, McRainey.
Oh, so he was on that.
All right.
Uh, I hadn't seen him since major dad.
I didn't know what the hell he's been doing.
He's really good on Deadwood.
All right.
And he's in game.
I'm not coming with him, it's house of cards.
Okay, all right, good.
He's working, baby.
That's good to know.
I also started to watch The Boy.
Again, the same goddamn fucking plot.
It's like a lady goes to a Victorian house to be a babysitter.
Yes.
The boy is a doll, but he's not real, but then he is real.
I just got bored.
I shut it off.
I gotta be honest.
I just didn't care enough to finish it.
But here's what I really wanted to talk about
during Pat's movie corner. It was an airplane to Amsterdam ten and a half hour flight.
Free entertainment as you know you get a little video monitor, you get all the movies you can watch.
Sure. I was so excited. So I'm gonna sit here, I'm gonna watch some movies.
Beautiful. It's late afternoon. You're drinking?
Flight. Yeah, I'm gonna have a few double scotches. Okay. All right.
Drinks were free. And I'm gonna watch some flicks. I can't wait. Yeah.
Now of course there were a few good movies on there that I had already seen because they
were nominated for Oscars and I got screeners or whatever.
Okay.
Aside from the obvious hits, I couldn't wait to read you this selection.
This shit show they provided on this fucking flight.
All right.
Latest in recent.
These are the movies in latest in recent.
Go on.
Chips.
I want to watch chips on a plane.
Absolutely, I'll watch anything on a plane.
Chips, boss baby.
Would not have watched boss baby on a plane.
The space between us.
With what's that?
No idea, space between us.
A lot of these I don't know what they are.
The space between?
Like a Dave Matthews son?
No idea.
The zookeeper's wife.
What's that?
No idea.
Is that a sequel to the Kevin James zookeeper?
Nope, okay.
A dog's purpose.
Oh, that trailer looked hilarious.
That's like about a dog who saves soldiers in Iraq.
No, no.
Dog's purpose is the one where the dog keeps dying and coming back.
Oh, okay.
You're right, you're right.
Allied, which is the only rocket...
Allied's good.
That this movie I've never heard of.
Allied's pretty good.
All right.
I liked it a lot, actually.
Dancer, which was a documentary about, quote,
the bad boy of ballet, end quote.
Well, let me stop you right there because I'm the bad boy of ballet,
and nobody contacted me.
Fantastic beast and where to find them.
Where to fuck them, yeah.
Didn't like it.
No, it was terrible.
Yeah, I watched it.
Didn't like it.
Fist fight.
We talked about it on here.
I would've watched Fist fight on a plane.
Oh, I tried to watch it.
No good.
It is terrible.
Okay, all right.
Inferno.
Try to watch it.
Oh, I never want to watch it inferno.
Not even on a plane, no.
That's the Da Vinci code three.
I watch one and two.
Those movies are fucking dog shit and they're two and a half hours each Jack Reacher never look back
I love the original Jack Reacher. I would have watched that on a plan the sequel is terrible Jack sequel passengers
passengers I couldn't finish silence silence. I saw it in a theater or I would have left
I would have I would have not finished at home. Why him silence is maybe Scorsese is worst. It's terrible
Why him why him I did watch on a plan? I started it. I couldn't finish it
It has moments that are funny, but you don't care.
It's, it's simmers at like a sea.
It's like right at a sea the whole time
and it doesn't really get much better,
but it did pass the time on a plane.
Why him is crammed in the night?
Last but not least, triple X, the return of Zander Cage.
Never even saw the original triple.
Me neither.
We're the sequel.
Now, here's, here's my face.
Diesel are cube.
The third one is diesel because that's why
it's called the return of Zander.
Okay, here's my favorite.
Yeah.
These films were referred to as the collection.
And then when you looked at what the description of the collection
was, golden OD, goldies in modern masterpieces.
So I think, all right, here we go.
Yeah.
Avatar.
Go fuck yourself.
Come on, I hate Avatar.
Body of lies.
By the way, they just announced for the next four avatars.
Yeah.
Gonna have the same villain here, that guy with the white hair.
Yeah, it's dog shit.
I don't think I'm gonna see the other avatars.
I'm I'm definitely not but I am excited Cameron going back to the Terminator franchise Schwarzenegger coming back
Playing doing the story where he is the got the actual human that they use to make the terminus. I'm excited about that all right
Body of lies the only de caprio movie besides the beach that I don't give it shit. Oh with Russell Crowe
I think some movie sucks joy
Joy the story about the woman who invented the mom. Yes
Which killed my project about a woman who was inventing the mop that I have been working on for years, and I was livid
Ready for this. Yes, the chance. I know you've never heard of that Efron. Nope
That's a movie starring James Corden as a Briton's got talent contest. Oh, no
Modern masterpiece. It was referred to wow. I don't I don't like James Corden
I once wrote a bunch of jokes for James Corden because I wrote for something called the Airbnb
be awards. Oh my God. And it was presented to me. Hey, we're in a bind. We need funny jokes. I
was like, no, what if we told you you can ask for any amount of money you want? I was like, okay,
I'll do it. All right. But I was writing jokes about Airbnb for James Gordon. Yeah. Side effects.
The Soda Bird movie.
Side effects is all right.
Modern masterpiece?
No, not at all.
Contagion is a modern masterpiece.
Source code, that's John Hall.
Can't even remember.
Terrible movie.
It's immediately forgettable.
The best of me.
Never heard of it.
Me neither.
What is the best of me?
With this next one's a doozy.
I don't know.
I don't remember what it was.
The internship, is that,
oh, that's not De Niro.
And I like the near one turn. This is with this is Vince Vaughn and
Tony Wilson movies terrible. Yeah movies terrible tried watching it
I was like all right the intern with the narrow by the way perfect plan movie very entertaining kind of sweet
The judge
Bob Duval
Robert Judger is on the lower level of acceptable airplane fair
But I would watch on an airplane. I turn it on I turn it on cuz our boy Creme Holtz the next the lady next
Me was watching it. I saw the Creme Holtz was in it. I was like let me turn it off for girls
I was enjoying it, but in the sapiest, it's not a good movie.
No.
It's very, it's the kind of thing that passes like if you see it with your dad when you're
12 or something.
Yeah.
And Robert is very good.
Down in junior, it's essentially, he's Iron Man except as a lawyer.
There's a scene.
There's actually a scene he makes out with a 22 year old bartender, and his brothers
are like, this idiot, what's he doing?
Then later he finds out the bartender is the daughter of the girl that he's in love with
in the town that he went to high school with. Then it cuts to him hooking up with the mom.
And he's acting like kind of weird. She's like, what? And he's like, I just want you to know,
like, I don't want to commit, but I'm leaving after this. She's like, when you're ready,
whatever, you, you call me and she walks out. And then he goes to himself plus I hooked up with your
daughter. And you're not supposed to at all think like, well, that's kind of gross, dude.
Like I know you didn't know I got the judge as an academy award screener. Yeah me too
Yeah, by the way folks if I can do a quick pause speaking of Bobby Duval I
Rewatched he he won best actor for it
But you want to talk about a great fucking performance and a great fucking movie tender mercies
You ever see that movie? Yeah, God. It's great. He play it's it's like crazy heart was ripping off tender mercies
He plays a recovering alcoholic country singer who's just like trying to get his shit in order, but okay
It's so fucking good.
I watched it recently.
Also, Devall's probably 55 in it.
At some point Ellen Barkham comes in and she's 18.
Ellen Barkham at 18 and like I gasped.
I could not believe how hot she was.
She's hot at 65.
I audibly gasped when I was watching it
and I Wikipedia tender mercies
because I loved it so much
and I learned that on the set, DuVal and Barken dated.
That was like, I'm just gonna pretend I didn't see that.
Oh my god.
I'm gonna pretend I didn't see that.
Another fantastic DuVal movie
that was mentioned on this Best of 97 list,
saw it on theaters at the time, the Apostle.
Great fucking movie.
Now here's my other question about the judge.
Vince DeWolfrio's in it.
Yes.
Why has he been reduced to now only playing the angry older brother and everything?
He also plays insane people like he was in Magnificent 7 as like the crazy guy
Which he does a lot to last two flicks the King's Beach good movie, but who gives a shit
I just don't care very average movie and finally finally in their modern masterpieces and golden oldies collection
The other woman, the other woman, which isn't a modern masterpiece or a golden oldie.
It's absurd.
That's the one with Leslie Mann, right, like Ava, not Neva Lungoria, what's her name that
goes to?
Big jugs, Kate Upton, Cammy Diaz and Kate Upton.
No, no, no, what's your face, face plays the mistress though?
The the girl that plays Will Ferrell's wife in the other guys the like ridiculously hot lady even men does
Avamendas. Yeah, I almost said even longer. What's the other woman? What am I the thing? We're like
It's like fucking
What's your face from
Sleepers in Seattle
Meg Ryan Meg Ryan's like husband or something is gonna pockets my dad is cheating with Avalongoria or something
Now the other woman is Cammy Diaz, I was right, right, Leslie Mann and Kate Upton, and then who's the other woman?
That's the three of them, Joe. Like, I was right on all counts. What are you talking about?
What's the one with meg Ryan and Ava Mendes, where like the husband's fucking Ava Mendes and they're like, we're gonna get revenge.
Well, the plot you're describing is the other woman, but the actresses are not.
Hold on, I'll look it up.
You're talking about the women.
No.
The women has even men doesn't make rise.
Yes.
And the husband's fucking even men does in it.
Well, that's the women.
Okay.
That's what I thought it was.
I haven't seen the women.
And it wasn't even as good as the women because it was just
a lesser cast.
Okay.
And a derivative plot as far as I can tell.
So there you go.
These were the flicks I was stuck with.
And I chose to drink and sleep.
sometimes you have to you know Joe could you because I don't know where we are
time wise why don't you take us into Joe scary stuff do you have something I do
it's just sort of an update on something I was talking about last week or last
episode but the Namco classics finally came out for the Nintendo Switch and it
It does include, finally, for the first time ever, a true arcade port of the slaughterhouse,
which, in my opinion, is really the horror game that started it all.
So that is very, very, very much worth checking out.
You should get your hands on that if you're a horror fan, it's a lot of fun.
It's a pretty wild game, it's a pretty dark game, and I like it, it's just really good stuff.
Are you killing people or zombies?
No, you're a regular guy whose girlfriend gets kidnapped into this haunted house, and
then you put on this haunted mask that turns you into basically Jason Voorhees, and then
you go through the haunted house and kill these demons.
But there's all kinds of weapons you pick up, like a two by four and stuff, and whenever you
hit one of these things, they splatter against the wall basically.
So it's fun. It's a lot of fun. Go check that out. I'll try to think if I have anything else for scary stuff.
I have one and as usual, I don't know if it fits the topic.
Oh, oh wait, I do have a new one though. Sorry. All right.
Let's just go fuck myself. No, no, you do yours. Wax work, wax work records just put out the Creep Show 2 soundtrack. One vinyl.
gorgeous gorgeous it's really just an amazing amazing production of this
thing is it songs or score it's the score by whom I don't know who did the
score but it's good it's got its moments but I would say as a horror fan or as
a fan of Krebshow to it's something every fan should own you just like the
covers so nice it's it's it's an impeccably done cardboard fold I don't have it
yet. I just have looked at pictures of it, but it's gorgeous. It's got an insert in between
because it's double vinyl. So it's got an insert on the inside, like a comic bookie sort of depiction
of some of the Creepshow events. And then the vinyl is themed. So there's an old chief wooden
head vinyl that is blue and brown to match chief wooden head colors. And I chose the raft theme,
which is based on the rap story, which is a clear vinyl with a big black blob on it.
Right. Very, very cool shit, man. Very, very cool shit. They did a really nice job.
Okay. So there you go. There's a scary stuff for you. Okay. And you can tell me
after of this counts for scary stuff, I love the new Queens of the Stone Age song,
which is called The Evil Has Landed. Okay. And it's about six and a half minutes. And it starts out
kind of like psychedelic, crazy. Then by the end, it's like almost like punk, like
they're old shit, super fast, like a rated R type cut. Okay.
Queens of Stone Age. It's like three songs in one. It's incredible. The evil has landed.
All right. And then to make it even more like scary stuff, I'm going to recommend Monster
and your parasol by Queens of the Stone Age. Okay. And burn the witch by Queens of the Stone
it. You got evil, a monster, and a witch. Does this count for Joe's scary stuff?
Well, yeah, it's horror themed stuff that isn't a review of a movie. Folks, I finally did it.
You finally did it. But it's a great single. I'm very excited to see them here at Cal Jam in October.
I like the first single off the new record. I thought it was good, but not great. When's the record
come out? It comes out about two weeks. Okay. But to me, they can do no wrong. I'm very excited
here. I'm excited for it. Now Pat if I can suggest why don't you take the helm and give the people
a blow by blow where we're at in the film while I freshen up our beverages. Oh thank you. Can you
tell me time wise where we're at in the film. God only knows these goddamn movie ones are just
marathon. She's preparing them a delicious dessert it looks like. Yeah the kid is now sunk into some
sort of he looks insane at this point. Yeah. I can't pull the time up for some reason. That's
fine. But we're about an hour seven into the recording. So I think there's only about 20 minutes left.
Okay. Yeah, folks. Joe has to go into a period of not drinking for a full month, very shortly,
like starting Tuesday. And I haven't told Joe this. I'm going to tell him now live on the air.
I'm going to do it myself. I'm under a period of extreme stress, and I find myself turning to
you know alcohol. Not excessively by any means, but just as a way to unwind. And I'd like to
kind of find another means at the end of each day. Not each day, but you know, it gets very stressful,
and it's a good way to kind of like, okay, I know or relax, but I want to try to find another
it means. So I think we're both going to take a week off for
drinking the podcast might get very boring and intellectual.
That's fine.
Going on in the Boba Duk now, I mean, the kid is gone. I remember
finding this movie very spooky set kind of some good jumpscares
and interesting, but I'd still keep it at about a B level. I mean,
I don't understand the people that found it to be one of the best
for our movies ever. I see it on a lot of those lists and disagree. I want to tell you
looking down the line folks. I work at Warner Brothers and I'm doing my damnedest to
get me and Joe into a screening of it. And I think I'll be able to do it. But one thing
I can guarantee is that we will be doing an it episode on the show because I think we're
to see it together so be sure you see that I've been almost caught up on the audio book which is
endless like it's like 48 hours long but I wanted to listen to it again before I saw the new movie
and if I did all this work and the movie is equal to like what that poltergeist remake was I'm going
to be very upset I hope it's good it's all I can say what else is going on you know
in the film. In the film she's hugging some man she's breathing heavily as the
subtitles tell me. I will say I've never been a Game of Thrones guy. That's a
fantasy show that fits into this podcast and what finally helped me was was
the subtitles. This year I turned them on. I don't know if it's a significantly
better season, although it certainly seems that way, because it's about to end. The episodes have
been super action packed, particularly the last couple. But watching it with subtitles has helped
me so much, because I've learned I just don't have a brain for that fantasy stuff. I can't go with it.
I don't understand it. I don't know what anybody's saying. I don't know who anybody is. This has been a
good season of Game of Thrones. I've never watched the show. I mean, are you a big Lord of rings guy?
No, you're not. I mean, I like them. I like them. Yeah, I you might like it. I think I might like it. I don't know, but
Yeah, but they're fine. Yeah, you know, I just
There was I always thought game and throws look cool, but I I was was like bummed that there wasn't more magic stuff in it
Okay, like the magic stuff a magic. It's it there is some, but I want it more. I want it like crazy
Fantasy shit, and it's not that sure
But uh speaking of Stephen King and it um I
Think it was bloody disgusting said that they saw a full scene from the movie, okay, and they said that
The kid nails Pennywise. Okay. They said he's she's fucking on it like it's great
um, I also
Have heard from a few people that have seen it or seen parts of it that it is very scary that is very psychologically scary
It is over two hours, which was something we discussed.
That's great.
And I know I spent a lot of time complaining about time.
I don't mind a long movie if it deserves to be long.
You can't do a thousand page book.
It's like the fucking dark tower is 80 minutes or something.
Well, the dark tower, I think that it...
You should do the dark tower, probably.
I think the it that it is probably going to be
the Wonder Woman of Stephen King movies this year.
meaning nothing's getting good reviews.
The missed series did not get a great review.
Mr. Mercedes is getting trashed already.
I've seen Mr. Mercedes get pretty good reviews.
I watched the first half of it.
By the way, you want to talk about,
I don't even know if they're gonna keep airing this thing.
Mr. Mercedes, I had not read the book at I own it.
It starts with a mentally disturbed man driving his car
into a big crowd of people killing them.
That's exactly what happened this weekend.
And nobody has linked them up.
the first episode aired on Thursday,
since it had happened on Saturday.
What is the airing on?
The billboards say like AT &T .com presents.
Randomly because I do direct TV, I have it
at the audience network,
which usually shows these pretentious black
and white interviews.
Yeah, well, so the pilots seem good,
I like Brendan Gleason.
Well, then it's, I do too, then it's mixed reviews.
Then it's mixed reviews,
because I've seen some really harsh reviews.
The dark tower got fucking trashed.
You know, so I think that it seems to be the one thing that they're doing.
And then the guy just said he wants to do pet cemetery next.
Yeah.
Which.
Oh man.
Pet cemetery is due for remake and honestly, so was it because, you know, a CBS mini series
is not going to be the proper telling of it.
Well, they just wish it wasn't the mama guy unless this is where he's like, you've underestimated
to me. I'm going to show you how I do it. Look, that last trailer I thought was great.
Yeah, it was. I thought it was fucking scary. Yeah. It got me, the trailer got me a couple
times. Yeah. You know, like it, and I think it's going to be way less jump scary in the actual
film and way more atmospheric. I also like to that they've all very adamantly been saying,
like, look, this is not a remake of the miniseries. This is an adaptation of the book. So, I
I think it'll be good, I think it'll be good.
I also like too, they're talking about how like,
there's a lot of moments in the film
where Pennywise does something weird
just because it's disturbing, you know?
Like, he'll just do a weird thing
because it's off -putting, like that to me is what,
what just happened in the bobbah duck?
She just pulled a tooth out?
She pulled a tooth out.
Why'd she pull her tooth out?
Why the hell did she pull her tooth out?
This is what happens when we don't pay attention.
I don't remember.
It's a big thing in a horror of the stir of echoes had a great tooth pull out.
I just sold stir of echoes.
I never loved that movie.
Oh man, should I have kept it?
You hadn't seen it?
No, I just didn't.
I didn't think it looked good.
Stir of echoes is fucking great.
I just sold it unwrapped to Amoeba.
I own it.
I mean, you can still watch it.
It's good.
I just thought it was going to be like mirrors with key for Southern.
I was like, no, no, no.
It came out like the week after six cents is the only reason I got buried
because it was kind of similar.
But I fucking loved it in the theater.
I had seen it a couple of times
and I watched it with Heather last Halloween
and it's one of her favorite scary movies.
To me, it's one of mine.
What's it about?
It's really, really good.
It's one of those where you don't even
really want to say much about it.
But they just do a real good job
of giving you like really likable good people
and putting them in pretty believable, scary situations.
Okay.
It's based on a Richard Matheson story who's a great poor writer. Yeah, I love Richard Matheson and it's David Cap who wrote like Jurassic Park and it is
It's a great movie. God damn it. I haven't seen the sequels, but it's very good. Why did I get rid of that?
I don't know, Joe. I just made an assumption. I was just like yeah, this is gonna be just like another one of these like I know what you did last summer kind of
No, no, no, it's really good really scary. It's kind of a bitch bastard. What'd you get for it? Dollar?
about that. You can get it on Amazon probably for $2 if you want about that. We're at the
part down the Babadook where the mom has become fully evil and she's saying terrible things to her
child like I wish it was you and not your father that died. You're a little baby your six years old
you still wet yourself so now we're in the phase of the film where the Babadook the mom and the
The Boba Dukker one.
She also told me she wants to make his brains pop out.
This woman was woman is a great actress.
She was great in this moment.
Yeah, she is.
This is good.
No, she's good.
She's very good.
Yeah, this is where like the, she's, you know,
you realize like, oh, she's crazy, right?
And she's got the kids, you know,
trapped in the house and she's,
Kid just shot her with a dart now. Yeah, the kid's good in this too. The kid is good. This kid is good. This kid is good.
Watched Hannah and her sisters. My favorite film of all time.
It's fantastic. I love it. Is the eight -year -old Asian girl in the film, SUNY?
probably she is right I don't I mean I don't it adds a real element to it because she keeps popping
up at it and you're like oh boy this is weird I don't Woody Allen looks easily 55 -60 I don't know
she hold on let me see I mean I I'd almost guarantee it I would think so though I mean it's me a
Pharaoh and Woody Allen there's like a maybe nine -year -old Asian girl in it when where who's the eight
I don't even remember.
And also then Woody Allen is writing at an SNL -type show with Julia Louis Dreyfus.
Yes.
And the first sketch, they're like, you can't air this and he's like, why not?
It's about child molestation.
Everyone's doing child molestation these days.
And it's like, wow, this is weird and uncomfortable.
Uh, hold on a second.
This is why man, SUNY PREV, I don't think it's her.
It almost has to, I unless you just was doing it so close to his life.
Oh, yeah, yeah, several Farrell's children are in the film, including SUNY.
Oh, that's really uncomfortable.
That really like, it brings it all home.
Yeah, he's 55, 60, she's nine.
I don't think he was 60.
Look, it doesn't matter.
She could have been 20, she was nine.
Yeah.
It's uncomfortable.
You know, you see how old it was, 1935, that movie
came out in 85.
So he was 50.
Yeah, 50.
Yeah.
Not great.
But there is no great age with nine is my point.
That's true.
Yeah, there is no nine appropriate eight is 81 now.
Joe, can you tell me what what a Alan's actual name is?
I used to know this.
It's like Alan Stewart Conex bird.
Yeah.
The um, I love that film.
Uh, it's got a young John to tour.
It's really great.
It does have a young John story.
And the young Richard Jenkins script.
Yeah, uh, Richard Jenkins, uh, but the great line is they said you can't name names in
in the Chad molestation sketch and he goes,
we don't name names, all we said was the Pope.
Right, right.
Which, and in that movie predates the Catholic scandal.
That's true.
Which is interesting.
There's some great dark jokes in that movie.
It's a very good movie.
It's an incredibly insightful film.
I've never, the reasons my favorite movie is
because I've never seen a movie that is better captured
my own internal dialogue or monologue, excuse me.
It's several characters say things where I go,
I've said that to myself, I get it.
Yeah, when Woody Allen says you're not going to die, you're surrounded by people in restaurants.
Like, it's a very, very accurate.
It's surrounded by people in restaurants.
And it's got great jokes.
It's got great jokes.
It does.
You prefer to crown the misdemeanors.
It's my favorite film of all time.
Yeah, so clearly.
But you do love crowds.
I love it.
It's not my top 10, but I love it.
Loaned to a coworker three years ago.
I said, I'm never getting this back.
Am I?
Went to get it off the shelf last night and realized I never got it back.
a folks Alex you can't learn anything anymore a folks you're giving it away
the mom is now laughing in a distorted man tied her up I think we're getting
to the end for the the sun in here just got so blinding I can't even open my
eyes oh I think the sun in the movie now the sun out the window now this is
heartbreaking the kids got the mom tied up she's saying he's saying always love
you always will and that's somehow is he's telling her he's telling her you got to get
the Babadook out and she's trying to choke him to death now. Joe did you have imaginary
are friends as a child. Now the kid looks like the demon to the mom. Right. Did I have
imaginary friends as a child? Yeah, pretty simple question. I think I did at one point,
maybe one. I don't think I did. I wasn't even popular with my imaginary friends. I think I had one
maybe, but I don't I certainly wasn't like hardcore into it. It was blanket. No
Like a favorite blanket. No, I had a blanket stuff that I called a rue for some reason
I was never given an explanation for that. No, cuz you're disgrace and my parents eventually
Pretend that they accidentally threw it away because I was getting to be like 11
Yeah, but come on buddy, and they pretend they accidentally threw it away
and I found out much later that they just threw it away.
Yeah, every kid's.
The excuse was fake.
Blanket has a weird nickname he's giving it like a baby.
Yeah, that's for Mr. Mom, my woobie.
Maybe it's time we put the woobie down.
Yeah, but that kid was five and I was in my early 40s.
Yeah, 11 is, I mean, that's fingering age.
Not for me, baby.
You're right there.
Unless we're talking about old Uncle Greg.
I don't have an uncle Greg and he didn't finger me, folks.
Sometimes we just do dark jokes to get through the day.
Uncle Greg.
That is a terrible uncle, Nate.
Yeah.
Hey, Greg.
We are right now at the part in the film where she just puked bile and blood on herself.
She threw up blood all over herself.
She's saying you can't get rid of the boba duck.
She just levitated the kid magically up the stairs
She's now chasing after no, I guess the Boba Duck took the kid he Boba took him oh
Jesus Boba shook
Boba duck now the beds bouncing up and down
Sounds like a Saturday night at my place
When's the when's the last time you had sex, Pat last time I had sex was last night
It's nice. Good to see you kids still have the fire. We still do I like to see put not fire with gasoline
You know what I'm saying. Hey, I hear you dude Joe one's last time you had sex. It's been a while
I've been at sex in a while
Okay, oh definitely over a month. Maybe two months. All right. It's been a little while. Okay, you know
It doesn't help that every time I'm on a date, a first date with a girl, I say, hey, baby, my cock is hungry.
I don't think that helps me get closer to getting away.
Why don't you feed it for me, lighting a cigarette.
Or sometimes I go, baby, penis is pussy hungry.
Oh, no.
Like that, and like that baby voice, I'll do it.
Like Frank Booth.
Blue velvet.
I watched Blue Velvet the other night. It is the best. It's great. Um, and, but I was watching
it and it's one of those movies where if you live in an apartment like I do, you're constantly
riding that volume button because you're like, uh, my neighbors must be like, what the fuck
is going on in there. Fuck that shit.
Paps Blue Ribbon. That's why Paps Blue Ribbon is popular this day. Is that movie?
Your boy Kyle McGlock. And then I tried to watch Dune again. I can't stay awake. I can't
do Dune. I can't do Dune. I can't get through that. I watched a Bronx tale again the other
night. I hadn't seen it since I was, you know, 15. It's good. It's not great. It's got
cheesy parts, but I like it. It's good. Yeah. It's a, it's pretty, a pretty good
fellow is a rip off kind of thing. Yeah, it's very Scorsese, like with the way
that he uses the music and everything. And, um, but I do, I do, I do, I've been
shopping my gum so aggressively. I'm worried this podcast is going to be
unlistenable. I haven't even noticed to be honest. That's good. Um, but, uh, it's, uh,
I like a Bronx tale. I particularly like the, uh,
They're just some great jazz palm and teary parts in it and I actually think there's some great life philosophies in the film right you know when he says
when
Cosmo, what's the kid's name Cosmo I think right no
Is it a Cosmo no
Yeah, it is car mod
No, no, it's like his name's like cool thing in a cramer. His name's like collusio and they call him like cause or something
I'll look it up anyway
when he's bitching about the kid that owes him $10.
Yeah.
And he's like, he keeps stuck with me, he owes me money.
And Chaz Palmitere goes, the guy's a bum.
He's like, you paid $10 to have him out of your life forever.
There's just great philosophies like that in the movie.
There is.
There's a lot of nice little one -liners.
Yeah, the thing where it's like you open your door for the girl,
you open her door for her and if she leans over and unlocks
your door for you, you know, she's like something special. Like, you know, like really,
now we all have automatic locks, so it doesn't work. Yeah. Well, it is, it is tough. It is tough.
I didn't say that the film contained modern philosophies. It just contained good philosophy.
Correct. I liked it. I mean, sometimes something that really blew you away back in the day,
you're watching, you're like, eh, well, when I was a kid, all I needed was an Italian actor
Yeah, and an old supreme song playing in the back. That's true. That was that was that was the man for me
I rewatch sleepers recently with Heather and
Fantastic, she loved it for me. It wasn't as great as it was in the day
But it was a really solid really well -made movie with like I just a
Unbelievable cast that's what was killer in that movie. That's a rough flick, dude
It is it is and bacon nails the Pennsylvania accent
Hey bacon is is just fucking killer. I want to recommend something else which is that memory says out of the gross
Philly actually. Yeah, what do you want a place job? Yeah, yeah, it's rough stuff. Bacon is hilarious in the new
Sandberg deal the the new HBO. I want to see that I mean tour to pharmacy. I love both of those the tennis one and the
Biking one, but bacon has some really funny shit in it. Now are you caught up on Twin Peaks completely?
what are your thoughts? I think the the last two have been bad the one two
weeks ago was a true low point when Audrey Horn comes back and is arguing with
that dwarf for 45 minutes. I like that one. Oh boy. If that episode didn't air
nothing would be different. You wouldn't have you didn't learn anything from that.
I felt that about the last five episodes. That one I was like at least like
they're bringing an old character back.
I had been loving it.
I had really been loving it.
And then, you know, last week's the week before,
I'm kind of like, I don't know, man.
What are we doing here?
I can't do this fucking,
I can't do this like in trans Dale Cooper thing anymore.
I can't do it.
Yeah.
And he's not learning anything.
Right.
He understands what coffee is,
but he still doesn't know how to open the car door.
Yeah.
It's just like annoying.
It's like this isn't fun to watch anymore. Not not ours on end. No. I do enjoy the revelation
That the revelations that are happening with evil Dale Cooper
I think some of those are kind of cool
How Bob is like this immortal spirit or whatever. I think that's kind of neat. I do like that Audrey horns back in
I do like I'm not buying at all that
that Ashley Judd wants to fuck the 80 year old father of whatever.
But I like that she's in it and I like that he's in it too.
I mean, like that big discussion about like pie inventory with the waitress there,
where it's like, look, I'm looking at the demographics.
You're not selling the right amount of pie for your budget.
it. If you use fresher ingredients, I mean, this thing goes on for seven, eight minutes.
Well, it's I have limits. I love David Lynch so much, but I have limits. Well, that's
what I was saying to you about the scene where the guy sweeps up for literally five minutes
in front of some reason. I hung in for that. But I do love your line about nobody wanted
more shock. Yeah. I mean, it's, yeah, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, apparently that guy wasn't
playing rock. And I've been saying this for the last few weeks now. It's to a point
now where it's unnecessarily confusing. It gets to a point where it's like, I get it.
You're a surrealist. There's absurdity. I get all that stuff. It gets to a point where
it becomes unnecessarily confusing. And I'm like, I don't understand what's happening anymore.
Because you're mentioning so many characters that I'm not seeing you're having people play
Supposedly a different character than they played in the first show yet. They're doing the same job
I mean, especially for a guy who I like I want to go with you on all this stuff
Mr. Lynch, but I can't I don't remember anyone's name ever
Like I mean to I spend every week kind of being like
What and with Twin Peaks I just want to be lost in the moment
The best scene they've done so far for my money
was when there was that traffic accident
and that woman was going insane, hawking.
Yes, that woman.
And then he goes over and he's like,
what are you hungry?
She starts screaming and screaming.
That performance was so insane.
That woman was so insane.
I was like, this is amazing.
And then when that weird sloth from seven body thing
next we started puking up blood, I was like,
this is one of the greatest scenes I think I've ever seen on television.
That was true twin peaks.
And I also really love I will say this I love that I love the turn of Bobby. I really like it. Yes
I like that. He's Bobby looks better. He looks amazing and I love that he's like now this
straight laced
Like he's a guy that's redeemed himself. I think that's really cool. Yeah, I think it's really cool that
That they have the kid that's going through troubles and like you see like the mistakes of their past and all that stuff
Yeah, I think it's very cool and in kind of a true way that you never see where like the guy who's an asshole in high school
Ideally by the time he's 50 is not still an asshole. Hopefully you hope that new guy who's an asshole is terrifying
But we see so little of him he doesn't register as a villain. Yeah, the guy who killed the the big fat lady in her trailer
And who I believe is all he did is killer because she's alive. I believe that's Audrey Horn's son
Okay, I mean that guy you're like whoa
What a villain what's going on with the sky and he disappears for eight weeks
Well, you know look all I can say is this I'm hanging in I'm hanging in disappointed, but I'm hanging in I
really hope that
I feel like there's going to be that moment where
Coop Cooper comes back. He's in the suit. Yeah, it's playing the music
It should happen by now and you're should have my there's I think there's still another 12 goddamn
Damn episode.
I know.
It's too much.
Lynch is like, I'm gonna walk.
You're not doing this right?
It's like, well cause you want to jerk yourself off
and just shoot a 800 hours of footage.
Like you guys could have done this in 10 episodes.
Yeah.
So, you know, whatever.
I mean, there really is about an eight episode chunk
that just didn't have to exist.
Oh, Christ.
That whole episode where it's just like,
and we talked about this already I think,
but where it's just, I mean, it's kind of creepy.
I guess but it's like I don't need to see three -minute montages of like the inside of nuclear
Smoke. Yeah, it's like this. This is there weren't any characters in that episode except for that one for whatever reason
Just because it was unlike anything I've ever seen on television that one worked for me
Look the idea sure
Yeah, but it doesn't it didn't move the show forward. I guess there's some connection to old nuclear testing now or something
right? The Bob and Duke just ended.
Folks, I know kind of a running joke of these commentaries was that we never talked about
the movie. This is as far as we've ever gone in terms of not talking about the movie.
But I think if anything it confirms that the Boba Duke was very overrated at the time of its release
It was unengaging to us in any way. I remember thinking it was kind of spooky, but maybe it's not as good as we all thought. I didn't care
Love you guys. Jody got any plugs. Yeah
San Francisco I'll be headline the punchline the final weekend of August. That's the 30th through this second of September
I believe
So that's happening. Check out the other podcast emotional hangs on Ferrell audio and in September, I will be at the draft house in DC doing some shows. So come on out for that stuff folks.
I think one or two have now been whatever but my new pen house column you let me down is
So far so good going strong so pick up a copy of pen house and read it digitally or a hard copy hard
I am on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh
I don't really have any plugs in addition to that
But what's this music I'm hearing the ice cream man credits of this movie? Oh
playing. Okay, the end credits. I was confused. I'm looking at an ad for Brad Paisley's comedy rodeo. Well, now it's playing the trailer for Brad Paisley's
Paisley's comedy rodeo. Maybe next week for our horror segment. We'll do Brad Paisley's comedy rodeo.
And look, my friends are on this show. So, you know, God don't blame any comic who wants to get a piece of that that country comic money. God bless my friends. Yeah, good for them, but
but I don't think any human being has ever said,
you know what comedy needs is more Brad Paisley.
Absolutely not, absolutely not.
Anyway, guys, thank you very much.
We will be back probably in two weeks from now.
I guess we'll see you then and we'll see you in hell.
You