Summer is here and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer, or check out
our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Waiter, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only, games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal -durable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Monthly 21 -plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gampler, offer not available in all states,
term -supply, see Fanatic Sports Book App.
This is a head gum podcast.
I'll see you on the train, you know what I say, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
We'll see you in hell your favorite, you know, the podcast you go to for the horror
commentaries and the reviews and the discussions and the sci -fi talk and the fantasy flim flam.
This is where you get it.
We're coming to you live from the uncut thick dick house.
I am Joe DeRosa across from me as my co -host newly scarfed Pat Walsh.
I'm liking the scarf.
I much like a dog might wear like a thundershirt to soothe his anxiety.
I like being able to pull on something that's around my neck.
So this week I've worn a nice scarf for Christmas and I've been wearing it.
It's not like silky or douchey.
It's just a scarf for snow sled.
It does say the word douche on it though.
It's douche brand, but it's not douche.
It's not a douchey scarf.
It does have the words official pussy inspector
embroidered on it.
Yes, well, I went through the training
and I earned that badge.
That's why you got the scarf.
When you graduate, they give you the scarf.
And I am allowed to officiate whenever I want.
Ladies so be ready for that and let's not make a huge deal out of it. Not in the workplace though, right?
No, it's got to be out of work
Now Joe, why did you tell James Frank go to do it again?
This bit will never end because there's that three new ones a day. I
don't know
What's going on with that? I mean he was on co -bearer and he said he didn't he said he didn't do it
But that doesn't mean he didn't do it, but I don't know. Maybe he did do it. I don't know idea
I'm trying to not jump into the I'm trying to be a
Balanced human being where I believe people when they speak out, but I also don't want to
Start throwing like you know the lynch new surround everybody's neck as soon as
There's a there's a blog headline or something. So it's it's a very very this is a very
Colbert handled the discussion very tactfully. I thought
But I'm not answering your question.
Why did I tell him to do it?
Because I didn't like the disaster artist.
That's okay, that's right.
And I didn't like the room.
And I didn't like Freaks and Geeks quite frankly.
All right.
Quite frankly.
I didn't like Freaks and Geeks.
Now, did you like Freaks and Geeks?
I know you didn't care for the disaster artist.
No, we'll talk about that when we hit the movie corner today.
But I don't remember Freaks and Geeks.
so I think I saw one episode with a very, very crazy person that I dated at one point
in my life.
So that sort of, we were dating and then when we broke up, I didn't really feel a thirst
to go back and watch more Freaks and Geeks because I love to hear who that was.
You don't know her.
Well, she was in Freaks and Geeks.
No, no, no, no, no.
I was dating a crazy person that loved the show and she was like, you got to see this amazing
show Freaks and Geeks.
and I watched one with her and I really liked it.
But then we broke up and I was like,
well, I'm done with that show.
I thought maybe you were dating Jason Siegel
or something like that.
Did you see the Franco co bear?
I didn't see, I don't need to see these things.
I know how they play out.
I know nobody's going for the jugular and everybody's,
well, the Niles all sound the same,
the accusations all sound the same.
And I think it's easy to just start becoming numb to it.
I don't want to do that either.
That's what I'm saying.
And it's hard to, it's hard to find your footing in all of this right now.
Well, Michael Douglas came out and was like, hey, nobody's accused me of anything.
I just wanted to say I didn't do anything.
He actually did that because he caught wind of some secretary or some woman that worked
at his company like 30 years ago was about to say that he had jerked off in front of her
or something.
So he, he gets on the horn to these major media outlets today.
And I was like, anyway, I'm just me, you know, fabled five decade actor, Michael Douglas,
just calling to say that I have never done anything creepy to women.
I'm surprised he didn't throw his father into the bus.
Just I would.
Why?
It looks like he had been thrown out of the bus, folks.
Why did they wheel Kirk Douglas out and have him talk?
Why did they feel the need to do this?
There's a lot of wise.
There's a lot of wise you could have asked about that golden gloves. Why did they invite Tonya Harding who to the to the anti -massage
Vert episode of the golden gloves. They invite Tonya Harding who was definitely involved in actual massaging me. Yeah
Nobody I think you pointed this out there. Nobody said a goddamn peep about Nancy Carrigan. No one cares about Carrigan at all
She's a footnote in the movie about her savage beating. She's barely in it
Jesus Christ. I mean, it's fucking, I don't know, I don't know anymore. I don't know
anything else. And Janie's up there going, thank you, Tonya for sharing your story.
It's like, fuck is happening right now. Yeah. Anyway, it's a while to end. Did you hear
this now? I mean, the, the hypocrisy, you know, it was no answer, but Tonya hard on the
other day is like, I got to say I never said this at the time, but I did just kind of
remember that I think I heard my husband talking at the time about how he was
gonna quote take her out just popped into her head now that she's going to the
the award shows it did she show up at the goddamn award show she's sitting at
the table next to a roby robby are you fucking kidding me sitting right there they
cut to her 18 times Jesus fucking crazy I didn't watch the show I can't I mean I
I have a policy to never watch these shows, period.
I watched show, I was angry and yelling things the whole time.
I can't remember the last time I watched that.
Can I ask her or a, yeah, I still watch them.
Now you said, James, go ahead and go do that.
Yeah, those were the words I used.
James, you wanna do it, you'd do it.
Uh, Franco, so you said you didn't care for disaster artists because it's this movie.
Well, let's, let's say it for the movie, but we haven't even gotten all your reason
for not liking it.
It is only going to be helped by this little anecdote.
Oh, okay.
James Franco calls Tommy Wiseau up to the stage.
Yes.
Wiseau comes up.
He leans in to say something and Frank goes, no, no, no, no, no, no.
He cuts him off, like almost grabs the mic out of his hand.
Then Franco just talks for another minute and a half and then walks away and never
lets wise they'll say a word.
And by the way, this is the Golden Globes where Mira, Sravino, Darryl Hanna, Rose, McGowan,
and Rosanna Arquette and about, I'd say probably eight other women, were not invited.
They were not invited to the ceremony because they are not famous enough.
That's literally all it is.
They were not invited yet.
You've got Tommy, YZU up on this fucking stage and we're all supposed to act now like this
This guy had a fucking vision and he was just doing the, this is like when there's a dumb
character on a TV show and then they interview the actor and they go, well, we always looked
at it as she wasn't dumb.
She just looked at things through her own lens or she was actually the smartest person in
the room.
It's how I play.
It's like Jesus fucking Christ, man.
He likes that.
Anyway.
Yeah.
I know.
I heard Franco took, took, wouldn't let him talk.
And then he's like, he's he's up at the Golden Globes.
I mean, that's see what follow in your dream can do.
It's like, yeah, but then you get your dream
and you're not allowed to talk
because the guy who's exploiting you
is winning an award for playing you.
Yeah, and making you look like a fucking lunatic, by the way.
Yeah, I mean, he is probably, but still.
There's no, the only, like the parts in that movie
where you feel sorry for him, it's like the way
you feel sorry for like the elephant man
or something.
This is making me very sad, like people who are looking at this guy, he's a freak, you're
not like somehow getting in touch with this guy as an artist and going, oh my God, he's
actually a beautiful soul underneath the tumors.
Tell me why is he who is not a beautiful soul underneath?
He's a fucking crazy guy.
I don't, at least that's what I took away from it.
Yeah, absolutely.
The elephant man is a beautiful, you got what I was saying there.
Great picture.
I never saw it.
Elephant man?
I've never seen it, but I know the story.
I read the entire screenplay, but I never watched it.
Dave Lynch.
I know.
Do you have a problem with looking at elephantitis, don't you?
Not in a prejudice way, I find it upsetting.
We've talked about it on the show where I've never watched under the skin.
So if I said I don't like looking at Asians because it's upsetting to me, that's not
Bryce is?
Yeah, this is the same thing.
Okay.
No, it's like, it's just, I mean, it gets me,
it makes me upset.
It just, you know, it's like saying,
I don't wanna look at, I don't know.
I feel bad, I feel, it's not vanity.
It's not like, I don't look at it and go, ew!
I just, it makes me very sad.
So I chose to choose not to purposefully look at it,
but I can handle it.
All right, I'm gonna jump out of the shadows
with a picture of Elf and Titus to startle you, don't worry.
Um, I need to get that, well, what I need to do first is get on with the show, and also
on where the Joe, your own way, Joe, your own way.
Very good.
There's one that you keep missing.
I keep missing?
A song that you keep missing that I want to tell you about cuz my friend Rocco used to sing it to me
They're afraid of the modern life. Yeah, yeah cartoon
I I would talk to the TV when I watched it. Yeah, and I believe that he was real and we were friends sure
There's a song he used to put my name into I don't want to tell you because I
Would love you for you to do it one day all right, but I also want to tell you cuz I think you'll never in a million years think of it
What is him?
He used to go, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yo, yeah, that's pretty good.
Yeah, it was great.
And then I would sing it back to him and I'd go, rock, I go, rock, I go, rock,
and we would laugh hysterically.
Of course, I know that song, but is that the Randa Randa?
No.
Sounds like them.
That song is awesome.
That could be my favorite 80 song.
Yeah, that might be my favorite 80 song.
I forget who sings it though.
Okay.
I do.
I mean, unfortunately, I don't even remember what I went into last time.
I have so many pictures here, but no, I think I do.
I've got a few.
All right, I watched, we can talk about it.
Well, we could maybe do this on the pod someday,
but no, we're not going to.
What is it?
A ghost story.
Hell's not.
KCF on the pod.
All right, was it good?
Folks, there's all this on a lot of top 10 lists.
It's KCF like in Rooney, Mara.
But Affleck does 10 seconds into the movie and then he's a ghost in a white sheet the
whole rest of the time watching over his wife.
I am not exaggerating when I say to you that there is a seven plus minute scene.
I've seen it described as everything from five to nine minutes.
Truth is I timed it out at about seven thirty one.
All right
Rooney Mara gets a pie from a neighbor as like a sarah your husband died
treat she
She stands at the counter
And eats this pie in real time with a spoon the entire pie for about five minutes
She eats this pie then she's higher pie. She eats from the pie and she eats from the pie
All right, then she sits down on the floor and for an additional several minutes continues eating the pie
Then she gets up, walks the bathroom, and vomits up the pie.
Then we just go on to the next scene in the movie.
I look it up.
I got to do a ghost.
Lot of chatter online about this pie scene.
People calling it interminable.
Even like people who were raven on the movie were like, this fucking director thinks we want
to watch this fucking show.
The director is saying it's the shot that he's most proud of in his career.
here. Um, and then, of course, a lot of people just saying that they hated it and what
was the point. But the movie, as you can imagine, is very, very slow and boring. Yeah. Um,
and why is he walking around on a sheet? He's a ghost. There's another ghost that he talks
talks to with subtitles who lives across the street, fuck everything about this fucking
movie.
I hate this goddamn thing.
I've never seen a scene of that before.
It's streaming on Amazon, it's, I've liked the director's other stuff kind of, it's just
kind of, it's a real endurance test, it's a bad movie, with some interesting visuals.
Okay.
All right.
right? I saw you're so cool, Brewster. What? It's a documentary about the
making of the original Fright Night. Okay. It's a famous line in the movie. It was
great. It was fantastic. They interviewed everybody. They got everybody back
fucking Stephen Jeffries who played Evil Ed. The William What's his name that
plays the main guy, Roddy McDowell's not in it because he died, but Tom Hull and
the director and writer Amanda is it burst from married with children who played
Marcy? I thought beers, but I'll show you. She you know she she plays the the
romantic lead in the film and it's actually her face on the posters with
that like deranged female vampire faces her. It was great it was fucking great
it was a great nostalgia documentary streaming on shutter right now you can
right night fan I'd say definitely check it out. It's just a great it's just a
great really fun documentary for the fans and it was cool hearing Tom Holland
talked about why he wrote the movie and how it was his love letter to horror
fans and and how much thought went into this thing and and just a lot of cool
little facts and movie trivia things and it and what not and you know just go
check it out if you like right even if you don't like Friday go watch the
fucking thing. Alright, you know, sick of it already. Go watch it already. I saw a film
that's been in the news a lot this week, all the money in the world. Yeah, that's,
this is just how we miss this in our hypocrisy of Hollywood overview. This is just a gorgeous
just unraveling of a tale.
I love it.
I love everything about it.
Movie stars, Mark Wahlberg, Markey Mark,
Michelle Williams, and Kevin Spacey.
Around Thanksgiving time, I see a big poster up
at the movie theater for this movie.
Then, uh -oh, Kevin Spacey's grabbing Dicks.
They're going to reshoot a leading role in the movie
with Christopher Plummer playing Kevin Spacey's role.
Because for some reason they had Kevin Spacey an old age makeup playing the park. Yeah, that didn't get
He's playing Getty the guy who owns the Getty Museum, which is currently on fire here in Los Angeles
They reshoot it and it was just
Revealed yesterday that well they have to reshoot with plumber, right with plumber
And and I was like how are they gonna do this because the movie goes all across the globe exotic locales
It's clearly very expensive.
And they actually reshot the scene.
It's not like they digitally superimposed plumbers head
or something.
So I'll get to the movie in a moment,
but the big story this week is that
Williams was like, I understand this is a terrible thing
about Kevin Spacey, I'll do it.
For the per diem, meaning like go get your meals in Rome
or whatever.
It was less than a thousand dollars.
For less than a thousand dollars.
She was paid less than a thousand dollars
reshooting the movie.
Meanwhile, at the same agency
These agencies are unbelievable. They are working out a 1 .5 million dollar deal. Yeah
Probably more than Michelle Williams made for the movie in the first place. Yeah
Just to do these reshoots any got it. He got paid for Robert. Yeah, Wahlberg got paid 1 .5 million dollars. Yeah, so do something that
But everyone was like, well, this is the right thing to do.
Yeah.
And would have just taken credit for it until someone exposed him.
I don't know who.
Like everybody else.
Yeah.
It is amazing.
This town is sick.
It is sick.
I mean, if nothing else, maybe it'll make people think, okay, every shitty thing I do could
be exposed tomorrow, maybe I'll stop doing shitty things.
I hope it has that effect.
I doubt it.
I subscribe to the philosophy that Chappelle puts forward in the new special in one of his new specials where he says
You have the bad guy scared which is good but fear unfortunately doesn't last and once they're not scared anymore
They're just gonna be bad again. We have to change our system. I actually grew with that
I think that's very insightful and I love both those specials. I didn't see the second one yet
But yeah, I mean, it's it's I mean you could hear
if you stood quietly in the valley at night here in Los Angeles, you could hear the echoes
of Ridley Scott's pats on his own back when they fired Kevin Spacey. I mean, he was so
vehement about that and outspoken and proud and whatever. And at the time I thought,
well, good for him, he did a really tough thing. And that's, wow, he stepped up to the plate.
There's no fucking way Ridley Scott didn't know about that deal. There's no fucking way
Well interestingly Ridley Scott when I read this big interview with him about it he was just like
He seemed more jazzed about the prospect of doing it like a filmmaking challenge when he's 80 years old and getting bored with directing
He was almost barely mentioning the space he think he just seemed like really excited by the opportunity to do this quickly and
presumably on their time but
The point is gang, all this work was done, all these secrets and lies exposed to make just the most average movie of ever seen.
Yeah, well, I mean look, you're not getting anything above average ever with Wahlberg or Ridley Scott anymore.
Wahlberg playing a smart person, always a mistake.
What is wrong with these people?
No clue. What is wrong? Who doesn't understand? Don't cast him in the fucking smart guy part. He's playing like a genius
And by the way strategic genius if I can if I can interject something about Wahlberg where I fucking can't stand this guy anymore
Aside from the fact that the only film of his he denounces now is Boogie Knight's because it was against God or whatever
He's a fucking lunatic, but
But this fucking guy is doing literally the highest paid actor in the world.
The highest paid actor globally is Mark Wahlberg.
He's doing fucking AT &T commercials because this fucking asshole needs the fucking money,
I guess.
And I'm talking about this with somebody and they're like, well, I don't care if stars
endorse products.
I go, I don't care about that either.
But everybody's bitching about the fucking dissolving of the middle class.
How do you think that's not fucking part of it?
The last year that gig went to an unknown female actor
who became known as the AT &T girl
because she was the fucking AT &T girl.
Now it's Mark Wahlberg just snatched
that fucking job from somebody.
That's right.
It's so fucking gross, dude.
Anyway, sorry.
And they're terrible commercials by the way.
He's an idiot.
He's one of the dumbest human beings on planet earth.
And he's a truly bad actor
unless he's playing the idiot that he is.
Yeah, well that's what my friend Jerry I remember said after we after when he did that follow that shitty follow -up movie to
Boogie nights with like Lou Diamond Phillips the big hit hit or whatever
I remember my friend going to see it and being like did it the movie sucks. He was like, but here's the real bummer
We we all thought Mark Wahlberg was like acting
Yeah, Boogie nights. He's just kind of that guy. Yeah, yes. Yeah, so
any wants to beat up an Asian man while yelling slurs. Yes, that did happen so
something to think about. Do you see Weinstein get slapped in the face in that
restaurant? Loved it. I were wound at five times. I was slapped in my
balls off. Yeah, and then it's also kind of like that God like who's who's sitting
in there? All these people just like look who you know who's over at that table?
Harvey Weinstein what none of you have any everyone should have been slapped him in the damn face the thing is he's now
Gonna probably sue that guy for five months. Yeah, and I know listen
I know that that's not the right way to handle things again
I was I'm the one saying we can't just form into the lynch moms
I don't wasn't right that the guy slapped him in the face. However, I am still a comedian that laughs
I wasn't laughing at the slap he barely fucking
I wasn't much. I was laughing at how Jersey the guy was. Yeah, get the fuck out of here. Yeah, fucking with those women get the fuck out of here
Yeah, who's the scumbag with Harvey Weinstein? I know steps in and goes turn the camera turn the camera
And you know he starts laughing and he goes, oh, what are you gonna do about it? Yeah, who is that piece of fucking garbage?
And also Weinstein's got more money than God. Why is he still in this country?
go somewhere. I thought you were going to say why is he wearing a quadruple XL Haynes t -shirt
to a nice restaurant. I think he's trying to hide. Yeah. I think he's trying to look like
slavvingly at homeless. Why is he at a Ritzie club? I don't get it, dude. Why have these privileges
not been taken away? Well, this one isn't a, hmm, I may be. No, he's done minimum some things,
Some terrible thing this is this is well look his he's he's technically a free man
So he's allowed to go into restaurants and then the restaurants are also allowed to say get the fuck out of here, which is great
But my point is is dude, you're the most hated man in the world right now go to go somewhere other than the fucking spot like country
Yeah, I mean, I'm just shocked at the audacity of a guy
It's like no, I'm gonna stay here. Just go out to restaurants. You don't like
rape women, weekly, nightly, for years and years and years and years, and not have some
form of narcissism, nobody's ever going to get me. I'm fine. He's still probably like,
this is all going to blow over. That's true. I'll get out of town. I go to Arizona,
goes within driving distance of Los Angeles. It's, I mean, it's a bad time.
Always, always.
Speaking of bad times and gross people, disaster artists.
Yeah.
I finally saw it.
Shut the thing off halfway through it.
Couldn't finish it.
Could not.
And I texted this to you when I was watching it.
I said, I just turned off the disaster artist.
I was about 45 minutes in.
I couldn't.
I was going to puke if I saw one more cool kid cameo.
This fucking movie, every part that has one line of fucking dialogue to it
From from the from the smallest like you know five five lines are under extra whatever bullshit part all the way up to the leads
This fucking thing is
There's like a scene they go into like a goddamn like to rent something
Hannibal is behind the desk is like the rental guy or whatever
I have animals my friend, I'm not shitting on Hannibal.
You know, then the guy that brings them into see Hannibal
is the guy from like fucking, you know,
parks and wrecker, some shit.
And then, you know, they're in the restaurant
and the producers being played by Judd Appetale
and the agent who's like the Shastey Hollywood agent
is being played by Sharon Stone.
She's in it for a second.
She comes in for two fucking lines.
And it's like, hey guys, you made a goddamn movie
about the beauty of the struggling artist
and how if you push and commit,
You can persevere. How about you put a few fucking unknown actors in this thing instead of making it this fucking circle jerk with you and all your friends
I was annoyed when the fucking thing opened with like Adam Scott
Like the most famous people in Hollywood Hollywood and talking about how brilliant the room is Adam Scott actually says
They're not talking about the Oscar -winning picture from 10 years ago
But they are talking about the room still you don't ever see that yes you do all the fucking. What are you talking about?
You moron people still gather in
Theaters across this country at midnight on Fridays to watch Rocky R picture show
Yeah, fuck are you talking about right because this is the one you and your friends went to shut the fuck up
Fucking movie stunk. It was kind of funny
I shut it the fuck off. I couldn't stand it. You should have been on debate team, Joe,
because I enjoyed the movie thoroughly, and you just convinced me that all of that was
shitty. I agree. It opens up with Kristen Bell and the legacy of the room. Let's not go crazy.
None of our, none of our parents know what the room is.
Could there be two more, it didn't penetrate the culture.
Could there be two more boring people
to see at the top of a movie being interviewed,
then Kristen Bell and Adam Scott.
I mean, your book ending, you just took two boring bookends
and put them right together at the top of the movie.
And by the way, throw Dex Shepard in there
for good fucking measure, you know what I mean?
And it's like and now these guys are gonna tell me why this fucking piece of shit movie is is really get the fuck out of my face
That's like when they did the funny or die
Ten -year like anniversary interview article and it's like Kristen Bell being like it was just about grab the camera and shoot the fucking thing
It's like yeah, was it about that Kristen?
Yeah, was it about that just go grab your red camera that you probably have lying at the bottom of a clock
and you're fucking, shut up.
It's not making it sound like you guys were struggling
in creating art.
Jesus Christ, they didn't interview one fucking person
in that funnier di article
who was just a normal guy that put a video up
and broke through.
Where did the article appear?
It was in a magazine.
I think it was in like a square or something.
But not one person in the,
it was like we're gonna celebrate
like this groundbreaking radical website.
And then all they do is interview like Kristen Bell
and fucking like, you know, and like Will Farrow,
and you're like, what is this?
What are you talking about?
People only care about celebrities.
That goes for everyone in this town
and everyone in America at large.
They only care about celebrities.
And it is bad when you,
we have started to refer to it as this town.
This sick town?
Yeah.
What else?
You see?
Um...
Excuse me.
I...
Soar.
I don't want to spoil a few we might do, guys.
Watch on Netflix super dark times.
I still need to see that.
Because Joe and I are going to discuss.
I think that's a great one for this podcast.
I watched Wind River.
What the fuck is that?
Stars Jeremy Renner.
The reason you haven't heard much about it this award season is because it was produced
by Harvey Weinstein and the guy who made it as fucking pissed and he's like all right all proceeds are
going to Native American women shelter like he's just trying to get anybody to see it but it's the
guy who did he wrote he wrote he wrote he wrote and directed the upcoming secario to which I'm very
excited about. It's called, it's called, it's called, it's called, it's called, it's called
rough flashback kind of scene,
where you kind of start putting shit together,
really hateable villains, nice message.
Who's the villain?
No, no.
Oh, he's the hero.
Yeah, Renter is a great villain.
I wish he would do it more.
He's like a kind of a dim bulb.
Yeah, he's not a, he's a sheriff in the town
and she's a FBI agent in the team up.
This guy loves right about sheriffs.
Yeah, he does.
Yeah.
And to add one more on real quick,
you talk about Renner being a good villain because that reminds me of when I saw where he was
absolutely not a great villain.
A little picture called the house with Will Ferrell and Amy Polar.
Do you watch that?
Look, Will Ferrell and Amy Polar are funny.
They are.
They haven't been in anything funny in many, many years.
But I step up to that plate again and again.
Yeah, I mean, what the hell?
This was less funny than get hard.
which was terrible with him and Kevin hard was offended me and way on levels
that I never even could have fatty yeah this was also less funny than daddy's
home which was nearly unwatchable Jesus Christ it was so horrifically bad and
it's just like what you're talking about the disaster artists we're in this thing
now and I'm not going to name names we definitely know some of these people but
like I'm not speaking for everyone in the movie this is one where every single part
in the exact same way is one of these like mid -grade comedians that are in every single
thing that gets made. They were in two episodes of Parks and Recreation which put them on
the cool club. Right. And now there's a town hall meeting scene where like 12 of the people
with lines in this scene are people you've seen on like Hulu's casual or transparent one
week or you know and we you know exactly who these people are they've been the
supporting roles in movies now for 15 years and it's getting really boring and
they're talented people and funny people they've been playing the same part
over and over and over for more than a decade it's getting real fucking old the
that's the least of the problems for the house now Joe tell me what you think the
house is about right pitch me the house I know what it's about it's about their
You know, well, they need money for their kid to go to college. Yeah, so they started an illegal gambling casino or an illegal casino like in their basement and
It's their house, which is a play on the house. Yeah
That's obviously how the movie was pitched and what it should have been but what it actually is
Is Will Ferrell and Amy pull or need money for college and their crazy druggy friend who just got divorced played by of course
Jason Manzookus
That's who I was, I couldn't remember his name.
That's the guy that leads.
Yes, that's right.
Frank go into Meadhan.
Manzookus offers up his house.
This like acquaintance in the neighborhood.
His this, so immediately 90 % of the stakes of the movie
are taken away.
Why would they do it in here?
It's such a stupid fucking choice
for a screenplay to do.
Like, okay, if somebody pitched me on an elevator,
It's welfare and any puller that need money for college to turn their house into a casino got it
They that's how the movie was even advertised that is not what the movie is
They make every choice away from the direction of comedy
There's not a smile to be had in it. It's a terrible terrible movie. I got to tell you dude. I am
Heart because polar is much much much much less of an offender than Farrell is
Yeah, and I like with Polar with making bad stuff.
You know what I mean?
Afraid.
Farrow on the other hand, I'm like heartbroken over it.
Yeah.
It's, it is a, it is a like gym carry level drop off where I'm like, dude, you are the
funniest human being on earth.
And these fucking things you're making do, it's like when Sandler started doing it, Farrow
lasted way longer, thankfully.
Yeah.
But you know by the time Sandler was doing like Mr. Deeds and you're just like, what the fuck
is happening here?
Mr. Deeds has some really funny parts.
Okay, I'll, I'll tutorial.
It's very fun.
It was a bad example, or not the best example, but you're, you're up to the end of the
good Sandlers with Deeds.
I mean, little Nikki, I think, is the official.
That's terrible.
Except Rodney Danger feels in it.
Yeah.
Um, I just bums me out, man.
The guy's so goddamn funny and it's like, you know, and polar too, I, I just hope that
And she doesn't continue on a streak of shit like this because she did something right
before this where I was like, what the fuck is this?
Was it baby daddy?
Baby daddy was years ago and it's not a terrible movie.
Maybe no, what was the first that her sisters?
Sisters looked very bad to me.
Sisters has some funny parts too.
They're both very average comedies.
So they're both light years better than the house or get hard or daddy's home or anything
or daddy's home. Daddy's home too. Did you see? I didn't say daddy's home. All right. Well I have
seen a couple other things but I'm actually going to take them into Joe's scary stuff. Do it
because it's going to piggyback what I said last week. I bought those full moon DVDs that were on sale.
Hittiest was one. Another one was called the creeps. I recommended you all go buy them and I watched
them this week. And by watch them, I mean, I watched three quarters of each. I couldn't
even finish these fucking things. They weren't even fun bad. Like I thought they were going
to be like kind of like tasteless and gross and like, you know, ridiculous. I thought
there would be some real, real value and at least the visual aspect of the films. And there
just isn't. They're just, they're just, they're just not good movies. I'm sorry. And I like
full moon I think they're cool I think they're a cool company maybe I just
saw the wrong ones but I think puppet master is as good as it gets with full moon
now look I haven't watched the what's the other one I got there rituals of the
cult the occult that's a three piece one with netherworld and some other stuff
I'm still gonna watch it I look forward to watching it I look forward to watching
head of the family, but as far as the creeps and hideous go, which are two, from what I could
tell, flagship movies for full moon features, holy shit, man. I couldn't, the creeps, I was like,
the creeps, the other titles, deformed monsters. And it's about a guy trying to bring
his literature's greatest monsters to life. So it's Dracula, Frankenstein's monster, Wolfman,
and mommy, but his experiment goes wrong
and they come out half the size or whatever.
So you got little people playing these monsters.
Oh boy.
So which, so I was like, all right,
that sounds like a pretty, it's like zany idea, I'm into it.
I'm watching this thing.
I'm like, obviously, I get like halfway through the thing.
I'm like, obviously, this is supposed to be like,
a kid's movie, I was wrong.
But you're supposed to be like a thing that you watch with your kids.
Okay.
Because it's like a zany crazy thing.
Right.
And there's like a four -minute tits scene.
They even said fuck wants in the movie.
Yeah.
They got a little guy dressed as a mummy rubbing this lady's tits as she screams.
I'm like, it doesn't make any sense.
I don't know what's...
What am I watching right now?
So, unfortunately...
Why am I jerking off to it?
Yeah, right. Well, I was jerking off before the tits even came out. Folks
Hittiest was was a was a hair better, but Hittiest was supposed to be about these like
Freak babies that break out of there for maldehyde jars and start killing everybody. I'm 55 minutes into this god damn thing
They haven't killed one person and then I realized oh, they don't have the budget to do like a ghoulies thing
Right so it just it just wasn't good
It just, they just weren't good films.
So I apologize if you went and purchased those on my say so.
They did do a nice job with the packaging
and the transfers were nice.
And the video zone feature at on them is pretty cool
where you see like the behind the scenes.
And here's the weird thing too.
I was like, obviously, the whole thing here
was a bunch of people saying like,
we're gonna make like a really, like a, like a camp film.
Right. You watch the behind the scenes, shit.
These guys are like, what a fucking joy it was
We put our heart and soul into these pictures. They're interviewing the actors. They're like this was so amazing
Yeah, I'm like it's it's not that layered. This is not a put -on these people really believed in this right
Or over time they grew to after going to a few of these like
Trade shows and things like that and people say oh, I love that movie it met so much to me
No, no, these are for interviews at the time. They're doing oh wow
Yeah, they're doing these interviews at the time
sometimes you'll watch like you know everyone because that's man tell me how
their favorite kill was me and Halloween five or I'm like I didn't he's gonna
be like no one ever told you that well I did once meet and I don't remember
her name because she's only in this this is the only movie I've ever seen her in
but I did meet the girl from the woman from Nightmare on street three the one
who burns herself with cigarettes to stay awake. And so she's the one Freddie Kills, Freddie
pops out of the TV and he picks her up. Oh yeah, we talked about. Welcome to prime time,
bitch. And slams your head through the TV and that's all she does. But I met her and I
meant it. I go, you're my favorite kill in all of Nightmare on Elm Street. And she said,
God bless you. Thank you. She made her fucking day. You could tell. All right. It was really sweet.
So why don't you lay off the Halloween five cast and crew right now, all right?
I watched a couple of these docs myself on the Bill and Ted's excellent collection DVD set
because no such thing in my opinion. Now I liked these movies when I was a kid but I always thought
they were a very pale Wayne's world imitator even though they were before Wayne's were. I loved
an adventurer, I didn't like bogus journey too dark. But weirdly, I've been hearing constantly
about people referring to this as one of the best comedies ever made. The original people
really love it. Just like a re -evaluation of this movie that's been going on for decades.
So I see they got the new ones. I watched an hour -long documentary on adventure, hour -long
documentary on bogus journey, there's some side drama where the writing team that did it had
like a bitter separation right before they started on bogus journey, which was very interesting
to hear about. And they're great documentaries, especially if you're fans of the movies. Tonight,
this week I'm going to actually rewatch the movies. But what I was seeing of bogus journey looked
I loved it so much. I loved that George Carlin was in it, like, playing like the time traveler sage guy or whatever. I love those characters. I loved the gag of, like, Alex Winner's dad fucking the, like, 20 -year -old that they, like, had graduated, like, a year before them or whatever.
I loved it so much. I loved that George Carlin was in it, like, playing, like, the time traveler sage guy or whatever. I loved those characters. I loved the gag of, like, Alex Winner's dad fucking the, like, 20 -year -old that they, like, had graduated, like, a year before them or whatever.
I just I thought it was awesome. My mom loved it because she felt like it was like sort of educational. Yeah, it was
It was just an awesome awesome movie. It was every kid's dream. It's you know time travel's like back to the future
But even like crazier. Yeah, and then I rented bogus journey and I was so excited to watch it and I didn't even I remember I didn't finish it
I was like this is too dark. I don't like this storyline of these robots
They felt it went too dark as well
Yeah, I'm intrigued to watch it again.
Sadler is very good as death in it, but yeah, it bums me out.
Now older people, people are age now, say, oh, Bogus Journey's way cooler and way better.
That's what I hear you.
But I think that's something that comes with age.
You know, faith no more in primus are both in Bogus Journey.
I didn't know they were in it, but I know they're on the soundtrack.
track. I bought I own to this day that soundtrack for the Faith No More song on it because that's
the only way you could get it Pat. Yeah.
Anyway, listen, we're 44 minutes in. We haven't even come within a breath of, well that's
It's fine because I imagine we're not going to have much to say here.
We're talking about what I thought was the third in the franchise, even though I've seen
the other three and realized morning of that it was the fourth, insidious colon, the last
key.
I mean, Joe, walk us through the franchise as a whole very quickly if you would.
Well, insidious, you and I did insidious three on here, I believe.
I think we did and I don't think we had a lot of nice things to say
In cities is a phenomenal horror movie. It's one of the the better horror movies to have been made in the last
15 years or 10 years whatever it's been
Stars Patrick Wilson and Rose Byrne
Their son has a demon attached to him. He's in a coma
Because this demon has this kid trapped in a place called the further
and Patrick Wilson has to go into the further
and release and save his son.
And then you find out that Patrick Wilson had also
been subjected to this as a child.
It's an awesome movie.
It's scary.
It doesn't rely on jolt scares.
There are jolt scares, but that's not all that there are.
There's a really terrifying scene
of an old man, baby, dancing to like 1910 piano music
that's very fucking creepy.
be. It's just a great moody piece. The second one is more of a sort of ghostly adventure.
I like the second one. People hated it because I think they wanted another straight, horror
thing. But I thought the second one was very cool. I thought they tied it into the first
movie brilliantly. They do things in the second film where you see that, oh, that's what was
happening in the first movie. They just do a really good job with it. I liked it a lot.
and I enjoyed the adventure of it all. Third movie is clearly when Patrick Wilson and Rose
Burns said, fuck this shit, we're done. So they said, okay, we'll start making prequels
that center around the Zelda Rubenstein of the insidious franchise. Lin Shea's character.
I can't, I know her name, I can't remember the goddamn characters name.
Lynn Shea is the old woman from something about Mary, the very tan woman Magda.
She is also the lady who does the tongue motion, the landlord in Kingpin.
Which is why I think it's weird that in both movies that she's the lead in, they have a
demon that goes, yeah, yeah, it's too obvious of a nod for me.
So yeah, I mean, we're part of that because of prequels for Lynn Shea.
Yeah, and I'm I'm gonna happen for Lynn Chase. Great actor
So they start making them as prequels with three so three becomes three is now
This is where it all started. This is only marketed three. This is where it all started. This was the big one
Three was not great no
Four comes out same marketing all again. You got to go back to the beginning where it all started
I'm like they already fucking did that. I thought right
So this one, part four is a sequel to part three and it's also a prequel to part one and it's called the last something which I always find fun.
Now the one positive I'll say about the movie. There are parts in the movie where they go back into part one and I thought that that was cool.
There's a scene from part one where a kid hears a ghost in his closet, and in this movie
you see Lin Shea in the further, like open a door and you see a shot of the kid from
the first movie, turn and look, and you realize, oh that's what he hears in that part.
Didn't even catch it.
I'm amazed that people have the memory for Insidious One when you're watching Insidious
Four.
I liked the franchise, and it's just falling off.
part I also like at the end she gets a call and it's the call to go help the
Patrick Wilson Roseburn family in in cities that I remember yeah that was
cool they just did some like little cool stuff like that other than that this
thing is a fucking hot log of shit it's so bad I mean with a shout -out to our dear
friend Karen Coguerra post of my favorite murder with Georgia hard stock
George a hard star. Jesus Christ. What? I said, harsh star. I lost the
ability to speak. I got to be honest. You look like you've been on the verge of falling
asleep. Not true. Through this. I'm not saying you're not invested. I'm just saying you
look tired. I'm strangely tired, but I'm here. We saw it with Karen. They do my
favorite murder in there. They're great. We get a lot of our viewers. I've learned listeners
from my favorite murder and from the Gilmore guys, oddly enough.
Very nice.
I asked, that question got asked on Facebook the other day.
Yeah, I mean, Karen must have just been completely lost
she hadn't even seen the others, but it didn't really matter.
I mean, you're watching a Lin Shea vehicle.
She can't hold the screen for 90 minutes, I'm sorry.
Well, I mean, look, I don't know whether she could
or she couldn't.
she's being handed dog shit to work with.
I mean, it's like, look, nobody else in the movie
even registered as being a character.
I'm happy for her, because I'm like,
that's pretty great that a woman at her age,
she's in her 70s, I believe, is getting to do a lead part
in a Hollywood film, and it's gonna probably make her
for the rest of her life, you know what I mean?
So I'm happy for her to have the work.
I wish they gave her better material to work with.
It's fucking ridiculous.
Then you got Bruce Davidson coming in halfway through this thing.
The performance he gives is one for the ages.
I mean, their scenes together are just the worst scenes in a real bad movie.
Yeah, it's a bad movie.
I don't even know where to start.
Terrible dialogue, terrible acting.
And then also there's this whole like subplot of like the house, the demon in the house is
making the men who live in the house act crazy and kidnap women and keep them in like a giant
Turned off freezer downstairs. I'm like, what the fuck does that have to do with anything? Yeah
Like it just it just didn't it was just so crazy. It was like what what is going on right now? And I mean
people this is a Blumhouse picture
It's a Blumhouse picture
Which we also saw a trailer for another Blumhouse picture called Truth or Dare.
It looks like one of the shittiest things I've ever seen.
But I'm like, this is Blumhouse.
How is Blumhouse putting this kind of thing and get out?
How are they putting both out?
How is Blumhouse not stepping in and going?
We need a better fucking script for in city is four.
Unless they're just saying people will go see it, we don't give a shit, it's going to make
millions of dollars.
It did, it made shit loads of money.
Probably what it is.
It just bums me out, man.
It's like of all the companies. It's like to me that company should be
should be
Comin' these scripts more and and putting it did better think about how great it would be if it was a good movie
Yeah
Like why are you mailing it at this point like it's just I think you know that those kind of movies enable them to make
The shit they care more about probably just they'll be churning out in insidious ever it seems like there's one a year
I don't know if that's true, but but you could but here's the thing
I mean, the first insidious made a lot of money and it's good.
The second insidious made a lot of money and it was good.
It might not set well with fans but it's a quality film.
I guarantee those fans don't care now that they've seen three and four.
The three and four, it's like guys, it's like sci -fi channel bed, like old sci -fi, I like
a lot of the what sci -fi channel does now but you know, you mean like the moth man.
Yeah, so I'm referring to your moth man movie. Yeah
It's just like I don't get it like why
Just make it make it decent for Christ's sake try. Yeah, yeah, it just didn't that this had first draft written all over it
I mean lazy writing. There's a part where you find out Lynch Bruce Davidson you find out his lynch is brother and
He's got two daughters. He by the way comes in Karen did hit it on the head she goes
because she's supposed to be her younger brother.
And they're having this dramatic face -off argument thing.
And in the middle of it, Karen goes,
and why are you older than me?
And it was like, yeah, it's weird.
When he's Davidson looks significantly older
than when she had.
Then he's got two daughters who I think are maybe 18?
Yeah.
That's never explained.
They're not 18, by the way.
And there's two, her side kicks throughout this movie,
are 40 -year -old plus creeps, one in nerd, one like an actively lecherous sex
perv. And the really the only story I was tracking in this movie was the love
triangle between an underage girl and these two 40 -plus -year -old goons who are
actively trying to fuck these girls and it's played for Comic Relief throughout.
Yeah and I guess the only explanation is is that the girls are not supposed to be
underage, but God damn it, they didn't look a stitch more than 17, which I know because
of James Franco is legal in New York.
Yeah.
But the movie doesn't take place in New York.
No, it doesn't.
Well, it does take place in Arizona or New Mexico.
God knows what the legal age is down there.
I'm shocked it was 17 in New York.
I had no idea.
Well, yeah, that's my point.
That's a progressive state.
Right, right.
You know, you get down into Arizona. It's like Christ. They're shipping them to the altar at 12 probably probably, you know, stereotyping
Arpeio
Welcome to our payo's Arizona. That's the racist share. Yeah. Yeah. Oh good. All right. Well
Yeah, and we were we were all confused by that that whole love mix
Um, it's a bad picture the demon even the way the demon the demon in this one. It was real mailed in
and it was like the way he looked, I mean,
it just looked like they went to a sort of paint
by Numbers demon book and we're just like,
yeah, they'll do this and this and it's like,
you know, the original demon in the first in Sidious
is so fucking freaky looking and it is cool
that that thing pops up at the end.
The red demon.
Yeah, but it's such like a cool take
and it kinda looked like Darth Maul,
but it didn't, it was fucking scary looking.
This thing it was just like, you know,
put a fucking big hole in its face and you know put keys on its fingers because you
gotta open all the red doors or whatever. I don't even understand what that
was. I know that's a reference to something that I'm not remembering but it's
sucked. You can easily skip this movie gang. Watch something better. Watch Super Dark
Times and get ready because once Joe watches it that'll be the next one we do. I
I will watch Super Dark Times before next week
and we can do that one.
We need to do shout outs.
I think, right?
Yeah, it doesn't last week.
I don't think we've done it in a while.
All right, hold on a second.
We need to do it.
Guys, give us your opinion.
Shout outs once a month enough or do you want it twice?
I mean, look, we appreciate you guys donating
and we'll do it twice if you want it twice.
But I don't know if anybody cares enough to I don't know. Let us just let us know. We appreciate the feedback. Honestly. Now that you guys are showing this really wonderful support on Patreon and everything like we will now more than ever.
We want to make sure we're doing right by all of you.
So, as the great fans you are, and that's patreon .com slash W -S -Y -I -H -Pod, and go there and
look at the tiers and donate, and we'll be adding some new stuff soon, and changing
stuff around, and keeping it fresh.
Yeah, there's merch on the way, and I would say on that for several years, there is merch
on the way.
There is literally merch on the way and it is coming to us through the help of the wonderful Emily Florence
Who runs the Facebook group
But it's coming very soon. In fact, she might have already started asking you guys about it
Anyway, shout -outs. You ready? Yes, Anthony V. Manito aka party McFly
Philip Rashad
Katelyn, Derek Clark, Alex Shipley, Joshua Taj Bozeman,
Culture Creature, Sean Pinnock, Amanda Liebson,
Timothy Lesto, Shane Nazarene, Shelby L,
John King, Clayton Stamper, Smelly Bubbles,
James Nassmon, Holly Barnes, Jeff Some Confidence.
That's a good name, Jeff Some Confidence.
Michael Madrigal, go to Mr. Suit Records
and Lancaster, Pennsylvania, if you're ever near it, David Bellinger, Tyler Zach, Kurt
Ziegler, Jenna Hunter McDonald, John Wolt, Justin Boehager, Adam Benbenek, Manny Rios,
Demonio Rubio, Brandon Gash, Edmund Agabau, Agabau. Paul Pickery. Pickerel. Pickerel. Holy
shit. That's a tough one. Paul Pickerel. I think this is how you say that. Jake Ferret,
Orferot, Chris Lindt, Tony Quinn, Rob Lines, Danny Rudd, Jacob Barrett, Jordan C, Maxwell
Will Ashcroft, Ryan Kohler, Joshua Christianson,
Barab Allen, Jonathan Face, Rebecca Cohen,
Chris Bowen, are that rhymed?
Mike Gibbons, Donnie Joyce, Michael Dawson,
Jennifer Smith, Luke Henderson,
Hader Ismail, Nick Walther, Connor Denahy,
Michael, just Michael, Steven Kaupa, Kaupa Kaupa Kaupa.
Kevin Swistowicz, Thomas Koza, Anthony J. Guajardo,
Annie Johanison.
Yes, Johanison.
Timmy K. Sean Florn, the Laura Smartinas, Megan Liebrand,
Scott Blikensdurfer, Alec Walker, Brett Wormer,
Wemmer, sorry, Brett Wemmer.
Tristan Carlson, Laura Sexton, Anthony Guajardo,
So, Brett Klinker, Brett Klinkner, Alex Lowe, Westend Thomas, this is the one.
We got to figure out how to say this guy's name.
It's the one with all the consonants in a row.
It might require a direct message to ask.
HV, yeah.
Can you message as much Westend Thomas, HV, D, H, Y, L, D?
I have no idea how to pronounce that.
Jared Blair, Josh Smallridge, Richie Verdugo, Chris Hopper, Emily Griffith, Emily Farns,
Sean L, Jordan Parker, Jordan Parker, Dave Comerick, Abby Manuel, Kim DeAngelo, Jonathan
Galatt, Michael McBee, Carla O, Stephanie Power, that's a good, honest name, Stephanie Power,
Yeah. Sterling Abrigo.
Geron Sanderson, Diego Campos.
Stefan Mussa, I believe.
Zoe Blaskevich, Edmund Dillon,
is Easley Kibinsland, Dan McLeod,
Lawrence Bunganiers, Alejandro Salgado,
Papa Spooch, Tegan McLeod, Matthew Little, Tracy Reddington, Sean Thomas, Amanda
Alzemora, Jason Weibull, the fabled Knight of Two Sandwiches. Drew Spindler, Andrew
Koval Sam Mitchell, Aaron Melonowski, Scott Nolan, Jack Gertz, Greg Sarnson, Benjamin
to Hia, Misty Zavar, Brandon Nocki.
Thank you for the phonetic spelling.
Dojne Wilford, Johnny Furg, Matthias Paujo.
Thank you, Matthias, for the pronunciation.
Superfan Giovanni, Michael Gold, Danielle Doer,
Eric Lamora, Stephen Reese, Walter Kiegan, Kevin Marcenek,
Eric Abanning, Lawrence Anderson, Jared Smolridge, Zach Schoendorf, Will Pottoff, Natalie
Craig, Nathan Baskett, Anthony Kyle Kinslin, the man whose name we cannot say, Ani Baba
Duck, Scott Patton, Reed Esthetic, Brian Buellerier, Emily Marvel, Robert Pearson, Michael IAO,
or ILO, Max Unwraff, Highton Davidson, Brian England, and John Weissen Gruber, whoo. Pat,
I feel very lucky. I feel loved. Jesus, that is a lot of fucking people. We're very blessed. Thank
you guys for the support. Thank everybody who's supporting us, but even if you're just listening.
And that's it.
I'm Joe DeRos' comedy at Gmail, I'm sorry, holy shit.
Joe DeRos' comedy on Twitter and Instagram, please follow me on Instagram, I'm trying
to get those Instagram numbers up.
And the pen house column, you let me down, it's out monthly, but you got to buy pen house
to read it.
So go start buying some porn.
I'm on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh tonight. I recorded Kevin Porter's new
podcast from Gilmore Guys. It is called Good Christian Fun. They talk about things in Christian
entertainment. We discussed the film Prince of Egypt. So many of you said you were fans of
Kevin. He's got a new show. I urge you to check it out. At a good time doing it. My show,
Living Biblically, premieres February 26th on the CBS Network, and I would be remiss if I didn't tell you the other young lady who was on Good
Christian Fun, whose name is Caroline Eli. I had to make sure I had her correct name. Thank you everybody. We will see you next time. We will see you in hell.
That was a hit gun podcast.