Welcome to we'll see you in hell everybody. Hey
Pat Walsh and one of your Joderos and the other how has everybody how you doing?
They can't answer us Joe. It's not a call in podcast.
You know I suggested that it could be not yet. It is a podcast however brought to you
by the Fengoria podcast network. For more information about the network including other programs
or on how to follow this show those shows any shows find past episodes of we'll see you in hell or any
of the other pods please visit Fengoria .com. And now here we are just you all see we'll see I
worked that announcement in that bumper. I thought we were just talking like old friends. Yeah no
I didn't realize you were reading something. That was all business. How are you doing Pat? I'm good
we're about a week out from Thanksgiving. I think this will probably drop a couple days prior and
we're doing a reverse theme episode because we're going to watch Stephen King's thinner and thanks
giving is all about getting a fatter. We're switching it up. We are switching it up. Now's the time to
go to your Netflix box. Your Roku your Apple TV your PS4 your Xbox one whatever it is if you want to
watch the movie along with us find thinner on your Netflix queue it up as soon as that
first frame comes on hit pause and we'll count off the play in a few minutes here in the meantime
speaking of Thanksgiving this is not our Thanksgiving episode I think we will probably drop a special
Thanksgiving episode I'm hoping I guess we have to now that I said that but I am hosting Thanksgiving
and Pat is you're coming I'll be there I'm making my traditional sweet potatoes which were
just so delicious last year but you don't eat them you don't like them. I don't like them kind of
slap in the face to me because everybody raved. I like sweet potatoes I don't like the way you did
them. Oh that's you personally that that style of sweet potatoes I don't care for I mean candy
gems. Yeah I don't like it it's too sweet everybody loved it. Well you know everybody loves that
you know that new fucking Bieber record oh yeah I was but the best thing I could reference I couldn't
think of it. No you're right though that's it I mean I haven't heard a song on it but everybody's
like do we have to really start taking Bieber seriously this is really fucking good you know what it
isn't I haven't heard it and I know it isn't guys a piece of shit and you keep you keep playing his
game he's an animal he's a fucking monster. Why is he a monster? If you heard of nothing he's done
in the past several years I've heard of he gets hookers here and there I'm not talking about hookers
he's egging homes but then again he's 18 years old 18 years old he's been fucked in his head since
he's 14 I mean it's what you know if I was 18 I got that much money I'd be a fucking asshole too
but we're all just like oh what's what's Bieber up there what's Bieber up to we shouldn't care
well you shouldn't care what your 18 year old nephew was up to yeah or your own son for that man
and then these people don't by the way they care more about what Bieber's up and look maybe I'll go
home and put this album on and I'll be like do I gotta start caring about Justin Bieber this
is like we know this is like when uh that fucking Taylor Swift album came out and he actually love
that album you'll probably like this album you fucking douche yeah maybe I will but like Swift seems
like a class act does she does she I kind of tired of her fucking aw shucks stammering you know I'm
just a girl from next door that just stumbled into fame she lost me when she started trying to
copyright phrases she used that she didn't invent like what I didn't hear about it like whatever
her catch phrases are a lot about these two says all the time she tried to like patent them
and it was like you didn't make up the words like what word one of them was literally like it's
all good oh squad squad goals or whatever it was like like shit that like some of them was like I
guess you could have that one but there were like ones where it was like that's like a phrase that
exists yeah yeah yeah I don't know did you like when Tegan and Sarah went off pop I didn't care
for that either no I didn't like that record I love uh many of Tegan and Sarah's albums but the
last few have let me down a bit yeah why they've released that like pop dance record um because they
want money you know and they're they're getting it ain't that the business we're in it is I uh
speaking a great pop music I actually love the new Grimes album I don't know if you know Grimes
I don't her first album was fantastic second albums just as good but in a popular direction
in a great way so I'm still very experimental I'm not against pop music no well obviously I don't
betray me don't you don't you don't you put that tag on me check out the new Grimes but I also
think the new Taylor Swift album is great speaking of pop music I just watched the movie Danny Collins uh
Pacino yes fanning and at betting Bobby canna Valley out Pacino and a good Jennifer Gardner loved it
loved it loved it it's a perfect movie to watch with the folks yeah it's got a little edge to it still
rated R plenty of fucks okay uh some drug business in it uh okay let's put you in the joint
no he carries a cross filled with cocaine around his neck and I'll roll with him
but I love the movie cried in the last scene in the airplane okay I really thought it was a
wonderful film about family about love about a man fighting himself let me give you my pick
for a great airplane or HBO on demand when you're hung over movie or family parent movie yeah
little movie called the intern starring Bobby Denise how was that an an half uh I like to
quite a bit it's too long it's kind of rambling but it's it falls in with that it's complicated
and all those movies where I just enjoy it yeah I saw it's complicated in the theater
I did so I like male friend of mine fine and we enjoyed it it's there's a great line in the movie
with Alex Baldwin where he he's talking about his steps on uh I think the kid's name is Rodrigo
great guardo I think it's at guardo it's very important that you remember lake bell plays the like
fiery Spanish girl friend or whatever yeah and uh doesn't look Spanish and she's but yeah she's uh but
then uh uh he says uh uh uh uh I was almost a Glenn close what's your name Meryl Streep
Streep the other Glenn close yeah Meryl Streep asked him about like food because she's like she cooks
in bakes uh huh and then he goes uh unfortunately rod rigo picks most of our meals and he has a very
limited palette yeah that's that's reasonably funny it's a funny joke uh let's get into thinner man
what do you say okay you can have food all right on you should see a couple paramount stars cut starting
to swoop in yeah we'll count one two three then say play on play you play it one two three play
that wait a second pause it we're not it didn't go why didn't it go
host because you're still on the side up titles like we're watching it with subtitles so we can just
like watch you know hear what they're saying yeah oh wait I know what to do one two three play
nope didn't go again god but what the hell is wrong with this
all right uh all right guys ready one two three play okay still didn't go hold on a second
listen wow just get back to that all right go back to the beginning you should be two seconds in
at most you got it paused and now we're going to go one oh wait a second give him a chance to rewind it
back this is brutal this is just brutal this is the stuff people like this is the real stuff if this
is the first one people are listening to they're never coming back well hey we don't want you then
yeah that's true scram okay ready one two three play there we go now we're rolling I don't know
if the subtitles are going to be on pat we the problem with the reason we were having problems is
because pat wants to have subtitles on because we talk through the movie and we want it to be able
to see what was being said pretty reasonable case we weren't listening and I couldn't get it off
for the subtitle thing I saw thinner for the first time probably 15 friends and I always thought
the preview is hilarious when the old gypsy goes my friend Jim who we mentioned quite a few times in
the smoke yes you used to always say that we were in high school yeah I got to tell you I would love
somebody to curse me thinner now it's to do any work and then you know you cut it off at a reasonable
time gypsies are usually pretty cool about cutting off a curse when you ask them nicely as we'll learn
now uh right off the bat I'm excited your boy Tom Holland made this movie why I see my boy
Tom Holland is a director can you not uh are you know are you unfamiliar with anything Tom Holland is
done I thought Tom Holland did like Larry Sanders show and stuff like that or am I crazy the Larry
Sanders show I thought he was a TV director but maybe I'm wrong Malcolm in the middle
are we talking about the same Tom Holland I think you're thinking about savage Steve Holland who
directed better off dead right no who is savage Steve Holland he boy I just said he did
better off dead that's the guy's real name savage yeah savage Steve Holland savage Steve
home was he a wrestler before he directed no he did one crazy summer better off dead a few others
all like a very heightened comedy style and they would actually put the word savage look yes
like macho man Randy that's insane man uh what's fucking insane who was Tom Holland Tom Holland
directed uh believe fright date oh yeah that's true that's correct I like fright night and I actually
kind of like the remake of fright there's also an English actor named Tom Holland is that the kid
that's playing spider man yeah it is now the actor named uh so glad they're rebooting that again
are you fuck no you and I saw that second spider man just train Rick terrible I sat next to the
a ridge the OG spider man Toby McGuire at a Mexican restaurant the other night how did you
talk to him about spider man no I didn't uh it was him and his wife who I gotta say I guess this
is pretty commented on not a traditional Hollywood type lady like I think she's like his high school
sweetheart like he fucked everyone in the world he was in the decaprio pussy posse where they
fucked everything that moved and then I guess he just called his high school sweetheart I was like hey I
got out of my system you want to come back well that's what I was sad to hear these uh Matt Damon
divorce room were swirling because he's married really his high school sweetheart are they swirling
Joe you're right out of the pages of an us weekly you go to the grocery store I saw it in the
grocery store I was in the cover or something but I mean I find it just said Matt Damon divorce rumors
are swirling I find that the gossip rags are often true all right it often comes true look at sheen
Charlie she they were saying that it is sad but he can a thinner wow come on all right I didn't feel
great about it but it's right there they were saying that for for years is this his wife uh yeah that's
his wife okay well this guy is a handsome chap when he's not in the fat suit Robert John Burke you know
what I got to say in the fat suit I find him handsome chap I you're kind of feeling it I'd like to
lay next to this guy that shake that his wife just made him now it starts on with a fat man that's the
whole premise of this movie obviously um but shake looks like it has about 1200 calories and for some
reason the daughter looks to be half black yeah two what completely white bread parents can pretty much
guarantee she's a good looking gal these days uh mildly creepy but I I know what you think she's
15 16 here when I would have been 15 16 so I'm still going back to the age when I saw it looks nothing
like either parent no not at all or even in their races as you said what I always wonder is like you
was you see thinner or you see like uh nutty professor like a movie where the whole thing is this guy's
a huge fat guy and everybody's laughing at him or you know that's the plot hinges on him being fat
and you go see this movie what if you're fatter than him wouldn't it make you feel really uncomfortable
or would it well they they they go to the you know I mean they they they try to go to a certain extreme
he he's 300 plus pounds in this well he's 300 we just saw which he lied to his wife said he was
297 he's a big guy I mean I don't think the average heavy said person is is under any illusions six
three three of those boys hidden there were didn't have any illusions
perfection yeah uh now who what's his guy's name you do his name Robert John Burke I believe
his name Robert John Burke this is Joe Montana of course fat Tony yeah what is Robert John Burke
also win this is the only thing I've ever seen him he's in kind of a lot of shit it's mostly like
TV kind of stuff you know I think he's in like you know Chicago hope hope fire dentist one of the one
of those I think he's a Chicago mercy I like this grease ball that's a slur I believe oh shit is it
I think it's a slur I didn't even mean I tell you and I mean it looks greasy uh well it is a
trial for mobsters oh is it well look you just saw Joe Montana what else is going on I thought he
was an attorney no he plays a mob boss in this okay so clearly I don't know what is Joe
Montana ever not played yeah a mob guy of some kind I don't think I've ever seen him play anything
else it's a good point house of cards great Joe Montana film I love house cards David Maven yeah Joe
Montana was the original Ricky Roma on Broadway he's terrific he has a story about opening night
the actors the actors curse or whatever it's called uh forgot all his lines on stage opening
no Jesus went blank it's a lot of lines too I mean I think he recalled them but he had a moment of
going severely blank now Joe do you think uh the same gypsy who by the way made this guy thinner put
the actress curse on him hold on let me finish my god damn Joe I got the joke but we're gonna miss
this pat just in the last thing goes I didn't even know they were telling it cuts now to a scene
of them on a speedboat with a gray -haired woman serving them food from them not just food it's like a
giant spaghetti meet a boat linking red wine glasses stokies yeah toasting wine on a speedboat all right
now I understand uh I think I have both red thinner and seen thinner and I did not remember any mafia
element at all I never read the book I always wondered if this was in the book thinner follows the
book pretty carefully I remember the book just being a much better version written by McDowell who
also wrote Beetlejuice or co -wrote Beetlejuice the screenplay not the book oh yeah the book is
written by Stevie King yeah Steve King Steve King I watched a pretty entertaining horror movie this
week on the indie side called we are still here and it was a horror movie that came out I believe
this year 2015 and if you're a horror fan I urge you to check it out it's short it's fun scary
and it's like you know like a creepy like main haunted house kind of movie okay but like it goes
insanely gory which those movies never are I love it and it wanted to be in a good mix it was really
fun where'd you see it I rented it Netflix I still get the red envelopes I'd love to uh I'd love
that you're still doing hard disk I do uh one at a time hard male Netflix God bless you sometimes
something comes out I just want to I want to see it or like if something's not on streaming I get it
God bless you going for a nice bleeding yeah I like a blu -ray watch a hard copy Netflix plus you
know like even if you return it four times which would be low you're getting these movie for about
two bucks you can handle two bucks I just I have so many DVDs in my own that I've never watched
yeah the streaming they're certainly not sponsoring us I think we can all agree Netflix streaming
doesn't have the greatest selection a lot I guess they won't ever be sponsoring this yeah I mean
or they could actually up their thing and listen to their customers but like we tried to watch a
Friday the 13th we're going to a special Friday the 13th podcast uh we're like yeah we'll watch
one of the numerous Friday the 13th movies that have to be on Netflix streaming and there were zero
I couldn't believe there wasn't one how hot is this gypsy by the way I actually just stop talking
because I fell in love with her much like a gypsy curse is that carry were I don't know let me look
it up that's why the iPad in here I saw her in the credits I think it's gotta be her whose carry were
she's just a hot bed they announced today that they're well they've been remaking Baywatch for about
a decade but they're doing the movie Baywatch and the star will be didario yeah I mean maybe
that best looking woman alive she's my favorite Alexander didario from True Detective yeah greatest
nudity in TV history and perhaps film history she might be my favorite woman that's ever existed
I actually when I saw that today in the in the old movie trades yeah I googled your reading your
to find out that she did have a boyfriend who she dating you thought you had a chance uh I don't
know if I thought I had a chance I just I just I don't know who she dating is one of those Christina
Hendrix things where it's like kind of a nerdy dude no she's dating Percy Jackson oh the lightning
thief yeah the kid to place Percy Jackson the poor man's Harry Potter yeah I said it by the way this
is Carrie were her and look what she's doing in oh she's were her right here I would ask her to be
my life mate we got her in these pictures sorry these red carpet pictures and she's doing the whole
gypsy thing in those two it looks like they've got her wet on the red carpet like through a bucket
on her what is she from Baywatch I know her from a great movie I've mentioned on this podcast before
called King of the Ants that no one in America has seen but it's kind of a horror movie isn't a
shatter film is she oh you asked me that last time too we're having the exact same conversation
we are it's not it's a uh lovecraft adaptation from Stuart Gordon director of reanimator oh my god
what's happening and it's not the it's not a remake of the shatter film but I ask you that too it's
definitely not it's a really disturbing unsettling like realistic horror kind of like a thriller type
she was also in shark needle 2 anaconda the original anaconda yeah eight -legged freaks that's a
powerhouse cast the original anaconda sliders show with Jericho yeah eight -legged freaks with David
Arquette who she only does big spider shit a lot of big spider stuff yeah uh David Arquette is the
star of eight -legged freaks and he is also as you pointed out to me I just saw the billboard the other
day playing Sherlock Holmes in a one -man we have to go we I wish we could do a live podcast from
the balcony of Sherlock Holmes it's supposedly a comedy yeah I'm sure it's hilarious I'm still confused
by it though not Joe I don't know it's like some sort of interactive theater experience where David
Arquette plays Sherlock Holmes I've been sent a lot of material about the Sherlock Holmes I am on
some mailing list that gets me Sherlock Holmes mailers really yeah that's why I brought it up I got
it like 12 emails about it's one of those things where living socials like you want a 50 % off ticket
how about a 60 % off ticket two weeks later how do you feel about a 75 % off ticket why haven't we
gone we should go we should go I'm a hundred percent in I think we'd be like this will be hilarious
and then two minutes in we're like all right let's go I'm just so curious of what it could be it's
just such an odd thing yeah so I think now this is a hand job seen in the movie his wife his wife
is going to give a moral sex in the car here which this I found strikingly out of character for the
wife character they're Steve King they're Stephen King which means he approves of this adaptation yeah
but not the shining no not the shining he he prefers to Steve and Weber we've talked about
yeah I mean it's terrible this guy is one of the most disgusting characters I've ever seen in a
movie this old gypsy man with a big sore on his nose since I have to mention the movie
parenthood and every one of these there's also a blowjob seen in while driving in parenthood
steen bergen martin and I remember asking my mother I watched it with my parents what's going on
and I was that this is how how good my family was with handling sex questions no one answered me
they just didn't answer no one had made up an answer they just kept staring blankly at the screen
that movie has a blowjob seen in it yeah uh steen bergen's sister says whenever
whenever marannas gets tense I blow him while he's driving and later on steen martin super tense and
steen bergen leans over and then the next shot is a car crashed into a telephone pole isn't that a PG
movie it's PG 13 I mean you don't see mouth penetration who I think oh really don't see full penetration
no you don't see marannas slurping and sucking the handle this pretty gruesomely realistically I like it
yeah me too so for those of you not watching his wife giving him the blowjob led to them hitting
this old gypsy woman in the street and killing her yep and uh this big guy this fat guy is a big time
lawyer and now he's got to go on trial and you can guess what's going to happen Pat I can guess
maybe he's going to pull a few strings maybe he's not going to be honest about what happened in that
car and maybe he's going to beat the rap and maybe just maybe that's going to lead to a curse yeah
what kind of curse gypsy curse thinner curse that's right ever gotten a blowjob in a car
no really well I have in a parked car I have I never not while we were driving I have it's it's
actually very difficult to focus while on on either thing it's like you're not giving either a hundred
percent I once got a blowjob in a in an elevator at a kinkos and a kinkos yeah they're
even have an elevator there was an all night kinkos in Manhattan and a girl and I that I was
girl I was dating went went in with me to this elevator that was stationary didn't move probably
because it was three o 'clock in the morning and they didn't need the elevator and uh she blew me in
it to completion you guys really put the kink and kinkos hey can't believe I never thought of that
shows you what a kind of a comedy writer I am sure it wasn't a FedExXX oh guys these are off the
cup get a little UPS there you go Jesus I'm glad I'm glad we're all great
we're all great the uh it was terrifying but exhilarating yeah the moment of finish was triumphant
sure well usually is I mean it was I just felt like I'd conquered I wanted to tell the manager
that I did it just because I feel so proud we got away with it you know what I just didn't
you're elevated so he got off yeah his judge his big time greased up judge friend right
who was the uh the guy sucking you off in the elevator who it was a it was a it was a very nice girl
she got married I believe oh let's let's leave her name out then I'm not gonna say her name but she
got married years ago and she was a lovely girl it's a crazy thing to sit there you know you
you look at your your lovely wife of 30 years and you know at some point she probably blew somebody
and a kinkos elevator that this is just what the life in which we live this is just this is the hard
cold truth of uh of the world we live in the old days you're married 18 no one ever touched her
everyone's terrible it's actually never learned you divorced 40 years later now our man our main
man's been cursed thinner at this point oh yeah he's down to 280 he probably just thinks it's all
the stress he's well he thinks so this is just great I'm just losing weight you think we got enough
potato chips there to put across the thing that he's fat look at this he well I liked when he
we came out of the I liked earlier when he came out of the trial of the mob boss eating Doritos
yeah I think I was my lawyer I'd be like you think you get a hold off on the Doritos yeah till you
get home hey tubby that's my mob guy getting better just fat lawyer this guy does exactly what I do hey I'm
down 20 pounds think I'll eat yeah I do that stupid it's stupid every time then you get back up
and you're like what the fuck was I thinking I have a I have a light day and I go and I eat uh you
know I go get fried chicken as a celebration or a war and then you never get that chiseled lean
body that you and I deserve you know that people expect really from a pat wash and a joderos I'm
this never gonna have a hard body I have accepted it and I'm fine with that I'm fine with a we
bless have a lot of sex with each other and others you don't have to have a chiseled bunny I'm I'm
plenty happy with with having a gently soft body sure you ever see the movie hard bodies on
us I up all night or otherwise no what's it about uh it's your standard TNA movie but it's a really
good one because it was italian it was uh you know funded by Italians but made in America it's
just your standard spring break movie but it had a real even even for like an 80s tit flick real
liberal nudity it's called hard bodies they made a hard body it's too of course anybody of uh
note in it I don't think so I don't think so now 80s movie they just uh they just remade zapped
really we're starting who uh a girl and she's like looking at dogs here's the point of doing a female
zapped no offense but here's what kills me about that it's somebody saying like oh let's do like
the feminist thing and remake it now with a girl and it's like a girl if you found the male one
despicable the girl version isn't any better it's still the same person doing despicable shit yeah
right well all I remember that they did in zapped was look under girls towels and dresses that they do
what they do what else do they do they probably shouldn't have been doing that yeah it was got they
use their powers for so is this girl gonna be looking at dogs is my question I don't know I didn't
see it pad I didn't research it I didn't even bother to read about it it stars Scott Baeau and
Willie Ames who later went on or maybe before went on to star in charles and church I wonder if they
make cameos in the remake of zapped oh god can only hope Baeau I was so happy when I saw him in uh
arrested development he had great timing he was funny it's a it's a recurring theme on this podcast
I love a comeback who does he play he was Bob law blah blah Baeau yeah you know I never saw a lot
of the arrested developments hold on I'm looking up zapped on my iPad here I want to see more about this
remake it's uh here we go here we go uh 1982 oh god it's a Disney channel original movie
what is the zapped remake oh well then what if the kids seek out the original and see that it's
soft core porn it's based on a book called boys or dogs let's see here is this a remake
is there an exclamation point at the end of zapped uh if so then it's a remake no but it's called zapped
and the z is like a lightning thing okay it could be something different
well hold on I'll look it up only one of us can look up at a time pet I'm not looking it up you can't
look up on your phone every time I look over to you on your iPad I'm trying to just be here with you
be present I'm just trying to get us some uh you know some info you need the okay it's it's I guess it's
not a remake okay well now I got to take back everything I just said okay but there's the original
poster with them pulling up a girl's yeah dress with static electricity right yeah I bet it was
pitched I think it came out in like 81 I bet it was pitched like as carry but a combo they use it yeah
to look up girls skirts it's pockies meets carry here's your check no I got a whole story I don't
need to hear it here's your check says uh telekinetic powers yeah that's what he used him for let me
take this opportunity to recommend a great little pop punk band in the vein of weezer called telekin
isis they're really good it's all what they have a fantastic almost perfect album called I think 12
desperate lines that would be the place to start okay it's the one guy he plays all the instruments
writes all the songs the insanely catchy like two -minute pop punk songs he does them all in his own
they're very like early weezer check him out telekinesis that's amazing all right I mean the uh they
do a very good job in this film of showing the gradual weight loss they do I buy it oh and I
don't think it was nominated for the makeup Oscar of course not because they no matter what hard
and comedy don't get taken seriously true this fact got to really bothers me he's looking good he
yes have you seen specter yet no is that guy inspector no it's just not good oh inspector that was
weird specter uh has an amazing opening and a couple decent scenes throughout otherwise it's
pretty shitting you don't see the villain to like two hours into a two and a half hour movie Christopher
Waltz yeah at some point you're like what am I following here there's not even a and then he shows up
at the very end I just don't don't have a big James Bond interest I never have same here Joe and I
always try to convince myself I do but I don't I mean you went to see the peanuts movie the other day
saw peanuts movie alone that's where I'm at but I always love peanuts oh my god it was really not a
good movie of course it wasn't it was a CGI peanuts movie yeah the hell did you think was going to
happen but then they also like will superimpose the black and white comic strips next to the CGI
action like somebody thought that was a cool idea or else Charles Schultz be on the gray it was like
you have to do this well I think that is kind of a cool idea that was the only part that sounded kind
of neat they did when they do it once you're like oh that's cool and then by the end you're like stop
taking me out of the story by imposing drawings on not that I was into the story because there wasn't
really a story this was a misstep by the way on the prop departments part he had a corn on his
plate already and he points for another piece of corn why would you do that can he two things of corn
but why wouldn't you just eat the first one and then ask for another one all right Charles you
know what I mean I guess you know he's gluttonous but it's he's I was like that part he pulls
a piece of meat off his lap and eats it did you see that done it but it was like a nice long piece
really worked look at this here's just dessert all right not that you and I have a great deal of
self control what do you eat if you have a week where you know you can just do whatever you want
I don't know what I mean I kind of eat whatever I want all the time yeah I don't
probably shouldn't be doing that which doesn't doesn't show but I really do try to regiment myself
I have a salad every fucking day for lunch I have a juice every fucking day for breakfast
but I slip up well what do you have for dinner I tend to not eat dinner but you know on the week
when the weekend comes around you know people are like let's go do this let's go do that you go
it's some drinks you do this you do that what is your terrible genes I do my best what is your what
is your you know biggest guilt meal I don't know that I have one thing I think if I could eat
anything it would be like a sheet cake from Ralph's but I don't do that but you're big on like let's
go over to the grocery store and get a piece of cake made a circuit slow down this conversation
let's back it up just a bit I've never purchased a sheet cake and eaten it I'm saying that's
what I would eat if I had the thinner curse you're saying you need a whole sheet cake if I had
the thinner cursing it eat whatever I want my first move would probably be something in the sheet
cake family look what and definitely not like this stupid cool whip frosting with a good like
although like a red velvet with it link a cheese definitely not red velvet yeah okay I'm talking
about like a child's birthday party sheet cake which you get like in an office when somebody has a
birthday that's gross I can't believe that's the I love a cake but I can't believe that's the cake
you'd go for I'd go for like a double chocolate no I have no interest in that but now if somebody
brings in one of those like the icing flowers or like we had in my house for my birthday party I get one
spoon of that icing and I want to just go into a coma and die I think it's disgusting it just
tastes like sugar it is but like you know certainly when I was a kid I was like how do I get my hands
on somebody to me nothing beats a Dunkin Hines chocolate cake yeah we're a Betty Crocker chocolate
cake and with the pancake and then you put the chocolate frosting on it just sounds very boring
to me oh so good man so good no I'm my my biggest Achilles heel is the old you know like fried chicken
sure ribs which actually I gotta be honest I think it's helped me in some way weight wise over
the years because it's it's it's not good for you obviously food but it's not sugar heavy yeah that's
true so even if you're eating fried chicken as your shit meal you're still at least getting the protein
of the chicken and stuff there is some value to it I at some point I used to have a pretty extreme
sweet tooth and at some point I kind of lost it which is great because you just start to feel
gross about any sugar at all as you get older mine's grown over the years but I still don't have
an amazing one which is why I won't eat those damn yams thanksgiving sure I love I love the yams
I would go like restaurant wise I think I could shithouse like some some pizza maybe would be good
you know just I I'd love to have this curse it's what I'm saying I don't I don't think you would
pet he gets frighteningly thin I don't remember how it ends I don't want you to tell me and it's my
hats off to the actor because he he really does get kind of skinny in this yeah you know now he
doesn't get meconny he's skinny but he gets skinny now do you think they did cast away style where he
went away and lost the weight or do you think he played the whole movie rail thin and just pick up
adding makeup to him throughout it's probably smarter like take six weeks off production
wait that's hard on the crew like is he this entire time is he rail thin and they just keep taking
makeup away right or is he normal and then one thing him to lose weight he went away for four weeks
and lost a ton of weight I don't know that's a good question I was wondering how they do that I
was there's that one episode of it's always sunny where called how mac got fat right and it starts
with him fat the wraparound is him fat in confession yeah and then the story is when he's in shape
and I was always like how did they do that they just thought of that ahead of time basically and
shot the scenes ahead of time yeah but I was like what if he never got what if he failed in getting fat
yeah well that's the time and energy I think he knew that's what I want to do for this entire season
but what if he wasn't able to do it everybody's able to get fat I don't think it's as easy for some
people yeah you know and he's a pretty in shape fella you know it is super genetic that's really
it's really shitty this part scary where the he now he's at the judge's house here and he's talking to
the wife and he's saying I haven't seen the judge where is he and she you this is where you find out
that the judge was cursed lizard they cursed him lizard yeah and he became a lizard he's growing she's
she's talking about memory the judge had that like scaly thing on his chest yes they're that's she's
telling him like that turned into like scales what did the old gyp say to you is that what he just said
it's what she said that's a slur isn't it I didn't know anyone ever said chip in that context like
it's short for gypsy yeah that's why somebody goes you jipped me I know that you're not supposed to
say that anymore no I know but I'm saying that's what that is but how can it be a slur if like
you've never encountered a gypsy in your entire life well who's it offending gypsies are real people
it's a Greek origin isn't that I guess but it's not like Greek slur it's a slur against gypsies what's
that it's not a slur against Greeks it's against gypsies well I'm just saying like if I if somebody
was like hey that's a slur against leprechauns I'd be like yeah I never know leprecha so who cares I
think it's more like how Sicily is part of Italy okay and you're Sicilian if you didn't
soulen the Sicilian in soul of the Sicilian you're still in souling Italians maybe something like
that does that make sense yeah I guess I didn't realize you worked for the gypsy coalition I'm just
asking I'm just asking I love he calls the mob boss and goes do you believe gypsies can curse people
this this sort of shit in movies like two gorgeous girls staring longingly at Joe Montana
we just believe the shit he's a mob boss and the girls want to be with a mob well I guess I
all right you know what they say where there's fresh green there's dew on the flowers I've heard
grass in the field play ball I've never heard the other one that's something my Nana told me when
I was very young she told you the green dude oh okay Jesus Christ I'm kidding I don't know your Nana
she could be a freak guys losing weight at rapid speeds and his wife is still not concerned
there's still no part of her that's like I think he might be sick why don't they do the scene where he's
like let's bone down I'm all thin now look through that in the clumps he was like I can see my dick
I think he's freaked out at this point the man at this point is lost about 150 pounds and he thinks
that he's got and he thinks he's got like cancer or something yeah I wonder if not that Robert John
he's a good actor but I wonder if they tried to go after like thousands of big actors in Hollywood
and they wouldn't do the weight loss they had to go after bigger actors and Robert John Burke for
the lead in this movie I don't know I mean this is the article release this type of movie didn't pull
in a major star in the 80s all right you don't look at the other king adaptations night pet cemetery
yeah true uh needful things that had side out and ad Harris
the side of the main guy in needful things the old guy yeah he's the old guy oh I didn't know that
ad Harris Bonnie Badelia ad Harris and Bonnie Badelia both in uh believe in creep show
is is that Harris ad Harris is in the first story of creep show a young ad Harris I believe it's his first
film okay what is this guy's name who the doctor no the actor I want to look at Robert John Burke
Robert 12 ,000 calories a day John Burke and none of them are freaked out
number the doctors are going you eat over 12 ,000 calories today and you're still losing weight it's
incredible it's like if I was a doctor wouldn't wouldn't you be like clearly you've got a disease
that we don't have on the books yet yeah well plus losing weight that fast it's terrible for your hurt
oh he looks good these days man yeah he kept it together he's got like a rugged like older
what like big show is he in now because I think he's in a uh well he was on rescue me there it is
yeah he was the priest in rescue me I think he was in limitless he didn't say it he was in true
story the Jonah Hill James Franco vehicle maybe the worst movie of 2015 he was in Robocop 3
yeah he played Robocop he took over for well he did I think
unless I'm mistaken uh let me see here uh Jesus Christ Frank Miller wrote the Robocop was one of
the Robocop 3 script true story there is a scene where uh Jonah Hill and Robert John Burke are
walking down the worst location in film history like this like a band and riverbed and they're
walking down it and the camera is like going out of focus at one point you can't see either of
their faces and it looks like if it was in a student film you'd be like guys you can't release this
this is a major motion picture it was a terrible film what is the what is the plot well it's a true
story uh and actually at the end when they cut to the real guy the Jonah Hill played it's the first time
in movie history where the actor was worse looking than the person he was playing I was like wow so
I wonder how this pretty normal looking guy felt about having Jonah Hill play oh that's right now
this is where he goes and visits the deputy that was also part of the lie the trial the deceitful
trial this guy's been cursed with like acne or something oh this is he doesn't look good he doesn't
look good that's a Kruger from Seinfeld yes it's got a lot of shit on his face here
mm -hmm and this guy's going to say you know they he the guy touched I forget what he says he doesn't
he doesn't say acne that's not that's not a good curse word she cursed me zits yeah I forget I
think maybe it's boils or something okay but wait a second um back to true story what what is the
true story is a true story the Jonah Hill character is a actual author um he decided to go in and
interview the James Franco character who's basically like a sociopath who kind of like plays
Jonah Hill from inside jail he's like convicted of murder or something it's really really bad
and just like badly shot you could tell they both thought it was gonna be their big Oscar shot
it's not good what's the what are the performances like
Jonah Hill's like really earnest like at every scene he's trying not to be funny instead of acting
uh is he good at it no and uh Franco isn't great at either I it's I have a hard time taking
Franco seriously outside of anything where he's not oh there you go there's a good look at the
guy's face let's see what his curse is where he's not a stoner yeah I can't I gotta tell you I'm not
a huge serious Franco fan by any means but one of the few movies that has made me cry 127 hours
I loved it a lot I uh I'm a big for Franco fan I just like him as a goofy guy yeah I agree I had a
hard time with him in in Oz the great and powerful I just didn't believe that he was in con man
now the movie was terrible yeah it was not Sam Remy's best no loving that new evil dead shot
yeah as first evil dying to see it it's hilarious the actions great I love it
I don't have fucking stars so I can't watch it yeah the pilot is really really good
and it's not on uh it's not on uh what's it called uh Netflix you I know you can watch the pilot
free online but not the other ones where do you watch it on my just google watch it for free
no pop up I did he say it what he was cursed with no it's not good looking it's pretty bad
it's pretty bad right yeah so everybody involved with this hidden run gets cursed it's the three of them
yeah that's different in the it's different in the book um hold on I'm gonna
oh now that zit guy just killed himself or he popped a zit one of the uh I'm gonna go back here
because uh even with the subtitles on we missed what his goddamn curse was
hey guys I'm also gonna tell you because I only mentioned it at the very end of one podcast that
our opening theme written and performed by joder awesome it's a very catchy song thank you Pat
that's very nice sure and uh as always thanks to the fans who reach out we love your comments
I'm gonna single out someone who goes by slo gen who's always like almost does a commentary on the
podcast through twitter and it makes us feel like we're being heard it makes us feel special and happy
it is very nice isn't it thank you slo gen it is very nice boils so his was
dunken becomes mutated with large boils okay now here's what I want to find differences from the book
because in the book I think it's three different it's two different curses I don't think it's
boils I think it's uh I think it's something else Pat and I can't remember this is the hard part about
doing research and being a co -host you know it's mm -hmm well no if you had done research you'd know all
this prior to the podcast that's what researchers why can't you do what is he eating now he's eating
the car he's just picking up a turkey carcass yeah and just eating meat off of it you ever get to like a
that's something I always find healthy maybe it's not as healthy as I think but like getting a rotisserie
chicken at the grocery store I do it all the time I do it all the time too but what makes me so sick
is obviously not eating the whole thing at once the next day when the turkey with a chicken has like
that disgusting thick glaze on it mm -hmm that's so gross to me what is it uh it's the fat congeals
it's the grease congeal so you gotta peel it off I do uh but if you heat it up it'll go away I mean
it just will yeah but that's so sick it is gross it's really gross um all right plot here I'm in the
book here okay uh old man gets the scales and then Billy is cursed with horrifyingly extreme case
of acne yeah both of them eventually commit suicide all right I guess look at all like I can
uh they made it a little more like tumourous in this movie yeah which is pretty gross it's not
let look up real quick what I'm gonna look it up it's my turn I want to know what was nominated for
best makeup this year I bet it's gonna be like Elizabeth or something stupid like that
they never get they never give these movies they're due yeah now this movie should uh this movie
should have been nominated now what do you think it is wife number do I find her attractive yeah absolutely
I think I've seen her in something also I don't know what it is but
what is this 96 I think it was 96 yeah I uh I just uh was in a diner in New York who walks by Chris
North for starters sure and then they play pool with them once in New York the guy that played the
bad guy in dirty work Chris from McDonald yes most people would have gone shoot him a Gavin happy Gilmore
shoot him a Gavin as well yes uh this movie has a 16 % on run tomatoes that's bullshit this is a good
movie I agree I like this movie just just that I agree well I'm just saying I like it I'm just saying
that for myself yeah uh all right 1996 thinner the nominees were deservedly nutty professor which won
uh ghosts of Mississippi which I remember having particularly bad makeup what the hell was the makeup
in that there's a Rob Reiner shitheele movie what was the makeup in it though just like I think James
Woods played like an old racist everybody aged with the makeup was bad as opposed to now where you
go into that part where he's an actual old race and Star Trek first contact which I guess had okay
Michael what the hell is going on with James Woods man yeah I don't know I'm reading this stuff on
Twitter it's I mean I don't care that the guys are Republican but I mean my God almighty's calling
people pigs and yeah he's going nuts he is he a Trump supporter I'm sure he is I mean I bet money
I wouldn't be surprised he's a Ben Carson supporter yeah I mean he is fucking way out man yeah
yeah tweeted to Obama to put down the crack pipe didn't see that yeah now he's suing some guy
because some guy called him a coke head or something I did know that and you're gonna tell me James
Woods hasn't done more coke than you were I could ever hope to see in our lives I mean that is
look actually I take it back I don't want to get sued try this to think it for 10 million dollars yeah
you can't do that look you played lester diamond people are gonna assume you've done coke once
or twice I can't believe that's the guy that played lester diamond yeah that's amazing to me
can't believe it's a guy from John Carpenter's vampires oh hate them a terrible movie
the running joke on that is that he asks like oh what do you what do you got a little wood
get a little teak a little mahogany yeah to a priest he lists different kinds of wood yeah it's
to a priest too hey father when I wrestle you to the ground there did you did I feel that you had
a little mahogany yeah a little a little redwood a little oak I love that this is movie is I didn't
realize sponsor about redos clearly but I didn't realize it up until the late mid to late 90s
Doritos were still in the old school bag with the clear front cool ranch when did they change it
when I am done with this Hollywood life maybe a year and a half from now my goal is to purchase
a ranch that I will call the cool ranch you didn't answer my question I what was your question when
did they switch the Doritos bag I've never been a Doritos guy I don't know I missed that clear bag man
that was so much cooler than the one I hate the one they have now they're it's like a kind of an
extreme bag now and it's been like that forever and it makes it so much less fun man yeah I missed the old
logo at a class at a time you know now it's just it's cheesy looks like snowboarders eat it
we mentioned Rob Reiner last week I came over to do the Friday the 13th and we didn't wind up
doing it but I was telling Joe last month of a night wasn't it really was I was always nice to see
the that was nice to see you too but we sat down had a drink and then just didn't do it yeah I went
to a writers guild event the they picked the 101 funniest screenplays of all time number one was
Annie Hall which is not the funniest movie of all time but I don't I don't argue that it could be
that ranked the best comedy of all time yeah I think I should have just said comedy screenplays
funniest I kind of threw me off but it was really cool and they interviewed Zucker Abraham Zucker
the interview with Fairleigh Brothers they had all these writer Mr. King King anywhere on the list no one
said Kingpin it was not on the list dum and dummer was give me a break someone don't marry was give me
a break well give me a fucking break I love both those movies Kingpin is a funny look they're both
funny movies there's no way they they go both on without Kingpin I agree but Kingpin is the
funniest movie ever made America doesn't that I agree with as well I think um but what I was going to say
Rob Reiner who directed Ghost Mississippi people forget the man had such a streak he did this is
spinal tap misery stand by me princess bride when Harry met Sally a few good men like just off the
charts like every movie he made was great yeah now not so much buddy of mine's working with him he
said he's great uh and Rob Reiner hosted this event he must be 70 years old this guy was so fucking
funny yeah well he's Rob Reiner he did not he didn't read anything off the paper he was supposed to read
he made fun of how shitty the event was like there he's like what are we doing a PowerPoint presentation
then they they they list the movies like the list goes up 100 down to one and they keep putting them
up and he goes we're in one of the nicest movie theaters in America nobody thought to put a clip up
we're looking at blue yellow text on a blue screen he just was breaking everybody's balls
and the funniest part of the night was John Favreau goes up because they were honoring swingers
which was like the number 100 movie which is way too late in the list yeah there's no way
swingers is below something about Mary and dumb and dumb or I'm sorry the hangover was number 30 folks
the hangover line so he go I'm saying hangover should be not on the list I'm not saying I agree okay
so and I like the hangover font fine but it doesn't come on top 100 give me a break Reiner
is standing up there and he looks pretty good and he goes ladies and gentlemen John Favreau
on Favreau comes up and he's huge and we just watched this clip where John Favreau is in a wife
feeder looking really cut with like muscles and as he walks up Rob Reiner goes look at you
Jesus Christ you got fat holy cow and then to have to walk up here right after we see that clip
where you look so beautiful in such good shape you gotta do what I do I've always been a little chubby
then when you're chubby when you're 70 everybody's like yeah he was always chubby you your 40 years
old you come up here looking like you're 300 pounds it's crazy my god you put on a lot of weight
he goes on and on and on Favreau did not laugh not at all I wouldn't have laughed either but the audience
was roaring it was really really funny Favreau didn't laugh at all well he went up and he was like I'm
so glad I came thank you for that wonderful but you know he didn't laugh no now do you think you
didn't laugh because he was a fender do you think he was just playing like the straight man no I think
he was probably a little both they had Peter Bogdanovich there right who directed the last picture
show on my favorite movies and Rob Reiner goes first question I got to ask right out of the bag
why do you think you can wear the ass cut why do you think you can pull that off like every line he
had was great and he's killing with the audience I assume the audience was roaring that's great
Bogdanovich goes well actually it's a it's a bandana not an ass cut and then Rob Reiner goes oh yeah
that's much less pretentious what's happening now that this became an action movie now he's having a
nightmare oh Joe good call I mean Pat come on I am very frequently fooled by the nightmare
so you're you're you're you fall for that every time not every time start going hey why are you
go this movie just went off the rails you don't stop first to go maybe this is a dream sequel if it's
too ridiculous I do but if they're doing it with as they should be doing it then you can't tell I
mean that was a scene of a lizard man driving into a tractor trailer if we're watching a horror movie
driven by a gypsy this is the world where curses exist Joe I'm just saying all right I'm just saying
now he's been kind of the same size for too long I feel
yeah is he I mean he went from 300 to 150 in 20 minutes and now he's been 150 for
an hour now he's getting a little gone that's the word right yeah gone works terrible vocabulary
Pat have ever told you that get a word of the day calendar I did I got no matter I can't remember
the goddamn words anymore waste you don't need it I mean when somebody drops like some giant word
talking to me I'm like get over your fucking self I don't think all this person's really cool
because I got this huge book I know a lot of words you know I was always really into language
and shit I'm not gonna use them in conversation and when they put them in movies I'm never like oh
good writing I'm like bad writing because that's not how people talk my writing job I work with an
author and he he drops some words sometimes and not pretentiously right the way he talks and I
literally I'm like so I'm like what are you talking what's you need to dump it down a little bit
yeah you gotta use the context clues and he's always nice he will explain the word and then apologize
almost like sorry yeah but sorry you're so dumb yeah I'll say that then I'll get him against the
wall and call him a nerd give him wisdom yeah our man here our main character is in is in
pursuit of the gypsies they're he's gonna try to get the the curse lifted is that what you would do
try to get the curse lifted if you had the curse would you try to find the gypsies to get it lifted
or we'd just be like yeah fuck it this is where we're at if I thought I was gonna die yeah I'd
try to reason with the damn gypsies sure I don't think there are people to be reasoned with is the
problem I mean anyone can be reasoned with she's a gypsy I assume I don't remember I assume the gypsy
asked him to do something for her to get the curse reversed probably well where do you see all right
where do you see if they can be reasoned with because he's gonna have it encounter with him believe it
or not as you could imagine I'm surprised I didn't go the route of him going I wish I was thinner
you know like was the plot of all these movies back in the back and it you mean like in big yeah
so you wanted this to just be big yeah no phone booth that dates it let's look up the other cast
members see what they're up to and this is this podcast too low energy people again again
another can answer us though answer us on Twitter okay what's going on in your life mine yeah
I'm just working on this writing job right now for the
I'm working on a writing job I'm very that's holy cow what's up that's the daughter now she's
now 34 so she's already she's my age well I'm a little older she probably wants somebody close to
her age how should see exactly like when I said she was hot it was okay oh wow
Bethany joy lands you look fantastic she's a member of the band Everly I think I know that band
she's married oh but divorced what's Everly I think like a pop band is that what she does now
believe so let me look up acting she was on soap opera thinner one tree hill
I never saw one tree hill I always thought it was a great horror title but it's not a horror show
no it's about casting the news shonda rhymes drama I don't know what one tree hill is about I believe
it started Chad Michael Murray I never watched it I watched Dawson's Creek and that's about as far
as I went is that part of the same family yeah along with Seventh Heaven starring convicted child
molester again you got a slip in a reference to molestash who that was some really weird
shit like he's just showing his dick to children right it was upsetting come on man it was very upsetting
because I really like that guy yeah he was not always sunny yeah he's great on it he and you
believe it you're like he's the greatest guy that's ever lived and you've fought you're those stories
like oh boy oh boy yeah one tree hill who who did you say was in one tree hill she had Michael
Murray what the fuck is that some pretty boy you know some little bitch he's like a big comedy reference
guy a lot of times because he has three names I have no idea who he is I've never heard of him
you're welcome white men in tech from town like it's dances with wolves or something it's how the
gypsies talk alright what do you want you know that's how the gypsies talk the uh now I told you they
can't be reasoned with he's trying to reason with the gypsies here and they're not they're not having it
see what is this accent he's a gypsy I don't think they did a lot of research into the gypsy
community he's it's a Greek thing I'm really looking at over there huh is that the daughter still
yeah I'm looking up like it's a beautiful woman actual pictures of her like you know
more candid shots I've heard these days 34 divorced I love that she's divorced
this is what happens I gotta say you're talking about the authenticity of gypsies just looking at
duty picks it's not duty picks that's just beautiful she just looks like a nice lady
and I'm not afraid to say it she was on Mary and Rhoda which was the Mary Tyler more Rhoda reboot
I worked with Rhoda lovely lady she's still alive right she's hanging in there she has brain
cancer she's hanging in she's doing okay now yeah you know she had a ton of lines in her show she got
them she got them down Valerie Harper yeah Charlie Day was on that show really oh yeah the Mary
the Mary and Rhoda right he was the mail room kid I never knew they rebooted it I think it was
like a made for TV movie I thought oh I thought it was a sitcom all right I'm obsessed with this
daughter right now yeah I know she's with a man named West Ramsey who of horses gorgeous
oh and he's my age damn you damn you Ramsey look at this guy that's your chance again Joe look at this
guy come on brother cheats on her oh god look at this hair on that hat this one he's got a strong
his mouth what is he an actor too I mean you know who the hell knows yeah American actor
uh star of the douche award he played in charmed oh god I guess is where they met the charmed
one tree hill although she was married for about 10 years so she must have remembered him from their
charmed one tree hill does is charmed is not part of the one tree hill universe is it it was
like on the same night on the wb but Dawson's Creek one tree hill and seventh ever the same universe
no no but they were all they were all part of the wb deal oh I thought you were saying it was like
the like there was a crossover no they made a lot of shows with the same kind of aesthetic
she uh the gypsy just shot something through his hand with a slingshot
how mad would you be if somebody shot through my hand with a slingshot if a girl jumped out like she
just did and yelled ho or whatever she yelled and shot a hole through your hand with a slingshot
I mean I would be it's a great question Joe I would actually be very angry I'd be furious yeah
because my hand would have a big hole in it yeah well it would hurt too yeah the the pain part
I didn't even think about so now he's cursing them back
can he do that well you know what his curse is don't you no
uh his curse is Joe Montanian his curse is Joe Montanian he's gonna go to the he goes to the mob guy
now who who doesn't dabble in supernatural forces uh -huh he dabbles in maximum forces oh he hasn't
go rough him up yeah he's gonna go now in the way the way the white man from town retaliates
how long into this movie are we Pat I'm gonna be honest with you I like the movie quite a bit
not long enough I was uh tired to sell right kind of lose my voice when this thing started now it's
barely hanging in I'm tired to sell right now well we get we got a rally we got to give these people
what they want we are I just took my pants off I got two more days of work this week and then I'm
off for the week for Thanksgiving I can't wait beautiful I can't wait I can't wait to cook a bird
for you and my closest friends well what are we gonna watch for Thanksgiving because Eli Ross
Thanksgiving is not a real movie uh well if thanks killing is on here we could watch that is that a real
movie yeah it's the one with like a killer turkey oh god it's not on here pro it used to be I don't
know if it still is thanks killing um but I almost think we could watch like a uh like like like
you know there are so many great ones for Christmas yeah I just feel like we could watch a Christmas
one for Thanksgiving and they yeah you're right like maybe we watch black Christmas for Thanksgiving
and then we watch gremlins or something for Christmas right everything's giving I watch
plans trans automobiles my fair movies of all time my friend once said if you don't cry in the last
scene you're not a human being I don't anymore because I've seen it 80 times but I did when I saw it
first I still gets me yeah it depends on if I've had a frosty cocktail or two certain movies still
get me every time at the end Malcolm X sure at the end always gets me well plans trans and Uncle
Buck get me if I allow my brain to think about John candy the actual man what part of Uncle Buck makes
you cry there's no sad part it's that final freeze frame I I miss John candy what's the final
freeze frame in Uncle Buck he waves he puts the whole family together it's got kind of the same ending
as home alone really he knows he's washing them the mom comes home they're all hugging he waves
they're gonna be okay he's gonna be okay he taught them something they taught him something
but it ends on a sort of like a freeze frame on his face it just I I I'm sad that he's dead is all
John is that all right he was not cursed thinner unfortunately too much oh John candy I thought
Joe Montana no John candy yeah it's a bummer Joe Montana is his Simpson's character that
Tony I mean it's he's the only person on the Simpson was sad from Phil Hartman where it's like
it looks like him it is him who is your favorite outside of the the main family which shouldn't
be your choice anyway but who would be your favorite Simpson's character no no interesting
yeah I mean come on he's the best would make my top 20 I love him oh
Moe wouldn't make your top 20 he might make my you might make my top 20 come on who's your
favorite I think I got to go Lionel Hots all right and Troy McClure is on that list as well yeah
that show I mean Brandon they've had good episodes through the years since since this but when Phil
Hartman died that's kind of the beginning of the end of the show I would put side show Bob I
love such a guy on the list I love such a I'm just a sucker for Kelsey grammar anytime he talks
in that Frazier voice that's the only way he talks in interviews he kind of doesn't talk like that
and it upsets me because I just want him to be Frazier all the time yeah you know what I mean
that's uh I use a uh such a Bob line all the time it worked from uh
one I think it's the I think it's a Cape Fear episode when he's in in the uh courtroom
and he's talking about killing Bard or whatever and then he goes at chiefly with Drone when they
object to it he goes chiefly with Drone like he's taking back his uh thanks so at work whenever I'm like
pitching something if people don't like it or whatever I throw him a cheerfully with Drone they always
enjoy they always enjoy that yeah that's nice I don't think I know where it even came from I just kind of
use it as my own well that's theft yeah I learned it from the fat Jew he's talking about the
Twitter person not the main characters oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I also love uh Nelson
no not Nelson uh Milhouse Ralph Wiggum yeah yeah Milhouse is hilarious Milhouse is dad is hilarious
I like the losers in the Simpsons world where would you put Flanders?
Flanders is funny a little one note for me Mr. Burns is always hilarious Smithers is worthless
uh you know I like how you said you like the losers in the Simpsons world there are no winners in
the Simpsons yeah that's true that's true you know I haven't seen a new episode of The Simpsons in
but sometimes people would be like I watched the other night and it was really funny I don't believe
them I was never an avid watcher but I watched a couple ones from this season on Hulu and they
were funny and they were funny okay you know they were I mean I was my whole life for 10 years
comedically it's all I love them so much what's your favorite sitcom of all time
Seinfeld for sure but Simpsons if I'm just looking at like the 10 -year block that I love would be
very high up there sure sure I uh it's been on 30 years at this point it's which is nuts yeah
it's nuts remember when it came out it was such a huge fucking scandal George Bush was like don't
let your kids watch this but my parents let me watch that but not in live in color which falls
a little racist racist when you just said it yeah now you see what Joe Montana just did he
went and poisoned all the gypsies dogs right put signs up that says like the white man from town
says hi yeah you know whatever very Italian way to say it uh but you know you think this is the only
movie where the mob goes up against gypsies yeah you know I'm produced Scorsese script that was
supposed to tackle the same thing but they're supposed to finally make that Pacino pesci deniro
Nicholson Scorsese mob movie they're saying they're making it we'll see better do it quick before
they all die uh deniro's looking good deniro looks great I mean Pacino Pacino looks fine
Scorsese looks good but he's 80 and he did Coke for 30 years he's like 75 okay right
I feel like he was 40 and 76 oh this is the beauty of the iPad he's about 80 I just picked it
up and saw the guy that's dating the daughter from this movie and I hate him maybe Coke keeps you
alive I work with Garrett Morris who's 80 he looks 40 he did cocaine for 60 years
yeah Scorsese he's only 73 okay all right that's that's good and he's you know he's one of those
guys that like as long as he's directing a movie he won't die yeah that's probably true do you
know what I mean but he's always directing so he's gonna die on the set of a movie at some point
I think like he I just think he's gonna be like a lane stretch where he finally goes like
all right folks uh you know I'm done I'm gonna retire and like the next day he dies yeah he's
gonna be one of those guys so I'm married like five times Scorsese huh so I'm married like five times
that's what happened to lane stretch she was uh you know she lived in New York at like a famous
like show biz hotel uh -huh till she was like in her fucking like 80 or yeah that's all that
move out by family Virginia whatever it was die like a week later yeah or something like that
yeah you can't live in New York that long and then go to Virginia you're gonna die pretty quick
yeah it was kind of a bummer man it's saddened people like her die you know it's very comforting to
know they're out there yeah Rickles will be sad as hell apparently he was on Kimmel recently still rapid
fire all right you know I was supposed to see him but you bailed out I made a mistake Pat but you've
already seen it I'll never say I saw him with Frank Sinatra that's pretty awesome I mean if you
think you're gonna get dancing to my life and top that experience would you rather see Don Rickles
and Frank Sinatra or Don Rickles and Pat Walsh I'm gonna go with the former all right sorry
however Frank Sinatra and Pat Walsh you might have a deal there you go that might be a deal I would
sing you a little Sinatra if I wasn't clinging to the last shreds of my voice right now I mean folks
we have to talk so long for these fucking things would you just have pity off oh that kids dead
they shove it rooster in his mouth yeah they paid their kid to like go be a lookout or something
and spy on the gypsies something I don't fucking know and the gypsies knew what was up and murdered and
put a rooster in his mouth because he's a cock sucker was that boy he's a gay he's a gay he was a gay
prostitute I didn't even put that together cock sucker that's interesting thank you oh that that
made it like a lot cooler that seed yeah like it's way creepier this whole movie like you know it's
well directed well acted the makeups great the effects are great I don't understand why it's got
such a low rating because people just treat hard like porn man it bothers me yeah it bothers me
if it's not like a masterpiece they're like oh it's just stupid yeah it's like and then everybody
just decides to get behind certain things once in a while we're like what the why did you all like
this movie yeah and sick do you know much indie horse shit I've seen yeah oh yeah completely half
fast put together but because it's an indie movie and people think it they're supposed to like it it's
got like a 98 % rating a perfect example in a movie I think actually has a 98 % rating as I just watched
the academy awards screener of grandmaw starring Lily Tomlin which I would give an F it wasn't
great I despised it she was she was really great in it I thought she was kind of cartoony and not
right I thought she was funny I enjoyed her quite a bit in it but first half of that movie is so
poorly done when she's beaten up the boyfriend I was just like what are we doing here I didn't buy
any of it I didn't buy one that little girl punched her in the face she got a black eye a five -year -old
girl punched her in the face my take on the movie was three my take on the movie was it was only
good because she was good in it like if it was anybody else playing that part it would have been a bad
movie I thought she was hammy and has been better in 800 other things I enjoyed her all right what
could I tell you you're in love with Lily Tom I like Lily Tomlin quite a bit the only scene I liked
her and him was the Sam Elliott scene I thought he was great well some corn yeah I just made some
corn that's some corn I'd like to be around that guy good energy I bet yeah yeah you want a beer
right I feel like I'm still taco tonight
okay in a case of retail I would just feel safe around that guy I'll take a lot of the mild
sounds please mild you got any of them there French fries when I was on the sling blood to put those
on my taco you a tater taco give me three of the tater tacos sir this is the bank
he's crazy in this version everywhere has tacos yeah it's just Los Angeles isn't it you
me had money taco if it's the goddamn bank put some money in a tortilla and slatted over
that's how Elliott do see I pictured a money taco being a bunch of nickels inside a dollar bill
like the the dollar is the I pictured it with shredded bills as the lettuce well and it's called
the called cash lettuce and cheddar so now you already got two key ingredients so the shredded
bills are the lettuce and then what's the what else is you got to make the whole thing out of money
yeah deposit slip is the tortilla all right not technically money but fine and then you throw
a couple pennies on top yeah all right that's fine I love that my tini goes in posed as like a
FBI agent yeah oh this guy's a do it all mob using one stop shop for a mob guy what huh was he
that's a rough scene he says acid bitch and then throws it in her face we've all been there
but that's not the real acid now he puts the real
that was fake acid see to warn her about future acid so he took the time to prepare a solution
of fake acid he did it to throw in her face and then immediately tell her it was fake acid
he's really rough in this chick up why why did he do that though because he puts real acid on her
forehead in a second okay cool I find that effective you throw a fake thing on her to scare or
then you go by the way here's the real thing now all right they didn't get a take of the spitting
scene where it wasn't like a baby blowing a raspberry here's the real acid the real deal
was he pouring on her tits they poured it on her coat thank you for explaining every second
of this movie because apparently I'm not following anything I mean with the subtitles on you can't
follow it I haven't even looked at the subtitles that I demanded you put on that was a waste yeah we're
wasting good subtitle money no they're helping a little because at least I I kind of know what's
happening this is a great scene he puts the he puts a jar a mason jar of acid on top of the girls
forehead she's to lie there still so she can't move I gotta tell you I would just stand up real fast
whip up and it would flip back behind you maybe get in your hair no it would not and it one
wrong tick you know what feel a glass with acid and we're gonna try this this is what you do you do
what she's doing or she whips her head to the right or left but I think you get out from under it
look she did it right her hands are free yeah well of course she's gonna get out he gave her a
message he was just scared all right she she she wouldn't have died if the acid felt her it just
would have burned her yeah but looks like the fandom of the opera for the rest of her life
well he's got a pretty mean gash in her forehead so he says he said to her there you tell the old
man to meet us at the watch tower whatever the hell it was lighthouse with the and lift the curse
so this is this is we're in the home stretch here he's gonna go sit down on the on the bench near
the lighthouse and wait for the old gypsy man and and you know the solution's gonna come through
or do you know what the solution is no I do
go ahead do you want to let me just watch and enjoy we can't just watch it enjoy no I mean let me
watch and talk to the guy and do a podcast that we do we have to talk through the whole thing
this fucking prism this verbal prison so thirsty hard one is a drink so water to Joe
a lighthouse action you ever see the fog yes I like the original the remake was real bad
remakes terrible those remakes are never good but I love the original
here's the gypsy with the solution very interesting solution
I hate this character he's gross yeah he's gross he's got that thing on his nose
how does a man with an open sore on his nose get a woman does he does what does he have a wife he had a
daughter well the daughter was the old lady he killed yeah that's the that's one of the
gags
his uh split in some pie by a lighthouse as the horror climax yeah no he's telling he's telling
him how he's got to fix everything with this pie you bleed into the pie see
see you give the curse to the pie that's ridiculous it's that ridiculous this is pretty
why the pie this this part's pretty rough
I Joe just jumped ladies and gentlemen well because he shoved a knife through the hole in his hand
and I mean my god how bad would that hurt not rather than put a knife through the hole in my hand
then pure hand again with that pie taking that blood pie gyrene bubbly bubbly gyrene
see he puts the curse to the pie why the pie Joe because he's got to now give the curse to somebody
else oh Jesus you have a problem with this no
he's got somebody he's going to give this pie to now see
hmm because he thinks his friend is banging his wife I miss that completely of course she did
sit over there yapping I have to I know I'm kidding come on I'm just giving you who's he
thinks banging his one his uh doctor friend he thinks his banging his wife okay okay but he's not
banging his wife he's just like telling his wife he's concerned about him right you know
but this is the problem now blood for blood he's got to go now give this somebody else which that
never works out when does that ever worked out now Joe if I show up to your house with a blood pie
there anything I can say that makes you go yeah I'll take a slice of that blood pie well he's
not going to tell him it's a blood pie it's full of blood that's pulsating he doesn't know it's a
cherry pie as far as this guy knows all right did it reseal itself uh yeah it's a magic
pot cut pet all right for Christ sakes it's a magical pie here's a little hollywood trivia that
pie is actually the same pie used an American pie yeah and that's how he gets rid of the thinner
curse it goes into Jason Biggs's dick yeah I just looked up uh that pie on IMDb and it was in
American pie this movie and uh pie the Darren Aaronovsky's first movie that's one of the movies I was
talking about when I said it just because it's an independent movie he gets 98 percent oh yeah pies
on an obnoxious movie I saw it in the theater I hated every second of it and I like Darren Aaronovsky
I did too I fucking love black swan I'll tell you that much yeah I never saw it it's so good
and the wrestler is one of my favorite movies of all time I love the wrestler I think I've only seen
the wrestler wasn't he supposed to do the robo capri make yeah yeah you know you didn't see
ruckum for a dream oh yeah that was great I love that you see the fountain uh no okay how was the
fountain fountain is visually amazing it's it's kind of silly but I liked it and uh actually was
one of the people that like Noah with Russell Crowe I thought was pretty cool that's Aaronov yeah
that's the Aaronov that one a lot of people said Aaronov you know but not me I said Aaron Moore and he
said I've got it'll never be enough because I'm Darren we're really bringing out the aim material
I'm so tired that I've contemplated three times just falling asleep on the podcast well the whiskey
didn't help I didn't need that one whiskey it was like it was like a sedative doesn't have that
effect my whiskey in particular jolts me up Pat's been drinking oddly every week when we do this
or every other week when we do this I have one drink just like you no I know no no I'm not saying
you let me finish the sentence all right I'm not saying you've been drinking every time I'm saying it's
odd what you've been drinking every time I bring a diet soda and I mix it with a little vodka it's a
delicious drink it seems disgusting to me that's like a you know cream sickle or something it's really
a hate cream soda love cream so diet creams is much better it doesn't have that oh that's right he
gives the pie to his wife he doesn't give it to the guy that he thinks is banging her oh jeez it's
pretty rough because he thinks his wife because he blames her for everything because she because she
had to suck my dick yeah she blew him he crashed the car this is the first wife in history who got in
trouble for doing a blowjob okay Jesus well then he really resented her that she didn't believe
him and then he believed that she was having an affair so you know look he's he's going to die with
the dirty solos the gypsy warned him here's the next morning the assumption is the wife is eating the
pie this part's pretty disturbing I guess she just had to take like a slice right shouldn't have to eat
the whole pie yeah she just had to eat a piece okay does this daughter eat a piece of the pie too
you want me to ruin it oh sorry Joe so there
you just got blood pie this is the part I don't get is he's I mean it's gross that he kisses
like rotted wife's face why would he do that I don't know because he's he's lost a shit you remember the
Clint Eastwood movie blood work yes it's pretty bad at some point he just opens fire on a public
intersection with a shotgun I don't even think he's a cop and it maybe he is but one of my friends
accidentally he's gonna say let's go see that blood work movie he accidentally said it's in high
school let's go see that new Clint Eastwood movie blood wipe we all started laughing so hard think a
movie that's just Clint Eastwood wiping his ass and they're being blood on the paper is like the opening
scene because that's probably what Clint Eastwood faces every morning in his edge and we just laughed and
laughed blood wipe it's another blood wipe getting old how do you explain this to the cops your wife
is rotted in bed well I assume he does this shit a bad piece of pie and they go okay and leave
you know it starts a funny story I didn't kill my wife for say I was cursed by a gypsy I had this
cursed pie funny story that and here's the part where the daughter's home she's not supposed to be
home yeah that's a good old twist and there's a second plate of pie in the sink oh boy which means
the daughter is eating some of the pie and now he's upset because the gypsy's words have come to
fruition oh no she's alive she's alive she's alive but she ate it for breakfast she ate the pie
for breakfast and that's it what are you gonna do it takes a little time to incubate huh it takes
a little time to incubate I think she ate it for breakfast whereas the wife ate it last yeah yeah sure
say she just had the piece of the pie for breakfast it was delicious she's been like extra cute and funny
yeah I know this is the finishing move puts her finger into it licks it off I gotta tell you I
wouldn't accept that kiss that was a it's that kiss always struck me as odd for daughter to father she
licks pie off her finger a little seductively and then leans in like almost ass perked out and
kisses him on the cheek it was not at all a weird kiss I'm just saying I wouldn't take the kiss from
a daughter who had that pie in her lips oh that's what you were saying yeah I was saying it was an odd
way to kiss I didn't find it weird you if your mother kissed you like that you wouldn't think that
was weird well there's no affection in my family of any kind but if my mom kissed me on the side of my
mouth or something I'd be like all right I'm not talking about your mom kissing you on the cheek
yeah all loved ones kiss her saying if she sticks her ass way out sticks licks pie off her finger
all right and then perks her ass out and kiss you all right you're right you're right that would be
weird well here's Mike his friend the doctor now Mike can I interest you in the piece of pie
I think he's gonna give some strawberry pie to Mike now breakfast pie Mike's like yeah that makes
sense he said that for those of you not watching he said I'm gonna dig into a big slice of this
breakfast pie he's holding the whole pie in his hand by the way I do love breakfast pie
so this is it he's gonna die now yeah and he just called damn but that's the thing I don't get
is he laughs that he's gonna kill the doctor as he shuts the door but he's already over his daughter
dying I mean the man's clearly just becoming animal well what are you gonna do folks now he's a
single man free to do what he wants you know I think my theory is he kills himself there he thought
about it but then I think he got turned on by the thought of killing Mike and now he's fine
hey sick he's sick folks that's our podcast thinner folks I hope you're not getting thinner this week
because it's Thanksgiving hope you have a happy holiday hope you eat a lot of food say hi to a friend
kiss a loved one say hi to a friend keep the keep the tweets coming at us we love it we are
taking your suggestions we're going to start doing them once we're out of these like holiday theme
episodes um we just appreciate your feedback give us five stars and iTunes if you can a nice little
review if you're enjoying the show um and keep your mouth shut if you're not and let us know your
thoughts if uh about us going off Netflix because I got to tell you I was I was looking at
a for a movie to watch it's getting to be slim picking yeah I mean we could always find something
but we would kind of like to know if you guys are it seems like most of you are not watching the movie
along you're more just kind of so that we could just start going to DVDs and yeah and up the uh
up the classic content right right bit uh this has been we'll see you in hell
presentation of the fangoria podcast network produced by Thomas Defeo executive produced by Ken
Hanley love fangoria love Ken love Thomas never met him ever met Thomas simply a nice guy at it's
not that I don't love you times never mentioned for press opportunities advertising inquiries and
information about we'll see you and hell contact kennett fangoria dot com very nice and for those of
you that live in New York City I'll be headlining Gotham comedy club December 18th and 19th and uh I
believe I will be at the stand in grammar see on New Year's Eve so uh come on out yeah and if
your fans of both horror and the Gilmore girls I am appearing this week on the Gilmore guys podcast
which is one of the biggest podcasts there is I think that drops probably Monday the same day as this
I believe so you can get six hours of me if you want all right well check that out also if you're
in LA I have a new weekly stand -up show at Malo on sunset and silver lake called creep show come on
out and check that out and watch two broke girls sure and it's with a tenth season fifth season fifth
season yeah uh which premieres when uh it just premiered thanks Joe just premiered all right folks
we'll see you next time thanks everybody happy holidays