Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz, only available
at Bed MDM Casino.
Spin on Spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp, Raken
Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only, games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as non -mustrable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gampler, offer not available in all states
terms apply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
And now, folks, let's get on with the show and in doing so, get on!
Who is the Jojo?
Patty Walsh, how you doing?
You fucking guy!
Uh, I'm good, Jo.
Thank you.
Uh, happy Thanksgiving, recording this live on Thanksgiving.
giving, not live, we're live, you'll be hearing it later.
Yes, we had to do two today, we just did our bonus app,
which we'll be going up soon.
For the bonus folks, and this is the regular app,
this is the last app of the November month.
Will we be doing shout outs to the Patreon customers?
If folks, you can't spell Patreon without Pat.
How are you on Pat Walsh?
I'm Joe DeRosa.
You know, should we do the shout outs at the top here?
No, I think people like them at the end. Okay. Okay. Well, I one thing I do want to do before I forget here is say big big thank you to Emily
Emily your last name. I'm it's floor Florence. Oh, it is that's how that's pronounced Florence as far as I know
It looks like it says floor renaissance, but all right, Lauren. I think it's Florence. Yeah, Emily. Thank you so much Emily came out to a show of mine in
Fort Worth, Texas
and said, not only incredibly nice things about our show and how much she was a fan and everything,
but she brought beautiful prints that she had made. I saw them incredible.
From an artist, Jeremy I think is the artist's name, right? The guy that we've been
listening to. Yeah, Jeremy, they were breathtaking. These were breathtaking incredible incredible.
I heard you I couldn't if you're on Facebook follow us on Facebook and check out these prints
They're on Twitter and Instagram as well and there's a total of I think to the guy you have the guys Instagram page, right?
I don't have it on here. No, I have Emily's all right. Well, let me get let me get it
I'm and I think that what I do is Jeremy Bannison. I was a wrecked and
I'm gonna look up that Instagram while Joe talks
Emily had printed out a bunch of the
The artwork that Jeremy had done for the show literally was not commissioned or questioned
in any way to do this.
He did it just out of the love of his heart and made several prints, the latest of which
features Pat, at the top of the page it says now on with the Joe and it's Pat sitting in
a chair and my severed head in his lap and it's amazing, it's amazing, it's got our logo
go on it. It's there. I think the implication was that I was going to use your sever head
to blow myself. Uh, I've kind of always thought that's how it was going to come to an end
myself. But, um, I let me give you his Instagram. The check out these prints. Jeremy
Benison, J E R E M Y B N N I S O N on Instagram. These are, if you're a fan of the show, you
got to check these out. And we, uh, we're going to try to get some way to to sell these to you
in some way and get people paid follow Emily too she's very cool yeah she runs our
Facebook page thank you again for that Emily we talked about it the other night but we
can't thank you enough for that here's Emily follow her at e -m -i -l -y -f -l -o -r -e -n -a -i -s -s -a -n -c -e check
her out on Instagram and check out Jeremy and you guys are the best and we really appreciate
fans like you, we appreciate all the fans, and we will be doing shout outs at the end of
today's episode. We're a little press for time. We're not going to shortchange anybody, but
we got to get it in, because we've got a dinner to go to for Thanksgiving. A Thanksgiving dinner,
you might say. I'd call it a Thanksgiving dinner. Would you spill in your drink all over yourself?
Pat just took a big slip sip of a, I made us a couple of gin and tonics while we sit
here.
No, I actually spilled quite a bit.
So when you're picking up a drink that has nothing in it, and then you switch to a filled
to the brim drink, it's a rough transition sometimes.
Yeah.
And I made him a little too strong, I think.
Well, as I said on the previous one, I've had one drink and I don't think I've ever been
in the strong in my entire life
because I never drink gin, nor should anyone.
So what direction do you think
that you're gonna head in today?
Look, when you haven't eaten at 3 p .m.
and now you're on gin too, I mean, it's anybody's guess.
Yeah, yeah, cuts you in the restaurant.
You call this turkey pat, that's the steak.
Yeah, throwing stuffing in the waiter's eyes.
This turkey's burnt, why is it brown?
It's pat steak.
Joe, let me take us down to Pat's movie corner because I have a lot this week.
Okay.
I gave myself a nice little hiatus from work and I've been catching up on stuff.
Good.
I've got some stuff too.
Let's get into it.
I'm going to move through it quickly here.
this season of Nathan for you as a whole a little disappointing and I found
that it was getting mean in spots. It was starting to feel like it's always the
issue with a jackass thing if they're not doing it to each other you're kind of
like you feel bad sometimes with the people and I felt bad for the people on
Nathan for you but the two -hour finale of Nathan for you is one of the most
amazing episodes of television I've ever seen in my entire life and you know I'm
Forcing Heather to watch it. I'm trying to get Joe to watch it. It's the kind of thing where once you see it
You want to tell everyone you know to see it
And I urge you to check it out. It was an incredible if it was a documentary
It would win every award. I urge you to check it out. It's fantastic
I'm gonna save my fav for last, but I will start with
You went and saved the
Fave
Fleses
Very nice, right there you go people pet pet is ear to ear smiling as he's singing that face is turning red
I'm a little worried about what's gonna happen in this restaurant today. Oh, it's fun
No, I I I'll start out with I saw a show called there's Johnny
Which is boy, I'm going to send you a review of that show that will make your blood boil
That's all I say it's a review of the show where it's like I
Guess they just wanted to whitewash over the negative aspects of Johnny's career and then it was like
It's like the whole review is this harshly critical thing of Johnny Carson right and I was like, who the fuck are you?
Like some BuzzFeed article where they're shitting on Johnny Carson and like what an ass holy was and how he never took any chances
Comedically and though I'm like, what are you doing?
All right, well in any case go on there's shit on Johnny Carson a show
I was happy to see got made I actually auditioned for it when it was supposed to be a see -so program
All right, and I got damn close wall. I got damn close
Uh, but as one of the million things, he almost got past security, that's how close he
got.
Uh, but then he's so folded and I thought, I guess, I guess that show's not being made,
but it did get me and it got made on Hulu.
Paul Reiser is behind it.
I'm a big Paul Reiser fan.
Paul Reiser.
Nice man too.
My buddy Andrew Schultz is in it.
He's very funny in it, playing one of the, I think he's playing the role I was supposed
to play.
Okay, because I remember as always I always audition for it'll be I get auditions people when they send you an audition
They'll they'll give you like a description of the character like with random words bullet pointed or a few sentences
My common phrases come up. It's just like sad
Alcoholic rush love to suicidal. You know, I mean these are the things I have to get asshole writer right
it. So I remember being the dick and it seems that Andrew played an asshole on Mon Masha.
Yes. Yes. And what a time. And a thalander. Yeah. So anyway, Andrew is very funny and
everybody's very funny. The show is very funny. It's shot a little too much like an ABC,
like a sort of like the tone of like a like a blackish would have. Sure. And I feel that
but it's not, we're a fresh off the boat,
or maybe it's probably a better example.
Old Bergs.
Gold Bergs is a perfect example.
It has that same tone as the gold,
and I feel like that tone is such a modern tone.
It takes away from the period -ness of the piece
and some of the nostalgia.
But aside from that,
what do you think of the period of a piece like Kerry?
Oh Jesus folks. Oh boy. The uh folks if we can joke in these troubled times. I got no
problem with you with the joke. It's just you say period. Joe uh Joe blushes. This is like
this is like when you like when daddy gets too drunk at Thanksgiving. I'm not again folks I've had
a drink and a and a eighth of a drink. We're gonna be sitting in the restaurant later
Pat's gonna be like, you got any of that day go dressing?
Grabbing it like motor boating a woman's ass at the table.
What I'm kidding.
So that's that's the first one.
I have it into the enjoyable show though.
Okay.
I saw folks.
I want to recommend a fantastic show to you on TBS.
It's called search party.
I was friends created that show.
Oh, really? Well, they're great. They directed as well. I don't know if they directed but my friend Syri Violet and Charles created that show
Yeah, they they direct I wrote on a wet hot with them. Oh, okay. Yeah, they're great. They're really amazing people the
The first season I watched in one night and I never do shit like that anymore. I thought it was so fucking funny
John early one of the funniest men alive the kid is a beast
He is like internet videos make my day and him on this show every line is funny. We have the same doctor
Okay, yeah, we'll see each other sometimes in the waiting room
We'll talk a bit and you know we're friends from the scene as you are in this biz. He's really fucking funny on this show
Yeah, and I think it's gonna make him a big star. Yeah anyway
You can watch the whole first season on on various sites
But the second season started this past week. They played two back to back that we're just fucking awesome
And it's become one of my very favorite shows on television. I gotta watch I don't have cable
I miss so much of this stuff. Wait, can you is it streaming though?
I
Should be on Netflix. Yeah, I put it on Netflix. Yeah, all right, but I don't hold me that I don't
I think it's a definitely on Hulu
I watched
Finally came out Jim and Andy
Well, I'm going to meet you head on on this one, Joe, because I watched it myself.
Those of you don't know Jim Carrey made a documentary that captures all of the footage
off camera from when he played Andy Kaufman in Man on the Moon. I also watched Man on the Moon
this week. I love Man on the Moon. I do to accept for one line that I'm going to do for you right now
from Danny DeVito to Jim Carey, so Jim Carey as Andy Coppin has a fake
booger in his nose. Yes. And then he moves the fake booger to the other
nostril. And then Danny DeVito, who has known Andy
Coppin for 30 seconds, he notices the booger gag and he goes,
Andy, you're insane. But you might also be brilliant. Yeah, yeah, it's
terrible line. That is the worst, maybe the worst line in biopic history. Yeah. And it's,
you know, Davido did what he could. It's not his fault. Right. But holy shit. Is that an embarrassing
line of dialogue? And the rest of the movie is fantastic. It's yeah. The line at the beginning is
a bit heavy handed too. When the dad goes, Andy, you can't perform to the wall. You need an audience.
kids. That's a little much. Yeah. All right. Yeah. I mean, certain parts, but especially
because of how seriously he takes it, when you watch this Jim and Andy documentary
about the making of that, it makes certain things a man in the moons seem pretty funny because
they're so stupid. And they're taking them so seriously. So there was all this footage for
man in the moon. According to the opening card, it's been in, it's been an evolved for nearly
25 years. I don't think that that is anywhere near correct. I believe it most that movie is 20
years old. It came out in 1999. Yeah, so, um, anyway, uh, but you know, care it, you know,
to what you think it is, Jim Carrey became essentially Andy Kaufman during the entire shooting. Super
committed, created an Andy Kaufman experience off camera in between shots. Studios didn't want the
Material to come out because they thought it would make them look like an asshole. They wanted the movie to do well
And they and the studio's right it did make him look like an asshole
How about those scenes where his the guy playing his dad and him have like these emotional breakdowns in the makeup trailer?
Yeah, I wanted to slap them both in the fucking face that dad character a day player coming in the do like ten lines
He's gonna suddenly he's living through
Jim Carrey's Andy Kaufman and being his father.
It's a little absurd.
Get the fuck over yourself.
You could tell that the one guy,
everybody is sort of buying into it.
Mealous Forman.
Yeah.
DeVito is even like being called.
Mealous comes off like a saint in that moment.
Yeah.
They're all kind of buying into this and playing along.
You can tell that the one guy that really isn't is GMati
and he's just kind of,
he's always off to this side just kind of laughing.
Jimmy is his awesome and man on the moon and also awesome in this documentary like you realize like the the actual person I
Look the worst brag ever, but when he came to SNL I spent some time with him right because he was terrified and he's like
The nicest guy the reason he's the only one in that movie not
crying
Because of the the feelings that Andy Kaufman through Jim carry awakens in them is because he's the only normal person on the fucking set
But you know when he was on SNL he was like so let me ask he goes how many people did they ask before me was it 40
Please don't tell me it was more than 50
It was 60 wasn't
You're telling me it was 75 people like the first thing he said to me and I was like you know
It was just such a treat that he was as delightful in person. Yeah, so then I'm sure somebody like that that normal
being on a set like that has got to be like, what the fuck am I got myself into?
Well, he says at one point, when they're interviewing him, he was just a day
player. This is well before he was famous at all. He was not a famous guy yet
and he was the guy at that time that everybody said, oh, that's the guy from private
parts. Well, he should have won Best Sporting Actor for private part, I would
say. I agree. That is one of the all -time great performance. It's, it's, it's a
really is. It's managed. I think it's the best he's ever been. Yeah, you got damn motherfuckers.
You sons of bitch playing pig vomit. If you have you haven't seen fucking private parts,
there's an underrated movie for you. That's a good biopic.
So on the same night is the re -release of Return of the Jedi at the Mid River's Mall 6th cinema.
The worst, my least favorite of the special editions because they added the song and dance number two.
Yeah, I like a song and dance. Okay, the results are in my pants. But anyway, this movie essentially
is supposed to be a tribute to the spirit of Andy Kaufman and what that spirit meant to
Jim and do you like Andy Kaufman?
I do, but I also kind of don't give a fuck.
I have it in context.
I'm not like, he's like my least favorite character on taxi.
Well, I don't like him on taxi.
I don't want a huge taxi fan.
I gotta be honest on a taxi.
But here's the thing.
What happens in the end of this flick is, they're not in the end, but like overall what
you take away from it is, it's really just Jim Carey celebrating himself.
He refers to himself throughout the entire interview as third person. Yeah, and people spoil our alert and I texted Walsh immediately Pat
I texted you immediately as soon as this happened
He says after they should stop this the last segment he goes after we stopped shooting
I was supposed to be in the REM video for the movie. I didn't want to be because right. I was done
Being Andy Kaufman. I didn't want to go back to that. I had lost myself. I it's all making sense
like I get it dude you went deep in and he's like this has limits you got to stop yeah
the last time the movie is Jimmy guy goes I wonder if I could do that with other people like
what if I just decided to just to be Jesus that's the last line of the fucking movie yeah
then he kind of like shrugs like fake humbly and like takes his microphone off yeah and he goes man
we got into some heavy shit there mic drop literally mic drop which which made it worse so when he
He said, we got in some heavy shit there.
It's kind of like saying, I think I kind of just dropped some truth on you that maybe
I'm Jesus.
That's how I took it.
That's how I took it too.
He was like, so I think I just kind of accidentally let it slip that I'm Jesus.
Yeah.
And my text to Pat was.
He's an egomania.
Carrie vaguely compares himself to Christ at the end of this end of the coffin thing.
I love the fucking documentary, by the way.
I enjoyed it.
The footage is amazing.
I wish every move I've ever seen had I had a 90 minute documentary about people behaving badly on the set
I mean what a dream the footage was amazing to watch
I love the Jim Carrey's idea where he was like I wish this behind the scene stuff was merged into the actual movie
Yeah, I thought that would have been fascinating. Yeah, they did that a little bit in American splendor
And it worked very well
Favorite a lot of American splinters when Paul Jimmy looks at the mayor and he goes now there's a reliable disappointment
My that's a great one. My favorite line is when he's still a kid at the beginning walking away. Why does everybody got to be so stupid?
I was just like I've never related more in my life to a sentence.
Yeah, but here's the thing. Oh, I'm sorry. No, I was just going to say.
Well, this is all I was going to say. My favorite part in the coffin thing is, and this is this made me.
I loved that this happened, but it also made me not like Jim Carrey Moore.
He's roused and Jerry Lawler through this whole thing and then they're cutting to Jerry Lawler and he's like
Yeah, he's like I knew Andy Kaufman. We were friendly
It was like when we were in private. He was really respectful. It was a show
He understood when to stop and he's like Carrie is doing the show with me privately and rousing me constantly
Yeah, and he just won't stop and then finally Lawler snaps on set
Well, the movie made me love Lawler.
Yeah, I already love Lawler, the king.
But it's the scene where it reveals that they're actually friends where you're like,
oh, thank God this is okay.
And when they're shooting that scene, in between takes where they're supposed to be friendly
in the scene, Carrie Rouse's, Jerry Lawler so much, Lawler goes after him, grabs him, starts
beating the shit out of him.
They have it on fucking camera.
And then Bob's mood and somebody else go to break it up.
And they peel them apart and Lawler's just screaming remember this I can do this anytime I want
Yeah, and I'm like such a great thing to say to a guy that has it come into him
It's just like just remember I can do this whenever I want right, but then I was like well, maybe that's fake
Yeah, maybe well, we have the news reports. I was like this feels a little fake. I don't know
Maybe Carrie was like we can't reveal that Jerry would do I was gonna do this to him, right? I don't know now
Off that this inspired me to rewatch a liar liar a
Movie I had a lot of affection for when I saw when I was like 17. It's not great
No, but you know like I had seen
Okay, so Ace Ventura is sort of reinvented comedy. I've heard it does not hold up well, but
But I was like, what the hell am I watching?
And I loved it.
The mask was very entertaining, dumb and dumb or obviously a masterpiece.
And I went along with Jim Carrier for a long time where like everything he made I liked
to some extent.
And I remember really liking Liar Liar.
I watched with the other night folks.
This is a terrible film.
It's terrible.
Absolutely terrible.
And he plays the entire 90 minute running time.
he plays, I can't lie, as a screaming sociopathic maniac
where in every scene he is screaming at the top of his lungs.
Why would you go that route with this material?
You have a great premise.
Why are you screaming in every scene?
I hated him and I hated the movie.
And I was shocked because I always loved it.
It's the same thing in the...
What's the Ricky Gervais movie with Louis CK?
We're invention of line.
Yeah, it's the same problem to me thematically
that that movie has where it's like just because you can't lie
doesn't mean you have to say terrible shit to everybody
at the time.
That's right.
I mean like every scene like in the bar with Louis
he's like I took a shit and then I jerked off right after
and it's like you don't have to,
you wouldn't be just revealing everything.
That's right.
You just wouldn't be able to have fake an answer for something and that's my problem episode on my show
We did that that shall not lie and he couldn't lie the entire episode and it was
Anytime we did that so it felt too stupid. It was like he he can't
He can't just be openly condemning himself
He just has to be if cornered and asked a direct question then he can't lie and
You'll we learn the lesson immediately that everything becomes
It comes unbelievable if you go the other route,
but every movie about lying goes that route.
Where now that I can't lie,
I'm gonna tell you the worst things about yourself.
That's not what it is.
Yeah, right.
No, it's like if somebody came up and said,
how does this dress look and you went terrible?
Yeah.
That's not being able to lie.
You're right.
Yeah.
Not lying, it's not going after somebody cold
and going, you look like shit today.
Exactly.
The funniest joke in the whole movie,
and it's the one time they do it honestly
And, you know, naturally or whatever, is when he's talking, he's having the heart
dart with the sun at the end and the kid goes, my teacher said, real beauty's on the inside
and he goes, that's just something ugly people say.
And he says, it so sincerely, and you're like, that's fucking great, like that's how that
movie should have went.
There are about 10 funny moments in Liar Liar, and that's enough to be a good comedy
to me.
But, on the whole, it was, I really was just bummed out by it.
And I wanted, it made me like all these movies I think I like that I saw when I was 15.
I bet if I re -watched on my name, I've gotten rid of a lot of movies because I bought things
because I was like, oh, I thought that was fun and then I go, oh, what am I doing?
And I've really scaled down the collection because of that.
But I also, that movie, because of the release, it came out on the same time, I always have
comparisons in my head between that and Devils advocate. Like I always picture
fucking love, Devils. Jim Kerry in the bathroom in the law house with Keanu Reeves.
Like I they there's a very similar vibe and they come out in the same year.
I see what you're saying. But Devils advocate is fucking awesome.
I my last one is what it's been for the last few weeks. But uh, perfect strategy.
Yes. Yeah, I want to keep up. This has become my favorite part of the show.
It is reliving my old favorite perfect strangers episode. I want to keep up to the audience and you on this journey
I'm deep season six now. Yeah, I'm officially through five. Are they living with the girls yet? No, okay
But the show is it's gone. It's the show is gone
It is jump the shark so hard. I can't believe I can't believe there's not a term about perfect strangers that means jump in the shark
It is it is just all become wordplay jokes
Give me give me the worst examples, please.
There was an episode today where I was watching it where Larry's like old I I love so much that on Thanksgiving day, you're watching
Deep season six episode the perfect. I put three in today. Okay. I put three in today. Yeah
The worst joke I saw today was Larry's friend from high school comes back and it's one of these things where his friend was the cool guy that always treated Larry like crap
But Larry looked up to him so he let him get shit on sure and the guy comes back and Larry wants to impress him
That's the basic plot, okay, but the guy's name
It's like is like
Bucky
So then literally the joke is just bucky balky balky bucky
Bucky this is balky, but like it like it's it's so it's so gone
Yeah, it's so fucking gone. There was an entire episode today called black widow was the name
Now, real quick, just to interject, when you talk about how it's gone, I watched a couple
this week because weirdly in my bedroom, I can get Hulu but nothing else.
So I was watching Perfect Strangers and there was an episode where, and I think it was
the roller skating episode that you recommended to me, but Larry says to Balky, it's the one
right before they're going to go to Las Vegas. And he goes Las Vegas, that place goes against
everything I was told I believe. Right. And I was like, whoa. That's a deep fucking joke.
Yeah. Perfect strangers. That's like a joke about like religion and faith. And they just
dropped it in the middle of this really stupid episode of television. Yeah. And that's the
It's sort of thing that would always keep me coming back to like a mama's family, perfect
strangers, a golden girls, because there'd be these amazingly written jokes that you're
like, whoa, whoa, whoa, like there's somebody in there who's great trying to get out of
this format.
It's why, it's why, and you're saying that went away by season six, I assume.
Yeah, the first five year in pretty safe company, season six, it's gone.
It's why the, it's why like eventually the golden girls wasn't quite as good, right?
it. It's why the it's the same way the honey mooners jumped the shark. Yeah. Where once they lost the
elements of realism, where you're like, that is so that character and that's a really, really
well written joke wrapped inside of a very broad premise. Right. Once that went away and it just
became about like, let's have this one do this gag and then this one do this again. You're like,
but that person wouldn't do that. That doesn't make any sense anymore. So black widow. Yes.
And then I watched another one about the ring about him buying which was actually funny in season six where he buys Jennifer the engagement ring.
Classic stuff buys it out of a jewelry dealer called like diamond Devon or something out of the trunk of his car.
And he's like, I got twice the diamond for half the price. She'll never find out. And then as soon as he gives it to her she's like, I have to have this appraised immediately for the insurance.
Yeah, and he's like we've got to switch the ring. It's ridiculous, but it's fun already. I'm immediately on board that one
I really enjoyed that that's worth your time in season six. I'm very interested
But the black widow episode
He's writing a piece about us about serial killers in Chicago
And he's looking through like city records and like the newspapers and things
for information sees a picture of Marianne Balky's girlfriend. She's apparently a serial killer
and you know and he thinks Marianne is now a serial killer she's been she's been let off off
four trials because they couldn't find a body all right goes to Jennifer he's like this is Marianne
you're living with a serial killer she's like well they don't even have the same name Larry's like
No, it's it's zero killers traditionally. They always use it annually. Yes, but they use their same initials, right
I don't know if that's true
And then he's trying to come into bulky that she's a serial killer
Bucky of course doesn't believe him
This is bone man. Yeah, here's one of the jokes in it back. He goes oh Larry
Oh cousin Larry now that you've saw the crime the case of Mary and the serial killer
Why don't you go see if you can see who killed Lara Palmer? That's one of the jokes
That's like, that's an end of act joke in this thing, all right.
Here's the, here's the climax.
Balky's going camping with Mary Ann.
Yeah.
Mary, he's, he walks in the department with a hatchet.
Larry goes, what are you doing with that hatchet?
Balky goes, Mary Ann said she needed a new camping hatchet.
So I bought her this.
She said it would be nice and sharp.
and Lyre's like, I think she's gonna murder Balky.
And then goes to a mountain where they're camping.
Ties up, Mary Ann.
Ties up Mary Ann.
Attempts to save Balky.
They get like stuck on a cliff.
I mean, it's got that's pathetic. So the centerpiece of this episode ends up being
balky and Larry stuck on a cliff and they need Mary and to help them, but Larry doesn't
want to help because he thinks Mary is going to kill them. And it's so obvious that a writer
just was like, what if we had these guys stuck on a cliff? Okay, well, how do we get them
to the cliff. Well,
ever you had that idea where he would think Mary Ann was a serial killer.
Well, now that's the one I want to watch more than anything else.
There's your perfect strangers.
I would like to call attention to probably my favorite movie of the year so far.
It's a movie that's doing very well at the box office.
And I'm glad to see it. It's called Lady Bird.
Uh, it is written and directed by Greta Gerwig, who was an actress.
I like, you know, never blown away by, but I like her.
But boy, oh boy, this was a hell of a, hell of a picture.
Uh, Lori Metcalf, one of my favorite character actresses of all time.
Of course, Jackie from Roseanne, also Uncle Buck, many other things.
And Tracy Letz, who I've never liked, but he's incredible in this movie.
Who's Tracy let's hear he's a playwright and he was an actor on homeland and a bunch of shit
But yeah, I guess he always plays an asshole and in this movie he played like the best dad ever and I loved him and Lori
Matt calf is really good in it and it's got C or C Ronan
From Brooklyn, which was my favorite movie of a couple years ago. Mm -hmm
And you know, it's one of those indie movies where like it gets great reviews and you're like
I bet it's probably not this good and then you go see it and I was like, no, it's it's definitely fucking that good. It's like
for me personally
My favorite movie of the year so far lady bird check it out great great movie. It's a it's a throwback to like like the late 90s kind of indie movies
We're like everything seemed to be good like a Juno kind of thing
It's way better than Juno. It's way fucking late. When you said the late 90s movies though
What do you mean? Well Juno's not late 90s Juno's like mid 2000 or something
Oh, you know like in the late well, I'm talking like the happiness days and in the company of men or whatever like
Okay, every in new movie was like something pretty special, you know, yeah
It was original and yeah ghost world. No, that kind of yeah, before they started putting you know archers of loath
guitar riffs in every single right. Yeah, I got you and
And it's just, it's got the same feeling.
And it had, you know, there's maybe one or two movies each year
that kind of tear me up.
This was, this was mine this year.
Last year was other people with Molly Shannon,
which was a similar movie to this that I loved.
And it was, of course, Manchester by the sea,
which I consider a goddamn masterpiece.
I love that film.
But this lady bird was something special. I urge you to check it out. And the last thing I'll mention because I have to mention it
Is that I am good friends with a gentleman who
Randomly got asked to be in the screen actors guild nominating committee. Mm -hmm. So he gets every screener of every movie that comes out
I just borrowed a shit ton of stuff from him. I can't wait to watch but
But this year, he was one of very few people who got their hands on a copy of a little
picture called, I love you, daddy.
All right.
Written, directed by, and starring Mr. Louis CK.
How is the film, folks?
I mean, just imagine you were in trouble for doing something pervy.
imagine the absolute worst possible thing that could be coming out during that
controversy it was so my skin was crawling every second of this thing he's got
Charlie days in it for like Charlie day plays a big role in it I know Charlie I
love Charlie I don't know I mean at one point in this movie Charlie sits and
And throughout the entire scene, it's 80 Falco yelling at Louis C .K.
Throughout the entire scene, Charlie Day is behind her miming jacking off for two and
a half minutes, Charlie Day, in a frame with Louis C .K., mimes jacking off while a woman
is in the scene.
But he's not doing it to be like a matchmaker in front of him.
He's doing it to be like, ooh, like trying to make Louis laugh, I would assume, right?
It is still kind of squirre.
You're watching it after these allegations, it blows the mind how on the nose it is.
And then there are three to four scenes where Louis C .K. and then John Malkovich explain
feminism to Chloe Grace Moritz.
And they make you sick and then at a certain point you're like, does he know that this is fucked up that these old white men are lecturing this young beautiful woman on feminism?
Or is he just writing it as if it's right?
And you don't know.
He's a smart man.
He probably knows.
I don't know.
Then there are scenes in the film where,
and I'll say there's five, six, seven, eight scenes in the film,
where women say to Louis CK,
look, men are perverts, it's okay.
You don't have to apologize.
Ooh, I understand.
Men are perverts.
Don't apologize to me.
They're, I'm not kidding,
but I say 10 different women tell him.
basically look women love perverts they're lying if they say they don't and he
also has 10 characters in the movie referred to him as a master you're you're
the best writer I've ever seen oh my god the best writer in the world it's to
To me, it's the most damaging thing Louis CK has put out other than his dick.
That's absurd.
It is entire career.
And I will say this.
I lost this at like a party last night.
And this room sat, it was one of the, it's how people must have felt when they first saw
the room back in the day.
I mean, I was, we were dying laughing at this thing because it's so fucking pretentious.
And on the heels of this controversy,
I mean, this thing's gonna blow your mind if it ever gets released.
It'll never get released.
In fact, I think you could be jailed for watching it.
I felt like I wanted to go to jail after I watched it.
I'll say this, you know, Louise has been, you know, a friend over,
not a friend Lee over the years.
Sure.
We don't have each other's numbers, but he's, I had to open for many times
and he's put me in his TV show and stuff like that.
And I've always had a very natural relationship with the man.
And I don't condone of any of this stuff, you know?
But it's a bummer.
It's a real fucking bummer especially for the women
on his obviously, for obvious reasons.
But I will say when I saw that trailer,
I was like, wait, this was the movie that just got shown?
Yeah.
Because it came out, like because it was like,
they shove the premiere of this movie because of this New York Times thing and then you read
the New York Times thing and then you watch the trail and you're like, this is what the, this
was the movie. Yeah. And it's pretty, it's pretty crazy. It is like, here's how Louis
CK tries to endear himself to the viewer because he knows that his character is so hateable in this
fucking thing. At one point, he's like, his daughter, Chloe Grace Morass is like, but
daddy, she keeps calling him daddy. That's, that's the weirdest part to me. Yeah, she's
walking around in a string bikini the whole time. Yeah, and I, the title of it, I love
you daddy. There's a huge celebration in the film when she turns 18. It's like this huge
celebration. It's fucked up. And then Malcolm is just playing Woody Allen, basically, because
because he's scared to have his daughter alone with Malcovic.
Malcovic, given the most hateable role,
I think that's Louie making a commentary on when he worked
with Woody Allen.
Yeah, I guess he's conflicted by it or something.
Okay.
But, I don't know.
I mean, for what I saw on the trailer,
I mean, the movie is, the movie is,
it's such a grip off of a Woody Allen.
I mean, I'm sorry.
I'm not sure.
Well, no, absolutely.
I mean, the guy's artistic ability, but I just mean like it's it's it's manhattan. He tried to make manhattan
It's a black and white film it deals with an older man and a younger woman. Chloe Gracemore. That's looks exactly like
Neural Henning. Yeah, they're playing jazz music movies black and white. They're playing this shit
So like Woody Allen plays this shitty jazz music in all his fucking movies, but Louis CK is playing a
Version of jazz music so shitty that it sounds like the score to sex in the city. Well, that's a thing
It's an actual jazz fan like Maramba's and shit
the movie sucks and
Eddie Falco
Yeah, beyond now be honest honestly because I mean the movie does sound not great. Yeah, be honest though
Put all the controversy should out your head. Is it in any way a redeeming film? No, no, no, no, it's just a whether or not any of this happened
You say this is a bad movie to finish my sense from earlier. He like to make you more relate to him
He talks about his daughter's like but dad don't we can we just take the jet and he goes
I'm not rich enough that I have a jet and he goes I have a card where I have access to a jet
Right, that's like that's what what he uses to humanize himself and at the beginning of the show
They're all celebrating because he sold three shows that week it plays like an entourage episode
It's it's fucking shitty. Oh boy
But Edie Falco one of the best actresses in America
Carmella soprano, perhaps my favorite TV character of all time.
And she walks into this fucking movie.
She's playing the like line producer, the scheduler.
And she is chewing Louis CK out,
because it's April,
and they're supposed to have a show ready to go by September.
She's screaming at him and then she starts crying about it.
And that's somebody so fucking out of touch,
even with his own business, because when I started writing my show, for example, you start writing in June
to be taping episodes in September. So in this show, he's starting in April to air in September, and
Edie Falco is sobbing,
because they don't have the time to creatively express themselves.
Well, because he sold three shows.
He sold three shows. I put my heart and soul into this company.
It is the most embarrassing scene. Everybody in the movie is is worse than they'll ever be again
The actors are bad because they're given unplayable material and
the Falco scenes are particular
When she's coming in like we've got to make the schedule
With the schedule yeah, I could not believe what I was saying. It's it's unwatchable
I wonder if that film will become like the Jerry Lewis clown movie. I think it will you know
I really do think it will
Wow, because this was a room of very funny people, comedy writers.
And I was laughing real hard the entire night.
There's a lot to chew on.
And it could get that kind of midnight movie, like, crowd of assholes live.
It was that funny to watch, because it's a guy who just is completely unaware.
It's like he basically, that was my joke.
I was like, they should have called this movie Exhibit a
Because it's like you could just show the movie in any trial of Louis the K and he would go to jail
Jesus
Oh boy, but all right. Let's move past. Well, yeah, that's what I was trying to say earlier. It's like
This whole thing is so tough
I hope I hope that our fans understand us enough that we can speak honestly and candidly. I don't like to be part of the pile on
with something like this.
And it's like, I'm not trying to just pile on the guy.
I've had a nice relationship with the guy.
I didn't know about any of this shit.
I'm sad to hear about it.
You know, again, I feel bad for the people
that had to deal with it and it sucks.
And, you know, I will say this too.
I also don't think it's fair that he's getting clumped
right next to Harvey Weinstein, which is, you know,
but this movie is, it was, it sounds troublesome.
I mean, you know, how do you talk about, I don't know what to say, mild, troublesome is mild.
Uh, let's, uh, let's skip the scary stuff this week, because we're, we're really
close.
He's got Chloe Grace Morath sitting on his lap in scene after scene.
I mean, all right.
Let's move fast.
Uh, let's move past the scary stuff, just scary stuff.
I got nothing for Joe's scary stuff.
I had something in it sucked and I don't want to, I don't want to do it just a bad shit.
Really just a re -recommendation for that John Carpenter anthology on vinyl. I've been
cranking out pages writing
listening to nothing but that album over and over and over. If you're a creative person, it's like
it's great stuff for writing or whatever you do.
Well that works and I was doing some writing myself to the lost themes records and those came
up before we ever did scary stuff. So if you don't have John Carpenter's lost themes,
times, values, one and two, do yourself a favor and get those beautifully, beautiful,
beautiful, beautifully written, very, you know, you could throw any one of those songs
into any John Carver movie it would fit right in or Stranger Things or the guest or all that
show, which brings us conveniently to our movie for this week's
uh, brawn cell block 99 and I would say it brings us conveniently to the movie because
this movie is basically a throwback to a John Carpenter style, yeah, 70s exploitation kind
of flick. Yeah. Uh, in fact, I was telling our friend James Pinkstone today about the movie.
I said, I think you really like this flick. He goes, what's it called? He said, brawn
cell block number nine, he starts laughing and I go, I know the title is awesome. He goes,
yeah, did fucking John Carpenter make it and I was like, no, man, but it's, it's very much
the vein of that. It's the guy who did Bone Tomahawk, which we never did an episode on, but
we discussed on the show. The company is CineFamily, great company doing really cool stuff. Wait,
CineFamily? Or CineState, excuse me, sorry, oh shit. CineFamily was just shut down due to more
sexual desaligations. Sorry, I just wanted to make that clear. CineState is the company, excuse me,
and they're doing some really cool stuff, the first of which I believe was Bone Tomahawk. Bone Tomahawk,
we discussed, but it came up again on the Facebook page. I mean, it's a Western, I would
say a slow but very entertaining Western. And then it takes a turn into cannibalism. And
there is a scene that is one of the most troubling things I've ever seen in a movie in my life.
And I'll say this, it was the most disturbingly violent thing I'd ever seen until I watched
brawl and sell block ninety nine yeah and there's the thing at the end of this
one I was like this is going to be this guy's like shummel on twist like the
end of every one of his movies is gonna have a the a violent thing that is so
disturbing I know that uh he's just constantly having to outdo it but we just saw
well this is a film it's okay this is a film Vince Vaughn like you've never
seen him before as they often say, wait, I do know how I was going to say, on the Patreon
that we just did, I'm going to drop a little business for us.
We just said our Patreon bonus episode, and it was fantastic.
It was an hour plus, and we talked about what are the scariest scenes in non -horror movies
that you've ever seen, and Bone Tom Hock didn't make either our list, but that would be
a great example.
Right.
We're basically a western where it suddenly has the most horrific thing you've ever seen
in your life. Right. Uh, this, this movie, are you, are you talking about the skull bit?
I'll just say it. If you don't want to spoil, then stop listening. But here's the sport. It's
an old, fashion revenge movie Vince Vaughn who is fucking awesome in this. He's really great. He's
really, really great. Uh, but he's just a guy. The gets out of prison. His wife's been cheating
on him they work it out she gets pregnant he goes to jail again they believe that he's
maybe an ex -boxer right and he's got some skills they establish early on that he's
almost a super humanly strong man like he when he finds out his wife is cheating on him
he beats the shit out of her car like to the point where I love that same he like rips
the hood off he goes fucking crazy yeah and it's almost it's almost not believable
But they keep it right there in the line and then he goes and then he goes in and works it out with her emotionally because he just handled his business with her car
Yeah, and when he goes to prison he goes to prison because he's doing a drug pick -up. Yeah, the two guys he's with
He says if I say ditch the product you ditch the product and they're like yeah, sure
He hears the cops he goes ditch the product the guys don't listen to him
They get in a shootout with the cops.
Vince Vaughn goes in, shoots the two cruxies with
to save the cops basically, then gets arrested,
then the cops are like, just rat on your friends.
Like you did the right thing and he won't fucking rat.
He's just a man of honor and superhuman strength
that ends up in jail and then it escalates from there.
And then they get him fucking naked in this movie.
And Vince Vaughn's been at the outer limits
It's about out of out of shape for a Hollywood actor for about 10 years, but he takes it easy, 20, 10, 20, he takes his clothes out of
And this thing and it's not like you're not like wow look at this hunk, but you know, he's like a dude and I love that
He didn't get all jacked up for it. He's just like a dude and then throughout the whole movie, he underplays everything, he was excellent in it.
And they keep you they keep you holding on for maybe a little too long for my taste before you get that revenge that you want, but that's the 70s style.
So when the revenge does come, it is extremely satisfying, but holy lord.
It's juicy.
That's juicy.
The skull scene that I was referring to when he stops the curb stops the guy basically and then flip some over and you see what he looks like.
Yeah, that's the thing I'm talking about.
I mean, holy lord.
He stomps it guys, he stomps it guys head, face first into concrete.
Yeah, then he runs it along the floor.
Yeah.
And then he kicks the body and flips it over.
And the guys, the holes of the face are still there, but that is it.
His face has been like ground away.
I mean, holy shit.
I was, I was loving it and honestly, it's the kind of movie that makes you like cheer
for when he says like, they're gonna rape him bloody, you're like, you're cheering almost
because you, they, in a very short succinct amount of time they make you hate all these
guards so fucking much.
Don Johnson, once again, Don Johnson, one of the comebacks of the century in my opinion, I
I don't like Don Johnson, I never have.
And I always wish they'd gotten somebody different,
full disclosure.
But like, why weren't we given that satisfaction
of him going all the way up the chain?
That's what kind of let me down about it.
Because, because, see, I liked that they didn't do that.
Here's why.
First of all, Don Johnson, let me say this.
Came back in, in Django Unchained,
came back in in this.
He's pumping up in these weird bit parts all of a sudden.
I think he's fine.
I'm enjoying Don Johnson lately.
I'm thinking, I think he plays a very, I like to mention 10 cups.
He plays a very good, unlikable guy, he's just good at it.
But I like that he didn't because it wasn't about, I need to kill innocent men for no reason.
Vince Vaughn respected the fact that Don Johnson was the warden in this place and he was a
prick and that Don Johnson was treating Vince Vaughn the way he would treat somebody that he
thought was a fucking lunatic, right? And he was like, I love that, dude, he kills the
guys he needs to kill. He calls to the wife. He says goodbye. And I like that Don Johnson
got it, too. He's like, you got your phone call, make the phone call. And then we'll square
this away. I like that they did that. I thought that that was cool. You've sold me on it.
You've sold me on what I already knew in my heart that I did love that ending to the movie.
But there was a part of me too, even when the movie was ending at like the two -hour
15 -minute mark, which is long for this kind of movie. I
Did sort of want him to like video game style go up the chain. You just want that release, but
That said I thought this was a really very well done movie and I loved it and this new cop police brutality drama
that they're doing with Vaughn, this director, and Mel Gibson, I don't know what the hell that's going to be.
What's that about?
But I feel like the director, and this is why people are getting a little uneasy about this guy's projects,
they're, it's always Vince Vaughn in this movie exclusively going up against minorities.
In this film?
Other than Johnson.
In a strange way, I would say.
I guess, yeah, you're right. I guess because the first guardian attacks is a black guy. Yeah, the bad guys that he has to betray eventually are his panic. Yes, or yeah, I mean there was there was a strange element to this, but it's just because
when he put together this new police brutality movie with Vaughan and Gibson people were are like their ears kind of parked up and then to hear that it was about
like cops who finally fight back because they're sick of you know people giving
them shit everybody was kind of like what is this movie going to be well maybe
it's maybe they fight the corrupt cops and I don't know what's waiting but the
guys the guys of provoca cure if you will and I like that I mean you can make the
argument you can make the argument with bone -time hawk that is the only
portrayal of American Indians and it is their cannibals that cut your
prediction half sure, you know, I think the guy you know Gibson's obviously a very controversial figure
I think we gave Gibson too much of a pass on this show probably I know I did on what on this show
I think we might have given Gibson too much of a pass you think we give him on the show
What do you mean the show on this podcast? Oh, I don't think we gave him a pass
I just think like we he it was fucked up and it happened and then he apologized and we all you know
No, we all got on with our lives.
I think that's the thing.
And I also think, and I've said this repeatedly about Gibson,
I don't, obviously, I don't like anything that he said.
No. But you hear those tapes and those voice notes,
I'm like, this sounds like a guy that's like,
having a nervous breakdown to me.
It didn't sound like a guy that was being,
that was the break we gave in the last time we talked about it.
But I don't know if that's wrong.
I think people do spiral out of control and,
and that was, it was backed up when he said,
on the thing when Ricky Gervace took the shot on me,
he goes, you'll have to ask the guy that said it.
I was like, I think he was like, I'll tell you this dude, my meds were off for the last
two months.
I didn't know that.
Did I tell you this?
No.
I take Prozac.
My Prozac was off by 20 milligrams for the last two months.
I didn't know.
I was mistakenly getting the wrong dose.
The pharmacy gave me the wrong dose.
The doctors, I made a mistake and I didn't realize I was taking too low of a dose.
So for the last two months, I've been taking 20 milligrams under what I'm supposed to take.
I wasn't screaming horrible racist things at people
or leaving voicemails, but I was really depressed
and I didn't feel right and I couldn't figure it out.
And then my doctor, when I went to get refills,
he was like, is this your dosage?
And I was like, no, it's supposed to be 20 milligrams higher
and he's like, you've been taking this.
And I was like, oh my God,
and sure enough, I started taking the right dosage
about a week and a half later.
I'm like, oh, I don't feel like overwhelmed
by the sun coming up anymore.
You know what I mean?
Right, right.
So, I do understand that there's a chemical thing in your brain that can, whatever, but,
you know, anyway.
Brown and Selbach 99 overall, I say, go see this goddamn thing and then this is coming
from a guy that was ready to bail about 45 minutes in because I didn't know what was taken
so long.
But once it got cooked in, once I realized where they were going with it, once I realized
What an homage it was to to again the carpenter yeah uber violin, you know kind of stuff from the 70s
I was like this is pretty fucking cool, man
I liked it. I've never seen Vaughn like that ever. No, I thought I thought it was really fucking sweet
I loved it and I I root for Vince Vaughn. I continue to root for Vince Vaughn
I love him because when he came on the scene that was like
That was like, you know, you get those once in a while.
I feel like we had those a lot in the late 90s
where it was like Owen Wilson, Ben Stiller, Ben Spawn,
where you get like a whole new comedic thing
that rarely happens.
It's like the last one might have been Jonah Hill.
Right, you know, it's been a while.
Yeah, Michael Sarah and Jonah Hill,
I think we're the last.
Yeah, and Rogan, Seth Rogan.
For sure, for sure.
For sure, for sure, but it's been a while
where you get like that. Holy shit, obviously, this person's like a big comedy star
whatever. Anyway, folks, that's our show. We got to do the shout -outs, Pat. Okay,
go for it. Hold on a second here. All right. Our Patreon audience, thank you
to everybody. As always, Patreon or not. But as promised, we give the shout -outs to
the folks that donated money. Derek Clark, Anthony V. Manito, aka party McFly,
I've set up a four best name in the business.
Phil Prasad, Tony Quinn, Rob Lines, Danny Rudd,
Jacob Barrett, Jordan C, Maxwell Ashcroft, Ryan Kohler,
Joshua Christensen, Barbara Allen, Jonathan Face,
Rebecca Cohen, Smelly Bubbles, Chris Poin,
Mike Gibbons, Donnie Joyce, or is it Donnie Joyce?
Michael Dawson, Jennifer Smith, Luke Henderson,
Hater is male. Nick Walther. Leavon. Don't be ridiculous.
Connor Denney. Michael Stephen Cooper. Kevin Swiss -do -Witz. Thomas Cosa. Anthony J. Gujardo.
Annie Johanison. Timmy K. Sean Florn. The Laura Martinez. Will Foley. Megan Leibrand.
and Scott Blicken's Dürfer,
Alec Walker, Brett Wemmer, Tristan Carlson,
Laura Sexton, Anthony Guajardo, Brett Klingner,
Alex Lowe, Ethan Whittit, Weston Thomas,
we've had a problem with this one before.
Have video hold?
This isn't the guy that said it's pronounced like this,
believe it or not.
It's like vintage or something.
Vintage?
If it is.
It's way easier than it seems.
I'm sorry.
I don't have it in front of me.
I apologize for mispronouncing anybody's name.
And again, we're not mocking it.
I think it's pronounced like Quidditch, like Harry Potter.
Jared Blair, Josh Schmalridge, Richie Verdugo, Chris Hopper, Emily Rosenbaum, Emily Florence,
Sean L. Jordan Parker, Dave Kamarek, Abby Manuel, Kim DeAngelo.
Michael Whitsett, Jonathan Galat, Pats, Tijuana Hand Maiden, Carla Oh, Mike Willes, Stephanie
Power, Hunter McDonald, Sterling, Abrigo, Giron Sanderson, Diego Campos, Jake Ferrotti,
or for rote, Stefan, Stefan, Musau, Zoe, Blaskevich, Edmund Dilland, Asley,
Kivinsland, Dan McLeod, Brandon Gash, Lorenz, Bunganears, Alejandro Salgado,
Papa Spouche, Tegan McLeod, Matthew Little, Tracy Reddington, Sean Thomas,
Amanda, Alva Zamora, Jason Weivor, Michael Curry, Curry, Drew Spindler, don't rush past my
Curry. He's one of my oldest and dearest friends. I didn't know that. I didn't remember that.
You say hello to my Curry like a gentleman. All right. Well, we don't want to make anybody feel
special or over anybody else. Sam Mitchell, Aaron Millinowski, Scott Nolan, Jack Gertz, Greg
Mike Soronson, Benjamin Tahia,
Misty Zavar, Brandon Knock, Brandon Webb,
Dajne Wilford, Johnny Ferg, Matthias Pagui,
Superfan Giavani, Michael Gold,
Daniel Duer, Eric Lemora, Michael Madrigal,
Go see Mr. Shoot Records and Lancaster, Pennsylvania.
Steven Reese, Walter Keegan, Kevin Mercenek,
Eric Abanning, Lawrence Anderson, Jared Smallridge,
Zach Showendorf, Dwarf, Will Pottoff, Natalie Craig, Nathan Baskett, Edmund Agabau, Anthony
Kyle Kinsland, Brooke Adams, the man whose name we cannot say on a Babiduk, Scott Patton,
Barbima, Barbama, Emily Marvel, Robert Pearson, Myspace Mike, Michael A .O., Max Unrath,
Dominic Bander, Heighton Davidson, Brian England, and John Wiesengruber.
Holy cow, a lot of people, thank you guys, we can't thank you enough.
You know, folks, I'm thankful for every last one of you.
Joe DeRosa comedy on Instagram come follow me at the Patrick Walsh Twitter and Instagram
Folks happy Thanksgiving
Have a great holiday season
We'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell