Summer is here and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer or check out
our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and the Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spin on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM game sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM dot com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Waiter, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and
West Virginia only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal throwable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning, or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberer, offer not available in all
states, terms apply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
This is a headgun podcast.
Hello everybody, apologies for the brief hiatus we were off for two weeks doing our personal projects, but now we are back
We're seeing you live. We're seeing you in hell
Now ladies and gentlemen
I'm a little tired of beating around the bush here. Let's just get right to it
On with the show and on
Oh, yeah, it sounds more and more like a petafile that runs a candy store like a curly
mustache.
You know what I mean?
I do.
That's what I strive to be.
How have you been, Wallace?
It's been a, I haven't seen you in about a week and a half.
It's been a real long time, especially for us.
uh, but absence makes the Harcro fungus as they say, uh, Joe was in Australia for the, uh,
Crocodile Dundee Comedy Festival, which is run by Mr. Paul Hogan.
Movie Festival.
Who's the Crocodile Dundee Movie Festival?
Oh, okay.
They just ran the three over and over.
Yeah.
And then films of lesser notoriety that were influenced by the original Crocodile Dundee
films.
You're you're young Einstein starring. Yeah, who's serious? He actually was running a competing festival. Oh
Holy shit. He's Australian as well, right? Yeah, but he was really spitting in the face of Hogan
He's tired of it. He said well, I mean
Was he a huge australian comedian that they tried to push here? I was a little too young to know it was going on
I saw the video box. I was like who is this? Why do they get in the movie? I actually have sort of an answer for this
Okay, great because I was there for the Melbourne comedy festival, which thank you again to everybody
It was a really beautiful experience. Mel born runs that, right?
Yes, he's a Jewish guy that lives in Australia
Yeah, really wonderful time
Pat I will say it. I've never and I'm not this is not bullshit, and you know me. I am not a people person
I've never met more
more beautifully spirited people than I've ever met in Australia.
They were, it's great, accommodating and welcoming and wonderful.
I've always heard that.
I should head down there.
I've never been.
Yeah.
It was really great.
But we were sitting out drinking one night me in a bunch of other comics who were from there.
And they kind of got annoyed when I asked this because they thought I was giving them shit
but I wasn't.
But I was like, what's going on with Paul Hogan and Yahoo serious?
Did they have a beef?
No, no, no, I just meant like in general one of those guys up to right and they were like the Americans are added again
I was like no, no, no, I'm not saying that to be funny like I'm really curious like they were huge in our country
For a little while and I Yahoo, he was pretty fucking big
I remember he was doing all the late night TVs when he was a standup. No, no, no
When when young Einstein came out he was doing all the like Carson and all that shit because they were and they were making this big deal
like he wrote it, he directed it, he produced it, he starred in it, and then it was this massive
fucking bomb because it was a terrible movie. But who was he? Oh wow, that I don't know.
What was he in something that I'm going to look him up? Well, they could, here's the thing
when I was like, so what are those guys doing here now? Right. They were like, I mean, they're
not any more relevant here than they are where you're at. Like we haven't heard from them
either. Right. So, uh, so nobody seems to know the whereabouts of Hogan and Sirius. I'm assuming
Yahoo Sirius was a stand up. Well, now I'm going to look him up. I mean, we're coming back with
the opposite of a bang. Anyone tuning in now is like, what is this? A fucking Yahoo Sirius podcast?
Are Yahoo Sirius? Yeah, there you go. Uh, he's 63. His name is Greg Gomez Pied. He's married to Lulu
Lou serious. They they've divorced. He took on her name. He created reckless Kelly and
Mr. Accident. So he thought of himself as like the next Jerry Lewis or so like he was doing
all of his stuff. Mr. Accident and Mr. Me is like a Mr. Bean. I guess so. It's like more
cuckoo bird noises. Oh, here's a dark twist. It's been pretty dark so far. In August 2000
Yeah, who serious tried to sue the search engine Yahoo for trademark infringement. Oh
Man
Oh boy, the case was thrown out because serious could not prove that he sells products or services under the name Yahoo
Oh boy, they were like you you don't sell anything. No one no one buys anything you're selling
We hate you
That's dark
That's a rough one, man. That in the, uh, the Joni from Happy Days news all in one week.
I can't, I can't really handle all this. This is, this is too much, too much, uh,
bright stars from the past that have burned out. Okay, the film's popularity propelled
serious to start them, which saw them appear on the cover of Time and Mad magazine.
A big deal. Time magazine. And even got him his own primetime slot on MTV.
It was a huge success in Australia, but a critical and commercial flop in the U .S. So there we go time magazine
He was on the cover of that I don't really believe
I do I remember there was so much fucking hype around that movie man. They were like
Look sometimes I wanted a bomb because it was so terrible like it's a terrible movie
Yeah, I saw it when I was a levive rented at some point and and and washed it for my memory even at 11
and I was spitting at the screen and it was infuriating.
But sometimes it works out with these foreign guys.
Sometimes it doesn't.
Sometimes you get a, you get a Yakovsky or not.
Sometimes you get a Yahu series.
Well, Smirnoff never ventured into film.
No, but he certainly sustained his thing for way long.
I just saw Yahu series on that midnight.
So he's still...
I mean, Yakovsky or Yakovsky or not, yes.
Was he still doing the, well, Russia's hot again.
He's probably loving this. Oh, that's a good point. Yeah, he can do Trump stuff
He was doing like a millennial
It was like a millennial Russian man character. So I forget. I don't know
You know Joe I sometimes watch at at midnight, but
In the Soviet Union at midnight watches me
Is that a like a shadow government like a like a red that's a classic yeah
Yeah, who serious would always do, you know, you know, in America, you watch TV, but in the Russia TV watches you okay, that was like his classic setup because like now, but I'm saying brother and that's a commentary on the big brother. Yeah, it's not just yeah.
Well, look, things are yet.
Yeah, I wasn't a big fan. No, you know, no. So I'm trying to think who else this has happened with.
And well Trevor Noah is a guy, right?
He's South African.
John Oliver.
I'm just saying guys with accents from other places
that became famous here.
I don't know what happens all the time.
Most of our big actors are always pretending to be American.
That's a good point.
Tons of them.
In fact, the star of a tonight's movie.
That's true.
Hugh Jackman.
And I feel like in tonight's movie,
which we're not gonna get to just yet,
he thought bellowing his lines would cover it up.
And it worked.
but you're really bellowed in this moment.
I'd like to make note for our loyal, loyal fan base.
That was second time, we had a perfect transition,
didn't run with it.
Last time was clown with it.
I blew it for you, you blew that one for me.
Well, if I had started into prisoners,
you would have been like, no, we gotta do the things.
Well, we do.
I know we gotta do the things.
I'm just saying that's two really great segways we had.
Yes.
Yes, let's do you have anything to talk about? I mean, I don't know what you can or cannot
talk about at this point with your with your pilot. Yeah, I mean, whatever else is going
on. I might as well just get right into it, folks. I mean, there is a little big news for
us both here. I think it's fine to say because the pilot is locked. I turned in the final cut
today. It has been well received by everybody who needs to receive it well. It tested fantastically
in the Las Vegas area, which is another reason why I love the Las Vegas area.
Yep.
And now I wait.
I've got about two weeks till I hear, but it just, I couldn't be any happier with it.
It turned out wonderfully.
And folks, there's an asshole in the script named Gary, the character's named Gary.
And he is a flanderer, a cheater, a dick.
Like everybody in the office hates him and talks at length about how much they hate him.
And I thought to myself, I got to get Joe in for an audit.
So he was written in the thing as like being like a kind of a six pack type guy which has
been quite the subject of discussion around there.
We saw all these people audition and we had some good people.
But our three finalists were all kind of like guys we liked they all kind of fit
the same mold they were good -looking guys who were standard douchebags I said
why don't we bring in Joe I didn't tell you when he was my friend they were
like yeah we can see somebody else Joe came in folks he got the part not
through an epitism because it had to go up CBS passed on almost every actor we
wanted you know I don't want them I don't want them they approved Joe DeRosa and
It felt good. Yeah, it felt good. It felt good to be part of it. I'd slide right into those roles.
You did. I know how to play a real piece of shit.
So if this goes not only will you get to see
this dream project of mine come to fruition, but you'll get to see Joe on CBS
which I mean Joe's generally not a network performance.
Middle America's not really ready for it. No, I
this is my agent, my agent said to me two years ago,
you're not gonna be a network guy.
So, yeah, don't worry about this pilot season stuff,
you're gonna be a cable guy.
And I was like, okay, that's fine with me.
And so far, he was right.
But he meant a cable installer,
as well as the agent, because the parts weren't coming.
But this was a much of a surprise to me,
as it could have been to anybody.
But it was, now if I can say a few nice words,
And actually, nothing he's just said was that nice.
Of course it was, he got the part, he killed it.
It was really a blast, Pat Walsh up there running the show.
The show runner is the title for those of you that don't live in Hollywood.
That's the job title.
I watched him run the show and he ran it like a champ.
And I can tell you folks, I worked for a lot of my friends.
This was a painless experience.
There was never once that moment where you're like oh my friend does that when he's at work
Yeah, I try to avoid that. It was just it was smooth sale and wonderful cast of people worked with some of
Some actors that I've admired for many many years. So I now correspond with
Yeah, it was just a really like top to bottom perfect cast. Everybody was great
um
And you know if I may too my horn I thought very confident in the material
And I had a bunch of alts at the ready in case something didn't work. I overprepared
To to a fault perhaps
But we were just ready to go and the whole thing could not have gone more smoothly. It was a blast
Joe and I got to spend like a week
You know at work which we haven't done. It was very fun. There were no explosions. We didn't scream
Nobody screamed no director mr. Andy Ackerman
and directed the final five seasons of Seinfeld.
So he was a dream legend for me to meet.
He ran a very calm tight ship as well.
And I just felt like a great kinship
and a partnership with him.
Everybody was happy.
Everybody hung out together.
Everybody went out after and had a nice time.
It was just a great group of people.
It was wonderful.
And I hope it continues.
I mean, that's the beautiful thing
is that it could go on for seven years or something.
It was a wonderful, wonderful time.
I actually found myself missing all of you just a week later.
Yeah, everybody has said that.
There's a little, you know, sadness.
Yeah, but Andy's the best.
Also directed everything becker, which I love.
Raymond, yeah, great show.
I'm on a years, cheers.
Yeah, for Christ's sakes.
I might as well break out the cast for you.
I mean, there's nothing to hide at this point where I'm just,
we're all just waiting. The cast is JR Ferguson who portrayed Stan on Mad Men. Wonderful man.
Oh, he's the best. He nailed an extremely difficult part. Lindsay Kraft, who you may know,
I guess from like Grayson, Frankie and she's done, you know, what's the HBO medical show?
Getting on. Wonderful woman. She's had bit parts and all kinds of great comedy stuff.
She's delightful Cameron Mannheim of happiness, which we always discuss on the show the practice. You know Cameron man
I wasn't happiness. She had the head in her freezer now. I want to watch happiness again. It's the first thing
I said to her out. She was like no one ever
Approaches me about happiness, but I was like hey, I didn't watch the practice babe
That's what I know she was she was wonderful and Sarah Gilbert
for Roseanne, a real treat meeting her.
I grew up with her.
She dated, of course, Mr. Johnny Galecki,
who was producing the piece on Roseanne,
and maybe in real life pre -Lezbianism.
I don't know, I guess I should ask.
They were both awesome.
Tony Rock, Chris Rock's brother,
but an fantastic comedian in his own right.
Old friend of mine, I've known Tony for 10 years.
CBS is describing it as a star making performance.
He's delightful. He's great.
June Squib, Academy Award nominee June Squib about Schmidt, about Schmidt, Nebraska. I'm throwing all to this woman.
Like I'm like, hey, instead of this, say this, instead of this, say this, add this, subtract this.
She's 87. She'd be like, yeah, I got it. Nailed it every time. She was perfect.
Who else was in the damn thing? Well, you had you had Ian Gomez? Oh, Christ. Ian Gomez.
He says, scene stealer, just a fantastic actor.
You know him from all kinds of things.
Kerber enthusiasm, Felicity back in the day,
my big fat Greek wedding, et cetera.
And then the amazing, Mr. David Crumholz,
who was just a killer, a very, very funny man.
You know him from Appetized Shit, you know him from...
Harold Lee Kumar.
Harold and Kumar, you know him from Slums of Beverly Hills,
where he dances in his underpants, a classic scene.
It's my my favorite movie of his and that's one of my favorite things I've ever seen is that I was so
Excited when he was part of when I found out he was part of the show. Yeah, I mean, it's just you
You watch it and generally, you know like every I've seen it now 800 times and like every new scene starts
You're like, oh good. It's this scene, which is a good feeling. I would be very angry and confused if they didn't pick it up
I don't want to talk too much more about it
But we've given you all the key information. Hopefully you get to see it someday. That's all I can really say
Hey, everybody was wonderful.
Yeah, I'd done and yeah, everybody was just great.
It was just a blast and we shot it in front of a live audience, which was awesome.
By the way, a real thrill because, you know, sitcoms, look, everybody agrees.
A multi -cam sitcom with a live audience.
When it's good, it's great.
And when it's not good, it's terrible.
Sure.
So it was fun to be part of a good one.
And as a comic, it was very rewarding if not a little frightening, but in a good way.
Yeah.
To have that pressure of being up there and having to get a laugh and all that stuff.
It has the immediacy of stand -up in a reward sense.
But then you also get the bonus of the acting where you can do it a couple times and change things and whatever.
So it was really great.
Yeah, the only real issue, and it was more an issue in editing was the tonnage of jokes.
people were stepping laughs were stepping on jokes and throwing off timing here
and there, but that happens. People get used to it, but you can see you can see
especially in the first takes when we were editing it, the actors like look a
little thrown almost by the laughter because we have been when you rehearse it, it's
it's like two people watching it and you do it over and over and then people are
like, am I not funny? Do you not like this? And I'm like just please just wait for
the audience. By the way, that wasn't me yelling like that. The other amusing part of
testing and Warner Brothers singing and CBS singing. Everybody was like, we're concerned
about the likability of Joe. So then everyone kept saying it and I was like, you're not supposed
to like him. He's the asshole. You're not supposed to like him. And then finally in the big,
like big discussion with CBS where they saw the final run through and like had
their final notes before tape night. She was like, look, we just, you know, you
can feel it. People are creeped out by Joe. And they're not really liking Joe. And
then Ackerman who rarely speaks, I mean, you know, to executives anyway, he was
sitting in the corner and he goes, then I guess I did my job. She goes, what? She's
like, I guess, I guess we did our job. I mean, he's supposed to be an
unlikable creep. So if you're saying he's unlikable and creepy, sounds like we did our job.
Yeah. And then I think they were delighted and surprised when you came out and got laughs.
Yes. But all these executives were married women and you could see in their face, they were like,
oh, I hate this guy. But that's, you know, it was necessary for the plot and we're not going to
spoil it. But it was necessary for where the plot goes. It was absolutely necessary. And I think
think we found a few things that gave him some likable, likability.
Absolutely.
Further down the line of the story.
But yeah, it was, I was actually quite shocked when we shot it in front of the audience.
How many laughs that that character got earlier in the script when he's being the most creepy?
I agree.
I was like, oh, okay.
Well, they're on board.
They get that this is supposed to be funny, like, and whatever.
Yeah, and everybody works with an asshole, like that's the thing is that, you know, Hollywood people forget that there are assholes in every office, you know, yeah, like they like there was a joke that we, you know, wild of not being in it, but something about how the office was all thrown into a tizzy because somebody had microwave cauliflower and Cameron came over and was like, this I don't get why this is a like who cares if you microwave cauliflower I was like anyone who works on an office knows the office
reeks when you microwave cauliflower or fish or whatever else right and we didn't
it got a laugh that's it's not in the show but I was just kind of like people actors
executives etc. they're not in the world that they are doing these shows for which
I think is why there's often a huge disconnect I had a I broke off from you
mentally there just for a second I understand because I had a fantasy when you
said the point of my character was to not be likable yeah I had a I had this jump
cut in my head to five years from now shows a success. I'm in some really serious interview
wearing an Ascot. Maybe on inside the actor studio with whoever the new host is bringing
it back. Yeah. Who would be the new host? I'm going to go with Matt Damon. What are you
talking about? He does those project green light things and everything. No, it would have
to be somebody that pompous who's not really a big actor. It wouldn't be Matt Damon. Maybe
Maybe they've learned from their mistakes.
That Damon is a humble, very successful actor.
I agree with that.
I'm saying maybe they go the other direction.
All right, I'm thinking out of the box right now.
All right.
Somebody who wants to support the young actor.
I think that's a good question
and I'm gonna come back to it.
Who will be the new, you know,
who would be probably like Billy Bush.
His return to tell.
Sure, sure.
All right, go on.
I'll tell you, the question was great for the momentum
of my story.
Go on, Joe.
But then in the interview I say,
I never saw Gary as the bad guy. I always saw everybody else as the bad guy
Yeah, and then then that then a jump cuts from that to the headline of me saying that and then the show gets canceled
Yeah, you have to love you have to love your characters. They do always say that
Everyone Gary Oldman got in trouble.
It was so crazy when he did that movie about what was that movie about the vice president
where everybody jizzed on her in the video and Jeff Bridges is the president. Oh, uh,
uh, fuck the contender. Yeah. Wait, everyone jizzed on her. I thought it was like one sexual
encounter. I think it was a gang bang video. Oh my god. I think I can't remember. All right.
But it was a sex video. But anyway, Gary Oldman plays like the right wing guy who's going after
And I remember Gary olden said in an interview. He's like why looked at my character is the good guy
Yeah, which he clearly was saying like obviously if you're playing that part you got to believe you're right
Yeah, he's the guy that he thinks he's good. Yeah
Yeah, and he got in all this shit and there was all this time
I was like you guys a fucking actor playing in a part in a moot. Yeah, yeah
Anyway, patty we're 22 minutes in we haven't even cracked
Yeah, we should we should get it moving because Joe and I are going to see the pixies tonight
Yeah, I'm very excited about
As far as movie corner, I mean until this afternoon about two hours ago
I have done nothing except stuff for this pilot except one night
I couldn't sleep due to nerves and I went upstairs and watched problem -child
Problem -child -two and the remains of the day
With Anthony Hopkins and Emma Thompson
I'm going to tell you, a problem child one holds up in a big ol' way, except the third
act is a fucking disaster.
Problem child too does not hold up at all, save for some amazing weird little jokes like
the one I sent you.
There is a scene where these two dog catchers, they're just normal guys, or 40 years old,
kind of ugly guys.
They're coming to pick up a dog and they're knocking the door and junior the kids, like
yeah, I'll go and get them, hang on, he turns around.
and while the kid goes back inside, the one dog catcher runs his fingers through the
other dog catcher's hair and leans into kiss him, he's a two men and he goes not now.
Then the kid comes out, they give him the dog and the dog catchers leave.
I wound up sending this bit to like five people, I was like, this is a brilliant joke, buried
in problem child too, clearly they were like, this scene's so boring, we ought to give
it's something. It's a child's, it's a movie for children. But what I loved about it was that even in
this, it was a, you know, at the height of like gay panic and like every joke was about that,
they just presented these men as, as secret lovers. Yeah. Who had to keep it under cover. Yeah. And
they, they're real butch -y when they walk up to the door. It's not like, yeah, it's not like one of
them is giving off any scent of, of being a feminine or anything like that. Right. So then, so they
really they really handed it quite respectfully if I may say so they did and we
talked about this list last time because I heard them on the Gilbert Godfried
podcast but it was those guys who did Ed Wood and people versus Larry
Flint and the OJ show they're incredibly talented they started their career with
the two -problem -child movies so I you know obviously they're talented guys and
that's probably why that joke slipped in there and the remains of the day I had
never seen because I always find British move like period pieces boring about
Butlers and everything you know down nabby. I can't can't get through it
I hate shit like that always have probably always will
But I was riveted by this thing for two and a half hours
They get into the inner workings of butlerism
Anthony Hopkins was almost as good as he wasn't sound to the labs
It's one of his best performances. That was a real streak a couple of years for him
I mean you're you're saying all the wrong shit right now two and a half hours a movie about butlerism
I got a period piece and none of this is exciting to me part of it is like I mean it was almost
I love movies so much and I hadn't seen one in so long that this night was you know
It was like when you get a drink of water after you've been in the desert or something
But I love the movie. I was riveted by it. It was very sad. I almost cried at the end
It's just a story about a guy who can't express his emotions
And maybe that's why it hit home for your boy pal Walsh. Well panty love to hear it. Yeah
glad that you enjoyed it. I'm going to keep my brief. I've seen a lot of stuff. Go for it, but I'm
only going to talk about two briefly. The first is one we've talked about before, but I finally saw
Army of One, the Nicholas Cage movie while I was on the plane. Yeah. Uh, can't tell if it was great
or bad. I liked it. Cage's performance is a new definition of chewing the scenery. And then I went
watch the interviews with the real guy. He's nothing like that at all. I talked about it on this
show and I hated the movie but I was so fascinated by the performance that I watched the extra features
and they were like, you know, once we saw this guy, we were like, oh, I mean, Nick, you can't even go
too far with this guy. He's a pretty normal guy. Yeah, eccentric, but not Nicholas Cage played him
at his most coked out and crazy.
I watched an interview with,
I went down a real rabbit hole on YouTube
after I watched this movie.
Yeah.
And I was watching interviews with Nick Cage
to see like what he thought about this.
I was like, did he hate this guy?
Right.
And but I found a good morning Detroit
or something interview with him
where he had him be a satellite.
like, okay. And he's like, and he's, and I forget the guy's name,
Gary, he goes, once I met Gary, I realized he can't stop talking.
He doesn't shut up. You're not going to get a word. And like he was saying it
with a certain level of disgust. And I was like, I think he actually just
didn't like this guy and chose to just completely lambast him. But then he
also said, they go, you look so good, Nick, you in the movie, you look
Terrible, right, you know, fuck you to this Gary guy, but he's like, yeah, I grew the beard out. I died by hair
Got a gut, which I didn't enjoy. I like going to the gym
So, you know cage just feeling himself real serious sure sure
So I saw that and I rewatched on the plane amongst many other new films, which we'll talk about on the next episode
But I rewatched Jurassic Park 3
and here's why I bring this up, I haven't seen it since the theater. I'm gonna
goddamn say it right now. All right it's the best Jurassic Park movie. Stop it. It's
stop it. It's the best Jurassic Park movie. I mean it's the best Jurassic Park movie. You make my job
easy. It's the best Jurassic Park movie. You make my job easy. It's the best let me let me pose the argument
why. All right the movie that you haven't seen since the theater when you were what 15 probably and I
I know I don't need to see this again.
I do own it because I have the trilogy.
Two is a worthless pile of shit.
I don't think I've seen two since the theater,
but one is that's one of my favorite movies.
Two is worthless.
Spielberg, I learned today,
Spielberg directed it via monitor
as he was directing Schindler's list.
That's offensive.
Two is not a good movie in any stretch.
One, wait, Schindler's list came out
the same year as Jurassic Park.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
Oh, he directed one the a monitor. No, no, no, he was directing when he was working he was working on maybe wasn't directing
better. There's no bullshit with a park. There's no bullshit with, uh, we got to wait
and build up to the, they drop these fuckers on the island. There is no park. They're
just in a goddamn jungle with dinosaurs after them. You got Bill Macy. You got Kong Skull Island.
But it was fun. It was better than Kong Skull Island. You got William. It's the same plot.
They're just trying to get to the boat the whole time. It's literally the same plot. Right.
But you got William H. Macy, you got Taylione looking just at her greatest step of all time.
Never my thing, but I love Macy.
You got Sam Neal returns, didn't even remember that.
Which is exciting.
He comes back.
The scene where they're walking through like the hanging metal rafters and it's all foggy.
And then the camera cuts to a shot of Sam Neal and they do like the slow jaws pushing
and he goes, oh my God, this is a bird cage.
And then through the fog, you see a tarot acto walk out
and it's this crazy tarot acto sequence.
It was fucking awesome.
It was awesome.
Jurassic Park, eh, eh, eh.
Stop, stop.
The raptor parts were cooler in this
because the raptors could communicate.
Now let me ask you, you're a bit older than me, not much.
But when you saw Jurassic Park when you were a kid,
you saw it.
I don't believe you.
I hated it. It was the first movie I ever saw that a heavy CGI in it and I didn't like it. Holy shit
I went to see it with my friends Kevin McNewell and Mike Kaczynski. We were
sophomores in high school. My friend Kevin said I've been waiting for a year for this movie to come out
I can't wait. I was like I don't see what the big deal is. I don't find dinosaurs particularly scary because that
That was the whole discussion we had in the Kong thing a giant monsters and that's scary to me
So I wasn't scared and then as far as stuff being cool
The Tyrannosaurus Rex sequence is pretty cool and I like when Raptor sequences
The Raptor sequences cool, too, but the Raptor just perfect really. I mean, it's it's almost a per per movie
I saw when I was 12 and it became my favorite movie
Unseating home alone which had unseated Roger Rabbit before it and then I probably watched you said it unseated home alone
And this is your
park quality. Well, I was 12, but home alone remains one of my favorite movies.
Fine. I like home alone just fine. But I'm saying, can you, can you say you're, this
way you're saying you're saying I was 12. Yeah, but now I was going to continue.
Okay, sure. I've seen Jurassic Park at least every couple years for the remainder of my life,
including when they re -released it about five years back in 3D. I went, got high, saw it. I was like,
this is, it's like seeing it for the first time again. I think it's one of Spielberg's best.
Oh, that's insane and I think it is one of the better thrillers maybe ever made. That's
I'll I'll accept the second statement one of Spielberg's best. That's insane. Sorry. That's insane. Sorry
Schindler's list so you and the Raiders of the Lost Ark close encounters in the third kind
Jaws you're putting fucking Jurassic Park up there with those films. I'm putting it. Yeah
Yes, that's nuts. I mean, I'm not gonna compare it to Schindler's list because that's not really a fair comparison
But yeah, I mean I already report is better than Jurassic Park. I like dress. It's not I like dress part more than ET
ET's fucking pussy shit, you know, I was never even as a kid
I didn't like ET that much. No, I I really do I mean and again when you see a movie when you're 12 and you've like never seen a horror movie
It holds a special place
But I still I feel like if dress parking out today, I'd still fucking love it. I will rewatch three
I get I pledge that to you by the next podcast. I will have watched three again
I I listen three without question has a thinner plot without question
But as far as a movie that I enjoy watching I enjoyed it more
I thought the action sequences were cooler. I thought there was it was more intense
I don't know. I just enjoyed it more there was there was director of Jumanji
So that might explain the intensity you're talking. Do you know do you know who do you know who wrote
it. No. Who co -wrote it? Excuse me. Alexander Payne. Oh, yeah, I didn't know that actually.
He did a lot of, he did like worked on Meet the Parents and all kinds of shit. Hold on. I've
been saving this joke for four days. Alexander Payne co -wrote Jurassic Park 3, which explains the sudden
appearance of an alcoholic writer dinosaur. Wow. And did you look it up on your phone?
You're looking at your phone. Did you write the joke on your phone?
I wrote Jurassic Park 3 dash Alexander Payne that maybe that's how I do for the bit.
I only looked at my phone because I lost confidence in it halfway through it.
Right, right.
Which explains the sudden appearance of, you know, you could do a lot of these.
Yeah.
Of a dinosaur driving an RV.
Did you have affection for three going in? Did you remember loving it?
No, I saw all three movies essentially against my will.
in the theater because people were like we gotta go see it it's the thing to do
hated the first one now I don't now listen let me say this if I rewatched
Jurassic Park now I don't think I would hate it still but I still think I would
like three better okay but you wouldn't hate it I saw I saw all three in the
theater let me hate it's too strong word didn't give a fuck about the first one
all right hated the second one that that's shit with the dinosaur peeking in the
kids bedroom wind, fuck off.
Look, and the Godzilla stuff.
I mean, I remember enjoying too.
And what I liked.
I went in begrudgingly and then I really liked it.
I remember thinking three was, I thought about three
about how I felt about Jurassic World.
Fine, I'll never watch it again.
Two, it had some good moments amidst the shit,
but yeah, I mean, one is a classic to me.
Right or joke, really bombed.
I thought you would think that was fun.
It's just me, I mean, it's not bombing.
I just know I but I kind of wrote it for you. I thought you'd like it. All right, sometimes I do things for you, you know, yeah
Look
Speaking of which let's get on to our today's movie Pat told me the other day. I feel like I'm being held prisoner by that joke
Pat told me the other night that he had already announced to the Facebook page that prisoners would be our next film
Yeah, I felt bad.
And by the way, I need to give it a little more props
because our membership is growing every time I log on
to Facebook, which is very rare.
I've got a bunch of requests to join.
Thank you, everybody, that's wonderful.
Just search, we'll see you in hell.
I believe it's the only fan page up.
And you know, people have been asking about merchandise,
Joe and I are on it.
We're not on it, but we're pretending to be on it.
We're going to get on it.
And actually I had some merch ideas, yeah, we're gonna do it.
Should I save them right now?
We talked about it a little bit before,
but yeah, save them for now,
because we'll talk about them off there.
But anyway, it was amazing to see like people really go
in depth in detail into each episode and discuss
and remember to line up.
I know, I'm already waiting for the backlash.
I'm gonna get about the Jurassic Park statements I've made.
I'm still getting shit about the sopranos.
I'm still getting shit about aliens, Halloween two.
Yeah, but it's a it's a wonderful page and Emily who runs it. Thank you so much. It's fantastic
Thank you, Emily. We complete essentially we forgot the first week
I mean we've been really really busy, so I wanted to say hey, sorry. We're gone for two weeks and also what's coming up
And you want to let people prep we've been saying we're gonna do prisoners for months
We got to do it and I think that's one I'll probably be guardians of the galaxy too. I
I am out of my skin excited to do Guardians of the Galaxy two because of a tweet.
So I know, I know believe it or not, folks.
I don't think Joe loved it.
I didn't see it yet.
Oh, I didn't see it.
You just heard about it.
I was just tweeting about what I had read that they had added Miley Cyrus in there somewhere.
And they released a song that was like the theme song and it's David Hasselhock.
The irony, the irony in 80s catch factor is so through the fucking roof already in just
just the advertising for this film and the soundtrack.
I can't wait to see, I'm gonna say it right now,
I'm the disaster that it is.
I've read a ton of early reviews today
that were all like, look, it's...
Oh, I thought it was already out.
No, I think it comes out Friday.
Okay, yeah, that makes sense.
Well, if it's not out in time, it won't be the next episode.
Hopefully it will be, but I read a ton of early reviews today
that the nicest thing anybody could say was,
it's not as good as the first one,
but it's still pretty entertaining.
Yeah, a lot of reviews that were like,
it's so full of itself and it's, you know,
it's so aware of how big it is and everything.
And I'll don't go on with preconceived notions.
Well, it's, it's, it's, look, I mean, James Gunn,
prior to Garden of the Galaxy,
which I loved is a very talented and interesting
but extremely uneven filmmaker.
Like he came out of the trauma world.
I like James Gunn.
I like him too.
I'm just saying.
And I liked Guardians of the Galaxy one, but it was before this fucking marvel and when I say Marvel
I'm referring only to Marvel Studios. I'm not talking about the Sony stuff. Okay. The Mar, the this Marvel
Train has gone off the fucking tracks. They are making John Hughes movies with people in capes. It's an
absurdity at this point. It's an absurdity. They're there. It's and I'm not talking about the the classic
John Hughes movies. I'm talking the Dutch years. I consider Dutch a classic. I like Dutch, but
There's Dutch is not man's plans trans automobiles, but I'll take poor man's plans trans automobiles
I'll take Dutch too, but my point is is you know Dutch is not 16 candles right actually do date
Do date is like homeless man's plans trans automobiles. I hate to do that and Dutch deserves better than to be called the poor man's pts
So speaking of the Marvel Universe, here's another joke I wrote just for this podcast.
Yeah.
I started watching this movie today and I thought, man, this latest Wolverine film is very
dark.
Oh, prisoners, prisoners.
I got you.
You needed to say prison.
Sorry, yeah.
Sorry.
They fucked it up.
But this movie is,
our movie is prisoners.
Keep an eye on time, Joe.
So we don't miss the pixies.
But prisoners, for me,
I saw it as an Academy Award screening type thing.
We invited all these screenings
and they sent them to your house.
And you go and they're always
kind of these boring prestige pictures, biopics.
You go and you're kind of bored.
And some of them are good, some of them are not.
But then I was like, whoa, like this is like a nasty dark thriller. I don't think it was nominated for anything
But it really blew me away. I thought I like Jillin Hall
I like Jackman. I'm sure it'll be fine
But I couldn't believe how good the movie was for me when I'm looking at like what is the serial killer
genre my top three from like my lifetime like from you know 81 on
I'm talking about sounds of the lambs, I'm talking about seven, and I'm adding prisoners
to the list.
Uh, yeah, I think, I think as far as this type of serial killer film goes, seven is probably
the best one I've ever seen.
Sure.
Master, but, uh, prisoners could unseat it, uh, or you thought better or, well, I don't know
yet.
I haven't seen it as many times.
Right.
But it's a, it's a damn close second on a first watch, the, uh, I'll say two things off
of the bat prisoners was so good,
it made me want to see the arrival.
And fewer movies have ever been released
that I wanted to see less than the arrival.
Well, arrival was a let down due to prisoners.
Sekario is a better,
Sekario was the follow up and it's a,
it's a better follow up, you know.
And swollen Paul Dano will be
hauntinged in my memory forever.
And I was thinking today,
I was, I was mad that,
I was mad that I already have another Twitter handle
because I thought swollen Paul Dano
would be a great Twitter handle.
He looks like a pig or something and it was so disturbing to me. Yeah, there's some real like
Shocking things in it and they just kind of stay on them the torture scenes are
Really aggressively uncomfortable and they go on and on and they're very well done
But that's the point of it. I mean the point is like
How far are you gonna go? It's not it's not rubbing your face and it's not like saw where it's it's torture for the sake of torture
Yeah, in fact, I would say that they they kind of they the torture scenes went on less
Length they were less likely than I thought they would be yeah because everybody had said to me this movie's brutal
It's brutal. Yeah, but like you know like there's the scene where
He's been punching Paul Dano and and it's you know
It's upsetting, but then he pulls out the hammer and he's like don't make me use this and I'm like holy shit
They're gonna show him with the hammer, but then he doesn't that's true so
But and then the guys use restraint ever since Dennis Villanuev who's doing the new Blade Runner as well
But Roger this the prisoners guys doing Blade Runner. Oh, now I want to see Blade Runner
But Roger Deacon's shot prisoners to me
cinematography was
Because I don't I don't agree with the thing of like if you don't notice the cinematography then it's great
I like a little flash to it. I agree and Roger Deacon's is one of the greatest cinematographers of all time
He's the colon brother's guy. He shot Fargo, which is maybe the best shot movie ever. Every shot in Fargo
I want to be a mounted on my wall
Particularly the parking lot the Snowden parking lot. I think that's one of the best shots ever
So Deacon's did it. I mean, this is the same way. Every shot it is like meticulously
crafted the story in a way that almost
Sadly never happened certainly in modern movies screenplays have gotten laser and laser and they're rewritten by ten people
and you lose the thread.
Everything makes sense in this.
Everything makes perfect sense.
There's not an ounce in the movie,
an ounce of fat in the movie,
and it's two and a half hours,
which is very, very hard to achieve.
I was impressed at how much the studio allowed them
clearly to keep this lengthy cut.
Yeah.
I'm sure it's skirted on NC17, I would imagine.
Just for intensive.
Yeah, but uh, and and tons of plot twists tons of plot twists that work that makes sense that make total sense and then also
Like it's it's I like, first of all
Jill and Hawk you don't know who it's you know, it's obviously a who done it because you don't know who done it right
But I've never seen a movie where I literally thought everybody at one point was a suspect
Yeah, there was even a part where I was like wait a minute did Hugh Jackman kill his own kids. I know. I know what happened
Jill and Hall comes in so weird and creepy in that first scene
I was like oh, so Jill and Hall's the bad guy then he gets in the car and he's the cop right and then I'm like
Well, wait
So he's a good guy and then I was like wait. No, maybe he's not maybe he did it. Yeah, he's got all these weird tattoos and shit like
The characters had like Dan oh has a massive twist like there are twists that don't that do factor in of course to the
the end result, but you're also just kind of like,
what a cool thing they did there
and gave that character this huge arc and twist.
That wasn't even really needed
because the major, did you see the final twist?
I saw the whole thing.
No, I mean, did you predict the final who it was?
Oh, no, my predict, I mean, we can talk about it.
This has been a fan request.
2013, I mean, come on.
My prediction had about halfway through the film.
Well, my dad saw a part of the movie with me
before they flew out today.
My dad's prediction was the kid is gonna shoot whoever
the kidnapper is with a rifle at the end.
That's why they did that deer scene in the opening.
And I was like, oh, that's interesting.
That could happen.
My mom's prediction was, Paul, I think Paul Dano
is gonna turn out to be a girl.
Okay, I don't know why she thought that,
but that's what she thought.
They left before the movie was over.
I'd say three quarters of the way through
what I thought was gonna happen was the suspect
the fact that kills himself in the room, in the questioning room.
I'm great was that guy, I've never seen anything before.
He was awesome.
Yeah.
I thought he was gonna be the grown up version of the kid that was missing where the ladies
like he's been missing for 26 years.
Right.
I wasn't that far off on that because he was a kid that was abducted, but then escaped.
And that's why he was fucked up.
Yeah.
Paul Dano ends up being that kid, which I did not see coming at all and I didn't, I got
That's so excited when Hugh Jackman, when he goes, he's got him in that shower and he's
like, he's like, stop that, I'll make you break.
And then it cuts to him going to the aunt's house.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I got excited because I was like, holy shit, this guy is out of his fucking mind.
He's going to kidnap the aunt now.
And then, but I didn't see the, I didn't see the twist of the aunt being the, that fuck,
yeah.
And she was great.
I mean, let's, I'm a little, you know.
But uh, there's that side, Alexa, stop.
My Alexa just went off.
Melissa, that sounds like Alexa.
Sorry.
Anyway, the, thanks Alexa.
The little side trip to that priests basement, you know,
like there's so much like great preppy shit in it.
Yeah, and I thought that that, I thought that priest thing
was just gonna be in there as a red herring
And it was just going to be like, oh no, it turns out that's not related and then when you find out
Oh, it's Melissa Leo's character's husband that was in that basement, which I got a I got to admit for me
I think that was on the second viewing because sometimes when I'm focusing so hard on one thing the other things get a little fuzzy
Sure
I'm a little slow with things, but I was just so excited by it and sometimes when I especially in a suspense movie
I hate having to focus on the plot because I'm so rarely scared or on the edge of my seat
as they say.
Sure.
That I don't focus the way I should.
Prisoners to me rewards like 12 view.
It's like seven.
I mean, I've seen prisoners six times.
I own it whenever it's on HBO.
I watch it.
I want to watch it an hour and a half of it.
It's, I think it's one of the best movies of the past 10 years, really.
It's a phenomenal picture.
And as I said to you earlier today, I loved it.
And I was almost disappointed that I loved it so much because we've been quite amicable these last few episodes
I know well the audience will probably split we haven't we haven't disagreed much and I really was hoping I would wouldn't like it
Just so we could disagree yeah, but we but I I
You know there was no
Sell in my brain that could rightfully dislike this film. Yeah, I love that I'm trying to get you to watch it forever
It's a it's one of those that somehow like I looked up and
Worldwide or whatever it made a hundred and something million dollars, but it wasn't
a smash really and it's one of those that you can still find people in your friend group
who haven't seen it and be the hero that tells them to watch this like unsung movie because
it's fucking great and not enough people have watched it that's what I'm saying.
The now the ending my old cliffhanger you think they got him out?
I think so because I think like I honestly think that was the whole point of him saying
They have the scene with Maria Bello, who plays Hugh Jackman's character's wife and the
mother of the one little girl. She is talking to Jake Jalenhall at the hospital at the
end and she says, do you think you'll find my husband? He says yes. And she goes, and I'll
probably go to jail and he said, yeah, probably. And I think the point of that scene was, so when
When you saw the cliffhanger ending, you realized, oh, he is going to find him.
They've established so many times for that movie that Jake Jones hall knows what the
fuck he's doing.
I mean, there's that scene at the candlelit vigil where he sees the guy that becomes a suspect.
Yeah.
And he literally just looks at him and it keeps staring at him to the point where the guy
runs.
You know, so all those, I mean, him running through the house, there's so many great set
pieces in it, like going back to these people's houses, there's the scene with all the snakes
and the chests that was crazy, like there's just so much memorable, great stuff in it,
and it makes you realize how lazy most of these types of movies are.
Yeah, that snake thing freaked me out, I don't like snakes at all.
And then even when Melissa Leo says, my husband left me, he had a thing with snakes and I don't
to talk about it. Even then I wasn't like, oh she did it. Yeah. Even then I still didn't think she
had done it. It reminded me a lot of the prestige in the sense that I love the prestige,
one of my favorite films. I need to rewatch it. But it reminded me of that in the sense of it's
this sort of tour de force also starring Hugh Jackman. It's two hours in change. It's crazy. The story
is completely evolving the entire time.
And it wasn't until the end where I was like,
oh my god, they're twins.
And I was like, that's the most obvious fucking thing.
And it never even occurred to me.
I was sitting there going, Christian Bale is magical.
How is he magical?
I don't understand.
You know, so this movie was like that to me too,
where I really didn't know what was happening
until it was happening.
Well, that's the best kind of twist.
And that's why this is the hardest movie to do well
is because you don't want the audience, if a twist comes so far out of left feel the audience
is like really like you just jerking me around but if it's too obvious you know there are
people who watch these movies and they're like you know seen one they know who it is.
I feel like prisoners is very surprised and they did it very well and to keep you guessing
for two and a half hours because then also you're killing off people who could have been suspects.
They did a great job. I'll say this too it's such a good movie.
That they in a forgivable way do the thing that I don't care for in many movies,
which our friend James Pinkstone refers to as the the Bond villain technique.
You know, nobody, nobody really likes it when a criminal or the bad guy at the end of the movie
just reveals his plan easily. But Melissa Leo kind of does that at the end of this movie,
but they've given you so much that at that point,
you're like, I appreciate right now,
just simply hearing what the fuck has been happening.
Yeah, and I bought it because, you know,
she thought she was on this righteous journey.
Right. So she wants to let the world know
what she's doing and that it's for good.
I mean, I bought the shoot, do it personally.
Yeah, it was, it's like a steel trap.
I mean, everything works, everything is set up,
everything is called back.
I have no complaints about prisoners.
I think it's an A plus movie.
The daughter goes missing, Hugh Jackman ends up missing with the whistle, her whistle,
the daughter's whistle.
Yeah.
That the daughter did find the mom said she thinks she's misremembering it.
Crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy film.
I love it.
The way the neighborhood is shot at the beginning, like in your average movie, that's just like
an exterior shot of the house and then we go into the house for Thanksgiving.
Like every shot is just, it was a movie where people gave a shit and that's always what makes
makes a classic.
The one thing I didn't understand, you went and missed this too, I don't know, there's
a part where, so they tell you that Jill and Hall's dad is a greater fird.
This is right near where I grew up, by the way, greater fird prison was near where I lived.
In fact, my dad is who was a deacon.
I believe used to go to greater fird when we lived there to visit prisoners and have like
Confessions and shit with them. Yeah
You know like or church visits with them and stuff and but anyway or no you would go to give them communion. Excuse me, but anyway
They say that his dad was a guard at the prison and then later you see Jill and all looking at the article that says his dad killed himself
And then they show you an address in the article and I didn't and they I mean they they they they
Specifically they do a close -up of the address
You're supposed to know that it's significant, but I don't I never realized I was like what I don't remember that I'd have to watch it again
It cuts to jail and all cuts back to the computer screen where the article is then the last shot is the camera
Tilted down to the address
It's very deliberate. Oh, yeah, I don't remember that I'll watch it again. Maybe I
Don't know and I love to that the detail that the priest who kills the pedophile is a pedophile
or as a sex offender I believe I think they say that so they think like and then
this guy like does this crazy extreme righteous thing to account for his sins
right right so you know pretty fucked up pretty fucked up movie in the best
way possible yeah Pat you told me to watch the time guess what I've been doing it's
time I've been watching that time it's eight thirteen guys we are going to see
the pixies we'll be back more than likely with Gardens of the Galaxy two but I
I will keep you abreast on the Facebook page.
But we're around now, consistently we'll be coming out.
There'll be no more of these hi -a -tai, or at least not for a while, for a while.
I got nothing to plug, except keep my pilot and your thoughts and prayers.
I would love to be able to bring you a show every week with Joe DeRose in it.
I mean, what a dream.
Talk about bringing, we'll see you in hell to the masses.
And I'm on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh.
Pat, we share the same dreams as we always have.
Except ever since we locked eyes in that Italian restaurant.
All the bottles of red.
Ooh, bottle of light.
At Jotaro's a comedy on Twitter and Instagram, as always, if you can go help me fix those
album reviews on Amazon and iTunes. I appreciate it. Go leave this podcast, a nice review if you like.
Like us and follow us on Facebook. Join the group. I don't think I have any, yeah. I'll be in
San Francisco for cluster fest in June. Yeah, Seinfeld. Ice Cube. A bunch of people. So I'll be up there
performing June 3rd and 4th at the festival. So, you know, maybe I'll see you there.
All right, and we're not doing Joe's scary corner of stuff. We'll do it next time.
Yeah, I forgot to do it. I would have done it earlier.
Guys, thanks. Keep comments and everything coming. We love it. Go to the Facebook page. Emily does
a great job running it. We'll see you in hell on Facebook. And that's it. See you next week.