Hey everybody welcome to we'll see you and how the podcast brought to you by
Fangoria podcast network for more information about the network including
other programs how to follow the show and find past episodes of we'll see
you and how please visit Fangoria .com good to be here my buddy Patty Walsh look
at with let's just address it right off the bat Pat say hi first of all hi I feel
like you're kind of dominating this so far Joe I haven't really had a chance to
make my voice heard there is Pat Walsh in one ear I'm in the other we keep
getting people saying why are you split why is one guy in one ear why is one
guy in the other it's so if you want to watch the movie you can have us balanced on
either side of it with the movie audio up the middle and I know for effect our
dear friend Karen Coguerreff very funny comedian and writer of Mr. Show
Fame she listened to every one of our episodes on her drive home from I forget
the state the Sacramento California she texted me a great great yeah compliment
about yeah it's me too there were no more me focused than the podcast but there
were no audio complaints no she had no audio complaints so I think we're fine
okay this week we're doing the shining so if you want to watch along with us
now's the time to queue up your DVD or get ready on Netflix everybody owns the
shining in one way or another yeah we should just get into it because it's two two
hours and a half yeah so this is a long one we're just gonna go if you need
time pause if not we'll count it off and hit we'll do a one two three play right
patty sure all right one two three play and we're in you got your Warner
Brothers logo there the movies rolling we have never gotten into a movie so
quickly now it feels good I also like seeing the Warner Brothers logo because
usually that means I'm getting paid I usually associate it with them about to
watch a batman movie yeah sure and usually that's not good I disagree I like a lot
well I'm talking about the old ones okay I like the first one and the other three
or you know Joe it's good to see yeah this is a fitting movie to watch because a lot
of people are snowed in and on these coast yeah it's the big blizzard of
oh six snow pockleps they call it yeah oh six sounds better than 15 doesn't it
it does I had one blizzard when I oh boy one blizzard when I was in New York and I
loved it you know there was more of it you might want to tighten your stand I
tried you're getting a little slide down see that see that one in the middle
there yeah no no no down that one that's the one you tighten Pat Walsh does not
work a mic stands guys been working in television all right for 32 years I
Scott my start on the Jerry Lewis telephone as a boom mic operator as a boom
mic you should know how to work that stand boom man the movie here comes the boom
is based on my ex -plates I said look I put on a few pounds Kevin James's plan
me fellas I was very angry about that I consider myself more of a Brad Pitt
John Ham type but that's fine as far as sitcoms go I always thought of you more
of a of a sort of a Cynthia Nixon type uh -huh okay then a then a Kevin James I
think out of the sex in the city gals I look the most like Cynthia Nixon I'll
take them yeah well you're both tall red headed gals yeah both love the ladies
am I right this is just an endless opening to a movie I love it it's disturbing
it is a little loud I think it's going to be a little loud for us Joe I can turn
it down a bit okay because I mean no one's even talking yet and I'm having a
little trouble well it's music is playing yeah you can't hear me and you though I
hear as far I can but I'm gonna have to struggle I feel like this kid is just have
you read the book the shining no I was too busy adjusting the levels hold on
talk while I do that all right I will Stanley Kubrick and Diane Johnson I wonder if
she ever wrote anything else I'm gonna look that up I love the movie of course I
feel like everyone loves the movie the book is a phenomenal as well and as I said
I have not seen the remake we've talked about it before with Stephen Weber who is
acting out my words this week on the show I write for I wrote him he's in prison on
the show and he's doing a musical in prison I wrote all these songs for him to
sing and I want to ask him tomorrow because I'm gonna spend the whole day with him
about the remake of the shining now when I like feels at once what I'd like to see
now is somebody come do a remake of that episode but cast Jack Nicholson in the
Stephen Weber part sure sure see see out Weber likes it that really blow people's
minds I feel like well yeah could you do a Nicholson impression because I feel
like now'd be the perfect time to do it like here's my take on Jack Nicholson in two
broke girls I think everyone can do an okay wait now we actually have subtitles yeah
I put them on Pat oh okay do you think this when you walk in and all this
equipment set up do you think it just pops up by itself well you at any time I
said you should put on subtitles you act like I'm asking you to like because now
we're going through the Apple or the Mac mini which is an actual computer which
means putting on the subtitles as easy as getting the progress bar to appear
and clicking the subtitle button on the Apple TV you got to fucking flip the thing
up and then I found a whole down pause or real pain in the ass just told them
that's the old Apple TV the new one is a whole another thing I have the new
one I haven't hooked it up I've heard don't hook it up it's more difficult than
the other one it's true it's a much better product it just takes a little more
there's a learning curve because it's you've had that other one for four years
and now this is a different device don't love learning folks I do love the
curves okay I still want to do Nicholson my impression of Nicholson in two
broke girls do it girls we got to make some fucking money around here
what do you think of that yeah this diner cash ain't cutting it man go ask the
gentleman that used to be on Saturday night live if he can give us a couple of
bucks I forget his name I think I must have snorted it up my god damn nose
circa 1978 that's fun it's not a bad show that's still fun to do we've added two
impressions to the show yeah we have Sam Elliott which Sam Elliott ordering food
Karen said to the Sam Elliott impressions were stellar okay good and and now we
have Jack Nicholson in two broke girls yeah think of another one oh and then I did
that half ass Sam Rockwell impression one time quarter ass I would say at
best I put my all into it so the effort was full ask the the accuracy is not
is not spot on there enough yeah now look at these beautiful subtitles if I
just may now is that a is that a is that a product of Kubrick's hand more is that
just how all the subtitles I guess that's probably how the subtitles are if
you're trying to get a compliment on your Mac many I'll be happy to give it to you
the subtitles look nice they look beautiful they do better than most I watched a
couple of foreign films this weekend the subtitles were shitty actually ruined the
movie almost because they looked so like tacked on that I was losing emotion for
the movie yeah bad subtitle bad set a bad lighting is another thing that'll take me
right out of the experience watch the movie called Phoenix it's on Netflix
instant on a lot of top 10 of the year list it was fantastic who's in it nobody I
mean German people so as far as we're concerned it's about Phoenix Arizona yeah
German people who do Phoenix no of course it's about the whole cause yeah it is so
hot that's the whole movie can we go to the breaking bad house after lunch that's
in New Mexico I think God damn it Joe sorry buddy sorry Joe's big a lot of
people like yes and with their improv Joe's big on the no but it's just tough when
you're part when you're an official part of the big of the better call solve
breaking bad universe when you're an official part of the canon the soul of
verse yeah it's hard to hear you know it's kind of like you just said like
remember in Star Wars when the Enterprise you say no no no pad it's not that's
Star Trek right so I'm just saying I didn't criticize you and I'm a key
key part of the two -bro girls universe I didn't say anything wrong about it
Nicholson's referring to Earl the cashier as that guy from Saturday Night Live
because he was on Saturday Night Live it's Garrett over the cashier or maybe the
actor who portrayed that's what I mean I meant the joke was that Nicholson was so
coked up he doesn't realize that he's good with the character I think I introduced
coke to the improv but that's fine anyway Phoenix is it's right after World War
2 and there's this woman who's had pretty it was had a lot in common with good
night mommy she had pretty severe facial reconstruction surgery and she I guess
that's that's where the similarities end but she bumps into her husband and he
doesn't recognize her because the reconstruction wasn't perfect and it's a
whole is he a monster is he a nice guy kind of thing was really good and the
final scene was off the charts folks I urge you to watch it's on Netflix since the
new film yeah about a year old speaking of I don't know why it's called
Phoenix I guess rising from the ashes now I it took me one second to think
about it now I completely understand yeah yeah sometimes I don't spend that
one second to think about that I don't either and it's and it's also so it's
not a movie about Phoenix there's also not a movie about the Marvel comic book
character the Phoenix now it's a movie about a German lady with a busted face yeah
really good all right six degrees of separation here there's also a movie called
Phoenix from the 90s that started Angelica Houston who Nicholson dated okay
what's that about I think it's her and I believe Ray Leota it's one of those
like desert steamy crime thriller kind of thing she banging Leota I don't think
so I tell you she's a wild -looking woman these days I saw her and transparent and
I was like Hachi Machi why she's just a wild -looking lady man what do you mean it's
either a lot done or maybe the sad state of affairs that just nothing done looks
like that now but her face was crazy and Angelica Houston has always been a
very severe -looking woman kind of an intense -looking woman yeah and I found her
delightful on the show but I was just like this lady I've never seen a face like
this in all my life and it's it's it's and how trying to be a dick it's just a
wild face and you could sure she would understand if you said this after on the
last podcast I talked about how I hate people shooting on Kathleen Turner's
face yeah but you know that's what you call Hollywood folks yeah he only sticks
up for his ethics when it's in style I I kiss your lips while I'm stabbing in the
back this is a filthy town I hear you it's a terrible town I've been very depressed
for weeks me too I don't like almost everyone that I come to contact with exactly
the same thing me too yeah I've I look it I look at Facebook oh I mean I'm
sorry I look at Instagram and Twitter in the morning and the entire time I
curse out loud at my phone I know and I I see people's pictures and I go I'm
literally in that blue chair where they're going oh you fucking idiot you
fucking idiot I have a bit about it in my act now let's do the same thing it's
me in that chair on the toilet being like why do I follow this person yeah find
moron here's my impression of me scrolling through Facebook fuck you fuck you
yep fuck you fuck you fuck you so I don't and I found myself some because I I do
what you're definitely not supposed to do which is I look at Twitter like right
before bed because it whips me into a frenzy and I look down the other night
reading these tweets and I'm digging my fingernails into my palm on my hand
making me so quietly angry you know I'm not happy I'm not happy that you're
depressed you know I'm not happy that I'm not happy that you're sad I am happy
though hearing that you're depressed only because it makes me realize I'm not
crazy no it's this city gets to you after a while it does and I'm glad we're
watching something cheerful like gallons of blood pouring off and as we were
saying that the shot of the blood river came into the hallway which is like
what is in my mind right now remember when we were at that heart convention and
we were in a cab with those two twins yeah they were grown up now we Joe and I were
in a like a escalade to the airport with the twins from the shiny and they
could not have been sweeter and I so desperately wanted to take a picture of them
but I was like I don't want to bug these ladies they're sweet old ladies they were
you know they're probably 55 they looked pretty yeah they look great they kept
whispering in each other's ears like they shared that weird twin secret
thing oh that's sexist by the way what I just did sorry what I've learned on
Twitter that if you know because I said yeah they looked great
and it's a woman that's that's me being a misogynistic pig what because apparently
I've never said that about a man before which I have all the time yeah I do too
I'm reading a lot of that stuff online about how like I totally agree like you
shouldn't say it's wrong to say to a woman like hey nice tits you know or be like
harassing or whatever like but it's starting to bleed now into like this thing about all
compliments where it's like you wouldn't tell a man he looks nice and it's like no I I'd constantly
do I went to a barbecue yesterday three of my male friends told me I looked great I told
three of my male friends how good I thought they looked I complimented their bodies I wasn't
trying to have sex with them I was saying you look really good you know just you didn't
tell me I look great when I came in Pat I'm always happy to see you and you're like the wife at this
point I get I don't got to do anything to bet you at this point you know when I saw on Twitter the
other day and almost sent it to you because it infuriated me so and I knew it would get your goat
so I didn't send was someone being like hey don't if you if a woman tells you her age and you think
that she looks younger than her age don't tell her she looks younger than her age because that's
not appropriate maybe she doesn't want to hear that now folks I don't know the this is what compliments are
like this is what compliments someone tells you I'm 50 years old new oh my god I wouldn't have
thought you were older than than 35 and also why would you make that into a bad thing and why are
you also only saying that about women if it's bad then say it's bad for men and women yeah people
often tell me I look quite a bit older than I am doesn't make me feel great but I would never
think to take to the internet about this I shouldn't go antics people are going to figure out who this
person is but why why I want to know I'll tell you after I was kind of like what well then what do
you want to I guess you can't really say anything it's not it's not it's not going to happen so I'm
not going to be the guy that's like we're barreling towards a society where but there are certain
it'll never happen but there are certain people out there that that really truly wish we lived
in an environment where there was no real interaction yeah unless it was somehow a hundred percent
gainful for them as individuals like it's it's it's it's insane it's insane you can't
it's crazy I don't even understand that that age one is blowing my mind like someone tells you look
great or you are are any compliment of that nature that doesn't bleed into your ass is incredible
whenever I get why that's weird of course I guess of course I've never said anything like that in my
life hello you look great like the guys in the sopranos said that to each other every day it's like
it's just a nice little thing but yeah this was it unless you you know that somebody wants to be
complimented on their age don't ever offer that information and I'm like I'm not even going to take
that and start using that in my life how would you know that that's a terrible thing how would you
know this is how would you know that so we have to design a system where when I meet you I go hello Pat
I like to be complimented on the following yeah my age my looks my rear end yeah like so then here's
I find offensive my breasts my career my what I also here's the alternative you meet a woman who says
you know look I'm 45 years old and you nod your head isn't that like a little weird and kind of
you look yeah that seems about right you're 45 yeah I've been saying for years for years I've
been having this debate with people it's sexist it's sexist towards women when people when women say
you never ask a lady her age that's sexist that's the second that means I'm treating you different
than I treat a man that's true but I do follow that rule I never ask somebody hold that I ask
away I don't care okay because I'm a feminist I'm a I'm a I'm a for quality sure that's a quality
I'm exhausted cats Steven said it best it's a wild world jump did cat Steven sing cats in the cradle
that was Harry japan okay he's saying it about his friend cat Stevens who was in a cradle at the time
they had a weird sort of baby fetish role play thing going on right a lot of people don't know
about that backstory right I have a good shining story from that convention yeah that we were at you
do you told it on the already told it on this you did you told on the live one because we were there
that morning at eight o 'clock oh that's right but it was a nice little story it was hilarious by 815 I
think I had had three screwdrivers on that podcast yeah we we kind of pounded that weekend into the
ground we drank all day that day yeah all day it was a strangely depressing festival you know we're
very alone in the world yeah that day was fun though it was fun we went from literally drinking from
quarter to eight a .m. until one a .m. that's true it was an amazing feat that's true it was an amazing
feat I was very proud of it folks I should also mention in case I die during this podcast which is
a stronger and stronger possibility that I last time I did we did this podcast which was nurse 3d
I'm walking back to my car and I was like oh I'm feeling extremely dizzy in light headed
and the next morning I woke up 5 a .m. mid -passing out which I've never I've never passed out in my life
I was like I'm gonna pass out I'm like oh no every time I would turn my head I would almost block out
and pass out so finally I stand up to walk the bathroom splash water my face I fall over I wake my
girlfriend up I'm like I need some help here she sits with me we're like I don't know what's going
on every time I move my head I would almost pass out I let it go I kind of went away throughout
the day and it came back real hardcore the other night at dinner I'm sitting at dinner break out into
a cold sweat I'm like oh fuck I'm gonna pass out again this is not good I go running out of the
restaurant where we eat it it's called birch it's a nice restaurant here in Los Angeles you made a
big scene in the middle of it not a scene not a scene I I kept it to myself okay it was concerning
I go to urgent care and the doctor is like ask a bunch of questions he's like you seem really
you know healthy I'm gonna do drunk history again I just had a physical while my blood work was
perfect he's like I don't know what it is like I don't really have an idea but usually in this case
it's an inner ear thing you have an infection you're not aware of I just lost the whole story because
and I'm furious that I've not been invited to do drunk history again well I don't make the choices
job could you just be happy for someone else I'm tired to be it happy for everybody else what could
you do it once I do it all the time why the hell is it cast already fully I believe so
do you tell your manager you're interested though they'll call and get you know
each immediate irritated all right all right so I'm gonna do it Joe's making this about him but
it's really about me folks and the doctor's like in her ear he's like I think it's just simple
vertigo I think you're fine I'm like boy that's a relief to hear doc this has been a really stressful
week or two he goes take this medicine which is just drama mean which makes me extremely drowsy but
it does help the offness because I was feeling pretty dizzy and then as I'm walking out the door he
goes yeah you know if it's if it's not gone by Monday you go get an MRI the only other thing I could
think of is it could be like a brain mass as I'm walking out the door right so of course that's
kind of nagging at me but taking the drama he did make it go away I'm not gonna get the MRI I'm
thinking it's not a brain mass but I could be dead at any point and then you guys will all treat this
podcast like it's a legendary thing because I'll be dead well I'm glad you're getting one more
drunk history appearance in before your demise and it's nice to know you'll be sitting at home going
son of a bitch that should have been me I just I just want to be part of certain things so you just
you have representation you say you know what I'd like to do I'd like to be on drunk history you didn't
make a call you didn't have to do that did you no I didn't did you I didn't don't you dare don't
you dare I'm sorry I'm kidding well good luck with that and I really hope it doesn't cause a
brain hemorrhage oh it's it's definitely nothing alcohol related I am I do know that much
sounds like denial to me folks well no I sure it's not the booze no yeah and I'm kidding I'm joking
why are you getting it isn't I haven't seen you a little while I'm breaking your balls a little bit
right where you get a fucking fresh oh boy what movie it feels like a score says yeah good
fellas come on I haven't seen you in a while I'm breaking your balls you're getting fresh yeah it's
from good fellows I haven't seen you in a little while Billy bats says it to peshy before peshy kills
right yeah I remember um now after we did nurse 3d coincidentally now I believe out of all the
podcasts we've done we've had a handful uh we're where it's been movies that we didn't really
respect or shock weren't that great or whatever nurse 3d was one of those few and out of those few
nurse 3d was the worst I would say we were an agreement that yeah it was a terrible terrible movie
um the girl that started it though two days after we did the podcast the girl that there
a news thing came out that the girl that started it is trying to now soothe the makers of the film
that was an old that was an old news story but yeah that was fascinating blaming her for
ruining her career yeah she thought it ruined her career and they dubbed in like a bad expressionless
voice she's expressionless through the whole movie right exactly but she she was blaming all source
clearly she's and she was blaming them for like she wanted 50 million dollars or something
for ruining her career you should look it up it's a fascinating story and just a classic case of
somebody who's you know out of control suing anyone who'll listen it made me mad it was one of
those things that made me mad in the morning when I read it yeah I got aggravated yeah I get it
I got real aggravated I get it she didn't win she's not going to this won't go out of trial
it's just the nerve yeah the nerve yeah this movie ruined my career well then why did you do it
hey hey sister you think maybe a light bulb would have went off when you were walking across a
kitchen sands and pants and your clam was swaying across the paprika shakers you think maybe then it
would have popped in your head that this wasn't a great idea yeah well look oh no it's because they
dubbed a voice in it ruined my performance her starring in anything would not have been a smash
she wasn't the kind of name that's going to open a movie she didn't realize that either it's just
passing the buck point in the finger she got a big opportunity didn't connect because I'll tell you
she wouldn't have been suing if the movie had made any money at all of course not of course not
if you have you been to the overlook hotel I know people who have I haven't but look at that the
gold room is the bar in my neighborhood the gold room named after the gold room in this movie I think
it's possible um and it's a gold room yeah in the movie I've never been there where's a Connecticut
believe me I wanted to look up that and also if this woman has ever written anything else I'm
going to do both now you're going to look up where it is yeah um yeah I've never uh the the hotel
from the innkeepers is actually not far from where I grew up okay I like the innkeepers my buddy pad
healy was on that acquaintance I should say we're not close but I like him and I see him sometimes
I'm a fan of Pat Healy yeah I'm not a huge fan of that movie but I like Pat Healy quite a bit yeah
and I like who's the girl that's in it I like her too I forget her name I forgot both their names
until you said Pat Healy and then I remember oh yeah that's the guy from what's that David Kekner movie
called uh I like that movie take the money for a finger yeah cut off your nose for money
cheap thrills yeah yeah that's a good movie she was a novelist essayist satirist who was the
Diane Johnson who co -wrote this movie I didn't even hear that you were looking that up they were looking
up the overbroker overlook hotel one thing led to another it's in the Colorado Rockies oh it's in
Colorado that's right really that's right oh yeah duh they're driving up those huge mountains I'm an
idiot you know I don't deserve to be on drunk history a damn full I can't even tell the location
of a fucking famous mountain range oh god all right that's all right I'm sure the answer is
somewhere in the bottom of this bottle of wine as I pour another glass I was surprised I've never seen
you drink wine ever uh what what calls this it feels less alcoholicy that's why thank
man many many parents enjoy several glasses of wine at night it's just the other night I drank a couple
wines I smoked some light reef a bottle of red then I put on my headphones and listen to the new mega
death album as I played a space video game and it was one of the greatest nights I've ever had in my
life honestly that's all I ever want to do except not mega death and not video games oh man it was
awesome the mega death that the like anthemic metal went so well with like you know fast frantic
space action sure it was it was a lot of fun man it's strange you should say that because I just
watched the decline of western civilization part two what am I featuring mega death what are my favorite
movies ever it's just the best I bought the box that the punk one should be more in my wheelhouse
because I really love ex you know and all that and I did love it the second one is something
real special well the first one is like more of I think a celebration of punk music whereas the
second one is kind of like look at half of these bands yeah because you got good bands in there like
aro smith and mega death and whatever and then you have those hair metal bands that one of the saddest
things ever is that guy that just is drunken his mom's pool the whole time I watch the full which they
have on the on the blu ray they have the full interview with him it's fantastic he's drinking like
just pouring bottle after bottle of vodka into his throat with his mom looking on talking about
he's a piece of shit it's incredibly depressing brutal and wonderful brutal my favorite line in the movie
though is when Stephen Tyler goes you can really fuck to a good aro smith song there's a million
great lines like that and Stephen Tyler's hilarious in the movie if you haven't seen it you got to check
it out it was unavailable for decades now it's out directed by Penelope's theorist who directed
Wayne's world and clueless no that's gonna be a heck of a link that's related directed fast times yes
okay speaking of clueless Stacy dash all over Fox news oh yeah saying outlandish things I think
that's kind of her bag now which is crazy that's everybody's bag when the acting gigs run out what was
she saying she was saying well she said she said we shouldn't have a BET we shouldn't have black
history month we should either integrate or not and you know what you know what's hilarious the
probably read this weekend BET showed like 40 music videos starring Stacy dash she also started
in a TV show that was on BET yeah yeah and she's also been on the cover of like a zillion like black
centric magazines like shabby and stuff like that they called her out on it on the view pretty good
yeah it's one of the only times in the view I ever saw somebody get called out where I totally agreed
you're watching the view with your morning coffee here I some look band I got what what do I gotta do
I don't need to prep it for anything like drunk history she's you know what I mean
drunk history you know what I'm saying I'm just sitting here I did a nice job on drunk history and
they asked me back can you just be supportive I can't and I won't I could but I refuse
our buddy Pete home just got an HBO show with Judd app happy for him congrats Pete
that that'll be interesting I remember when he told us the idea yeah and now it's being made
is that weird it is weird that's how it works in this business go on Stacy dash
no that's I got nothing else I was I don't remember why I watched the view clip I somehow
I linked to it now since we we tend to get a little like oddly political on here lately what do
you think about this whole boycott of the Oscars for they're not being African -American nominees I agree
with it but I agree with it 100 % the problem though is I do think that the people that are boycotting
should have been boycotting other things a lot long much longer ago sure you know I think the
Grammys deserved a lot more shit than they got for letting you know Macklemore and Iggy Azalea
sweep the hip hop awards you know so that's that's absurd I'm a little disappointed that that that some
people that are boycotting didn't get involved until it seemingly directly affected them but I agree
with the ant vives response to Jada Pinkett no because Jada Pinkett's like I'm gonna I'm not going so
ant vive which here watch this video the first one she hates Will Smith she despises Will Smith
yeah but the video is off the charts funny it's supposed to be fun but she makes some real grade points
and she's like she's clearly just so angry with Will Smith but she's like you know back in the day
when I wanted to have the cast unite and get a little money for the rest of the black actors on staff
you know what your husband told me Jada he said your deals your deal and my deals my deal so
fuck off wow and then I got fired so now maybe you could do a little work helping other people get
jobs then your billionaire husband and your billionaire children it's it's incredible wow all right
take look that's that's those are fair points man sure and then she's like Will Smith didn't deserve
she's like that accent what what accent is he doing in that movie because it was different
and everything so now I didn't see concussion I may have a concussion I may be dead by the end of
this podcast so I will check it out if I live see it but yeah I don't know that Will Smith has
to be nominated I don't think he I'm not saying he just necessarily deserve to be nominated I'm saying
this is what I was gonna say before you cut me off with your own agenda I like it by watching you
what what I was gonna say was the problem doesn't lie with well the problem does lie with the
Oscar with the award shows on whatever the real problem needs to be fixed is projects enough projects
aren't being greenlit yes that allow any diversity of actors to be acting true so that's the real
problem you know there's this focus on like well what are we suppose the people that are opposed to
the boycott there's a focus on like well what are you supposed to do just nominate people just because
and it's like no that's not the solution either the solution is hollywood should be making more diverse
programs and I'm getting really really tired of people saying like the diversity issue isn't an
issue it is a fucking issue flip through your TV shows and your stations and everything it is
uncanny the amount of white faces sure and you can make the majority argument all you want
but in real life we are all far more integrated with people of different nationalities
than we ever see on these TV shows and quite frankly I'm kind of getting tired of like
the fucking Stephen Avery clans of the world determining what I get to watch on my TV well it's
middle America so is the Avery family this true okay show another ball and have you watched all that
I it annoys me here's what people are getting behind that's what people are people are getting
on yes and when the fact is no one has any idea if you did it or not because it's the most biased
document let me say this let me say this I loved it it's insanely biased let me say this
publicly please please let me say this publicly he was sent to jail wrongfully in that first 14 -year
term whatever it was that seemed to be the truth it seemed to be that he was sent to jail incorrectly
absolutely it does seem that things were conducted during the trial in the second trial that were
possibly designated that it was a mistrial possibly he was framed I'm not disagreeing with any of that
my only problem with the soul thing is every single person that is the loudest mouthpiece for
this guy to be freed is the exact same person who had they known Stephen Avery before this big
mishap happened they would have tried to run him out of town with fucking torches yeah like the guy
did so much creepy shit before any of this and for some reason that's just that's just like ignored
now it's like it's like all the sexual assault behaviors and everything it's just ignored
not saying so he should be imprisoned for life because of that or he deserves a mistrial because of that
I'm just saying everybody I know that supports this guy is like it's like you're the exact person
that would like be tweeting against this person yeah like it's I mean people take to Facebook about
this shit and it has like overtaken their life and it's just like you know how many millions of times
this has happened and the fact that he is wide is sort of more irksome because this happens to black
people I think infinitely more than it happens to white people I love the it's one of my favorite
M &M lyrics when he talks about Columbine and he goes well now it's a tragedy yeah that's the only part
I remember yeah it's like that that kind of shit has been happening in other communities for so long
and they just don't demon as a mass killing they demon as like an unfortunate economic problem
in this in that neighborhood or whatever yeah it's like it's it's so fucking ridiculous man I'm really
really really getting tired of one of the greatest things I ever heard somebody say in regards
this sort of thing I saw Mark Marin at comics once in New York and some like sort of right wing guy
said something like criticism heckled him or criticized him about something he was saying and like
the heckle was something along the lines of like well I don't hear those people complaining you know
speaking about like yeah people in economic straights and stuff and Mark Marin goes you know why
because anybody that really should be complaining is too busy working three jobs to feed themselves
that's true it's like I'm really kind of getting tired in order they have a mouthpiece to go complain
about it on the every person I hear tree stumping about it about any sort of real issue it's always
seems to be a very privileged white person yeah that's always who gives the most of the
man and they also do nothing about it so like yeah exactly I posted 800 Facebook things about it
have you done anything this is doing anything yeah have you talked to any your city councilman
right have you gone to any town hall meetings right have you tried to get behind certain legislation
of course not and that probably wouldn't do shit either but like it certainly does nothing you posting
on Facebook about it's just the whole thing makes me sick I hate everybody on the right and the left
yeah well make me sick yeah your pieces of shit well I'm watching this thing to talk about you
know because this is a movie podcast the staircase is like an eight part genius documentary about
did this guy or did he not kill his wife one of my favorite things I've ever seen you can rent it
you should look for it it's on Sundance originally but at the end of every episode you're 100 % convinced
like the end of episode one you're like oh fuck this guy definitely killed his wife the end of
episode two you're like the system is fucked clearly this man didn't kill his wife right and because
they're just they're toying with you that's all these that's what a documentary does right so
for making a murder for 10 parts to never give you a single bit of conflicting information when there
is ample shady conflicting information is really very fucked up and if I watch the thing too I mean
my girlfriend were pacing around the house like this the system is fucking we got into it so
but then at the end of the day you're like wait a minute and then you start reading all this shit
so he answered the door when this girl came in a towel so he had called her several times from a
blocked number you know like there's a lot of weird shit that goes on I'm not going down this rabbit hole
but there's tons of stuff that is very important to this story that is not in the documentary
and then the people keep posting about it are ignoring that stuff still because they're choosing to
believe what they want and not believe what they don't want it's a classic it's a classic argument that
is always posed and put forward when you're dealing with people of faith yeah whether the faith is
God or Stephen Avery's existence innocence or Woody Allen's guilt or whatever it is people
draw their own conclusion they have faith in what they believe to be true without any real hard
court proof to support it either way either way and then you and then you argue them and say but
what about this and this and this and it's like arguing with a Jesus freak yeah they can't answer
your questions right well that's just because you know that's a it's not just be no I just
presented you with a fact yeah so now what what's the counterpoint to the fact right what's the argument
so then the girlfriend goes on Nancy Grace yeah she's like uh which I also
want come that's the old con dog bark like he used to beat the shit out of me all the time and he
was insanely violent and he's very fucked up and he told me don't ever say anything about it or it'll
ruin my case and on and on and then you tell this to people and they're like yeah but it's Nancy Grace
well okay you hear and maybe they did pay her off for her story but you hear it's
I don't it's Nancy Grace you hear well that girlfriend's clearly not you know a reliable source I've
heard that from a different yeah oh she was she had a DUI so she's an unreliable source of whether or
not she was abused now here's the thing here's the thing if that girl now when that girl was telling
that story I was I wasn't sure if I believed her or not I was like well this could just be a
convenient thing to be saying right now I don't know but it doesn't mean that I'm just going to
completely discount it it means to me that the jury is still out on that sure and again once again
had this been a situation where Steven Avery was not wrongfully imprisoned and a woman had come out
against him with the record that he has already yeah and said this guy beats me she would be given a
hell of a lot more credibility and if anyone any one of these people many of whom are like are my
friends would hear this from her and she said well you know he used to be the shit I mean they're like yeah
I don't know if I believe her because she was an alcoholic folks that's insane and that's what
you would scream in somebody's face about doing in a bar if it wasn't tied to this documentary that
manipulated your emotions right you know that this this stuff's going on all the time now don't
doubt the victim you have to believe the victim and I completely agree with that but they're
choosing to not believe this victim and I realized that beating a woman doesn't make him a murderer
but it does certainly factor into a trial for a man accused of murdering a woman I don't necessarily
think he did it I don't necessarily think he didn't do it I don't know I love talking about it
but it's the people who are a thousand percent sure you just want to shake and be like what the
fucks the matter with you the jury's out that's my point yeah that's my point of course and people
are latching on anything the new thing now which I've seen 800 people posed is that there's a really
obese serial killer who was in the area around this time and there's a picture of a guy who looks
very vaguely like this would be serial killer in the background of one of the trials now I don't think
it looks anywhere near enough like him to make this case but everybody's like well that proves it
was a serial killer you're latching on to things that prove the point you've already decided in
your mind are true it's again it's it's faith arguments well then why is it in the Bible right exactly
well okay that was written a hundred years or 60 years or whatever after it was passed on word about
yeah but it but then but that's similar stories after a hundred years it's like for Christ's
yeah you know does it honestly does a better job weekend and week out of presenting this stuff is
date line date line every every commercial break you know you're like okay but I didn't expect to
hear about that they're not bias in any way reporting this shit and I don't know how a documentary
that is a billion percent biased is being hailed by everyone at this mass as this masterpiece as
much as I enjoyed it it's obviously extremely entertaining well here's the other here's the other
point I would like to make about this documentary obviously the go -to defense for Avery's innocence is
always is always he was going to sue them for a money they didn't have right right they didn't want to
pay this was clearly a setup you never hear the flip side of that argument you never hear the flip
side of that argument which is okay so if we're just going to believe that he was framed because of
this coincidental instance of him because theoretically getting them into a position where they owed him
this money yeah okay why don't you flip that around and go well couldn't you just say it the
other way couldn't you say you're just saying he's innocent because they were going to have to pay
him this money do you see what I'm saying of course you could just flip it the other way and it never
gets flipped the other way yeah I complete I completely agree uh the reason I saw by the way I
almost lost that completely no I thought halfway through it I kind of forgot what I was trying to say
I thought it's the terror that came into me when I finished episode 10 of making murder my whole
reason which I have not heard anybody really discuss we talked about it a lot at work is my whole
reason for thinking he couldn't have done this is because I'm like it takes a sociopath to be this
convincing and this man is very close to mentally handicapped you know so when he's like
presenting his case you believe that he didn't do it just from watching him talk I agree
and an idiot which no offense is what Stephen Avery legally is technically classified as
or a moron or so there's actually IQ determinations and he is like a moron or a mental
mentioned there's all these different terms right uh and he's like 10 points above Brandon the brother
who everybody's like you know this this that kid was obviously taking advantage of I don't necessarily
think he had anything to do with it but this guy to put a pro in his column I don't think he's smart
or savvy enough to be sticking to the story for this long and not have some I think the most
fallout if he's not guilty I think the most likely in my opinion the most likely
explanation of or the most likely alternative events was probably the nephew all the stuff the
neighbor yeah and the neighbor said we're putting this on your uncle and if you say any different
we'll fucking kill you sure that's you know and I know that I'm not the first person to say that
but right that to me all right I could buy that but I've heard a bunch of theories I think they're
all pretty plausible it's very fun to talk about I just people really scare me people don't realize
that they are exactly the same as Fox news but for the other side that's what bothers me Bill
Mar is Bill O 'Reilly but for the other side yeah it's of course but nobody on the other side of
anything and neither are right anybody on team Bill Mar anybody on team Bill O 'Reilly will never
understand they're just as bad as the other person no they won't ever see them I tweeted as we
talk about this it's funny before we did the podcast I tweeted my favorite thing that I've ever tweeted
okay it has to do with this all right I try to live my life somewhere between Sid and Nancy and Ron
Nancy that's my favorite thing I've ever tweeted that's where you want to be somewhere between crazy
anarchist and ultra conservative I thought you were at first saying between Sid and Nancy which is a very
small no I try to live somewhere between Sid and Nancy and Ron and Nancy okay all right I think
that's a good philosophy yeah I agree Joe you know potentially murderous heroin addicted
couple yeah and two of the most elitist pricks that ever lived yes I'm wearing between there right yeah
I would agree all right uh I wanted a little more this is my favorite shot of the shining and I believe
completely ripped off by my favorite shot of boogie nights when marquee market sitting on the couch
yes staring vacantly into space because he's like that's enough of this for me they're both thinking
different things in these moments but two of my favorite shots I don't think it's all coincidental either
that as we talked about uh Steven Avery and we spiraled down into that whole thing yeah it was parallel
to Jack Nicholson losing his mind in this movie yeah uh I love that Stephen King wrote this as he was
like a coked up alcoholic who like presumably was kind of hating his family for keeping him from getting
worked on like there's a lot of layers of this movie have you seen room 237 yeah I can't stand it
I hated it just a bunch of fucking idiots yeah I hated it so they can't have tomatoes represented the
American Indian and then I loved when the people that worked on the shiny came out and they were like
no yeah it was just what we had to put there yeah because we worked in a kitchen well they're like
put Kubrick was such a perfectionist that he obviously chose each thing to represent something
or he chose it because visually he liked it you idiot I liked it as a everyone can take different
things from a movie exercise yes but I found it boring and I found everyone in it to be criminally
this movie I will say is the most perfectly framed film unbelievably shot movie for sure
I've ever seen every shot is perfectly framed yeah it's like it's like a comic book panel yeah it's
really really beautifully shot you could I think you could watch this sound less for sure oh yeah this
is a good background at the party movie I know true Kubrick heads find this to be lesser Kubrick it's
far and away my favorite of Kubrick's movie who finds it to be lesser Kubrick I think your real
Kubrick heads your real film heads do for sure because it's you know it's a horror movie and it's not
trying to say something but it is actually saying a lot of things I mean to me it's just as valid as
clockwork orange and I would almost consider clockwork orange or her movie yeah I agree almost the first
half a full metal jacket is a horror movie the second half is not great in my opinion I hate the
second half yeah but that first half is I mean every every second up until Vincent Napier blows his
brains out on that toilet is I mean it's masterful yeah for sure yeah I think I was 10 years old when
I saw a full metal jacket my dad rented it with me and that's that opening scene with Arlee
Irmery whatever his name is like you know your 11 10 11 years it blew me it was like when I saw
dice clay for the first time right I just was like this is the greatest thing I've ever seen or
like when I saw Alph for the first time well not really but when I saw my first episode of Alph
which kind of changed my life did you think Arlee Irmery was more effective in full metal jacket or
saving Silverman I gotta I gotta tell you I love him in saving Silverman and I love that he makes
out with the guy at the end of it saving Silverman folks no one would call it a good movie but
laugh for laugh it is fucking hilarious who's in that against Steve Zahn and Jack Black like at
their funniest before they cared about anything they both seem like they're high in every scene and
Silverman and no not Silverman Jason Biggs who is adequate Jason that's why I meant Jason Biggs
and Amanda Pete who played the girlfriend and every one of those movies back in those days
there was nobody better to me than Amanda Pete it is such a funny movie and I watched it very
recently and was howling laughing there's so much funny shit in it a lot of it seems improvised by
Steve Zahn and Jack Black who are gods at that time for me I just watched the that guy Dick Miller
documentary yeah about the Dick Miller about Dick Miller the character actor yeah and when they got
to the burbs which is one of my favorite films of all time uh they they interviewed Corey Feldman
and Corey Feldman goes I was pretty wild back then I remember I was smoking weed on the set a lot
in my trailer with Sam Kinnison Sam Kinnison's on the set of the burbs yeah yeah smoking weed with a
17 year old kid or whatever that's really bizarre and uh and then it cuts to Dick Miller now and he
goes he was a quarry was a bit of a smart ass and he starts laughing and then it cuts to
pre -scene footage before the director yells action and Corey Feldman is dancing around in the scene uh
huh and Dick Miller goes shut the fuck up kid we're trying to get some acting done
and you're action is I'm Dick Miller on Netflix or where to see it I want to watch that I watch
it on Hulu okay I don't get Hulu uh it was great he was in Gremlins which we reviewed on the show
he's in Gremlins he's in all the Roger Cormin movies he's in every Joe Dante movie now I worked with
a comedy writer whose name is Mark Torgrove he's half of a writing partnership
and me and Pete work with them on outsourced he tremendous show
uh better than the rapid guy honestly you ever see it no it was better than the rapid guy put the
mic in front of your face maybe this is why nobody can hear you it's I am tasting it it's not
directly in front of your face I can tell from here but I feel it on my mouth what do you say
after that we do the podcast tonight we go up to a bar and have a few we talk about this every time
I'm fine to do that you'll do that definitely tonight yeah I think that's a good idea since I'm on
drama mean and it might be dying but yeah I'll do it for sure all right because Pat I've got to
tell you there's a void here that can't be filled that surely alcohol will feel and you'll wake up
feeling even better tomorrow I keep thinking tomorrow be the day I wake up and I go now's the day
it doesn't it's not common you got to have a kid I think that's what I'm realizing more and more
I think I got to have a kid no no that that would be the most depressing thing so I'm trying to
dies within a year this will be used in the dog trial in the truck yeah in the in the frame
Joe de Rosa was framed yeah ten part net series about that'll be called the death of Khan yeah by
the way by the way if I was the center of a documentary docu series that wasn't impeccably shot
yeah let's see how many people rally behind it I can tell you right now people are going to come
out of the woodwork against Joe de Rosa and I'm leading the pack folks uh mark torgrove
uh was auditioned and was cast I believe he'd have to clarify but I think he was cast as Danny the
kid in the shining and Kubrick saw this other kid like to more game the part but he basically had the
part and to tell you how much Kubrick must have a vision in his mind is that this guy I worked with
looks identical to this kid really and Kubrick must have just like envisioned a kid like forget
talent not that this neither of them are talented this they're fine but like he wanted a kid who
looked exactly like this apparently because they're identical how old are who they are talented you
mean you said that wrong I'm sure that I'm sure this guy was a talented child actor I don't know I
worked with him as a 50 -year -old comedy writer 40 -year -old comedy okay whatever but a Danny
I think he's fine I think he didn't like you know succumb to drugs or anything but you know what I love
about this always odd to me in a movie by the way if I may don't they're doing this father -son scene
Jack Nicholson is in his like underwear in a bathrobe and he's holding his son on his lap yeah now
in a true father -son relationship this is fine but this isn't this is a set where an actor sure
has to take this child on his lap a little awkward yeah yeah I would think
yeah I was sure you know you're dealing with when you do a sex scene in a movie do you get a
boner I did do a sex scene once in a movie I everyone everything I've heard is that you do not
because there's so much I did not it was the most it was the most awkward thing I've ever had to
go my life right what movie was this so I cannot watch it it was a comedy that I directed and wrote
with Bill Burr and Robert Kelly called cheat oh you wrote yourself a little sex scene did you uh well
my character had a sex scene and I played my character so I had to do the sex scene but uh it was
it was a almost fully nude sexy yeah it was comedic but it was awkward and I took my the film
went to the Tribeca Film Festival pet oh I don't want to brag but first ever directorial effort
goes to Tribeca Film Festival um the Tribeca Film Festival which is spearheaded I believe by
Dirty Grandpa Bobby De Niro oh I I only know him as Dirty Grandpa okay okay fair enough I only
call him Ronin uh anyway um I but my you know I took my parents to see it right and it was kind of
weird watching the sex scene with my mom next to me what I want to say here is look at Nicholson's head
folks there is not one not one star above like fifth down on the call sheet working today
who's rocking that level of balding they don't allow it unless you go bald like Bruce Willis or whatever
else and I respect it so much that he was headlining these movies back in the day and we just
he also is not a he's also not an impeccably good -looking man no he looks like he looks like everyone
of your buddy's dads from the suburbs and that is what plan and simple makes people like when people
talk about this heyday of 70s movies that it was a better time of movies there's no other way to look
your actors your biggest actors at that time were Dustin Hoffman Al Pacino Robert De Niro Jack
Nicholson Jean Hackman these aren't good -looking men they're five feet tall and the most of them
the women of that period too were not to me like these like these like bony -assed fake -titted you know
Angelica Houston was uniquely beautiful sure Merrill Streep was uniquely beautiful sure Glenn close
was uniquely beautiful sure you know it wasn't this like and you bought them like they're there
really aren't any of those people working today who don't fit into that exact mold and those people
are never great actors really they might have presence but they're never great actors and that's why
less and less I'm excited to go to a movie because I'm always like what are we doing here who's in
this they're all kind of the same yeah it's a bummer it's a shame this kids got great sweaters
through the whole movie by the way well this was one of the theories because he had an Apollo sweatshirt
that they thought it was some sort of thing about the faking of the moon launch uh for crisis
what was the theory about his Mickey Mouse sweatshirt earlier there was one I think it was about the
disney vacation of America or stupid garbage John I'm gonna step up for one second cover for
for two minutes all right that's about to spill beer on himself empty and I am not so it's a
first beer we're watching a movie I'm when you say someone that paints a picture of me
panceless you're not talking into the money dumping up which doesn't help the picture
get up to get your beer you're gonna miss the best part of the movie which is now the witch scene
I believe oh no it's not because he doesn't see the witch Nicholson sees the witch as Pat
proclaims his sobriety he just walked across the room you're not on the mic pat they can't hear you
and you're still talking it's it was yeah he almost did it my big fat Greek wedding he got up and
walked through the headphones still on it almost did that jerk back fall down thing that Nia
Nia Vervato what's her name Nia Vervato John Vervatos I believe was the star of my big fat Greek wedding
and my big fat Greek wedding part two is coming out where somebody else gets married or they're
renewing their vowels or something I don't know here's my review of my big fat Greek wedding part two
seems like somebody renewed their bowels that's gonna be my review of that movie when it comes out
seems like somebody renewed their bowels because it's a piece of shit get it but I am a John
Corbett fan from back in the section the city day so I support anything that guy does and Nia
constopolis whatever name is she you know she does a good job I like her she seems like a sweet lady
Nia Vervato's something like that anyway Shelley Duval is just running on jack Nicholson and
I believe this is the scene where she's gonna tell him that Danny Solo witch up in the room and this
is this is to me one of the scariest things that's ever been committed to film once he gets into
the room with the witch Nicholson I mean the if you ever read Dr. sleep the opening chapter
is about Danny as a child still after the events of the shining being revisited by the witch in his
apartment with his mom and the witch smearing her shit on the wall in the bathroom and it's one of
the scariest fucking things ever read my life is Dr. sleep the shining sickle written by Stephen King
yeah I didn't read it that's crazy I own all his books and it's mostly about a grown -up Danny
dealing with this like sleep cold or something but the opening takes place right after the events
of the shining okay I didn't hear anything about it being good I never looked at it got very good
reviews okay this witch lady comes back at the beginning though and it's it is scary as fuck
I watched this weekend so I had my own little blizzard the doctor told me to not leave the house
which was great I watched so many movies watch this documentary that's on Netflix called The Nightmare
yeah about sleep paralysis it was scary I think I should make a horror movie but that's the kind
of thing that like once I hear about it I will find a way to work that into my life having sleep paralysis
I there's another documentary called The Nightmare that is also about sleep paralysis
really which I don't understand how two movies about the same topic with the same title were made
no and you can't find anything about the other one online but it's on Amazon I've watched it okay
um and anyway when I saw that they say in that documentary it happens to people that tend to
open themselves up to it by worrying about it and being concerned and I had a bit on stage where I said
I will get this sleep paralysis because they say it'll worry about it yeah if you worry about it you'll
get it and I'm like oh so so it's definitely gonna happen to me then okay great it's it's pretty
scary shit when I was googling uh this constant dizziness or whatever they were all saying like as
soon as you find a way to stop thinking about it you won't be dizzy and it's very very true
like I haven't really engaged with anyone coming over here and like talking and stuff I I'm not
feeling dizzy at all but when I'm sitting in bed like I wonder if I have a brain mass I get real
dizzy real fast I mean it just sounds to me like you're being a little pussy well I've really never
had any illnesses of any kind of my entire life um so I don't think I am being a pussy it was very
serious I can't speak to that because I haven't been with you your whole life but the time that I
have right on you I found you to be Nicholson is hilarious in this movie these faces are faces I make
whenever anyone speaks to me which I'm sure they don't appreciate they are I would imagine like
I would bet at that buggy night scene and I'm I'm imagining Mark Walberg is a pretty dumb man
I bet Paul Thomas Anderson showed him a still of Nicholson making that face in the shining because you
know oh Paul Thomas Anderson is obsessed with the show I should just make this just do a check
you want me to make this face I can make this face that movie uh I it's one of my favorites but originally
de caprio was cast and dropped out of the last second to do Titanic and as much as I enjoy de caprio I
think he would have been too good for the role and Walberg being dumb helps that movie immeasurably
in my opinion the fantasies I'm having right now that Walberg hears you saying this somehow
and beats you up in public are so vivid in my mind I pray that Mark Walberg beats me up in public so
that I can get five million dollars from it that was a tweet that was another tweet you want to hear
another tweet ahead Jesus Christ John yes when when will the whole be filled for you Jim never just
don't on me all of the Walberg brothers have to pretend the other ones are cool I don't follow
that one how do you not follow that I well oh like Mark has to pretend that Donnie is cool and Donnie
has to pretend that Mark is cool they all have tool bag brothers you don't get it but they're all
actors I forgot six and they are kind of cool aren't they forget it man all right why does your
Mac many keep going in and out of focus because it's underneath that because there's there's a
there's a there's a piece of a single piece of plywood between this and the fucking shit time Warner
Router okay so this is the guy that you met in the elevator yeah by the way folks I kept saying
earlier the witch scene we were nowhere near it apparently I think I thought that was happening but we
are in the bar scene now with the bartender and in this scene he does talk glad you asked me that
boy yeah he talks in a very proper accent in the scene and with the affectation almost English
sounding and then in real life he's like there were no cups in my room he said literally something like
a jerky boys character in real life and I'm like this guy's the greatest actor of all time that he can
switch from this voice yeah to what he did in the shiny well you can tell him briefly again about
meeting the man in the elevator maybe they didn't hear it I was in it if you didn't hear the
episode I was in an elevator Pat and I went to a harcon in Denver called mile high har to do a live
broadcast of we'll see you in hell where we did maniac cop two in a theater with some very lovely
loyal people that came out fans of that show of that movie and some of them fans of this podcast
anyway the if they were when they came in they sure were when they left you know we a I always say
if we can if we can reach one person Pat we did our job and I think that's roughly what we do
anyway we uh the first night we were there we got we arrived at like 10 o 'clock it was kind of late
and we were going up to our rooms to drop our bags off before we went to go uh drink
because even though we had to wake up at 7 a .m we still felt the need to go drink
uh because there's missing pieces inside of us emotionally
sure anyway and at the front desk and they're giving us all of our things to check in and whatever
and this 80 -year -old man walks up and they say uh mr so -and -so this was given this was left for you
from the festival people and they hand him a medal of love but he goes well what's in it
and the guy kid at the desk who was clearly high remember how high that kid was
he was so high folks and although you're working the front desk at a hotel you better be a little
hot in Denver and high baby yeah so uh he goes well what's in it he goes I don't know man and he goes uh
he goes well what what what was it given to me for and the guy goes I don't know and I'm thinking who
is this crazy old man and then uh he goes there are no cups in my room by the way zero cups there was
not one cup uh and the kid goes we will send some up immediately and then I got on the elevator with
this old man and this other guy and uh the whole ride up he just kept telling me they're no
cups in my room can you believe it wall -to -wall not one cup how do you have a glass of water there's
not one cup that he gets off the elevator and the other kid goes that's the bartender from the shiny
yeah I was like I don't understand that how does a guy like that never win an award he is clearly
so far out of his own personality in this film sure but like is that a guy who ever acted again you know
it doesn't matter look at him in this movie he's great but you're not going to nominate this man for
an academy he was in real life he's time daily and in this movie he's like time daily
hey star of cag in the unless yeah who was the star of Kate Nally remember Kate Nally well it was
it was you know it was Jane uh Kurt Jane Curtain from from us and now and the other
front of mine made love to her daughter once I bet she's beautiful I found Jane Curtain to be striking
I agree completely um she reminded me of my aunt Sammy who has passed
not that I had the crush on my aunt but they were pretty women at Sammy yeah that sounds like a
christian wig character she was a lot of fun she was a lot of fun all right you drink amaretto straight
up never saw anything like it in my life what is amaretto a liqueur it's a it's an almond liqueur
that most people mix with milk yeah or coke or something right she would just take it straight
love damaretto all right down by the bottle I admired that about her um it does sound more and more
like a christian wig character as I continued to describe yeah oh Sammy loves her amaretto yeah anyway um
Jane Curtain who was the other lady in Kate Nally christian wig lives in my neighborhood I just saw
the other time oh I also look who lives in the rich neighborhood everybody can you have a little tacked
haha I also uh have now seen and my girlfriends these are all the time Andy McDowell who walks like
apparently 20 hours a day around my neighborhood I love Andy McDowell she's great my father once
told my mother he would leave her if Andy McDowell expressed the slightest interest in which might
have contributed to their divorce I don't remember the two the two women of that generation that I
would pay lots of money to sleep with yeah are Andy McDowell and Mary steen virgin is my number one
steenberg is the best I never did much for me I find steen virgin to be with every passing year
just hotter yeah steenberg for sure oh my lord she deserves dancing now let me share my
tears her that's a great that is a power looks I love I love them together let me share my tweet with
you about Andy McDowell I think I tweeted this once to the lovely Karen I'll try to give it more
support than you gave my two tweets anytime I've ever mentioned a tweet in the show you've spread
your cheeks and shout on it but here we go what do Andy McDowell and my uncle Gary have in common
what they both ruined four weddings in a funeral yes arm you've said that tweet on this show I think I
have this is one another of my favorite shots is this guy with a portrait of a naked woman with an
apple yeah it's scabbing brothers just like sort of the angelic character in the film yeah and then
they finally show you him in his home quarters and he's got tits all over his room I love it which is
great I love it which is great and it's I feel that it's a statement to say sex is not evil sex is
beautiful violence is evil which is how this man will meet his end unfortunately yeah do you love
the Simpsons parody of the shining the Shining they ever saw it oh you don't watch the Simpsons not
really I bet you'd love it I've seen many episodes I like it I just said it's parody of the shining
is is perfect really to the point where you almost mix up the two play scamming and brothers
uh well it's actually the Scottish janitor is him is this character he's filling that role and
who's Danny Bart yeah but and you know Homer is you know an ankle sin yeah you should just watch
it's 10 minutes it's it's gonna be well Marge's Shelley Duval right you do you find Shelley Duval
attractive there's somebody who also could not exist in today's climate um I sometimes sometimes
you know who I found quite attractive uh in her uh in her formative years was Lily Tomlin
never my thing at all I've never a young Lily Tomlin has got has got Williamsburg Brooklyn
written all over she was a doll that's not my thing either I she was never my cup of mustard
nor was Shelley Duval I like a young Lily Tom Shelley long
Shelley long is kind of boringly hot though there's it's I like Shelley long I mean I always was like
I was a cursed alley guy yeah over Shelley long yeah yeah I I always liked Rebecca does this
the witch you're referring to yeah this is the witch okay now we're in the scene that bathroom
is amazing could you imagine having that bathroom in your house just all green
ladenolium and ceramic now they made that for the movie right yeah of course that that's just not
the way that this bathroom looks right now this is kind of the way that the the in an upstate
California looks which uh it's where a couple of friends of ours are having their wedding don't
mention their names oh Madonna in is uh I got a room there for the wedding I did too and they all
have like really creative cool looking rooms like this I get a weird discount on my room where I got like
that it was called like the like trail hike package oh gosh it's something about two cantines or
something okay but it was cheaper for some reason I don't know why can I tell you and I'm not proud of
this this is one of those scenes like Beverly D 'Angelo in the shower indication where when it
starts happening I can't help but think of the thousands of times I paused a VHS tape and masturbated
to this thousands of times I mean look your business is your business pet that's all I had and I
can't stress enough folks that's all we had was pausing a VHS tape it was tough back then to get
your note off it really was what year are you talking this for me it would have been you know
I guess I was 1990 I was you know 10 years old pausing VHS tapes and they were they had to be VHS
tapes that were PG like 16 candles had PG breasts six candles is rated or though it's PG it has 16
candles is not a PG movie you want about a thousand dollars on it no I don't want a bit of thousand
dollars on it how about ten thousand dollars okay it has it has the f word it has smoking of
reefer and it has tits and it's rated PG why do you think I've seen it more than perhaps any other
movement just looking this up I know he's not he's on Twitter folks I'm not that's just what open when
I open it's the devotion to the craft I that's just what open brings 16 candles yeah I had or like
I was allowed to watch vacation because it is PG my parents forgot about how was that movie PG
it was because it was just prior to the PG 13 rating but nowadays it would have been an R you can't
show tits f word and joint and not have it not be rated are yeah they say f in it don't they don't
they fucking forgot my birth then go yeah this part's pretty good so gross
now what is wrong with her skin is it rotting off yeah
God bless this old lady she's like yeah I'll do a full frontal
I wouldn't have pegged her as a witch well that's how he describes her in the sequel book
grand that's why I say that that is really rough stuff man yeah yeah and in the in the in the doctor
sleep he talks about how her flesh like sticks to the wall because it's like rotting off it's pretty
gross now Stephen King's famous quote about this movie is that he hated it of course and he said
Stanley Kubrick apparently wants to make a movie that will hurt people the hell does that mean
I don't know it's his notorious quote about the movie where it's like but shouldn't horror kind of
want to hurt people I don't think Stanley Kubrick wanted to hurt people I think he was just I don't
either I think you just thought it went too far which I don't really see it's not like
criminally disturbing movie it also doesn't go as far as the book goes yeah I never understood
Stephen King's issues with the movie that thing in the in the movie where you see like the guy like
with the bear yeah costume on or whatever yeah that's like a bit apparently I think a big thing in
the book where it's like these orgies where they would dress up as like bears and stuff right so
it's probably just he cut stuff out that Stephen King didn't want cut out but like it's so
insane to me that Stephen King will like a indoor silver bullet which you and I watched it well I
watched and then you fell asleep but you can't love silver bullet and it was a 1 a .m. screening
and I don't know Joe no but I loved I loved it I had a great time watching it who was entertained but
obviously the shining is a better move we should at some point not for this podcast because who
would listen to us for four hours but we should watch that Stephen Weber version I don't really want
to yeah I'd be curious I'd be curious to see it yeah I mean who else is in it hold on I'm going to
look it up probably Nancy Travis she wasn't everything in those days I miss Nancy Travis where she
bid I think she's around she's probably got her money and happy let's see here she was the
long -suffering wife in that shelly Duvall is looking good right there yeah okay that's good stuff
she was on whatever one of the one of those sitcoms that lasted for like 45 years
since I'm sure she made her money let me see here okay the shining oh she's still on it last
man standing with Tim Allen yeah that's what it is but before that she was on a different one
called with Michael Mallay or something well she's still on last man standing this is the one before
I know she's still on last man's stand let's see here Nicholson ever get plugs or anything he was
still pretty balding by the Joker I feel like he wasn't that balding though yeah he must have
gotten a little something done I'm trying to find the drivolta is full plugs at this point like I it's
it's easily spotted I guess when you see some but like Jeremy Piven was obviously bald in the 90s
then came back with full hair nobody seems to care you know who plays the wife in the TV miniseries
Rebecca Demorne oh I love Demorne which she bit up to Melvin van Peoples in the scam and
crudders rule okay I love him the rocks the cradle that's a genre movie I wish they'd make a lot
more tomorrow Demorne is 56 these days checks out now there's the cover of the miniseries which always
looks like Anthony Michael Hall to me that is a terrible cover well you said you wanted to see the
goddamn thing yeah I stand by it directed by Mick Harris now Mick Harris also directed riding
walkers well I don't know he directed a bunch of the hell razor sequels that weren't good but he also
directed the riding the bullet adaptation which I bought today based on the fact of that it got
such good reviews what's right in the ball it's another Stephen King adaptation okay he did sleep walkers
good review it was it was well received okay yeah I'll watch him got accolades two prime time Emmy
awards okay fair enough I love Nicholson on this saying now what do you love about it I just
there's some there's some element of a husband really discussed it with his wife that always
just makes me chuckle probably because it reminds me of my childhood sadly just a man yelling at a
woman I got to tell you I'm looking up pictures of Rebecca Demorne current pictures and I think I
want to marry her folks I mean it's this is what it's come to chose googling pictures that you can't
well back at Demorne and showing them to me I mean are you disagree she looks very attractive
but she always did phenomenal she was in the in keepers wasn't she we are now that was the lady from
top gun oh okay well she was in something like that who was that Kelly McGillis Kelly McGillis
last year uh oh Demorne is single I'm sure you have a strong chance Joe I think I could have a shot
with a lady like this she's she's heading towards 60 well make sure if she tells you that she's
60 you don't say that she looks younger she's married to Patrick O 'Neal sportscaster and Bruce
Wagner novelist so I mean it seems like she's open -minded to an artist type are you an artist time I
would say so all right I'm gonna make a play for Demorne get in there hey that's not make it sound
crash Pat all right I want to miss Demorne I have a Joe Derosa on the phone for you oh my put him
right through what an artist type what does he want he says you're holding up really well okay he said
you're pushing 60 and he thinks he's got a chance at that well he's not wrong by all means
all right scamming brothers is now calling the hotel and
they're closing in now correct me if I'm wrong we have roughly an hour remaining
oh christ normally we'd be out at this point we have an hour remaining we're at 122
usually we end at 130 so we better whip this into shape Joe well I mean we were doing great I
knew we shouldn't do this goddamn movie you promised the people you did I had nothing to do with
that we said we should start saying what we're gonna do no I know I never said that so now we need
to pick what we're doing next next no we're not doing that because we're gonna end up in this
fucking jam again we get another hour another hour maybe we should smoke some reef what do you think
I think you're gonna be miserably slurring your speech am I slurring no no well I need you to ramp it
up have another beer or something because you're getting slow over here oh people I think though I
think you'll find they're loving me out there this goes out live right right folks tweet in your
thoughts time to take some calls hey folks that would really help if we could take some fucking calls you
want me to I can't tweet for people said yeah questions about the shining yeah do that all right but
you gotta talk while I do it pecs I can't do two things at once I'm not a god googling Rebecca
DeMorne photos can you blame me it was worth it the juice was worth the squeeze oh do you not
agree uh okay well let me let me think about what I watched this weekend I watched some curb
enthusiasm I'm rewatching that with my girlfriend I think you and I have a a Larry Richard Lewis report
about us who's who I think you're definitely Richard Lewis you're out of your fucking mind you're
very the sky I'm Larry David well okay all right I'll be Richard Lewis fine you get to be the
star there's a shot of Richard Lewis when he they have to help a blind man move where that ridiculous
Harry has is drenched in sweat that me and my girlfriend paus and laughed out for like an hour and a
half it's one of the funniest things I've ever seen and I love Richard Lewis why would you take a
personal I because I want to be Larry David I relate to him okay all right you can be I relate to
him you can be them both you know if I had said Larry David you would have said I'm Richard Lewis that's
not true uh I watched uh Phoenix as I mentioned I watched western civilization which I mentioned
this is this is death I can't think of what I watched well this is riveting well you're also not
you did tweet all right um I watched a lot of dark how long you can carry this what are some new
documentaries that I watched pets stop please uh this is sad at this the nightmare which I already
mentioned right I watched a documentary called deli man what's deli about the New York Jewish
delicate tessence it was wonderful save the day so what it was wonderful it's just people talking
about how thinly sliced their corned beef is it's they interview owners of the most famous deli
to contestants that are still in operation it was wonderful okay it was wonderful a lot of Jerry
stiller interviews about how much he enjoyed the yeah we used to go to Carnegie deli and Sid Caesar would
get behind the counter you know stories like that that's not a real story from it but you know what I mean
well I just put it in my must see pile no I love see I love a deli though because I have class
I like delis joe doesn't mean I want to watch a documentary about them it was wonderful it brought me
great great joy all right uh canters was in there that deli like 45th and 8th or something by letterman
45th and 7th maybe and I ate there with friends when I first moved to New York and they came with a
check and the sandwich was going to be like $24 yeah and I left you walked out now I'd like to go
back and give them that money but I was like I I couldn't have afforded if I wanted to well who who
I was like fuck this and I walked out who paid for it probably does the waiter pay in that situation
you were alone now I was with people but we got split checks so you walked out I said I can't do
this and I left and what'd your friends say afterwards they were like it was pretty expensive and I was
like I'm sorry I can't even afford that if I if I wanted to afford it I was gonna have to wash dishes
like I was in the muppets take fucking man at and back with the rats he paid his dues folks
everything in New York I was like this can't be the price every everywhere I went
coming straight from Missouri I'm uh I'll say to all of you
almost through a full bottle of wine yeah yeah which I don't know if that's a lot
or not it's that should be your intake for the evening usually really but I've done it I've
drank a bottle of wine I watched a movie called Uncle John yeah I keep seeing the
starting John Ashton of Midnight Run fame what year was this movie it brought out
this year it was kind of interesting it was like half that was a like a romantic comedy
and the other half was like did Uncle John kill this guy or not and they keep going back and forth
and you're like how are these connected and they kind of sync up at the end how's John Ashton
it he's great it wasn't an amazing movie I'm a big fan of John it's worth a view I love John Ashton
myself is he funny at all in it price divorced I learned because I looked him up he's not funny
at all in it no because he is a funny guy yeah we got a couple questions here you want to answer him
let's do it did you get a real boner or a fear boner when the sexy lady in the tub became a
rotting corpse real turning into fear I'll say real straight through okay real and then it got harder
and then the other one just says I can't think of any questions okay that's health there well the
unequalized was the boner question I did have to sort of when before the woman turned into a rotting
hag I did have to sort of mentally stunt my potential boner because I was feeling it a little bit
which I always kind of feel sitting next to a hunk of a man sure like Pat Walsh now even out of this
day just simply a naked woman walking on the screen can just pop up a bone zone sometimes
I that definitely when I was a kid I was relentless but nowadays I can usually keep it in check
because of the amount of disgraceful porn that we've been subjected to through the end well yeah yeah
but I I've reduced my masturbation intake to I don't know maybe once a week twice a week I barely do
it anymore so nowadays I get that sort of young kid flare again when I see an attractive woman in a
movie and I'm like oh I'm gonna see your boobs like it's kind of exciting nice I still have that I
just might not spring to attention immediately well because you're a degenerate pervert that's true
whose mind has been just rat just destroyed by filth also true everyone in this scene has used the
N word and we're watching it with subtitles which makes it extra uncomfortable yeah yeah it makes me
a little uncomfortable I'll tell you what else didn't help the Oscar cause and I loved hateful
eight and you know I helped I loved hateful eight what else didn't help the cause was the fact that one
of the white actors to get nominated was Jennifer Jason Lee playing the most racist character in history
yeah yeah and Samuel Jackson I never saw mentioned or discussed as a potential nominee
which I think people just take him for granted at this I agree just a thousand percent because he was
incredible she was very good in the movie but I don't think she deserved a nomination for it
necessarily I got to tell you my money would have been on what's his face the sheriff guy
Kurt Russell no the guy that plays the race of sheriff that becomes Walton Goggins yes yeah
I don't know anything you could have snuck in there if this was Samuel Jackson's first movie he
would have won best actor that's what's kind of fucked up probably was he nominated for public
fiction he was he famously lost to Martin Landau for Ed Wood and in the little box they put the
actors faces in the five little boxes you see Samuel Jackson go shit mother fuck in the box on screen
I don't believe that Joe what do I gain from making that I have seen that we here's why I don't believe
it Google it it's a widely publicized club you don't gain anything but you also believed last week
that I had seen get hard with you which I didn't see and then I remembered who I saw it was my friend
Jared but Jared but you can see this it's one of the most famous moments in Oscar history he's got
the box on him and he says he starts cussing in the box he's really genuinely angry he did probably
deserve to win why you telling me this because now I want to look it up just watch it later I already
told you what happens I'm gonna forget later somebody telling me all you like Samuel Jackson said shit
when he was facing the box I don't need to see it I believe it happened I don't need to watch I don't
believe it I don't believe you I don't believe any of your bullshit I don't fucking believe a thing
you're saying right now man okay I think you're full of shit and I've thought it for a long time
and it feels good to finally say it to you how much longer do we have in this movie
Joe holy god 10 minutes has passed since we last checked I gotta stop doing this I I have a right
to entertain these people now I truly thought we've pledged to entertain them I truly thought about
20 minutes had passed and nine minutes they know why because you're finishing off that one is that
what it is yeah why don't you have another drink because I'm trying to keep myself in control I'm
enjoying a beer sippin it like a gentleman fair enough you're doing wine shots over in the corner I'm
not doing wine shots I've just had a few glasses of wine well what's in what's in the what's in the
news what's going on in the news the hell is the matter with you you excited about suicide squad I am
actually are you no because that guy has only made terrible fucking movies and this will be terrible
to me training day no he didn't he wrote training day wait isn't suicide squad the guy who made oh no
that guy's doing Batman and Superman David Avery wrote training here or air excuse me wrote training
day he directed end of watch he did a watch yeah so the guy who is doing Batman and Superman's axe
Snyder he's the one who makes all the turtle movies except only terrible movies why are they
interesting David I air with this huge franchise I fucking love them to watch I think it's like a sort
of crime thrillery kind of thing and they were like this guys good at that all right no I like then I
like David I'm Zach Snyder you know I enjoyed the dawn of the dead remake I said that is amazing
and then everything else hot trash I don't like watchmen but I think it's a good movie I just
didn't particularly care for it it was terrible but at least it was long what else do you make he made
sucker punch which is one of the worst movies ever made in my opinion I liked man of steel oh why
didn't you like man of steel hated it why just joyless I he made 300 I like 300 all right you didn't
like 300 I didn't like 300 oh boy he just makes like soulless you know movies with nothing to relate
to in them and I hate them all except one of the dead we've gotten zero other questions
why don't you retweet this and see if it helps chill what are they gonna ask questions about the
shining what do they gonna ask but we can answer our own questions like it'd be fun to hear people
from the audience say you have more followers than I do well I know we don't need to bring that up
I mean I don't think they enjoy you as much but you have more followers I do I do but look you have
all those followers on vine so what do you I'm gonna send a vine out somebody just I'm kidding no
I was making fun of vine somebody just asked do you like ice cream Joe that's their question do you
have an answer for that they asked you I mean I like ice cream but do you have an answer about me for
that I would say you like ice cream yeah wrong how little you know me you don't like ice cream I
have a most of the time well I will have an allergic reaction to it because many milk but you like
it I like the flavor of it Pat but I can't eat it all right folks I rest my cast all right
what do you take with all these colors like they're a lot of use of reds like hard orangey
reds in this blood's coming blood's coming what do you take of the blues
uh somebody's gonna blow it you get that from blue well we discuss blue in regards to nightmare
on home street yes blue well that was sleep in nightmare on home street correct yeah what do you
take in this movie I'd have to start watching now looking for blue I have a look at the framing of
that shot is it it's what if this was your house it's insane it looks like the grand Buddha
paste hotel yeah it's insane how perfectly framed the shot is every shot is perfectly framed like that
nuts look at it did you enjoy eyes wide shut uh yeah yeah that's fine I liked AI better
I hated AI and then I watched it recently and loved it I liked AI better and I hated
eyes wide shut because I was expecting a lot more fucking watch it again recently and loved it
what is the I don't even remember what the plot of eyes wide shut is there's not much I mean it's
just a marriage collapsing Tom Cruise goes to a sex party and that's it it's kind of caught up in a
underground world of sexuality okay this wife's like every guy I see I want to fuck let's try to
get a rise out of them just about a marriage falling apart okay and does Kidman ever get banged
outside of the marriage no she talks about wanting to she walks around in a negligee okay
okay so it's it's it's Tom Hanks banging Tom Cruise Tom I know I'm kidding Tom Hanks banging
it'd be funny that alone would be you know in all the movies the Tom Hanks has been and I've seen
him all baby I don't think we've ever seen Tom Hanks have sex unless you can prove me wrong maybe
big when he feels that woman's up I don't want to see Tom Hanks have sex it's no ruin you don't
it's going to ruin Tom Hanks for me it's going to ruin Tom I have a Tom Hanks impression but it's
only visual so I can't really do it on the podcast okay but I have a great Tom Hanks visual impression
can I say it uh yeah but I don't think we should do it right now it's my point all right because
nobody can see it you know what I mean yeah I could do it for you I mean I don't care I'll see
it after see it after she's got very hungry I'm hungry let's say it's 815 it's that time yeah I'm
jealous of the people in this movie that they have this big industrial kitchen well this can't food in
it I would like to eat some of that right now um what do you think about I think I might like
might benefit me to have a pantry like a house with like like that like a kitchen and I am told this is
your food for the entire year right and if you eat it you know at a reasonable rate you gain no
weight you lose no weight by the end of the year this is good for you I think I would kind of love
that why don't you ration it out why don't you and Annie McDow and Kristen Wigg have some sort of
rich people neighborhood meeting yeah where you have a system where this this happens all right I
will we all share a communal thing yeah okay you know sorry the rest of us are out here
living real life I think it's a great idea because you know Wigg and McDowell ain't
much and that leaves more for Papa wait to me looks like she could put it away she's a thin woman
but she looks like she might like to get down with like some pizza or strumboli strumboli I just
strumboli vibe Annie McDowell I picture eating seeds maybe leaves she's finding on the ground now
from the amount that she's walking I worry about her health um but Wigg I think you could pull up and
you know have a beer and some ribs with her probably you know um maybe not strumboli which I don't
think people really actually I eat it what is strumboli it's like a personal pan pizza it's the
better version of the calzone a strumboli is a large dough baked dough product from your pizza places
okay uh and it's you know it's the full dough thing like the dough cover like a calzone is there dough
in it but it's large and it's filled with stuff okay so you get a cheese steak one or an Italian
meats one or a pepperoni and cheese or a meatballs sure and they're delectable they're delicious the
calzone will have the calzone always has regatta cheese plus mozzarella and and whatever and it's a
personal size thing strumboli is for multiple people and it doesn't ever go to cheese it's always
mozzarella and meats and it is delicious folks I am sorry why I'm sorry you had to listen to all that
well what was wrong with that it was fine it was fine what was you asked for the strumboli was it
was fine uh well then why did you say that Kristen Wigg this year also not mentioned in the acting
races was amazing in a movie that is also now enough looks called welcome to me which I loved
okay she plays a very mentally disturbed woman who wins the lottery and decides she's gonna make a
talk show starring herself okay to bring herself fame and I fucking loved it I saw when
as in theaters not one person has mentioned it to me not one person mentioned it for Oscars
that's what that's why this business is so fuck people like racism obviously is a major problem
but they send you they send people who are in the academy screeners of the movies that are coming out
and if a movie does not get sent to people's houses it has zero chance of being nominated sure never
once has a movie or a performance or a screenplay been nominated for an Oscar that I wasn't sent at my
home as a member of the writers guild and the actress guild of America and you will get movies that
don't get nominated for instance pat and I both received this year furious seven I received two copies
of furious uh and not mad Max and I gotta say yeah I love mad Max it was the most fun movie I saw
a year next to Star Wars I don't think it deserves a best picture nomination in this year I do
think it does I don't know what I what else I would put above it this year was a terrible year for movies
when I'm looking at this giant stack of movies that I was sent for my consideration I'm like most
of these fucking suck oh there are other ones are okay there are other movies that could have been
nominated yeah for sure our go that was three years an award and at one best picture
national treasure I was disappointed to see didn't make that that was 12 years ago and was not
nominated the breakup which people write off as just a comedy but I think has a lot of emotional value
you think these movies all come out this year I believe all movies come out every year okay every year
again and again uh movies are never finished they're just abandoned here's a movie I love that
should have gotten a little love uh sleeping with other people starring Jason Sudegas and Allison
Brie I thought that movie looked terrible I did too but I didn't and yet it was great and I bet you'd
love it and folks I heard that's my if you take away one thing this week watch that movie it's great
Pat Walsh if you haven't noticed is a big fan of uh he wants to see a lot of the SNL movies get
nominated I remember when ladies man came out and uh looked was looked over he was very angry
same not as man as terrible so the other people is the rock SNL movie the rock spary he was real mad
about that one you mean because today this isn't it that makes it an SNL movie it's an essence based on
that sketchy used to do so as welcome to me these are all based the fuck are you talking I'm doing a
guy that thinks all SNL characters or actors do SNL movies based on sketches that's fine
well who's not yes -ending now I said that's fine no that's not a yes -and that's what's called a dead -and
yes and my favorite of those SNL movies was probably dream girls my favorite SNL movie is wired
did you see wired I tried watching it it's starring Michael Chickles as John Bullys
it's terrible did you read wire you mean the movie where uh John Bullys she's corpse wakes up
and goes and relives his life at the be uh it's terrible oh they do it like screwdriver he wakes
up in the morgan leaves and it's like what am I doing here and escapes I want to watch him
and goes and like re -witnesses his life or whatever I want to see like who plays acroix who plays
all these people Dan Acroid uh was played by uh we talked about her earlier Glenn close
very odd choice I always thought Glenn close should play George Washington that's an uh and it's
always sunny in Philadelphia it is I uh here we go here we go who who in this room that wrote for
that show wrote that show all right there's not where I was going with it but Glenn close looks
exactly like one of our founding fathers and you know it hey everybody in case you didn't know
pat wrote for it's always sunny in Philadelphia some of his jokes made it on the air
that was one of them I was in a video study day that was going out of business and selling off all
there was of course it was selling off their complete inventory where was it uh Santa Monica
Boulevard it's called video hut Santa Monica and what and why on earth would you not tell me
because I asked you to hang out all weekend and all weekend you kept talking about like I'm too dizzy to
hang yeah I have vertigo I can't try again uh I went over I bought uh five they were doing five for
20s oh that's actually not that kind of deal I got some movies for going at a business one movie
take one movie I almost bought because I only went in to get horror movies right one movie I almost
bought that I did not buy a movie called mothman written by Pat Walsh they had a DVD copy they have a DVD
copy that might not have been ours it was your name is on the back of the box I looked at it oh well
thanks for picking it up Joe you didn't think I'd want it they didn't even send me a copy I figured I
could just buy it off of Amazon if I ever really wanted it it's terrible you well that's what you've
told me and I was like I don't know if this is worth owning just because my friend co -wrote it
well I would like to go I bought a lot in the great Hollywood video close out of about three four
years ago maybe more something tells me mothman will still be there out there you I didn't know they
did a release of it because contractually I am supposed to get a DVD copy of it and I did not
receive well it's on DVD and I looked it up on the internet to make sure I could buy it elsewhere if
I ever wanted to because I didn't want to waste one of my fives on it thanks Joe well because you
tell me it's terrible truth be told you just watch it to be like this is ironically funny truth be told
I wrote a terrific horror comedy version of it that was not shot the version that was shot is
perfectly fine by sci -fi channel movie standards it just doesn't take into account any of the cool
shit that was written for it yeah well that's part of why I didn't buy it I was like this isn't Pat's
work no this is the work of some suits yeah
liked of my life I just jumped in on the on the line to let people know we're still watching the movie
yeah you're not I'm gonna announce that you've you've killed this bottle I haven't killed it
there the remainder of the the remainder of the bottle is in the glass okay why are you being so
judgy I'm not being whenever you drink you accuse me of being judgy I'm not being judgy I drink myself
and I'm not being judgy okay it feels a little judgy right now if we have this conversation every time
every time I drink yeah that seems judgy you saying that all right I want to eat another beer buddy
I'm drinking a beer it's you're nursing it come on man you're making me feel bad folks I have work
tomorrow yeah you said you wanted to go to a bar after this and you said you would do it
this is the alcoholic mentality folks Joe says we should go to a bar after this then an hour later it's
you said you wanted to go to a bar because I said we should do that and you said yeah let's do it folks
I kind of don't want to anymore anyway we don't care when we could get it by tea I'm getting tired
from the we can say all the things we want to say that we can't say on this month there's a great
taco truck at the end of my street we could walk down to that sounds great I also have leftover KFC
in the fridge you how often are you getting KFC I go about once a month how's your cholesterol I have
no idea and I don't give a shit once a month you're fine I'm assuming it's fine I'm in decent weight
what do you get a you get a 10 piece today I got the eight piece bucket plus two large sides
mashed potatoes and gravy and coleslaw of course and I ate four pieces and some sides for lunch
got and I thought even if I eat the other half for dinner that's meals for the whole day that's
I actually have done the calorie calculations of a bucket of KFC yeah it's way less than you think
it's like 15 calories or so at the end of the day you're eating chicken and then you got some
fried bread shit on it and like it'll it'll be about two thousand calories what all said and done
which is what you're supposed to eat I cut it in care when I lived in New York I would get
Popeyes on a Saturday for a hangover but I haven't had fried chicken like I love it I haven't had
done a very long time KFC is the best fried chicken on planet earth in my opinion the
the uh what do you make about them not using chicken they use like gelatinous orbs that they
farm insane it's retardedly wrong it's not a thing you're not supposed to say that we're wrong I'm
sorry it's retardly incorrect it's no it's it's come on it's crazy it's like it's chicken it's
fucking chicken all right gelatinous orbs that's what they say they farm out like things that
aren't a lot ever like they're I don't know there was apparently a 60 minutes about it I didn't see it
and what did 60 minutes say that that's true that that's where this report came to be what do you
think is Chinese food like when you get orange chicken here we go with the racism now that's nothing
here we go with the racism I asked you to keep it off this podcast I'm saying when you bite into a
piece of orange chicken it's not chicken yes it is it's a piece of chicken then why does it not look
or taste anything like any other piece of chicken it's it's a chunk of chicken that they roll in a
batter and fry what the hell do you think it is I don't know that's why I'm asking but any sort of
Chinese food does not look or taste anything like chicken it's delicious here's what I can't wait
for when I when I in tomorrow when I say I'm posting the podcast and you say please send it to me I'm
worried about the Chinese chicken remarks I made but I'm not at all worried about it you never are
during the podcast you didn't hear me say is it dog or cat that's kind of what you're insinuating
which is like the oldest of racist thing I'm saying what is it because it's not chicken and I've
always wondered it is chicken pet okay it's chicken deep fried in so much batter that you can't tell
it's chicken anymore all right it doesn't have the texture or taste or appearance of chicken general
sounds chicken to me always tastes like chicken except fried sounds a little different an orange chicken
is more like a bread it's heavy breading on very little meat I'll give you that all right but it's
still tastes like chicken to me all right anything else any other about it next races you want to dissect
in one fell swoop I stand probably by this is not being even remotely racist anything that I've said
is not even remotely race talk about Indian food now what is that a ravi I like Indian food and I like
Chinese I don't like Indian food I love Chinese food I hate Indian food I'll just say it they're
saying that Indian food now is like the official cuisine of London because London has no
aside from like bangers and mash seems like the worst food I'm playing a fucking fish on chips when I
went to London I was like I I definitely lost weight I was walking a ton and I was like I'm not
excited to eat any of this and anytime I ask anybody to recommend a restaurant they would recommend
Indian food it's not like going to Italy I don't like it it's all in that it's on that thick gravy I
don't care for it and there's a lot of like is it ginger flavor well Indian food is like a curry a
tikka masala tikka masala that sounds Italian does folks I think we might be getting a little preview
of John drunk history right now yeah no it does tikka masala yeah it does say another Indian
cuisine I'll do it Italian this is not questionable in any way for you racially but me suggesting
that orange chicken might be something other than chicken is race well what else do you think it is Pat
I don't know I'm just curious what no you you have an idea in your head clearly you're going
somewhere I have no idea and I order it so obviously I don't think it's dog or cat well what do you
think I'm just wondering what is happening pork maybe why would it be pork if it wouldn't it chicken
cheaper than pork I have no idea I really don't all I know is like you get a grilled chicken it looks
entased one way you get a fried chicken it looks entased like grilled chicken that's fried gentleman
for the Chinese food for for you don't know what that is for the critics of my wine intake on this
podcast Pat Walsh just pulled a beer out of the pocket of his army jacket so I didn't have to get
out so he didn't have to get up again John Rambo style this is my third of the evening this is my
third glass of wine you only get three out of a bottle folks get four out of a bottle all right that's
why you get a bottle of wine for a couple when you go out on a nice 10 so I'm on my fourth I'm fine
barely a glass ahead of you you've been demanding that I drink faster than I get a beer out I'd like
you to criticize me faster please drink faster is it so much that I want to drag you down to what I am
to what there is no in Pat it goes on and on it's a cycle of pain more questions from the fans on
Twitter I tell you what I love is some of those nila wafers the best cookie of all time this guy just
said give me a shout out on the podcast that's fine shout outs to jacko his handle is what
underscore is underscore riso yeah I don't know what riso is I would not have given him that channel
contribute something ask a question then we'll give you your shout out our friend barn wood
b -a -r -n -w -o -u -l -d barn wood said you belong in the east coast Joe oh these are very me centric tweets
which I don't mind are you getting anything over there no check here neighbors I hear neighbors
walking by I've the thinnest windows in my new apartment the thinnest windows and as Pat has heard
apparently my upstairs neighbors are rolling around back and forth on the floor or something what
what have they been doing up there he might be a noise that he can hear us giving a full
podcast you know who knows a full commentary on the shiny so this girl Samantha Shambley
she's all excited oh my god oh my god why can't I remember all my questions yeah that's I read
that one already Samantha we want to hear your questions well I love that you have Garfield you got
anything else or is that it on your Twitter page I'm a big fan of Garfield I used to laugh so
fucking hard at Garfield what was it that you like the lasagna it was just the high jinx between him and
the dog it was generally his disgust with John and John's loneliness his the lasagna the naps the
hating of Mondays is a smile at best but when he'd really lay into somebody I would laugh out loud I
used to love Garfield and friends and then the spin -off Hampton and friends who's Hampton it was a
pig on a barn they used it to pat out an episode of Garfield because Garfield didn't go in any adventures
really well one thing I did oh yeah Hampton friends I remember that now like to one thing I did
enjoy about Garfield it really was the personality of a fat man that loathed the world yeah you know
and just really demeaning towards the intelligence of that dog yeah well dog was stoked to talk yeah
it was almost like he was he was prejudice towards mentally handicapped people or something
pretty hardcore stuff when you think about it there was also heathcliff which is just worthless I hated
heathcliff terrible heathcliff would always do the thing which is one of my favorite comedy trips which
is put a whole fish in your mouth and come out which is the skill yeah another question over here
is it a true crew brick is it true that Kubrick insisted on real blood coming out of the elevator no
well I don't know is it true that can't be true right that is from Dave 5545 I mean maybe are they
talking about like animal blood I think I have heard that rumor before all right I think there's
supposed to be an amazing shining documentary I've seen the documentary that comes with the Kubrick
box set I've seen that one too it goes into the shining they don't mention anything about that the
one where it's like him playing the music yeah he's yelling at Shelley do you have all the whole time
yeah yeah well Shelley did all despised him apparently that's pretty intense well there's the argument
of he hated her or that's what he needed to do to get the performance yeah I mean he he brought her
to like the brink of sanity which she hated about him this is like that error filmmaking where they're
like he couldn't get the take so he went up and kicked him in the balls yeah and then he got it baby you
know like now you couldn't do anything like that at all yeah because everybody's a pussy I just
read it article about vinyl the Morons Corsese show and they talked about how Olivia wild and one
takes spat water in Bobby can of all his face and they talked about this in the article like 25 times
like it just brought this wrongness out of the performance they were so blown away by it
there would be a very minor thing and I'll also tell you this can of all it spat some water in
wild space and it was discussed can of all would be thrown out of Hollywood thrown out of Hollywood
you can't you can't spit in a woman's face in a film set or in life or should you I'm just saying
it was odd that it was discussed so often now this is a topic rarely do we get political in this podcast
but the pan has been lobbying for this for years they'll the right for to spit water in a woman's
face I've never spat anything in anybody's face I'm just saying they talked about it like it was a return
to the roots of cinema and I was like I wonder if Bobby can of all had spat in Olivia wild space how
that would have gone down oh BC did you go out for the Ray Romano role in vinyl I have no idea I
auditioned for it I didn't get it I think you probably went out for the Ray Romano role I went out for a
role of a really arrogant record executive that insults a lot of people it's probably Romano they talked
about the scores as you're seeing as addition to being like who is this guy he's fantastic they're like
you don't know who Ray Romano is he's like no clue who is it and that's how I got another question
here this one comes from Mitch Oliver 14 M -I -T -C -H -O -L -I -V -E -R -1 -4 who would you rather take to the
prom Betty or Veronica or Jughead Mr. Willoughby we got here from Rob Larrick at R -L -A -U -R -I -C -H
Rob writes in quite frequently actually yeah is it me or do the twins look like the byproduct
of an incestuous oompa lumpo relationship there is a bit of a strange look to I will say this
when when we saw them in person they looked like completely normal people they do look a little
hotter in this movie as kids so I wonder if it was a makeup thing or not what do you think I think
it was just them they they were intriguing looking women I thought another one from Mitch Oliver 14
when the hell is the Jeepers Creepers episode coming I mean Jesus Christ show get on my level I hate the
movie I think me loving it and you hating it would lead to a great show it's not on Netflix currently
and we're unfortunately locked to Netflix because of this TV setup situation I have in my new
apartment so we will get to it eventually recorded one over in my place because then I would
have to bring all the equipment over to your place do you understand how this works pet you really
don't do you you just throw things in the sand yeah you think you just come in and you just sit down
and talk and it's just a you have no idea the work that goes into this do you I know the work Joe
do you know the work I know the work but do you appreciate the work appreciate the work
where's your pocket be I saw Danny Collins I loved it so much yeah it was a very good film
all speaking of Bobby can of all I loved it speaking of a man who has fake hair by the way Bobby can of all
I truly truly love the film yeah it was a good film I liked it quite a bit yeah it was completely
slept on it was great I believe Pacino deserved an Oscar for it I think he was nominated not an Oscar
but I think he was nominated for best actor any comedy at the Golden Globes which he lost
he lost to Matt Damon in the Martian yeah exactly that hilarious picture of the Martian right
Danny Collins isn't funny either but it's it's a technical comedy as opposed to the Martian
it's got funny parts it's a dramedy but it's really good I it's uh I think Pacino just can't
bring in any audiences anymore but I it's a kind of amazing it wasn't a hit because it's just a straight
up the middle very likable movie yeah no he's he's great at it he's great at it
Correll Steve Correll was originally cast in the Bobby can of allie role and then the movie would have
done better but he had to drop out Pacino said you got to I wouldn't have bought it with Steve Correll
yeah you don't buy Correll as Pacino can of allie you buy as Pacino's son Pacino insisted on
can of allie once Correll dropped out I love can of allie I was once in a bar with him my good friend
Seth Herzog was talking to him because I guess they're pals and I remember looking across the room
and thinking oh that's the guy from the station agent is before he was kind of famous yeah he was in a
I think in a play I saw called take me out I may have told the story before but I take me out was
it based on that song this is based on the France for news yeah okay no I used to I didn't have
a cell phone I first moved to New York and if I had a date I would have to be like meet me at this
intersection and you have to just meet me there at this time or we won't hang out so I used to go in
and try to get student tickets to Broadway shows to take a date so I would get in there two hours ahead
of time right trying this is your this is your inside the actor studio right talk so I was like if I don't
find tickets here for 20 bucks I can't bring this girl to anything so I don't know what I'm gonna do
so I finally get tickets that the Pulitzer Prize winning play take me out so I meet her and I'm like
hey I got a ticket it's Pulitzer Prize winning play it's supposed to be amazing and she's like oh great
we sit in the front row I keep talking it up like because I can tell she's not excited I'm like
it's supposed to be so good I'm so excited to see this the first thing that happens the curtain
opens and there's a bar at the top of the stage with water coming out of it then I realized it's
a locker room scene take me out it's about a gay baseball player who has to come out like to his
team mates I get to take me out to the ball game but also take me out of the closet it starts by
some penis and cracker jacks yeah exactly outcomes 12 full frontly nude men they stand above me
because we're in the front row which is what these $20 tickets are you thought all my dreams have come
true looking up into the taint balls and dicks of 12 men with this girl and I've been telling her
again and again this show's gonna be so great you're gonna love this show and she looks so red face
and mortified it was a really pretty traumatic event and who who does Bobby canna Valley play I'm pretty
sure he was in it he was one of the guys in it I might even be wrong about that I know Daniel Daniel
soon Jota was in it who was in rescue me but just looking up at a lot of dicks and it was very
uncomfortable and we did not take the relationship past that point I mean I don't understand what the problem is
it's like taxi driver I'm taking civil shepherd to a porno theater I'm like it's nice to meet you
now let's go sit in the front row looking up at a bunch of guys that bad I think it didn't go well I
think she's a square man she was a square definitely but she didn't like it hey jack I think she's a
square I think the girl that I would like to continue hanging out with would have been like this is a
hilarious right thing to happen it would have understood that you wanted to crop on that stage and put
those dicks in your mouth yeah one after the other right right one after the next like you were
sampling frozen yogurt yeah yeah exactly yeah I mean she just doesn't get you dude no all right
fair enough it happens uh scatman crothers is about to die by the way I mean again this is really the
only big jump scare in this moment perfectly frame shot he's walking between these pillars it's
perfectly framed Nicholson is about to come out and hit him in the stomach with an axe and also like
okay so this is a perfect like jump scare in this movie this has really never been replicated in
horror movies either like they're not ripping off this they're ripping off insidious or whatever
the fuck you know insidious is great I know you love insidious jump it's fine but ripping off what you
mean like a guy jumping out with an axe like where it's just a long steady shot and you actually see
the guy walk into frame and stuff you don't see that really in horror movies sure you see a quick
jump cut jump cut jump cut sure somebody opens a window and there's somebody standing behind them sure
flash a lightning now here's my question to you obviously this movie is about this character that
Nicholson plays going mad and wanted to murder his family because of the spirits in the hotel
do you think that this would happen to any old guy do you think in a different situation this guy
wouldn't have tried to eventually murder his family or do you think it was this was all meant to be
I see the movie a little bit more as a metaphor for alcoholism and people doing things they
would never ordinarily do okay I don't even necessarily buy the whole spirit element of it so I
think they're they're telling you that this guy left to his own devices drinking career not going
how he wants it to go is turning against everyone in his path I think he didn't want this family I
didn't want to why didn't want to wife didn't want a family that bear suit is so disturbing it is
I see that a lot online now it's like a meme the bear blowing the old man blowing the old man who
doesn't have his pants down by the way he should have his pants down doesn't have his pants down and
the bear couldn't be blowing him because there's a bear mask true so what was he doing nozzling his nuts
I think it was maybe maybe it was a time before you could show man blowing another man I don't know
but it's I think cruising starring a young alpacino came out around this time and was there a blowjob
scene there's fisting in cruising fisting I think it might have been between two cruising is alpacino from
William freaking who did the exercise yeah alpacino goes undercover in the gaysine and then becomes
it's up to the viewer whether or not he becomes gay himself but there's so much gay sex club action
fisting and all that who gets fisting extras in the background does Pacino do any hardcore sex
no but he's around it and he's clearly very conflicted by it okay a couple years back James
Franco did like recreations of scenes from cruising as like a movie because he's into those art pieces
not as a joke to like yeah like as a statement you mean yeah I don't know what the hell that was all
about okay if everything James Franco did it was the thing where he did the acting lessons
on funny or die didn't see him and he tries to get his younger brother to day Frank
day Frank going to play a scene from rebel without a cause as the as having a crush on him which
I always thought was very funny on his brother huh on his brother yeah yeah yeah we're in the tail
stretch of the film here Jack Nicholson is now chasing young Danny around in the snow I'm honestly
so angry that I'm not in New York to experience this blizzard why because I get so fucking sick of the
weather being the same here no one wants to hear you can plan about that I'm telling you something man
you I missed the snow 10 minutes into that blizzard you'd be like fuck this no I love it and
everywhere I go home for Christmas and I want snow and it's you love it when the snow is falling
tomorrow we still can't get anywhere and it's all grace ludge I always loved the snow and when I was
in New York and they canceled the subways and I had to walk to work I fucking love the snow
I love it that's something different it's something fucking I think that's idiotic
it's just differences of human beings I just think I'm saying what I'm saying is is is is a light
snowfall is very nice this kind of snowfall where you're trapped I don't think you'd want that no I
was essentially trapped all weekend I enjoyed it I watched a lot of movies seat now she sees the ghost
so there is a thing to the spirits sure or is she saying the true nature of her husband oh god
we don't know I think it's obviously a fucked up hotel I think they put drove them over the edge
fair enough it's a haunted hotel but I think really it's supposed to be seen as a metaphor for
now is this this sequence here where they're running through the snow the maze whatever yeah
is are they truly outside in the snow or is that a set I would imagine everything in this movie is a
time I feel like they're really outside I feel like in the documentary you see that they're really
outside in the snow okay I think like I know all of the Vietnam shit and full metal jacket is in
London like I think he so liked controlling his environment that he made sets anything you want
remember that part I assume that's a Asian press too that's the looker where they sample me so
horny oh yeah she was all me so horny anything you want 10 dollars time yeah and then they sample
it and me so horny oh me so honey you're too live crew fan yeah I find some of this stuff outrageously
funny do you think there'll be a too live crew straight out of comps them yeah I think that's the
follow -up bring that TV back is the yeah there you go that's a mad TV sketch you're absolutely right I
think easy you should have been nominated this year the guy that played easy yeah of course I agree too
he was fantastic I agree I thought F. Gary Gray should have been nominated F. Gary Gray will never
get the respect he deserves how frequently is a best picture nominated where there's not the director
also nominated it's it never happens almost never well when you're nominating only five directors but
up to 10 movies stupid they also that's what's weird too is they could have had two more slots they could
have had one for shredded accountant but it didn't get the votes apparently so what are you going
to do so it's it's not the same number every year no maybe not even five years ago they decided instead
of five best picture nominees it could be up to 10 right which I think is kind of weird but it was
done after the dark night because they thought like maybe if we start letting in some more commercial
movies it's up to 10 but not people will watch it but not 10 right no you can be 10 but I think
it doesn't have to be 10 no I think they have to get a set number of votes that apparently
straight out of Compton didn't get patty here you go here's a question for you another one from Rob
Larrick I recall a shining reference on it's always sunny seven or eight years ago did you write that
there was a very heavy one flow of the kukus nest episode when I was there yes I remember that
but I don't remember what he's talking about with the shining it's possible I don't think I wrote it
maybe it was empty left yeah maybe I remember when I was there they did that very heavy kukus nest
episode with Davido I love that episode yeah that's a really great I think I'm in that I am in that
episode who do you play in it I play the comedy club mc oh that's the same episode pretty sure yeah
now the comedy club episode isn't that the episode where Dennis goes into the insane asylum that's
why I'm thinking it's the same one no the other one is the other one the kukus nest one is Davido ends
up somewhere at the end and it's suddenly kukus nest it's not the same episode okay all right I just
watched season 10 on Netflix I think each episode of this podcast you have said I just watched season 10
of always sunny on Netflix that's not true it's can't can't be true because I just did it okay maybe the
last episode I said it you know you're real you're real you're real prick tonight I'm not a real
I don't mind saying it because I'll let these people know what the real real real relationship between us
is I think I think they know when is this movie going to head Pat I have to pee so bad right now I'm
going to pee between your legs ooh baby do we have one bathroom in this place yeah okay that's fun
no I'm just wondering because I also really have to pay well we can cross streams I don't care
I was in a bar last night buddy Brooks and I said let's cross streams and you got kind of weird
about it weird like let's do it or weird like weird like why I don't want to and then I was a little
tipsy and I was like why not who cares then and that makes me look more suspiciously trying to get
him into the bathroom well you did once try to pee on a tree in front of my girlfriend a lot of her
female friends and I thought that was odd when was this we walked away when did this have an
exhibition a streak when did this happen about a year ago where Georgia Vince the whole gang where
where were we it wasn't assaultive we all just took a step away I know it wasn't assaultive where did
it happen though on a on a public tree on a street I think it was outside of Kumail's party perhaps
it was just kind of like well this is happening we all have to walk away you were trying to
perhaps holler at one of Heather's friends I said this maybe why she's not enchanted with you
because you peed on a tree I was not trying to holler in 30 minutes after meeting I just come on man
sometimes you got a pee I know I know wouldn't you like to pee there are some night especially when I'm
taking the trash out at home I'm like I would love to just pee on the side of my house and mark the
fucking territory back when I had a front yard I love peeing outside I'd go outside and be like I could
just pee right here you can you really can yeah I mean you know I don't find it offensive but that's
just me that's in certain states it's it's it's a sex crime and I think in all states it's a sex crime
no not in all states that's not true but if you pee in public and get arrested for it in like
Texas you have to like you have to register as a sex offender is that nuts I actually think that's
truly answer it's it's crazy Steven Avery by the way has a lot of like shaking his dick at people
crimes on his repertoire who Steven Avery who's Steven Avery shall we discuss Steven Avery for the
middle hour of this pot Roger Avery I thought Roger Roger Avery co -wrote pulp fiction oh Steven Avery
the director of suicide squad oh well that's David I air it's Roger Avery directed killing Zoe
and he co -wrote pulp fiction Steven Avery is the man who was on trial for murder that we've
oh yes yes making a murderer sorry I got a little we're wrapping this up just in time I got a
little confused I'm sorry I got a little I think you'll see my face in this photo if you look closely
enough thanks so yeah he does have a lot of sex crimes that aren't pissed involved but they're
they're also not like rape they're just like it's I jerked off on my cousin's car thing
you ran yeah he ran at his cousin with his dick out and jacked him on her car in this
conversation nuts what do you take of this closing shot where you see Nicholson in the I love the whole
I celebrate the entire film I'm not saying I don't pat I'm asking what you take of this shot where
he's finally in this picture do you think this hotel absorbs people and then makes them a part of
their history do you think that a ghost from the past spoke to him I'm asking your interpretation of
it I because he wasn't in the picture at the beginning correct well yeah I would assume so yeah I
take it that the hotel just like makes you a part of it I guess you know all right yeah folks we
watch the shining for you that's the last time we'll be watching a movie of this length that was
insane if you're still listening thank you so much you're a true fan of the show this was you
can follow Joe DeRosa comedy on Twitter you can follow that's my Twitter that's not Pat's don't get
confused mine is Joe DeRosa comedy mine is the Patrick Walsh Twitter violence to Graham yes and
for those of you in San Diego as they say it in the anchor man films I will be at the American comedy
club the first week in a February the I think it's the fourth and fifth right for four shows come
out come out to a show let's hang out you can also hear me on Ali and Georgia Ali Ward and Georgia
hardstarks podcast which just came out and you can also hear me twice on the best of you made it
weird Pete home podcast telling two different stories now you're just all over everything these days
aren't you and soon my second appearance on drug history and well I also will be doing the
can I kick it show with Al Jackson and tone bell as we do at the riot LA comedy festival this Saturday
January 30th at 3 p .m. special guest Moshe cashier so anyway we'll see you soon folks you've been
listening to we'll see when hello presentation of the fangoria podcast network produced by Thomas
DeFail and executive produced by Ken Hanley of fangoria entertainment for press opportunities
advertising inquiries and information about we'll see when he'll contact Ken at fangoria .com thank
you thanks folks