Summer is here, and Bed MGM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MGM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Waiter, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only, games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal, durable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees and here's another, no other sportsbook has
an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fancash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fancash,
guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook, winning hits different here.
Monthly 21 -plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberer, offer not available in all states,
term -supply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
Howdy folks, welcome to We'll see you in hell.
This is the podcast where you get your information about horror and sci -fi and fantasy films.
Sometimes it's a review, sometimes it's a commentary, sometimes it's a little bit of both.
And today it's a review, a review of a little film called The Nightmare Before Christmas.
And here we are, Joe Perchett, Patwixth, Halloween and Christmas, which I feel is the perfect time to watch this film.
I agree. Joe and I saw it at the Hollywood Bowl. We left before the ending, and I didn't realize it until the next day, but it was the highest I've been in years.
And we got real drunk, too. So my memories of the evening are shady, but I know the movie quite well.
Well, what did we do after the, you and I went to the board nurse prior?
That I remember.
After I think it was just a directly home, wasn't it?
Or was that when we went and got that pasta at that Italian place?
Was it that night?
No, that's when we saw Halloween.
Oh, okay.
Which we're talking about on the Patreon and we'll be released shortly this month.
Yeah, that's the bonus up this month. The uh, what the fuck was the I?
Don't think we went straight home. I think we did
I don't think we did we walked out we got a lift and we were out the door. I
Know this home early. Maybe you went out
Maybe you had some Odyssey. You never know what me, man
It can always down by the train tracks
Yeah, I'll go down there, cruising. I call it cruising for hobos.
Sure. Sometimes they're down there, and I'll say, hey, is that a handkerchief tied
to a stick in your pocket or are you just happy to see me?
A bindle, they call it.
Yeah, that usually works. Yeah.
Maybe ride the trains up and down with them.
Right
We're here. We are again seeing each other for our hour a week
shameful. Oh, I don't understand why you can't now. I just asked Pat to hang out
Pat asked me to hang out. I said I got a show at eight
Then he said I wanted to hang out I said won't you come to my show with me and then he goes I got to go home
Which feels like him saying I don't want to go to your show. No, I said instead of doing the pod tonight
night. Do you want to go to the roost and have a good time? I was like walkable to
the roost. Joe said, I got a show at eight. I'm like, all right, call my lovely wife.
I say, yeah, let's stay in and watch a movie. I get here. Joe says, hey, you want to go to my
show? I say, no, I'm going to fucking move with my wife. What do you mean? It's reasonable
to a movie or probably just watch something. Yeah. The screeners are coming in real slow
this year. I've received three the WGA screeners. I got a quiet place. The wife, which
which I discussed on the live pod.
I don't think anything else.
I got to quiet place twice.
Yeah.
And I'm in three unions and I'm not getting any screener.
I keep every day I get four letters telling me
where I can go see something.
Right.
For free.
Oh, bite me.
I used to do it all the time and now I'm just like,
fuck off.
Send it to my home.
That's where I'm at.
Also, too, this bullshit of, you know,
Netflix and Amazon Prime will send me these like I'll get like a box of I got a box from Netflix the other day
It was like five movies. Yeah, I had the same thing. I have Netflix
What do you want me to do with you got Netflix pictures? Yeah, I didn't get that. I got Amazon Prime shows
There's one Amazon Prime show. It's called forever Fred Armason and Maya Rudolph
I ain't saying this thing.
Is it good?
Are you ever seen any of it?
But all the reviews, I read a hundred of views
and they were like,
due to a request by the creators,
we're not allowed to discuss the show.
Excuse me?
Then finally, once people started reviewing it,
it's like, yeah, it's really pretty unwatchable,
but episode six is the best episode
of the television this year.
So it's worth sticking out to get to sick fuck yourself. Yeah, I know shows improve over time
But if it's unwatchably bad and then one is the best what are you talking about?
I hate that shit. The commercials for that show annoy me. It looks very annoying
I haven't seen the picture looks very pretentious, you know
Another one of these things with the couple that stuck in the pattern
and holding pattern, and who cares?
I don't give a shit about anything anymore.
No, I'm getting to like, you know, like a rigs
in lethal weapon kind of vibe.
Like if somebody put a gun in my face,
I'd stick it in my mouth and bite down, you know?
I don't wanna get too dark here at the top.
But just don't care.
Would you just bite down or would you sensuously suck it?
I guess it depends on my mood. Yeah, you know, but yeah, I mean, I woke up today. I
Open I usually as always on Saturday morning. I have a tremendous amount of work to do. I got to get a script out and
I always open the door to my deck
Sit out have a nice breath. So I go
So breathe in like a mouth full of like physical ash
like tasteable, a gritty in my teeth ash.
Yeah, it's, it's bad.
Oh, yes, lie for it a little bit.
Well, why do you have this chair pushed up against a?
Well, it wasn't pushed up against it.
You sort of flopped down and I just had a,
say shoved it backwards.
Now I'm kidding.
It's, yeah, that's where it's supposed to be.
I had a few people over last night.
You know, these kids get wise.
They move the chair around as a joke.
It's funny.
Sure.
Yeah, but the city's under siege.
It's horrific.
These fires are incredible
that I don't mean that in a good way, obviously.
Like it's pretty mind blowing.
And the winds now are coming tomorrow.
So I assume that's going to really blow the bad air,
not only blow the bad air down into the city more,
But also it's potentially going to start the fires up again. Yeah, my cat went out and was like
Came in like eyes caked wow like for I mean, it's it's bad
I am facing kind of the the mountains and shit our Griffith Park
but
It's really bad and I don't know if you saw
Our president's tweet this morning, but he he believes it's the state of California's fault
And actually plans on punishing us for having fires, which I think is pretty cool.
The guy just can't say the right thing, he ain't even trying.
You see, this weekend he is talking to, in 2018, he is talking to a black female reporter.
She asks a very reasonable question, he goes, you are so stupid, that is such a stupid question.
You was so stupid.
And he's like, I watch your show,
not the first stupid question from you.
You was so stupid.
At least it's an equal opportunity offender.
Sure.
The accost of thing, you saw that, I assume,
releasing just completely altered footage
from the White House.
You didn't hear about this?
No, what's the accost of thing?
Jim accost is a CNN reporter.
He's asking Trump questions.
Oh, the reporter, I thought you were talking about
the lawyer that's not a cost. No, sorry. Good. This young female intern by Trump's like snapping like
get his mic, you know, really. Yeah, I saw that part. And she goes over and really it kind of
aggressively tries to grab it. And he's like, excuse me, miss. And he puts his other hand on the microphone.
He's like, miss, I'm trying to just ask a question. Excuse me. The White House tweeted out by
by what's her face, Sarah Huckabee Sanders, tweets out a doctored video put out by like
info wars Alex Jones's site where it's sped up there's like a almost like a fake hand
feel to it where he karate chops her arm and the press secretary of the United States releases
a ten tweet thing like the White House will never tolerate violence on women and everyone
One is even people like, you know, you're die hard,
Maga people are like, okay, we all know
that this is heavily doctored, like come on.
Yeah, we're getting into a real weird area.
Yeah, and then you got Antifa going to Tucker Carlson's house.
Queen Antifa?
Queen Antifa, yeah.
I actually did not hear about this story.
They weren't officially called Antifa.
that was an antifa -esque type of group.
They found out where Tucker Carlson from Fox News lived,
went to his house, spray painted on his driveway,
chanted as a mob, racist.
You're not welcome, get out.
His wife was home alone, she was so scared,
she hit in a cupboard.
She was like, I thought it was a home invasion.
I didn't know what was going on.
This world's losing its fucking mind.
Look, I had a spy, Tucker Carlson,
but I don't think the man's wife deserves
to be holding up in a cupboard.
I also don't think you're allowed to you people it is beyond my comprehension that people think because I don't like you
It means I can come to your house right and do mob shit. That's lynch mob shit, dude. That's fucking crazy
Yeah, it's crazy. Is anything gonna be done?
In a court of law anymore at all
It's just you know, it's just
Just everybody is losing their fucking mind.
Everybody's acting out of spite.
You got Trump being a dick with the CNN guy, and then Antifa, and then the Antifa will
go, well, now we're going to go to Tucker Carlson's house and scream at his wife in the
house.
You know, it's like, everybody is acting out of fucking spite.
Everybody.
It's fucking madness.
This is becoming, you know, this is becoming, this is becoming what's it called?
The, uh, the, uh, the, uh, Israeli, uh, conflict about the Gaza Strip, okay.
This is like the conflict over there where it's this, I should tell you I'm quite dumb.
I'm not sure I'm seeing the correlation.
The Gaza Strip fight between the Israeli people and I'm really blank on the other side
of it.
I'm not too bright either.
The Gaza Strip thing.
It's an Arab country on the other side.
I have friends that come from there and I can't remember the name of the country right now.
Anyway.
Folks, look, you're always going to hear the hard -hitting political discourse on this
But it's this big, you know, conflict that's been going on
for years and years and years and years.
It gets very violent, and then, you know,
everybody on both sides says, well, he started it.
No, he started it.
No, he said, and it gets, it's to a point now
where it's like, guys, regardless of who started it,
stop, this is insane.
Like, this is, like Brian Reagan had a joke about it.
Like they need a good dad to go over there.
Like, I don't care who started it.
And it's like, that's what this left versus right thing has become.
It's like, I don't care anymore who started it.
Everybody fucking stop, man.
Like, well, it's not gonna stop and I do feel that it is, it isn't always was the goal
of the right to sort of flag this conflict into happening, but the left falls for it again
and again.
It worked.
And now we're just kind of butt fucked.
This is the sort of stuff where we're 30 years before this stuff gets resolved.
We're just falling to shit by the hour.
Hey, hey, hey.
But here's the bright side.
I watched a documentary called Tricky Dick in the Man in Black,
which is about Johnny Cash's performance at the White House under Nixon.
And they get a lot into, like, Nixon's tone with the country
and his stance with the press and the Vietnam War and everything, almost identical to right
now.
Of course.
So that's the part of me that I just go, oh this happened before, it'll pass.
But it was the same thing.
He would like publicly say in his press conferences, he wouldn't say the press is lying.
he instead would say, the minor, the major minority is the voice of the press. This is a handful
of people. This is not the perspective of our country. And then he would talk about the silent
majority. And you know, back then they said it was a dog whistle for racism and he was announcing
the press and the reporters had to fight for their freedom to express them. It's literally the same
thing. It was identical. Right. It was identical. And then Johnny Cash went to the White House,
pissed off all his fans because he was the biggest musician around. So that sound
fucking familiar. It's almost identical. You kid rock all over again. You'd almost think,
wow, I was gonna say Kanye, but oh sure. You'd almost think there's a there's a prototypical
map of this somewhere, you know, like a diagram set where on the White House wall they
go.
Sure.
We're going to run the old tricky dick.
They're heavily in place by him and Reagan.
It's all bad, but you don't you don't turn to us for this folks.
No, you don't.
You do turn to us to your sentence like tricky dick.
You do.
And you don't know about a president.
you turn to us to put politics aside and get on with the show and at the same time
and boy am I drawing a blank rifling through Spotify for anything that would
fit on with the boy. Maybe you could, Joria. Joria doesn't anybody want to. Joria. You
know that got your number. You know that song. I do it. That just came up on your Spotify
five feet. No, it just popped into my head. I saw a clip of it on, you know, on TV the other night
they were playing that song. Great song. Laura Brannigan. Is that who does it? I have no idea.
Gloria. Gloria.
I got you some. You could tell me, you could tell me it was Vicki Lawrence, I'd believe you.
Sure. Because she did sing that night, the night, the lights went out. The lights went out in
Joe -Rigia. I could have done that. You know what you could also do is in the hour and a half
you're drinking alone at the Tamo Shanner before we record. Maybe you just look up a song
in two seconds. Wasn't alone, and I like the spontaneity of it. Who are you with? I was
with an elderly prostitute. Is that so wrong? Hold the old marrow. It was my friend, Charlie.
having a nice evening.
Her name is Charlie.
It's a God.
Are you with a man named Charlie?
Was it Charlie Day?
No.
A different Charlie.
A Charlie that I don't care about.
That's correct.
Got it.
I mean, you should.
He's a nice guy.
Seems like a nice guy.
How could you be named Charlie and not be, well, Manson, I guess.
Sure.
Bukowski.
Not nice.
No.
Yeah.
Flicer.
the voice of Roger Rabbit.
Very nice.
I would think.
I don't know.
Also, you know, the potential Zodiac killer
in a very tense scene in Zodiac.
That's right.
Great performance.
How does he do that thing with his cheek?
Prr, prr, prr, please, please, Eddie.
But like, I saw him do it.
Like, he actually did, yeah, I can't do it.
He makes his cheek, yeah.
Like, I would have to do that with my hand.
Yeah.
That's crazy.
easy. There's never a Roger Rabbit sequel. It was talked about for years and didn't materialize,
but it was my favorite movie when I was good. I wanted to go full frontal in the sequel.
Right. That was the problem. They couldn't get any funding. What do you think the sequel would have
been about? Maybe he starts fucking the cop. I think there's a sequel to the book. Eddie, which I read,
who censored Roger Rabbit. The book is terrible. There's a book. The book before the movie.
Uh, Eddie Valiant is dead. I mean, Bob Hoskins is dead. Well, now he is. Yeah. I
don't think we're going to get it, but it was being rumored pretty recently. But, hold
on, the book is called Who Sensored Roger Rabbit? Correct. And it was written as a prequel
to the movie. It was written and adapted as the movie, yeah. Oh, the, so the book that
the movie is based on is called Who Sensored Roger Rabbit. That's cool. Why is it called
who censored and not who framed.
I don't remember.
I read the book and I hated it.
It's an odd, and the book is about cartoons in the human world.
That's correct.
That's a weird, I don't know, it seems like more of a visual thing.
I agree.
Joe, did you know, and maybe this takes us over into the screaming and news psycho, but did
Did you know that they are making a creep show television series?
I did.
There's not a lot of information out about it, but I'm very excited.
I'm very excited.
Who's making it or anything?
I don't know anything about it, to be honest.
I want to say, like, maybe Paramount Network or something?
I don't know.
I don't know who's making it, but I am happy that that's happening.
I'm excited for Jordan Peele's Twilight Zone, Twilight Zone, but what are we going to get CBS?
All access, is that what it's on? Something, yeah. Yeah, I can't do that. I mean,
Christ almighty, Jordan Peele can't get his goddamn show in the air. Yeah, I mean, CBS all access,
that ain't on the air unless they pointed up, you know, an extra million or something.
I'm saying, it's like, what are you going to do in this town?
You're going to be on, uh, what do they got the good, the good nanny or something on
there? Nanny time, it's called. Yeah, the, I think it's the good nanny time, but
yeah, it's, it's Fran Drescher as a DA ball, bust and DA. Right. And she's bad at the
job, which is why the title is ironic. Right. She's a bad, they say that every
week, they go, I ain't seen worse as the catchphrase on that show.
So, and it just doesn't flow off the tongue.
Everyone that says that you can see in their eyes, they're just not feeling the catchphrase.
So screaming in at News Psycho, while we're there, up against it, is she the story Jason
Blum, old Jason Blum from old Blum House pictures, responsible for so many movies we've discussed
on this program, just was booed off the stage.
stage. He went to the Israeli film festival and I guess he was being awarded you know for some
achievement or something and it was the day of midterms and he somehow took receiving an award
for movies where people are murdered every five minutes into chance for him to politicize it and
Talk about how he's fighting Trump or something and got boot off the stage.
What do you get? He thoughts on that?
My thoughts are why would you discuss Trump at a film festival A?
Right
B
Particularly at a Israeli film festival right makes no sense
You know and and then so so everybody starts booing him right right and he just keeps going keeps going
What as a possible they were saying blue
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
maybe move off of this, keeps going.
Then the booze start turning into people screaming,
this is a film festival.
We're here for entertainment, right?
Then that all starts.
Then that turns into, just keeps plowing through.
Then that turns into them standing up
and telling him to get the fuck off the stage basically.
He turns to the lady who's the host of the event
and goes, they're gonna have to drag me off stage.
And then turns back and continues a speech that's supposed to be about open -mindedness and understanding
the perspectives of others and not just shutting them down or whatever. And he's saying, he's like,
out of one side of his mouth saying, because you're booing me, you're proving my point that everybody's
closed -minded. And then out of the other side of his mouth, he's saying, this is the beauty of America
that we can express ourselves like this,
the goddamn thing didn't barely made sense.
And then the lady had to call security.
She had to call security onto the stage.
And then when she did that, he was like,
okay, I'll go, I don't need to be drug off.
It's like, oh, for God's sake.
At least you just said you're gonna have to drag me.
Yeah, just fucking go down with the ship
if you're gonna pull your dick out, leave your dick out.
You know what I mean?
Like, don't pull the thing out unless you plan to bang.
So bombs over Baghdad, did they, was he talking about Israel in some way, or why take this platform
for them? It was the midterms, and he was like, just as you, the filmmakers, came here today,
many Americans went to the polls to express what their vision is, like it was like the biggest
I'm like, dude, just take the fucking plaque and leave.
Right.
Jesus Christ.
And by the way, Mr. We all need to be better.
Oh, he actually said these words.
He goes hate speech inspires, like on Twitter later,
he was like hate speech inspires, hate crimes
and violent speech inspires violent crimes.
And yeah, blah, blah, blah.
And I think his tie -in was he was trying to say
because of the shooting.
I think that was his way in.
But he did, I'm pretty sure, make that analogy of the movies and the voting booths.
But I think it was because of the shooting at the synagogue.
He was saying like, this is all the fault of the White House, and I don't know whether
they agreed with him or not.
They were booing him so God damn loud.
But anyway, he, what's it called though?
So he goes on Twitter then and he gives this like ten -tweet explanation, saying like, you
people do after something like halibut,
they go online and they go,
it was a beautiful experience.
I'm so honored to have been,
it's like a shut the fuck up man.
You're furious right now.
Number one.
And then he goes,
you know, we need to be better
because violent talk leads to violent acts.
And it's like, you know, maybe not the guy
that runs Blum House should be telling me that.
Sure.
I love horror movies, I get it,
they're movies, they're fantasies.
but dude, you know, there are plenty of people out there
that would love to see his company shut down
because they think it inspires violence toward women.
Right.
Right, violence toward children.
Violence towards men.
So maybe you're not the fucking mouthpiece for this.
Jason Blum.
All right, relax, relax.
You got lucky with Get Out.
You had nothing to do with it.
Jordan Peele is a tour de force powerhouse of a talent.
He made a spectacular movie for you.
CBS All Access.
Stop acting like now you're the guy with the vision.
If you had any vision you wouldn't have made the last five fucking movies
I saw your company put out.
Damn.
That's the truth.
We're dare.
Which is one of the shitty movies.
Did you see Truth or Dare?
I know a lot of people thought they were watching that one
and watched a different, even worse,
truth or dare on Netflix.
Truth or dare?
Insidious?
Oh, she was there.
She was there with us.
Lin Shae?
And she had to just stand there.
Oh, boy.
What was she winning in a ward for?
I don't think she was winning anything.
I think she was there with him like,
I don't know.
Dating?
Maybe.
And then he gets full of stage and then
the host goes out and she's like,
like, okay, so come on guys, we're here to have some fun.
And like, has to get it on track, like a party clown
that like, barfs on himself at a kids party.
Right.
Have you ever known a movie to like,
more joylessly rack up $200 billion than Halloween?
Nobody is really enjoying it
and it just kind of keeps churning along.
Keeps churning.
I've talked to people and they're like you see Halloween yeah you see it yeah
And you just kind of start talking about something else like no one even wants to get into it
It's just kind of like yeah was a movie. Mm -hmm. Yeah not much to say movie where the first kill is a seven -year -old kid
Yeah, and then this guy goes on Twitter. We need to be careful. We'll put out exactly
I read today
I guess it, yeah, it definitely works in the Screamin' End news cycle.
Can I go too hard on Blumb, am I going to, am I, am I, am I, am I in danger of black
bawling myself in this?
You're fine.
You'll notice I stayed silent.
I want to work in this town.
Well, yeah, but you also told those stories at the live show that I can't believe we're committed
to tape.
Look, maybe Kelsey Grammar won't work with me again.
I have, I don't really have any plans to work with Kelsey Grammar, so that's fine.
I guess I don't have any plans to go to Blumbhouse.
That's that is until I'm pitching a script.
Sure.
I read that Avengers 4 the running time is over, don't say it, over, don't say it,
three hours.
So I'm clearly not going to see it.
I didn't say the last one.
I refuse.
Three hours.
That used to be for like the 10 commandments and shinlers list.
Now, you know, like trying to tell like the story of a nation,
the story of a group of people,
the story of the Holocaust.
Right.
Now is the running time for a movie
about dudes in plastic suits punching each other.
while, you know, the luminiers play whatever the fuck these terrible movies are.
It's dodged shit and they just keep adding characters. They just keep adding characters. Yeah.
It's it's I hate it. Yeah. I'm sick of it. Yeah. I'm not excited about Aquaman.
Oh, please. Oh, looks terrible. Jason Momoa. Do you see Venom? No.
Oh, I read that Venom is exactly the same movie,
almost shot for shot as upgrade.
And I find that really sort of fascinating.
And they -
Wait, that was a Blumhouse movie.
That looked good.
Upgrade is good.
All right.
We should do it on the show.
I was being a little unfair.
They have some good movies.
Yeah, I feel like I don't think it's ever fair
to associate a studio with like nothing but quality.
There is no such studio.
No, no.
You're gonna make a dog or two and that's part of being more than a dog or two
Hey, you know, they slapped their god. I mean this this this fucking anthology thing on Hulu is yeah. Oh, yeah, yeah
What's that? We talked about the show the end of the day. All right. Yeah, it's a lot of horror anthologies coming out
And that's your bread in the butter. I like horror anthologies, but
Not ones where each episode is a 90 minute movie. That's not an anthology
That's a movie is the expression. That's your bread and butter like is the the indication the implication there that bread and butter is
Delicious the best you can do. I always thought it meant come between the buns
Jesus Christ. No, it means like how you make your money your bread and butter. Okay
Like what my what like that explains it your bread and butter would be making television right you see I
I do, but how does that explain it?
Well, it's like, I think it's derived from,
you know what, butters my bread is a TV.
You know, like, that's how I make my money
to buy the butter in the bread, you know,
or the butter for the bread.
Okay.
I think I don't fucking know.
Well, I look like a fucking historian.
Could he remember the other country still can't
in the Gaza Strip conflict?
Joe, let me take you if I may, down to Pat's movie corner.
45 minutes into this podcast.
I TMC Turner movie classics does a great job
throughout the month of October
of playing great old classic horror.
Usually I watch a bunch of these.
I've had really no free time of late,
but one night I couldn't sleep
and I checked out the curse of Frankenstein.
And the curse of Frankenstein is...
Frankenstein going, son of a bitch.
Yes, right sort of like a real foul mouth Frankenstein
It was a
Peter Cushing Christopher Lee vehicle. Yeah, always cool to see I believe I've seen this film
It was a hammer film. Yes, you know, they always talk about this golden age of British horror hammer
I thought it was boring as bald
I hated it and I like the world of hammer films. I like that like Tim Burton influencing
Gothic horror. This sucked. It's considered a classic of the form.
I'm not a big fan of the 50s releases from Hammer. It's got that some of them. The color
film where it looks like it's black and white, but like somebody painted like 20 % of the screen
Yeah, like using the wrong colors. Everybody's cheeks are rosy. They all look like like footballs
Those hammer those 50s 1950s early 60s hammer films if you walked in the room on Christmas day and one was playing
You'd be pretty sure it was a Dickens flick. Yeah, exactly. There'd be no part of you that would think it was a Frankenstein movie
There wasn't anything close to a scare or a jolt. It was just boring as fuck
You know, it's like on that Edgar Wright greatest horror movie list, it's, you know, highly praised,
really didn't care for it, folks.
I already talked about tricky dick.
Yeah.
And damn it.
I didn't finish this one, so I can't talk about that.
Watch Candy Man 2.
Farewell to the flesh.
Yeah.
I've only seen Candy Man 1, which I like a lot.
I've never seen 2.
I love candy man one. I didn't think candy man two was great. It's not a bad movie. It's just pretty boring. Okay
They do a really good job of I don't remember if they did this in the first movie or not, but his backstory
Is pretty cool. All right, because every element of candy man it makes sense like so
So you say candy man five times in the mirror. He shows up and kills you with his hook hand sure
and then they're bees everywhere.
And in this movie, they really get into the backstory,
which is he was a slave who started dating,
or fell in love with a slave master's daughter.
Yeah.
The slave master didn't approve.
The town murdered him by pouring honey on him
and having bees attack him.
and they held up a mirror to his face
so he could see how hideous he was as he died
from being stung.
And then a kid, a kid like Lick the Honey
and was like candy man, you know, like as a joke.
And I was like, it's actually ties it all together
pretty well, like that's, but anyway,
aside from that aspect of it, I wasn't really into it.
I never quite understood the concept
of a guy that you know they do a terrible thing to him. Yeah. And then and he's not a bad guy,
he's like a good guy they did a terrible thing to. And then he kills innocent people after that. I
never quite got that you know I get the if he's out to avenge his death. Sure. But you know this movie
he's going after people that like you know there's like a professor that thinks like it's just a legend
like it's this silly ghost story. Right. And so he does the candy man thing in the mirror,
and then he gets killed. Yeah. What did this fucking guy do? You know, Joey, it sounds like this
candy man ain't so sweet. I'm done. I saw a picture called psycho three. You and I on this show
No Discuss Psycho 1, Why League Knowledge is a classic and all -time great horror film.
We discussed two and three too.
I think what I had not seen through.
Okay.
But two, you know, of course, Tarantino famously said he prefers to one.
I found two to be kind of entertaining.
I found three to be a fucking blast.
And the reputation it has from almost everyone is that it's shit.
I thought it was great.
It's got some weird like sleazy sexy energy to it.
There's like trashy sex scene that goes on
for while Anthony Perkins did it.
He was like a notorious Hollywood freak.
I thought it was very well directed.
It had great shots in it.
The plot was kind of like fine,
but I thought it had a real visual style.
I liked the sleazy trashiness.
I had a good time with it.
I think it's very underrated movie.
equal to two.
I like too much better.
I don't hate three, but I feel like it's more or less,
two had a story to tell.
Once you get past two and you know,
which begs the question, was he cured?
Is he still nuts?
Right.
Is he gonna kill again?
Once you get two out of the way,
then it's just like, well,
now it's just a movie about a guy that kills people.
But it isn't, I mean, three is essentially an extremely well done slasher movie, but it's
better than any of the Friday the 13th.
It's better.
I wouldn't say that.
The fact that it has this reputation of being shit is ludicrous, I think it was super
entertaining.
Look, and you've disagreed with me on this.
It's get such a harsh reputation because it's a sequel to Psycho.
Right.
I've said a million times.
The Godfather III is not a bad movie.
I agree. People bash it because it's a Godfather sequel and because of Sophia Coppola's performance. I don't think she's that bad at it
It's supposed to be one -on -one rider would have been a better film. Why is when I wasn't when on it it she was
Exhaustion what she usually means drug addiction
But she had like she dropped out a day before shooting because of exhaust. She wasn't even that famous then
No, she's on the up and up move at that point her career. Yeah, that's a low -hand move, baby
all right I'll do one more now I won't wait how many did I do one two is your
third and I got one more two what was my second what was my first one candy man
two I did candy man two that's it isn't it yeah then that's my second yeah so
I'll do one more now your second yeah I'm just gonna do one more is what I'm
I'm not gonna do three.
It's already, we're at the 40 -minute mark.
We haven't even touched on the goddamn film yet.
That's how this works.
You're getting mad at me.
Night visions.
Night vision, night visions.
You know, this is where I'm gonna save night visions
for scary stuff.
But on the night tip, I re -watched Night of the Demons
For, you know, an honor of Halloween, still a really fun horror movie, goofy horror movie,
doesn't make a whole hell of a lot of sense, but it's a really fun watch, and the practical
effects are pretty outstanding in it.
There's a scene where a woman, and it's the same actor that was in return to the living
dead that danced naked on top of the tomb or whatever.
She puts a also in sorority babes in the slime ball ball around.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
She shoves a lipstick into her nipple, and I'm pretty sure I know how they did it, but
they pulled it off really well, and it looks very real, okay?
Like she actually inserts this thing through her skin into her boob.
But it's just really great makeup effects.
The main demon lady is really scary, and it's fun, it's just a fun 80s horror movie.
It's what you, it's kind of what you hoped every one of those movies on the shelf in the
horror section would be in the 80s and I think this is one that delivers.
Okay, and I watched because Joe said he won't discuss it with me on the show.
The first purge, I really enjoyed the first purge movie entitled The Purge with Ethan
I left 15 minutes into the purge election year to watch Mike and Dave need wedding dates, and I'm glad that I did and
This fourth one makes the decision for me that I'm done with the purge movies
What I liked about it was it developing a political conscience because these movies
Scream out to be political and they try it a little but don't quite ever go there in the purge movies
this one really did have a point of view. It was an interesting point of view, but it felt like
anti -Trump propaganda made with a Trump supporters level of sophistication I would say.
I don't understand what you mean, but you mean what you mean. I agreed with the message, but it was
done in the kind of crude, not very elegantly told style of like, you know, a movie that
you think was pro -Trump.
An anti -Trump movie made with the quality of a pro -Trump.
I think it's impossible to do that commentary anymore where it doesn't come off as clunky
at this point.
It's so tired and trite, and we're all very aware of it.
So anytime you see it now, it's just like come on guys, you couldn't do that and you have to remember
Well, when did they make this movie was everybody not doing it at that point?
I don't know there are there are cool
Really cool moments there are there are you know, there's like
Some of the villains in this are dressed like in
You know blackface style masks the villains are kind of like white supremacist types, okay?
So to see the hero like it was a black guy
choke this guy in a black face mask out
and hold on the choking for like three minutes.
Like we see the life go out of his eyes.
It's like, okay, this movie has a little more on its mind
than the other purge movies.
I just don't know that it was done all that well.
The list of Tomay is in it.
It looks like she shot her supporting role
in about 25 minutes.
Risa Tome is in the first purge.
The first purge, why?
I don't know, you know, it is that kind of blue model.
It seems very cheap.
It feels like...
Is it a blue house, plum house?
It was, I believe.
It feels like a tail's from the hood segment
and not a particularly good one.
Not as bad as tails from the hood too,
but it's a very average horror movie.
All right.
By the way, not as bad as tails from the hood too.
I mean, that's what are you even saying there?
Right.
That kind of leaves all movies you know that's like saying it well the the house of the record. It's not as bad as Christian rock. Yeah, yeah
Pat can I can I share a little scary stuff with you? Please can I drink your last beer?
There's really one left. Yeah. Yeah, we could share it with two straws now, but you know
If you bring me a whiskey over something and
And now I'm fine.
Anyway, I gotta do a show tonight, people.
You know, I can't go on that stage
half in the bag, like Sinatra used to.
Scary stuff this week is a little TV show
called Night Visions.
And the reason I wanna do this is a scary stuff
is because it has been off the air for years.
It's out of print.
You can't buy it anywhere except bootleg.
I got bootleg copies of it.
But it was a horror anthology show hosted by Henry Rollins of all people, okay, who I love
and I'm a big fan of, not a great horror host, sure.
And you know, it's like any anthology from the early to mid 90s, you know, it's got
it's great moments, it's got it's boring moments, it's got it's stuff you don't care about
it, it's got stuff that you love.
But I think if you can find these episodes somewhere,
it's worth your time.
It kind of slipped under the radar,
a little more than some of the other anthology shows did in the past.
And there's a particularly good episode with Jack Palens,
called Bitter Harvest,
that I highly, highly recommend you watch.
But that's the scary stuff for this week.
this is the jack pounce from city slickers to coal and the legend of
curly's gold yeah he does curly he's doing curly in the segment that's kind
of all he can do no I mean curly from the three stages yeah yeah it's a it's
a sort of a biopic episode at one point he runs in circles on his side on the
floor that's called the curly shuffle yeah remember that was a hit song the
like the 80s, I guess?
Yeah, I loved it when I was a kid.
I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you, I see you,
he didn't direct it, and yet it's Tim Burton's
The Nightmare of Worker, so you got to love it.
Yeah, you got to love it, these people.
Look, I thought this was pretty cool
getting to see it at the bowl.
Tim Burton was not there.
I was led to believe he would be
unless he came after we left.
But we did see Catherine O 'Hara perform some
of the songs from this film.
She is a hero of mine.
Me too.
We saw Danny Elfman perform at length, not really a hero of mine, but cool to see him.
He's a hero of mine.
Music score wise, some of my favorite scores of all time, but like to see him perform vocals.
I'm an Oingo Boingo fan too, so.
Okay, that's not my thing at all.
And Paul Rubens, Mr. Peewee Herman himself came out.
And
comedian
Greg Proups Greg Proups was in like the chorus. Yeah, the guy who voiced the oogie boogie character was there who was great
Man, they went bat shit when that guy came out. They did I guess that's everybody age everybody's favorite character or something
Yeah, I mean
For me give you a little context. I
And when this film came out in 1990, I want to say three.
I was deeply obsessed with Tim Burton.
It was John Hughes and Tim Burton for me.
I love Beetlejuice, Batman, Batman Returns, Edward Scissorhands, Peewee's Big Adventure.
These were my favorite movies.
This was a time when the man not only could do no wrong but hadn't done any wrong yet.
Every movie he made was a masterpiece at this time.
So this comes out and I knew we didn't write it erected, but I was excited.
I remember it was sold out and I saw Adam's family values instead, which is
a extremely underrated movie and very funny. I think I've talked about it on
this show. Joan Q. Sachs great in it. David Cromwell is great in it. When I
eventually saw it, I remember feeling like, huh, I like everything about this. I like
the music I think it looks awesome the stop motion is incredible and yet
something kept me at a distance from it and it has kept me at a distance from
it right up to the present day. I don't get into it in the way I get into his
other shit. I tried several times over the years to watch this movie always tuned
out didn't give a shit. Thought if I'm gonna give it a chance front to back this is
is the way to give it a chance.
This is the first time I saw it in its entirety.
Same thing, you know, it's cute.
It's a cute idea.
The animation is phenomenal.
And it is something I feel like I should love.
But just kind of just don't care about it.
Yeah, the songs are catchy, but not catchy enough.
The story is fun, but like never quite good
or well developed enough.
the jokes are fine but not really funny the only really good joke is when they
give the parents severed heads you know as gifts which is in every trailer or
this movie. Visually I find all these movies do not quite match up to how
incredible they look your corpse brides your carolines or what is it
coral line. I like the coral line a lot that's why I was always surprised I didn't
Did this I don't know what it is with this flick. I don't I'm just yeah
There's someone I really liked was Frank and weeny. I loved Frank and weeny. I didn't see that and it's just a beautiful black and white
movie the voice cast like Martin Shore plays three parts Kathanaire plays three parts if you can see it in 3d I recommend it
But it's just not my thing. I had a decent time
But that movie is 79 minutes
that's you and I left early
and I was happy to leave early.
We had great seats.
It is sort of, in its own way,
it's almost like a reverse Grinch who stole Christmas,
you know?
But it is very Grinch influenced, I would say.
I like, I don't know what, you know,
the, I felt like the plot was a little disjointed. Like, you know, he's
sit like a very throwaway line at the beginning is when Jack Skellington
is telling those three evil kids to like get everything in order so they
can take over Christmas. Right. And he's like, don't get Dr.
Buggity involved. Whatever that guy's name is. Okay, Buggie. Yeah. And
uh, and they're like, yeah, okay. And of course, they do. And it's
And then all of a sudden in the last like 20 minutes stretch, this Ogidi Bugidi guy comes
into the mix.
And you're like, this doesn't seem like it needs to even be in here.
Yeah.
It's really badly constructed.
I feel like, and it's written by Carolyn Thompson, who wrote Everett Scissorhands, and I remember
loving that movie, but I, you know, it, of course, I love that movie.
But like, from a story standpoint, it's a very bizarre story.
and I feel like she kind of came up from being close with Tim Burton, but it follows no sort of
structure, the movie, especially for being a kid's movie, is sort of confusing at times to me?
In what way?
Maybe I'm just bored, but I tune out of it and by the end I'm like, what's going on?
Every time I watch it, it loses me. Every time I watch it, I'm talking about
But I remember for Christmas, I mean, I follow and love Edward Scissorhands, but there's
just a big Edward Scissorhands fan always loved it.
I mean, I recognize it's a good movie, it's just not for me.
Yeah.
It's just not for me, it's too, it's too goth, it's just too goth for me, I can't get
into it.
Did you have a goth phase ever?
No.
Okay.
Why the fuck would I have had a goth phase?
You know that bar next to Bordner's where we drank before this movie is a they have a goth night
And I've been there during it, but that's a barrel of laughs. I'm sure there's always a huge line outside and the one time
I was there and going into Bordner's on goth night. I saw a woman standing with a man on a chain link leash
News wearing a sign that said I have a small penis. That doesn't sound goth -eat -me. That sounds more
or it was, it was, yeah, but they go hand in hand.
They go, do they?
Yeah.
I feel like the Goths are too sad to hurt anybody
besides themselves.
Gothen S &M are pretty close.
If Goths are having sex, it's S &M.
I don't think that's correct.
If any fans have any insight into this,
I'd love to hear about it.
Yeah, I know.
The most Goth thing I've ever done was make out
with a girl in a graveyard.
yard. And I went to see the cure three times one summer when I had a really kind of weird
period, a couple years back, I got really into the cure. I never did anything. I once
I wore one of those, those little dresses with the white collars. Right. That was pretty
goth. And when I met you, you were a juggalo, which is different from goth, but, but very some
crossover. Very. And jugalos, you know, we don't bleed. Right, except all the same color or
something like that. They got some phrase like that. It's like, we bleed black and white or something.
We all bleed red or something. I don't know something. Okay, some fucking thing.
You should like, well, how much would we have to collect from our fans to go to one of these like
jugalofests and report that? I've been to one and I performed it one. You did stand up there.
Yeah, yeah, if you if now if you go back and check out my first half hour special, uh -huh pat
Which I know you won't do
Is it on Spotify
No, there's a TV it was for Comedy Central, okay. I don't have no
Yeah, my first album I closed with the same bit
I closed with a bit called the worst gig ever and it's it's about when I performed at the juggle. Oh, okay gathering
Yeah, it's quite a tale and it's all true. It's very I'll check it out. You don't want to go there dude. Yeah
Yeah.
They sharpened, not when I was there, but like the year after I was there, they sharpened
a shower curtain rod into like a spear and threw it at somebody on the stage at one point.
Another year they threw human feces at Tia Tequila.
That one I did really.
And then I'm sitting there saying, guys, I want to hate you.
Yeah.
But, you know, but that was the one thing I kind of,
I thought it was fun.
Imagine getting hit with human feces.
The worst fucking thing ever.
Nobody deserves that.
It's terrible.
I had another thing to say about the nightmare
before Christmas.
You didn't say much about it.
No, I did.
Okay.
I did.
There's just a certain type of person that loves this movie.
Yeah.
Yeah, my friend Jerry growing up, he loved it.
He loved it.
Uh, and, you know, look, they sold out the Hollywood Bowl.
I mean, several nights.
Yeah, it's like the only other movie I think they did that with was Star Wars.
Yeah.
Like, you know, so it's like people love this movie.
Right.
Um, just not quite sure, it's, well, it's the look of it.
I mean, yeah, but there are a lot of things look like that.
There wouldn't be that kind of fanfare for Coraline.
There wouldn't be that kind of fixture for the Rudolph,
off the Red Nose Render Christmas special,
there's something about this particular film
that drives people nuts.
Let's see, Rudolf the Red Nose Render Christmas special,
that's, I mean, that's the fucking chip to me.
I love that chip.
It's awesome.
I don't think you could fill the Hollywood Bowl.
No, you could.
Several nights in a row.
No.
And I don't think people would go crazy
if they were like, hey, the guy that does the elf voices here.
What if they had like a hologram burrow odds?
I'd go see that.
Yeah, I'd go to them.
Every time it's my favorite Christmas song of all time.
Silver and gold.
That's a holly jolly Christmas.
Ever -holly jolly Christmas.
It's my favorite Christmas song of all time.
It's a good one.
I love it.
It puts me in the spirit.
I got my Christmas records up in storage.
I got to get them out.
Mine are dusted off and ready to go.
We're getting our tree this weekend.
I'm putting the tree up with my folks
when I go home and Thanksgiving.
Okay, it's gonna be real nice.
You're putting it up already, huh?
I like to get it up.
I figure maybe it'll have a 1 % adjustment to my daily mood, and that's needed because I'm at about a
zero percent. Now what what what if I came over dressed as an angel and
Just sort of hung from the top of the tree every morning. Would that put a smile on your face? It would help all right
I'll think about it. Have you ever done Santa come?
No, is that where like all the department store sanders go?
No, it's just a bunch of people, it's basically a bar hop through a city with everyone dressed
as Santa.
Why are we not doing our own?
Well, it became very fratty and douchey over time, but I went to the LA one 10 years
ago.
I had no friends, and my one friend here was like, we should do this.
And I made some friends.
I still have to this day from it.
We had a blast.
We saw like 19 bars all across Los Angeles.
You take subway as you take, you know,
the train system.
And it's really fun.
I would love to do it this year.
We should do it.
It's usually like right after Thanksgiving.
I would do it.
My question to you is, why can't just you and I
dress up as Santa Claus and go to bars?
There's nothing saying we can't do it.
We could do that tonight.
We could.
But, are you still coming with me this Friday night
to see plans transomobiles at the Beast of Theater
at midnight, me and Heather and maybe,
can no longer go, I got a show at midnight at 1220 spot
at the Lafactory, yes on Friday night.
Entertainment doesn't sleep, Pat.
Thought maybe we could do that movie on this show.
It wouldn't fit the format at all.
It literally not, that's you can't even stretch that one.
But, I'm so excited to see this thing
at the theater, I really can't wait.
I'm sad if it wasn't at midnight,
I could have still went but it is at midnight and so I can't and that's how that
goes. Yeah listen I gotta get showered because I gotta go do a show. All right but look listen
it's everybody that's suffered from the wildfires here in California you're in our prayers and our thoughts
and absolutely hope that you get through it as best you can it's it's it's it's a truly truly
uh, just disaster situation. So, uh, that's our show. Um, we, uh, we'll talk to you soon.
Next week we were, I think we're going to do clue coming up on one of these, uh, we'll,
we'll be doing, um, I mean, look guys, we were, we might do Susperia, but my friend Jared
saw it and I was like, how was it? And he goes prepared to step into it to somebody's vision.
And I was like, oh, God, and I can't wait to see it.
I brought up Neon Demon and Krat, not Kresh, mother.
No, both of which I hated, he liked mother a lot.
He also hated drive and Neon Demon.
But he did say he liked this, but he said it is very much
like a man's artistic vision.
It is, you know, like he's like, I sort of feel
I feel like I'm gonna love it and I often think about how we can even, how I can even
be friends with somebody who doesn't like drive.
Neon Demon I get, drive I don't understand and certainly both better films and mother
by about five billion percent.
Oh god, shut up.
Mother exclamation point, excuse me, is the title.
Shut up.
But I am excited to see it and I think we should go to the beast of this week and check it
out and do it on next week's show.
Yeah, I can't promise that, but yeah, that's, you know, we'll try our best.
So we'll probably be doing Susperia, we'll probably be doing Clue, and I mean, that's, you
know, and then your bonus live app this month, the second live episode, we'll be coming out
where we review Halloween.
And one of these times we will be doing the Make Good Patreon where Joe and I will do some
like long epic commentary.
By the way, and correct me if I'm wrong, anybody out there, because maybe I read it wrong,
because I am the one that made a mistake,
whatever with the patron, I did look back through the months.
It looks like nobody was charged for July,
just for June, just for July.
It looks like in other words, you were charged for one month,
accidentally, not two.
And it looks like when I put the pause on,
it actually worked for June,
but then automatically started again
at the beginning of July, which makes sense.
Yes.
Because I remember putting the pause on
And I was like, wow, I don't understand what happened.
And I think it just automatically restarted
and I didn't click like manual restart or something.
So it looks like, and again, if I'm wrong, I'm wrong,
it looks like we missed one month and not two,
or charge you for one month and not two.
But just because of the weirdness,
I wanna do some big long, maybe a three -hour movie commentary
or something, just we're gonna do something someday.
I'm gonna force Joe to do it. He keeps saying I don't care about the fans. I say Joe, we got to do this
We're gonna have done and then I'll spit right I'll go here's what I think of the fans
And I'll pull up the patreon page and spit on to it. Yes under my own computer screen
He would do that. He would spit on his own computer. He was spitting on his screen. It never made any sense to me
He'd get it in the keyboard
That was doing good fellas. Yeah, all right. I gotta go. I'll be at the Philly punchline Thanksgiving weekend
again, I will be in New York City, the weekend of July 3rd, 4th and 5th, or January 3rd,
4th and 5th, at Gotham Comedy Club.
Come on out.
I'm working the new stuff.
I got a new bit about witches that I'm really excited about.
I'm on Instagram and Twitter kind of at the Patrick Walsh, the cool kids there is Friday
nights at like eight thirty seven thirty central or something like that it's
also on Hulu very funny program. So I got folks we'll see you next time we'll
I'll see you in hell.