Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer, or check out
our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz, only available at Bed
MDM Casino.
Spin on Spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM game sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as non -mustrable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberler, offer not available in all states,
terms apply, see Fanatic's fourth book app.
Folks, it's your favorite duo of handsome burly men here for the, we'll see you in
hell podcast brought to you by the Starburns audio industry's network.
And we're going to talk some fucking horror movies.
folks we're doing Mandy today the new Nicholas Cage picture and we'll get to that soon enough but
first we should just catch up haven't been in the same room as Joe and over a month I know you
guys kept getting quality content but that's because we planned ahead and thought about you the listener
yeah yeah where's our thanks is what I'm saying where's our thanks Pat it's good to see again it
It is currently 10, 10 a .m. on a Sunday morning.
I just want to show the listeners what we're up to.
Hold on.
Yeah, I had already opened mine.
It was a bottle that wouldn't have made a noise anyway, but let me just mine it for you.
That was me opening a bottle of Stella beer.
I was discussing with Joe.
I just can't make up my mind, Don.
Is it good or is it disgusting?
You know what Stella is good with?
No.
is a sharp cheese.
Okay, the bitter happiness of a Stella
meets a sharp cheese nicely.
Other than that, it can get out of my face, right?
Other than that, I never want it.
All right.
How was the South Seas, what they call Asia?
I don't know.
Okay.
I learned nothing new about geography.
Yeah.
I just know it's not orient.
It's not called the orient anymore?
No.
I should know that you probably shouldn't have been saying that in every bar you would end to over that
I'm digging this orient
Yeah, yeah, no, it was great man. I went to Hong Kong
Yeah, right after the tsunami thing happened. I hear that's the best time to go to Hong Kong. It was
the
We were actually in a Providence right outside of Hong Kong, but it was also hit by the by the same storm
the efficiency and diligence in which this city was put back together, at least where I was,
was astounding. Like, we were walking through the street one day and there were in the middle,
like, dude, it looked like they had measured it out in the middle of this one street,
just perfectly piled stacked trees that had fallen. Yeah.
Branches everything like well kept like it's it's it's being run very efficiently over there is what I'm getting it, but
America there's a natural disaster
Maybe they go down there three months in to say hello and then fly out immediately again. Yeah, so
It's a different world over there. I had a great time
The shows were tremendous. I went also went to Shanghai and then I went into Japan and went to Tokyo
did shows in each of the three cities, met some hellians, people showing up, like
did I'm a fan of the pod, I can't believe you're an Asia right now. Like they
had traveled over to see the show from the state. No, they live there. And they
were locals or transplants. Some were expats, but some were native Chinese people.
Yeah, I met a very lovely girl whose name is escaping me right now and she was from
China. She was born and raised there and I got to be honest with you. I felt like
a goddamn beetle when I was talking to her. Yeah. She made me feel very appreciated as
it entertainer that I was there entertaining. I said, hey, honey, tell the rest of the audience.
No. She was really amazing. I met another wild fan in Tokyo who flew from Korea to see
my Tokyo show. Really? Two -hour flight from Korea. I thought he would just drift over.
Flew over. Yeah. Was there for one night to see the show? Had a few drinks with me before
the show. I tried to take time with each person that was a pot. Any fans that came up I tried to
take time with but the podcast was four or five people there. Yeah come on. Yeah but the podcast
fans in particular because I was so taken aback like and flattered that people that far away were
listening to this thing that we do over here that we at many times in the early stages thought nobody
he cared about. True. So anyway, I had a few drinks with him before the show. He was
then removed from the show for being too drunk. Oh, no. I forget his name too, but buddy,
if you're out there, I hope you're not beating yourself up about it. He tried to get
on to the stage at one point. Okay. And then the owner said, you got to leave. Makes sense.
But and I met another one or two hellians in a very nice kid I met at my one of my shows in Shanghai
That's small I'm blanking on everybody's name right now. I apologize, but he was a really great kid
And you don't like to make the listener feel special. Well, it's it's
You got to understand the amount of alcohol it was being dumped sure all every one of these memories now
I recall one of the last words I heard you say before leaving was I don't think I'm gonna drink over there
I just want to go out and see the city and the culture and I
Managed to do both okay. I said what the fuck am I doing? I'm not gonna I didn't I'll be honest
I think I had three big nights
But that was kind of it. I
Most nights I would go back at a reasonable time get some sleep get up the next day go out and do some stuff
Yeah, do the show
Would you ever jump on a bar and yell socky at to me, baby?
Everywhere I went even if they wasn't a bar
I church. Yeah, yeah, yeah, the library. Sure
It was a great time. I had a blast. Thank you to everybody the came to the shows and then thank you all sort of the people that came out to Atlanta
For my album recording which is now done how to go went great good albums in the can
And I'll be released get it out and let me listen to it
Yeah, it's it's gonna be released exclusively to Sirius XM. Okay, I'm sort of soon. Great can't wait. I don't have Sirius XM anymore.
I've been under a lot of stress. I'll just be real honest with you.
the job of running a show, it ain't fun.
Even when you think it's gonna be fun, it ain't fun.
They come at you from all sides.
We came out big, we wound up with the,
they had the plus three numbers,
we had like a 2 .0.
Congrats on that.
On a Friday night, unheard of,
and then everybody starts kind of swarming in.
Now it's like we gotta protect this.
So, oddly, the ratings coming out and being so good, we're like this bad thing for the vibe of the show,
because everybody gets so scared about losing it.
Oh, boy.
That said, come up with some very funny episodes.
We just shout out the Thanksgiving one.
I think it's going to be the weirdest episode of television that's ever aired.
I love it.
We had Julia Duffy from New Heart.
I love Julia Duffy.
Charles Shawna -C from the nanny.
Which guy is the British guy. Oh, okay. Yes, I met him in an episode of Sullivan's son. Okay. Yes, that I took my parents. I love that guy. Yeah, and then Clyde Kusatu from Mash fame
Who was he on mash? I've never seen mash, but I know he was on mash. You know he's on he's been an every sitcom ever
He's like a 60 -year -old. He's nine years old now. He's older. Yeah. Yeah, and retirement home. Yeah, that's right
I forgot but they play these like psychotic foodies and they get trapped at their party and they're basically have brought them there
Like to make fun of them under false pretenses and we went in such a way such a sick way with them that they were
Like psychosexually obsessed with food
And there's a scene where Julia Duffy pops up next to old Vicki Lawrence. She's like classic, you know wine jossal
And she says, you're into Mary, aren't you?
Who's like the head, booty?
She goes, what?
No.
She goes, I should warn you.
Mary's not into women.
And then Becky goes, ah, okay.
And she goes, oh man.
Becky's like, what?
She goes, Mary is only into food.
I'm like walks away.
It was the craziest thing I've ever seen.
But people were fucking laughing.
I think it's gonna add it together very well.
I forgot that she does kind of have Hannibal Lecter's voice.
Well, we just locked into it one day.
We were like, who else does she sound like?
And I was like, oh yeah.
She's a psychopath.
Ah, that's awesome.
She was amazing.
And, you know, still very sexy.
I always was attracted to her in the new hard days.
Well, she was the, she was the angel in the new hard days.
Sure, yes.
Yeah, yeah.
Palas can be, like, makes me look like a creamy tan.
All right, all right.
but delightful. It's been fun. And the cool thing about the show, which is on Hulu and Fox,
and then I'll drop it, is all these old actors are dying to work. So you can get almost anybody you
want. They're just sitting around. It's fantastic. Yeah. I saw the pilot. I loved it. Yeah. So
it was very funny. And nothing to do with that. But I know. But it's only going to get better now
because the wash man is on the job. I concur. But I love the pilot. I thought it was really funny.
The short guy Leslie Jordan holy shit. It's the funniest man on this guy
This is a breakout star of the sitcom year. I mean without question and this guy is yeah came out fucking swinging
He's my favorite. Everybody was great, but he I was like Jesus Christ. This guy is like killing it man
He's an animal. We started giving him like long speeches and he kills all those and he's just like
He's 66 and never got a break really and he's the funniest man I've ever met Jesus Christ
So he's attacking it sometimes where you got to be like hey, let's bring this down a little bit
Sure, he's great. It was addicted to crystal meth for many years
Once shared a jail cell with Robert Downey Jr
I love it anything's possible. Yeah turn it around. So he's the everybody is great on the show
I thought the show is very funny. I love that it's about older people. I
our Dabney Coleman plot line into there somewhere.
Couldn't agree more.
And I've got a bit for the show.
And I actually do think it's a funny bit.
Yeah.
There's a funny bit.
I'm pitching you this for the show.
All right.
It's a quick joke.
There's a kid who's coming in to do some kind of beauty
cream presentation for the older folks.
Sure.
Young cream.
OK.
The kid's kind of a burnout.
The boss goes, do you know what you're doing?
And the kid's like, yeah, I got it.
I got it put the cream to stop your creepy skin and then the boss goes
Creepy skin creepy please do not say creepy when you go out there
It's a funny bit. I like the bit junk
Yeah, so you maybe you I don't know
Maybe we'll work it in who knows you it probably not but you know, it's a funny bit
I wrote a town of my photo. Yeah, there's a good bit for something. I told my grandma
I'm gonna get this joke of hers in the show that she didn't even remember saying I probably told
you this maybe not on air about five years ago I was day after Christmas and I was of course
having breakfast at the casino with my mom and my grandma so we're sitting there eating and my
mom goes I'm like what are you doing tonight my mom goes I got to take my friend out she's been in
a really bad place I got to take her out my grandma's like why I was like 90 years old eating her
doesn't even look up she goes well you know her ex -husband killed himself and then she started dating
this guy that she really liked and then he killed himself.
My grandma again does not look up from her food and goes well she sounds like a real catch.
Which I still talked to her about is one of the funniest jokes I've ever heard.
That's really funny.
My mom talking about the pain of a close friend and like Sophia on a classic golden girl.
She slaps her down.
Very funny.
I enjoy that.
But I was going to say one more thing about the show.
The live show?
Your show.
My show.
I had one more.
You see Jamie Farr on there?
I did, in fact.
I lit up.
I'm like, yeah.
I loved it.
Like they've got these little walk on rolls and they're going to toss them out to like these classic
like sitcom stars.
Well we've made it.
We've made him like the Newman.
He's so dorky.
It's a different vibe than Newman.
He's just like a huge dork and like ruined their good time
because he's like the screech, if you will.
Right, because we didn't realize it,
but the audience goes completely fucking insane
for Jamie Foxx.
It's awesome.
I just kind of like he's an old guy sitting in a chair
over there.
I see a winkler popping in this at some point.
I'd love it.
I would do a Dick Van Dyke, a Carol Burnett.
Yes, absolutely.
I think you need to push for the mama appearance.
Oh, yeah, mom meeting Vicki, it's got it. It's got to have. In fact, I think you do an unofficial
where they're not the same characters. You just bring in the cast of Mama's family. Oh, yeah.
For they play different people, but it's an unofficial reunion. Yeah. You know, you get that guy
from F -Troop on there. Ken Barry. Yeah. Yeah. He's still funny. I'm sure it will. He might be dead,
but I think he's still alive. I bet you the kids old enough at this point would be in the
fucking old age who Julia Duffy's character was named Francine and Vicky at one
point screams in her face, we got it, Freddie was the line. And then she came over
and she was like, I don't want to say franny because there remember there was a
character on Mama's family. I don't want to remind people of franny. And I was like,
yes, I do remember franny. Now it's an over went, we got it, Francine, which was
funny or anyway, it all worked out. And Vicky Lawrence is tremendous on the show.
I love her you have you gotten to sit down talk out that iris
You use whatever the fuck you still haven't watched it with me. So now what the hell is it called unis unis the serious drama version of mom as well?
I've held out because I thought we would watch it
We promised the fans we would do a commentary episode on it. I'll bring it over him
We should do that even though it's outside of our
Well, it's not really that outside of it. You got a 30 -year -old lady pretending to be 80
yeah that's scary. It's odd. Yeah yeah I don't have much life stuff to report
that's all I've been doing. It's very long hours and grind and grind. All right well
yeah and I just auditioned for Charlie Day's other. How'd you do?
Thing that he wrote. The Apple show. Him in back lane. Yeah. The audition went well.
I have no idea.
Ram, you know, I was looking at that calling sheet though and it was that sign -in sheet.
I was stiff -comp on that fucking thing.
Yeah.
Some real stiff -comp on it.
Who'd you have?
Like a Jamie Kennedy.
Stiffler.
Stiffler?
I won't name names but there were one or two people on there I was like, fuck man, this guy
still has to read for shit?
Yeah.
Like, there's no colder job than actor, I'll tell you that.
Jesus Christ. It's a brutal gig. We take a little wager on the set of what will be the first day and one of our extras will die
Which is wait? What are our extras all fall asleep? They're they're all people. Yeah, but at some point. I feel like that's gonna happen
And that's not gonna be a fun day. I hope that doesn't happen as do I
But who knows
Who's you got of the same extras to write because it's pretty much yeah, it's like it's like
Like the counter lady in Seinfeld, she's gotta be there, they're in the same place.
Now on the way in, I told Joey I had spilled some coffee on myself and I said do you have
maybe a shout wipe and Joe responded, what the fuck is a shout wipe?
You never heard of a shout wipe?
Why else would I have responded that way?
You know, shout, shout stick, any of the shout products?
Yeah, just a little wipe, you wipe it on the stain, it goes away immediately.
You rub it out.
Coffee doesn't stain. Did you not know that on a black he's wearing a jet black t -shirt?
It's all on my class my bright blue slacks. Is it still there?
No, yeah, it dries clear usually, but it's brown
So does the same thing I can't explain it all right
also
that this
Record rack is a structural
Issue way into happen you can't put
50 pounds of records on the top half and nothing on the bottom half.
The bottom half was going to be all my rap CDs. I should flip it the other way.
You should definitely flip it, but you'd need to put something on the bottom with weight
or else the top's going to come crashing through the bottom. I was surprised it didn't already.
Well, shit, do I need to pause this and do that right now?
No, I think you can make it, but yeah, I was wondering. I was like, this doesn't look
Right now I when I was putting I have this giant thing similar to that would thing to put on my album's on and
I started putting them on at the top because I have alphabetized them because I have OCD
I was going through them and once I had maybe three rows on the top the whole thing almost just gave
But this is smaller. It's more compact. You should be fine. But I do it sooner than later. I'll move it down. All right
There's a big question on everybody's mind right now, and I'm afraid you're not going
to ask me.
And I can't believe you haven't asked me yet.
Oh.
Well, what I'd like to do first if I may is get on with the show.
That yeah.
We were so excited to see each other, we forgot about all the necessary things.
And also on, with a Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe,
Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Joe, Kylie Minogue, Kylie Minogue, Kylie
Minogue.
Now you're in a, you're in a zone now where the, the syllable doesn't even rhyme with
Joe anymore.
I couldn't sit here and think about it again.
That's not what I was referring to that I thought you were going to ask me.
Oh, you thought I was going to ask you why did you tell Brett Kavanaugh to do it again?
Yes.
Well, then what is my answer?
Pat, it looked good on paper.
Yeah.
The execution with...
No, I can't.
Is that a bad joke to make that it looked good on paper?
No.
Yeah, I have no answers.
I have no answer.
Some dark developments. These were these are dark times. I do not like the man or do not support the man
The trial. I mean you you couldn't make it up. No the parodies of it were less funny than the actual trial that the thing with the thing with
Excuse me the actual trial was funny than the parents of it. Obviously, but the thing with Matt Damon was really fucking funny it was it was it was I
Love that it just start he sits down just goes what
Yeah, I feel bad for Ford.
I've known so many guys like Kavanaugh on my day,
like the worst people on earth.
I mean, here's the thing is like,
look, whether he did this thing or not,
this is the guy you want on the Supreme Court.
He's ripping his hair out.
It's like, Jesus, if you can't handle this pressure,
what the fuck are you gonna do when you're,
yeah, but he's there for life.
I mean, sitting up there sobbing about his dad's calendars.
Oh boy, dark dark times it wipes it in there staring at him that being said before
people before are people that are fans that may lean right think that we're
pushing too hard in one direction I would like to say this publicly I at this
point have been condescended to so severely by people on both sides of the coin I
don't want to leave my house or not be drunk anymore yeah I don't want to
talk to anybody. Yeah. I feel bad for people that bad things have happened to, but I can't get
yelled at anymore. I just keep getting yelled at by people on both sides. I don't know what I'm
doing wrong. Yeah. I just leave me alone. The world is divided. And maybe it's time for a new
a new course. And maybe that's up to us. You know, you and me start the new, the quote, new course.
Yeah, you know, maybe we maybe we maybe we start some paying a pilgrimage or something
Okay, let's all get together and move to this other place and start fresh. They'll be Thanksgiving -style foods
Yeah, get more people on our side. Why not? I mean, we can call ahead and have it delivered for when we get there
I'm gonna talk about roughing it here. I'm just saying you know, let's I'm in
It anyway, so
So, my dad loved calendars. He imported on me a love of calendars. March, April, May,
June, July.
The man is a real piece of work. I got to Pinkstone's house the day of the hearing.
Yeah
I've got to Pinkstone's house the day of the hearing yeah, and I did write a I did write a melon camp style song
Yeah, my rival the uh, but I got there the day of the hearing and
His wife was Jessica who's really wonderful. She was very wrapped up in it and great gal
She yeah, she's great and she was talking about it a lot
So we were all kind of talking about it a lot and how crazy it all was
But Jim was the first one to actually say to me and it like hit me in the gut
It was so funny, but he was the first person to say to me like
He actually thought like he was actually pointing to a calendar being like nowhere here doesn't say I raped
Right in my records. Yeah, so I was like yeah, you're right that is fucking bad shit. It's really funny to me
It's obviously the darkest of situations, but
but his whole thing was very, very funny to me.
When they asked him about the drinking game,
when they asked about the devil's triangle.
Do you have a plate of quarters?
Yeah, no.
It's like quarters.
What a prick.
I just wish the guy had said, like, how do you play it?
Yeah.
No, tell me the rules.
Every time I'm watching any courtroom thing,
I'm like, ask this.
Don't ask her if she's nervous.
I hate that shit.
Oh, so you said you're scared of flying,
But it says here you went to Hawaii once like this isn't your chance to be fucking it's why I bury Mason
That's why I think it's orchestrated. Yeah, it's like there are obvious questions that just don't get asked
Right like and you're like yeah, because if they answer those questions, we would get the answer too quickly
Yeah, and then you don't get TV content. That could be it. I mean it's nuts
It's did I talk about the the interview with Conway on on
Uh, uh, um, Cuomo on CNN, no, they did like a 35 -minute interview with her.
Oh, Kellyanne Conway.
Yeah.
I'm, we're not on a Tim Conway, Dwarf and full Dwarf here.
It's a new Dwarf.
It's Dwarf at the White House.
It's a Trump parody.
Right.
Uh, no.
But so, so he interviewed Kellyanne Conway for like 35 minutes about like, did Trump pay these
women off to hush money.
And, you know, they're just going around in circles and you're 15 minutes into this thing
and you're like, why doesn't he just say to her, if the tape we heard wasn't him learning
about the payoffs, what was it about then, that's all you got to say and then you get your
answer. And all she has to say is, this is what the tape was about. You're wrong. Yeah.
But neither of them will say that. And you're like, of course they won't. Because then
And you don't get 35 minutes of two people screaming at each other out of it.
You know?
And I was like, this is all just a big fuck, oh god, I can anymore.
I want to stay in the house drunk.
I don't want to be part of anything anymore.
I agree.
You know?
I think a lot of people don't.
Anyway, um, let's get on, on a brighter note, head on down the street to, uh,
bath movie corner. Yes. Well, folks, I ain't seen much. Um,
let me see. Do you have one to start? I don't even know what I've, if I've seen anything,
I've seen a ton of shit. Okay. Uh, you know, I rewashed dirty rotten scoundrels. Okay.
So I hadn't seen in years.
You seen the film?
I was never a big fan of it as a kid.
I think it was a little too dry for me as a child.
Yeah, Steve Martin was my favorite.
And it was one that got significantly less play
than everything else, even like parenthood.
And I was like a 10 -year -old boy.
I liked more than this.
Watching it again, it is a movie with three hilarious scenes
and the rest plays like a moderately
entertaining caper kind of thing.
Yeah.
But the scene where he's trying to remember the guy's name and the prison cell is one
of Steve Martin's funniest scenes of all time.
The scene where he is repract the idiot boy and Michael Cain keeps whipping his legs to
prove that he is paralyzed is maybe even funnier than that scene.
Right.
It's got some great stuff in it and Steve Martin and Cain are delightful together.
But just not, not a classic. My initial opinion was right.
Uh, I rewatched Big Top Pee Wee.
I would love to rewatch Big Top Pee Wee. I've not seen it 1 -100th of what I've seen the
other one.
Uh, Pee Wee, you might not be uplifted rewatching it.
Yeah.
There are things I never picked up on.
Okay.
He's very physically aggressive with women throughout the film.
Oh.
Like like at the beginning like the gag in his date with his girlfriend. Yeah, is that basically he wants to fuck her and she's clearly not fucking him yet
Uh -huh and repeatedly through the lunch picnic. He's just jumping on her
Okay, so it's it's kind of weird because not just because of the that action but also because it's pee we herm in doing it
Right who in the Netflix one they were subtly referring to him as being homosexual well that I was fine with what
I didn't need was the metaphor of the milkshake
being him jerking off and coming to Joe Montenia
or whatever that fucking actor's name is.
Joe Montaliano.
By the way, you see in that fucking commercial
with that tool, Joe Manjiannello.
It's him and his wife, the modern family.
And yeah, the Hulu thing?
Yeah, it's like tips or whatever.
And he's like, tip one, never fly first class.
You'll never be able to fly coach again.
You're trying to get us to like you?
You're trying to sell me a product and this is the attitude you're greeting me with.
What a cunt.
I've never flown in first class in my fucking life, you're going to talk to me like that.
I met that guy once.
I didn't like him.
I met both of them.
I liked her quite a bit.
She was very nice.
She seemed like a fucking prick.
He came three months into Brokero that came sniffing around the set for Beth.
I was like, 25 years older than her.
Like get out of here.
He was like, where's the blonde?
Where's the blonde?
Yeah, well, I probably shouldn't have told that story. What do I care?
Hopefully he was a single man. Should have told Brett Kavanaugh do what he did. That's right. The uh, we uh
What else today? Oh, oh, but big top Peewee
Aside from the
Physically aggressive side of Peewee hermen that you have no desire to see
Uh big for yourself. It is a
It's insane. It's batshit.
The movie opens with him waking up at his bed with his pet pig.
Okay?
Okay. You go through a cool 11, 12 minutes of this movie of him and his pet pig
just tending to their morning duties on the farm.
I don't know if something the pig starts talking.
Okay. I don't remember that.
Yeah, they don't, they, they inch, you're like way into the fucking movie at this point.
If you had a talking pig dust them off in the an act one
As soon as you wake up. That's the first thing morning to the pig. Yeah
Pig says good morning back right established what's going on here. Yeah, they're all the way into the laboratory
Scene where Peewee has invented this other plot line this B plot where he's invented a miracle
vegetation growth serum guy that makes tomatoes grow like really it makes no fucking sense. It's it's insane
Is it possible that for the first half of the film, the pig was giving Pee Wee the silent treatment?
No, the pig is just not talking because it's one scene. Maybe they were in a fight.
Then you don't know what time period it is. It's kind of jumping, but from time periods, it's very odd.
Girl from hot shots, right? Valeria Galina? Yeah, she falls in love with Pee Wee Herman.
And then his other girlfriend is Penelope Ann Miller.
Right. It is two of the most beautiful women that I've ever walked the earth. Well, I think they know that joke. I get that joke.
Um, they don't, they don't play up on it. Okay. There's no like, can you believe Pee Wee dates this lady? There's none of that. Yeah. Um, or at least that I remember. But, uh, it's funny.
Krispie is always great. He's married to a woman the size of his thumb that he keeps in his pocket. All right. I remember that. Very odd.
I didn't like that, yeah.
There's the scene where he fucks the Italian lady,
and they cut to like a train going through a tunnel
and a volcano and it's not stuff you wanna see
in a P .W. Herman movie.
I'm sorry, like I don't want sex jokes, it's weird.
Sure.
And then, what else was there?
Benicio del Toro's in it as a dog face boy.
Right, right.
it. It's just an odd picture. Yeah. And Phil Hartman has nothing to do with it. You can, his absence
is very clear. Yeah. You can see when Phil Hartman breaks off from the troupe and isn't the guy behind
the guy anymore. Right. It's just obvious. I wish Phil Hartman had ridden more. I think that's it,
really. It's the only movie I think you wrote. What? Peewee's big adventure. Yeah. I think he got
But I mean, in genius movie, I have been writing for David Allen Greer and watched the
entirety of the Carmichael show.
I thought, you know, let's see what his strengths are in Multicam before you start writing
for him.
It's the, in my opinion, the best Multicam sitcom in years.
It's a very good show.
I absolutely love it.
And I'm not a massive fan of Drod's stand up just being honest, but I think it is a
the jokes are fantastic they keep them coming hard and fast and they talk about
really serious shit and funny and kind of crazy ways. Yeah, I thought they did a
great job with it. I know Gerard he's a friend he's a great dude and I thought he
really pulled off a unique thing. Yeah, with that show. It's all on Hulu. It's
really good. I'm gonna go with my theme for this episode of Movie Corner is I'm
I'm gonna go with all the things I re -watched.
Okay.
The great outdoors.
Oh, do I love the great outdoors.
You know, as a kid, I wasn't a huge fan.
I re -watched it.
Holy shit, it's a great movie.
That's John Candy, Dan Acroid, and Net Benning.
First of all, Net Benning, when I was a kid,
I didn't get how funny she is in that movie.
She went over my head.
She's fucking brilliant.
That laugh she does through the whole movie,
she's fucking amazing in it.
Acroid, that was lost to me as a kid, that fucking speech he gives the kids, stay, apparently
escape from the cages, the army kept them in, found some local campers, slaughtered
an anthem.
Right.
So no more bad thoughts.
Yes.
Written by the great John Hughes.
Candy, of course, is, you know, wonderful in it and endearing as ever.
It's a great, it's the good version of summer rental, summer rental sucks.
You want it to be great.
Summer rental has several big laughs, including the classic dog food drop, which is one of the
funniest scenes of that time.
What's the dog food drop again?
When they realize they're in the black family's house, so then they got to get out really
quick.
And John can he's like, oh, just got to grab a few more things that you have this whole
bit and the family's staring at him.
And then he comes down with this like four hundred pound bag of dog food and then the dog beside him bottom breaks out
Floor can't he like slips in it the dog is eating it. It's incredible
That's a funny scene. I think it's funny when he cracks the raw egg on the dashboard
It's got some laughs. Yeah, overall. I don't think it's a great movie. No movie where where the main plot is a sailing race
No, it's as a favorite of a lot of 80s comedies built to a sailing race. Yeah, except one crazy summer
That's the one right sailing race movie that I had rafting really
now
You did you like the young teenage romantic sub plot the great outdoors which I remember grinding the movie to a massive halt every time it happened
Where he like puts the pool cue between her legs in a very weird by accident yeah, but I
No, I didn't, no, of course I have very little interest
in that subplot these days, but I will say,
as a kid that went on summer vacations with my folks
and had many summer week -long hookups where you were like,
I wish we could be boyfriend and girlfriend,
but we live in different worlds and all that shit.
I thought it was cool to see that in a movie
accurately portrayed, and I liked that the girl
was this tough character that was kind of like,
Yeah, I'm not like a fucking tourist attraction, right? You know, I thought that was pretty spot on so
So I thought it was well done and just boy. We got to break it up. Yeah, it's it's boring
You can't you got a scene where John candy eats a 98 ounce fucking steak
Yeah, I don't give a shit if this kid's falling in love
That's true. It's true
So I enjoyed it. I enjoyed it. Nice rewatch on that one. I rewatched the
great Edward Murphy in Arsenio Hall and coming to America really of course I've seen many times but I
mean talking about one of the best comedies ever one of the best comedies with with arguably the
greatest Easter egg in comedy history the trading place as well that's insane yeah nobody had ever
done anything like that before right that was insane yeah that movie is awesome the favorite character in
the movie. I mean, I really love the barbershop scenes. They're great. Of course.
Who's the guy with a little face who's like not in makeup? Do you ever act in anything else?
Yeah, he's been in stuff. I can't remember what, but yeah, yeah. The part where they're like,
I saw this happen. He's like, no, you didn't. No, you didn't. Then he goes, no, you did not.
me was the hardest laugh I rewinded like a kid I used to rewind that scene over
now I just kept rewinding it and watching it. Rocky Mossiano? Yeah it's an
awesome movie my favorite two characters are the people that the characters
Arsenio and Eddie Murphy play at the church fundraiser. Oh sure like Arsenio
as that disgusting preacher right and then Eddie Murphy as that singer it's like
like that, but it's, that is, that is a fucking masterful.
Yeah.
Piece of work.
Is that chocolate?
Uh, trivia question, you know who the young boy was getting his hair cut in the barber
shop, Saints?
No.
Cuba?
Gooding?
Junior?
Oh, you know what?
Maybe I did know that.
Cubes.
A couple of years before boys and the hood.
Uh, I'll close this out if that's okay with, uh, unless you got another one.
Now go ahead.
rewatch the usual suspects on an airplane. Sure. Kevin Spacey. I mean, what a fantastic movie
that's just a sad reminder of people you liked that went down. Yeah. Because they fucked
up. You're watching Kevin Spacey in this fucking tour de force performance. You're like, he's
gone. He fucked up. Right. Expert directing by Brian Singer. He's gone. Well, no, he's actually
I can't believe it's crazy that he's getting to direct another movie anyway walked off the set of the last one. They couldn't find him. Yeah
He's tainted
Obviously from from from what was his been said about him. Steve involved. Yeah, not to mention his personal life, but yeah
Steven Baldwin awesome in this move. Steve moment is so I forgot. I'll awesome Steven ballad
Now Steve bone isn't done anything bad, but he's like a super Christian like super right wing dude down
You're like, oh my god, I just can't relate to the guy anymore, but like I'm like, why can't you be Steven Baldwin again, man
He's fucking awesome in that movie. It's back that electric Steven Baldwin magic sliver. Um, fair game. Yeah
No slivers William Baldwin. Oh, okay
Steven is fair game with Cindy Crawford. I think that's also William. Oh, okay. Steven's was in posse bio dome. Yeah, yeah
I remember being so excited to sneak fair game because it was like an R -rated movie with Cindy Crawford. No, no, no, no. No, of course not.
First time they said fuck and I was like, oh no, what if it's rated R for the language? And I'm just watching a Cindy Crawford movie.
It was.
But plenty of great performances by people that are still out there doing it. Peter Green, Kevin Pollock is fantastic in it.
who else is in it, Gabriel Byrne?
Yeah.
The guy that died that plays, who's the Kobayashi?
You know, the guy that's like Kaiser Soze's like Spokesman.
Pete Postal Thwite.
I don't know what his name is.
He died.
British Pete Postal Thwite.
Yeah, the guy that comes in and he's like, it would be a great mistake.
Mr. Adelaide.
Yeah.
It's Pete Postal Thwite.
I don't know how you know that.
or can remember that. He was nominated for Best Supporting Actor for In The Name of the Father, 1994. Daniel DeLewis, directed by Jim Sheridan.
Quick, scary stuff. We got to get to the movie. We're 40 minutes in here.
Yeah, and I got a lot to say about this picture.
Quick, scary stuff. Go out, do yourself a favor. Go out there by the new Cypress Hill record.
They put out a new record. It came out on Friday. It's the first full record that DJ Mugs, their original DJ producer, has produced in like 20 years for them.
It's back to their roots. In my opinion, it is, it is their fifth album. It has not their ninth album. It's the one that should have came after Cypressil 4. It's dark. It's spooky. It's stony as hell.
but now it's great. Hold on. You didn't say spooky in there, which I guess
qualifies, but this is not a scary stuff. It's a very dark. No, absolutely not. You
would never let this fly. If I just recommended a rap album, I enjoyed and
scary stuff. No, no. The tables have been turned. If you listen to this thing, now I've
learned how to do it and you've lost it. If you listen to this thing, it's got a
a horror element to it.
Listen to it first, and then tell me no.
Does Dracula have a verse?
Let me ask you a few questions.
Yes or no?
It's a very dark one.
No.
Does Frankenstein have a verse?
He does.
Fuck.
Does a mummy sing?
I'll look at some point.
Yes.
And he says, word to your mummy.
Okay. A few times, word to your daddy.
Does anyone say the phrase?
is whatever happened to my Transylvania twist at any time.
That gets said, whatever happens in the torture chamber,
stays in the torture chamber.
That gets said a few times.
I'm not as good as puns as you are.
No, you're not.
There's probably, I don't think you're gonna revel in it.
I don't think that counts, frankly, but okay.
Listen to the record and tell me it doesn't count.
Well, I guess I'll watch it with the light song
Because it sounds so scary to it. You can't watch your record
Schmuck
All right, you can watch it spin on the on the player. That's what I meant
Let's get to
Yeah, what man speaking of records maybe we do a
Do we do in a me but today?
I might have worked today. Oh, yeah, for Christ. I'm sorry. Sunday. We can go next weekend
I don't want to go next week. I want to go today. I went while you were gone also. We're hanging out. All right. Let's go to the let's go
Well, get some food. We'll go to a Meba. I'm all I already agreed. Don't push it. Yeah, good. All right
Folks, we'd like to talk to you about the 2018
Film Mandy. I'm gonna look up the director's name because if ever a director deserved a little shout out
It's a tough name.
It's like Panos Padanko.
It's his father, a little movie trivia.
His father directed the film Cobra
in several other 80s films.
Yes.
And while you look up this guy's name,
if Panos Cosmotos.
Yeah.
Director was George P. Cosmotos,
who directed Tombstone.
Yeah, that's his dad.
Yes.
And if you watch this movie,
and also his other movie,
Beyond the Black Rainbow,
I think that's what it's called.
More so this movie though, you get the feeling
that what he was trying to, I got the feeling
that what he was trying to create with Mandy was
the 80s movie you wish existed.
Yes.
It takes place in 1983.
It looks the way every VHS cover of an 80s action movie
made you think the movie itself was gonna look.
Right.
It's got all the elements of an 80s movie,
it's got horror, it's got action, it's got revenge,
It's got crazy violence, but it somehow does not have to me that like tongue -in -cheek
spoof of the 80s quality that like a
Drive sort of has in spots things like that where it's an homage. This felt like its own thing too
Like a mix of that. I agree some crazy news shit. I agree. I felt like he was not being cheeky about the 80s
I felt like he was saying like
What my exact impression was
He was like remember when you saw the box for macobre with Stallone right and you thought it was gonna be like this
But it wasn't yeah, here's what it when I thought it was gonna be like and you're like holy shit
It's a beautifully shot movie. I would say should win best cinematography
I haven't seen anything close and while we're at it
I'd give best actor Nicholas Cage
I haven't seen anything they can compare to this performance this year cage is great everybody's great cage
That's seen where I'm actually I'm going to go see it in a theater just because I want to like take an edible and
Go rock that movie because how fun would that be but I rented it last night and turn on the lights out and still had a great time
But like that seemed with Nicholas Cage where he's like screaming in the bathroom and his underwear and keeps pounding vodka. Yeah
I was so glad to be able to not watch that in a theater with everyone laughing at that right because I actually found it like a moving scene
Yeah, he plays the pain of it so well that when he does get a little kind of ash from evil dead in the last half hour
It still feels pretty grounded and funny
No, I I love that scene and I love that that scene started a weird trend for a few scenes in the film
Of of him abusing substances to get through his revenge right ladder
For some reason he is a bottle of vodka stashed in the bathroom
room, which makes you think -
It's not a haul, it clearly.
Yeah, it makes you think maybe he was dry and now he's,
you know, that's where his bottle was hidden.
So he does that.
Then he, when he kills that demon,
he does the fucking coke off the table.
Yeah, awesome.
And then when he kills the other demon,
he takes the cigarette off the ground
and lights that and smokes it.
So I like that they kind of had this weird,
like, substance trend that he was kind of off the wagon.
Well, at the end, it was acid, I believe.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, yeah, he also takes that acid. Yeah, yeah, I love like I like the more subtle humor more than the kind of more obvious wise cracks my favorite being when the old I guess that's Bill Duke he's awesome is like telling them that monologue about it that awesome monologue
Then at the end he's like the odds are very good that you're going to die and they could over Nicholas Cage and he goes hold on be negative
That was awesome. Yeah, that was really funny
But it was so solemn and serious in the first hour and a half that they really bought like a chainsaw
Dual and all that crazy shit
Because like you really believed he loved Mandy
Those Satanists were some of the best cast freaks of all time
That guy when he goes into his his leaders bedside that whole scene. I was like what am I watching here?
Yeah, and that my favorite of that pack was the gray hair lady. Yeah time out of our body and
Yeah, and that was the one thing I was disappointed with in the film.
Yeah, I thought she was going to get a really amazing on -screen kill because she was so fucking
devious and so full of shit.
And I did like that it cut away and then you just see her head roll into the room, but
I will I she's a character where you're like I want to see her get it.
Yeah, as much as you want to see the main the main leader guy get it right while screaming
I'll suck your dick.
Yeah, that that was a odd choice is that what you want. Yeah, why would you think that's what he wants because he's I mean he presented his cock to the room he clearly thinks he's hot shit. I followed that that plot.
Wait, the leader thinks he's hot shit. Yeah. Oh, you're saying like he's like why wouldn't you want me to suck your dick? Yeah, I think he thinks he's some highly sexual being it was definitely something sexual going on with the guy that comes to his bedside.
He was clearly fucking the woman.
Yeah, and then he was fucking the younger woman.
Right.
And then Mandy was gonna be his latest woman.
Yeah.
Talk about brilliant writing, too.
That thing where he does that whole fucking ten -minute speech
when they're on the acid about what he has found
and how he's the chosen one and he selected her and all that shit.
And he's playing that music that he wrote.
And then the scene ends with him with her being like,
is this your song?
You wrote it?
Yeah, it's about you. Yeah, and then she just starts laughing in his face. Yeah, and you're like, Oh, they're gonna kill her now
But yeah, that was such great writing. It was fucked up, man
And then they stayed on Nicholas Cage's face for so long like
Playing like the anguish of watching it was but it was it was a great movie
I thought I really loved it. Then like of course all the visuals are awesome the drug visuals
But then even like that scene early on where it's him and his wife and a canoe
And they do like this overhead pam or it just keeps going up looking down on them. I was like that
Probably took a day to set up on what I'm assuming was a very low -budget movie. There's no reason for it to be in there
The director clearly just wanted to like make every shot and scene awesome and he did yeah
There were there were scenes where I was like I would love to have that framed on my wall like the
Yes, take a picture and put it up somewhere
Now it was a beautiful film. I enjoyed it thoroughly my favorite of the year
thus far. I haven't seen this close to it, but yeah. I would, uh, what do I agree with that?
Black clansman. Well, Christ, we're at the end of the year. Well, Black clansman, yeah,
was was way up there. You know, the same, same been a great year. Solo for me was way up there.
And I know you're not going to put it in the same categories of Mandy, but I, you know,
I give it a B plus. Um, but man, this was, as, look, I can say this much, as far as horror movies go,
This was where this type of genre of film. This was the best I've seen in a long yeah since get out
I would say yes the the horror elements of it are actually really spooky too like all the face
Blending stuff and all that was really freaky. That was freaky and it had still had kind of a homemade quality like nothing felt
ILM me
No, it was all practical effects. Yeah, there was like a lot of like lighting shit. Yeah, which really worked well
which is tough to do because that can come off very quickly as like student
filmy yeah if you don't do it right and he did it so well yeah I just thought
it was a great movie yeah this is the first movie in a long time that I plan to
watch again I have it for the 48 hour rental or whatever and I'll probably
watch it again tonight I loved it I will probably buy a blue ray of this same
here. And I've seen, I think I've seen beyond the black rainbow. I want to go back and
rewatch it. I know it's a little more of a sci -fi picture, but I haven't, but I'm going
for it. It's on shutter. So I'm going to go back and watch it. But anyway, that's, that's
Mandy for you folks to hogs up. I will say to Pano's, this movie's doing very well, Mandy,
Like way better than expected and it stayed in theaters a lot longer than expected
Don't I don't want to see your name on like Dr. Strange for
I want you to make some more movies like this get a little bigger budget if you need to
But don't go make these fucking superhero movies Pano's you're too good for that
I mean talk about the changing of the tide the predator, which is still haven't seen me neither which I would like to see would love to tank
Yeah fucking tanked
Well, I mean, no, it's it's like maybe finally this big budget shit is kind of
Going the way the dodo kind of like it did when like Nirvana and Pulp Fiction came out right and you know
And we can get back to some
Some more actual like you know genuine filmmaking. I hope so
Folks our live show is October 20th. There's a 7 30 and a 9 30 it is sold out
Again, I don't know if I want to check with the venue if they have some sort of stand -by -line cool kids Friday night on Fox
D Patrick Walsh on Twitter and Instagram and
I did a master class podcast. It's on Stitcher Premium right now with Sean Clements and Ben Rogers
Joe DeRosa comedy on Instagram though you won't see me there much these days
Almost phased. I'm almost completely phased out of social media
you, which is great. But anyway, I'm still on there. You don't see them any happy. I have
an internal piece that I have a hard time describing, having it out of my life. But anyway,
I am on there. I will be headlining the Philadelphia punchline Thanksgiving weekend, two shows
Friday, two shows Saturday, you know, right after your turkey dinner on Thursday. So come
on stage just got hanging out the bottom of a dress shirt.
Yeah, that kind of thing, licking grease off my fingers.
Yeah, wishbone hanging out of pocket.
We'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.
Also, there's another one coming up today.