Summer is here and Bet MGM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer or check out
our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and the Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bet MGM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Bet MGM in game sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal, durable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided in
applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamber.
The football season is full of guarantees.
And here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October.
If your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 Plus.
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamber.
Offer not available in all states, terms apply, see fanatic sportsbook app.
Hey folks, we'll see you in hell.
It's the podcast about movies.
Just movies anymore, you know.
Used to be hard and sci -fi, fantasy now, you know, these other genres have been creeping
in.
Why don't we, don't put baby in a corner.
That's right.
I'm here with that.
Jennifer Gray.
Skies.
Patty Sways.
All right.
How did Jennifer feel when she heard pat trick Sways, he died?
Go ahead.
Gray.
Kind of just sad, really.
That's what sad is.
It's kind of slapping me in the head with tail.
His asshole is right in your face.
What I want to need it after a long day, Joe's moved into somehow the more the most exclusive
parking center in all of Los Angeles.
You can find a spot in Beverly Hills faster than around here.
I can't believe there's no parking around here.
I finally find a spot and it's like no parking from 6 p .m. to 8 a .m.
It's just like an abandoned spot under a tree somewhere.
Like, okay, go up to sunset, can't park here 6 to 8.
What time is it?
6 .49.
Jesus Christ.
Tyred.
You're having a hell of a day.
Tyred of it.
Patty.
I mean, does that tell you anything?
This is what I want to work.
Patty's dressed like Rosanne on the early seasons.
Yeah, like pilot episode.
Sweat pants, hoodie.
It's dark.
I want you.
Look, let's not discuss it on the show, but I'm concerned about you.
I'm concerned about myself.
I mean that sincerely.
Patty and I, the testament to our friendship, we had a text exchange today that would have
two years ago come, turned into a fucking World War III, but dissolved a fuse very quickly
with both of us, almost saying I love you to want another.
Well, I just, you know, I confessed to Joe.
I was like, look, until you texted me, I was unaware what day of the week it was.
So like, forgive me if my scheduling's a little hazy.
I've been up about 48 hours.
I almost went to the red bull today, but I knew I would just wind up feeling even shittier
so I didn't do it.
My entire room is ill.
There's no one there.
It's fallen apart.
Jesus Christ.
All they get a multi cam on the air, you know, it's exactly right.
It's exactly right.
It's like the people in the White House aren't this stressed.
That's honestly true.
And it could be so easy.
At the end of the day, it's that the people holding the strings have a fundamental lack
of understanding about why people watch television.
But let me leave it at that.
Fair enough.
I'm not talking about it.
Well, I'm going to get off this topic.
Folks, let's get on with the show if we could, and at the same time, on with the Joe Man.
Terrible one.
All right.
It's okay.
It can't all be just a terrible one.
I don't hate it.
Scooters gone.
That's new in my life.
So now tell me about that.
Is this something you can talk about?
Because I know you were starting to rant about it the other night.
It's excited about this scooter.
I bought it.
Called the shop when I bought it said, I don't need a driver's license, right?
Yes.
Because my license has expired.
And I'm having a hard time getting in for a test for a new one.
Repeatedly.
Yes.
Yeah, you're fine.
You're fine.
By this thing, wheeling all over fucking town and this thing.
Meanwhile, there's a little space on the back that looks like it's for a license plate.
So I call the manufacturer today.
I go, are you supposed to send me a license plate for something for this thing?
They're like, no, no, no, no.
You got to go get that yourself when you register it.
I go register it.
I thought you didn't have to register this thing.
You said, no, you got to register it.
Why wouldn't you have to register it?
I was like, well, you don't need a license to drive it.
And he was like, what are you talking about?
You need a license.
Long story short, I find out the, yeah, this thing is not a fucking, they told me at the dealership
that it was classified as an e -bike, even though it didn't have pedals.
It's not, it's actually considered a mo -ped, which is a level above scooter.
So I look up maximum penalty for driving without a license in L .A.
Six months in jail.
Whoa.
Yeah.
So you could have been arrested.
So I called the place.
I'm like, guys, you sold me this thing.
You told me I had a license.
I'm driving around all over the place.
I could literally went to jail.
Do you realize that?
And with, I will say this, with very little pushback, they gave me my money back.
They had a strict no returns policy.
I got into a little bit with it, I got into it a little bit with the woman that it sold me the bike.
Because she was kind of doing the whole like, well, I thought you meant motorcycle light.
I'm like, you didn't think that I meant that.
Yeah.
I gave you an expired driver's license and you let me test drive it.
She's like, well, for a test drive, sure, it's like, you can't test drive anything with an expired license.
That's not how this works.
Right.
So she then kind of, in a roundabout way, put me, I thought she was giving me the run -around.
She gave me the owner of the shop's email.
And I'm like, you got to be kidding me, man.
She won't even give me his number.
But I, lo and behold, I emailed the guy he called me back within minutes.
Okay.
Was apologetic.
Called me later again that day.
He's like, I'm just going to give you your money back.
Came today, did the refund over the phone right in the lot there and rode off with the scooter.
Beautiful.
So, you know, nothing lost, nothing gained.
It was, you know, I got to ride a scooter for free for a month.
Right.
And that's where we're at.
Now, I don't know what the statute of limitations on this crime is.
So people, you know, if your brother or your husband is a cop or your mom or your aunt or whoever,
don't go blabbing about what I did, you know.
Right.
I don't want to have to fly to Bermuda until this thing blows over.
I guess I can just take us over to Pat's movie corner.
This is a broken man.
Folks, I should tell you,
we're, it took me about an hour to be able to form sentences today.
So, I understand you're lucky.
You're lucky you're getting what you're getting.
Listen, I understand.
I've seen all these movies.
They're all like pre -Christmas.
I feel like, but I'm just like getting to them now.
What did I watch?
Well, you know what I watched the other day, Joe?
That's what you talked about last week.
You HF starring Weird Al Yankovic.
Pepe, Pepe, Pepe, Pepe, Pepe, Pepe, Pepe, Pepe, Pepe, Pepe, Pepe, Pepe, Pepe, Pepe, Pepe, Pepe, Pepe, Pepe, Pepe, Pepe, Pepe.
Well, A, after Joe and I wrapped here last Friday, we had a great hang and watched that Harvey
Leeds State of Shock video by Weird Al that Joe had told me about.
And I screamed laughing.
I had a great time with it.
And I also watched the John Candy Food Repair, which I found hilarious as well.
Yeah, then we watched another sketch where John Candy just basically beat the shit out of Guilda Radner for five minutes
And that sketch was hilarious. Wait, what was the person that they were like they were oh, it was mailman
She went to the post office and she didn't put a return address on her package
Correct, and she's like why can't I just send it and like they take Dave Thomas takes her in the back
And he's like time to play good postman bad postman John Candy comes in his bad postman
Yeah, he's throwing her into these boxes and God bless Guilda Radner. You could see in the sketch
It was like she's sick. It's towards the end of her life and she's still doing these pratfalls and everything she was very funny in it as well. Yeah, she's amazing
Never never a good movie career though, you know like she never even found one vehicle that was a good movie for her
I feel like she didn't get it much of a shot, right? I mean she fits I mean haunted honeymoon and hanky -panky
You know she did pictures. Oh, yeah, I guess those dead did go on for about a decade
There's Gene wilder ones and I mean none of them were any good. They never really gave her anything funny
Anywho you a chef
While it did make me laugh out loud as much as it did when I was a kid, let's say
It's just a very charming movie. Yeah, and the whole you know, it's not just a collection of sketches, which would I you know
I think have bored me, but like the story where he just picks up all these misfits and
They all get their little moment of triumph in the end. They're all bullied in some terrible way throughout the film and they all get their triumph in the end
You know, it shows the heart behind the hair if you will weird out as a very sweet side
Billy Barty is great in it, you know getting his revenge Michael Richards. I forget you know
Basically playing a mentally handicapped person, which I didn't think of him as that as a kid right but it's you know
It's clear that he is, but he doesn't with respect for the character. It's a really good performance. Yeah, he's great at it
Fran Drescher is wonderful. She's great in it
It's a great movie. I love the film. It originally was supposed to be
like a
Walter middie. Yes, thing
Where was just about this guy with an overactive imagination?
Which happens in the beginning? Yeah, and then they kind of never go back to that premise
And also the part of the best friend was offered to Seinfeld. He turned it down
Right. Yes, I we we were at the same Wikipedia page apparently. Yeah, I watched some of the special features
There's a new shout -out factory DVD. It's great. I wanted to draw back of the film is I'm sure they told me had to have a music video
And I don't understand why he didn't do one of his classic parodies. He does this
Beverly Hillbillies. It's basically just singing the Beverly Hillbillies theme to the tune of
Money for nothing by dire straits and sting and
It's lame and the animation sucks and it really bogs down the film right in the middle when it's kind of taken off
One minor quibble the rest of the movie. I really love
He was pitching also that's another little fact about weird out
He was pitching that Beverly Hillbillies premise like around a couple people said no
To like pet so he got it in his head that he wanted to do a
song about the Beverly Hillbillies for some reason he was pitching it around the song like I read that he had approached
I was Prince I think
and to do a parody of kiss
But it was gonna be about the Beverly Hillbillies or something and Prince said no. Yeah, it's on his page
We read like the the people that denied him right the whatever
and
What was one of the other ones one one of them was oh
Eminem approved the parody of lose yourself but didn't approve the video. Okay
Because he I guess you thought it would be bad for his image yourself. What was the what was this song?
snooze yourself about hitting the alarm in the morning
You're gonna be shocked when I tell you this
Jews yourself and it was about converting Judaism good Lord. It's kind of a
Kind of a heavy topic for a weird outside. We have
Not a joke in the thing. Okay. No, I don't know what it was called it was called like
I don't think it's a play on the name. It's just he just wraps it though. All right
Folks, I watched a little picture called leprechaun two Wow
sequel to leprechaun one the original sequel to leprechaun one not leprechaun returns that
Hard thing that was just released
What's the story of leprechaun two I'll tell you the story
He is in a thousand years ago. He falls in love with his slaves daughter. Okay
his
Slave won't let him take his daughter so he thwarts his efforts to to to land the daughter
And then and then the leprechaun says in a thousand years. I will wake and I will find my bride then okay
You know, they're just kind of playing by the sea of their pants at this point with these rules sure
You know anyway thousand years later in big bright Los Angeles the leprechaun awakes and of course
There's a girl there that looks exactly like the girl. He was in love with a thousand years prior. It's sort of a Dracula thing and
bad acting and
Loosely written plotlines and so I will say this about the movie it
You can see the effort
It's not very well directed
You can see the effort and I like that. I like that. You can tell they were trying to make a fun horror movie
The kills in it are fantastic. They're so great
Practical effect kills all right
I've had more fun watching it than I ever do the first one and
I would quite frankly return to it and a little fun movie fact the guy that plays Jack Klampus
In Seinfeld is in it. Okay, he plays like a drunk that owns like a tour of the horror
Hills of Hollywood. Yeah
And he's like sort of the comic relief and his death is really great
He he makes the leprechaun promise him that he'll give him a bunch of gold. Okay, and the leprechaun does
And then all the gold appears inside of his stomach so his stomach just starts
Bloating out and clinking and clanking. It's it's it's actually some very cool practical effects. Is he explode?
I think so. Yeah, I forget all right, but it's when did you watch it?
We could go
That's troubling you that I can't remember if he exploded. Yeah, it was a week ago. I mean look
I got to be honest with you leprechaun too is not a film
You know, it's not the paper. You know what I mean? You're not sitting down going. It's not spotlight. You're not going
I got to really keep track
Would now do other things while you're watching it
If you reference as like the kind of movie that that rivets you to your seat the paper starring Michael Keaton and Glenn close
Wasn't that Tom Hanks movie that just came out called the paper the post. Yeah, that's what I meant
That wasn't fucking riveting either. I just meant like it's not a newsroom drama. You're dealing with it
You get up you walk over to the window. You go get a drink of water, right?
You know the paper not a terrible film. I believe he does explode because he keeps going get it out of me
Sure, and then I think it's stomach explode. Sure
I
Watched a film that I saw opening night in theaters one of two movies I can recall where opening night me and my buddy
Ben were the only two people in the theater one was the now beloved cult classic office space
The other is the very little beloved by a very small cult
cabin boy. I
Loved the cheesy sets and effects and I thought there was a lot of big laughs to be had
When I was a kid. I loved like the cupcake flying up and spitting tobacco at him and stuff
I was just you know
I didn't even smoke weed at this point. I was just I thought all that stuff was funny as an adult
I find that less funny. I find Chris Elliott
about equally funny and annoying and equal measure but sometimes the he's so annoying he's funny and
And what I found particularly great this time out were the four performances of the seahands on the boat
Okay, Brian Doyle Murray
You know like just these like old gruff dudes. You were an odd like comedy team. They cracked me up
I know Brian do a Murray and Chris Elliott because Brian Nolan Murray was also on get a life. That's correct. Yes
I I love I love older
Chris Elliott stuff is newer stuff
There's something
Eagle heart
It's like two I don't know what it is. It's two adult swimming or something
I don't know but I like that older Chris Elliott stuff. I don't like the film cabin boy though. I like the first like half hour
Yeah, and then once they get out to see and it gets all like Bertnie. I'm kind of like yeah
Yeah, I mean, I watched a pretty sizable documentary about it with Adam Resnick and Chris Elliott
They talked about just how absolutely heartbroken they were when it came out and their agents were like you'll never work again and they sold a
pitch
Like a TV pitch like bought it in the room and that they were not to their car all excited like let's go get a beer and celebrate and
Somebody in the meeting told their boss who they hired a pitch from and they were like the cabin boy guys call them now in
Cancel Wow, so they're like driving to the bar and they call them are like yeah, we just realized you guys did cabin boy
So the project's done Jesus and essentially neither of these guys worked for many many years
Cohen brothers, I mean, I excuse me fairly brothers used them to great effect in Kingpin used
Chris Elliott and something about Mary, but you know, he didn't really get to do anything creatively just just as an actor and that that sucks
But the movie Adam Resnick is like no if it was me and Chris Elliott and we got our chance to do a movie we would have done a
One million dollar thing where Chris works in an office or something. Yeah, where he's like a bluser right yeah, yeah, exactly
But they were like Tim Burton loves the show get a life and he wants to do he wants to get back to his peewee's big adventure roots
And just work with on a small budget with a with a comedian and have some fun and
Chris Elliott was like amazing
Well, we'll write this for Tim Burton
So they spent forever getting it into this C adventure with all these big sets and the
Bominable snowman's and everything which is not their comfort zone
Tim Burton drops out but felt bad about dropping out so he goes you should have Adam direct it and I'm like
I don't direct how am I gonna do this big budget action movie and that shows you know
The movie is not well directed, but I do think it looks cool. It's got a nice energy to it
It's very short and director is funny in it and I just had a good time with it
I liked it and if you've never seen the film do yourself a favor as David
Letterman says in the film
Watch it at least for the letterman scene because the David Letterman cameo amaze the only time I've ever seen him in a movie and
He it's one of the funniest four -minute scenes I've ever seen
Keeps calling Chris Elliott Jennifer. Yeah, which is
The the weirdest name you could pick like you know, you'd think Sally
Beverly is always in there. Yeah Nancy or something, but Jennifer is such like a weird choice
Yeah, I mean if you have no interest in this film
I'm sure you can find that clip on YouTube and it's incredible
I think the only time Letterman's ever been in a movie although he almost got the
Lead role in airplane the Robert Hayes role. Oh, yeah, okay anyway fun fact
sticking on the course of the first film I talked about I watched the howling two
Okay, I've seen one but not the sequels one is an interesting film. It's it's you know
It's a cool flick. It's not Joe Tante's best work, and it's certainly not the best werewolf movie I've ever seen
But it's a solid horror flick and it spawned a
series of many sequels obviously
The howling two stars Christopher Lee and was panned people hated it
I thought this thing was fucking great. I thought it was impeccably shot
The director did a lot of really wonderful stuff with flash cut flash cuts and edits and things and in these weird inserts
Throughout the entire film the acting could use a kick in the pants
But the lead actor the lead female actor in it is quite good and Christopher Lee is always is mesmerizing
Unfortunately, the head villainous vampire is terrible and the head male lead is really bad
but
It's worth the price of admission for Christopher Lee for some really fun practical effects for some good deaths
And it's just a mood piece. It's it's very very well shot. It's very well shot. I don't know who depaid it
But whoever did knew what the fuck he was doing so go check out the howling two. Okay
How many howlings are there? I was like seven. Oh wow or nine or six. I don't know somewhere in there
I
Think we're up to three or four fucking how to train your dragons
I think they think they think they would have learned how to how to train it by now
Yeah, I love like I saw like a headline today like how to train your dragon three doesn't bring in the bucks at the box office
It's like and even though they were still making these fucking. No, I think think everybody's about done
It's like when a new ice age comes out. Yeah, still making ice age movies or mono as a squirrel or whatever Dennis
Lyrius like a mongoose yeah
Mongoose smoking cigarettes. Yeah, that's a good message for the kids
Well, he's not really smoking. Oh, I'm just saying like, you know, it's a mongoose with a tood. It's right. It's Lyrius
I
Dusted off another old chestnut goes by the name of splash
Tom Hanks Darrell Hannah
John Candy Eugene Levy I
I
Remember this being one of those and I've mentioned a few of them lately on the show where like when I was a kid
It's like holy shit a movie with Eugene Levy John Candy and Tom Hanks
It's also rated PG and there's nudity in it quite a bit of nudity
I just thought
What a dream and I'd rent it fairly often and I'd always be like
Yeah, I didn't laugh much. I know it's a beloved classic. It was a huge hit. Is it funnier now that we're older?
No, it's very charming. I enjoyed every minute of it
Yeah, that's how I remembered it. You know, Hanks and his prime
There's almost nobody better in terms of like especially a guy who can handle the romantic side and the funny side
There's very few better. He gets and we don't get this anymore out of Hanks. That's classic annoyed
Hanks. Yeah, it's a lot of like come on Freddy
He's getting really wound up through the whole movie. Yeah, well, it's get that kind of Hanks anymore
You never get it
I thought it was gonna be Lady Killers and then he was playing Colonel Sanders when I went to see it
But like League of the Run was the end of it
League of the Run last time you ever got like classic Hanks. Yes, and a true classic John love its performance
Who will be coming up shortly on the cool kids and was an unbelievably sweet man
I loved him and he was very very funny. That's good
I was doing his voice all week. He had a line that we we've all been doing all week in the room where he goes
He set up a joke and then he goes that's my little joke
And at every time I would pitch him a joke
He goes do you want me to do it as me? How do you want me to do it as your impression of me because I couldn't help but say the line in his voice
That's great. Which some actors take as a line reading man
They don't appreciate it, but he was very cool about it. That's great. I just was like love it set up man
We're not looking where we want the hits. He's calling already right or you see him
Do you have you shot? Can you get him a message? No, we've shot it last week. All right worst week in my life. All right
Well, not because he's in one of my favorite tells from the crypts ever. Oh, okay. I want to let him know he was you know
He hung around one of the talk. He's a nice man
He's in an awesome tells the crib with John Aston about what it told him a failing actor who gets cast in a
Rendition of Macbeth. He's really it's a great episode and he's funny in it and then it also he's also great in the dramatic
Portions I love them in the opening scene of happiness some great dramatic work from John love. It's the beginning of happiness
Anyway, the hell was I talking about splash and you know, Ron Howard's second film after night shift was a huge hit
Laulgan's and Babalu Mandel wrote it who did a lot of the best movies of the 80s and early 90s a lot of them directed by Ron Howard
But they did you know parenthood and
Cities slickers they wrote all kinds of like you know classic, but multiplicity, which doesn't get enough love anyway
Splash is charming the romance is good Darryl Hannah is naked a lot especially for PG the hair doesn't cover the boobs as I thought it did
They're pretty out there
And John candy, okay, he's very funny in it
He plays a racket ball while drinking from a can of beer and then that's a great scene hits
Hit some and I watched this when I watched the A &E biography of John candy which had footage from his funeral that was real hard to watch
People just sobbing but candy they said in this biography that he did this in one shot
They they had cleared like half a day to do it
And they were like yeah, you know, we'll probably need about four hours till we get the shot right and it's just John candy
It's like all right. I'm up. I'm gonna serve drops the ball hits it
It bounces off the wall straight back at him and hits him in the head and then he falls forward onto his face
So John candy walks out actual beer and he had drank like 12 that morning actual beer in his hand
Hits the ball it bounces directly back into his head
He lands the pratfall perfectly and then he was like all right. Let's go get drunk
Because they had four hours for him the schedule. I mean just a
Dream Eugene Levy's all you know, he's kind of annoying in it. He's got that old fro
The the greatest line in comedy history and film is in splash
The little boat no Jay Okreson and I say it to this day and laugh hysterically
Okay, but when she shows up naked at the Statue of Liberty the tour guide goes BOTCHY BALL
That yeah since I was six years old
Like levels me that was screenwriter Laul Gains. Oh, I didn't know that that that potchy bull
Yeah, and that's what always made me love the tour scene in so I'm married an expert in crowd
I was sort of at a little nod to splash that scene is incredible and so I'm right now. I watched and I like hang on
Oh, sorry hang on because I was gonna say my favorite line, which is sorry Tom Hanks is knees to knees with this old sailor like fat guy in a tiny little boat
And they're out in the ocean, and it's like this sputtering along or whatever then it dies
So John Tom Hanks is like what what's going on? What's going on?
And he goes I don't know it looks like the engine's broke. I'll be right back
So he jumps into the water and starts swimming Tom Hanks like you can't leave me here in the middle of the ocean
He goes be right back. I'm gonna get the little boat and then Tom Hanks looks around this tiny boat goes the little boat
Incredible and that is the old frustrated Hanks that you don't see anymore
The one thing that always bum me out about that movie as a kid was the entire movie is overcast
It is a little gloomy. Yeah, there's not a sun shiny shot that they're always done with that doc with like where the fish come in and everything like
It's a gloomy film a lot of doc stuff. Yeah, I
Saw horror new war, but I'll tell you what it's on. I want to watch that. I think we should actually review it for the show
Right to an excellent documentary. We've never really done a documentary
All right, we'll save that and instead I'm gonna jump to a different documentary that I watched
There's also about a 80s horror movie staying on theme
Unnorthon untold the path to pet cemetery. I think I've maybe talked about this. I
Maybe have talked about this on the show. I don't know that there's enough here to that we could review it
Right, okay, horror noir. There's a lot to talk about. It's great, but
And I want to talk about this pet cemetery documentary because I just re -watched it and it's also gonna lead us into screaming in I
You know, look, it's it's a low budget. Don't know Frills documentary
You're not getting any Stephen King interviews in this thing, but you're getting interviews with
Basically everybody else that was in the movie from the man they had to hire to play Zelda
Right because they needed somebody so skinny with literally no shape to his body that they had to hire a guy and
Then put him in like this bone makeup. Yeah, which makes it even like that scene even
Stranger, you know what I mean, right and
Believe Pat and Oswald sites that is the scariest scene in horror movie history. It's the scariest thing
I've ever seen in a movie in my life. I watched that I watched pet cemetery with my friend Brian Peck
for a sleepover when we were about 10 or 11 my mom let me rent it that scene came on we were white as ghosts
We were so fucking scared and we made a vow to each other that we would stay up all night because we were too scared to go to sleep
Yeah, and we would keep all the lights on and I kept up my end of the bargain. He fell asleep. Okay
I felt so betrayed and I was so terrified, but anyway
You could have just stopped it. Well, no, it was after the movie. It was like later tonight like yeah
Anyway, we it's a great doc. They interview everybody. They talk about where Steve the place where Stephen King wrote the book
Which was in was in a was in a room that he rented in a in like the local, you know, was that a coke book for him?
I know misery was
Dude, it's like it's like late 70s early 80s. It's way earlier king than I thought it was
I think misery and kujo are supposed to be like his cokeyest and the shining was his alcoholiest. I think
But he was teaching at a college up in Maine
They show you the real pet cemetery. It's based on they interview the lady who started the pet cemetery that it's based on
Yeah, she's like I can't believe it my little pet cemetery became a book like right
It's a really cool little documentary. They talk about what it was like on the set lots of love for Fred Gwyn
People can't say enough about this guy like everybody's like you just wanted to hug the guy. Yeah
Hey y 'all on going up to that pet cemetery. Are you yeah with the kitty cats and their the dogs now right the the famous line
Yeah
Can you do a main accent?
I
Got a got a not on that road
All right, that's pretty good. I feel more like I'm doing a Fred Gwyn impression. Yeah
Kind of like your love. It's thing. It's not really that we're doing the accent rapidly
We're doing the guy that does it right. I always do a
Fred Gwyn when I'm dry and I was a vine of mine
Whatever I'm driving to Vegas, you see a sign that says this way towards ghost town road
All right, so I always do and the vine I was in a rocking chair on a porch
That was rocking back and forth and I was like you teens ain't going up that a ghost town road, are you?
Last group of teens went up a ghost town road didn't come back down
That was the whole bit like the guy at the beginning of like a cabin fever type film. Yeah, yeah, I got you congrats
By the way getting joke of the day on a that was cool. I hadn't seen that punch. What was it wasn't punchline? It was up
Some comedy club funny bone
Which is I believe is the St. Louis comedy club
But if you've played the funny bone in St. Louis. I have not but I've played other funny bones here
Let me let me do you the theme song from when I was a little kid that they would play on the radio. It's it's awful
Here you go funny bone
comedy
Funny bone. It's a comedy club. Jesus like that
Like with that that shitty like trombone voice where the guys like yeah
I got to tell you you're in stiff comp when you're when to get the shittiest comedy club song
Yeah, it might just take in shittiest. It's real bad
I ever talked to this show about the store and their commercials called dirt cheap in St. Louis. Yeah
It was this place and unfortunately it was before I drank but it was kind of like a precursor to Bevmont
It's called dirt cheap and they had like clearly off the back of a truck
Whiskey beer cigarettes, etc
but and so anyway, they did commercials from when I could remember watching TV till when I left Missouri when I was 23 years old and
It was this guy who looked like he had been drinking the big like the the tall Jack Daniels
like the the one that like kind of waged your arm down and look like he had been having one of those every day
since he was 16 years old and he was about
60 or he might have been 30 he like no one had ever aged more than this man
He looked terrible like his teeth were rotten. You can find these ads. I believe on YouTube
But he's a terrible looking man and he he's the owner of dirt cheap fun fun
He insisted on being the commercials and there was a chicken, which was a man in like a stained chicken suit
The yellow with the orange beak chicken suit
So it really showed the the dirt and like that they hadn't had the suit cleaned
So the chicken's going around and then there would always be a
big jugged woman
Like some sleazy skank if you will not to judge in like a bikini or something
So then they'd be like dirt cheap so the the the chicken guy would go cheap cheap
fun fun that was kind of their hook
then
The hideous man who owned it the hot woman would look at him and
His face would be replaced by like Fabio
Then it would come back to the ugly man which would actually make you jump. It was so horrifying
And he would go come on down to dirt cheap
And remember like he was out of breath
The more of our whiskey and beer she drinks the better you look
So a pirate ran dirt cheap. That's right. All right. You can find it online. It's the real deal
I'll look it up
Back to pet cemetery on earth and untold you know folks you get it
It's a fucking documentary about the movie
It's worth watching you you get to learn some fun stuff. I'm excited to get to scream in in
Second trailer for pet cemetery
2019 has been released
And they have made some
major
Changes in this thing. Yeah. I don't know how I feel about it
Starting with this
One of the things they say in the documentary
That everybody sort of agreed upon and also Stephen King wrote the screenplay for that adaptation. Yeah
Boy did I hijack your review by the way. I don't care. Telling a full story of my child
I kind of had nothing else to say. It's a fucking you know, it's a making of sure you know, uh worth my time
Yeah, I think it's fun to watch. It's just that's why I said like it's not one we could really get a lot of discussion out of they talk about two
I've never seen two. I don't think they mentioned two you hate to right. It's it's it's
Dog shit. How's Eddie furlong in it? How's your Eddie furlong? He's my Eddie's all right. I mean he's as good as you can be with this
Fucking material. He's it's like sure. It's dog shit. I mean clancy browns in it and it still sucks. Yeah
um
It's a terrible movie, but anyway
So Stephen King wrote the screenplay of the first film
Adapted from his own book, of course. Uh, so I thought you know, obviously he did a pretty good job of hitting the what's important of this script
Uh or this story to to to get onto the screen
This and one of the things they say in this documentary that I found fascinating is they said
What this story is really about is the secrets of men and how men destroy a family
You know, so it could be a metaphor for adultery or addiction or whatever. Yeah, but this concept of
the man of the house
ruining his family because of his own ego and what and I think that's
truly insightful especially today sure um
Would I don't like have you seen the trailer the newest trailer?
Uh, no, but I've heard it that just tells the whole plot well tells the whole plot but right I've read the book
Well, but here the changes okay gauge doesn't die the daughter dies. Okay
The wife is there the whole time
Okay
So those two things right off the bat you're like wait a minute what like so I get veering like if you're doing a remake of a shitty horror movie
And you want to veer off and do your own thing great
You've got a beloved classic Stephen King source material. Why are you riffing on it at a time when nobody can land a decent horror movie
It's look. I still want to say it. I'm still intrigued, but I just don't know how I feel about this
Because the wife being there the whole time
There's a scene where the dead daughter the zombie daughter walks up and he goes hug your daughter and the wife is terrified
You know like
The whole point of the wife going away is so the husband can execute this horrible deed of burying their dead child in this
Mac whatever the fuck it's called burial ground. Yeah
Now she's just there or she comes home
I mean maybe maybe this look maybe the footage in the trailer is that it's when she first comes home
And then she gets killed like it is in the book. Maybe that's all it is. I don't know
I'm a little perplexed
By the choice to kill the daughter
Instead of the son
Because it's sort of
Ruins to me
the concept of from the original story which is
The daughter being terrified of death and not understanding it
And then having to learn how to understand it through her own little brother dying right now
Maybe that's just next out of this thing completely. I don't know. There also seems to be this new element of
A child cult
Where they all wear these animal masks
And it seems it seems a little
Stretch to me. It just doesn't seem very plausible to me. What's so scary about the original is
it is supposed to be this
Place of purity for children to find closure with their dead pets and then when you go past that place
There's a saw it. There's a spoiled ground where evil lives
And when you got kids dressing up in these like paper mache bunny rabbit masks going out to bury. It's it's just odd
Right, and it's not something that I believe kids would do ever in now or then or any at any point
It just doesn't seem believable to me
And then last but not least
And I hate to criticize the man. I'm sure he'll bring the emotional weight to the part it needs but lift gal
Said in an interview he was questioned about why would you not do the main accent?
And
Instead of just saying because it's then it's gonna sound like I'm doing a Fred Gwynn impression
Right, and I had to change something right let's gal goes
You know
We just felt that when you try to do that accident it sounds put on
And it's not necessary. It's like are you
Taking a shot at the Fred Gwynn per
Did you do what are you doing?
You
So now I will say I think I read in entertainment weekly or some shit
That lift gal did say I didn't want to do an impression of Fred Gwynn maybe two different interviews
But I think he was given his props. I love lift guy. I don't think we need to take him down
I'm not trying to take him down
But he did say this thing and he said he did two reads one with it and one without and they decided to go without
But
Look I'm intrigued I dare I say I'm I'm still excited to see it
Maybe they made these weird changes and it works right and it's this awesome new
Alternate version of pet cemetery. I mean, it's like debut directors, right?
Or I think it's the guys who did starry eyes which I never saw but I heard was a really good horror movie
I know I believe it's the isn't it the producers from it
Yeah, but I think the director is the guy that did the starry eyes
So my fear is is that it's going to be another it's an area where it's like you take this really dark deep
Material and then you kind of reduce it to like a fun jump scary thing and then you don't give a shit
Let me go ahead and give you what I 100 % guarantee that's what it's going to be because they don't look at the box office of it
Green light pet cemetery and say do something different with it. They're going to want the exact same shit
Apparently it two is three hours long and actually I was kind of like okay good
Maybe they're going to do it justice and they're like no, we're going to cut an hour out of it get it down a size
uh
You know bill haters in it. I like the
You know, I like the kids side almost as much as I like the adult side
But I don't have the highest of hopes for it too because it's the same team as it won and it won
Folks was not good. I look forward to seeing it
I'll be there opening night in the way that I looked forward to seeing kill bill two
I don't know. I remember seeing kill bill one and thinking
Okay, that's pretty cool. Are you kidding me?
I don't love kill bill one. I love kill bill two
Well, I certainly agree with you there. Well, I agree with you that I love kill bill two, but I saw one
A. I had had a picture of sangria with my dear friend Sarah Pontear. How you doing Sarah?
uh
I went into this thing drunk as fuck. It was like 90 minutes long
I just thought it was so fucking awesome
And if it hadn't been the midnight show, I would have gone in and seen it again
But then too, of course, I'm much deeper more
Awesome experience who's the Tarantino movie choose an amazing movie the first one is the grind house movie the first one is
So it's so cool. Listen, it's it looks incredible the music's incredible the findings incredible
I am not saying kill bill is on the same level as it
I'm saying like I like to kill bill just fine, but when I went in what I wanted was not what I got completely and I left going
All right, man, that was you know, I'd see it again
And then when I saw the second one suddenly the quality of the first one jumped up immensely for me right
So I hope that that happens with it too
I hope that that that that I see that and I and I go wow here's the depth that I was looking for in the first one
And now this makes the first one kind of a fun just a little intro
What I'm thrown by is why
uh
They they threatened or not threatened they they promised they were coming out with this kill bill the complete the whole bloody affair
Like it's a cut that Tarantino did himself that's like the whole movie
Edit or both movies edited into one thing with additional scenes and it's like a four -hour
The entire kill bill epic and Tarantino apparently edited this thing and it was rumored to be coming out
And never did maybe that's tied up with the Weinstein shit because it's you know Weinstein and him were pretty tight
Tarantino I'm dying to see I want this I want to be able to watch this right now
Tarantino promises things that are heartbreaking when he doesn't deliver on yeah
Remember when he said his next movie was going to be the Vega brothers. I do
He was going to be mad soon in trouble. I was like holy shit
Yeah, and then he never he just never did it
And you're like he probably wrote it and it wasn't up to snuff or something, but um let's get to our movie of the day
We even need me to announce what the fuck it is yet a little shop of horrors
I mean it's mainly we're gonna talk about the
The 80s version I assume I've seen both of you. I have seen both we can kind of cover both here
Yeah, I mean I find the original I don't know a great deal of I know a lot about Raja Cormin the man and the
career, but I haven't actually seen many of his movies
um
But the original shop horrors is pretty fun. Jack Nicholson plays the sick dental patient that Bill Murray plays in the
Frank Oz 1986 version that we are discussing
Um, and it's okay, you know, it's cheap. It's shitty looking, but it's got its charm
I think it's considered one of the Cormin classics right that would be on any one of your Cormin box
That's whatever for sure. It's got it. It's got its charm. Uh, it's weird. I saw the I saw the newer one first
And wasn't thrilled that it was a musical when I was seeing that I remember showing it to my cousin Dominic
And he was all excited to see it and I was like yeah, it's a fun movie and then we were watching it and he and he goes
Damn it, why didn't you tell me it was a sing along
And I was like you mean musical
Sing along yeah, but then when I and I remember I was like yeah, I kind of was disappointed by that too man like
I'm not thrilled that it's musical, but then I went back and want
But then I learned that the remake was a adaptation of the stage the Broadway show right
And then my mom was like, you know, there this is there's an old movie called little shop horrors
And I rented that and she even told me Jack Nicholson plays that Bill Murray part
Yeah, and uh, and then when I watched that I missed the sing -alongs
It sure it didn't seem right anymore. So uh
it was uh
Not that enjoyable as if I can remember, but uh, yeah, but I don't know I've been seen it in years
But the remake I still I find enjoyable
Uh, you know we we can start with the best performances in the film
Well, hey, I'm gonna I'm gonna say I don't like your tone
why
Because you it sounds very dismissive of what I consider
One of the best movie musicals of all time or sing -alongs if you will
It very well may be like for for me we're talking top three easy
Very well. Maybe I'm not a big musicals guy. It's a wonderful comedy. It's the songs are awesome
And I remember every note of them which like you know, you want to talk about Mary Poppins returns
As the movie was playing I was forgetting each song as it played like there was no hooks to anything
little shop a horizontal hooks. It's uh Howard Ashman
and
Tim Rice I might be wrong. I was wrong last week. I kept saying
Bernard Herman instead of Edward Herman Bernard Herman is the composer for Hitchcock
Edward Herman is the dad and the lost boys or the the guy should be and weses dating in the lost boys correction
but uh
Yeah, the songs and this thing are incredible. They're like 60s do -up songs. You got the girl group stuff with
the shantels I believe including
Toshina Arnold from Martin. Yeah Tisha Campbell's in there Tisha Campbell
I just for me this was everybody I loved in 80s film and
and
They're all at their best. I mean, this is my favorite Rick Moranis performance by far as Seymour
Song suddenly Seymour is a fucking banger. Ellen Green who all like that song. Let me get that in. I don't like that song
I think it's a one of my favorite songs of all musical history and I am a bit of a student
um
Ellen Green almost never acted again. She's incredible. They she's the only person they brought over from the Broadway show
Hey, where's she been? What happened to her? She I think she was on like
You know pushing days pushing that's right pushing daisies
but uh, you know
Obviously she didn't have like a conventional Hollywood look is probably what what herter but she's awesome in this movie
Steve Martin is
So good should have been nominated so funny as the dentist and
You know, it's one of his few performances where he really inhabits a character and like blows it out a lot of times
He's kind of just like
Steve Martin or you know in the early days the dumb guy
but uh
He's awesome in that character and like really menacing and scary and his song dentist another classic. I like that song
John candy uh
Has a cameo. He's hilarious as the very weird the weird radio guy. Yeah, he's great
You got a Jim Belushi coming in for a pointless cameo and he's fine
You got Christopher Gast who's hilarious in a very tiny early role from him
The movie is directed by Frank Oz one of the most underrated comedy directors of all time also the voice of Yoda miss Piggy etc
I love uh, I love that Frank Oz direct look. It's a spectacularly crafted film
I'm just on a huge musicals guy
But that doesn't mean it in by any stretch. It's a bad movie um, it was written by Elliott Miles Goodman
who wrote
Dirty rotten scoundrels
Great movie uh, no, I'm sorry
He's best remembered for his frequent collaboration with film director Frank Oz from Goodman scored
Such films as dirty rotten scoundrels. What about Bob house sitter
For his score to Oz's little shop of horror Goodman was nominated for a golden globe for best original score
Songs were written by Howard Ashman
Both of these men are dead. Ashman died young. He though from complications of AIDS at 40
That's correct. That's a shame
Because he was he was hit in fucking grand slams. I believe is it Ashman and Tim Rice
Just says Ashman here. Okay. I mean Ashman also did like little mermaid and stuff
He did lit. Yeah, he his key collaborative rice for for Disney stuff. Okay, but not a little mermaid beauty in the beast Aladdin
Jesus Christ. Yeah, those are some fucking hits. What the fuck dude
That is dude 89 mermaid 91 beauty in the beast 92 Aladdin
Pretty impressed
He he created the off Broadway musical version of the Korman show. Okay, so this this film was based on that
It seems like that's mainly what he did and then he wrote some songs with this with this rice character
Well the only new song in little shop of horrors that wasn't in the musical on Broadway is
Mean green mother from outer space. I like that song which was nominated for best song
That would be one of my least favorite songs of the of the soundtrack
Of course because you've got you've got to be difficult
You've got to disagree with me
I used to mow a lot of lawns listening to that soundtrack, but you got to shout out Levi Stubz
The lead singer or at least one of the lead singers of the four tops who voices Audrey too and just a perfect fucking choice
Not even like a big name choice like they probably could have gone with prince or
Little Richard or something little Richard would have been great too, but it's just the perfect voice for it
Feed me see more etc
I don't know if you've never seen it. I highly recommend and when I was a kid there were few movies. I love more than
A little shop of horrors and it does make you miss Moranis
I mean what a treat what a delight. I miss him although, you know
I think he'd be I've seen him recently like he he went on today's show with like some
Cowboy songs he had written like wearing a cowboy hat. That's all he does now. He just does these music albums and
You know, it certainly didn't make me feel good. I'll tell you that they were comedy songs, right? Yeah, he had one but like a gentle comedy
Yeah, he had like a bar mitzvah one or something. Yeah, like there was like he does like these theme comedy
What can you do go see little shop of horrors go see everything we talked about we didn't talk about one bad thing today and check out that
Pet cemetery trailer. I'm sure most of the hellians have already let us know in the Facebook group what your thoughts are on these changes
I'd love to know
Coming up in future episodes will do hard noir. We are going to do the hills have eyes remake
um, and you know some other bold shit. Oh, well, you're gonna watch the spear yeah
Oh, yeah, Susperia also is coming up. I think we're gonna have a real nice conversation about Susperia
I gotta I gotta get that from you. Yeah. Oh, yeah, you're right. I'll bring it over
Let me add it though because I'm making a list here of stuff we're supposed to cover
um, that's our show joderosa comedy on
Instagram
Uh, when's this come out Monday? Uh, so March 29th and 30th bonkers comedy
presents me
At top golf in Las Vegas
Two shows one per night. Is that like one of those indoor golf places? I think there's like indoor driving ranges and shit in there
But I'll be there. There's a chance patty Walsh might be there. Oh, yeah, I think indoor golf. Who knows?
I mean, I'm not saying if you come we gotta hang out at the golf place all night we can go gamble
Uh, I was saying like
It sounded like you were saying I was coming to see you, but I was saying yeah, I might be out there. I like indoor golf. Oh, I see
I get it a little slam now. I get it my
My next short story premieres in the March April issue of penthouse. It is called menu change
Look for it on stands also penthouse .com is now live and you can read my past articles my op -ed pieces that I wrote for them
I don't know how many are up there, but a bunch are up there. So check
of that out and also
Uninformed podcasts with billburn myself at patreon .com slash burrow. Thank you very much
Folks, I'm at the Patrick Walsh on Twitter and Instagram cool kids. There's on Friday night starting
Well, actually the previous Friday if we're airing on Monday
We're doing like a run of eight new ones in a row
So be sure to check them out
Great run coming up
also on hulu and
Check out our fantastic Instagram page. See you in hell pod, right
Yes, run by Emily Florence at at Emily Florence. That's probably not right
Uh, I follow her but
I guess you could look jump
But uh
Anyway
On the Etsy page. It's hog house. It's the hog house shop per store the hog house boy
We should really know this stuff better, right? Well, I know I knew the Instagram you you you dropped the ball on there
No, I said it's see you in hell pod, right? Yeah, yeah, it is see you in hell pod and then let me just confirm
Emily's because she handles all the uh, it's Emily D
E Florence Emily D .E. Florence Emily D .E. Florence. Okay. Uh, and thanks to uh
And I do follow you. I just don't always know what you're thanks to joe tilly for the uh
Frazier mock -up
That was awesome. It was disturbing and it was awesome. It's awesome mine. I look as if
I look like the hills have eyes in that in that thing. I mean, I don't look much better, but uh
Yeah, it's it's a lot of great fun posts audio clips
Fan art, which we always are just blown away that that even exists
Check it out the hog house page on Etsy is where you find the merch and uh, if you want to listen to the patreon
Go sign up
Joe, what's that address
Because the patreon, uh, you know, especially with the Oscars coming up
We did a pretty in -depth and I think very funny like one of our best episodes. I think the discussion of the Oscar films
I believe the patreon is patreon .com slash Ws
Why iH
And it might have the word podcast on it Jesus Christ. I mean, I don't know
Now we need to look it out. This is if you just if you google you will see you and how in patreon it'll come up
But hold on. Oh look. Oh look now you have to
Okay, babe. Okay down for maintenance. Thanks patreon
Wow, yeah, they really are down for maintenance, aren't they
All right, we can't tell you but if you google it you will find it
um
Thank you for listening. Thank you for all your support and love have a good uh week. Bye
You
It's a cool show