Huff, puff, and spin the house down at Golden Nugget Online Casino!
Right now, new players can deposit just 5 bucks and get 500 total spins on Huff and
more puff!
The slot that's blowing players away!
Download the Golden Nugget Online Casino app, and use promo code Nugget1.
That's code Nugget1 to enjoy 50 spins a day for your first 10 days!
All on our players' favorite game of the summer!
Now's the time to score daily bonuses and spin for all the bacon on the game everyone's
hoffat about.
At Golden Nugget Online Casino, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberler.
Please play responsibly.
21 and over, physically president Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia
only, void an Ontario.
New customers only, nonwithdrawable casino spins issued as 50 spins per day for 10 days valid
for featured game only and expire each day after 24 hours.
C -terms at GoldenNuggetCasino .com slash promos ends at 11 .59 p .m. Eastern on August 31st, 2025.
The football season is full of guarantees. And here's another. No other sportsbook has
been offered this good. With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until
October, if your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash. If you bet on football
with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan cash. Guaranteed. Switch to
fanatic sportsbook. Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 plus, gambling problem called Winning 100 Gambler,
offer not available in all states, terms apply,
see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
Howdy -duty folks, it's your main man.
And we'll see you in hell back to give you the juice on all the horror sci -fi and fantasy
films you love.
One part of that man is me, Joe DeRosa.
So we'll see you in hell is a man and you're a part of the man or a woman.
I don't want to, I don't want to put it in a box.
All right.
So I'm also then a part of the man or a woman or maybe we're a little bit of both.
My name is patch walls. Maybe we're two bottom halves. One with a penny and one with a VJJ. Okay. Yeah
Okay, we recreate produce with ourselves. I
Was thinking more like stuck on you with Greg Keneer and Matt Damon, and I've always
Looked at Simon's twins is one
Because they share so much
Not those two they only share like a little stomach flap
Yeah, it's a real, I don't like when they shortcut the Siamese part in a Siamese twin movie.
I agree.
When it's this little thing, it looks like if they used a straight razor, they could separate
themselves.
You know, really get in there.
Give me what it's really all about.
You want to like a Cronenberg?
Yeah.
Separation scene.
All right.
Yeah.
You know, like the fly, you know, I go in there, you go in there, we come out there.
Right.
you know, one of those kind of things really mix it up. Yeah. There should be a
Siamese twin DJ name mixed master something. I don't think they still do mixed master.
Well, I'm just saying because of them because the mix, you know, they're mixed together,
these two people. Speaking of DJs, Joe and I just went to the land of DJs this weekend,
in Las Vegas, Nevada, and they have a new ride called Land of DJs and it's a DJ Conor
themed Roseanne ride.
That's a lot of fun.
Everybody's favorite character.
You think anyone's favorite character of Roseanne is DJ in the entire world?
I'll tell you, I've been rewatching the old ones.
Yeah.
DJ is a real winner on those old ones to the points that I don't understand why he's in the new
one so little.
I think it's because he's not a kid anymore.
Right.
He's like the little kid, he's very cute.
He looks like Roseanne and he comes in with great zingers.
Well, and they also make him really weird
where he like kills squirrels and stuff like.
And the new ones, he'll literally sit in the scene,
like sit at the kitchen table
as an entire scene plays around him and say nothing.
I feel like he must have said like I don't want to act.
I'll just be a part of it.
I'm sure he was very excited to get back to it
And get the money, but they just aren't writing him jokes because he's not landing them because he's not a pro like the others
Well, but Becky came right back in swing and she hasn't done anything. It's true
You know, you got to give the guy a chance. Maybe they saw him on his feet and we're like
Plus Rosanne loves him. He co -hosted Rosanne's talk show with her. Really? Yeah for a couple seasons. Is that Rosanne's nuts?
No, it's before that
Anyway, sorry, we went to Vegas.
Went to Vegas, had the batch party.
I gotta say it was just an absolute delight.
It was, it was a really nice time,
really great company, good food, good times.
I actually was a little sad yesterday.
I kind of missed everybody.
I felt the same.
Yeah.
It was kind of a rare thing.
I've been to so many batch parties
where there's a weird energy
or there's somebody who's not jelling
or somebody gets too drunk or somebody's
like trying to cheat on their wife. And you're like, Oh God, this is going to be
uncomfortable at the wedding. Whatever. This was just like 10 nice people hanging
out. No one got sick. No one got weird. We didn't do anything that will shame us
or our families for generations to come. Yeah, it was very tame. We had, I had, you know,
As I talked about on Twitter, I had Annie Lenox come into the suite and give us a three
hour performance for the 10 guys that was kind of in lieu of a strip club situation.
She played the big hit twice, which I liked, opened and closed with it.
She opened and closed with walking on broken glass.
Yeah.
Why?
I don't know if you remember why, yeah.
Yeah, tears streaming down my face. I was high on an edible at that point. Just sobbing.
And I did like the new takes on the old Eurythmics tunes. There was the Baroque version of Sweet
Dreams, sort of acoustic, Renaissance fare almost version. So that was good stuff.
The, uh, it was a great time. Great people bonded with people. I've not had a lot of time
and a bond with re -ignited flames with old friends
I don't get to see often, made new equateancies
that may become friendships, it was a nice time.
Friendships that may become lovers.
Who says they didn't already bet?
We went to the pool, we all gambled,
we went to downtown Vegas, we had meals,
delicious meals.
It was great.
It was a great time.
Very odd
Service in a Greek restaurant 10th service in a Greek restaurant. I'm I'm I think that first waiter actually walked off
And what could be construed as a huff?
I'm convinced that that was like a Gordon Ramsay exit. Yeah, I can't fucking do this mate
That's what he did right
We don't know why he did the waiter and I've had nothing but good service this place is great Greek restaurant at the
cause a problem called Milo's.
To Milo's form and themed restaurant.
All of his movies are, there's props on the wall
and they play Rock, Me, I'm a Deus, Over and Over
on the speakers and then Man on the Moon,
the REM song, they play as well.
That plays a lot.
You've got, you know, I forget it.
I think we're done.
But yeah, the waiter was like, so anyway,
it's one of those deals with the waiter's talking
for like 10 minutes and everybody's getting
kind of uncomfortable.
By the way, to one guy.
Yeah, not addressing the table, and I don't mean with his eyes
I mean talking only so that one guy can hear him who was he talking to was I could tell him he was given John
Fulton all the information okay, and Fulton was the one that was like I I think you need to be telling this to everybody
Yeah, there's ten people at this table right I got all pissed off
Well, yeah, he's telling us like generally what we do is he's basically saying I'm not gonna give you the menus
news. That was a big part of what he wanted to do. And he goes, so we'll just give you
all sorts of appetizers and family style and this and that. And then we're going to build
your menu up to the fish course. So we're going to start with the fish and work back.
But and then finally, you know, he's like, or you know, I can give you menus or whatever
in the knee and goes, yeah, we'll take menus. The guy goes, oh, storms off. And then for
the rest of the meal, we had a new waiter. You know what I think, I think I just cracked
the code on that while he did that. I think he was pissed because he was probably trying to put on
us some thousand dollars. Oh, absolutely. Thing. And we said, no, we don't want to do that. And
there goes his, you know, $200 tip or whatever. And he was pissed. That's probably right. I would
guess. I mean, I don't know what Milos's off menu strategy is. I don't know either. Meanwhile,
we ate that when we were done eating about 20 more dishes came to the table and everybody owed like
100 bucks. Yeah. We handled it. It was great. It was a great time. Now, I did have a few drinks.
Yes. That's fun. By a few, I mean, no more than 10 or 12 each night.
I got to tell you though, Patty, it was a good time to have a few in Vegas. Yeah.
But a lot of it for me was drinking in a vacuum, which was like, we're off the beaten path.
We're in a very contained, you know, circumstance here, I'm with a bunch of guys, nobody's trying
to, you know, nobody's trying to impress anybody here or whatever.
And I was just, you know, it was fun, but it actually made me look forward to coming back
and not drinking again, like I didn't slide back into, well now the cat's out of the bag
and I want to, I want to just keep doing this.
I enjoyed it in those moments, but I didn't, it was weird, I didn't miss it.
I thought like when I did it, I was like, it's good.
Gonna be like, oh god, the old sweet baby's back.
But I also never realized how much I'm able to drink without feeling that drunk, so that
was pointed out to me.
Well, especially if you're off at that long, there should have been a dip in the tolerance.
They didn't seem to be.
Not a one.
Yeah.
Whatever.
So anyway, but I had a great time. It was a personal journey. It was a journey with friends. Yeah, and it was a journey with you. Now, I
Don't think you should have hooked up with all those other women during your bachelor party. Uh -huh. I don't think that's your opinion
Frankly, it's not one that I share. I had a lot of fun
you know fair enough they seem to enjoy themselves they did I got admit they
did only a couple of them were paid to give me that sort of performance the rest
all they voluntarily all right what what else is going on and nothing right not
really that's I'm in wedding planning mode we're getting ready to it'll be a
a couple of weeks away, but there will be a hiatus.
So start girding your loins for that.
We're gonna take a couple of weeks off.
I'm gonna go on my honeymoon and so forth.
Yes, but so maybe you stockpile,
maybe you listen to a half an episode
and then you go, I'll listen to this next one on Monday.
But then again, you're gonna get hooked
and you're gonna wanna finish it, you know.
We bring that heat.
Well, and that's the thing.
You don't gotta hog down on the hog house every week.
That's right.
You can ration it out.
these 90 minute ones that could have been three for you.
You know, you get off of your capitalistic greed horse,
where you got to listen to the whole damn episode all at once.
Ration it out a little bit.
There are children in third world countries
who get one podcast a year.
They have to make it last.
Yeah, we are going to have to take a hiatus,
but that's fine.
I mean, you know, it's been a while since we've taken a break.
A really long time.
We've had discussions where it's like,
well, if you're coming back in town,
I guess I can miss a few shifts at the plant
to get the, and then I'll leave.
And I'm like, we could just not do it one week.
I mean, we don't owe these people anything,
and as we learn, they don't seem to owe us anything.
Oh, you mean headgum.
Yeah, that's right.
Are they better fans?
No.
They're gonna say, well, the Patreon people, sure.
Yeah, it does seem, you know, somebody asked the other day,
hey, if you did a live show,
I'm sure your network would really get behind it
and really, I don't even know if they know
we're on the network anymore.
Here's how that call would go.
Hey, head gum, it's Pat and Joe wanted to talk about
doing a live show.
Who?
Well, we do the show, we'll see you in hell.
It actually does really good numbers for your network.
We'll see you in what?
Podcasts we haven't done podcasts. It's like little genie's spice world where she talks about all the her beloved spices on the rack
Stuart is that a real show doing 45 dates this month across the globe. No, I made it
I wouldn't but I always say follow the head gum Twitter account and it'll be like
The twelfth annual head gum comedy bash and there's 45 people's faces holding microphones
and little thing.
I'm like, not aware this was happening.
I wouldn't be surprised at this point if we went down to head gum to the office and
we're greeted only by an old sort of sleazy looking janitor that says there hasn't been
in a podcast studio here in 40 years.
That's gum.
I haven't heard that name in ages.
Yeah.
That's a rocking chair creaking on its own off the side.
At this point, I feel like that's maybe what's happening,
but anyway, folks, we are, we thank you
to our dear friends Ken Hanley and Emily Florence.
They are setting up our, or in the midst of getting
the logistics together for our first live show.
So it will, I'm assuming, per the discussion so far, probably be in Los Angeles.
You know, so the ball is rolling with that.
And of course you can visit the hoghouse store on Etsy and you can buy merch from that
store.
Patreon is WCYIHPod on Patreon.
WS. Oh, sorry, WSYIH pod on H on Patreon WSYIH pod on Twitter and
See see see how see you and help pod on Instagram. I gotta I don't even think I'm following our fucking Twitter page
I have to have we do it. Who's it running it you? I opened it and it's that we should really give it over
We should or connect it to the we got to do some Instagram thing. I can't stand, you know, you know, my take on Twitter
It's like stepping into a fucking cesspool. It's disgusting. Where's every day?
Horrible. I did, you know, I had this morning, like a weird 7 a .m. wake up, which just keeps happening. Can't sleep in
I'm scrolling down Twitter for probably from 7 to 7 30. I didn't see a joke
Now, I mean, here's the thing, it originally wasn't jokes either, sorry, I understand
if it's not a lot of, I'm fine with that. Originally it was supposed to be an update
on your status. I'm here doing this right now. Uh, maybe you're here too. That was the
original, whatever one's parents think of Twitter. I was like, oh, so you just tell people
you're having a sandwich. Yep, you got in my day to tell someone you were having a sandwich
was gauche because people didn't have sandwiches. If I was going to tell someone I was having a sandwich
I'd say Ernie I am having a sandwich I didn't need to get the computer involved. You know who
I would tell I was having a sandwich the man who ran the deli so he could make it. Because frankly,
Yes, me. He's the only one who needs to know.
Joe and I both have elderly Jewish fathers who did not teach us Judaism, but they practiced.
But I, but that's originally what it was supposed to be and that's what it was in the beginning
and then it became a very comedian heavy thing and it was a lot of jokes and it was fun for a minute.
And now it's just people stroking themselves, one way or the other, so I don't necessarily
hate that it's not jokes anymore.
But I also, it does annoy me that it's not, it doesn't annoy me that it's people stroking
themselves.
I mean, look, I wasn't too thrilled with the idea of telling people where you're at either.
But I never did that check in bullshit on Facebook.
Fuck you.
I mean, how big brother do you people want to live?
Oh yeah, I'm gonna let the fucking computer and internet know where I'm at at all time
What are you fucking insane? It's bad enough. You gotta got the em satellite in your pocket. Yeah
I was on Instagram this weekend, and I could bring it up and it's like tell people you're at the Las Vegas strip
I was like actually bitch. How the fuck do you know I'm on the Las Vegas strip?
Location services, baby. I turned them all off
I don't like it you should have said that in a cat Williams voice. I would have really enjoyed that
Excuse me bitch. It's like how in the fuck do you know I'm on the strip?
Who
I who wants their location services on who?
And then some of them it's like you need it every time I get on it's like
Go ahead and set up your cloud and I'm like I don't do the cloud next and then I'll go no set up the cloud
And it'll do it five and six times. There's a term for that. They actually that that type of software is coined like
I don't remember the term, but it's it's something along the lines of like pester software or
No, it's whatever and the idea behind it is it will annoy you until you comply. It's it's worked before. Yeah
Now I'm just like nah, I'll click this off ten times while I'm also
Trying to buy a ticket to something and everything else lots of two. I love these fucks that are all screaming up
and down about texting while driving, which is, yeah, I agree, it's not a good idea.
But the reason I call them fucks is because they never seem to mention the fact that when
you're trying to responsibly use your phone while driving, say type in or even Siri voice
command in an address or something you're trying to find, the 18 fucking pop -ups that start
are coming up.
Yeah, like these or the are you driving
or the thing that goes whoops?
Yeah, you're not the passenger thing
has nearly gotten into many accidents.
It's just like Jesus Christ.
So anyway.
Also, it finally, because when I got a new phone,
it was like using the old version of Gmail,
my Gmail worked beautifully for a decade.
I'm like, all right, I don't wanna upgrade
to this new Gmail, but fine, I do it.
Every time I get in there, I think I have an email,
But instead there's an advertisement at the top of my in my mail
It's like you check out postmates two for 20 or I'm like the fuck out. This is my Gmail now. You're gonna advertise in
Yeah, it's sick of it. It's well. You can shut off the advertisements in Gmail
Cuz I had those for a while and then I figured out you can turn them off all right, it's a horse with a different color
Joe let me take you to Pat's movie corner. Well that was don't forget that that was our new segment
called uh uh witch in moe
which and grown uh yeah any variation of that phrase uh yeah let's get down to the movie corner
I haven't seen anything okay I haven't seen much I think that's true I don't think
I have watched a single thing well I'll bring up a thing you mentioned last week that
I watched okay I watched John Mulaney's kid gorgeous special yep what a fantastic piece
to work. That was great. It made me so happy. I was really laughing through the whole thing.
Yeah. He's the delivery's great. He looks great. The set's immaculate. It's exciting seeing him in
that big Radio City Music Hall room and he fits like that is a guy that was crafted genetically
to perform in Radio City Music Hall. It just agreed. All really seemed right. I really,
really loved it. I think it's an interesting choice for him to throw on the occasional
fuck. Yeah, because I feel like I feel like it's not adding to his comedy in a way that
it adds to most other comedy. And I feel it's of course I'm not like, well, everybody's
got to be dirty. I don't care about that. I'm just saying he could, he's already at the
radio city level, but I think if he dropped it entirely, he would never stop touring the
country and being a huge comedian.
I think what it lets him do is stay a little dark.
But he's got pretty dark material.
No, I know.
Well, I feel like if you take out all the curses
on top of that, then all of a sudden people are like,
why is this nice guy doing a joke about a child murder?
I guess that's true.
You know, it keeps it a little dirty.
It wasn't even a complaint.
It was just something I was curious about.
Oh, you're theorizing, Pat.
Look, I love to sit down and talk shop with you.
Who are your guys?
my comedian guys.
That's what Mark Marin asked everybody.
Oh, okay.
I love the special, I thought it was great.
I watched the new Regan special, I'm a huge Regan fan.
It was a special, it was okay.
I mean the latest one or the other new one?
No, the latest one on Netflix.
That was kind of rough for me.
It was all right, I think he just did it a little too,
because he did one from Radio City Music Hall
on Comedy Central, which was fucking excellent.
And then this one came out like six months later,
I think it was just too close together.
I also know because he mentions it on the radio city one he's going through a divorce or he just split up from his
So I'm imagining his head is probably
Then at the end of this one it says that is in memory of my dad his dad just he's probably going through a rough patch here sure
And he's not a guy that's gonna get on stage and be like let me tell you what divorce is really all about yeah
He's a very funny man. I would love to see his divorce material
Yeah, but you know, it has it has its moments that it's not a bad special. It just wasn't I've seen so much a rig and that it wasn't one of my more
One of my favorite ones, but but it was still fun to watch
I
Oh
Last but not least I attempted to watch
several of the tremors sequels
equals. Do you mean you started a bunch of them? Are you finished any of them?
Couldn't get through one goddamn one of them.
I've seen and I was excited to see aftershocks, the second one.
But as we've discussed on here, they had them above ground as dogs.
Well, aftershocks is still underground.
I think three is where they start to.
I think halfway through aftershocks, they become dogs.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
yeah. I didn't get that far. You know, I enjoyed your guy. What's his face in it?
Gross. Ward. Bill. What's the Fred Ward? Yeah, Michael gross. I didn't even get to
the bacon. I mean, it's it's like it's like a movie with just Costello. That's right.
I didn't get to the part where Michael gross turns up. Yeah, he's in there. And he's the
star of the future installments.
Yeah, I was just very bored by it.
It wasn't very well directed.
There was no suspense to any of it.
So I turned it off and then I put on tremors three
back to perfection.
Just didn't really care.
Yeah.
And the tremors TV show has been
not taken up.
Pilot was shot, they passed on.
Dad, did we talk about that?
With bacon though.
Yeah, do we already talk about that on here?
We might have mentioned it.
It's just odd.
I don't understand.
It is.
I mean, it could have just turned out really bad.
But for any TV show to have bacon, you think it'd be a get.
Now, why is Gross not in the TV show?
Because he's supposed to be like monster hunting around the world.
And Bacon is...
Wait, he wasn't in the new Bacon one?
I don't think so.
I think they kind of made a decision of, like, Gross will be the movie guy.
and bacon will be like the TV guy.
And then eventually we'll mix the two together.
I think we're really trying to do like a Marvel thing.
Like we're gonna do it.
How weird is that that Michael Gross
would be the movie guy and Kevin Bacon, the TV guy?
Well the movies are direct to droid phone.
I mean, they're not, things are getting huge releases.
They do very well though.
They make money.
What is the picture that's out now,
my trainer was talking to me about this morning
and called Ghost Stories.
I thought he meant the Casey Affleck joint, but he didn't.
No, it's supposed to be great.
It's based on a play that ran, I think, in England
that was supposedly very scary.
Movie's supposed to be very scary.
Who's out yet?
Just a little indie.
Little indie.
I think you know what Gregor's in it.
There's some notable people in it.
I can't remember.
Is it out?
This guy saw it on the theater last night.
What do you say?
Said it was very scary.
now is this a this big muscle bound man said it was scary your trainer that's right his name's
and I'm not kidding Dirk as if it's an 80s teen sex romp and who says it isn't yeah all right
Let's move past the movie corner all right Joe's scary stuff you know I'm reading a book
currently right now by a guy named Ramsey Campbell who's a horror author I discovered
when I just googled scariest books that's all I did I wanted to find a new horror author that I wasn't
familiar with. And I just Googled top scariest books, you know, whatever. Okay. And I found
an article I can't remember who wrote the article, what outlet it was on, but they basically
said like for your money, these are like the 10 or 15 scariest novels you can buy. All right.
You know, I think it was on there. I think Pat Cemetery was on there. A bunch of stuff, Richard
Matheson Hellhouse, you know a bunch of a bunch of stuff you expect to be on there, but there was also stuff on there that I'd never heard of and
One of them was this novel called The Face That Must Die, which the title alone. I was like, well, what's that?
Written by an English author British author named Ramsey Campbell who everybody from Stephen King to whoever has said
This is the greatest horror writer of our generation. This guy is completely amazing
Okay, but yet he's sort of an unsung hero, you know, Ramsey Campbell. Okay
So I got the book I had to get it from a place called like the the flea market bookstore in like Massachusetts
Because it's out of print. I got it realizing that it was only really it was only published by a very small publishing house in Los Angeles
because
Because the majors wouldn't publish it, because apparently it was too dark.
It was too much.
I've been reading it.
It's quite creepy.
It's very weird.
It's basically about a man whose paranoia is absolutely overcoming him.
And it's great.
It's hard the way I like it.
It's written in that, who's the guy that wrote Bright Light's Big City?
What's that guys?
Jay McKinney. Yeah, I like when horror is written in that sort of style. That's sort of it's
poetic and it's it's figurative, but the language is very personal and and very direct and
and it reminded me of something like that. Also reminded me of the works of the guy,
what we talk about when we talk about love, the ramen karma. Yes, terrible with names, but I like
these writers very much. Anyway, I love ramen karma. It's a book. I'm not done it yet, but I would
recommend it if you want to read something that's edgy and disturbing and dark. All right.
And that's just scary stuff. Yeah. I'm actually already a book of I'll be going on the dark.
What's that which I think actually does qualify for scary stuff. It is about the Sacramento. I wish we had a confetti thing like at the supermarket when the Bundy's get the one millionth customer.
It's you you hit it you hit it dead on today. It was written by Michelle McNamara who was the pretty recently deceased wife sadly of Pat and Oswald.
Oh, okay, and I had long heard that she had been tracking this Sacramento strangler.
The cops are not giving her credit, but it seems like she's was pretty highly responsible
or at least her work shown some light on various people.
Wow.
And her writing is incredible.
I've listened to it on an audio book and it's just a fantastic book.
It's about her life in growing up and how she became obsessed with True Crime because
she seems almost disturbingly obsessed with crime, this crime in particular.
Right.
And she goes into her life and what kind of broader to that point, but also into tracking
the Sacramento Strangler than all these little things that play like those scenes in Zodiac,
same city, different killer.
Right.
But, you know, like really disturbing accounts of what took place with these people that
he killed.
And I'm halfway done. It's an amazing book. I highly recommend it. And it's
Karen in Georgia, Kilgara Fennhardt, so thank you again.
I'm often talking about it on my favorite murder as well. Thank you again, by the way,
to Karen in Georgia are my favorite murder friends, because somebody just wrote me again and said,
Hey, I discovered you recently
through another great podcast, my favorite murder. They recommended you and I love you guys.
and I'm bingeing your show now. I appreciate that. It's very, very nice of you. Thank you guys for
the shout out. I'm thanking for the fans that are doing this crossover thing. There is a kinship.
There is a bond there both thematically and personally. They talk about killings and we kill it every
week. I actually, yeah, so there was some scary stuff for you. I'm going to see if there's
anything for deadlines. I forgot to check before I got one today. Oh, well good. Let's just do one.
What do you have? They are finally making Bill and Ted three. It's actually happening no longer
just rumored. Everybody's on board and the movie is happening. And it's directed by Dean Parasso,
who directed Galaxy Quest, which seems like an awesome fit to me. Sounds good. I love Galaxy Quest.
Sounds good and it's called Bill and Ted face the music who they got Keanu Reeves and believe it or not they they got Alex Winter as well
I'm very excited to see it
That's really watch the other two which I've almost forgotten I'm on movie web com right now
And it does say it's officially happening. That's very exciting also two stories above it
First look at Keanu Reeves is John Wick three begin shooting can't wait so
And then two above that, Kimmelissa McCarthy stopped infinity war at the box office.
The answer is no.
Yeah, I mean, unless it's been out for six, seven weeks or something.
Anyway.
Life of the party.
Back to school.
Yeah.
I mean, I'm not saying, I'm not shit, I'm not.
It's a cut McCarthy.
But it's not like like life of the party is good, right?
And then look, and you know, that's not set out of Marvel love, people.
It's very interesting to me that McCarthy is like this unquestionably.
a huge comedy star, but she's had like two successful movies, one arguably not her movie,
bridesmaid.
Well, I'm excited because she's got a drama coming out and it looks dark and I look
forward to seeing that.
I got a drama for you, Melissa, I've been I haven't shown it to you, but I've got it
and I tell people I want you to be in it.
What is it?
So I guess she's kind of like a Cohen Brothers -y type project I've had for quite some time.
Did you write it already rodent was never able to show it's any one or shop it around and now I am so I made do that
I don't know it's like a thriller all right with some dark comedic elements
But yeah, I like the sound of this I think I might have told you about it. I like the sound of this. Thanks Joe
All right, onto our movie for today, Walsh, we're doing Infinity War.
Well now that Avengers is going to be an issue I haven't seen the film.
We're doing something a little different today where Joe is going to explain Avengers Infinity
War to me.
So I don't have to see it.
I've seen every one of these superhero movies and I'm done.
And the reason we're doing this is because often Pat will see a movie and say, you know,
you really should see this for the podcast and I don't want to or vice versa.
I didn't really want to see Infinity War, but then I saw it and I was like, you should
see it for the podcast.
And he said, I don't want to.
And I said, you know, why are we doing this to you?
Why are we making each other watch these damn things? Right. Let's just if one of us sees it
and we explain it to the other who gives us shit. This is probably the only time we'll do this. I
don't know. I'm gonna say no to that. And there might come a time where I'm staring down the the
bullet end of a movie pass and I see Infinity War book. Let's see let's see if I have four to five
hours on on an afternoon. I'll go check it out. I'd like to hear that before we say we will or we
won't do this again. I'd like to hear the fan reaction to this because my thought is the fans will
be very excited about me explaining the adventure's affinity war to you adhering your reactions to it.
Now, I'm going to pull up Wikipedia and I'm going to read through the synopsis to make sure I don't
miss anything. Well, you're not going to read the whole plot thing. I'm sure it goes on for days and
days. No, it's it's it's probably about four paragraphs and I'll read you the highlights.
I'll just you know take the the major parts we need you know what I mean. Okay.
Does go on for days and days. All right. Now that spoilers ahead people. So the movie opens
with Thanos played by Josh Brolin. Sure. And he has not been in the movies thus far.
Well, he shows up. He was in Guardians of the Galaxy.
And wait, he's in Deadpool as well playing the same character?
No, he's in Deadpool playing a completely different character.
They're both Marvel.
Yeah, it's stupid. That's so stupid.
Yeah, it's stupid, I know.
Doesn't Deadpool ever interact with the Avengers?
People are complaining that Deadpool did not interact with the Avengers.
It is so nuts to me to have Josh Brolin play two characters in this giant Marvel Universe
with the thousands and thousands of actors they could have gone with.
There is no middle class.
That's true.
It's gone.
Five people get all the work anyway and that's not a shot at Josh Brolin.
I like Josh Brolin but I don't think he should be playing two characters and I think it's
weird.
Loki in this? Yeah, he's in the beginning. Okay, Thanos played by Josh
Paul. Who's a great villain, by the way? All right. Josh Paul was one of the
only things of this movie I really enjoyed. But Thanos is on Thor's ship, the one
they're on from the end of Ragnarok. One playing Abba out the side or something.
Yeah, no, that's Galaxy. Guardians of the Galaxy. It's hard to remember which is
doing which at this point. There's a bunch of zany ships in this universe. They're
For some reason it's all from the late 70s and early 80s.
Right.
Because for some reason a guy from Asgard understands
what irony is.
Yeah.
Anyway, Captain America would be listening
to like the Andrews sisters.
He's from the 40s.
Captain America barely graces this thing.
Really? Okay.
And when he does, he's wearing, he is an Avenger now.
Pat, I gotta be honest with you.
I don't know who's an Avenger anymore.
Here we go. Hulk.
Well, they split up in Civil War.
So I don't know Panther Black Widow, but they're not Avengers anymore
Batman
Yep, the Smurfs
Grumpy and Doc
Blitzen
Thanos is on the ship
Cheach and Cheung and
Shimp Tweedie
Thanos is on the ship. He wants the infinity stone
You know these rocks that
sure can destroy it undo the universe yet Dr. Strange walks around one hanging
around his neck for some reason. I remember that being a sticking point for
you. Infinity stones are what? These are supposed to be enough plot for 20 movies
the pursuit of these fucking stones. There are five stones that were spawned out
of the big bang. They created John Galecki, a Gulligan, a Larson, some in it in a season
three episode. Parson, Galecki, Indian guy, Stone, and then I think Bob knew hearts on
it for some reason, Stone. Sure. But blonde haired lady, Stone, haven't seen the show. I've
honestly never seen a full episode. My dad loves the show. Everyone's dad loves the show.
who loves it. Anyway, these five stones were spawned from the big bang and I guess created
the universe. And the person that is able to harness these five stones again could undo
or control the universe in any way they see fit. That's why Thanos is after them. And
the Avengers are always trying to keep it out of the wrong hands. I got to be honest with
wall. Clutchers. This has been going on since before the first Avengers movie, this infinity
war, I mean, these infinity stones thing. Right. These guys have gotten plenty sidetracked
of number of times. Yeah. Thanos has seemed to have taken his good old time in pursuing
these things. Yeah. Why wasn't Avengers 2 about Thanos? Why is Avengers 3 about Thanos?
Why did it take this guy so long to go find these stones? I do not remember the plot
a lot of either Avengers 1 or Avengers 2, and I saw them both.
Avengers 2 was a movie where Loki, Thor's brother, tried to rain down Armageddon on planet
Earth, yet in several movies after they trusted Loki again, only to be betrayed.
Because that's what you would do if Hitler, if he didn't die during World War II, it came
them over like, Hey guys, come on. Yeah. You trust Hitler. Yeah. Sure. Sure. Um, so anyway,
Thanos kills Loki at the beginning of the movie. Cause for some reason, Loki finally decides
to be a decent person. Even though he was a piece of shit still in the last Thor movie, was
is he like, low key at least in person,
or was it gonna, you know, it didn't work during
the Thor review, for me at least, I'm sorry.
I think we're not just, we're just not hearing
everybody laugh, but everybody's probably laughing.
Go on.
Anyway, low key decides to stand up to him.
How did, by the way, Pat, you know how
do you decide to stand up to him?
By sneaking up to him with a knife behind his back.
This is a guy who we've seen in several movies now,
trick numerous people by creating an illusion of himself right so instead of
creating a fake version of himself in front of Thanos where and then the real
him sneaking up behind Thanos to stab him he just says I'm just gonna walk
directly up to Thanos hiding a knife behind my back like a Dennis the men is
slingshot with Mr. Wilson scene uh -huh Thanos snaps his neck you know like
personally I was like thank Christ this guy's finally fucking dead. He's not, though. You know that, right?
That's why I don't understand why people give a shit about these movies. I think you die. You're back. You're summoned.
They run into you in the past.
Then the Hulk comes in and tries to fight Thanos. How much ruffalo
as Bruce Banner is there because to me that is one of the most annoying
performances in movie history.
Well, I got great news for you, Pat.
Okay.
Banners outside of the opening scene,
entire thing in this movie is he can't turn into the Hulk.
It's this big metaphor for impidence.
So all you get is banner.
And it's all boner jokes.
Huh?
It's all like wink, wink, boner jokes.
No, but I mean, it's not wink, wink, boner,
but when a guy's going, I can,
I've been having this problem lately.
It's like, what am I supposed to think of?
I don't know. Well, maybe that's just what you're thinking after. I mean, I had an
erection the entire time. Maybe that's the problem. But then at the end of the movie,
so it's all ruffalo. Oh, it's 110 percent ruffalo. Did you ever think you'd see the day where you
were pissed about a lot of ruffalo in a movie? No. I didn't. Well, was that Avengers 2 where it was
him and Iron Man walking around like in tight jeans? No, that was Thor Ragnarok. Thor Ragnarok.
He's walking around grabbing his dick the whole time.
Ruffalo was insufferable in Thor Ragnarok,
which was an insufferable movie.
He's worse than this.
That I have heard and heard on this batch party weekend
described as the best of the Marvel movies.
He's worse than this.
So anyway.
Iron man.
Anyway, Thor kills.
I mean, wait, no.
Thanos kills Loki.
Wait up, Iron man.
Thor escapes.
Okay.
he's in space the guardians of the galaxy pick him up how much of these movies
costing it's it's listen here's what kills me and I've said this non -stops
since I saw a few percent put on your set it's a million dollars I truly love
I truly love and I this is this is everything has to be fucking justified these
days whatever you say you have to qualify everything I am not a Trump fan I do
not like Trump, but you know what else I don't like?
The people I know, which is several of them.
That bitch to me about like the grossness of Trump
and capitalism and money grabbing others.
And then in the same breath are telling me how awesome
the Avengers Infinity War was.
That is Trump.
It doesn't get more corporate America than that.
There is only one company that could have afforded
to make this movie.
Disney, you know, the company that's literally about
to monopolize the entertainment industry because they're buying every single production
company in studio.
That's the same fucking thing.
It's so annoying anyway.
It's ridiculous.
It's too much.
We're back to America, you know, well, America needs to learn our place, then stop making
everything bigger and better and anyway.
Well, if it call I would imagine it costs $250 million. They make it across. They make a billion worldwide.
You're not even close. Three to four hundred million dollars nuts. And it's now made two billion
one point two billion dollars worldwide. Well, so they're just going to keep coming, but I mean,
you could make four hundred really good decently budgeted indie movies literally for the same cost.
literally four excuse me four hundred yeah so anyway so then I
carefully pick your scripts and shit you're gonna get Oscars you know like
you don't throw four hundred darts and not have some bulls eyes in the mix
and you're making things that you can sleep about I'm sure these people sleep
just fine so the Guardians pick up these movies the Guardians pick up Thor yeah now
Now, this is, mark my words.
This is all this movie then becomes at this point,
is seen after scene of introductions,
to characters you all know and love.
It's like, it's like a, like, like,
it's like a, it's like the first episode
of the Rosanne reboot or something.
It's like, we're gonna reintroduce everybody now.
It's been 20 years.
Let's give everybody a big entrance,
except this is a movie where everybody
you've you've seen all these fucking people eight months ago in the other movies
they were yeah so that's what suicide squad was to different song for each
person yeah yeah I guess you were meeting them at least exactly but to us as
quite suck so but anyway so so Thor gets thrown down to I mean wait Hulk gets
thrown down to earth and he lands in Dr. Stranger's house so you're like oh shit
the wars and doctor strangers together they don't know each other and this is what I love to
Hulk is like
We got to we got to move fast. They know it's just coming. We got to move fast and strange is still like who are you?
What are you talking about?
Under a year ago, I watched you go into another dimension and bend time against gods of the universe
You have the audacity to question the authenticity of this man
They do the same thing.
Then they call Tony Starkin.
Tony Stark's like, who the fuck are you and your cape?
It's like, haven't you seen enough of this already
to know that this is the way things are going
in your world?
People wear capes?
I'm not saying this movie.
Then Hulk is like, listen.
Banner I mean, it's like, listen, Tony.
Doc, strange.
We gotta get the team back together.
Right.
And strange is like, who's the team?
Somehow he doesn't know who the Avengers are.
Stark's like, you want me to call Cap?
I'm not doing it.
We had a falling out.
They're literally telling the guy,
the world is about to end.
And we need to save it.
And Tony Stark is like, I'm not calling Cap.
We had a falling Cap.
What is happening?
He has to contemplate whether or not
He's going to patch it up with Captain America. And what are we 10 minutes in at this point?
I mean, I lost all track of time. My friend Bobby Kelly who's a dear friend of mine at a very
funny comedian told me this movie flies by. It feels like it's an hour long. I called him after
this thing. I go fuck you dude. This was every minute of two and a half hours. This thing people love
him. People love him. So anyway, but what's weird to me is that comic books
Unless they they are not anymore, but they were always sort of fringe things, you know, like
The nerds would go for comic books
So how did it become this thing now where everyone loves this shit?
They shouldn't have this universal appeal because they're
Really weird. They're not that entertaining
Because everyone loves them across the board
It's the nerds that supported these things and I did I was into them. Yeah, and I'm not gonna open up the fucking Batman superman cannon worms
But my taste is all I'm gonna say look I shit on Justice League. I shit on suicide squad
My taste is not changed since I was a kid right like Batman for the same reasons then that I do now
I like that like that it's dark. I like that. It's creepy. Yeah, it's why I like Gotham
it's why I like Batman vs. I like a brooding bat. I like that. That's what I like. A lot of
these nerds in my opinion grew up in the same way I did and fucking got soft and now
want to go see a goddamn popcorn watered down version of a thing they loved. Not one of
them is criticizing the fact that all of these Marvel movies are missing grit or missing edge
or anything that the comic books have. I like the comic book versions. I don't like the movie
Then they all say the same thing. It's just amazing. They pulled it off. It's like, well, okay, that is amazing
But I'm sorry. I'm not impressed by the fact that the biggest fucking movie company on the planet
Right figured out how to contract contract
72 with the biggest stars on the planet. It's like I'm supposed to be fucking impressed by that like yeah, yeah, okay
I guess that's a feat, but whatever anyway, that's what you know you've been complaining lately about
your job prospects yeah you need to get in one of these Marvel movies you need
to get in the Marvel universe and they'll pay you forever who am I gonna play
they make you'll be in four movies a year that's that's agents talk but you get
yourself a role as one of the key Avengers so that you're gonna be in all these
movies then even once you're not in they're like you're getting that call so
You and Scar Jo flying out together.
Let me get to Scar Jo dating a dear friend of mine,
Colin Joes.
Your dear friend is Colin Joes.
I wouldn't say dear friend, but I've known Colin for years.
We're friends.
When I went to CSNL, I hung out in Colin's dressing room
and we were, we were, we were for a very friendly.
Well, then he must be different than he appears in the shows.
I always thought he was a smug ass.
He's a very friendly guy and he's very, very funny
and he's a very nice guy.
All right all right so anyway, so you know Thanos is gonna send the fucking ship down to earth to kill everybody because there's two infinity stones here
One's got one is in Dr. Stranger's hands and the other is in
Vision's head. So now we jump to his vision. Exactly. You know, you remember when Tony Stark's computer turned into a person
Paul by play by Paul Bettany. You want to talk about three elements put together in a sentence
that I don't ever give a shit about? Which, when did that happen? Ironman?
No, it happened in like Infinity War. This is what it happened in the age of Ultron.
The computer is Siri, whatever the fuck it was called, turns into Paul Bettany.
Yeah, I remember them. All right. Who's in love with the youngest of the
sisters, the Olsen sisters, who is seemingly somehow more boring than the other two.
Well, I love her and Ingrid goes west and Indy type things.
Well, I need to see the movie, Martha Marcy May, Marlene about Colts, great, great movie.
All right.
I'll give her a good one.
And scary, by the way.
I've only ever seen her in these movies and in Godzilla.
Oh, boy.
Uh, anyway, with uh, Cranston. Yeah.
What a bad movie that was. Terrible. Well -reviewed.
Because everybody's on the payroll these fucks.
Anyway, then they go, I don't know. Then you're in Scotland and vision is there because this chick is fucking this computer man
and for some reason, she's in love with him.
So Vision is a key villain, Paul Bettany.
No, he's not a villain.
He's got this stone in his head
and he's like Thanos is coming for the stone.
And then Bettany, like any computer will it goes,
just rip the stone out of my head and destroy it.
And then his girlfriend is like,
no, I can't do that, I love you too much.
This whole movie, it's the opposite of Star Trek.
Remember the whole thing in Star Trek
and the original movies with Spock,
the needs of the many out need the need out the way the need.
Spock sacrifices himself at the end of Rathakon.
Fucking heart breaking, it's amazing.
He's like, I'm gonna kill myself to save everybody.
This movie's the exact opposite.
It's everybody being like, well, I could destroy the stone,
but then that would mean my girlfriend
wouldn't be here anymore.
It's also like ripped the stone out.
The robot will probably still be standing there.
If not, put a couple of cords in his back together
and he's up in Adam again. It's a robot. Apparently it's more than a robot. It doesn't make any sense.
Oh, then a robot. That's the same thing that happens. Here's my question.
We've been talking for 10 minutes. I've heard 25 major characters' names, minimum.
Oh, we're not even close. Why are we bringing tribute in the talking robot lover? Tribute.
Triumph
Why are they bringing him in vision vision try up the insult comic robot. Why are they bringing in this new character
That seems completely pointless. He came in because he because pat you saw him in a movie for seven minutes
Three years ago, right he's got to come back because everybody has to be in this fucking thing
I'm even get yet to spider -man coming into it who they went and pulled out of the Sony network
to get into this goddamn movie,
because this fucking thing wasn't jam -packed enough.
Now they're bringing over Spider -Man.
The kids Spider -Man from Hong Kong movies.
And they couldn't get Deadpool.
Do you pay?
People are pissed that Deadpool's not in it.
This isn't enough.
Where's Wolverine?
Where's Deadpool?
How much do you fucking psychos want?
You're sick!
Well, then it's like how then when like a Wolverine comes out,
But how was anybody supposed to get excited about that anymore?
I was excited about my parents who's a comedian
and likes these movies.
And I don't know how I feel about these,
but he said once after the first Avengers movie came out,
and I don't know if he still feels this way,
but I agreed with him.
And he was a big fan of that movie.
He goes, I don't understand.
Like now they're gonna do another Captain America.
Why wouldn't he just call the Avengers?
Right.
Any problem you have, why wouldn't you just call the,
and it's like, yeah, no, that's exactly right.
It doesn't make any fucking sense anymore.
So anyway, now Spider -Man's in the mix.
He's flinging webs and he gets sucked up into space
with Tony Stark on the subject.
Is he trying to get the infinity stones?
He's trying to protect them.
So now wait, Tony Stark was dabbling
with Spider -Man in the homecoming picture.
Yeah.
Yeah, so they cross over into the Sony verse all the time, yeah, okay.
So they're in space, Peter Parker should die because they're in space, but luckily Tony
Stark has a Spider -Man suit in his pocket.
After he tells Spider -Man to leave, he's got a Spider -Man suit in his pocket that, you know,
out of a quarter turns into like an Iron Man Spider -Man suit, so Spider -Man now can be
space. Uh, okay. Thor, he ends up somewhere with the guardians of the galaxy and they have to
ignite a star. Is anyone fuck in any of these Avengers pictures? No, no, no.
Uh, why don't they fuck? They're all incredibly hot in the prime of their lives.
They're they have common goals. What's his face? Why aren't they fucking? What's his face? His girlfriend gets killed
It should be like the goddamn Olympic village every time you turn on Avengers
Everyone should start with them all fucking. Yeah. Now what's his face? His girlfriend gets killed
Maybe that's why they don't fuck I bet that for the green the green lady from yeah guardians
Thanos tosses her right off a cliff. I killed her so she doesn't even get the
it shouldn't even get to die in her own franchises movie.
No, she dies in this movie.
Okay.
A couple people die and it made me happy.
Quite frankly, because get some of these goddamn characters.
They gotta clear out some of them.
I hope they killed off fucking Aero man from the Avengers.
He's not even in it.
Hawk?
He never shows up.
Good.
Who the hell wants to see Jeremy run a running run?
Are you sure he wasn't in it for 45 minutes
and you didn't notice?
He's not in it.
Because that's what that character brought you to him.
And that's another one thing that pisses me off about these films.
Where is it?
Scarlett Johansson Black Widow still going strong comes into every fright not a suit. I've never seen her punch anyone
Not a god damn shield not a superpower. Just coasting through these fucking battles that four is having a hard time with never seen her throw a punch
Anyway, it is hawk mentioned no not mentioned no, and they finally killed it too
Idris Elba, people are like, can you believe they killed Idris Elba?
I'm like, he has three lines in every movie, get rid of him, get rid of some
characters. He's like the gatekeeper in Thor's house. And that's the kind of
role that you need to get. Yes, you got three lines you walk in, you walk out, but
you're part of the universe because everybody, plus then now we're doing these
the inclusion writers. So Idris Elba can be like, yeah mate, I'll do you free
lines and avenges eternity wars. But I'll tell you this, you pay me the same thing. You pay in
Chris Pine. Well, I could do that, too, because I'm a little bit...
Chris Pine in these pictures? He was in Wonderwall. He's Star Trek.
Paying me the same thing, you pay in Chris Pratt, mate. So, I could do that. I'm going to do that.
Play up my Middle Eastern, right? Yeah. Anyway, so Spider -Man and Thor are in space with different
people and then Thor has to harness the power of a star to make a hammer and he makes it
and he's able to endure the power of a star flying through his body, yet Thanos can still beat
him up. Try to figure that one out. Thanos normal size or giant? He's not even Hulk, he's like kind
a Hulk size. Okay. And then Thanos kills Gamora. And then Thanos lets his plan be known
finally, which is, now I dig this. Alright, this is the part I kind of agreed with. Alright.
All the good guys are like, this guy is nuts. We got to stop him. Thanos is like, I'm not nuts.
You people can't be trusted with the universe.
All you did was over -occupy it.
Population is out of control.
That's why people are in this scene.
Yeah.
Because that's why people are starving.
He goes, you know what happened to the planets
I went and got rid of half the people?
Happy children, they're all eating.
Because this is what happens.
You leave it to the humans, they ruin everything.
That's true.
And he goes, all I want to do is wipe out half of the people,
randomly, I'm not gonna select, okay, it's not a genocide, I'm just gonna randomly remove
half of the people, and then everybody can have enough supplies and shit again.
I'm with Thanos. It makes sense. I'm with Thanos. And for two reasons, one, if I'm not
in the group that's killed, I get to enjoy the spoils. Two, if I am in the group that's killed,
I'm dead. Yeah, it's a win -win for me. Yeah, and then you got Tony Stark being like that's out of line, man
You don't know you're talking about it's like Tony. Why don't you go back to your hot tub connected to a helicopter?
Seriously? Get out of my face, you billionaire cunt. Why wouldn't if you're Tony Stark
Wouldn't you just stay at home and enjoy your the life that you've made for yourself?
Who the hell knows? Yeah, goops it's why I still in this it was why I was shown
that into the Civil War, Captain America,
they fucking ripped off Batman and said,
and all of a sudden it was Tony Stark's parents
were murdered by the winter soldier
and that fuck you, fuck you.
That's Batman's thing, that's what defines Batman.
That's why he's Batman and they just fucking took it.
Anyway, so at the end, there's a big battle.
I think it's in Wakanda, Black Panther shows up.
And that happens, that doesn't happen till the end.
Sort of toward the end, and then is the whole Black Panther gang involved?
A lot of them.
I bet this thing costs more than $400 million.
And then Bruce Banner at the end is in the Iron Man Hulk suit because he can't turn
into Hulk, which is stupid writing because it's like, if you're not going to have him turn
into Hulk, why are you putting him in the Hulk armor suit?
Why can't he turn into Hulk, drank too much?
They don't explain it.
He goes it's just a little problem I've been having and he goes we got to talk big guy
They don't explain it. No, they don't do some little thing like I guess I'm not as angry as I do
Like that would be a funny bit
He's gotten in touch with his anger because he started going to therapy, but now he can't become the Hulk
That that took me four seconds to think of you went from a movie where he literally could be the Hulk at will
Right to a movie where he can't turn into the Hulk and he doesn't understand why
And he's a scientist right anyway mumbling it even big battle out of the fucking Wakanda thing and
Thanos wins
And then half of the Avengers disappear into dust and die
That and that's what everybody's upset about yeah, and people are going now
Let me tell you the ones that disappear and just to die okay, okay, okay
Starward Chris Pratt
from Guardians. Black Panther, Spider -Man, right there off the bat. These fucking idiot fans are
going, I just, I can't believe they're dead. They're not dead. They're, they're already making
their next movies. Chris Pratt is literally in the press every day talking about how awesome
Guardians of the Galaxy 3 is. Nobody is dead. One of the people so upset about, because they're
Idiots
But aren't the smart people I've seen who are upset about it? Are they just upset that it ends abruptly?
Does it end abruptly? I've met smart people that
Yeah, because they can't wait for fucking months to see these characters in a movie again
Right. That's what a cliffhanger is now, but now every one of these movies has to start with an explanation of why they're not dust anymore now, too
One of the snowmen is idiots watching these movies and making the biggest things in the world one of the
Stones is the time stone these movies are Trump you can reverse time with the time stone
Yeah, that's one of the things you can do Thanos does it at one point and saves himself from being killed
Right, so they're obviously that what Dr. Stranger's doing with that time loop at the end of strange
We kept fucking with that fire monster Pat who the hell can remember and who the hell could give a shit
It was a pretty stupid bit. I just don't care. I don't care anymore
or the movie for what it was.
I don't care, I don't know.
Was fine?
Yeah.
It was for me too, too much too late.
I've seen the film already.
These things are just on repeat as far as I'm concerned.
There's zero suspense.
Anytime somebody dies, I don't believe they're dead
as we've established.
Right.
I can't get into a movie where that's the case.
No.
Can't do it.
Comedy or something, maybe, but that's it.
now so to have an action movie where no death is permanent you you're you're
ruining the whole point of an action movie there's no thrills there's no
suspense and then I love this right here's the hidden scene ready yeah it's
Nick Fury comes in finally Jackson in the movie yeah see has he been in any of
of these movies in an acting role outside of the end credits.
Yeah, he's been in a lot of them,
but he hasn't been around for a while
because he's supposedly dead.
He got killed in Captain America winner soldier.
Okay.
Now he's back because nobody stays dead.
It's like a fucking Freddie Krueger thing at this point.
It's ridiculous.
Anyway, he's like, ah, we got trouble.
We better send out the signal or whatever.
And he sends out a signal on his page
And you see that it's like the Captain Marvel segment. He's calling Captain Marvel. It's like
It's like so how many times you guys gonna do this bullshit where it's like uh -oh now we're in over our heads
I better call in yet another super hero and also
Captain Marvel exists and doesn't know this is fucking happening right now. There's an all -out war happening on planet Earth
So we haven't seen Captain Marvel yet in the Avengers diverse
Nope.
And who is portraying Captain Marvel?
What's your face?
Brie Larson.
They're making Captain Marvel a woman or Captain Marvel is always a woman.
In Marvel, Captain Marvel is a woman.
Okay.
In DC, Captain Marvel is Shazam.
DC's came to be the first.
Marvel stole Captain Marvel.
I love Brie Larson.
and I don't want to see her go down this road.
She's already down it.
She was in Kong Skull Island.
Yeah, that's true.
This is what everybody does.
They, they, they, you know, my hat's off to Clooney.
Clooney's the only one where it was like, he was like,
yeah, I made a shit movie, Batman and Robin.
You know what that movie meant?
I meant I could do any fucking movie I want to do now
because I made enough money.
Now I'm doing a movie about when they used
to wear leather helmets and football.
That was a terrible move.
Bad example.
But I'm just saying like yeah like like nobody does it like Merrill Streep's another great example
She did a couple big things and she's like now. I'm gonna go do this Woody Allen movie in
1977 that shot in all black and white
Yeah, what do you mean like nobody does that anymore? Yeah, the one for me one for you has kind of gone away and a world where you can make
$4 million to do three days work on Avengers 5
Then it's like oh now that I've tasted that I'm not going back to doing these interesting movies
Anyways, anyway, that's your Avengers.
The hogs up or hogs down.
My hog is down.
I actually will not see this movie.
That's my pledge to you.
Even with a movie pass sitting in my wallet
where I can drive 10 minutes and see it for free.
And I initially had a hogs up,
but I'm going to hogs down on this one too.
And folks, let us know if you like this format.
I thought this worked out very well.
I thought this was very fun.
Why was your hog up?
I mean, when I saw it initially, I was like,
you know what, I'm not gonna be a prick.
I guess it wasn't that bad.
And then the more and more I thought about it the more angry I got and the more I didn't like it and then explaining it to you
I realized even more how much I think it's stupid right but let us know if you like this new take occasionally for movie reviews
jokes and
Avengers. Oh, yeah, how many not as bad as Thor, but enough jokes and
They all there's one funny joke where spider -man goes on Peter Parker
to Dr. Strange, and Dr. Strange goes,
Steven Strange, I'm Dr. He goes, I'm Dr. Strange,
and Peter Parker goes, oh, we're using our made -up names.
Okay, cool, I'm Spider -Man.
And I was like, that's a funny joke
because I always thought it was funny that no,
or weird that nobody ever said like,
so your last name is actually Strange,
and you're a strange sort of a superhero.
That joke's funny at all.
Well, that's an affront on me and the cops.
Sorry, I don't like it
or I didn't like your performance of it.
one or the other. Folks, we are not taking the haters now. We've got a few more coming
your way. Well, no, no, that's not true. We have one more coming their way. One more
coming your way. And we're going to do the bonus up for May. The bonus up and hopefully
one more regular app. But then the hiatus will happen. Yes. We'll let you know what's going
on with that via the Facebook page, which you should be a member of. We've crossed a thousand
members. Thank you guys and gals and all the people around. I'm on Twitter and Instagram
at the Badger Walls. That's all I got folks. Jota Rosa Comedy on Instagram and Twitter
and come see me and say hello at Rooster Teeth Feathers in the Silicon Valley last week in
It's it! See you next time.