I'll see you in hell.
We're back. We'll see you in hell.
Episode two, number two.
Episode two, this is a big one tonight.
Nightmare in Elm Street.
Nightmare in Elm Street, one episode two.
Directed by Wes Craven.
The movie, not the episode.
He also directed the podcast tonight.
He's not happy with our performance thus far.
Get out of here, come on.
We're thrilled to be here doing this with the Fengoria podcast network,
newly launched Fengoria podcast network.
A proud moment for both of us.
I'm Joe DeRosa.
I'm Pat Walsh.
Thrilled is extreme for me.
I'm having a nice time.
But I wouldn't say thrilled.
Fair enough.
I mean, you want to bite the hand that feeds.
No, absolutely.
Listen, so we're jumping right in.
I feel like we open the series with children of the corn.
And now the second episode, we're going right to Nightmare in Elm Street.
I don't think it gets any more classic horror than this.
It doesn't.
We discussed doing leprechaun.
Pat made the point of he didn't want people to think it was a thing where we were just
making fun of movies because I don't think anybody thinks leprechaun is a great horror movie.
No.
But we wanted it to be.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
We wanted it to be.
I wanted that remake, that new one that came out to be awesome.
The new leprechaun?
Leprechaun origins.
Really?
Is that happened?
Oh, yeah.
I didn't know about that.
I met Ricky Gervais once on a radio show and I said, why, of all the things you made fun
of on Life's Too Short, did you never make fun of leprechaun?
And he was like, oh, mate, I'm sure we did.
It was just, he probably got cut.
Oh, okay.
Fair enough.
Anyway.
I'm cackled like a madman and told you he didn't believe in God.
Yeah.
Let's fire it up.
I actually get tense when we're talking and you haven't started it.
I don't know why because this goddamn Apple TV, you know, it does this on and off thing.
Yeah.
All right.
So we'll count to three and then say search and that's your cue to pause the podcast.
Search for Nightmare and Elm Street on your, whatever your device for streaming is.
You know, these are all movies that are on Netflix and stay.
You can go ahead and search for it now.
You don't need to count down to search.
Well, it's just like I'm going to wipe your ass for you.
You know, let's give them.
I'm fine.
Nightmare and Elm Street.
We'll say play.
You do a play and then immediate pause.
We're all on the pause screen.
And then we go one, two, three, play.
Yeah, but they need time to do that.
And it might not be fast enough.
So they're doing it now as we see it.
But what if they weren't?
Let's just give them a countdown.
Let's just be good.
Let's countdown everything you do.
All right.
Here's the countdown for you to go find.
When you hear me say search, you pause it.
You go, you find it, whatever.
One, what are they pausing?
The podcast.
So they can go find the fucking movie.
They're listening.
Just let them go do it.
One, two, three, search.
Like a dog.
Joe in the morning when he wakes up.
Before he brushes his teeth, I have to come over and go.
One, two, three, brush.
And then he brushes his teeth.
Now just in case you got confused because Pat talked
through the part where we're supposed to say we're back.
We're going to give you another chance.
One, two, three, search.
We're back.
Okay, here we go.
You've unpaused.
Now, this is how we do this.
You hit play.
And when it gets to the first frame of the screen,
you, of the movie, you hit pause again.
And the reason we do this is because load times vary, right?
Am I overexplaining this?
I feel like it couldn't be less complicated,
but being made more complicated.
Okay.
I'm trying my best.
What do you want to be?
But I just feel like people are going to get confused.
I worry about that too.
All you're doing, everybody.
And I think we might have to adapt this for a future one.
Is you're going to hit play and then hit pause.
So now we're all on a screen that has like one second or two seconds on it.
Right.
Because everybody's load time is different.
That's where we do that.
Everybody's load time is different.
Everybody's Wi -Fi is different.
Yeah, time warning.
You're going to be waiting 30, 40 minutes.
Oh!
As you would say.
You're going to do, uh, when we count down, one, two, three, play.
We all hit play.
Now we're going to watch.
Okay, so now you've got it paused.
Hopefully at this point.
I hope so, or else.
I mean, if you don't, I don't know.
I don't know how you hit play on this podcast.
Okay.
Okay, so here we go.
Uh, on, uh, play.
One, two, three, play.
And it's playing.
There we go.
We got new from New Line Cinema.
New Line Cinema is on your screen.
All right.
Hopefully we're all on the same page.
And the thing I think you're missing, Joe, is that they don't need to pause the podcast.
They can look for this stuff while listening to us.
What if it takes some while?
What if you're dealing with a slow man?
I mean, I think that's all I'm saying.
I am dealing with a slow man.
Uh, he, he's always got to quip.
Now, I'd like to start with something completely unrelated.
In the last episode, we talked about how much of a disappointment the poltergeist remake was.
Right.
And we both speculated that perhaps the new vacation would not be up to par.
Uh, it's got to, I believe it 26 % has terrible reviews.
And Joe and friends, I'm here to tell you I just came from seeing it.
And it is extremely funny.
The vacation remake.
There are a lot of big laughs in it.
Here's the fuck out of you.
Now, whenever they go for a huge, like a set piece, a huge over -the -top scene, those don't really work.
But everything else works.
And now I'm going to confuse it even further by telling you I didn't love Ed Helms or Christina Applegate in it.
But I thought the movie was really funny.
I thought you were going to go into a thing about the nightmare in Elm Street.
Oh, we're going to get there.
Okay.
But I thought it was very funny.
And the kids in this remake are so fucking funny.
The little kid, basically, the one gimmick is that it's a younger brother, bullying his older brother.
I thought those parts in the trailer were funny.
That's how you show.
That kid cracked me up.
The little kid in that movie, both of them were great.
And the movie gave me a lot of laughs.
And I'm sorry, I spoke ill of it.
And nobody's telling me to say that.
I promise.
Then why is it getting such bad reviews?
I think critics just kind of generally hate comedy.
I'd love to sit next to these people and see if they truly didn't laugh throughout the movie.
I can't believe that.
You're telling me this movie's...
All right, I'm going to believe it.
Listen, here's where I'm going to believe it.
Terminator Genesis, as we talked about in the last episode, terrible reviews.
Yeah.
Terrible reading.
I love every minute of it.
I might just start going with the opposite.
And Rotten Tomatoes is usually, if you really read the reviews,
it's like, oh, this is a good review, and they're putting it as a bad or vice versa.
Okay, fair enough.
But I'm telling you right now, it's very funny.
I usually go by what Richard Roper says.
I'm a big Richard Roper fan.
Sure.
Well, he's a very incisive film crew.
If you're watching the film along with us, which, you know, you don't have to do.
I guess we should have mentioned that at the top.
I forgot to.
But, you know, you don't have to watch the movie along with us.
You can just kind of listen to this.
Just walking through some pipes.
But if you are watching, she's walking through some pipes.
Now I'm having anxiety about the fact that we didn't tell them at the beginning.
They didn't have to watch the movie.
Well, no, they know.
Do they?
Yeah, we have a whole description of.
Remember?
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Okay, good enough.
Good enough.
I worry about everything.
Here we go.
Also, I wish we had slammed Peter Travers because he's a far worse critic than Richard Roper.
No, I really meant what I said.
I like Richard Roper.
I like him too.
He's a very like man of the people type.
Yeah.
I loved Ebert.
Ebert's my favorite of all time.
There's no better film critic.
I don't know if I'd be doing what I'm doing with that Roger Ebert.
Here's my favorite Ebert review.
You ready?
He said, uh, Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull loved it.
And he said, uh, was it as good as the first one or the second one or the third one?
I don't know.
That's like asking me if I ate four pounds of sausage, which pound was the most delicious.
Oh.
Well, I'll tell you that fourth pound was not the most delicious one.
You should have a little better memory than that.
It was a great analogy.
My favorite Ebert review is of a horror movie.
M. Knight's Lomalon's The Village.
Uh -huh.
And it's such a funny, perfectly written review and I urge you to look it up online because I won't do it justice.
But the final paragraph of it is such perfect, funny, trashing the movie comedy writing.
What did he say?
Okay.
Uh, we'll see.
I just said, if you should probably look it up.
I'm going to botch it.
But the gist of it was, uh, it's the kind of twist that may, I'm going to botch it.
It's the kind of twist that makes you want to, I'm going to botch it.
Look at it.
You're saying you're going to botch it as if it was smooth sailing up until this point.
Will you forced me to say it when I said, God damn it, Joe.
Now here's a part that I'm glad you asked that question.
And this is a thing I was always slightly confused about in the, in the original nightmare in industry.
Is she, are these children dancing and singing really there?
Or is she dreaming this right now?
Because look, this is reality.
And they shot that in a very ghostly way.
Yeah.
Were those supposed to be the girls that Freddie molested?
Well, they'd never say molested in this, in this original.
That's something they more clarified in the remake, which I enjoyed.
Uh, I know people say it sucked, but it did suck.
To those people, I say you didn't see parts four, five, and six in the theater.
Sure.
Like I did.
I mean, it was just nice to have a scary Freddie back again.
I was happy about that.
New nightmare was good.
Did you like Freddie versus Jason?
Uh, I like it now.
I had to watch an interview with the director who said he wanted to make like a classic monster fight movie.
Uh -huh.
Like a Godzilla versus King Kong, like over the top crazy, whatever.
Once I saw that and understood where he was coming from with it, I was like, okay, now I like it.
Right.
But I had to see that because I went into the theater.
Again, opening day.
And from the minute in the opening monologue where Freddie goes, then they forgot about me.
And that's a bitch.
I was just like, what is he going to surfboard right now?
I never liked his wise cracks.
But I went into Freddie versus Jason thinking it was a legal thriller along the lines of like Kramer versus Kramer.
And they would each have attorneys and maybe it was a divorce case.
For custody of the kids.
Yes.
That's the other kids that they would no less.
Yeah.
For murder.
For some less murder of these children.
Uh -huh.
Going back to vacation for no reason since it says an vacation podcast.
But when you watch the new movie, note that there's a bizarre obsession with pedophilia jokes.
Like there's 80 of them.
And they're not all great.
Now wonder why they wouldn't take some out.
It's a little weird.
Who's making the pedophilia jokes?
They're everyone.
Everyone in the movie is basically hinted at as being kind of a pedophile.
Want to make note again.
Second episode in a row.
Strong pedophilia theme.
I'm telling you.
Once again.
It's on the brain.
What?
Well, watching a movie about a pedophile.
One of the most famous pedophiles ever.
He's not quite a pedophile in this one.
What are you talking about?
He's a child murder in this one.
They don't ever say the pedophile thing.
Sure they do, don't they?
No.
They make a point to say it in the remake.
And if you watch any behind the scenes stuff with the remake,
they say like we wanted to make them even more unlikable.
So we brought out the pedophile under tones.
I thought for sure they did.
I mean, I guess the assumption is in this that he is.
I mean, yeah.
You know, Johnny Depp here is 17.
I think his age is gorgeous.
He's just beautiful.
Yeah.
Now he looks kind of like Stephen Tyler floated up on the beach.
But still beautiful in it.
He looks like Stephen Tyler got raped by Stevie Ray Vaughan's scarf collection.
Or Stephen Tyler's scarf collection.
Both Stevens, big on scarves.
Yeah.
That's true.
Now, which of these two were you more attracted to?
Heather Langenka, or I don't remember Tina's real name, but the blonde.
I think I'd go with the blonde.
I think she turns me on a little bit more.
She's a little bit pixie vibe.
No, I always loved Langenka.
I like to run a ABC TGIF sitcom called Just Ten of Us about a family of basketball players.
Yeah, that movie was a coach.
That sitcom was shot about eight years after this.
And she played a character two years younger.
Yeah, that's true.
Which always confused me.
But I did like his spin off a growing paint.
That's true.
It was a good show.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
And then now scream, which we also took bandied about viewing and talking about tonight.
And which we will in the future.
Of course we will.
But scream, I guess clearly, those are lots of this movie directed by the same guy.
And they found the exact same person, Skeet Ulrich, to play the Johnny Depp.
Like you wouldn't know they were different men at that time.
What happened, Skeet Ulrich?
Where are you?
I don't know.
I guess maybe because his name was Skeet.
And then when it hit the rap world, his name basically represented coming on something.
It's one of my favorite Hollywood minute jokes by David Spade.
It was when he was big.
And they put a picture Skeet Ulrich and he went, hey Skeet, Johnny Depp called.
He wants his DNA back.
Yeah.
I love the balls of David Spade.
Like really not having any sort of film career at that point.
Just taking on the hugest people in Hollywood.
Got in trouble for it.
I know he trouble for it.
Yeah, Murphy.
Yeah.
But it's great stuff.
It's great stuff.
It's the good stuff.
It's the old stuff, as they say.
Now your favorite nightmare on Umstreet, is this one?
Yeah, I mean, when our question number one in my book is the best.
I think number three is the second best.
And I think seven is the third best.
Seven is the new nightmare.
I've only seen one, two, three, and new nightmare.
And then I've seen all the modern day ones that I thought were all kind of trashed.
Two's got some fun moments, but it's not a great movie.
But I put it above five and six without question.
There's a great documentary about the whole franchise that discusses the intent
homosexual overtones in nightmare known street two.
Yes.
And I got to tell you they weren't far off.
It's like a there's a really interesting thing going on there.
And it's like not that suddenly done either.
No, no, it's written or directed by a gay guy.
I think a gay guy wrote it.
And there's a tremendous documentary called Never Sleep Again.
That's what I'm talking about, yeah.
On Netflix where he's like laughing like.
Yeah, I just thought it was fun to put like a lot of gayo undertones through the whole thing.
Oh, it made the movie a blast to watch.
I like it.
Wow, they're.
Yeah, you got that fucking gym teacher that's like I'm going to make you do laps at midnight.
Yeah, because you caught me in a gay bar now hit the showers.
Yeah, exactly.
And then Freddie chooses to whip him.
Yeah.
Freddie like whips him while masturbating or something like that.
The one part I didn't agree about it with was when they go.
And that documentary, they're like, it's clearly a gay metaphor when he.
Could run.
He's with the woman that he loves and he leaves her to run and retreat to his friend's bedroom.
Yeah.
And I was like, well, he runs away because he's going to turn into Freddie and kill her and he's terrified.
Right.
And he goes to his boy's house like that's what any guy that age would do.
I think he also though has like a pretty lengthy choreographed dance in his bedroom.
Yeah, that ends with him popping a cork as his dick.
There it is.
Yeah, it's a it's an enjoyable film though.
The part with the bird bursting into flames is pretty crazy.
Yeah, I remember that.
And then the end is the standard house party.
Actually, horror movies don't give you a lot of like house party getting attacked by a killer.
Wes Craven says in that documentary that was the part where he realized that he was like they blow it.
It's off the rails.
Why is Freddie appearing in real life?
Yeah, there's something like if there's that many people around,
you're not that scared because it's kind of like well, at least you're there in it with people.
And then watching it, you're like, well, they're not going to kill everybody.
By the way, if you're watching along with us, Rick just came inside of Tina.
I mean, he might have pulled out.
We don't know.
He might have had a rubber in those days.
They're wondering who Rick is.
He's the guy that you can't tell if he's Italian or Puerto Rican.
He's just kind of right up the middle there.
Maybe a black Irish.
Nobody knows.
Is there some, there's a little nudity in this I think.
We were bemoaning last night the lack of nudity in the horror genre, which I think is a real shame.
Because you could always count on teen movies and you could always count on horror movies.
And now neither, and usually they're PG 13 in both cases.
I watched mirrors this afternoon starting the great key for Sutherland.
And you see Amy Smart from the back naked.
I remember that.
You see her butt.
I mean, it's just a tremendous shot.
And I was out by myself.
It was three o 'clock in the afternoon.
And when they showed her ass, I went, ooh, nice.
Which should mean, yeah, I should be never allowed to be to date ever again.
Yeah.
It's a fairly real creep.
Ooh, nice.
Now don't say that in real life when you see a, when I see Amy Smart naked.
When you're making love to Amy Smart.
Who would not be doing anything particularly smart that night?
I'll tell you that much.
Look at this hospital blanket.
They have on the bed.
This is great.
This is crazy.
Blue hospital blanket.
I want to say last night I said, I made some remark that I didn't know if any girls would be listening to this podcast.
And I want to retract that.
It was a very sexist and stupid thing to say.
And I know many girls who watch horror movies.
I don't know why I said it.
I can't believe that's the thing you're worried about after saying that the happiness is a tremendous film.
A lot of people think happiness is a great film.
The film's going to be good about difficult subjects.
I just want to mark two episodes in a row.
Lots of pedophilia talk and talk of the gay undertones in a horror movie.
Because last night we got into the molester that made powder in fun house.
Look.
Or fun.
Was it fun house?
It was called the fun house.
The fun house.
The Frances Ford Copeland.
I believe.
Oh no.
What's the movie Sam Rockwell?
Sam Rockwell is very, it has a very early film.
That's a horror movie.
It's not fun house though.
That I do not know.
I can't remember.
This one of my favorite parts of the movie when Freddie comes through the rubbery, he makes the wall into like a latex.
Just really great, cheap, well done special effects that don't look cheap.
As compared to our last one, the children of the corn.
Look at that.
That looks perfect.
And you know this movie had no budget.
Yeah, and it looks really shit.
And children of the corn decided to put like a sticker over the screen to represent a man.
And turning to flames.
But by the way, this whiskey I picked up today is delectable.
What's the name of it?
Let's give him a shout out.
I can't remember.
I left it in the other room.
Pop a bourbon's drink hutch.
Something like that.
Yeah.
I think uh.
Oh, I don't know how to afford it.
Whiskey Dick so howling hand.
Something like that.
I haven't met him once or twice.
Good guy.
Great whiskey.
Sure.
Any uh, you think there may be doing a little Christ symbolism with Freddie coming out of the wall in front of that crucifix?
I don't know what it would be, and I'm not smart enough to speak further on that, but maybe they are.
Well, is that Ernie?
That cookie jar is Ernie, right?
Yes, that's an Ernie cookie jar from the back.
Good eye, Pat.
Thanks, Pat.
Uh, I never noticed that.
Good eye.
Absolutely.
Uh, I think the, I don't think that's Christ symbolism.
I think it's supposed to be, the symbolism is he knocks Jesus off the wall.
Like, yeah, yeah, yeah.
God can't protect you.
Sure.
When he comes out of the rubber wall.
Is this a look you like the, uh, the lady in a dress shirt and no slack?
Does anybody not like it?
Just fantastic.
Is anybody complaining about this look?
I gotta say it doesn't happen much in my, uh, day to day life, but it happens in movies all the damn time.
Now, if you're watching along with us, and if you're not going to worry, it'll be described.
Uh, we're about to see a shot, and it's the scariest Freddie has ever been and will ever be.
They will never make Freddie scarier than this moment.
Tina is now in the alleyway.
They stole that shot from paper boy, the video game.
Yeah.
Of the trash can live right?
Well, it's like the park coming up where the guy on the boom box makes a car crash happen.
Yeah, exactly.
Uh, that is the scariest thing ever.
The long arm Freddie, and he's just laughing like a witch.
It's so fucking scary.
And it's something that would happen in a dream where you'd be like,
this is God puts the claw over his face.
There's that guy.
Look at the way he's running.
Yeah.
Oh, it's so scary.
And he's just toying with her.
That's what the great part is.
There he goes.
He disappears, reappears in front of her.
He can catch her if he wants, but he's going to have some fun going with her.
Now, going back to paper boy, the video game.
I...
But can we just, can we point out this part?
This is the second scariest thing Freddie ever does.
Joe, are we doing a paper boy, the video game podcast?
Are we doing a nightmare on Elm Street podcast?
Cuts the fingers off, and green slime jizzes out of the...
Yeah, that's pretty gross.
Fingers.
It should have been thicker and pusier.
Wow.
Sorry, Pat, that it didn't more closely resemble actual cum.
I apologize.
I do come green.
Well, do you ever see the watch Vince Vaughan movie?
I sure did.
I think you liked that quite a bit more than I did.
I loved it.
But my favorite joke is when the Indian guy is rubbing the green slime between his fingers,
and he says, it does feel like cum.
The taste, the color, the texture, and it's bright green.
Yeah.
And then you find out later in Ali, and you're like, oh, it's, yeah.
Right.
Ali and cum.
That's a good, I remember that joke.
Great joke.
This is amazing special effects right here.
It is.
Similar to the Joe Beth Williams and Poltergeist being thrown around the room.
Very similar.
Anything hotter than Joe Beth Williams and Poltergeist.
We didn't touch on that last episode.
I used to really, I would like, I would be like, this is going to be my wife.
I would like her to be Joe Beth Williams and Poltergeist.
And any more, any more of a dad than Craig T Nelson.
I know.
And what I also love is that that movie's PG and the parents are getting high up in their bedroom.
They're getting, they're sitting in bed getting high.
I love that about Poltergeist.
I'll tell you what my dream is.
You know, Sam Rockwell was in the Poltergeist remake.
Oh, and in that one, they'd drink a half a glass of whiskey instead of getting high, by the way.
Which tells you everything you know about the remake.
Yeah.
Here's my dream.
I want to make a coach remake starring Sam Rockwell now.
Okay, well, it's coming back to TV.
I know.
Let's get success.
Let's get Sam Rockwell in there.
Now, who's playing Doberth or Dwayne the Rock Johnson?
I'd put Dwayne the Rock Johnson in the Doberth role.
I'd put a tanning chaedum in the Doberth role.
Tanning chaedum?
I think you're done drinking.
We're 20 minutes in, you just said tanning chaedum.
Oh, Channing chaedum.
Sorry.
That's great casting though.
Yeah, no, it's good cast.
I'll see if tanning's available.
There's Michael Jackson from the beat of video just hanging out in the...
My take on Channing chaedum has always been that both of his name sound like things you'd call your taint.
Yeah, I could see that.
I wrote that as a joke for the Pete Homes show.
Did they deliver it?
Yeah.
Ooh, baby.
lick my Channing.
Or lick my taint.
And then again, then she goes, what do you mean?
And he goes, you know what I mean?
My taintum.
Yeah, correct.
Classic dirty stuff.
So, folks, ladies out there, if you ever consider having sex with Joe,
just know he might say things like lick my Channing, referring to his taint.
And he also, upon seeing your butt, might go, ooh, nice.
So, Nancy is now in the police station with her parents,
played by...
Home over Jones.
Jon Saxton.
From Enter the Dragon fame.
And...
You're literally clinging to his hair.
And a woman who is the most melodramatic actor of all time.
I've only ever seen her in...
I mean, this is just...
Yeah.
Look at the just weepy eyes.
She looks like Petunia Pig from the Looney Tunes.
Or something.
Who's Petunia Pig?
Porky's Girl from.
Who's Girlfriend?
Porky's.
Like the Minnie Mouse.
You know, Daisy Duck.
You're blending all kinds of cartoon worlds right now.
I'm saying they all had their girlfriend.
And Petunia Pig was the girlfriend.
Okay.
They're all boring, bland characters, unfortunately.
This guy should take some of his eyebrows and put it on top of his head.
I love Jon Saxton.
Do you ever see Enter the Dragon?
Of course, and I...
He's in Rambo, right?
Uh...
No, you're thinking of Richard Crenna.
No, I'm not.
I think Jon...
I know who Richard Crenna is, but I think he might be in Rambo, but maybe he's not.
He's in Rambo?
I thought he was.
Look, I don't know everything.
Well, I love Jon Saxton.
I mean, my first blood.
Same old.
I can't remember the line.
He says to Black Belt Jones in Enter the Dragon, but it's great.
Look at this lady hitting the Vodka at 7am.
There's something in this lady having common.
Anyway, Batch Paper Boy.
The obstacles in Paper Boy.
It's like trash can lid.
Guy with a boom box.
You know, Rabbit Dog.
Don't forget Rabbit Dog.
He's talking about Rabbit, just a dog.
And then within seconds, you're face -to -face with the Grim Reaper.
That's quite an escalation of obstacles, Paper Boy.
I don't know.
Is this a bit?
I don't know if it is.
Sounds like a bit to me.
Do you understand this to Jerry Seinfeld?
Which I believe is it?
Have you played this Paper Boy game?
Have you seen this thing?
Then shows up the Grim Reaper.
I remember encountering this guy many times in my paper.
I said five minutes ago, I'm dealing with a can of sprite.
Now I'm face -to -face with Grim Death.
That's...
I like...
I don't know if any video game has...
And you don't know who that guy is standing against the tree.
Is he real?
Is he not real? Is it in her head?
Is it not?
And I've seen this ten times.
He's just a dude watching her, man.
Like in a tiny dark girl.
But now he's gone.
Oh, out jumps the Italian and or a Puerto Rican kid.
Sure.
He's got her in the bushes now.
He's wearing a shirt and a leather jacket?
Here's what happens.
If you're not watching with a Tina, my favorite girl is now dead
because Freddie killed her with his long arms
and her boyfriend that gizzed inside of her just before that happened.
Right.
A boyfriend here played by a young Liza Manelli.
They think that he killed her, so he's on the lamb, if you will,
from the cops.
So now he's trying to tell Nancy he didn't do it,
but of course the cops show up because her dad's a cop.
And for some reason, he's in barefoot.
He's wearing old Navy jeans, no shirt, barefoot, and a leather jacket.
He's dressed exactly like Stanley Tucci was
and that Levi's commercially did all those years ago.
I know that's a deep cut people, but trust me, it exists.
Tucci in this outfit?
There's a Stanley Tucci Levi's commercial.
It was one of his first acting jobs.
It's out there.
Guys got a body like a rock.
Okay.
I wouldn't doubt that.
Now this is what I was going to ask was, wait a minute.
Oh, paper boy.
It wasn't a question.
It was what I was going to say about paper boy.
Yeah.
I don't know that any video game.
Look.
Oh, by the way, that's the lady from something about Mary.
It's not about Mary and now in Sidious.
And now in Sidious.
She got this role and the in Sidious role because her brother, Bob Shea,
is the head of New Line Cinema, but I think she's a great actress in her own right.
I love her to paint in Kingpin.
She's fantastic.
I love her to paint something about me.
And I'd like to have sex with a young Lin Shea here.
Really?
I would absolutely like to.
I'm not going that far, but I think she's a handsome woman.
I'd like to.
I would enjoy that.
She's a mousey.
I like it.
Sure.
Okay.
Great.
Now, by the way, third recurring theme, Kingpin, two episodes in a row.
Well, you figure out movies at least 90 minutes.
I'll never go 90 minutes without talking about Kingpin.
Sweet, sweet Kingpin.
Look at this shirt that this kid's wearing.
Yeah.
Looks like a stained glass window.
He's a guy that likes a party.
Right.
He's the guy that has a donkey at his party in the 80s.
Do you remember here?
Now, this should be a segment on the podcast.
When was the first time you saw this movie?
Do you remember?
Oh, yeah, man.
I was 11 years old, and I was obsessed with it.
Okay.
It was the greatest thing I'd ever seen.
I mean, this was my godfather at 11 years old.
Oh, okay.
Oh, that's disturbing.
Nancy's friend Tina just showed up in a body bag.
I think if I'm not mistaken, a worm is going to come out of her mouth in a minute.
I think so.
Or a snake of some kind.
Now, see, because of my fear of VHS horror boxes,
and the fact that I was not allowed to see already movies until I was actually 17 years old,
which really don't care for my parents doing that to me,
especially since I was obsessed with movies my whole life.
Sure.
I don't think I saw, and I'm not sure until I was about 17 years old,
and I thought this is pretty scary, but I had it built up my mind as though it was going to ruin my life.
It is a scary movie, for sure.
Well, think I like about 80s horror movies.
You get to notice how different the clothing styles were back then.
It's crazy how much things change in so little amount of time.
Nancy's dressed like my aunt Rita.
Well, some of these outfits are going to are kind of big in hipster circles,
like where we live here in the little city.
Nobody's wearing a pink sleeveless sweater.
You can see it out there.
With a collared shirt and khakis.
Baggy khakis.
This lady shows up in the documentary.
The Where's Your Past Lady?
She's not great.
No, I found it.
She's great right here, which turns into Freddy.
Yeah, I take it back. She's pretty good.
Yeah, she's awesome.
And there's leaves in the hallway when Nancy starts dreaming.
This is what makes this movie so great.
He adds these, Wes Craven was showing it adding these elements to the set,
to the different sets that really made it feel like a nightmare.
Like in the beginning, you see loose cattle running for no reason.
Yep.
Through a watery like boiler room hallway.
She's in her, she's running through her high school now.
The hallways are all dark.
There's leaves blowing around.
Freddy has the extended arms.
These are very specific qualities of nightmares.
And I think that's really what gave this movie.
Yeah, I mean, I've seen it a bunch and it always feels kind of fresh to me too.
Why do you think, because this movie, I think,
costs something like 5 million and made 50 or something like that, you know.
Horror movies usually make good money.
We can look it up.
Why aren't more horror movies good?
Well, they feel like they'll just make anything now and they're all kind of the same.
And why can't, like everyone's scared of stuff.
Why can't you put your own personal take on a horror movie and make it good?
It's my philosophy that horror most of the time gets the porn treatment.
And they say, well, as long as you have your money shot, it's who cares.
Yeah, true.
And the money shot in a horror movie is a kill.
And I think that just like with porn, you know,
there are the Bert Reynolds guys from Boogie Nights being like,
I want to make a film.
Oh, look, Freddy had maggots coming out of his body.
There are those Bert Reynolds type saying I want to make a film
and I want to make something truly erotic.
And then there are other guys saying it doesn't matter.
Yeah.
Have people fuck on camera for as cheap as possible.
That's all that that's all I mean, but he cares about.
So the best example of like a porny type horror movie is like the Final Destination series
where it's just kill, kill, kill.
But those are really fun.
Yeah.
Like I just put the time in and have a clever kill, you know, at the very least.
I like that series.
All of those have really good kills.
Well, this is why I can't believe that you're a fan of the Jeepers creepers franchise.
Look, maybe I'll rewatch it.
I really enjoy Jeepers creepers.
Please don't rewatch it till we can rewatch it on here.
Yeah, for sure.
I just, I'm dumbfounded that you thought that movie was good.
I don't know.
Sometimes it just happened to be out of the house, you know, when I go to a movie.
I'm like, yeah, I like that.
But it came out when we were like 17 or something.
No, it came out when I was living in New York.
So I was 23 years old.
Really?
I liked it.
I don't know what to tell you.
I had a nice time.
For any also in these in these original films had a much more pervy sexual vibe to them.
Yeah, does he not later?
No, later he's putting on sunglasses and eating pizzas and shit.
I mean, it kind of lost like what made him a creep.
Isn't Rosanne in like the fifth one?
She's in the sixth one.
Okay.
They play crazy people in the town.
All right.
Yeah, Freddie's dead is an abomination.
I mean, it's, you know, I still watch it.
Yeah.
Because it's just, you know, it's bad fun.
But like, and you also own and I guess must enjoy the Freddie TV show, right?
I own every episode.
Oh, okay.
It's a shit show.
Congrats, Joe.
You do you like the show?
No.
Why do you own it?
It's fucking terrible.
It's just stupid.
I'm a completist.
Yeah, I enjoy the fact that I own it.
Yeah.
And I enjoy watching it with people to be like, look at this.
Right.
But it's, you know, so for Camp Fact value, I enjoy it.
But no, it's, I can't stand by it in any way.
Is it, he's haunting a new person each week or others?
Is there a cast that we follow or what goes on?
Well, you know how everybody who is a fan of Nightmare and Elm Street thinks, you know,
if they only would do this without Freddie, that's who that, that's who the show's for.
He's in like two episodes.
The other ones are just like about people living in nightmares.
And that's it.
And he's an England in the other ones.
He's, he hosts all of them.
Okay.
But it's literally, he's like the crypt keeper.
Yeah.
And then there's two episodes that the Freddie character is actually in.
You think?
And even those aren't that great.
Huh?
What, what kind of house do you think England's living in?
Like, is he doing all right?
He's got to be, man.
I mean, it's, it's the money he must have made off of this thing.
But people are often wrong, you know?
Like he probably made 50 ,000 for this.
And then by the end, at the very most, he's getting a million.
You know, and that, that money is 25 years old at this point.
Well, look, let's, I mean, here's the thing.
There's, they couldn't do this series without him.
Uh -huh.
So there's no way that by the third movie, he wasn't like, go fuck yourselves.
Or if you want to do this, this is how.
What if they get some shitty contract where like here,
you're only going to get X amount of dollars no matter how many times we do this.
Well, let's, let's look up Robert England.
All right.
Celebrity net worth.
Is there any reliance on this?
How do they know it on celebrity net worth?
I don't know.
That's why I'm asking.
Is there any, any, any way, reliable?
Or is this just a chit -chow?
No.
I think people would be a lot more upset if everyone knew exactly what they had.
14 million.
All right.
I'm getting 14 million.
I'll buy that.
You know, how much do you think you made for the adventures of Ford Fairland,
starring Andrew Dysclin?
I mean, look, even if you make scale on a movie like that,
the unions make sure that you get your residuals and stuff.
That movie made money even though it was,
wasn't as big as it was supposed to be.
Yeah.
That's true.
So, I mean, you know,
I imagine it was pretty decent, I'd imagine.
Yeah.
What I love when you go back and watch documentaries about old movies,
which I always do if they're available on the DVD.
I love that shit.
Yeah, the making of -
Right.
There was a good name.
It'll be like, it'll be like,
Ford Fairland, the adventures of creating a movie.
Yeah.
Exactly.
Who framed Roger Rabbit?
I'll tell you who framed the movie, Roger Rabbit,
the people who shot and directed it.
It's like, wow, that's the title you want to -
Anyway, I love how, especially like in this,
like I watched a lot of this night right now,
it should documentary.
It's about eight hours long.
It's so long, but it's great.
Everybody in it seems hurt that their character, what they think?
I don't know how they went ahead and made Nightmare on Elm Street 4
without janitor number two, is like janitor number two's opinion.
Right.
Everybody in it is like, I was shocked that I wasn't asked back
as though people are wondering what happened to like the guy
who died at the end of Nightmare on Elm Street 8.
Right.
I mean, this is such a great shot.
Nancy's in the bathtub legs -
That's supposed to right there.
That's a claw coming out.
They did this in the remake.
I was very happy that they paid tribute to the scene in the remake
and they didn't really change it.
Okay, maybe I do want to have sex with Nancy
and she lays their spread eagle on a bathtub.
Ooh, nice.
Tasty.
Oh, Joe.
I'm kidding.
Come on.
What is bath pillow?
Who has that bath pillow in the tub with them?
Well, overall, let me look at this.
Look at the towel.
Look at the bath pillow.
Look at the sheet.
They're all that same color of blue.
Is that telling you anything?
I mean, I don't know.
What does blue signify evil or something?
Blue signifies -
Maybe it signifies Friday's coming.
Because so far, every time we've seen blue, Friday's shows up.
Well, let's look that up.
All right.
I like this scene a lot.
Yeah, this is great.
This is great scene.
Look at the little nudity right there.
Once again, getting pulled under water in a bathtub
and it's an endless -
a bottomless sea.
I mean, it's just good -
It's good nightmare stuff.
I agree.
They don't have to do this.
What?
All right, and I know a good nightmare
because I wake up nearly every night, nearly screaming
because I have night terrors.
You do?
A little bugged about me.
I do.
I wake up every night like I'm in a horror movie and go,
I'm not looking forward to that when we're like the odd couple
and live together.
You mean like in three months?
When my house was four closed.
Well, I joined the club on that one.
I was -
I have it happen a whole lot.
And it's not a -
it's no way to live.
I don't know what it says about me,
but I have a real problem with them.
With the night terrors?
Yep.
You're about the third or fourth friend of it.
Look, there's another towel.
And the bathrobe is blue.
Look.
And the hand towel is blue.
All right, this is what I found.
This is what I found.
I'm a little big on that color coatings movies.
Ready?
Let's see if we can make any link here.
Do it.
Blue symbolizes trust, loyalty, wisdom, confidence, intelligence, faith.
You just looked up what is blue represent in general?
Not in this movie?
Yeah, but I'm saying let's -
Oh, all right.
I shouldn't -
I'm sure Wes Cravingen to go -
I've got -
The door is blue.
To the house, the front door.
The same color blue.
I think I really made a big discovery here.
Blue symbolizes trust, loyalty, wisdom, confidence, intelligence, faith, truth, and heaven.
Death.
Heaven.
Yeah, baby.
Blue is considered beneficial to the mind and body.
It slows human metabolism and produces a calming effect.
Dreams.
Sleep.
Yeah.
Blue is strongly associated with tranquility and calmness.
That is.
It has a meaning.
The people -
It's featured every time the people are having nightmares being killed by Freddy because it's calming, it's soothing, it makes them go to sleep.
That's -
That's very interesting.
I think that's what it is.
Yeah.
I'm very excited about that.
Now here, Skiddlewards comes in this exact same way in -screen.
Does he really?
Yeah, through the window.
Johnny Depp's coming through the window of Heather Langenkapp's bedroom.
Yeah.
He's climbed the thorny rose bush vine outside of the house.
Now when I was a kid, the only way I could watch are ready to move is if they were on Channel 11.
Look, he's got blue sweatpants on there.
Look, I've made a really great discovery here.
This is nuts.
It's all over the fucking place.
Look at that Tush.
Who?
On John or Heather?
Let's pretend I'm talking about Heather.
Heather also has like a giant mosquito bite in her forehead or a zit or something.
She does.
But I like that they left it there.
That's like in the Witches of Eastwick.
There's a scene where Michelle Pfeiffer is a huge cold -sworder lip.
Really?
And it's real.
And the director was like, no, leave it because you're sickly in this scene and that makes you more human.
And she went with it.
You know who that director was?
George Miller, director of Mad Max.
He did Witches of Eastwick?
You sure did.
I mean -
And Babe.
And Babe Pigg in the city.
Yeah.
Only the second one.
I had a tweet once.
I'm looking for a babe in the streets and a babe Pigg in the city in the sheets.
Yeah.
I mean -
I still think that's funny.
I mean, I would have went like this.
I'm looking for a babe and by that I mean a Pigg in the city.
Sure.
I would have went like that.
All right.
Probably.
That's fine.
I think it's tighter and that's how you get to it.
Well, you're connecting -
Some were in the 178 Faves range.
I guess America thought differently.
All right.
Sorry.
George Miller -
Now, Witches of Eastwick -
Yeah.
Which bothers me is -
Was Witches of East in the TV show in any way linked to it?
No.
Not linked at all.
They just ripped it off like that?
Yeah.
It's embarrassing.
I was just about to say and now she's gone.
But Lincoln Camp looks exact -
Not it looks exactly like -
It gives me a very similar vibe to Jennifer Jason Lee in like fast times,
which came out the same year.
I mean, Jennifer Jason Lee, there's another one.
Just smoking 80s hot.
You know, Joe, these women have lives and personalities.
It's not just, you know, pieces of meat.
All right.
Fair enough.
But I do love her.
You'll be apologizing for that next week like I apologize for my thing.
I mean -
It's a very apologizing heavy time.
I'm an American culture.
I don't think Jennifer Jason Lee would be upset if she heard me say -
No.
Smoking hot.
Probably not.
Yeah.
I love J .J.
She's been great in so many things.
There's a great movie called Georgia where she plays an alcoholic.
And she does like a ten minute like terrible -
She thinks she's a great singer.
And her sister actually is a really good singer.
So then like she does this ten minute van Morrison song and it sounds so terrible
and she's so wasted and it's one of the hardest things I've ever had to watch.
Check that out.
Georgia.
I'm sure it's not on DVD.
It's a VHS maybe only.
I don't know how you're going to watch.
How do people watch movies that aren't on DVD?
Well, Netflix streaming like we are right now.
Well, this is on DVD and blue right now.
Sure.
I have a huge VHS collection but nobody has a VCR anymore.
I had a tremendous VHS collection.
I had a basement wall covered.
The prized possession or the centerpiece of it was the film FATSO starring Dom Deloise.
Sure.
I'm up with Anne McRough.
Can't get the fucking thing on DVD.
It's $150 on DVD.
I'm sorry.
Not Peter Deloise.
The other Deloise kid.
Michael Deloise.
Yeah.
In a diner recently.
Okay.
Told him how much I love FATSO.
He said, I have an original poster.
I'll give it to you.
That's awesome.
Never heard from him again.
I got to find him.
I got to go find Michael Deloise right now.
I don't think it's going to be that hard.
I don't know him.
Is he on Twitter?
I don't know.
My friend knew him.
I got to find him.
I had always heard Tell that Dom Deloise was a closet game man.
I don't know if that's true.
I had heard that too.
I don't think so though.
I think he just was a mildly effeminate guy.
Yeah.
Michael Deloise.
Great guy.
One of the nicest like the gentlest eyes I've ever seen in a man.
Okay.
Seriously.
And was thrilled.
I was apologetically saying to him, I love the movie FATSO.
And I'm sure you get this all the time.
Yeah.
He was so clearly touched.
Well, now here, this is what I always say.
Because we live in here in Los Angeles.
We see a lot of celebrities of all of all ranges.
Yeah.
A list down to your zealous.
And the good rule of thumb is like if you go up to Tom Cruise
and you're like, Tommy, I love Top Gun.
Right.
He might humor you, but he doesn't care.
And he doesn't want to talk to you.
If you go up to like, I saw Richard Reel in a diner the other day.
Who the hell was that?
Richard Reel was in office space.
He was the guy who goes, it's a jump to conclusions man.
I love that guy.
And he was on cheers and he was also, you're going to love this connection.
Remember last night I brought up mysterious scan about the pedophile?
Yeah.
He played a John, like a John who picked up a street kid to like have sex with him.
So in the movie he has sex with Joseph Gordon Levitt.
And he's like a disgusting hotel pervert.
And how old is Levitt in the movie?
18.
But like, is he playing a kid though?
Yeah, you know, he's playing like a teenager.
He's supposed to be like 15 in it.
He got molested and now he's like a hustler.
Okay, I got you.
But so Richard Reel sitting there and I was, I was saying to the person I was with,
I was like, Richard Reel's the kind of guy who you go up to him in a diner
and you're like, hey man, you're just the best character actor.
And I always love seeing you and stuff.
Sure.
And he's so funny in office space and blah, blah, blah.
And he would talk to you for an hour and be so flattered and go home and tell his wife.
Sure.
Some some Kate cannot to him in a diner.
And I didn't do it.
But like, those are the people who love, why don't you do it?
Because he left.
While I was talking about how these people love being approached, he left.
This is another great nightmare detail.
When Nancy is trying to run up the steps and she's stepping in marshmallow.
The steps are turning into marshmallow.
Great point.
This is just a dream.
It's not real.
That's what she keeps saying.
And then boom, through the mirror Freddy.
What a great shot.
Good scare.
What a great shot, man.
Let me, I want to tweet out right now that we're watching this.
Do it.
And that people should be sending us questions.
So if you could talk for a moment.
Well, now do I need to say one, two, three tweet before you?
No.
I'm just going to, I know you're like a countdown, huh?
A lot of smart mouth coming from you tonight.
Why don't you just say, by the way, you're, you have off tomorrow?
I do have off tomorrow.
Yes.
I'm off on script.
I mean, do we take this party on the town after this podcast?
Yeah, let's go get drunk.
We're sitting here sipping whiskies.
That sounds fantastic.
I got a late morning tomorrow.
Tomorrow's my non -workout day.
Yeah.
You're exactly like me, Joe, and that if a drop of alcohol touches your lips,
you want to go drink until two in the morning.
Yeah.
It's a problem.
It's a sad pathetic problem.
Yeah.
You're never going to be like, yeah, I'll have a beer.
You have the beer, then you have 17 beers.
But I should say this isn't a drunk podcast and we're not drunk.
We're not drunk.
But I mean, we've had, I have two wines before this.
And then I'm sipping this delicious whiskey.
Oh, I didn't know about the wine.
And I'm watching my, one of my favorite movies, one of my best pals.
I mean, you know.
How thanks, Joe.
That's sweet of you.
I don't.
Keep talking because I got to tweet this.
Okay.
Yeah.
Going back to VHS.
I had this huge collection.
It's like everybody who bought beanie babies and thought they're going to be rich.
Or like, I have all these baseball cards.
I thought I was going to retire at age 21 from my baseball card collection.
They're all worth nothing at this point.
So my VHS, I get on Amazon.
Like, yeah, I can get some money for these.
They're classics.
You can't get one penny for a VHS.
Unless it's not available on DVD or it's going out of print.
So I sold a VHS copy of Rad, the BMX biking movie.
I remember you telling me this.
For nearly $500.
And it was in, I put on there, not good condition.
The box was completely beaten up.
I stole it from Blockbuster Video that I worked at.
And I got $500 off it.
If you love it, would you pay for it?
I stole it.
I worked at Blockbuster.
I sold it to myself for like $2.
No, I didn't steal it.
I don't mind here.
We passed a statute of limitations on a hard crime.
They fired me for other things.
I didn't really care.
That's a terrible company.
And they're out of business.
So they can't do anything.
I think maybe you should go down to Barbados until things blow over.
Blockbuster fired me because I was making too much money.
My friend said that.
I think $8 .25 an hour at the time.
My friend, Mike Bello, said that to me once back in high school.
I had a job and...
I'm sorry.
It wasn't my job.
It was a place where my buddy worked.
And he gave me free food or something.
I was panicking.
I was panicking that we were going to get in trouble.
And then...
The moral people, Joe.
And I was going on and on to Mike about like, am I okay?
Do you think I'm going to go to jail?
And he said, I think you need to go to Barbados until things blow over.
It was such a sharp comment for a 17 -year -old kid.
The other movie I had which made me some money was...
Somebody gave me as a Christmas white elephant gag gift thing.
A VHS copy of a movie called Gator Bate.
And essentially, it was like kind of a deliverance knockoff,
but it had like a Playboy playmate on the cover.
Sure.
And it was an exploitation movie where she gets sexually assaulted in the buy -u
and then she goes to kill everybody who wronged her.
So I was like, how funny gag gift I never opened it.
Cut to 10 years later, Gator Bate is only available on VHS
and I have a new sealed copy of it.
And I sold it on Amazon for like $250.
Jesus Christ.
That's what you got to do.
You got to watch the market.
Speaking of Gator Bate, I almost bought...
I'll spit on your grave recently.
I was out in...
The Ridge?
Up in Toronto.
I almost bought the remake.
I'd never seen the remake.
I've seen the original.
And that remake was so miserable.
And I didn't buy it.
I was like, I don't need to see this.
It's just too depressing.
Yeah, it was too much.
Too much.
It was depressing.
I don't...
It has tapered off considerably,
but there was about a three -year window
in about maybe the mid -2000s
where rape was an element of every horror movie
and it bothered me so much.
There's a lot of these like weird...
Like last house in the left, that kind of stuff.
Yeah, and which was also a West Craven remake.
Now, but there was that one in the woods
with like Stallone's son.
That one was like...
I don't know.
It's just like where every scar
is like watching a woman get raped for 25 minutes.
I'm glad that the era of movies is over.
Let me look it up.
Well, Pat looks that up.
We are now at the funeral scene of Rick,
the guy that killed Tina.
Yeah.
You know this is all...
He's since it's a horror movie podcast.
Probably 45 dudes just went...
Yelp the name of the movie at this party.
I'm usually that guy, by the way,
but I don't remember those.
If you're watching along with us,
you would have just seen that Rick had the saddest funeral
on planet Earth.
Apparently, had no parents or family.
It was just Nancy and her folks
and a couple loose friends and old ladies.
Sure.
John Saxon now coming in.
Nobody believes you Nancy.
Nobody believes you that a supernatural burn man
is killing your friends.
Nobody wants to hear it.
This is one of the things I hate about horror movies.
They always have to have this part
where the person is like,
don't you get it?
The clowns are doing it.
Everybody's like, yeah,
why don't you get some sleep, sweetheart?
Well, look, if I came over here tonight
and you were like, Pat, don't you see?
The birds are going to kill us all.
I'd be like, Joe,
the hell's wrong with you.
You never believe that person.
But why does nobody ever say
you've been perfectly sane
until this point?
This is the first...
I'm going to go ahead and give you the benefit.
Could a crazy thing you've ever said.
Let's spend five minutes exploring this
as a real possibility.
Yeah, nobody ever goes,
you don't Nancy,
if it weren't for you painting your name on the wall
with your own shit,
we believe you.
Nobody ever says it.
Everybody's like, well, you're a sound of sound mind,
but fuck it.
I don't know what, you're nuts now.
Well, you're my daughter,
and I love you more than anyone in the world.
Charles Fleischer, by the way.
The voice of Roger Rabbit.
Exactly, and we said who framed Roger Rabbit.
By the way, I thought of the perfect name
for a documentary about who framed Roger Rabbit.
Who framed Roger Rabbit?
Beautiful.
About the shooting of the movie.
Yeah, exactly.
Charles Fleischer was also amazingly good
and creepy in Zodiac,
which is one of my favorite movies
of all time.
He's wonderful in Zodiac.
Charles Fleischer.
He's so good in Zodiac.
Yeah, everybody.
And there's 800 speaking roles in Zodiac
and everybody ended his perfect.
A bit of a horror movie veteran, Charles Fleischer.
Also one of the cast members of Demon Knight,
which is one of my favorite horror movies of all time.
I never saw it.
I only saw Bordello of Blood,
which I was watching.
Bordello of Blood outside of the Dennis Miller scenes
where he's just being like funny,
is not good, being allegedly funny.
He is funny in that.
Okay. He is funny in that.
When Charlie wrote his own dialogue.
He's funny and Joe Dirt.
Yeah.
When he's looking, my favorite line in Bordello of Blood
is when she's looking for her brother who's missing
played by Corey Feldman.
And she goes, my brother's been missing.
I need your help.
And she shows him the picture of Corey Feldman.
And he starts laughing at the picture.
And he goes, oh, I gotta put this in a locket.
All right. Yeah.
I should check that out.
Now again, now back to Zodiac.
The scene where the Zodiac killer kills those two teenagers
at the lake.
Yeah.
And Zodiac's not really a horror movie,
but that is by far one of the scariest scenes of movie history.
Dude, that part scary.
That part scary when he goes to the guy's house
and he thinks like he might have found the Zodiac
and he's not sure.
Yeah. Zodiac, I mean,
it's probably three hours long.
There was a summer,
not long ago, where I watched that movie every night
for like two weeks.
I was obsessed with it.
Yeah, it was a great flick.
That was the first movie where I was like,
oh my god, Robert Downey Jr.'s an amazing actor.
Yeah, and so it was like a Jullin Hall, frankly.
Yeah, but that was Downey Jr.'s comeback.
That was the first movie I think that he did after he got off the drugs
and everything.
Yeah. And it was like holy shit.
Yeah, this guy's like no joke, man.
Oh, he killed it. He was really, really, really funny,
which, you know, he kind of brought that to the part
it wasn't really on the page.
This movie that I'm talking about was 2005,
called Chaos,
right in the heart of like rap horror movies,
2005, four sadistic thieves,
including Sage Stallone,
Sylvester Stallone's son, who died recently.
Did he commit suicide?
Did he just die? I think he had an overdose.
That's a shame.
They brutalized two teenagers looking for drugs in the woods.
There you go.
And it's so bad.
One of the bad guys are good guys.
He's one of the torturers.
But you know what, I remember the most,
and I shut the movie off at this point,
but they cut off the girl's nipple.
Oh, come on.
Like, what are we doing?
I like a horror movie to be a little fun,
and I realize a lot of people like to crave shit.
You know what, nipples are fun,
but not when they get cut off.
No, I like a nipple attached.
I always have. Let's get back to it.
Call me old -fashioned, Joe.
Good old -fashioned nipple show.
I don't like a nipple being cut off.
If you're watching along with us,
we're in the hospital scene now
where they're trying to monitor Nancy's dreams.
And they just had one of those machines
where...
Which I'd never buy.
Like those machines with all the pens
where the ink lines are going smoothly.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I mean, who was able to read that?
The doctors always look at it.
They go, no, no movement.
They might not even use the natural movement.
It might only be like a movie -only construct.
I don't believe it's a real machine.
It's absurd. It's like the lie detector.
I don't believe it exists.
I do not believe it exists.
I pointed out the blue door.
But the final scare of this, I'm not mistaken,
is Freddie coming out that blue door, right?
He grabs her like at the end of care.
Yes.
And Wes Craven did not like that ending originally.
Come on, Wes.
It's a great ending.
And it's okay.
It's kind of defeats what it is,
which is she defeats Freddie.
I'm not scared of you anymore.
He disappears.
And then he just magically comes back
in what is supposed to be real life.
Okay.
So, it's a good horror movie ending.
But I remember Wes Craven saying like,
it was merely just a setup for a sequel
and he didn't think that that was the point of making the movie.
Nice buns, Nancy.
Remember when Wes Craven
directed like one non -horror movie called
Music of the Heart with Meryl Streep?
And they never did a non -horror video.
I refused to watch it.
I saw it.
That was during a time where I saw every movie.
And then gave it a letter grade
and a spiral notebook.
Oh, God.
That was my life, people.
Now, here's...
I think I get music of the heart of C+.
What was it about?
Meryl Streep's maybe teaching poor kids
or deaf kids or poor deaf kids or someone.
But the kids never live under stairs
or turn evil or anything like that?
No, no, no, no.
Okay, I don't have no interest.
Now I'll tell you a Wes Craven movie
I remember watching in maybe Junior High
that is so bad, it's called Shocker.
Well, Pat, I swear to God,
I was just about to bring up Shocker.
Bring it up, Joe.
I also think Shocker sucks.
Here's the thing.
Wes Craven said...
He thought it was a commentary on the media, right?
Well, I believe that is true.
But he also said that he never got his...
What he thought was fair royalties
for the franchise of Nightmare on Home Street.
Okay.
So he said I decided I was going to create another franchise
and not make the same mistakes I did contractually
like I did with Nightmare on Home Street.
And he made Shocker.
He thought that was going to be it.
And it was terrible.
Yeah.
I felt bad for...
I have such respect for the man,
but I felt bad for him that that didn't work out.
But then he came back with Scream.
And I was like, okay, now he got it with Scream.
He nailed it with Scream.
And Scream's great.
But Wes Craven, you do have to ask yourself,
how do you write and direct this thing?
And then he made so many bad movies.
How does it all happen?
You know?
Well, he made bad ones and good ones.
It seems to be the...
How do people make movies that are so bad
and then so good?
And music is the same way.
It's just...
Sure.
It's scary.
It really is scary.
Because you and I are both in the creative fields.
The biggest fear I have in my entire life beyond death
and anything else is losing my ability to be funny
or good at what I do.
Well, as you know...
Look, you know, I used to be real hard on guys.
You know, I'd be like...
I'd be like, you know, why did John Carpenter make
this many good ones?
And then these other ones that kind of sucked
were the perfect movie and then so many bad movies.
But, you know what it is?
I finally realized like...
Well, everybody doesn't have the advantage I do of being a stand -up
where it's like, no, this is what it is.
Put it out or don't.
And nine times the attend they will and it's fine.
But, you know, as a writer, and I've staff written, you know,
things get picked apart, things get changed around.
People get last -minute doubts and everybody has a hand on it.
And then by the end of it, sometimes the final product
isn't what you want it to be.
Especially with a horror movie.
That's true.
If you're dealing with the studios.
I think they pretty much had free reign in the 80s and early 90s.
But if you look...
If you look, there's a clear line that gets drawn with...
Craven's a great example.
In the jump from a young New Line cinema,
which was not a big boy studio.
It was a very indie studio.
It was very grassroots.
They call it the studio that Freddie built,
the house that Freddie built.
Right.
I mean, and who doesn't?
You know?
I mean, I hear it every day in the coffee shop.
But there's a clear line in quality that gets drawn
when it jumps to the major studio stuff.
Now, I think they let him dance a little more to his own rhythm
with the screen movies.
Well, the screen was written by Kevin Williamson,
so that's a different thing too.
It was.
And I also think for some reason they give more slack
with slasher movies.
You know?
They set this with the...
Slasher movies are...
There are a little...
Anything without a supernatural element is a little more legit,
I think, because it could really happen.
And they let...
They let horrific things go a little more with the...
Like...
It's the opening of screen.
It's disturbing.
Like...
Oh, for sure.
They cut...
He cuts...
Drew Barrymore's throat.
He's gargling on her own blood.
It's very disturbing.
I was terrified by a screen when I saw it.
And now it's more...
Of comedy.
It works as more comedy, but it's a really good movie.
They all are.
But you know...
When they did the Nightmare on Elm Street remake,
they said one thing we want to do is we want to make them look truly like a burn victim.
Right.
And then they said, well, we had to reel it back,
because we didn't want people to like turn away from the screen every time they saw them,
because it was disturbing.
I'm like, no, make it disturbing.
Yeah.
I want a monster that sticks in my head and gives me nightmares.
That's why the extras just freaks me out so much.
Yeah.
It's so scary looking.
You rarely get that.
And who played Friday in the new one?
Jackie Earle Haley.
Oh, yeah.
That was a good call.
He's graded playing a creep.
He's graded everything.
He plays mostly pedophiles now.
Again.
Little children.
It's...
My girlfriend...
When that movie...
At the time.
My girlfriend at the time.
When that movie came out, gave it to me on DVD.
And I remember talking to a comedian named Julien McCullough about it.
And I said...
I love Julien McCullough.
Yeah, I said...
My girlfriend just gave me a copy of Little Children.
And he said...
You should examine your relationship.
Yeah.
That's all weird.
That's a good movie and a good book.
Top of the movie is...
I mean, there's...
Literally the most disturbing scene I've ever seen in a movie is when he's jerking off
in front of the school on his date.
Sure.
And the woman starts crying.
Yeah, it's terrible.
It's...
Once again, pedophilia rears its head on me.
We'll see you in hell podcast.
Yeah, we need to stop.
Look at this lady.
She's got a very...
She looks like Virginia Madsen is melting.
The lady from sideways.
Why am I being so mean to this woman?
What's wrong with her?
She's so dramatic.
I love...
I find her sexy in a string.
Yeah, I mean...
I'll lick her up.
By the way, what's in the back of Nancy's sweatshirt there?
Nancy's...
The pajamas all day.
Bathroom.
I'll lick her up.
A nice vodka drunk.
Sure.
Why is an alcoholic mother always a vodka drunk?
Well, because that's true to life, I think.
And now there's so many delicious flavors of vodka.
It's a great time to be an alcoholic mother or aunt.
You got toasted marshmallow vodka.
I'd go my own way.
I'd be doing yeager bombs the whole time.
I'd get that.
That's it.
Just straight yeager bombs.
One after the next.
What's interesting, we talked about her having a zit
and now she has kind of a red nose and et cetera.
Like the 80s were talking about Anthony Michael Hall earlier
because of vacation.
Like all the teenagers had zits.
They were real.
This is in the studio movies, the indie movies.
The teenagers were real.
Yeah.
Now, you can't find a teenager on screen
who doesn't look like she's been airbrushed.
And it's not real.
Everyone's ugly and awkward and weird when they're teenagers.
No, you're absolutely right.
And if I may point out,
the scene we're in now,
Johnny Depp.
Johnny Depp is wearing a...
He's wearing a belly shirt.
Yeah.
Which I like.
But he's also in his bedroom,
poster on the wall,
rush,
grace under pressure.
Never realized that was the poster.
Never saw that either.
Glove rush, one of my favorite bands.
And the poster predominantly blues and purples.
It's the only Russian album.
Actually, counterparts also has a blue album cover
but it wasn't out yet.
Up till this point,
that was the blueest of the...
Yeah, I love it.
Blue phone.
Johnny Depp on a tan phone.
She probably blew Johnny Depp earlier.
Oh, you guys.
I'm just trying to have fun.
Geez.
And he said, don't rush it.
Have some grace under pressure.
Look at this, folks.
This is why we write the TV show.
I just watched a documentary.
I never liked Rush.
I just watched a Rush documentary
that I loved.
Also on Netflix.
Oh, it's...
Beyond the lighted stage.
Well, it's tremendous.
It's great.
It's fucking tremendous.
I might go see them next week.
Actually, this week...
Where are they playing the forum?
Are the staples.
Uh, I think the forum I can't go.
It's my buddy's party.
I can't go.
I never saw them.
They were never my bag.
But whatever.
I saw them once.
I love respect them.
I saw them once and I was so drunk
that I weaped during spirit or radio.
You know.
That's rough.
Where I'm at in my life at this point.
I was three years ago, but whatever.
Uh...
Here's the famous line.
Don't fall asleep.
She just told you, Johnny.
She's not fucking around here.
Even you don't believe her.
Look.
Nobody believes her.
That this guy's coming into their nightmares.
Here's why there aren't more great horror movies.
There are great comedies.
There are great whatever.
Blue blanket on Johnny Depp's bed.
True.
Sorry to cut you off.
I'm sorry.
The reason is...
I think...
That kind of one -line premise.
If you fall asleep, you're dead.
Is obviously such a perfect...
You walk into any studio and you go,
Hey.
I got a movie where if you fall asleep, you died.
They'll hand you an oversized novelty check.
Right.
Uh...
And those premises just don't come along that often
because if they did, somebody would have thought of it.
Sure.
And comedies the same way.
Like the 40 -year -old virgin.
I would imagine...
Somebody walked into a studio and said,
the 40 -year -old virgin and they said,
Here's money.
Right.
Because it's perfect.
And those things are...
They seem so easy to come up with, but they're not.
Right.
A simple one -line premise.
And that's why whenever I ask somebody,
they're like, Hey, can you read a script of mine?
I'm like, Yeah, what's it about?
And they go, Okay.
So there's this guy, right?
And he's like an air traffic controller.
But he never really...
And I'm like, Okay, this movie is not going to happen.
Right.
You need to, for better or worse, be able to say,
Here's the movie in one sentence.
Right.
I agree.
Especially for comedy, especially for horror.
And if you want any sort of success,
if you want somebody to give you some money,
you want to do it weird indie, you know,
you can't explain David Lynch's movies in one sentence.
Sure.
But, you know, those aren't the big hits.
Well, I would agree with you.
Fuck about David Lynch, by the way.
I love David Lynch.
I would agree.
My favorite types of horror movies are...
horror movies that establish very simply,
there's no escape.
You have to face the fear.
Yeah.
So...
That's why when people go to these movies,
they poke holes in them.
Like, I used to only go to the Magic Johnson theater to see...
I think we're going to say to Magic Johnson's movies.
I was like, I didn't know he made films.
I would only go to the Magic Johnson theater
and Compton here in LA,
because for horror movies,
because I loved people shouting out of the screen.
And I would have so much fun and laugh
and yell out myself at times and stuff.
But if people are watching your movie
and they can be like,
don't do that, you idiot.
What do you do?
Like...
Right.
That means nobody's buying your shit.
Right. Right.
What you're saying is they can't have an out
and then that's truly scary.
They don't have an out.
It's truly scary.
All the best horror movies, there's no out.
Nightmare on Elm Street.
You fall asleep, you die.
Yeah.
Texas Chainsaw Massacre.
All the hillbilly inbreds are running the town.
You can't get away from them.
Yeah.
The exorcist.
Your daughter is possessed by the devil.
Right.
You have to stay here with her.
Yeah.
Look at that mask on the wall, buddy.
Look at this.
On Nancy.
Taking it off.
We're only getting it from the back.
But it is delish.
You know when I was a kid,
because it's all I saw,
something about a rear side bottom boob
is almost sexier than the whole thing.
I love it still to this day.
But that little small of a back right there,
you could really grasp that waist.
All right, take it easy.
Take it easy.
I'm getting worked up here.
But I was watching mirrors today
and I thought once again,
brilliant premise for a horror movie,
What's everywhere and you can't get away from them, but isn't that kind of what Poltergeist 3 was mirrors water puddles?
Yeah, but mirrors did it way better. I guess do you like mirrors?
I don't remember I enjoyed it very much. I remember Poltergeist 3 was terrible
Poltergeist 3 is to me unwatchably bad as much as I left Tom scarrett
Sure, I don't need you guys to the day. I got braces and they're the same for the kids braces attacking
I mean when I was a kid I loved Poltergeist 2 now that I'm older. I don't like it as much
But it's not a bad move that preacher guy stole out of fun from phantasm right same guy. No, not the same guy
Are we sure positive? Okay, not angus scream. All right phantasm 5 eagerly awaiting that it's made
It's done. It's doesn't come out yet the actual release or you think it'll go straight now to go straight to vid
But but I mean you know the guy that did phantasm did John dies at the end. He did bubba ho tap right
He does a lot of great stuff on cost gorilla. Yes, never saw John does the end. I liked bubba ho tap along, but he's got phantasm 5
I believe this way to get it together for Christ. I mean she's stashing bottles all over the house this lady
I don't think and I've been a big advocate of drinking for about 10 years. I don't think I've ever drank out of a bottle of liquor
I did once recently my friends and I went out for a big party night and we were starting it at a girl's apartment
And I bought I finally did this I always wanted to do this but one of those little glass pint bottles of whiskey
I've done that and just drank the whole thing at her house. It was a lot of fun smoking cigarettes
I felt like you're real like I was on the case, but you never picked up like the 10 pound bottle of jack to your lips
Yeah, no, I don't stash like Nancy's mom does a three -leater
Fuckin that in the linen closet along with the one in the kitchen that I hide behind my back. Yeah
Here's Johnny Depp's dad. He's not a good actor. That guy looks like he gave birth to Johnny Depp, right? Yeah, yeah, I mean that's viable
I had a friend tonight. I had that phone. I was a kid. I had to answer here talk about horror. I had to answer every phone call until I was
17 until I left that got out of the house basically. I had to answer every phone call. Hello, Walsh residents, Patrick speaking
Who made you do that? My dad. What was he a Nazi? Well, no comment. Hello, Walsh residents, Patrick's big and my friends would be like
Pat, it's Ryan. What's wrong with you? Who the hell? Yeah, what is that bullshit? And then even like my dad's friends would be like
Why do you have to say that? Can I just talk to your dad? I'm like, I'm sorry
Now if you noticed it we've passed it
But they just showed exterior shots of the houses a moment ago. Both houses draped in blue light
She's wearing a blue members only jacket with a blue phone and a blue bedspread patty you really cracked into something here with a blue
Blue row baby, you really cracked into something here. I'm proud of you, man. Thank you blue towels in the closet blue towels in the linen closet
Blue phone is now ringing
Blue tissues on the on the shelf. Blue my mind is what it did
Blue phone is now ringing the police in the back. That's the police. That's the police and her dad's a cop. What do you think of that?
Oh blue painting on the wall. Yeah, they really did their work here. This is the part where the tongue comes out right on hold on
Here we I'm your boyfriend now, Nancy
That was always gross
Do you think Freddie's breath smells like when he looks her face like that? That's not good, man. Yeah
I went to
film school and I took a class where this
professor
Would talk he would make every movie into a game movie. It all had a gay subtext and it was fascinating
How he did it like some like he would talk about Rebecca the old Hitchcock movie where clearly the maid is like has a lesbian interest in her
Mm -hmm. You watch and you're like oh shoot. You're right. I never saw Rebecca as a good
It's it's a great movie especially with that bit of information
But then like he'd watch die hard and he'd be like well clearly John McLean is gay and the room would kind of laugh and then by the end of the class
And it wasn't the class wasn't like finding gay subtext in movies. He just did it
So like you'd be like maybe John McLean is gay. He was a fascinating man
By the way Johnny Depp asleep on the bed now blue sweat pants blue number 10 on the belly shirt
And now he's dead and there's another blue blanket on the bed
He just got pulled in the bed by Freddie and now a blood fountain shoots out which I enjoy quite a bit
Yeah, it's a good shot. You only get one take of a blood fountain shooting out of a bed. Yeah, this is it
What do you think I guess they must have poured it in or how do they do that?
It looks like it's shot is going in reverse maybe that's an upside down room
Okay, yes, I can't believe I have to explain that to you look what I do
I love the magic of cinema Joe. I like to let it wash over me and confuse me and dazzle me
Yeah, that's clearly an upside -down room now. I bought the special edition
Braggar of the nightmare on street VHS tape my friend Jim and I split split it
We found it one night at at a you know Sam Goodie or something one of those old record stores
Warehouse music. Yeah, something like that when you listen on headphones like what we're doing now
Yeah, it was pre DVD we found the double VHS and we bought it because the second tape had a bunch of bonus features on it
Uh -huh, which at that time was pretty unheard of on anything. Yeah
But the bonus tape had deleted scenes
Okay, and one of the fast forward through to find the next scene like the ones that you cared about
Yeah, and
But one was Johnny Depp's bloody corpse coming up out of the hole in the bed and then plopping down
Before anybody discovered what was happening
So it looked like he had just been murdered and it was a great shot
Relief on the I have the blu -ray box. I'm sure it's on there somewhere. I'm sure it is too
I don't I don't know why though. They would have a lot of members only Jack cut it out of the film
The dad now is very upset. He's throwing up because his son
His son's blood I stripping through the ceiling that'll that's upsetting. Yeah, I would guess so
I'd guess so now do you like the the part of the 13th series or do you find it a lesser?
Uh
Yeah, I like it. Uh, I don't I don't like it as much as nightmare on street, but
I've only seen for a third. They're great. I mean, I think the ratio of good ones to bad ones is is equal
I mean for the 13th might actually have a better batting average
Okay, nightmare on street
Simply because there's more so they have more chances to make better ones
But they don't have a classic like the for the first part of the 13th is not a classic
It's just kind of okay slasher moving. I don't like the first one
I think what the remake did was best which was establishing the events of the first one in the opening credits basically
Um
Two is to me. We're afraid of the 13th really kicks in two's great three's great four's great. Oh, okay. I gotta watch all those five sucks
Six and seven are great after that they all kind of suck takes Manhattan
That's a waste of time in my opinion Jason takes Manhattan is
Okay, then there's Jason X and space. Yeah, Jason goes to hell is number nine Jason X is in space is Jason goes to hell set in hell
No, it's just the idea that he goes to hell at the end of it. Okay
Um, and they thought some fucking horseshit thing about like you know
He's it's an ancient demon, you know, anytime they do that it's like get the fuck out of here
They try to do that with Michael Myers and the curse of Michael Myers. Yeah, it's stupid
um
But uh for the 13th part six is my favorite of all of them and really I mean just what's the premise?
Uh
It's called Jason lives
Okay, and uh
The opening of the movie is fantastic. It's uh the guy that plays horse shack and welcome back cutter
Ron polillo, I believe. Yeah, and uh
And then the the grown -up like a different actor, but it's the grown -up version of Corey Feldman's character. Okay from part four
um
He he wants to make sure that Jason is actually dead so they go to a cemetery to dig up his corpse
The dig up his corpse. It's there
Kid pulls out um
An iron pole from the fence
starts stabbing Jason repeatedly out of rage right
Lightning strikes the pole reanimates Jason. Okay Jason punches horse shack through the chest
Hand comes out the other side holding his heart. It's a great fucking flick me. All right
And he talked about Daribont on the last one Daribont director or he wrote the third nightmare and I'm sure correct dream warriors
Diddy yeah, thank you wrote it. I thought Craven wrote that one
Just look it up Daribont wrote four then maybe by the way Friday the 13th reboot
I didn't even realize I knew they were working on one. I didn't write it comes out in like November
I thought the 13th reboot. Yeah
Now didn't they already do it right after 13th reboot?
They did and I thought it was solid and it didn't for some reason get any traction
But it was then one of the scariest kills ever he put he takes a girl and puts her in a sleeping bag
Yeah, but she's can't get and then ties the sleeping on the tree over the fire. That's so scary man
Hold on nightmare and I'm street three. Let's see here
This woman's unattractive woman. Why was I so mean? I don't know
I mean the strange part is is she's six years younger than we are right here
People just looked older back then that's Sarah's true. Uh, let's see nightmare on Elm street part three
74 % of rotten tomatoes deservedly so
Patricia in the bad during this makeup scene
Patricia Arquette
Screen debut if you yeah, I love screenplay West Craven Bruce Wagner Frank Daribout and Chuck Russell
Chuck Russell, I think did like the mask or something
Uh, I want to see what else Daribout wrote and his early career
He was a he's primarily a screenwriter
Memoron Street 3 love it the blob love it the fly to love it
Fly to a good. I love fly one. I mean the original
Well, it's not the original so still remake but the fly with Jeff Goldblum to me is could be my second favorite hard movie ever
Yeah, it's one of the most disturbing things that I've ever seen in my life. Yeah, but I love the fly too. It got it kind of bad rap
I think it's great. All right. I'll say it
I don't I didn't I never saw a lot of those bad sequels like I never saw Predator 2 but I love Predator 1
I never saw Predator 2 either
You see and Danny Glover and you're right
Chuck Russell did write the mask. He wrote
He wrote
He wrote Eraser
Oh, that was a rough one. He also wrote memory when he shoots that alligator and he goes y 'all luggage
Yes, I do that was the trailer, but he also wrote collateral wouldn't one of my favorite Michael man movies. Oh, cladderals a fantastic movie
Yeah, you adapt it for you Chuck Russell way to come back baby. Oh was a producer on back to school love back to school
Who doesn't that's always very inspiring to me when somebody's like got a couple hits in the 80s and then you're like
I guess they tapered off and you see they wrote some big hit in the 90s. I love it. I love it. It's a cool movie or the 2000
Coro dream scape love that
I don't know dreams Dennis Quaid. Yes, I do know dreams. Do I tell you I saw Dennis Quaid at a party the other night
Who's part of when I was at the Montreal comedy festival. Oh, yeah
Yeah, Quaid was there. I'm walking out of these funnier than Dennis Quaid
Well, he was doing a reading the Jason rightman was doing of the big Lebowski. What was he playing the nihilist?
He was playing Jackie Treehorn. I think he was playing the big Lebowski
No, Michael fastbendered was playing no fastbendered was playing the dude the dude right. Oh, you're talking about
I think Quaid played the big Lebowski. Oh, that seems wrong. I can't remember, but it faddled
Creed it doesn't matter, but the the point is is I got off the elevator in the hotel everybody was saying and there was like 10 people
On the elevator and we're walking to these glass doors to go outside and you through the glass doors
There's a set of stairs and there's this guy in the set of stairs and I just turned to everybody in the elevator
That was on the elevator and I go is that Dennis Quaid? Yeah, and we all started laughing because it was Dennis Quaid
It was like the most random like what the fuck is he doing here? Yeah, we didn't know that he had done the reading
Looks amazing of course have two brothers ever to look less similar than Dennis and Randy Quaid
Dennis Quaid I stand by this should be Indiana Jones next
We could get four five good movies out of him as Indiana Jones. He's perfect for it. All right
He's perfect for it. He looks great. He's got that indignant like come on
You know he's like Dennis Quaid. I love him
Do you favorite Dennis Quaid movie? I was just on the tip of my tongue. I was gonna say how much I love interspace
That probably is the best one, right? Yeah, I mean, it's just a great great movie Joe Dante
I love a Joe Dante. Yeah, I have an A. Madden A is a great underrated movie
Yeah, you know, I had a twilight zone the movie poster signed by Joe Dante and nice
Fucking when I moved him seemed to disappear with all my other valuable paintings
What can you say? I'm not accusing anybody. No, you know, but
Right, yeah
We're in the climax of the film at this point Nancy is
Nancy has purposefully gone to sleep. She said booby traps around the house. She's now in the boiler room
Home alone sound home alone. Yes, Nightbird. I was treat gets very home alone at the end. Yeah as does
That great James Bond movie
I
Well actually the not so great one quantum of solace
Anzlet like an abandoned house and James Bond sets a bunch of traps that movie is also home alone
You know, I always wanted to do was do a short with McCauley Culkin about the kid from home alone
Getting out of an insane asylum in his thirties
because he
horrifically mutilated two men that came into his home. Yeah, I mean, that was my fair movie for years when I was a kid like it's a
I was I was McCauley Culkin's age when that came out. It was like a dream come true
And I love John Hughes and remain a huge fan
but uh
I watched some I guess it was probably on the DVD like an a DVD extra and
Chris Columbus the director was talking about how Joe pesky like basically came from the set of good fellows to do home alone
Right as like an afterthought and he's like we have days of footage
Of Joe pesky like screaming in McCauley Culkin's face
I'm gonna fucking kill you and he's like note Joe
Joe he's a 10 -year -old boy and this is a PG rated comedy. It's like he's an improv guy and he'd get real into it
And they'd be like you're not at good fellows anymore Joe. Oh, that's beautiful
You can say like you want to like break his nose or something fun like that
But you can't say you want to murder him and bury him in the desert
Is there anything funnier than Daniel Stern getting the transfer to put on his face?
It's the best scream in movie history I would say. It's
You know what another great one is Bruce Willis and death become sir
I like a man with a high -pitched scream. It's always funny. I never saw death become sir
Believe it or not. I wasn't rushing to get to the new Goldie Hahn vehicle
Look fine, but it's really good Robert Semeckis. It's uh, it's a very funny
Bobby Z very funny movie great special effects and it has a lot to say about aging and Hollywood and culture and it's great move
Nancy just found Glenn's headphones in Freddie's boiler room Glenn was Johnny Depp right
And in case you were mistaken. They did have a label on them that said Glenn
uh
You know, I thought the other label that said headphones was a bit much. I I felt like West wasn't really giving us credit there
Why does Nancy currently have blood all over her fingers?
I don't know what was the yeah, why did she get oh because she picked up a
Well, Glenn's headphones
What did she land in that she's fine. She's dreaming. Oh
Yeah, if you're not have you lost the premise of the movie already?
She landed in some rose bushes Freddie's gonna jump out she's gonna wake herself up in a minute
And this is the whole thing she figures out halfway through the movie. I can bring Freddie into real life
Yes, of course. All right
Now she's about to wake up. There he is, but he doesn't know what she can do
She tackles him he thinks easy kill
boom wakes up
And who hasn't had that feeling
What do you mean? Well, I have this feeling every night. We're like you're about to be brutally murdered in your dream
And then you are like wake up. Please wake up and you jolt yourself away
You know, I have that feeling every time I go into a pitch meeting
Night terrors. I'd love to sleep over one night and hear those things. No, you wouldn't. Oh god. I would
I should probably double down on the therapy as I am like it's like whenever you like talk about something in public
It's like oh wait
This isn't normal that I jolt awake nearly being murdered in my sleep every night and you scream
No, I usually go like
Now here's what bothered here's what always bothered me about Freddie
Freddie coming into the real world. Yeah, because they do this in Freddie versus Jason too
Comes into the real world. Freddie versus Jason also. We are talking horror movies. Yeah
You'd you'd think the first thing he would do is start going
My fucking skin hurts. Yeah, no
It's fine burn to a crisp. Yeah
Doesn't no, it doesn't seem to phase him at all. They've always bothered me
Things like that bother me. All right, you know
She just broke through a window with an umbrella
You know, sure why not you could bring her window with an umbrella. Yeah, here comes Freddie look
I mean, it's home alone. He gets a sledgehammer. That is home alone. There he goes
The only thing this scene is missing is he came to his nuts. Yeah, or paint cans being thrown in
Uh
This gets a little paint canny right here. He runs through the
He runs right through the trip trip wire and sets off the lamp bomb
Yeah, and just kind of gives like an ouch like a
Yeah, maybe I love it man. She's screaming out the window for help. That was a weird choice of takes
There's a cop across the street and he goes maybe I should go tell the lieutenant. Did you just see on the stairs there appear?
Yeah, that's like a giant bottle of burp. Oh, she's gonna grab it. No, no, this is one of her booby traps
Okay, I was gonna say the mob just leave a bottle out
Which and she throws ahead and it just shatters on his chest. She's re -burning him now
But now she's burning them on this side. There's a man in a Freddy Halloween costume now getting
He's on fire that literally looks like the Halloween costume of Freddy. I bought at right aid when I was a child
There he goes
He is making sort of Schwarzenegger noises
Come on you're better than that pet. That's his big line, right? You're better than that. What is that an old pet?
It's like a Kevin Pollock routine all right. Well, I'm not saying that's not a
Dissa Kevin Pollock. I'm just saying he's been saying that for a long time
Well, I don't know Kevin Pollock. I don't follow his career. I do. I like to be grumpy old men and diner
Was he wasn't in diner? No, I love him and grumpy old men
He's in a lot of movies that seem like diner. You know pop. That's my Kevin Pollock impression for sure
Hey, pop. What do you get a doofodeta pop? He's got that Queen's New York thing to him
The cops are now in the house. They're here to help Nancy
And she's leading them downstairs because they're smoke coming up from the basement where she set Freddy on fire
How by throwing a bottle of
Bourbon into his chest
But what's this?
fiery footprints up the stairs
Again, this is what starts to bug me is I love the movie. I'm not knocking it
But this is now a real man that has been burnt on top of burnt skin
Yeah, and he's still somehow running around the house to kill people
We're into like 12th and 13th degree burns. Yeah, he's on top of the mother trying to burn her right now
And
Now the mother is look blue again. Yeah, the mother's corpse burnt to a crisp sinks into a blue abyss
Look isn't that Saxon's wife? Yeah, he seems oddly non -plussed. They're divorced. Oh, okay
She was a bitch. Yeah, well, there's an extra is 750 a month. I don't got to spend that's what he's thinking right now
You know what Saxon should have yelled there now you deal with their bullshit Kruger. He should have yelled that as she sunk into the bed
She's your problem now
Krugs
By the way watch your credit cards baby
That's you know, it's another way the movie could have gone once again the whole room is blue
Which makes you question, isn't it? Did you ever think about that until I laid that truth bomb on you?
No, it's killing me though. Yeah, it's killing me
Shyamalan does it like unbreakable is an extremely color -coded movie if you watch it purple and you know
He's talking about making part two
Man, that'd be great unbreakable is such a fucking classic. I love it and I'm pissed that he's that I'm like
Why did it take this long for these guys even talk about making it?
It's such an awesome movie like make the second one make everyone talks about it like it's a cult favorite and it made like
$150 million. Yeah, he was still the man. It's like make the next unbreakable
Unbreakable another great effect shot here Freddie comes up through the sheet
And it again, it's like a latexie kind of a kind of a condom kind of a dick going into a condom vibe
So my theory here is now Freddie's back. He's still alive. He magically comes out of the bed
My theory is is she's actually dreaming here. He doesn't realize she is
Okay, however, she still defeats him
because
She realizes I don't I'm not scared of you. Yeah, which is how she felt through the whole booby traps in area
Can I blow your mind again real quick? Yeah
Home alone the big turning point in home alone like the act two when he's like I'm gonna defend everything
He yells. I'm not afraid anymore
Yeah, like three times in a row. Yeah, I'm not afraid anymore
So movies the same movie let's let's change the statement I made earlier
Home alone gets very nightmare on Elm Street. Yeah, not the other way around. Yeah, get that furnace in the basement causing trouble
That was scary the neighbor
How much okay, that was kind of a children of the corner thing Freddie just turned into television snow
She's not scared anymore. She opens the door. Here's the daylight. Look at those blue eyes blue red
Here rings lies
I believe she had bluas in the whole rest of the movie that she now and I believe a blue outfit they do color contacts on her
Yeah, see I think that whole end is supposed to be she's still dreaming the whole thing is she's still dreaming
She thinks she's awake. She thinks she defeated him. She hasn't she's still dreaming
Our mom's wearing a smock for painting with giant buttons on it
Let me tell you something about what the mom looks like right now two words. I like he
Again, ladies gentlemen, please don't have sex with joderosa
You're just gonna hear I love this access buttons down the front. Yeah
Yeah purple and blue
Well, I guess everything's happy from here on out. I guess we're gonna sit stop. It looks like never mind this
Smoke that's everywhere. Yeah, it looks like I mean smoke just billowing all around them everywhere
Nobody seems to notice it. They're dreaming. Oh wait a minute. I thought this was the end and everything's gonna be fine
She's still dreaming the car is Freddie stripes the mother doesn't notice. Yeah, it's something's wrong
That the car looks like a Freddie car suddenly. Yeah, and here we go mother in front of the blue door
What's gonna happen? Uh -oh? There's the little girls from the beginning
Right
And here's Freddie's arm and he pulls the blow up down through the window. Yeah, that's kind of a weird effect
Well, I mean, you know very
I like the end of Kerry as well one final like when the arm jolt's out of the grave. It's a very final shock
But that's only in the remake
No, no, no, no. Does that happen in the original what they don't do it in the remake they do do it in the original and her arm comes out of the grave
It's beautifully done in the original. They keep zooming in on these rocks and it's uh
That beautiful woman whatever her name is Amy something and she's at the grave then the hand comes out and grabs. Oh, yeah
That's right. I forgot about the okay, you're right Amy Irving. Sorry Steven Spielberg's ex
Um, that's it song
It the we're at the closing credits. What's the song playing? Yeah, did they be like is this song like when that what they used to do
We're like there had to be a song about the movie
Like it's a nightmare on M street talking about a nightmare
Well, let me see if I can find her before we sign up on the street
Nightmare on Elm street like the song and who's Harry Crumb by the temptations
And they it's they say who's Harry Crumb they go it's called big fun parentheses Harry Crumb. Oh god, I'm ready
It's a big fun
Harry Crumb
Uh
This is the uh
According to YouTube the Everly Brothers. Oh, no this can't be the Everly Brothers. No, it's not the Everly Brothers
I mean the Isley Brothers
It says the Everly Brothers all I have to do is dream. No, that's whenever I want you all I have to do that's in the remake
Oh, yeah, you're right. You're absolutely right um is your backdrop on your phone grease the movie
Yeah, I think that's funny
Okay, it's from the scene. It's from the you're the one that I want to see and it makes me laugh all right
Um, I can't find left was important uh changing the read it it it as we're wrapping up here
So you don't have to listen to Joe Google on this podcast send us movie suggestions thoughts ways to improve things
You love whatever because we're starting out. This is new to us as well
Um, any suggestions you got did you tweet out earlier? I did I forgot to look oh my god
Uh look there's nothing saying we got it and if there's any questions right now I'm gonna look at Twitter
We're gonna answer okay. Can I reach you the one comment under the video? Yeah, please do on YouTube of the ending song
Please do there's no information on the guys that did this song
It's actually a really great song good drumming awesome synths
Why is there no info on this band? They're called 213
That was posted six years ago
Not when the movie came out six years ago when YouTube came out that uh that was posted
We have any questions. We do. I'm gonna read through them. Do you think Freddie Krueger served in NOM?
Do you think he's seen some shit?
I think it's a great question the timeline adds up to me
I would not be surprised if he served in NOM
But I bet they would have mentioned it at some point during this series because why not?
Yes, and yes and actually if you're going into pitch and I'm on Elm Street sequel and like the 80s or whatever
You really should have done a NOM
A NOM themed that would have been perfect great question and our man Ken Henley our point man over at Fengoria
Yeah, and the Fengoria podcast network and all that stuff
He said us a bunch of questions. I say this is a good way to end is just answer
Yeah, Ken's questions. He says his Joe checked into a health care facility after admitting he liked Johnny Depp and Tusk
What a beautiful question because it's one of the worst performances in recent movie history
And you know who else didn't like it from everything I've heard Kevin Smith
He was like I hate that I have this guy and it's such a great get but he's ruining my movie
What are you talking about? That's what I've heard through the great fun people who worked on that. Oh, I don't believe it
I think that's our shit
In all seriousness though funny Freddy or scary Freddy
For me scary Freddy funny Freddy is annoying of course is new nightmare the best sequel for me. Yes
No threes the best sequel new nightmares the second best sequel. Okay
and then
Would you recruit in small towns? I don't understand what that means but
Yeah, I'm just gonna say no thanks for listening everybody. I'm at Joe DeRose a comedy on Twitter
I made the Patrick Walsh on Twitter violence to Graham and
Guys we'd love your feedback. I hope you're enjoying the podcast
Yeah, give us some feedback as an aired yet, so you know what it does we'd like to know we'd love it
All right guys, thanks a lot for listening take care
And we'll see you in hell next time