With a major selection of the looks your kiddos love, starting at just $4 in the Walmart app,
a new school year means a stylish new them.
Who knew?
Buying skater skirts and crocs that say, I'm casual but cool.
Sparkly sneakers that say, it's my classroom, you're just learning in it.
And preppy polos that say, I'm the teachers pet, even if they're mommy's menace at home.
Buying their favorite styles, starting at just $4 in the app.
The Walmart you thought you knew is now new.
New season, new chaos in college football.
Big stage, big opportunity.
This Labor Day weekend, the Wildness Lives on ABC, ESPN and the all new ESPN app.
What a way to start!
Featuring top 10 teams like Clemson, Notre Dame, Alabama and LSU and Bill Bella checks debut at North Carolina.
It's so special these teams collide.
Don't miss a lineup filled with electric natures.
Welcome back to college football.
Kick off week, presented by Modella, Labor Day weekend on ESPN and ABC.
Also available to stream on the all new ESPN app.
Hey folks, we'll see you in hell.
This is the movie podcast you turn to during your darkest hours.
We're here to do a Q &A today.
Usually we do Q &A's on the Patreon page.
But you know, lately we've done a few movie reviews on the Patreon page.
So why not put a Q &A up in the free stream?
And we're going to go front to back.
Oh boy, that is a long shake.
He's scratching.
That's my dog.
Khan.
That's enough.
That's my dog scratching.
I mean, it's like you know when you shouldn't do it.
What are you going to do?
He's a dog, you know what I mean?
You've been scratching your balls the whole time.
I don't say anything to you.
I don't make noise.
My balls are quiet.
Anyway, we're going front to back Q &A.
No segments today.
Just questions and answers.
So let's get to it.
Pat first up from Andrew Campos.
He asks, who are Joe's and Pat's favorite comedians?
My all time favorite is George Carlin.
And contemporary favorites are Maria Bamford, Cat Williams, and Bill Burr.
Yeah, I mean, my favorite as of now is probably Edward Pepitone.
Often discussed.
Got a shout out, Cat Williams, Brian Regan.
I feel good with that list.
It's a great list.
Chris Rock.
You know, I still love Jerry Seinfeld.
I can't deny that.
No.
They're all great.
I should have a woman in there as well.
Who's my favorite lady comic?
Maria Bamford is pretty amazing.
She's the best.
All right.
I'll go with her as well.
Okay.
What's one movie that you're in Monique?
I love actually.
What's one movie that you're embarrassed you've never seen?
You know, I was just...
Well, I said it on the last podcast.
I'm very embarrassed that I've never seen any of the big Mark Bergman films.
I feel like it's a film fan.
I should have seen those by now, and I still haven't.
So that's mine.
Yeah, I mean, for me, it's definitely something foreign.
I've seen most American movies.
I've seen a lot of foreign movies.
But I haven't seen a majority of like Fellini, Truffaut, Bergman, all your big ones.
And I just sort of knew when I was like 13 and so forth trying to watch everything
that I wasn't going to get this stuff till I was older.
So now I am older.
It is hard to come home after a hard day and crack open a Fellini film.
But I need to start doing it.
That was Sean Liles' question.
Okay.
Nick English asks, will you ever review a Jeremy Sonear flick?
We have, maybe not on the main thing, but we definitely talked about Green Room.
And I think we were going to do an episode and didn't or something, but we talked about it.
I think Green Room is a masterpiece.
Yes.
Absolutely loved it.
Easily one of the best modern kind of suspense horror type movies.
Yes.
You know, we talked about hold the, we didn't do hold the dark in the movie corner,
but I thought that movie kind of sucked.
I didn't see that.
And was a let down for him.
That was a Netflix of Ridge.
But I loved Blue Rowan.
I have not seen Murder Party, although it's new to Shutter.
And I think Green Room has me very excited about what this guy does next.
I loved it.
All right.
Next.
Mysteries of our asks, who would make up your dream festival or concert?
Pick any five bands or singers, living or dead, any genres.
Also, please come to Texas.
It's a big question.
Let's go with, let's go with three.
Okay.
Sure.
Living or dead?
Living or dead.
Well, I would go Zappa, Motorhead, and original lineup, NWA.
Things that can never happen.
Yeah.
I mean, you might as well go dead, right?
Why would you pick a living band that you can just go see, yeah, whenever?
But I would go look, I don't even know if they are one of my favorite bands,
but you got to pick the Beatles.
You could be one of the few people in our generation who's seen the fucking Beatles.
I feel like it doesn't mean as much so if you can just bring them back from the dead.
I think it means more.
Really?
People would be even more impressed by that.
Fair enough.
Beatles.
Let's do, I got to have Elvis Costello there, even though he is alive, of course.
I never saw Bowie.
I'd love to do like a 70s Bowie.
I'd love to do a one of those last tour, Johnny Cash.
You know, I actually don't want to see him in his prime.
I like the end of the career stuff from him.
And I would love to see Otis Redding, you know.
All right.
How's that?
That was plenty.
All right.
I went for the full five, Misty.
I listened to your question.
I, Joe wanted to negotiate.
I have boundaries.
Alex Shipley says, Joe, what is your favorite thing about Pat?
Pat, what is your favorite thing about Joe?
You're probably going to need a few minutes, right, Joe?
Yeah.
Rattle them off.
I ain't going to have to go with that sweet ass.
Oh, come on.
No, I look, Pat is my favorite.
My favorite thing about Pat is he's with hilarious human being,
one of the funniest human beings I've ever known,
and I've told him that many times.
And he's a friend that I can rely on and turn to,
not always emotionally, but, you know,
when I hear you out.
When I need, when I need some sanity in my life,
he's a very reliable friend.
He's what I call a very dear friend.
You know, I'm proud to know the guy.
Ditto.
Next question.
Joe also extremely funny.
Belongs on that list of comedians.
And, you know, he's a man,
and they're increasingly rare in this town,
in this day and age.
Who says what's on his mind?
Says what's on his heart.
I appreciate that.
Thank you.
It's got an honesty,
and he's got honesty with humor.
And that's what I like.
Thank you.
Jerome, just two soulless men,
exchange and compliments.
Yeah.
That's right.
Jerome can cade.
Is living in L .A. worth it to do what you guys sometimes
seem to love, slash sometimes seems like it's killing you.
You know, Pat, if I could just jump in.
Please.
It is killing me.
Yeah.
And no, it's not worth it.
That's the short answer.
Yeah, I often wonder,
would I not be happier elsewhere?
I would almost have to be.
However, you can't really do this anywhere else.
And I lived in New York.
And that wasn't really for me either.
I think I just, I'm cursed.
But I like L .A. time to time.
Big picture I think it's fine.
I wish we had fucking seasons.
I wish we had less people.
And I wish that when we got less people,
we got rid of all the people who suck
because there are so many in this God for second town.
Yeah.
And it doesn't feel like a community
and it doesn't feel like home.
And I've been here for 10 years.
And mostly the reason for that is the people.
Yeah, Seinfeld said it best.
He goes, I've lived there for 10 years.
When the show ended, he go,
they go, are you going to stay in L .A.?
He goes, not moving back.
Yeah.
And he goes, been here 10 years,
still feel like I'm on vacation.
Yeah.
I was like, yeah, that's exactly what it feels like.
A vacation wherever one is trying to stab you in the back.
Yeah.
It's almost like if you went on a lifelong murder mystery
sleepover weekend vacation.
Sure.
One of those dinner things,
bed and breakfast things where they have a fake murder.
Right.
Like that except constant.
Yeah.
All right.
Mike Madrigal asks.
Mikey.
Are there any books, short stories or comics
that you'd like to see adapted into a movie?
Horror genre preferably.
But I'll leave it open.
I would like to, yeah, that's a,
I'm glad you asked that.
I would like to see most of
a skeleton crew, the Stephen King book,
which is all short stories.
I would really, really like to see most of those stories adapted.
But the one that stands overall,
and it's not in that book by King,
that I want to see a really good adaptation of is
the man in the black suit,
which is the first appearance of,
you know, the man in black.
I'm assuming it's the same character.
But, you know,
it's just a really creepy story.
It's really, really creepy,
and it's awesome.
And it's everything I love about a horror story.
It takes place like, you know, in the 40s,
and, you know, it's a kid in the woods,
and he runs into the devil,
and it's got almost a fairytale quality to it.
It's just an awesome, creepy story
that I love to go to sleep to.
Okay.
But that's the one I'd really,
that and skeleton crew,
the stories in that book.
How is the graveyard shift movie?
I recorded it and I have a watch.
It's a, it's not good.
I mean, it's a fun look.
It's a fun Sunday afternoon.
I don't want to think.
Maybe I'll doze off in front of the TV.
Maybe I won't, I got a pizza.
It's that kind of movie.
You're not going to watch it and be like,
wow.
Right.
Let's Heather.
I want you to watch this so we can go discuss it.
Sure.
You know, but you know, it's passable.
It's, it's, it's, it's,
it's TV horror decent.
It's not a TV movie,
but that's about the level it functions at.
Alan J. Howlett asks,
if you, Pat and Joe,
personally could remake any movie
using Nick Cage, Jackie Gleason,
and John Candy as the main leads.
What movie would you make?
I mean, I'm just going to say Ghostbusters.
You got those three.
I'd love to see what they do with it.
I would remake Fatso.
Sure.
John Candy Gleason, who's the other?
Nick Cage.
Yeah, I'd remake Fatso.
I'd have Candy in the Del Louise role.
I'd have Cage in the role as his brother.
And then I'd add a character
where Gleason is, is the heavy set father.
Why don't you have Gleason and Drag
as the end -bank rough character?
So you have a movie.
I mean, come on.
Mick Mack asks,
Roses, when are you going to direct again?
You love anthology horror,
you write good, short horror themed stories,
and you direct it a short,
albeit comedy that got into Tribeca.
Yeah, it's time, baby.
We need horror tour Joey of the Roses
to put those Blumhouse fucks out of business.
Love you both, Mosle.
Thank you.
You know what's funny?
I've always seen directing now, I'm kidding.
As my true call.
Yeah, go into the Jerry Lewis response.
Right.
No, directing, look, I directed my hour special.
That was the last thing I directed.
I'm, you know, I'm working on something
and I'm hoping that it comes to fruition.
And if it does, I will let you know.
But I am definitely, you know,
sliding back in that direction right now.
In fact, I got my camera out today
to kind of boot that thing up for the first time in a while
and start shooting some film and stuff with it.
So, you know, it's something that I am anxiously
looking forward to doing more
and trying to get back toward
and actively trying to do so.
So I will keep you posted.
Okay.
But thank you.
That's very nice to hear.
Luke Physioc asks, what are the scariest
most intriguing VHS box movie posters
from your childhoods?
I mean, to be real honest with you,
I'd be thinking of ones whose title I don't remember
that I would just use to masturbate to for years at a time.
I'd look at the thing, take a mental picture
and take that thing home with me.
But, you know, horror was a genre I usually avoided
at the video store because even the box has scared me.
And I can't think, I know there was one called
like Night of the Demons 2, I think,
and it was a woman.
She had like a head lollipop.
Yeah.
And I really thought that was freaky when I was a kid.
That's a great one.
Look, mine, oddly enough, is my favorite horror movie,
The Exorcist.
The cover.
Excuse me.
The cover of that movie I still find chilling.
Like, I can't even explain why.
Just the mystery of a man in like a suit and a top hat
under that street light staring up at the window
and you know there's like an awful thing happening in the house.
Like that, I still find that cover very haunting.
So I'll go with that one.
Carl Clark asks, have you ever kissed a man in the mouth?
Yeah, but like, you know, in like spin the bottle
where you got to like, like not like passionately.
You had to do same sex kissing and spin the bottle?
Yeah, you had to pick the guy on the lips.
That was always kind of the role.
Like, hey, if you want to be able to make out with the girls,
you got to kiss the dudes.
But you didn't have to make out if it was singing.
We would just pass and move on.
This was Missouri.
Yeah, I mean, you know, yeah, you do it there.
There's a cross burning on your front lawn.
Right, exactly.
Five minutes later.
Yeah, I have not romantically, no.
But I'm open to it, Carl, if you're asking.
Kevin Driscoll asks, what are your all -time favorite movie kills?
Any genre?
Look, the best movie, my two favorites are three favorites, actually,
are all Jason Kills, which is odd,
because I'm not the biggest Friday the 13th fan.
But part six has Horshack getting Jason punching through his chest
and then coming out the other side of his body, holding his heart.
Then there's the one in the trailer where he takes the woman
and slams her face into the metal wall and her face.
You see from the opposite side of the wall,
it makes the imprint of her face.
And then in Jason X, when he freezes the...
I came over as a man or woman, he freezes their head in dry ice
and then bashes it on a countertop.
And it just slushies everywhere, the head.
You know, like the one where he just slams the guy sleeping back into a tree?
Or the girl sleeping back into a tree?
That's a great one, too.
Friday the 13th for not being great movies, you know, overall.
Some of them are.
They just have really great kills, man.
Yeah.
I love in simple plan when the wife comes in with the shotgun
and just blasts him into that kitchen.
I thought that was like amazing.
It was surprising to me because it was not that sort of movie.
But like the shotgun blasts him across the room
and it's amazing in that movie.
I love that.
And then you know, funniest, biggest crowd reaction I got to go with Deep Blue Sea
when that shark eats sandblow Jackson.
I've never seen Deep Blue Sea.
Well, spoiler alert.
But it has a very justly beloved killing it by the shark.
I recommend.
Okay.
The movie's stupidest hell and has a terrible theme song by L .O. Cool J.
My head is like a shark's fin.
Awful.
Awful song.
Was that a release as a single?
Yeah.
And the sad part is the line he's quoting in the chorus is from I'm bad.
I'm bad is the best L .O. Cool J song of all time.
And in that song, it's just in the verse.
He goes, I'm like, Jaws, my head is like my shark's fin.
And it's awesome in that.
Yeah.
And then he takes it and does that Deep Blue Sea song.
And it's terrible.
It's just terrible.
It's rough.
And I think he thought he was going to get like that wild, wild west money.
Although the Deep Blue Sea song is better than Will Smith's Wild Wild West.
I mean, that's that song and movie or the worst of the worst.
That's yeah.
Ethan Gammage asks, what are Patent Joe's favorite script writing resources and tools?
I mean, you got to get final draft.
I know there's a few other programs that people claim to use.
But if you have anything but final draft out in L .A., I know you get kind of laughed out of a room.
But as far as resources, tools, a really great user -friendly beginner's guide to writing
is that one I recommended last week, which is the Thomas Lennon and Ben Garant.
It's called like guide to writing movies for fun and profit or something like that.
I'm sure you can buy a used copy for five bucks.
It's just really great practical advice.
It's more of a how to make money in this business guide as opposed to a how to make art.
But what would you expect from those guys career?
They made balls of fury for crying out loud.
But the new Herbie.
But that's a very funny and well written book that I recommend checking out.
The other one people like is like story by Robert McKee, who's the guy that Brian Cox played in adaptation.
I tend to go away from people who say scripts have to be written a certain way.
I tend to get most excited by things that don't follow a pattern.
But there are plenty of guides for how to write your script kind of seem like everybody else's script.
Best guide is to watch and study movies and break them down and write what happens and write what the scenes are.
And use them like that, Joe.
Excuse me, I agree with all that.
I used to use final drafts.
I started using this other program that is final draft compatible.
You're using Microsoft Word.
I think it's called text at it.
I started using a different program that is does fountain format.
And also it is compatible with final draft.
And of course, now I can't remember the name of the fucking program because I am brain dead.
I will find it before we end here.
But what I do like about this program is it has a great memory feature as you write.
So when you start to write a certain thing like a character needs to speak or interior.
The bathroom or whatever, it does a lot of auto filling for you.
It does a lot of great predictive stuff.
So it will start to format your thing for you so you can sort of just write without thinking about like,
oh, I've got to hit enter and then indent to the character and then do this.
It's very, very convenient.
And then as I said, you can export to a file compatible for anybody else to use.
But final draft is kind of the be all end all.
But anyway, I got to find the name of this.
I can't believe my own draft is without question, the most annoying computer program that has ever lived,
riddled with glitches.
I have never been angry at anything in my life than final draft.
That said, everyone says you have to do it.
It's like Apple.
So everyone just goes, okay, we'll keep doing it even though everyone agrees that there could be a better option.
Yeah, so I'll find the name of this app and just throw it out there in case you want.
But in the meantime, everything Pat said about how to write and what you should do to prepare to write.
I agree with.
I think the only real work is doing it.
Practice makes perfect in that sense with writing.
You have to write bad stuff in order to write good stuff.
And you have to watch a lot of stuff.
I mean, you know, there's the rare person that is able to just kind of sit in a dark room and never watch anything
and crank out these brilliant things.
But that's rare.
You have to watch movies so you understand why certain devices are used.
And they don't have to be Hollywood movies.
The general rule that I think does apply to almost every movie, even your art films,
is act one, put your character up in a tree.
Act two, throw rocks at the character in the tree.
Act three gets your character out of the tree.
That's a very basic, general thing.
But if you follow that, you're likely going to get your movie made.
Act two should be the longest and most substantial.
Act one should introduce your characters in your situation.
Act three should wrap it up.
But slug line is the app, by the way.
Yes.
There's so many books you can buy for cheap.
You have to fucking internet.
There's podcasts, galore.
Check them all out.
Adam Schulte, best martial arts movie.
Best recent one.
And I didn't see that other Netflix one that I heard was great with the long title.
But I thought the raid was awesome.
Marshall arts, you know, I, that's a genre I've seen maybe 10 movies.
I've seen like the Jackie Chan's.
I've seen Enter the Dragon, which I love.
And that's about it.
But the raid was really, really cool.
And I'm just, I like crouching tiger to some extent, you know.
But I'm not, I'm no expert.
Mine will always be Enter the Dragon.
Yeah, it's not the flashiest, but it's just awesome.
And it's, it's the format.
It's sort of the prototype for like all the great fighting video games I love.
Like, Enter the Mortal Kombat and all that stuff is clearly based on Enter the Dragon.
Right.
So that's mine.
Mike Jerbino asks favorite Pierce Brosnan movie.
Oh boy.
You know, I love kind of like random questions like that.
Pierce Brosnan's best movie.
And I also get to recommend one that not enough people have seen.
It's called The Matador with Brosnan and Greg Keneer.
I agree with that.
Written and directed by Richard Shepherd.
Brosnan is very, very funny in that, that movie blew me away at the theater.
I think because my expectations were so low.
And another great underrated Brosnan is the Taylor of Panama.
It's like a more real life James Bond.
I thought he would have been a great bond.
He was, he was saddled with the worst scripts in the entire fucking franchise.
He had terrible James Bond's.
But it's everybody anymore.
It's the same thing with Dalton.
And the Dalton was replaced with, with Bronson and you say the same thing, right?
And then it's the same thing with Daniel Craig.
Like that first one was great.
And then every other one everybody is like, these are terrible.
Yeah.
That's a franchise that just has never really, I've never left like, yes, awesome, you know.
I bought the box set.
I haven't seen three fours of the bonds, probably.
But those two, Taylor of Panama and especially the Matador are excellent movies.
I think Brosnan is great.
Look, I mean, looks incredible.
There's a man I'd kiss in the mouth.
Ditto.
What's your favorite Pierce Brosnan?
Mrs. Dalphine?
I agree.
Run by fruiting.
I agree with, oh god, I hate that fucking movie.
Oh, I like this.
So much.
He was at a run by fruiting.
Now all that, when Robin Williams is doing all that stuff, it's a little hard to watch.
Oh my god.
No, I'll agree with the Matador.
I like the Matador.
Awesome picture.
And if you want to hear some of the worst singing in film history, check out Pierce Brosnan in
Mamma Mia.
Oh boy.
Where he should not have sang.
Let's be real.
Rira, excuse me, B -ron asks, you're both up to perform the importance of being earnest on stage.
Which one is algae and which one is Lady Bracknell?
Okay, you have overestimated our intelligence.
I don't appreciate it.
I'm going to, in the importance of being earnest, play Ernest P. Warl.
And I will have Joe play Vern.
Well, I would like to play Ernest Borgneye.
That's fine.
All right.
I've never seen the importance of being earnest.
I haven't either.
I'm no, you know, I'm no dummy.
I know some stuff.
I don't know.
I'd like to play algae, I guess, in the interest that I can make a lot of fungus jokes.
Sure.
I'm a fun guy.
Yeah.
That's one right there.
Kevin Morrisonic asks, to both of you, what are your favorite pre -1960s horror movies?
Also, my birthday is next week and was hoping one or both of you could fly across country and help me blow out the candles from my big birthday bash at the skating rink.
I'm 25.
Attendance looking a little light, so it would probably just be the three of us.
Keep me posted.
I will not be there.
Joe will not be there, but happy birthday to you, Kevin.
Yes.
You're 25.
Please just enjoy your life.
Please.
Please know that it takes a turn at some point.
Enjoy your life.
It's like, and you got to cherish him, like he has Billy Madison famously said.
Yeah, yeah, you do.
Those years, they don't come back.
My favorite pre -1960s horror movies.
The haunting is incredible.
I think that is 1960, but just an awesome flick.
Joe, you got one off the top of your head.
I'll try to Frankenstein.
Brighter Frankenstein is awesome.
No question.
I like a lot of those.
Anytime I watch an old school horror movie, I'm always really pleasantly surprised.
My favorite old school thriller, let's say, is notorious.
Hitchcock's notorious is easily his most underrated and just a perfect movie.
Pre -60s.
Hitchcock, I'll go with strangers on a train.
Yeah, also a thriller, I'd say.
But yeah, strangers on a train is pretty awesome.
Yeah, but there's some good ones.
The criterion has some good ones.
You know, like really creepy, interesting ones.
Yeah.
From that period.
The uninvited is a really cool old ghost story, if you've never seen that.
David Belinger wants to know, and actually started his question, just wanted to know.
If you guys have ever seen 1986's, nothing in common with Tom Hanks and Jackie Gleason.
We had a Gleason talk.
We were just talking about this yesterday.
We were.
We were at the weed, we were drinking to go to the weed fest.
Yeah.
We were talking about these movies and how there was the, they did nothing in common.
And then there was the ripoff one with Billy Crystal and Alan King.
Memories of me.
What are the odds that that's the question today?
That and the Singleton thing have me wondering if perhaps I'm controlling the worlds.
I think I think you like the Ursula the Sea Witch is a little mermaid.
I love nothing in common.
Yeah, I like nothing in common a lot.
It's an entertaining movie.
Much like Hanks, Gleason is a guy that started out comedically strictly and then turned out
to be a tremendous dramatic actor.
And I'm bummed that we didn't get to see more of it before he died.
I guess he did some of it in the 60s.
We don't recommend for a prize fighter.
He's great in that.
A record for a heavyweight, I mean, he's great in the hustler, you know.
And the hustler.
Yeah, he's fucking awesome.
There's an awesome movie.
So I guess we always kind of knew, but I like that movie a lot.
I think it's very touching and I like anything like that.
We're like the snappy young rich guy who learns the meaning of life and realizes
that it's about love and it's not about money and all that shit.
So it always starts with like the credits are rolling and he's going to work.
And then he like goes to check his watch and dumps his coffee into his lap.
Yeah, yeah.
And you know, as he's walking out the door of the wife's like, and remember,
it's Janie's birthday tomorrow.
And then the car door shuts.
Yeah, yeah.
And he doesn't make it home for the birthday.
Yeah.
And then 15 minutes in.
He's at a meeting at 9 .30 p .m.
The Jamie's birthday.
Somebody says birthday and he's like, fuck.
Yeah.
Goes home.
The kids asleep.
Yeah.
The wife's got a candlelit dinner set out.
She's like, well, it's gotten cold, but you can heat yours up if you want.
Candle's melted.
Anyway, that was a time when Tom Hanks was doing like three pictures a year.
It's, yeah, it's in the, it's of his 80s output, which is pretty ample.
It's, I would say about a six.
It's above average.
What actor, hemi under asks, what actor or actress would you add to the expendables lineup?
And what actor or actress would you remove?
I'm going to focus on adding because I mean, these movies are just about getting as many people on the billboard as you can.
We don't need to subtract.
That's just bad producing, hemi.
But who would you like to add?
That's a great question.
I'm trying to think who, who do they?
I mean, Chris, they even had Harrison Ford.
Who the fuck else is last?
They had Ford in there.
Ford's in the third one, yeah.
I only saw one, too.
He's in the third one.
I mean, Norris is still kicking up.
Norris is in there.
They got snipes in there.
They got, Norris is in there?
Yeah, Norris is in the second one.
Shit, I didn't know that.
Yeah, I mean, maybe there's nobody else to add.
There's got to be Segal.
I assume is in them.
Segal's not been in there.
So he must, they must have some beef.
And I got to be honest, I don't want to see Segal in it now.
Everybody hates Segal.
So you read that SNL book.
There's a whole chapter to note how much they hated Segal.
How much he sucks?
Yeah.
What an asshole he was.
I mean, they had Van Dam.
They had Schwarze.
They had anyone you might want.
I mean, it might be fun to throw in like a, you know, a black
exploitation guy or something.
Get a little diversity.
I got one.
Through, through Jesse Ventur in there.
All right.
And if you can't get him get, what's his name?
James Adobe and to do his amazing impression.
Yeah.
I mean, whole Hogan will be fun.
Sure.
I think like Billy D Williams or somebody might be cool.
Yeah.
That would be cool.
But he was never that kind of action star.
No.
Carrow Weathers would be good too.
Weathers.
I feel like he's been in them, but maybe he hasn't.
I'm shocked he hasn't, because it's Stallone's thing.
Why would he not have Weathers in there?
He had Lungren in for Christ's.
Yeah.
Matthew Ruiz asked Pat, will you ever tell your Mexican strip club
tale on the pod?
No.
I told it once.
I told it.
I think the best I'd ever tell it.
I don't even know if I'd remember the details anymore.
So no.
Clayton Stamper says, if you could freaky Friday style body swap
with anyone in the world, who would it be?
So that would mean I'd be my personality and someone else's body.
I guess, right?
Yeah.
I guess so, right?
I mean, I'm going straight to Gosling.
I want to live as Gosling.
I wouldn't mind living as Mike Patton for a little while.
He's one of my favorite musicians.
He's always doing awesome shit.
He just did this thing in Belona, Italy, where he has a second home,
which right off the bat, that's amazing.
Where it was him and a piano player for two nights and a small thing.
I'm like, it's fucking unreal.
How do you do that?
How do you get to do things like that?
I would do that.
Well, you should learn to play piano.
It would be a good start, Paul.
Yeah, I know.
And I'm going to have to get a home in Belona.
And then go to Italy, would be another one.
Patrick Baxter asks, if you were in charge of casting a modern version of the Godfather,
who would you cast in the lead roles?
I mean, good question, but Jesus.
You know, I hate to go there again and he doesn't really look Italian,
but Gosling would make an awesome Michael Corleone.
He plays that all in his eyes just beautifully.
He'd be a great Corleone.
I hope they don't do this, by the way.
Sonny, Bobby Canna Valley is Sonny.
I've seen enough Canna Valley.
But that's a guy that can explode.
You know, I think we can do better, can't we?
I'd like to get Giovanni in there in the Duval role.
Yeah, he'd be good.
Who do you get?
Giovanni would actually be good in the con role,
if you want to really mix it up.
Who's a good, like, explosive young actor?
We don't have those anymore.
Shia LaBuff.
Oh, LaBuff would be a great sonny.
LaBuff would kill.
It's a little too young, but that'd be the perfect comeback vehicle for him.
But who do you cast as the Godfather?
Fredo almost has to be Hashemi, even though he's too old,
maybe Sarah, Michael Sarah, that's Freda.
I mean, I think he could do it.
Yeah, he could do it.
The Godfather himself, Mr. Marlon Brandt.
I mean, they show full people out of this business at 53.
I know.
It's like, you know, like what's his face?
Christopher Plummer.
Yeah.
Is the only old actor can think of it.
He's too old to play that part.
Yeah, you'd need somebody pretty surprising.
I wonder if you get Nicholson out of retirement to do that.
You know what they'd probably do is have Pacino play the Godfather.
If they actually did this, which they'll probably pitch in about one year.
Yeah.
But or peshy.
Who's going to step into that role?
I mean, or maybe John Lithgow could do it like in pet cemetery and just walk in and be like,
hello, I'm the Godfather.
Yes, it's me because he doesn't want to make those same stupid choices that a previous actor met.
I did it because your daughter has touched me in a way nobody's ever touched me.
Good question.
I hope that doesn't happen.
Sarah Catherine asked, do either of you have a script in mind that you would love to make into a show or a film?
And what is it about?
Absolutely.
I have a television script that I am extremely excited about that is leaning into more of a Cohen Brothers -y type area.
More of a thriller vibe.
John Rive always loved.
And I have a thriller feature film that I kind of need to finish that is really about
the bizarre circumstances involving me getting my home.
And sort of a fictionalized version of those events.
So yes, I always got stuff in the pipeline.
I hope you see him someday.
I'm currently writing a horror screen.
I'm almost finished, actually.
I don't want to talk about what the plot is, but I'll be actively trying to sell that soon.
But I have another horror screenplay that I wrote with my friend, James Pingstone,
who we talked about frequently on this podcast.
It's been denied left and fucking right.
But it was a horror anthology.
It was four stories at all intertwined.
They were all devil -related.
And it was called The Devil Knows Me.
Which I thought was a really cool title.
When we first started taking it out, everybody said nobody wants to see anthology.
And now anthology is everywhere.
And now they're like, this is too high -brow up a project for somebody in your position.
You need a lot of money to do anthology.
I mean, it's always fucking something.
At the end of the day, I can't get the goddamn thing made.
And I would love to, because the stories are a lot of fun.
Very tales from the dark side.
Very throwback creep show.
Fun horror.
It's the thing with 80's of people.
You never know if they're telling you the truth or if they just think it sucks.
And they're just lying to you.
Like, you never know what the deal is.
Right.
I also, by the way, too, wrote a screenplay with my friend Joe Bolter.
Who used to co -host Craig Ferguson's radio show with him.
Based on a story that we developed with Craig.
That was something we talked about on air at one point.
Right.
And Craig said, this would be a great movie.
And we kind of developed a story with Craig.
And then Joe and I went off and wrote the screenplay.
I hope we get that made at some point.
Yeah.
Because I think it's really funny and a really fun, trippy movie.
I mean, keep an eye out.
Movie business takes an eternity.
But we'd both have stuff to, yeah, for sure.
We're off to a great stop.
Isaac DeLorenzo asks to help me settle a longstanding argument of the two X -Men movies.
Do you prefer Logan or Days of Future Past?
Days of Future Past, 125 ,000%.
Joe hated Logan.
I thought Days of Future Past kind of helped breathe a little life into a dead franchise.
But I love Logan.
I take it way over Future Past.
It needed something that different, I think.
He'd be good in the expendables.
Jackman.
Yeah.
Yeah, he'd be fun.
Chris Goodnight asks for Joe, what video game would he most like to see as a movie?
See?
I told you I get messages about video games.
Okay.
What video game would I like to see most as a movie?
You know, man, that's a tough one.
That's a cursed thing.
It's never done right.
Every time they do it, it sucks.
But if I had to pick, I would like, because it's so impossible.
You know what?
I'd like to see Castlevania movie.
I like the cartoon a bit on Netflix.
But it's a little, it's a little too, I don't even know what the word is.
It's a little too adult aimed for my taste.
Like, it's not that fun and it's not that adventuring.
It's a little too heavily into like the themes of religion and good versus evil and the characters.
You know, like that Castlevania done properly could be an awesome Indiana Jones style medieval
horror movie.
Like it would be so fucking fun.
Right.
But it'll never happen.
You know what would suck as a movie?
You know, Zelda's funny.
Yeah, because that's one of those games.
Well, I think the games are great, but it's not.
If you like talking to a dwarf for 20 minutes, it's text just scrolls endlessly across the screen.
You got it, you know, there's a lot to, there's a lot to take in.
Anyway.
Daniel Rudd asks, any good scores on record store day?
Actually, to my knowledge, I've never gone to the record store on record store day.
I find it's become a little, you know, the stuff you're getting is like,
just people trying to squeeze some more money out of things that have already been released and so forth.
And it's so crowded.
I usually don't care much for records today, but I got four amazing scores this year.
I got a double picture disc reissue of Motorhead single for overkill.
Okay.
It was the radio edit.
It's the first time it's ever been released since it was originally released in the 70s.
It's got a rarity on the B side.
And then the other picture disc is bomber, which is my favorite radio, Motorhead song ever.
And that's also got a B side on it.
Amazing packaging.
Great fucking little two seven, double seven inch package.
I also got a cool Keith exclusive called something complicated trip.
I think it's called.
I'm waiting to get that in the mail.
I got a Zappa exclusive.
It's a, it's, I think it's called Frank Zappa's Guide to Guitar Point.
And it's basically a compilation that was sent out on cassette only in the 80s with guitar magazine.
And never released ever, ever again, anywhere.
And they released it on vinyl this year for the first time.
So that's incredible.
And then finally I got, and I've been waiting for this because the vinyl has been going for $200 for years.
Frank Black teenager of the year.
Oh, I would have liked one of those Joe.
I had to buy it online.
You had to, they, so they reissued it on white vinyl.
They also reissued his first one.
I don't care as much about it.
Is it still available?
Yeah, you can get it for like 40 bucks.
Oh, yeah.
But that vinyl has, that's the best Frank Black solo album.
Of course.
It's, you know, the vinyl has been $200 forever.
Yeah, that's why I never got it.
Classic album.
Yeah.
The guy who did the music for the Biblically pilot played on that album.
So I had like a thousand questions about him.
Oh, all right.
Michael Borland asks, what are the best vacations you've ever taken?
Much love from the Twin Cities.
Thank you for that.
You know, I haven't taken that many vacations to be honest with you.
But my honeymoon was pretty awesome.
I went to Greece, had a blast.
Young love.
My best ever solo trip was London, Paris, and Amsterdam.
I just fucking rocked it out and had a great time.
I went to Rome.
Actually, this is on my buddy's honeymoon because his wife got a job with the rock cats and had to leave the honeymoon.
It was like the once in a lifetime job opportunity.
So he's like, I'm stuck in Rome for a week alone.
So I went to Rome, and we got fucking hammered in Rome too, guys, having a great time.
Sure.
And then I also, I had a great time when I went.
We used to go to Myrtle Beach in the summertime when I was a kid.
I built like 14, 15.
And I just remember making new friends down there over the course of 10 days,
looking up with women that were way out at, well, the girls at that time, that were way out of my league.
Right.
Just the wonder and magic and just never remember people be smoking weed and drinking.
I wouldn't do a thing.
I wouldn't smoke weed.
I wouldn't drink.
I was so happy and content.
Oh, little did I know.
Little did.
Yeah.
The drop off.
It's coming.
Daniel Doerr asks Pat, my Facebook free pal, Stephanie Power, wants to know your most embarrassing story from childhood.
Well, where do I start?
I've told a few on here.
Patrick Walsh's Faggin comes to mind.
The girl sitting.
I watch the way you say that.
I'm saying that's the role.
That's what everyone called me for years.
Oh, that's how it's spelled on the thing.
Oh, okay.
Sorry.
Girl sitting on my back and forcing me to eat gravel at recess while everyone watched.
First day of kindergarten.
Guy slicing my thigh open with a broken piece of glass.
And folks, this was the teacher forced to eat worms by one Ronald Lifton.
I mean, I could go on and on.
There's a lot of embarrassing moments in my life.
Childhood to the present, frankly.
Candice Yurkovich asks, who would you most want to throw cold spaghetti at?
Hmm.
God, such a long list for me.
Mariah Carey's way up there.
Not wouldn't make my top million.
Oh.
She just, there was a time where she irritated the shit out of me.
But she's not like a holier than now type.
That's who you want to head with spaghetti.
Well, times have changed.
I just, I used to have a bit about that.
I wouldn't want it to throw something at Mariah Carey.
It was during the Nick Cannon years when they were showing people how they had like a candy store in their house.
Right.
But yeah, I guess she's kind of falling off the list.
I, man, I got to tell you, dude, falling off the list.
I, and a lot of stages.
I have really grown to dislike Molly Ringwald.
I think it really fucking sucks that she is tossing hues under the bus in every interview chance she gets.
And acting like she wasn't there on the set, making these movies, too.
And that, like, it wasn't a different time.
And that everybody was a little blind to this shit back then.
Because that's how progress works.
She bugs me, man.
She bugs me.
I think that was a really cheap move.
I feel like you actually hitting a 50 year old woman with spaghetti, though.
You're not going to feel great once you've done it.
Probably.
No, and it would probably show that times haven't changed much.
All right, let me pick a man.
I know who I would definitely throw it at.
It's a real life person, and I can't say his name on the podcast.
Oh, yeah, I'm not even thinking normal.
Oh, Christ, I know a lot of people that I could just go do it right now, too.
I have a number one so strong that I can't even really think about joke answers
because I'm so focused on actually throwing spaghetti at him now.
Now that you say that, I got a number one real, that strong, too, who lives right in this city.
That mind us, too.
Yeah.
That's what I'm saying.
Okay.
All right, I take it back about Molly Ringwald.
All right.
Yeah.
I'll see you on the show.
Will you, John Wint asks, will you consider coming to Madison, Wisconsin, to do the live pod?
Broughtson beers are on me.
Was going to say no until we got to that second part.
Yes, we'll consider it.
We'll always consider it.
It's a matter of supply and demand.
If we can make the show work there, we will come to do it.
Madison is a great town.
It is being discussed.
And we're trying now for hopefully Chicago, so we'll see what happens.
A .J.
Madden asks Pat, can you share any details about Norm McDonald has a farm?
Yes.
My friends, John and Hayden, who did the Herald and Kumar movies and now run Cobra Kai, approached
me about doing this show where Norm McDonald and Harris are farm.
I fleshed this thing out like you wouldn't believe.
I actually tweeted Norm McDonald about it and he followed me and I never worked at the guts to go any further with it.
Right.
I've heard and I hate to hear it but I've heard he's notoriously extremely difficult and it probably would have been rough.
But we thought this thing could maybe get some traction going at Comedy Central or Adult Swimmer, one of these places.
And it's something that could happen, frankly.
I don't know.
We all got caught up in other projects and it didn't go.
But I've got an amazing treatment.
It's one of my favorite things I've ever worked on.
Would you say it's in Development Hell?
I would.
And we were going to have Will Sasso as like a handicapped farm hand.
You know, it's kind of similar to the party plate and dropped dead gorgeous.
Okay.
I just think it would really work.
Sounds funny.
Every week it's him talking to the animals.
So you're going to keep licking yourself there.
That's the cold open every week.
So much great.
Kyle Kinsland asks, what is the most crazy party experience you've had?
Oh boy.
I don't remember.
Oh.
I mean, I've had a couple.
In my place with just about five or six of us.
Yeah.
And how comes the Molly and God knows what else?
Right.
Next thing you know, it's seven a .m.
You're sitting across from all one another in the living room.
Everybody's going, I don't understand what's happening right now.
Yeah.
You're saying things like, do you ever think about it?
We're not really inside.
It's all outside, man.
Yeah.
You know, I've had a lot of those.
I had one really great part.
I had two really great parties at my house.
And then eventually I was like, I don't want to have to rebuild my house after these parties.
But the first one in particular was your classic 80s party that gets out of control.
To the extent that, as I've told you on the show, Julie at Lewis was in the house.
Either Tegan or Sarah was in the house.
You can tell anymore.
There was cocaine all over the bathroom.
I didn't touch it.
It wasn't offered any.
There was Han from two broke girls.
The great Matt Moe was the next morning in his underwear in our office just like passed out.
I was like, morning, Matt.
Just some great time.
I was sick as a dog the next day.
I had to sleep over that night.
I lived half a mile from you and I had to sleep over.
I was so fucked up.
Yeah, it was pretty damn fun.
But, you know, I've never like shot a man.
Liz Feezer asks, fuck Mary Kill, Kevin Bacon, Kevin Costner, Kevin Hart.
Well, you marry Costner.
That's obvious.
You fuck heart and you kill Bacon.
Bacon's played too many creeps.
Why are you killing Bacon?
Because he's played too many creeps at this point that I can't.
Bacon's got a good size hog if that interests you.
And while things he's got a good size hog.
He's played too many creeps.
I can't see him not as a creep anymore.
I know he's not, but he's played too many goddamn creeps.
I would kill Costner just because I never need to see him in a movie again.
I like Costner.
I love Costner.
But you're going to be bored in that marriage, frankly.
No.
I like a lot of laughter in my marriage.
I'm going to marry Hart.
Fuck the bacon.
All right.
Heath Keane asks, what's a conspiracy theory you're embarrassed to admit that you think holds weight?
Joe, I imagine that would be all of them for you.
I believe that Kennedy was killed by, I believe that was a government.
That's one, that's one I definitely believe in.
Okay.
I don't believe that it's, that it was, I believe in it so much I'm afraid to talk about it.
All right.
I'm a little embarrassed by that.
But that's the truth.
Yeah, I think there's some truth to some of these.
I mean, anytime anybody's like, would the government really do that to us?
It's like, have you been paying attention at all?
Of course.
So I think, you know, like releasing crack into the ghetto, I think that that one's absolutely true.
Well, I mean, it has to be.
It's like, you know, people who live in the ghetto aren't getting the crack and guns into the country.
Yeah.
You know what I mean?
Like so.
Okay.
Cassie Williams, if you only got to rewatch one TV series for the rest of your life, which show
would it be?
Ooh.
My, my, my.
I'm going to have to go with Frazier on that one.
Wow.
And I'm going to go with Seinfeld.
I believe possibly Soprans, but I think I'm going to go Seinfeld.
I think regardless, you're going to get sick of it.
Part of me wants to go Simpsons because there's 30 seasons I've never seen of it.
And 10 seasons of it are great.
But I think I'd get sick of that show.
Jeremy Griffin asks, any movies that you would absolutely not review, I wouldn't ever watch that Serbian film, you know,
the one where it's got like a baby being fucked or whatever it is.
What is that?
Serbian film is one of the most controversial movies ever made.
It's called Serbian film?
A Serbian film, yeah.
Yeah.
I wouldn't review that.
I also wouldn't review the landmine one where the guy stands there while his girlfriend gets
raped because if he steps off the landmine, he's going to blow up or whatever.
When we were at our horror fest, we saw that.
Yeah.
Yeah, that kind of shouldn't see the movie.
But I'm not, I'm not feeling it.
When they told me the premise of that, I was like, imagine telling your mom that that's the movie you made.
What's it about, honey?
Well, we wisely instead chose to go see the corpse movie where the dead woman gets fucked.
Yeah, I was like, what kind of a festival is this?
Yeah.
It's like, that's not really horror.
It's just awful.
Rich Hurley asks, Bill Polman or Bill Paxton?
Come on, dude.
I'm going Paxton.
Paxton 100 -0.
I love Polman, but I'm going Paxton.
I don't love Polman.
In fact, I'll go Bill Sadler over Polman, too.
Josh Gardner, what's your favorite candy bar?
Snickers.
Okay.
Fine.
And what's your McCaw?
Yeah, I was coming out of my mouth.
I was watching McCaw.
But also, I think butter fingers are so good that I have forbidden myself from eating one for like 10 years.
And if one touched my taste buds again, I would just eat butter fingers for like a week.
I find Fifth Avenue to be the superior version of the butter finger.
I don't hate a Fifth Avenue.
I don't even know if they still make them.
The best candy is giant chewing nerds.
And somebody texted me that they have, or somebody messaged me that they have an Easter brand.
And I'm just going to pretend those don't exist, too.
Because they're too good.
My mom sent me a box of Easter stuff.
That's nice.
Placing with disgust.
Because I need this in the house.
Yeah, true.
You know, I got peeps and cookies.
They're like baked chocolate bunny.
I like two of them, and then you want a puke.
That's about right.
Yeah.
Emily Florence says, can we get a Pinkstone guest episode?
I don't see why not.
Absolutely.
In fact, I was just talking.
That's actually very, that's a great idea.
I was just talking to Pinkstone.
He's coming out to visit at some point or he's trying to come out to visit again.
I think that'd be great if the first guest we ever had in this thing was this buddy of ours that we've talked about.
Yeah.
And listen, he would certainly have a lot to say about these movies.
Eric Law says, favorite acting family and least favorite?
Favorite is, I'll go with the Phoenixes.
Sure.
I'm going to go with the Bridges.
But I love the Bridges.
Least favorite?
Yeah.
I'm going to go with the Wains.
I'm going to go with the Kardashians.
Are they acting?
I don't think so.
You see that video?
I saw.
Did you hear about that fire at Notre Dame?
Yeah.
No, it was at, and why did you do that?
Did you hear about the fire at Jeff and Bose Family Reunion?
They say that it burned a lot of Bridges.
I'm going to take my turkey out of the oven.
Are we nearing the end of the list here?
We got some more, but you know, a lot more.
Get your turkey.
I'll do the next one.
You have to watch a lot of movies and shows for your job and the podcast.
Does it ever get boring?
You know, I've been bored by movies for sure, but I am always just very happy to be watching a movie.
There's so many less pleasant things you could be doing with your time.
So, the movies themselves might be boring, but no.
I like watching them and talking them with Joe.
I think Joe would agree.
Janet O 'Loughlin -C asks, can we get a spin -off podcast where you all just talk about music?
Look, we hear you loud and clear.
I think you guys like when Joe and I talk music and we'll start peppering it in.
Then we don't got to start a new podcast.
Because I think we're fine just doing one.
You know, we'd kill each other.
Travis LH Pernox says, why do you guys dislike all the movies I love?
I'm sorry, Travis, it sounds like you just have bad taste.
It's not intentional.
Megan Hummel says, do you have any movies from the criterion collection that are on your wish list to buy?
No, because each sale, I buy the ones that I need.
It winds up being less than $100 a month to have the entire criterion collection.
Because I've been collecting it for a very long time.
But the next one I'm very excited to buy that they announced would be...
Let me see if I can... God damn it.
I don't remember.
You know, I don't have to remember everything.
They're doing a new do the right thing.
I have their old do the right thing, collect criterion, and it's awesome.
I'm excited to have that in a new remaster, because that's an amazing movie.
One of my favorites.
I'm excited to do the...
I really want to get the Igmar Bergman criterion set.
It's $180.
I got it every one of his movies.
That's the thing I want to get next.
I got it and it's great.
And they're doing Blue Velvet.
That's the one I'm most excited about, frankly.
Now then.
Next, a queue.
Tim, Calb.
Oh, man, that's a name.
CalbFleesh.
What would it take for you to get in the spaceship on a one -way trip to Mars?
Zero interest.
Never would do it, ever, ever.
Sorry, Tim.
We'd be declined.
You're off.
Heighten Davidson asks,
smartest career move you guys ever made.
Interest.
I hate to say it moving to LA.
Oh, but that is the truth.
All right.
Look, yeah, that's probably it too.
I mean, I never expected to live out here.
I got to really cite my old writing partner for lighting that fire
and getting us out here because it just didn't...
New York was such an overwhelming experience and I knew nobody here.
But, yeah, that's what I always tell people.
I'm like, first and foremost, if you're calling me for advice from Illinois,
I can't take you seriously.
You have to live in New York Los Angeles if you want to pursue a career in the arts.
But that's some good advice and the advice I'm about to take
is to do something I'm passionate about and want to do,
which I have sort of forgotten to do for the last ten years.
And it's time.
Don't chase money.
I guess would be it.
What I would say.
However, make some money if you can't.
Megan Hummel says,
do you have any move?
Oh, read it.
Emily Rook.
When you guys finally get over it and hook up,
will you want to get married?
And what will your wedding look like?
Will we be invited?
Who?
Man, you, Joe.
I always thought of it as more of an aloping situation.
Yeah, we would not want anyone there.
I think we would go together to a place where we could drink a lot.
But it's basically a marriage at this point.
Yeah.
A lot of drinking and bitching.
Pat and I have had several hangouts just sitting in a bar, no discussion.
The passion's gone.
Yeah.
I don't see us ever drinking enough to hook up.
But I do see that like if we hit like 60 and it's all fallen to shit
that we could have like a nice common law, roommate ship.
This is a, yeah, this is an albundi situation right now.
We're together but the thought of sex disgusts us.
Exactly.
Tegan McLeod asks,
if you had to describe yourself with one or a few moves
which would you pick?
I've always said that the reason Hannah and her sisters is my favorite movie is
because I've never related more to a movie in my entire life.
It is the most insightful film I've ever seen.
The inner monologues in it are so spot on and the characters are so well developed
and it's just so painfully relatable.
Oh, that's the one for me.
Like it's just, it's just a, I find it's fascinating how insightful it is.
Okay.
And geez, I mean that's an interesting question but as far as like something that made me feel seen or whatever.
At the time, definitely high fidelity.
I think a lot of men learn how to be better in relationships from that book and that movie.
A lot of stuff really hit me.
Like it's not important what you like, it's important what you are like.
I had always looked at relationships the other way.
You know, you hear, be dating a girl and she says she likes modern country and I'd be like,
see ya.
Right.
You know, the character of the person is more important.
Yeah, something like that but I could definitely think of a better answer with more time
that represents me myself.
Samantha Lippard asked was moving to LA hard on you guys, especially when the business is getting you down.
Do you ever entertain thoughts of moving back to Missouri or Pennsylvania?
Do you see yourself ever leaving LA?
I love hearing about you and Joe's career and the mental emotional side of it.
And Samantha, I ain't told you the half of it.
I ain't told you the tenth of it.
Yeah, I would definitely leave.
The second that I can figure out a way to keep this show going, my career going and not be here all the time, I will leave.
When I have the means to come in as I am needed, meaning come in, record the show when we need to.
Ten to the meetings, whatever, any of that stuff, not lose my footing in the business, I would 110 % leave.
Life's too short and you know, it's not that every other city is so much better.
It's just the constant being surrounded constantly by the business.
It's just not a healthy way to live.
Shit people, every act stabbers.
Yeah, and then every single billboard you look at is related to your industry.
It's like if you worked in politics and lived in DC, like I've got to imagine that's fucking maddening.
Sure, you know, it's got to be maddening.
Fair enough, I think I would never, ever, ever, ever move back to Missouri.
I could see myself leaving LA potentially, but I do feel like I'm kind of here for the long haul.
And I'm fine with that, you know.
Sometimes for me, the fantasy of moving is just, man, I'd rather live in Malibu.
Yeah. You know, some place where, okay, I got to drive in for two hours, but whatever.
But like the point is, it's just not living in the nucleus of it like I do right now, right?
Lupé Pita Pachico asks, what's your favorite chick flick?
A real little bitch cry fest. 127 hours doesn't count, but of the female persuasion.
Like beaches, steel magnolias, joyluck club, etc.
I've never seen joyluck club.
I liked beaches. I like steel magnolias.
And I love terms of endearment. I think that's a great chick flick that gets me.
The notebook is a great one.
Love actually.
It's not a, it's not a tear jerker, but it's chick flick.
Nine to five.
Is the greatest piece of feminist cinema ever made.
Yes.
More people need to be watching this movie.
It's a great movie.
Scott Sweeney, heard any good original film scores recently?
PS Pat, your Creed II cruise control joke was such a home run.
Thank you.
I appreciate that.
It's very nice.
A great film score that I like to write to lately is under the skin.
It's a very disturbing piece of music, and it's fantastic.
I always go to the carpenter records.
I've been doing Goblin Suspiria lately.
Yeah, those two John Carpenter albums are awesome.
The themes and son of themes or whatever.
And the phantomous records, like Patton's band, I like.
They're a little chaotic, but they serve a nice purpose for writing, even with the chaos.
Gaspar Noez climax had an amazing soundtrack, not a score, but an amazing soundtrack.
Ken Hanley asks, hello Ken.
How are you, sir?
You're going on a big vacation.
You need someone to watch your pets fill in for you at a hot work, and someone to come with you.
What horror characters icon would you choose for each and why?
Wait, wait, say this again.
You're going on a big vacation.
You need someone to watch your pets, someone to fill in for you at work, and someone to come with you.
What horror characters or icon would you choose for each and why?
It's like a math problem, Ken.
I'd have Jason watch the pets.
I feel like he wouldn't hurt the animals.
Okay.
Phil and for me at work, I'd have a pinhead, because he seems, he seems like he's good at his job.
Yeah, you know, he's perfect.
Any out of towners here tonight.
I was thinking in this I had a, I had like a job at it.
Oh, okay.
Oh, yeah, I'm a comic.
I forgot.
Yeah.
I guess Freddie then would have to be, or the crib keeper, I get the crib keeper to do my comedy job.
That'd be good.
And then to bring with me on the trip, I mean, that's who, who the hell the, you know, could be a horror character as well.
So I'd bring Jamie Lee Curtis from Halloween and make love to her.
I'm going to go with that too.
Someone to go to my job, I mean, definitely somebody who can handle trauma, which is pinhead, right?
He's the master of sorrow.
Yeah.
And also I feel like he could, you know, stick it to the people that are shitty.
That would be great.
So he would take them to hell where they deserve to go, many of them.
And then to watch my cat, I mean, I somebody nice, you know, I don't let it just anybody watch my damn cat.
I'd have my friend Brian do it again because he did a great job last time.
But he's not a horror character.
I choose Brian.
Sorry.
Dave DeWitt, am I still within the hour?
I think you're just barely going to read these last few.
Where are we at?
Yeah, let's read them.
We'll just get to the end.
Edmond Agabbo.
Hello, Edmond.
I relate to you guys so much and I ask this genuinely, do you think you and Joe will ever be happy?
No.
Yeah, I mean, sadly, the answer is no.
And my therapist thinks no.
And I don't think there's a way out of it for me.
But I think striving for happiness is the best way to be unhappy.
I think one day when I get away from the constant prodding of this industry, I will find some piece.
That's what I think.
I don't know.
But who knows?
Maybe it's me.
Jake McAlvin says you guys still working on something together?
Not really, but sort of.
Yeah.
Michael Rose asks, what's the last property out there that you guys love but are fearful or hopeful
as it's eventually remade, adapted for screen, et cetera.
For me, that's misery.
I don't think they can't improve it.
I don't know why they try to do it.
Yeah.
I got to say I'm not crazy about them doing the whole season of Castle Rock with misery.
I don't know.
That doesn't sound like a good idea.
But we'll see.
We shall see.
Kevin, my phone's going to die.
Let's rush through.
Let's get these last ones done.
Did Pat really throw a glass of milk in Sandy Bullock's face as Kevin Regatti?
No, that was a tweet.
It was just a joke.
I would.
Ben Lee says, Pat, you talked a lot in the interviews for Living Biblically about how the rabbi
and priests that you had for advisors were really funny.
Did they really make you laugh?
Or was that just Hollywood talk?
Not trying to be a dick.
No, they were funny guys.
Nothing they said like made it on the show.
But they were really funny and they had a great take on things.
I thought they were really cool.
Joe wins the next time you'll be in Pittsburgh.
No idea.
Probably.
I would guess about a year.
Okay.
No idea.
Sorry.
Joshua Boesman, what's a typical day like in your job as showrunner and how fucking scary is it to run the show?
It doesn't have to be scary.
It is the people sometimes within your camp, sometimes without your camp.
Who make the job, can make the job, terrifying, miserable, oppressive, depressive, destructive,
a place where you don't trust your own instincts, that can definitely happen.
It's scary.
It's a tremendous amount of pressure.
I don't think what it does to the body is good.
It's just a non -stop onslaught of stress and pain and attitudes and backstabbing.
And it's rough.
It's rough.
That said, when it's clicking and when the stuff's good, it's a lot of fun.
When the audience is laughing, it's a lot of fun.
Would you say you're sticking when it's clicking?
I'd say I'm sticking when it's clicking.
There were certainly times I loved.
Not to get too into specifics, but things can break bad, as they say.
You never know.
Okay.
How does Joe prepare material?
I saw him in Dallas and he was fucking hilarious.
Thank you.
It's usually things that infuriate me and I turn them into into bits.
I mean, honestly, that's usually what it is.
Something really irks me or doesn't make sense to me.
Yes.
And or is just a dark part of my own life and it's a fun thing to kind of explore and admit to on stage.
Sure.
And that's basically it.
All right. He also says that you guys love sneakers.
He gave us sneakers.
I still haven't watched it, buddy.
I'm sorry.
It's on my list.
I promise I'll get to it.
I loved it when you gave it to me and I loved it when I watched it again.
Gorious movie you've seen or favorite Gore movie asks Samantha Keifer.
Gorious movie.
I mean, you know, upper right master Little Strike was pretty gory.
Dead ranks.
I don't know if it's the gorious, but I mean, it's certainly a contender.
Yeah, I just watched, you know, well, like Dead Alive.
Oh, yeah.
That's a good one there.
I really found that troubling when I was a kid or younger.
Leo Lopez says if you guys separately were tasked to revive the erotic thriller genre with new movies, what would they be called?
I don't know what it would be called, but I always had a description of one of these in my head that started with a reluctant handyman.
Sure.
You know, fill in the blank, Shen Tweed comes in.
I'm going to call mine Ladder 69.
It's going to be set in a firehouse.
It's like back draft, but with a lot of butt sex.
Talk about a back draft.
Bri Alcuri asks, I think Troll 2 is truly one of the best worst movies.
Have you both seen it?
And what did you think?
I have only seen the documentary best worst movie and I haven't actually watched Troll 2.
I've reached an age where so bad it's good, you know, I'm just always bummed out and I think about the people who made it and they probably didn't think it was going to be bad and blah blah blah.
I'm not a fan of things that are bad being good, but Troll 2 is the exception for me.
I think it is an amazing astounding film.
I saw it on HBO by chance years ago and sat down to watch it because I was like, oh, I didn't know there was a sequel to Troll and by the middle of it.
I was like, what in the fuck is happening before the middle of it?
So I quickly purchased it.
I proudly own it.
I love the documentary and I love the love the people have for that movie and I love that the cast and creators understand and get a kick out of that.
So yeah, I love it.
Steve Calpa says, we all love your impressions and funny takes on music.
Can you fellow seriously consider adding a music segment to the podcast?
You may and we'll start talking more about music.
That's a pledge.
Well, let's not.
It's a pledge.
Let's not promise.
It's not a blood oath.
Steve Murdoch says, name a scene in a film that has a moment of such bad acting.
It ruins the film for you.
Set up the scene and do impressions.
Please, and thank you.
Oh, boy.
Is that the last question?
There's a few more.
We're going to answer these as quickly as we want.
We're in an hour, almost 20 minutes right now.
We're giving the people what they want.
And I let you guys go over your hour by the way.
I know.
But Turkey's getting called in there.
This is a marriage now.
Look, just when I just watched poetic justice with Janet Jackson,
she's good the whole time, but they never asked her to stretch too much.
And then she does this scene where she's talking to her friend Regina King about how she drinks.
And she's like, you're always drunk.
It's like you're always going to be fucked up.
Just like, just like my mom.
Oh, boy.
And that was a moment of granted.
It'd be hard to fix that line.
But that performance did not work for me.
It doesn't ruin the movie for me, but Spartan, a David Mammoth film.
Yes.
One of my favorite David Mammoth films.
Kilmer is awesome in it, but he's got a couple moments that make no sense.
Yeah.
And the one that sticks out the most that my friend Chip and I often discuss is a guy is telling a guy that gets shot
is telling him, like, you know, on the, at his hospital, but he saw the light, meaning, meaning like,
he saw like a signal that they needed to crack this case.
And he goes, I saw, or he said, he might say the sign or something, but he goes,
I saw the sign, and Val Camero goes, then you truly are blessed.
Because I think it's supposed to be that he thinks in a, in a, in a haze after being shot, he saw God.
It's an odd fucking scene.
Okay.
And I don't understand why David Mammoth who wrote it and directed it didn't say like, Val, that's not coming across.
Kilmer planned blind in a movie called that first site is some super embarrassing acting.
Daniel Draeter asks, and I have seen him ask this question several times.
So we should probably do this.
Can you please watch and discuss the swimmer starring Bert Landcaster?
I don't think it's a horror movie.
I don't know what it is.
I don't know how to get my hands on it.
But you know what?
Yes.
Maybe not Joe.
I will watch the swimmer and get back to the swimmer.
I don't even know what it is.
Jason Wybell says if you're for it, we have three more.
Forced to hang out with them.
Do you, do you hang out with Taylor Lawtoner or Taylor Kitch?
I don't know who either person is.
Taylor Lawtoner is the guy in twilight.
That's not Robert Pattinson.
No idea.
There's Kitch.
Kitch is Friday night lights and John Carter from Mars, which I didn't say.
No idea.
I'm gonna go with Kitch just because his last name is Kitch.
You definitely prefer to hang out with Kitch over Lawtoner, but I'm gonna drop them both
and select Taylor Swift.
Chris Marsh asks do you have recurring dreams or nightmares?
Not recurring so much, but for example throughout this last job I would often wake up screaming.
Wake up without my wife next to me because she had left because I was grinding my teeth
or screaming in the night.
So yes, constant ongoing night terrors as I sleep.
I have nightmares almost every single night.
Not like nightmares where like a ghoul is chasing me or anything.
But nightmares where like something terrible happens to somebody I love.
I get into a horrific relationship ending fight with somebody.
Right.
Just very emotionally disturbing dreams.
Or something really beautiful happens and then I wake up and realize it's not real.
So yeah, every night, bad dreams.
Alright.
And Sam Becker, have either of you ever wanted to direct a feature or even a horror short?
Yes.
And I'm trying to do so hopefully sometime soon.
Yeah, I prefer the thought of writing to directing, but it's something I could see myself doing certainly.
I think I am good with actors generally in terms of getting the performance I want and so forth.
So that might be fun.
And last question.
What's your favorite Mortal Kombat character from Will Potorff?
Baraka!
I don't even remember.
Just say Scorpion.
You like Scorpion.
My favorite was Scorpion.
I like the girl, Chun Lee.
That's Street Fighter 2.
I like Chun Lee.
But hey, we'll take it.
Alright folks, that's our show.
Jotaro's a comedy on Instagram.
Thank you for all the questions.
We gave you what you wanted.
We'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.