Huff, puff, and spin the house down at Golden Nugget Online Casino!
Right now, new players can deposit just 5 bucks and get 500 total spins on Huff and
Mortpuff, the slot that's blowing players away.
Download the Golden Nugget Online Casino app and use promo code Nugget1.
That's code Nugget1 to enjoy 50 spins a day for your first 10 days, all on our players'
favorite game of the summer.
Now's the time to score daily bonuses and spin for all the bacon on the game everyone's
hoffit about at Golden Nugget Online Casino.
Gambleing Problem Call 1 -800 -Gambleer, please play responsibly, 21 and over, physically
president Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia only, void an Ontario.
New customers only, nonwithdrawable casino spins issued as 50 spins per day for 10 days valid
for featured game only and expire each day after 24 hours, see terms at GoldenNuggetCasino .com
slashed promos ends at 11 .59 p .m. Eastern on August 31st, 2025.
The football season is full of guarantees.
And here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if your
football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
winning hits different here must be 21 plus gambling problem called winning 100
gambler offer not available in all states terms apply see fanatic sports book
app
Hello everybody and welcome to another episode of We'll See You in Hell. This week we'll
be reviewing Justice League. So I guess we'll get on with the show. And also on with
with a Joe what was that down with the sickness down with the sickness well I like that
quite a bit can we start a thing where every for the next couple episodes you do a thing
where you incorporate some old shitty pop song into the thing all but I'll try sure
I don't know why you think that was a shitty song did you did you like the down with the
Sickness absolutely not a terrible song. I will say I saw this disturbed yeah
Yeah, yeah, and I saw disturbed once at Osfest. Okay, was drowning pool on the bill
I think it was
I like that song
Yeah, that's a good song. That's good song. I think it was literally the year that guy died so they weren't there
Did he drown in a pool?
No, no, no, he drowned in a little pool. I call addiction, Pat. Oh, well, I think I think it was a drug. I think I don't even know if that's true
I've been known to dip my toe in those waters
What?
choppy water choppy choppy waters. I um
But I saw disturbed and I didn't like their music
But they did do a cover of land of confusion by Genesis and I thought that was pretty cool. Hey, that's one you hate that's huh?
Hey Genesis
Why I mean one of my early cassettes was the shit Genesis that I'm sure you don't like with the weekend
I can't dance on it. I can't dance. I got a curve ball straight here. I do like that album
No, no, it's not not a bad out, but I figured you like the prog shit which I admittedly have not heard
but actually the
Presidents foam masks in the video. Yeah, yeah, it's on sucks. You're nuts video sucks too well
Sort of garbage pale kid. No, you know, that was a TV show. That was a popular TV show back then called spitting image
Okay, and it was like puppets that looked like deformed versions of the
Celebrities. Yeah, and then like impersonators. They do sketches with the puppets
It was kind of a precursor to your cranky anchors kind of a thing sure. Uh, I actually prefer
You look at a guy like me and you say this man's a tastemaker. He probably let dope awards in my mouth
He probably, he, uh, he probably likes the early stuff, the Peter Gabriel, uh, I don't
know.
The Genesis of Genesis, if you would.
Yeah.
Sure.
There you go.
I, uh, I actually prefer the Phil Collins stuff and only the later Phil Collins stuff, you
prefer solo columns.
No, no, no.
The Phil Collins Genesis after Gabriel's gone and only the later portion of that, I prefer
for self -titled Genesis album forward.
All right.
I'll easily put solo columns over any Genesis.
Actually, Abacab forward.
You like solo columns?
Oh, come on.
Did you say you put it over a gen -
You haven't heard the right gen -
No, I haven't.
Abacab and like -
That's all and -
You mean, that's all.
Yeah.
Looking at you, you looking at him.
Yeah, that's a good song.
I would've thought that was solo columns.
No, that's right in the -
You're right in the sweet spot right there.
Oh, that's right around Sussudio.
Yeah.
Where it's interchangeable for one or two albums.
Susodio's Collins.
That's solo Collins.
Billy don't lose my number is solo Collins.
I consider easy love or one of the best songs of all time.
It at one point in my life, at one point in my life it was my favorite song that had ever
been written.
It's great.
And it's a great showcase for Philip Bailey who really steals the track.
Yeah.
I saw Phil Collins.
The second concert I ever saw was Phil Collins at the Civic Center or at the Spectrum.
and Philly, and he, uh, the whole first, it was two acts, it was shown two acts, whole first act.
Oh, Christ, it was terrible. It was just all his homeless ballads. That was the whole first act.
I mean, he wouldn't lay off of the shit. Another day for you and me and paradise.
I mean, I'm not joking, dude. It was a whole fucking first act of ballads.
And then the second act he came out swinging, Sussudio Billy, it'll lose my number.
got a black guy to come out of the wings to sing the Philip Bailey part for
Jesus' love. I don't think Philip Bailey from Earth Wind and Fire was just
sitting around in the wings waiting to go open and then come out and
don't attract again. I don't think they open. Yeah that's a great tune man.
Crazy drums too. If you heard, well he's a great drummer. Yeah but if you listen to
the just the drum track from that song like just the drums you cut out
everything else, it's out, they sound like fucking like heavy metal, it's only a heavy metal track.
I love that song. It's, it's amazing. So we had the one homeless, I actually really hate that
shit when super rich people do that, those balance. So like another day for you and me in paradise,
there's so much wrong with that song. So Phil Collins probably has a hundred million dollars minimum,
bare minimum. He's saying it's another day for you, Joe. And me, Phil Collins, in paradise.
as if we're on an equal plane.
So if you want to get us on an equal plane,
why don't you give $99 million to the homeless
and then throw me 500 grand?
Like what are you talking about?
Right.
Well, I think what his point is is
anything off these streets is paradise.
Yeah, I get it.
I just don't like the comparison it makes.
And I hope he donated a lot of money to the homeless
if he's gonna put that song out.
Something tells me he didn't.
Yeah, I mean, I've never heard of it.
I mean, I don't know, you know, but now the other one I hate especially once it gets to be Christmas
and I occasionally I'll throw on the Christmas station trying to jumpstart my heart with those
paddles kickstart my heart is motley crew. Yeah, that's that song's awesome. Kickstart my heart is one of the greatest songs ever
Yeah, and I hate motley crew, but that is an amazing song. I'm not a huge motley crew fam, but that song is awesome
and that song made the movie shoot him up look so good but I thought it was
too obscure to get into I saw that movie because it was in the trailer the
trailer used kickstart my heart in a beautiful way and the movie sucked terrible
movie GMOD couldn't say GM GMOD a children a man and they couldn't put together a
movie look kickstart my heart climb you need it climb oh that's right I don't know
what happened something happened something went bad he hasn't been in anything
Watchable in 10 years. He's another I love the Nick actually on stars. That was a great great show gone too soon
But Clive Owen and Gerard Butler. It's the same story. It's like what happened to you guys
You guys were supposed to be like the guys. Oh, one's way better than but
I
Well, I mean look but we're played the Phantom of the opera. You played
He okay good example, Joe
Well, I'll move back but when you put it back to back with the with the 300 guy that's like
It's a big it's that's a big difference. Yeah, but oh, one's like a good fucking actor. He's been great in many things
Oh, sir close. There's a great fucking movie and he steals that move
He is awesome in that he's disturbing in that fit. Yeah, love that move. Oh
Disturbing that's the key word for when we get to the movie corner
I have to because that's my remember to so I can remember what I watched should I scream for it like Puyi's
Playhouse when we get to the word disturbing. Yeah, yeah
Yeah, um, but what I was gonna say so I hate those sort of preachy songs from people that you know are probably not doing anything
And my least favorite for the Christmas season so you have to hear it a lot every year
I hated it when I was a kid up till now
Because he used to bum me out so much
So this is Christmas. Oh, yeah, and what have you done? What have what have you done?
That's how you're starting your Christmas song. Listen, I don't need more guilt. John Lennon
and can go fuck my dick in mid -air.
I fucking hate John Lennon.
I wrote one of my pen house articles
was about how world peace is like a,
it's just, it's fake.
It's not a thing that can ever exist
yet everybody goes, we need world peace.
And I shit all over that fucking give piece of chance.
Yeah.
Song.
And I was like, this fucking guy,
like he's so rich, his protest to war was,
I'm going to live in this like five star hotel with my wife right for a month. It's a golf fuck all your self
He sucks. My favorite songwriter, Elvis Costello
Has this great song
Called the other side of summer in the first love that's our first line is wasn't it a millionaire who said imagine no possessions
That's not the first line. It's a great line in that song. That's that is in his dark
Mark divorce alcoholic days and it's one of his worst albums but it's some of his nastiest
lyrics.
He had a bass player who wrote like a tell -all book about his time in the band and he
wrote this entire song that's a fuck you to this guy that like no one knows but him called
How To Be Dumb.
And it's like this guy wrote the book How To Be Dumb.
And that's also the movie, I mean the album where he looked like John Lennon.
He looked terrible.
He came up with the long hair and the glasses.
It might be like a rose, was the name of that record, a rose.
That's one of my least favorites, but the lyrics are like just so awfully mean.
And I like that, but the songs are like unlistenable.
Some of the other side of summer, that was the great song, yes.
That album was preceded by Spike.
Spike sucks too.
Spike's a terrible album, but Veronica is in the contender for my favorite Elvis Costello
song.
That's right.
As long as I'm the time to really get into Costello, but I mean the man's first four albums are unstoppable if you want a place to start and
Yeah, I could I could go much deeper with you on a huge fan of the man
Well, if we're not gonna celebrate Elvis Costello, let me celebrate somebody else go for our dear friend Karen kill
Gare if I talk to her today on the phone I care
Karen it's such nice things to say about the podcast and how much he loves when we bicker. Thanks Karen
And I told her it very meant very much to both of us to hear that.
And I said, where do you fall on the hog house argument?
I know Karen liked all of that.
And she immediately laughed and started, now I can't remember if she said she liked it or
not.
But I know she did like that it made you aggravate.
Sure.
Uh, so she gave me a suggestion for something new instead of hog house.
Let me hear it.
and she said, Pat might find this less offensive.
We're coming to you live from the house of thick, uncut dick.
And then she said, a lady voice would go, ooh, ooh, ooh, yeah, that's pretty good.
But then I said there should still be the Tim Allen pig noise after that.
Thick, uncut dick.
Oh boy.
It's way worse, I'll tell you that.
And I think we're going to see Karen Colgaraf's name and deadline for this harassment.
and frankly, talking to me about thick, uncut, dick, Jesus.
Just to call back to last week's episode,
and because I talked to Karen about a 10 year on the phone,
I said, you know, I don't know if you've heard this one yet
and she had, and I just want to share a nice memory
with you, Pat.
Okay.
I've never gone back and listened to our own episodes ever.
Right.
Ever.
Last week was the first and only time I've ever gone back.
And I didn't listen to the whole thing.
I just listened to the segment where we talked
about perfect strangers. And I said, I think that's the hardest I've ever laughed with my friend Pat.
I mean, we were when we told you the hatchet thing. The hatchet thing. Yeah. And you scraped that's
pathetic. And I remembered it so clearly. That's what that's why I was laugh. Like because it's such a
terrible like late and late in the run sitcom plot, I was loving it. But then like in mid laugh, I just
I saw it. I remembered the cliff. I remembered everything and it took me to a real nice place.
Anyway, speaking of nice places, how about we pop over to Pat's movie corner?
Are you aware of how buttery smooth the transitions on this show are?
buttery smooth. He has Joe to make a transition. It's like, oh, the next scary Joe stop.
I don't know why you have to come after me. Sorry, I'm not high all the time like you.
I'm not high. I mean, it remains. I can't tell the difference anymore. You're under the influence so
frequently. I can't tell the difference. Oh, come on. I'm kidding. Jesus Christ. I saw you taking
and sips out of your flask during the movie.
You got a problem.
Joe, I'd like our listeners to know
there is nothing in me but water.
Like, if you're gonna tell them every time we have a drink,
you don't also have to tell them we're drinking,
when we're not.
I know, I'm kidding.
I'm just making jokes.
Because you took that shot at me about the transitions.
No.
The about you transitioning.
Yes, about me, transist.
All right, go ahead.
What's the first movie you saw this week?
That's movie corner.
I saw a lot of films guys because we're heading into screener season and
First well, if actually the shape of water the new Guillermo did Guillermo the old. I already I did
But we could probably do that on the pod so I won't I won't go into it
We should that's and then we'll talk one. I look forward to reviewing all right. Well, if you want to see a woman fuck a fish
That's a good place to start either that or Joe's bedroom
room. Yeah, exactly. Are you the fish or you have the fish? Okay.
Yeah, I saw the disaster artist. James Franco's retelling of the making of the
room considered the worst movie of our time written by and nobody is
mentioning this. The guys who wrote 500 days of summer, which I thought was a
really great movie. I love that movie. And this is a really, really great script as
well and it's just this weird thing in Hollywood where like people will talk about
this movie has so much fucking hype I've never heard the writers mentioned once
and they're big writers I was like oh cool the writers the least respected man in
Hollywood I always say it no respect at all anyway the disaster artist I loved it
it's extremely funny and at times just because I have you know like people talk
about, you know, bitch about Christopher Guest for this too, there's an
air of mocking people that sometimes I don't love, right? I can't help
it feel bad for the person in question. But because the God, what
is the guy's name? Jesus Christ. James Franco. No, no, no, no, the
room. Seth Rogan, the guy, the room, the, the actor. Dave
Franco. Jesus Christ. I don't know. The actor in the movie, the
room. Katie Ducakis. I can't remember her name. His name. I don't know. Who cares?
All right. Well, anyway, he's such a outlandish and at times, hateable character that I didn't mind it,
but it's really funny. It's kind of got its own sort of weird vibe to it. Franco is very,
very good in it as he can be from time to time. Now, is it a strange sort of celebration of the
guys an endearing in a way where it's kind of like this guy had a dream and he went
for it and he did it.
Or is it?
I mean, they get there.
I'd imagine.
Yeah.
Tommy Wiseau is his name.
I looked it up and then remembered it, but it's very entertaining and like every single part
down to the tiniest part is filled by like some cool comedy person.
It's a good movie.
And there's a lengthy scene early on at, you're in my diner, the Astro diner right here
in at water. The Astro Diner. I love the Astro Diner. Yeah. All right. Well, that's pretty
cool. All right. Great. Well, I got to see that. I haven't seen it yet. Disturbing. Disturbing.
I saw the documentary Rocco. Rocco's modern life. Not quite. All right. I saw the documentary
Rocco about Rocco Sofretti, the very famous Italian porn star with Rocco Sofretti.
Where was it on Netflix?
It's on Netflix.
It's not an easy ride, people.
I thought this thing was going to kind of just be like
sort of a fun romp through the porn world of Europe
or whatever.
You know how many people have a fun romp
through the world of porn.
It is a deep, deep,
deep twisted tale of a man with a serious
sex addiction.
Many times in the film he does things I find
Questionable at best. Well, his pornography from my from my heavy viewing days of college and so forth
he
Was always like way more aggressive than I was necessarily comfortable with he's very aggressive
He tells a story at one point when his mom died and he's weeping about how his mom died when he was a teenager, I guess
And he said his mom's friend who was like 60
like is like comforting, comforting him.
Like 60 might even be too young.
Like she's just like an older, like older older.
And he said, does a story where he's like,
he's like, overcome, overcome with sexual density.
And I whipped my penis out, and I put it in our mouth,
and I come in three seconds,
and I run out because I feel terrible, I'm mortified.
You're like, he's just, he just tells him about assaulting a 65 -year -old lady, and he's
telling it just like, and it's weird because it's made by, it's made by Italian, I think
Italian filmmakers, at least European filmmakers.
So they've been very, as far as I can tell, very different approach to documentary.
They don't spin any part of it to be like, here's how you should feel.
They just kind of let it sit there on camera which made it more disturbing for me right to watch
It's a heavy flick, dude. He's got two kids. He's got a wife his wife has he's she gives him the total blessing to do porn
Do they as their pornography in the movie?
You see you see them shooting, but you don't see like insertion or anything like that. Don't
You see the opening shot is his dick is a close -up of his dick
literally, but there's a scene with his two sons where he's like, his one son is like,
I am very proud to call you my father. I love you. And he's like, starts crying. But
then his other son isn't saying anything. And he's like, you judge. I can tell you judge.
You don't like what daddy does. You know, it's an upsetting film. It sounds like every, every
Every part of it upset me, but it was interesting in a very morbid way to see what somebody
who makes that kind of cinema, I guess you could call it, for a living is actually
like off -camera, like what is this guy's thing and it's disturbing, but then he's got friends
that are feminists.
I was confused.
I didn't understand quite the thing with that guy who got into trouble.
the one -point star that was in that low -hand movie, it's the guy's name.
Oh, he's in it. James Dean. James Dean. He's in it. Yeah. I mean, he's got trouble.
He's clearly like an acolyte of his. Like, he's way too rough and it gets weird sometime.
And then these women started coming out and being like, yeah, some of that was not authorized.
And some of that was not on the menu. And sometimes he would choke me and it got too real.
Well, Rocco seems to do a very, and they show this throughout the film, a very intense interview before they shoot.
Right.
Where he'll be like, what is, what is okay?
And the girl go anything and he goes, what does this mean? Anything, anything.
So, I liked that he at least did that.
Sure.
But, again, you can't, it's hard to get past the 65 minute.
No, I'm not past it.
Yeah, it's, you can't really get past it.
It's a disturbing film.
I mean, it's, it's interesting. But again, it's morbidly interesting. Right. I saw three billboards
outside of Ebbing Missouri. I haven't seen it yet, but I heard it's very violent. Yeah, it's
pretty violent. Um, hell of a cast. Francis McDormand, Sam Rockwell, um, everybody in it is good.
what he Haroldson's awesome in it, the kid from Manchester by the sea, the funny kid,
like the kid kid, the main kid, whose Peter Hedges son, Peter Hedges author of my favorite
book, What's Eating Gilbert Grape, also a very good movie, of course.
That lady just died.
Who?
Tomorrow.
From Gilbert Grape.
Yes, that's correct.
That's very sad.
It's also has Max mom in it, the lady with the buzz cut.
You know a wonderful actress, Sam Rockwell's mom. She's a great guy. It's always Sonny and Philadelphia is
Yes, Mac his mom Sandy Sandy. I don't know her last year all the time and we had the same vet Neckopark
Okay, they'd see her in there and I was always too nervous to say you're Max mom. Oh, she would have loved that that kind of actor always loves it
Yeah, they don't get it very out. She's also the grand mom in Napoleon Dynamite. That's right. Yeah, but on the
Box it says for your consideration and it lists everyone on the entire cast except her
Including people with like two lines and she's has a sizable role as Rockwell's mom and is really great in it
And then I thought I found that offensive
some of these
Some of these I'm glad you brought it up because some of these for your considerations are it's a they're offensive
They really swing forward. They're offensive. Don't send me Logan as an Oscar screener
get the fuck out of my face. I know. You know, Hugh Jack. We got split as an Oscar screener. I'll take
that before Logan. I thought Logan was a better movie than split. You know, I get why they might
drum up something for that guy playing three roles. Exactly. Exactly. You know, I didn't think it was a
fantastic movie, but I liked it. The three billboards. It had the best trailer in five years.
like I couldn't wait to see it. And it's good. It's very entertaining. Martin McDonough,
the guy who did in Bruce, it also has Peter Dinklage. It has such so many big tonal swings and
misses. And like the whole movie is McDormand trying to get justice for her daughter who was
It's burned alive and while being burned alive was raped.
And she's putting up billboards in the town like how did they rape her while she was
burning her?
Like they they killed her then raped her then littered body on fire God Jesus Christ.
So she's putting on these billboards.
I want justice for my daughter.
Why don't you guys do anything for my daughter or whatever.
And in a movie like this, where where that is the setup, they also have scenes where Sam
Rockwell is like dancing like he did in Charlie's Angels while listening to Abba on headphones.
I love nothing more than Rockwell dancing in anything. He does it in a matchstick man.
I love when he dances. But it's not you see what my issue is here, Joe.
And then this is not the movie for dancing. No, and then like they're marketing the god damn thing
like a comedy. It's well, and I admire it what it kind of what it goes for. But for me,
the transitions were too much.
Then at one point somebody is like thrown out of a building
and like no one in the town cares or notices.
Like this is in the trailer, I'm not spoiling it.
I think McDormand goes, who threw that can at me?
And this 13 year old guy goes, I don't know.
She kicks him as hard as she can in the nuts.
Then the girl next to him goes, I don't know either.
And she kicks the girl as hard as she can in the vagina.
Then gets into her car and drives away.
And it's never mentioned again.
And you're supposed to be rooting for Francis McDormand as she's doing this to children.
Yeah, but it's also supposed to be like a grounded movie like
How am I supposed to take anything seriously in a movie where
Two children are kicked in the crutches
By a grown woman and you never hear about it again in a small town
And I also think they didn't need to make the the belding noise when the kid got kicked in the nuts
And a boy yo yo yo yoying. I mean come on
But McDormann is great, Rockwell is great.
Well, they're always great.
I've never seen that happy great.
And Harrelson is great.
But to go into the plot issues with the movie
would be to spoil it.
But I'm excited for you to see it
because there are moments in this movie that
if they had just been given another minute of thought,
you would have had a really great movie on your hand.
But there are so many moments that stretch credibility
and believability, that it took me out of it.
And I'm a guy who's always, when people
gripe about plot holes like ads and movie and joy it,
this one was a bridge too far for me.
It's a bridge too far.
Well, maybe those moments were in there
and it got ruined in editing.
You never know.
There's so many cooks with these goddamn things
and that's why everything gets ruined.
I saw a film, I got the Hammer Film Collection.
I was over at Old Fry's Electronics.
They had a hammer film DVD collection. It was two DVDs. It's about six movies.
And let me get over here. It's the line on the.
Now you're talking about the Adam's family, right? Starring MC Hammer.
Yeah. Well, you know what the Adam's grew. They do what they want to do when they say what they want to say.
Hammer films collection. This is a very cool collection you can pick up for very cheap.
Now wouldn't this be Joe scary stuff?
Well, I'm gonna talk about the movie I watched.
Okay, once you get off my back.
So that's got a bunch of movies on it.
Two faces of Dr. Jekyll, scream of fear,
the Gorgon, stop me before I kill, exclamation point.
I always like one of those old movies of the exclamation point.
And then Curse of the Mummy's Tomb.
I get to feel like, like, shouldn't there's list?
six dollars. But anyway, I watched the two faces of Dr.
Jekyll and man, I really enjoyed it. It starts Paul
Massey, who are immediately and Christopher Lee, who end
and also Dawn Adams. Oh, Adams. But anyway, I immediately
looked at what was that? You said Adams family. Dawn,
Oh, okay.
I immediately looked up Paul Massey,
because I was like, look at all the,
you know what I'm talking about, Adam's?
It was amazing.
And, you know, aside from some hammer films and stuff,
I couldn't really find much.
He, one of these guys that kind of eventually
went into teaching and lived a quiet life teaching
until he died, but was a,
but was a really tremendous actor,
but he plays Jekyll and Hyde,
and he plays it very differently.
The Jekyll character he plays,
like as disturbed with like a beard and like creepy looking and then when he
becomes hide he's very handsome and smooth so it's almost like a nutty
professor kind of deal but it's not funny obviously and he also plays hide with
this like shitting and eating grand on his face the whole time so he says these
horrible things to people because he's like so violent and hates people but it's
just like, I told you to go right now.
And he's got like a big smile on his face
and it's very creepy.
Just like a 70s picture.
1960.
Okay.
Really racy for a 1960 picture.
I mean, there is a lot of sexual talk in it.
They do say the words, they say bitch, they say whore.
I think they say shit at one point.
Okay.
It's pretty edgy for a film that old.
But anyway, you know what's hammer, man?
And it's it's it's it's classic old hammer stuff. It's you know, it's English horror. It's a lot of fun and I enjoyed it very much. It was released in the states under different title though. I think in the state it was called like jackals.
Jackals.
What's that called when you have all the balls swinging back and forth gauntlet summer at my place.
Hello, it's called an abacus I believe it was it was called like Jekyll's gauntlet or Jekyll's
mania or something you're describing is called an abacus. No the gauntlet they did in jackass too
when they're swinging the balls back and forth they run for it anyway I enjoyed it it's a nice classic
film all right for you to check out. I've seen a bunch more but I'll split them up I'll do one last
I'll do I'll do too quick. I saw call me by your name. What's that? The critically acclaimed
picture about a boy a young boy's homosexual awakening. Oh, that's the one James Woods got.
What's that the one James Woods got shit for? Yeah, that's what's got army hammer and right.
You know, it's like a I guess sort of like a love story between these two and it's a little weird.
the kid 17 and army hammers like you know 30 something they have this little like romance well
that's weird. Yeah but I kind of dug the movie it was it's very slow but it felt like you know
like a French romance it just happened to be a you know also kind of about child molestation and
everyone's talking about how erotic it is and I made a little uncomfortable by that talk
How ironic it is?
Erotic.
Oh, erotic it is.
I mean, there's, yeah, I mean, there's, there's, there's come, you know, there's some stuff.
There's come.
I just read that they had to digitally remove army hammers, nuts from some of the shots of
him when shorts, because his nuts were hanging out the shorts.
It's a very homoerotic picture.
Well, look, there's nothing wrong with homoerotic.
Child erotic is just, yeah, it's, it's all weird.
Yeah.
I mean, I'm not, it's all weird, but I like the movie and Michael Stulberg from a serious
man is great and Eddie has a justly acclaimed monologue at the end of it that Mike just
get him the Oscar.
Well, look, and I'll say this, you know, and I said, as I said about the Rocco picture being
disturbing.
Yeah, I am a believer that that if it's something presented as art is meant to be presented
as art.
It is what it is and it's meant to spark discussion and whatever.
So I'm not saying it's okay. I'm just saying these disturbing things exist within those
parameters
You know, so, you know, I'm sure both of these I'm sure that film will eventually be on Netflix as well. Yeah
What's the other quick one?
Molly's game
Which I don't think is out yet, but it's the new Aaron Sorkin movie that he wrote in his directorial debut
You also like wildly critically acclaimed, but it's about
the direct jobs.
No, that was a Danny Boyle and spotting.
Sorkin wrote it.
Correct.
There's nothing I'd want to see less than anything Sorkin wrote.
Well, this is road and directed so you can only imagine.
I always sort of admired his writing until I crossed the threshold
of being 18.
You know, I think he's kind of an embarrassing writer at this point.
and this movie, people are all over this movie's nuts.
It's about this woman, woman who held this top secret poker game
for your Tobin McGuire and DeCaprio and all these people,
and wound up getting into some trouble.
They got, you know, the IRS and the FBI and all this stuff.
And I'm probably, and I'm sure they don't show any of that.
It's just people talking about what happened.
That's exactly right.
It's fucking horrible.
So I'm like, I'm a real poker guy.
I love poker and there's only a movie about poker
like every three years.
And so I'm always excited.
and poker people are always really excited.
So, me and my friends were pumped to watch it.
There's no poker in it, A, because Sorka probably didn't even bother to learn the game.
Michael Sarah kind of plays an amalgam of all the famous people.
He's not really giving anything to do.
Kostner plays her dad, Jessica Chastain's dad.
He's boring as shit.
She's boring.
And they're giving all these giant passionate speeches about how she should be allowed to
run an illegal poker game.
So what he's what he doesn't understand is when you're doing these giant passionate speeches and the presidents doing them
And it's about the on the west wing right the world's going to war and stuff
Then you've got some fantastic television, right
But then when you try to do it on studio 60 and everyone's screaming in each other's faces about making a Saturday night live show
It's you start to look kind of fucking stupid and in this movie to still be doing these big speeches
I don't know. I'm not this angry about the movie by the way. I am. I haven't even seen it. I'm pissed off and to be honest
It was mildly entertaining, but like the way people are raving about this thing
It's just long speeches about things that are not important
Acted kind of squarely and kind of boring. He sucks. It's just where boring movie jobs the movie jobs with
Ashton Kutcher could yeah literally better. That's what I heard then Steve jobs. I only saw a job
And look, nothing against Ashton Kutcher, but you got to fuck something sideways because Ashton Kutcher's one
That was the one they kind of rushed out and it was like sort of had a little bit of a maid for TV movie
But it was like god damn it
It was entertaining to watch and I enjoyed watching him flip out and all that shit right that fucking
Sorkin one was was just people walking around backstage
Before they had moving it's terrible. Yeah, Sorkin's next movie is gonna be play
Yeah, Shorkin's next movie is gonna be him looking a camera explaining to you what the movie's about. Yeah, just him telling you a story
He just looks like the kind of guy where like you just don't want to be caught talking to him at a bar or something
You know, he looks awful
Which is no no reason to judge the man, but it comes across in his writing. It's just like
lecturing you endlessly and it's tiresome
All right, well Pat, I'm gonna round this out here. Go ahead
and I think you know what I'm gonna close this out with.
Sigmund, I call as of right now, PS, I love you.
Perfect strangers, I love you.
Just made that up.
Well, it's stickin' forever.
All right.
Perfect strangers, I'm still on season six.
I'm thoroughly working through season six.
Okay.
We're recording these episodes close enough together
that I'm not able to get a ton of episodes down in between.
But boy, oh boy.
Any high points?
I will say this, the relationship between Larry and Balky has become so tense, I'm going
to go ahead and say this, you know, you don't see it, but I believe in my heart, that
off camera, Larry beats Balky.
I believe that in my heart, because there are, because Larry beats Balky, because there are
There are many, many moments where Balky does something and then runs in fear, covering
his head.
Okay.
So, I believe the insinuation is, is that Larry is smacking him around.
Larry.
He said him once if that's happening, yeah.
Apple tin has become just a piece of living shit.
I mean, just, just, you know, I've said before, he's like the worst guy, just horrible,
just a horrible human being.
Okay.
the episode I'm gonna I'm gonna choose to highlight too quickly here. One episode was about
their his grandfather visiting. His grandfather's like I guess supposed to be like 80 or something
right and and he's like you know Balky we're just gonna have a quiet weekend with old pop -up or
whatever and he shows up and Balky's like you must be pop -up Apple tin or whatever and the old guy's
I was like, nope, from now on it's buzz, right?
Okay.
I just came back from a rock and roll cruise
that I've never felt better.
Who's portraying buzz?
I don't know the actor, but he's a real Lloyd Bridges type.
And then he's like, I gotta pump up my Reebok sneakers
because I'm gonna hit the town tonight.
You know, like sure.
It's this whole thing he's like got a second lease on life.
Right.
And then the whole episode's just Larry being like,
you have to act like an old person.
stop it. That's all that is Larry beating down the grandfather emotionally. Until the
point where the grandfather is walking around in a suit and he just goes, this is the
suit I want to be buried in. I'm just going to wear it until I kick out like it's, you
know, and then like, of course they have to get the guy acting young again and Larry, if
you can believe it Pat, learns a little lesson about himself in the end. That sticks for
or I can imagine 45 minutes until his next abomination
because every week he learns the lesson
and then every week he just does something terrible again.
Has Larry been responsible for anyone's death?
Well, no, but he is.
I've seen every episode by the way.
I wouldn't remember them all, but I've seen them.
Well, do you remember this one
because this is the one I really want to talk about.
Go on.
Larry has a cold and for the 86th time in the show's history,
Balky says, here's what you do to cure a cold cold on Mepos. Larry again swats him away.
You stupid fucking immigrant. Get out of my face. You know, like still doesn't believe him.
Even though Balky's cured him like a hundred times before. Right.
Balky gets this plant in the mail for Larry from Mepos that has peppers on it.
And if you eat a pepper, it cures the cold immediately. Let me guess. These hot spicy peppers.
They're not hot and spicy peppers, holy shit.
They're just peppers that you eat,
and it cures your cold.
Because Mipo's apparently also has plants
that have not been documented by science or anything on them.
You know, this was a magical island at this point.
Larry still doesn't believe that the thing cured him,
then gives the peppers to other people to be like,
just tell Balki it didn't cure your cold.
It cures their cold immediately.
Larry goes, we found the cure for the common cold.
old. We have to keep this plan alive. Balky's like, okay, but you have to respect it.
You have to let it grow gradually. You see where this is going. He's got a pitcher of
plant food, even though you're only supposed to give it two drops. For some reason, it makes
a giant beer hall pitcher of this plant food. And it says, you know, Larry, whatever you
do, don't overfeed the plant. Larry then tricks Balky into going to sleep. So he can then
poor all of the food into the plant overnight. The plant grows all over the entire apartment.
Okay. He then Jennifer comes down. She's sick. He gives her their living together.
No, no, no, you have so many worse episodes at the show. Yeah, I know. I know. When they
move into that house together, shit gets bleak. Like we're talking like me and my sister as little kids
like yikes. Where's the quality control? So I'm coming to the point, gives Jennifer the pepper
from the giant plant now. Yeah, we're going to be rich, bulky, typical stuff. You know how these
guys roll? Gamers. Dreamers. What do you think? What do you think happens? Take a wild guess.
I don't know. Do you think the pepper cures her?
or because it was overfed, does it give her a cold?
Well, Pat, I'll tell you this.
All right.
It actually cures her until she grows a mustache.
Oh no.
She goes a mustache.
And I don't mean like a little extra hair.
You thought that I would guess that?
She walks in.
No, of course not.
It's the point is it's terrible.
She walks in with a fucking Sam Elliott mustache and says like you better you better you you better get to explain and I fucking for I can't ever remember
It's nonsense at this point. That's that's really stupid. It's a it's pretty bad. It's pretty bad
And it's just because he overwatered it now it turns the peppers into mustache growers and I believe only in women
Oh man, women yeah, undocumented by science. All right, we've charted the entire globe. Yeah,
nobody's ever discovered this plate. Well, it sounds terrible. Yeah, watch one. I'll
save that one for next week. Oh man, a real bad one. I got nothing for scary stuff. Hit us.
Let's get on to Justice League. I were 42 minutes in. We haven't even gotten to the movie yet. I got
one thing for scary stuff. Look folks, there's a lot of controversy around Star Wars Battlefront
2 with the loot crates and all that stuff. If you don't want to know what I'm talking about,
look it up. I don't. It's a little too much for me to try to explain right now. But look,
basically here's the thing. The game was offering in -game purchases for these things called loot crates.
And what you could do is you could buy a loot crate for a certain amount of money and it would give
you items, weapons, whatever that would allow you to advance more quickly in the game so you could get
better at the multiplayer. People had a shit fit. EA just lost something like two billion
dollars in investors or something because there was so much backlash over this. Belgium
was going after them for legal reasons saying they were putting a legal gambling in games.
I don't understand any of that. It's just like any other crate service that you do.
There's a million of these crate things out there. They got them for clothes. They got them for
DVDs, they got them for Blu -rays, they got them for music, they got them for video games.
These are services.
And everyone says, well, it's a way to cheat, to get ahead, it's a way to pay, to get
ahead in the game.
Yeah.
Well, some of us don't have 27 -hour straight a day to sit in front of the fucking TV and become
experts at Star Wars Battlefront 2, which is mainly a multiplayer online game.
Some of us want to just enjoy the goddamn game.
So who gives a fuck?
Who cares if the guy you're playing against got better because he bought it or got better because he worked for it
It's still the same opponent who gives a shit and it's still the same
You know your experience doesn't change in any way exactly so so
Look I look the game is awesome. They took the Luke creates out of it
So I have not utilized them
I got it mainly for the campaign because I'm not a big multiplayer online guy the campaign is awesome
It is finally our next generation first person Star Wars shooter. It's fucking awesome. You're on the dark side
It's great. It's a blast. I'm loving the game. All right, so I highly recommend it.
And now on to the film Justice League which Pat I mean looked like he was going to
do all but spit on me during the during the show. I told him I saw it last night as
well, I saw two nights in a row. That blows my mind. Well, I wasn't dying to see it again.
I was just like, if you want to do it for the pot, I'll see it again. I mean, the best
thing about it was that it was under two hours. I mean, that's a, in this day and age, a
true blessing. Yeah. I suspect you liked it quite a bit more than I did, but I was very
bored by it. I couldn't track really any sort of story at all. I guess there was a bug
man trying to kill them. I mean, I had never seen Wonder Woman, so that meant nothing to me.
I was deeply bored throughout and I thought the dialogue was atrocious, embarrassing. I thought
the flash, I've always liked that actor before. I hated the flash. I guess he, I don't know if he
was autistic or gay or what he was supposed to be, but it was not working for me. Autistic or gay,
This is the comparison you go. I couldn't tell with the way he was playing it
Which I was supposed to think he was and then that one moment when
Aquaman comes up with his shirt off and he goes oh, I was like I guess that man
He was gay, but then he also got flustered when he talked to Wonder Woman
So I no he says well listen first of all folks
Pat's on his phone for half the goddamn thing way I was on my phone way less than you were during during the movie
I saw it already.
I knew the plot.
I wasn't on my phone much at all.
I glanced my email five times.
There were a couple times you were on the phone.
You missed major plot points, and then you turned to me
and you went, who was this guy?
And I was like, yeah, you were on your email.
I don't care.
If you're talking about cyborg.
Yes.
Blah, blah, and cyborg.
I didn't, I mean, I don't know.
I guess I didn't perhaps get his introduction,
But also I turned to Joe and said this is the most boring character in the history of film and I meant it
I like you said it to me and honestly I think the black community should be upset that that is the
Representation they get in this movie is literally for my money the most boring character
I've ever seen in a movie in my entire lot the guy delivered his lines in a monotone
He's a robot
You got to give me something more than that. I mean that that was a pathetic excuse for a character
Uh, I disagree. I've never been a huge cyborg fan. I liked him a lot in this movie. I found him interesting. I don't like that they had him say Boo yeah at the end. I thought they have him say Boo yeah at the end. That was absurd. Um, I thought he should have said.
Uh, this is when like all the, the everything is saved in the world together in the whole Justice League like unites and they cut to him and he goes, Boo yeah.
Yeah, I think he should have said,
whoop, there it is.
That's what I would have liked.
And then maybe they play the song
until we get to the secret scene,
which I would not see.
I, all right, now let's back up here.
This is a sensitive subject for me.
I liked the movie.
I didn't think it was fantastic.
Okay, I liked it.
I think Joss Whedon's fingerprints,
where they were in this movie,
were very obvious. What were some of those lines? Like a couple that I looked at you at. Do you
even remember what they were? Well, that fucking news clip where the lady's like,
my this alien took my fucking man. I'll shove a thing up as fucking ass. Why was that in the movie,
Joe? I don't because because everything that I'm going to say, something very controversial right now,
everything Zack Snyder in this movie was great. It was all very well done. You can tell the
Zack Snyder parts you can tell like the whole opening sequence with Batman was fucking cool and it felt very like watch
Man -ish and like it was dark and it was shot cool and it was fun
I thought all the action was just incredibly weak. I like the action. I liked watching step -and -wolf beat the shit out of horses
And I thought that was fun. I thought that was like you hate horses. I'd always have horse killed my father in the war
Yeah, his it was the war horse actually the uh no, but I I just I think um I
Thought the Zack Snyder stuff was obvious and then he had to exit the film because his
tragically daughter I think committed suicide
Yeah, and they brought in Joss Whedon to sort of do patch -up work and then so then that makes the movie disjointed because now
There's all this fucking comedy bullshit in it. Yeah, and and and it comes in like halfway through the movie
It's this like folks. It's embarrassing. It's embarrassing stuff. It's this like very like
slick sort of dark graphic novel DC vibe kind of thing that everybody hates because everything
has to be a fucking comedy now. And then all of a sudden there's like slapstick shit. Now the thing
with the flashes, I didn't mind the way the flash was written and I liked Ezra Miller. I thought he was
good. Because that is how the flash is a lot of the in the comics. The flash is kind of a smart
a hard -assy guy and he's kind of awkward and so I liked that they finally did a portrayal
of the flash like that.
I liked it.
I thought Aquaman's stunk.
Aquaman at least had a little charisma, I guess, I mean.
Well I thought Ezra had charisma, I just thought like, it was getting taken away from him
because his lines were bad.
His lines weren't great, but I also think too it's this look, it's the symptom of these
movies.
the everything now nothing is amusing anymore because everything Marvel made everything to a fucking comedy right now
I will say this and this is all I asked from you wash. So I asked from you
Do you think that this movie?
deserved a
44 % from critics and Thore Ragnarok deserved a 93 % from critics
Absolutely not, and honestly, I sort of hated them both equally. I didn't think I
one was particularly any better. Are you really hot or something? I'm very hot.
Look, you're having hot flashes. I am having hot flashes.
Weaving your face. It's very temperate in here. I'm also dressed as Mrs. Doubtfire.
I want to quickly clarify what I said in case anybody was offended, but like what I'm saying is when
we first are introduced to the flash. He does this whole monologue that might as well
be the Parsons from the Big Bang theory, where he's like, I'm quirky, I'm, I, right.
And I thought that was him being, I thought he was autistic. I thought the character was
autistic. No. And then unless I'm reading too much into this moment, I thought they cut
over to him when Aquaman is shirtless and he was like, oh, so I'm not saying that autistic
gay or equatable or I don't you know of course none of that I'm saying I think
that's exactly what the character was so inconsistent that I didn't know what he
was supposed to be I he was I look maybe he's both I don't fucking know I but my
interpretation of that character was because he says the Bruce Wayne like I need
friends on people are too slow I can't yeah he's he's I think he's like a super
genius and he doesn't know how to talk to people and he's awkward so like when he
He lands when he saves Wonder Woman and he's like laying on top of her and is like heads
on her boob for a second and then he jumps up and he's awkward.
He's just like, oh God, sorry, sorry, sorry, you know, like he's just not how to act.
You know, look, it wasn't, it wasn't a fantastic film.
It was 27 ,000 times better than Suicide Squad.
Hey, I can't argue that, but I also did not finish Suicide Squad.
It was better.
I would say it was better than Man of Steel.
I still really like Batman Superman. As you all know, we won't go down that road in the
bait. But, um, but you know, I like stepping off a lot as the villain. I don't see why he
had to be CGI. I don't get that. It didn't. There was no need for that. He could have just
been there were there were ways because I kept thinking of was Tim Curry and legend. And
I was like that was done without any computer. Right. Well, they didn't have it back then.
And I believed that that character was nine feet tall, and real, and I thought they
could have done that with Steppenwolf, but instead they made him computer generated,
and they made him look less like Steppenwolf looks in the comics, which I didn't understand
what the motivation there was, like shit.
And people really liked the Aflex portrayal of Batman, and Batman was a Superman.
I thought he was terrible in this.
I loved him in this. He's my favorite Batman still. Oh my god. Well, what?
Who are you putting above Aflick?
You're gonna say Keaton because that's what everybody always says putting a million miles above Aflick Keaton stop and
I mean I might go ahead and put
Well, I certainly put bail above him. I love bail, but I like I didn't hate Kilmer. Oh
Shut up Pat. I mean Clooney sucked Kilmer. Affleck and his scenes where he's talking to Wonder Woman when they're not in their costumes. I was like
Boy, this guy's been fooling us for a really long time. He is a bad actor, man
I don't I liked him in in comedies and then everything else. I'm like, what are you doing? He didn't like him in the the town?
The town he can stumble into it and good little hunting. Yeah, you know like he's got a thin line he can walk
I think he's a great Batman, he's not going to play a normal person.
I don't think Batman is a normal person. That's why I like him as Batman.
I think he plays it with a darkness. I like that they hint that he's an alcoholic.
I didn't even seem to drink in this movie.
There's this this the scenery pours the giant glass of whiskey
when he's like making up with Wonder Woman and then look that giant, man.
It looked delicious.
Yes, but they make a remark in Batman Superman like that.
He's constantly drinking wine.
They show a scene where he's waking up with a woman
and she's still asleep and he like immediately
takes a squig of wine.
I like the darkness of it.
I really like Jeremy Irons as Alfred.
And I also, I'll say this too.
I liked Danny Elfman's callbacks
to the John Williams Superman theme
and to his own Batman theme
Because I felt like it gave the Warner Brothers universe a little more continuity on film that's seen where the bank robbers are going in
Or not the bank robbers, but the terrorists are going into the bank of the beginning and it's playing that like crazy Danny
Elfman piano music. It's like yeah, that I feel like I was watching like a Tim Burton Batman movie again, you know, and it was fun, but it was like it's just
DC's just got to stick to something man
I like they're they keep people keep exiting and entering and then they're going back
and they're reshooting and whatever.
DC has to tell everybody that's saying
their movie suck for being dark to go fuck themselves
because their movies are still making money
and now people didn't like this one as much.
Peter Travers, that little fucking shit.
No worse movie critic in America.
I mean, he trashed it for having too many jokes.
It's like you fucking suck every Marvel movie's dick.
He is the worst movie critic in America.
Yeah, and he writes just to get quoted in trailers.
I hate him.
Yeah, he sucks. I mean, he's up there with Sandy Kenya for me
Sandy Kenning's a better film credit than Peter Trevor
Sandy can you Trevor's like have a review. This is rolling stone like it's a big deal that are used to be a big deal
Now it's a shit magazine, but he's like for 20 years now. He's been like give me a movie
Thanks for yes, Andy the departed the departed. I mean he'll he'll say like things like
a whiz -bang action -packed thrill ride.
You're like, Peter, you're supposed to be a serious film critic.
He just wants to put that in the chair
so we can see his name.
He's a whore.
I was a much better film critic
when I used to review movies.
I really was.
I had great reviews.
And I urge you all to Google the Trevor's Walsh beef
of 2006.
Well, there's no, and actually you won't find any of my reviews
because they took the site down, unfortunately.
it was heated. Anyway, my final say on Justice League. Pretty good. Not amazing. I don't think I'll buy it,
but I thought it was still a step in the right direction for the DC Cinematic Universe.
And I think it's a shame that their Affleck is now talking about exiting and
you know, and people are saying that this wasn't as good as Wonder Woman. I mean, there's just so much
Feel bad for DC. I don't know why everybody's fucking hating on him so much. I mean Jesus Christ, man
I'm sure DC will be fine Joe. Yeah, I hope I thought the film was bad and I thought I was boring
And I don't really have much more to say than that
Joe it's been it's been a lovely evening. I don't like it. I like that we're seeing movies together now
Yeah, we didn't use to for a while
Well, you're busy. You're running a TV show and I'm staring into the abyss
James Cameron's the abyss. I thought you want a fan. Oh, I'm not but that's my favorite line and how the Grinch stole Christmas
when he's going over his schedule
when Jim Carrey's going over his schedule and he goes
He goes one p .m. Starran to the abyss
Very funny. Do you like
That movie I never saw it. I only saw that part and it may be laugh really hard
Then I tried to watch it and the second they were like let's show you the backstory of the great
Yeah, no, it's a very bad move wanted to spit on the television. It's a very bad move. Yeah, it's better than the cat in the hat, though. Yeah, yeah, um, folks, thank you for your time. I am on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh. And I think you're actually getting pretty close to win my show will premiere. I think it will be in the early next year, living publicly. Look for it. Joe, Joe to row.
a comedy on Instagram and Twitter and read the penthouse column, if you can. I mean, I know you
need to go to pay money to read it. God forbid. But you let me down my op ed monthly in the penthouse
and, you know, there's some other shit coming along soon somewhere. I'm sure at some point. Oh,
and thank you to all the Patreoners. Thank you very much Patreoners. See you next week.
That was a HitDum podcast.