Summer is here, and Bed MGM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MGM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Bet MGM Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal -durable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
Gambling problem? Call 1 -800 -Gambleer.
Howdy folks, it's another episode of We'll See You In Hell, your favorite podcast for
horror movie sci -fi and fantasy film, commentary, reviews, discussions, and such today what's
on the palette. Well, I'm going to tell you guys what's on the palette or the docket
or whatever the fucking expression is. We're going to be reviewing Helen Mirren's Winchester
her. Today. Winchester. I barely knew her. I certainly didn't win chest hurt. And
that's my dear friend and partner, Patrick Walsh. Hello folks. Yeah, we are going to
talk to you about Winchester. Joe and I for the first time, dialed it up in Sin City together
lost Vegas, Nevada. I went out, I saw him open for Bobby Slayton. Yes. I tell you folks,
this was a tense evening of comedy. Bobby Slayton's whole thing is, you know, he plays it like it's
1975. He's going after minorities, he's going after sexualities, he's going after ladies. And
Uh, Joe's Joe kind of went the same way.
Oh, I did not, I'm not, it's not a, it's not a criticism.
You, you played to the room, but uh, it was, uh, at what point did I go after minorities
on stage?
Yeah.
I, I, but just in fairness, Bobby's a dear friend, just what Pat is saying is he's an insult
comic.
He's an insult, which, which in this state, we all wonder in this day and age, how would
a Joan Rivers or a Don Rickles go over?
But like he's sure.
He's very much in that vein.
And he's the sweetest guy on planet Earth.
Yes, in this day and age, you know, it was, uh, it was tense at the Joe, um, you
know, and Bobby Sladen just, they did material you, I don't personally think you would
see in LA.
I've done it here.
And, uh, you know, there were some jaws on the floor.
There was a, uh, some heckling.
There was, uh, a tense couple of minutes where Joe was like, what'd you say to me?
What'd you say to me?
It was a wild show.
Well, I got heckled over the homeless joke, which I've done many times in LA.
That was a fairly innocent joke.
Yeah.
I said I was like, but I, I, yeah, I like it's stricken from the record.
You're on it.
I did not go after minorities and gender you're taking this to person.
I'm just saying it was a, it's a, it's a Vegas showroom.
Anything goes.
I mean, it is a self point casino, which was a real trip.
It was a fun way off the strip.
It was a fun night of club, clubby comedy, you know what I mean, it was fun.
It was very fun and it was a good time.
I was happy you were there.
The next night the crowd was much looser and it was more fun and it was just more like
everybody's kind of enjoying themselves.
But this is the thing as a stand -up that does the road.
When you start getting pushback at all, your knee jerk is, well now I want to be worse.
Right. So I think that was happening with every comic that night where it was kind of like,
well, if you guys are going to be fucking assholes about tamer jokes, we'll then fuck off, you know.
Yeah. I mean, my only point is that it was just kind of like a show I hadn't seen in a while.
It was a fun point. I get your point. You want to talk down. You want to say, I'm better than you.
Hey, look at me, everybody. Look at my big dick. Some people are woke.
Some people are still fucking asleep and I'm just drink to Mr. Joe Rose. I don't care.
For your cis perspective, we did some gambling. It was cool to meet like, you know, some,
some of Joe's fans who are just the drugs of society. All right. Can you stop with this?
No, I'm kidding. That guy we gamble with, you know, he was betting 10 grand on the Super Bowl.
And he won. Yeah, he won. That guy was awesome. That guy was one of my favorite
guys he's in. He was coming from Florida. I could have party with him all weekend. I assumed he
had some. I saw him the next day. Yeah. He, uh, because we were. Okay. So, so basically Pat and I
were going to go see sticks with my man with my agent, TJ. I didn't even know if I knew sticks,
but I knew some sticks. I knew some sticks. And I turned to Pat halfway through. We were going into
the show like, even my agent when he gave us the tickets was like, yeah, you guys probably don't want
come to this, but we were like, let's go. Let's go. We're in Vegas. I'm glad we did.
I didn't know if I was going to like it. Halfway to the show I turned to Walsh. I go, I think I love
sticks. As you said, yeah. It was great. But with the night before, we were doing it.
That song is so awesome. Yeah. The night before playing Blackjack with a guy that was at the show
Yeah, who was the nicest dude in the world very cool, but did in in all fairness looked like a look you look
Like you'd be like the bag man in a in a heist movie or so I loved it. Yeah, but we were debating on if renegade was a stick song or not
And nobody knew but Pat and this guy said that they thought it was I was I
bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp bomp b
It's something out of my head.
We were saying it all night.
It sticks.
We were singing it all night.
Yeah.
And so that was funny.
And then also when I was driving home on Sunday, because Slayton gave me shit the entire
week at about going to see sticks.
Right.
He's like, oh Christ, they suck.
Yeah.
You know, like he just wouldn't let off.
Right.
So then I was driving home and he called me and while I was driving back from Vegas and I
answered the phone and he just goes, lady.
Oh god, they fucking suck. Yeah, how horrible was it? I go I was actually great
I was like I think you would have liked it man. Well, they didn't play a lady unless we missed it
It was one of the three songs we missed. They did which I'm
What a fucking song that is it was a lot of fun, but this dude
This is how little I care about football, but you know, he said he's in town for the super big man guy
Yeah, he goes my wife's passed out on edibles upstairs
He goes, uh, but I'm dropping 10 grand.
Betten on, uh, Philadelphia.
And I was like, good luck, man.
And when they won, I was over at the cosopalton washing the Super Bowl at a little
Super Bowl party, but genuinely not giving a shit.
And everybody's cheering and all I could do was think, that dude just probably made
himself a nice chunk of change.
I'm happy with what do you think he won?
Just 10 grand or do you think he won like 30 grand or something?
I don't know how that worked.
No, I mean, there's odds and stuff, but you wind up, they take a cut like you, you have to, I don't know, you, you wind up winning maybe
If that's right, I wish I had bet fucking 10 gram, but I think if you bet a hundred and they win you get back like
80 or something. Okay, so you probably walked to the grand, but there was some sort of point spread and I, I have such a
a gambling bug in my brain that I never even got into sports betting because I'm like,
if you don't even know what sports are about, why would you ever do this? So I don't
want to learn the rules. It's why I won't learn craps. I don't need more vices. I do my
black check. I do my video poker. I love to gamble. And I got to tell you something, folks.
I walked into the casino. They said, sir, we have a craps table. I said, no, thanks. I'll
folks. Yeah, it's interesting. I said, uh, hey, where in the casino is your most risky gambling?
And they said, uh, well, the buffet is right over there. Folks, folks,
going, I did eat at the South Point buffet. Uh, I stuck to the fruit largely and fruit
and meatballs is what I had. But, uh, barbecue meatballs. Don't leave that, don't leave that detail
out. But it comes back with these meatballs. They're covered in a red sauce that was not
marinara. They were barbecue meatballs. Yeah. Look, it wasn't the nicest place, but
I had a nice time. I had fun. I like the South Point, because it's got that sort of
old downtowny Vegas Atlantic city kind of vibe. But I also like the Cosmo. We were up at the
Cosmo. You had a fernite, and it's flashy, and it's fun, and it's cool, and you feel cool
be in there, but it's a little out of my league, you know, it's their minimum bet table
is like 25 bucks. I can't, I just can't. I got a, I'm a low stakes guy. I'm a low stakes guy.
And Pat saw, we gambled side by side many times that weekend. My luck sucks. Yeah, you just
saw what I was getting dealt. I just, I'm just not, I just have bad luck with it. And as
You saw, after a lifetime of terrible luck, I can't lose at the end of it.
I, something snapped in me and it was the kind of thing where -
Just take sure to, uh, an arrow coming through the -
Oh, of course.
You always say that in the -
In your head.
You're something happens.
But, uh, I mean, it was the kind of weekend where like, I'm at the south point, I sit down,
I beat Joe there, and I texted him like, I'm just sitting down, I'm here, and I immediately
get a royal flush.
I don't even want to tell you how much I want.
But it was sick. I got to be honest. I don't care to hear again. I know because it made me sick there
But then it wasn't that one so much. I swear to God. This is true
And I said this to Kurt Bronno or the other day. Yeah, Pat won so much money in Vegas
I honestly contemplated saying to him just give me a thousand dollars
What does it matter? I gotta tell you give me a thousand that is how people
Treat you when you're winning money and I've got a story about that
But it was the kind of night and this is what happens when I go to Vegas
I was walking up to bed me and Joe and Joe goes in to buy some you know, Lou or something at the gift shop and
While I'm waiting for him because I'm a compulsive gambler. I sit down to put $20 in this slot machine
I don't even like playing slots and while I'm waiting for Joe. I push the button. I
Win 86 dollars. I don't even know what I did and I just cashed out and was like that's just an additional
66 dollars. I just won before going to bed forgot six, but anyway, here's a here's a little story about
About society. It's a story with a larger point to make
So Joe went home Sunday morning and I stayed a couple extra days at the Cosmo. I went to the Super Bowl party and I gambled
Having a nice time and I go over to plan in Hollywood. It's a little more fun a little more vibrant and
I'm gambling and I win a jackpot. I'm sorry folks
of $3 ,010 and I'm like whoa excited I'm sitting there I'm waiting for them to bring me out the money
they bring you out and hand you the cash right this woman comes and sits next to me I she's she
looks like she's in between having a home and being homeless right and sure enough that's exactly
what the case was and she's like how will you she goes that I'm having the worst luck you know I'm
36 years old how old are you like yeah same age right she was boy we're in two different places
I mean I just moved out here from Staten Island I my boy from was supposed to meet me and then he dumped me
I got no place to live I got this was a this was a Neil Simon character. Yeah, exactly. Okay, I got the you know three kids back home
You know, obviously you know one of them one of them's 21. I'm like okay, you're 36. All right
But she's got no money to send me and you know, then
nobody to send me they could to still be college roommates for Christchurch talking about back to school
She goes my mom, you know, she she's a laid -up and sick and she's got no money to send me and I
I'm substranded out here and the details of the story are
Not quite adding up, you know, I'm like, why did you move to Vegas without having a home, but now something's up here
We're talking and the frustrating thing is when you win a nice size jackpot like that
They intentionally take forever bringing it out in the hopes that you will lose it because you're you're on the high of winning
So I'm sitting there at for 20 minutes
This woman is bitching about her life to me and it didn't have the feeling of sadness because I felt like a hustle to me
But I'm like, okay, that's that's really bad and I'm saying like look I wish you the best
I'm so sorry. I'm hoping for you. She was I got to tell you I mean like you right here you got
$3 ,000. I mean that if you gave me just you know 300 of you know that that's my that's my first
dinner in a week and a plane ticket home. You know I can get a plane ticket home for 250. So you'd
really be doing me a favor with that 300. And I'm like so we're just skipping right but beyond like
Hey, could I have a little money?
She's waiting for me to offer it to her.
We're asking for a specific large dollar amount,
but you could tell in her mind she's like,
what do you need it for?
You just got $3 ,000.
I want it!
I gamble, and I want, that's what you're supposed to do.
Do I donate it to charity each year?
I absolutely do.
Am I gonna hand it to this woman?
I don't know, I don't think so.
I don't think, no, in all fairness,
I don't think throwing a $20 chip in a homeless man's face
outside of the casino counts as donating to charity.
He appreciated it and then also it doesn't help that you say get a job as you do it wiped wiped it through the crack of my ass
But no, I'm talking I'm talking to this woman and I'm I'm saying the just nice sweet things to her and I'm I'm honestly wondering where it's gonna
Go because in Vegas a lot of times you're talking to someone and the other the other hammer drops. I'm a prostitute
I'm this I'm that and I'm like, where's this going? And finally, she says to me like, I just you could really change my life here
You could really you could save my life
She's trying to like look me in the eyes and I'm not looking around the eye and I'm essentially whistling
I pretend to get a phone call I stand up. So I'm like, hey, yeah, I'll be over there in a little bit
You don't know okay doing the whole bit completely made up phone call
Because I'm still waiting for them to bring out my money. Then I'm gonna be sitting next to this woman with three grand in my pocket
Who's basically like she said to me at one point?
I mean, I'm not somebody who's gonna steal, you know
I don't ever want to be somebody who steals she's drinking an extra large like 44 ounce Starbucks iced coffee
This is their cooler that they shut over. There's something going on. It's their cooler. They come out
They hand me the money. They want to give it to you all on hundreds
they do I'm putting it into my wallet and then at the end I said hey could I get
20s for this hundred whatever I said they hand it to me I give the woman 20
dollars sitting there for a minute and she goes oh so it's just just gonna be a
20 I love that wow that's that's that's that's guts this is a complete stranger
that I am handing $20.
Right.
Who honestly, I think is just bullshitting me, frankly.
Of course, yeah.
But, and, you know, I was like,
Let the sad state of the world we're in.
You have to window shop homeless people at this point,
because there's so many people
that are taking advantage of it's disgusting.
It's a horrible reality we live in.
I give her the $20, she's seeming like very disappointed
and she walks a little bit away, kind of looks back at me.
gets out the cell phone and is talking on her cell phone with this giant star
box. I'm like, is somebody gonna slip my fucking throat now? This is where Vegas
it always takes a turn. This is like 4 p .m. like on a beautiful day, you know, like
there's always this weird element there that's just uncomfortable. So she walks
away and I'm sitting there and I'm excited with my three ground. I'm like I need
to get out of here and they go, oh shoot we didn't bring you your W2. They have to
hand you a W -2. They go back to get it. Swimma comes up, she goes, can I get you a drink?
Bar tender there. The drinks are free in Vegas if you're gambling and you tip them all
a dollar. This is what everyone knows. Dollar a drink. It's standard if you're a billionaire
or poor. You have to tip them a dollar. It's a free drink. Sure, yeah. This lady comes
over, big sassy broad. She goes, can I get you anything, honey? And I go, no, I'm good.
And I go, you know what?
I got another weight while they go up to get my form.
Sure, I said, I'll have a Vodka soda.
She goes, okay.
Comes back with it, she goes, oh look at you.
You won't, it's still flashing.
Hey everybody, this guy just won 3000 cash.
She was, look at you, big winner here, big winner.
And I go, yeah, then I hand her the 20.
And I said, can I get changed, please, to tip you?
She goes, puts her head so far away from me like she's gonna puke.
She goes, you just won $3 ,000 and you need change for the tip?
Well, were you gonna tip her just out of curiosity?
Five.
Yeah.
But I mean, I'm just sort of like staring at her and I go, well, yeah, I said, I have hundred.
I go I I this is what I have is a 20 just you can't just give me the 20 you just won three grand
I
Go you know what lady take take the 20
She puts it in her pocket and walks away
Hands during shake in the head then she comes over and she's like you get sweetie. You need another one?
I go no, I'm fine. Well, I'm like I'm getting shook fucking down here
Well, I don't know I don't know who I agree with in this the first one I agree with you the second one
and I have to tip a waitress $20 for a drink
that she walks a foot away to get and hands me.
Simply because I won money?
All right, fair enough.
It's insane to me.
Fair enough.
I mean, I'm not a cheap man.
I am a very good tipper.
I go over 20%.
But everyone knows the arrangement is a dollar.
Me winning doesn't mean everyone around me.
It's a gross.
It's a gross town and it's filled with hustlers
and people that are looking for breaks
whatever it is, you know, you're gonna encounter that a little bit.
In both cases, I gave complete strangers who did essentially nothing for me, $20 cash
and in both cases, they treated me like I was an asshole.
Well, that's shitty.
I mean, I don't even know what to say here.
That's shitty.
I'm not in the wrong in that scenario.
I think you've said enough right now.
And if I had a hundred in my pocket and I ask her for changes, that the same scenario?
I don't know.
It's a weird town.
It's a dirty, weird town.
It's a dirty, weird town, you know, it's, it's, you know, dirty,
weird town, it's the Pope.
I don't mean to rush us along here, but we've got a couple segments we need to get
to and the first hour to the first I'd like to drop and I'm rearranging things a
little bit. But I'd like us per your suggestion in my total agreement. We need to do a very
special crane shots today. A very special crane shots. And I wish we were playing a mournful
organ toss salad and scrambled eggs behind us as we talk. But the great John Mahoney has passed
to played Martin Crane on Frazier, the dad. And I am literally still sad. I got this news about a
week ago by the time this comes out, it'll be a few weeks, I think, but I'm very sad about that.
I was too. He's the heart and soul of the show. I just today finished season one,
which I know it gets better from there, but it was entertaining, of course.
You know, Frazier Tweet, everything about him. I was almost emotional. Frazier's
our Kelsey grammar tweets, he was my dad.
I loved him.
Yeah.
Yeah, I know.
And then everybody had a great story to talk about that.
Perry Gilpin tweeted the picture of him singing
at her wedding and you're like,
Jesus Christ, it's so sad.
It was very sad.
I mean, he lived the full life,
but the other day, almost that he died,
act like he went into hospice like,
he was about to open in a play.
That was crazy.
he was just an awesome actor, some movie performances I could call out. He's really great in
Moonstruck as the flandering husband. Everybody kept saying say anything. I didn't. He's awesome
and say anything. Who is he and say anything? He is the girl's dad who the whole movie, this
like sweet romantic comedy. He's like kind of the tough ass dad. And then in the third act, it is
revealed that he has been ripping off the senior citizens at the old folks home he runs
and taking their money.
And he's got like a scene where he's like, you know, taking a leave in Las Vegas shower
like sitting in his clothes in the bathtub crying.
It's an amazing performance in a one of my all time favorite romantic comedies.
I love him in Barton Fink.
He is awesome in Barton Fink.
He was good in everything he ever did.
He was a great actor and you know the fact that he's best known for Martin Crane, I'm
sure he'd be happy about that because it's a whole other character.
I agree and I will keep this crane shot brief with my favorite reminiscing about my favorite
Martin Crane scenario that I've ever seen on the show which was when Frazier and Niles
discovery shoebox that's Martin's and he won't tell them what's in it and then
they find out what's in it is there's the there's songs that he wrote for
Frank Sinatra throughout his life and he's like at stupid I don't want to you
know and they're like dad let's put one to music and I think the song is called
like she's a groovy. She's a groovy. That's the one he wants to do more and the lyrics are absurd.
It's just like she makes my heart go babby booby. Ridiculous but the funniest part and the whole
thing is him trying to instruct Niles what to do like or catch really with the piano like how the
music supposed to go and like Niles will like play this these chords and he's like no not like that
It's got to go swabby, beep, beep, beep, boom, swag.
It's a very, very funny.
I'm excited to get to it.
I'm a Sinatra fan and I that was a very, very funny joke.
And then there's there's one line he has in another episode where they're in a
breakfast buffet.
And he comes back with his plate and he goes, he goes, look,
phrase pigs in a blanket on an omelette pillow.
Oh, and oh look, it's snowed cheese.
All right, all right.
Marty Crane, Reston Peace, we'll miss you Mahoney.
John Mahoney.
Fantastic actor.
Into Pat's movie corner.
I've got nothing for it.
Oh yeah, I mean, I'll keep it brief.
I saw a couple things.
All right, here's the deal, so my good friend Brett, we're going to see a picture and we're
We're at the, we're meet up at the Cheesecake over at the Glendale.
Uh, uh, for my first meal of solid food in 10 days, I had the salad because you were
doing the fast, right, or the cleanse, excuse me, and we're looking through these titles
and I'm like, we might just have to pack it in unless we want to see something for a second
time.
There was nothing to say.
I remember the day you went.
I was like, there's, what are you going to go see?
There's nothing to play.
We're about to see Paddington too, which people have been raving about and we're like, we're
two grown men. I mean, we can't do this. And Brett goes, look, you're going to make
fun of me. But my favorite movie, perhaps of the year, was Hugh Jackman, the greatest
showman. Oh, my God. A musical about PT Barnum. Right. I laughed. But, you know, I have
similar taste to this guy. I'm like, really, it's good. He goes, it's really good. I don't
hate the occasional musical. I think there's there's been almost no good ones in recent years
but I'm like well trust you on it. I didn't even consider that an option but let's go.
This thing's been critically panned. You know it didn't even do well. Money wise.
I didn't even know Michelle Williams was in it. She's the lead in it with him.
I didn't know that. I sit down on this thing. The opening number starts up.
I got both elbows on my knees, enchanted, leaning into the screen, riveted.
And there were people there who were clearly seeing it for their 20th time.
Really?
You know, like singing the songs and shit.
I thought it was great, and it is such a testament to how like critics can just immediately
just shit on something and then you just never think of it again.
I mean, it's so good, and especially if a critics job, it's supposed to be evaluating something within its genre.
If you're evaluating this thing as a modern -day musical, it's the best one in 15 years.
Well, now I want to see it.
It's extremely entertaining, and the songs are great.
It's the same guys who wrote the music for La La Land, which I don't think was the strongest part of that movie,
But these are good songs and then also you're getting like lavish dancing musical numbers by circus freaks
Bearded lady. All right. Love that all right, and they have their whole story of like their
Complete outcast in the town. Yeah, he's like come on come do this for me
And they're like you're just gonna exploit us and laugh at us
Which is of course what PT Barnum did? There's a little revisionist history here. Sure he assures
And that's not the case, but as he starts getting more and more successful
He becomes an asshole and the way these old musicals used to be he's he's abandoning his wife and kids
That he's not letting the freaks into the fancy parties. He's getting invited to now. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I tell you
I love the story. I loved him in Michelle Williams and I love the songs. I
Thought it was a great movie now
Please I'm overseeing it a bit. It's a B+. But if you like musicals at all
There's no way you would not like this movie and I'm really confused as to
the critical response. There's some of the, there's like cool dancing and singing. I had a good time.
I don't know what to say. Please tell me there's a bustling sort of tension, tension number.
It's show time. Gotta get these elephants washed. Why isn't the clown on the rope yet?
Is there one of those things? I mean, the first number is like the curtains going up. Yeah,
Snaps, you know, it's all right. It's really entertaining. All right, I'll check it out and I'd say it's one to see it the theater
It's a spectacle and there's there's you know trapeze artists and all kinds of shit. It's fun. Very good. It's fun
Pat I'm bringing back an old segment. We haven't done a while. You're not even you don't even have one for no
But that's why I'm bringing back this old segment. Okay, because I haven't really been watching much
I've been playing a lot of video games and not watching much and all right
I thought I could do a scary stuff
But I'd actually like to bring in the old segment that never had a title remember we said we were going to do news stuff. Yeah, it was hard related
Like horror movie related. I mean, so a new segment called news psycho
As a news cycle like news cycle. There you go. Yeah, Pat
I can't wait to talk to you about this because folks. I got to be honest with you are real Winchester is going to be pretty god damn brief
It's, I dread even having to talk about, we'll get to it.
Shape of water, we've discussed it at length on this show.
Shape of water.
We've discussed the disturbing nature of an Oscar nominated film having a beastie
alley scene in it.
It's the whole plot of the film.
There is for sale, and it is selling like hotcakes where they're tweeting like, get it now because
because we just did a repro and they're going to be gone again.
A shape of water inspired dildo.
Oh, no.
That is a green and blue dick, assuming the fish is dick.
Are there scales?
No, it looks sort of like a human dick, but it sort of doesn't and it's a green and blue.
Yeah, it's huge.
think. Yeah. People are buying this to fuck it. People are buying this thing to fuck it.
Do they have on the box Octavia Spencer going like, what's that fish dig look like? The review
I read essentially one of her lines in this front runner for best picture. Or the article
I read about it said like, said like, this is even a gag in the movie. Like Octavia Spencer
or japes about the fish dick or whatever.
And then it said,
it's the front runner for best picture.
Yeah. And it said, if you're,
and it literally says it's integral,
hey, apparently there are many people there
that are envious of the woman that gets to fuck the fish.
So there are these people who are buying a fit.
What the fuck is going on?
I mean, I get it as a gag gift.
But you just know there are people who that movie was like thank God someone gets me and might desire to fuck a fish man
And the dildo was just the cherry on top
That's troubling. Here's where it needs to stop
Here's why it needs to stop
Because we need to remain a progressive society. Yeah, and when this starts happening when the fish dick dildo craze starts happening
It means that my grandfather, who was angry and hated everything, was close -minded and
prejudiced, it means there was a hair of value in his argument when he would go, well,
what's next?
You're going to fuck fish.
And our answer was, you know what, and we all said, no, that's ridiculous.
We need to be progressive.
Stop it.
that's got nothing to do with it. We guys, we have to put a stop to fish fucking fantasies.
It's not right. It's weird. It's weird. Please, can we just keep it amongst the humans?
So you're going to get no disagreement from me on this point.
That is our new segment news psycho. It was the best I could do on show. I don't hate it.
You said on the other podcast, it sounds like Barbara Walters saying cycle, which is
a cycle.
Yeah, I agree with it.
How about screaming in?
I like new cycle.
We'll stick with it.
Well, listen, I'm just trying to think.
I tell you, I always was sort of indifferent to Barbara Walters and I have such hatred for
her now after watching that clip because that's another one for Pat's movie corner.
or I finally watched that documentary about the undercover
pedophile ring that they're showing for free
because they couldn't get a release for it.
It names names of people of the PG 13.
Believe me, I did not want to download the movie.
No, no, no, but it names.
What do you mean it names like a people like Hollywood
or something?
It's a documentary much, it's by the same woman
who made deliver us from evil, which was the documentary
about the sex scandal in the Catholic church.
OK.
Okay, and it is about the pedophilia pandemic in Hollywood, and they name names.
These actors, these, you know, who do they name?
Dish of the dirt.
Well, that's the thing.
I think due to fear of lawsuits on such a low -budget movie, they're naming names that are
pretty low in the totem pole, but they're guys who are still working.
The one that's opposed to topple Nickelodeon is this guy, Dan Schneider, who runs all these
Nickelodeon shows.
He's this big fat guy.
Oh, that guy from head of the class.
Back from head of the class.
Oh, no, really?
Not just really, but like, he gets in when he finds out,
you know, people with like weak stage mom parents.
He's beautiful young girls, including Ariana Grande
and all these people.
And fucks them, molests them.
He has a foot fetish.
He'll, he'll, he's still, while this is all going on,
he'll tweet on Twitter, send me pictures of your feet.
He's, he's that guy who's asking these young girls
that are his audience do that.
As he runs children's TV shows,
he's practically saying indulge me in my fetish.
Correct.
And one of the actors from those shows
is a convicted child molester
who still works like side by side with him.
And what they do is they start giving
nothing other guy from head of the class, is it?
No, no one from head of the class.
No, no, no, because he was on head of the class
but then the other guy, the guy that played
like the leather jacket on head of the class
also used to work with him in doing like kids TV shit.
Maybe.
I don't know.
I don't I don't want to criminate the guy. I think they wouldn't mention that day. Yeah, let's not but
They they have so much stuff and they go into Brian Singer and stuff like that as well good, but
Dan Schneider, Jamie Lynn Spears who is Britney Spears's sister the
Rumor that is apparently about to be broken by Ronan Pharaoh that's the the thing that eventually topples it because these people all sign
and these agreements, and the parents get so addicted
to the money, they don't even report the stuff
when it comes out.
Jesus Christ.
So I forgot to mute the TV again, sorry.
Sorry, good.
Jamie Lynn Spears' baby is allegedly,
and this is apparently just waiting to break, his baby,
that he impregnated her when she was shocked,
the fact guys baby, and she never said who the father was,
who's a big celebrity.
that is the rumor there. Amanda Bynes, who everyone mocked for years. Oh, this crazy bitch.
She's insane. Look at what she's writing on Twitter. Right. She has started to come out and
start tweeting and saying, like, I'm an adult now and I may have been under an NDA, but I'm not
anymore. This guy raped me, et cetera, et cetera. Jesus Christ. And it appears to be about toppling.
If you want to watch this video or this feature -length movie, you Google it, but that's if that's
something you want to put into your Google search. I did not. I definitely toyed with not doing
that, but it's a legitimate movie and you can watch it. It's not a child porn movie. It's a movie
saying it's actually a PG -13 movie, I think, to cover that. But also, what is this going to do with
Barbara Walters, though? Because she's on the thing. I think I talked about this on a previous one,
where this is I always go on these tangers but uh Corey Feldman is on there trying to talk to her
about it and she keeps cutting him off oh okay going like you're trying to throw an entire
industry under the bus and you should be ashamed of yourself you should telling Corey Feldman
who's saying I was molested by these people right you're you're you're making a fool of yourself
I thought she was disgusting and this happened like two years ago it's not like a 70s blip she regrets
That's, um, anyway, that's not, not a fun watch, but if, you know, there, people have
been talking about the shit for a long time, and I think there's got to be at least some
truth to it.
So, well, if you hear that, the fish dildo doesn't sound so bad.
Look, I'd certainly prefer someone make love to a fish dildo than a child.
Oh, right.
You know, that's true.
Uh, there was a man, apparently, the video's gone viral in some, some respect that, uh,
but in Philly that ate horse shit after the Eagles won.
I saw that.
I didn't see it yet.
My friend was talking about it
and kind of saying it was weird.
And I said, who's he hurting?
I agree.
You don't hurt anybody.
Who's he hurting?
He's eating shit of a horse.
Yeah.
Not doing anything to do to the horse.
We all celebrate in different ways.
That movie by the way is called An Open Secret.
It's free because they want people to see it.
Where can you see it?
Like on YouTube Google and open secret free and it's they they tell you at the top
This is a PG -13 movie. We want people to see it and get the word out. Please watch
Okay, check it out if you want
And on to our review of something almost as tragic as what we're talking about
It's a little film called Winchester starring Helen Mirren
About Lady Winchester the the the widow of the guy
Mr. Winchester, whatever his name was, who created the Winchester rifle and the family
had a lot of so -called blood on their hands because this rifle was used in a lot of the
slaughtering of many people and in wars and all these things.
Lady Winchester in her later years now widowed feels tremendously guilty about it and has
built what is known as the Winchester Secret House I think it's called. Now I have early in my
relationship with Heather. She got us a weekend getaway to Monterey and one of the sites she planned
on this weekend getaway was the Winchester House. So I have been there and I texted Heather that I
was going to see it and she was like oh apparently they shot some of it in the house see if any of it
familiar. And I was like, Oh, right, fuck, I've been to the
Winchester house. Okay. And I got this text right before the
movie started. So I was really excited to watch it because I
really enjoy that's a great tour to take if you're in northern
California. It's really fun and cool and creepy. But boy, this
movie. Well, here's the problem. So if you don't know the story,
the reason this house is so renowned is that she had a she built
Built it literally 24 hours a day, seven days a week.
They were continually constructing rooms, deconstructing rooms.
They built something then they demolished it.
And her take on this was, some people say she was building the room so to make the house
maze -like, so the ghosts of the dead that were slaughtered couldn't find her and haunt her.
In the movie they say she was building these rooms because it was a giving the
Gosa chance to come home and have their reckoning and and be at peace and
and they you know they could forgive her or whatever look it's a tremendously
interesting story. It's a fascinating backstory with a fantastic social commentary that they do
at one point mention in the movie, which is, look, you can't have guilty for somebody using your
product in the wrong way. That's not your fault. There was a lot of opportunity here to kind of hear
They're both sides of that argument to examine the paranoia of this woman, to delve into
whether it was justified or not, to delve into whether or not this place was actually haunted
or not.
And at the end of the day, I thought it was going to be essentially sort of like a fox
catcher with like horror elements, like let's go into the world of this billionaire.
What a love that because I fucking love fox.
you know who lives in this weird sprawling estate and is very uh...
inigmatic and and and reclusive and
and we don't know where this is going to go and if they're stable or what
it i was so excited and they took this thing and they turned it into
a definite
horror movie conjuring ripoff and it
sucked
it fucking
sucked. They made it so there was no doubt that the place was haunted. Everybody is seeing
the ghosts. People that don't believe in ghosts are interacting with ghosts who are posing
as butlers in the house. Right. The scares were cheap. The scares. I mean, there was nothing
even remotely scared. It sucked. The guy is Jason Clark, the guy from Zero Dark 30 and
a great show that I, for some reason, keep mentioning on here called Brotherhood, this show
that you've been on showtime.
He was also Conner in Terminator Genesis.
Yes.
I liked him in this movie.
I liked Helen Mirren, they do what they can because I do try to say something positive.
But to tell you how forgettable and empty and just like joyless this movie was, Joe and
I saw this movie on Saturday morning, this hotel had a theater in it, which was kind of cool.
with the intent to then review it for the podcast, right?
We watched the movie on Saturday, last night,
Thursday night, I'm like, so what do we want to do
on this podcast?
Joe's like, Winchester, I had forgotten that I had seen it
and I'm not kidding you.
I had forgotten that I had seen a movie I saw four days prior
because that is the perfect word for this thing is forgettable.
It's not like it's terribly shot or something like that.
It's just the most boring, forgettable telling
of a really cool story.
And I think we both agree.
It could have been an awesome movie.
And it started cool.
The opening is creepy.
Yeah, it's the time period.
It's kind of interesting.
There's weird shots.
Before you get to meet the character,
there's weird shots of Helen Mirren walking around the house
with a candle in a black veil.
And it's really cool and creepy and whatever.
And then they get into the house and as soon as John Conner gets into the house
It is immediately just like who gives a shit anymore like he's seeing ghosts immediately in that. Well, fuck this
This is stupid. Yeah, and then they'll introduce something cool like that little
Intercom system so she's like these each one of these tubes goes to a different room of the house if you whisper into the tube the person in that room will hear it
Yeah, it's like 1902 or whatever.
So you're like, oh, that's really cool.
What a great setup for some cool horror action coming up
and they do fucking nothing with it.
The movie sucks people.
It's a must miss.
Yeah, I can't.
I was just gonna say, I can't,
I can't in any way recommend anybody to see this thing.
Too long.
I think I had about 10 % of the rotten tomatoes.
I try to give the stuff the benefit of the doubt
and I really went and again, first 15, 20 minutes
I was in and then this fucking thing went from nowhere to worse.
Oh, it's Winchester, more like Los Chester.
Which speaking of which of other poorly reviewed films
that we'll be discussing at some point in this podcast.
I haven't watched it yet, but Cloverfield Paradox
is now at I think at a 13 % or something around it.
I mean people are really saying it sucks.
People hate it, but that is one that we will definitely do
because I really liked Cloverfield,
and I really loved Cloverfield Lane,
10 Cloverfield Lane.
So I'm excited to watch it.
We'll be doing that as well.
Well, apparently the problem is
is that the last this happened with Cloverfield Lane
and it worked.
Yeah, it was a movie called The Cellar.
Right, right.
They shoved it into Cloverfield, it worked.
They said this one was also a different movie.
They shoved it in, they're like, yeah,
it doesn't, it's just a shitty sci -fi movie.
Yeah, you know, so I don't know, we'll see.
But I'm curious to see curious as well and also coming up we have we're going to do blade and blade two I
Think that's that's pretty much it folks also the bonus patreon episode this month is a return to the commentary format
We just recorded it. It's very very funny and it is the craft. I
put out a
request for
requests for that film and all of you fuck that up. So we just decided to do the
craft. So check that out. It's Patreon. You can sign up at Jody Address if you
will. Patreon .com slash WSYH pod. There it is. There's also merch available now. The
a Hoghouse store on Etsy.
And that's it, right?
I think we're on Instagram.
See you on HellPod, we're on Twitter,
WSYIHPod, and that's it, yeah.
Anyway, oh, I'm doing a big tour in April,
so I'm gonna be posting the date soon, release,
and they might actually be out now
by the time this comes out,
but I'll probably be coming through your town
if you're in the Northwest Midwest region in April.
Jodoros, a comedy on Twitter and Instagram,
Jodoros, an info for tour details.
I'm the Patrick Walsh Twitter and Instagram
and win this airs.
I think we should be getting very close
to the premiere on February 26th of Living Biblically.
It airs on CBS, it airs at 9 .30 pm, 8 .30 central.
It's a very funny show folks.
I hope you watch and tell your friends
is because apparently they're not doing a lot of advertising for it.
Thank you very much.
I didn't do on with the Joe, so I'll just simply say on with the Joe, I'm sorry about
that.
Sometimes we forget what a little more into it than that.
Jesus Christ.
Just on with the Joe when the Joe is over.
How about it and that's our Joe and we end there.
And that's our Joe.
That was a hitgun podcast.