Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal, durable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning, or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 -plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberer, offer not available in all states
terms apply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
Hello everybody and welcome to Will see you in hell. We said we'd be back, we back, and
now without further ado on with the Joe. That's a real, that was an odd one. I didn't even
do it all with the show. I mean, that's how tired I am. I couldn't even do my whole catch
for it. I'm exhausted. It's it's it's currently 11 .20 pm our time. We we're doing this very late
tonight because we just saw Guardians of the Galaxy volume two. We were like let's just let's go
right in and record the podcast but I think we're both quite tired. Yeah. Pat I know you've been reading
scripts all day. You're in the scripts that I meet with a different rider every like 45 minutes.
That's which is fun and yet it's like being on
21st dates and one day and this is for those of you that don't know Pat secured himself a nice pilot there at CBS
And they asked him to start talking to writers not a bad sign not a bad sign. I mean, I'm just keeping you right here in my
Nervous brain if you don't want to be there. That's true. Still don't know
Well, but you know, meeting with writers seems seems like a good sign and
It's been fun you read it read a shitload of scripts you say I like this one
I like that one bring this person in you see if you can deal with them try to put your staff together
You know, it's fun. It's fun. I
Think that's great. Yeah, I like it
But then just like a first day, you know, you get in the room and somebody starts talking and you're like oh no
You're there for another hour
Why in an hour do you have to do a long meeting? I'd like to get to know somebody. I
Think I think you're talking to out of your microphone. Yeah, that's probably true. But uh an hour is
God bless you. You're a man that commits. I don't I don't get it
I'd have him I'd have him come in. I'd say spin it around. Let me see what the back looks like make it clap for daddy
Ten minutes in and out
I have no excuse to be tired, I didn't really do much today, I started swimming for exercise, so I did that for a good 20 minutes today, in the pool and the complex, that you walk by every time.
All right.
So I've been doing that in the morning.
It's hard to judge a man when you're wearing MC Hammer's
garage sale trousers.
I'm wearing my DC Comics pants to commemorate the occasion
in protest.
No, not in protest, just as part of the occasion,
as we stroll down Marvel Lane this evening.
And then I had to get a new iron today.
OK, that was a big thing.
They had the same irons since I was in college, so today I went and I got a new one because it wasn't working anymore. I don't iron. I don't do it. How do you, how do your shirts?
Becoming clean when it hits a point. You'll take it off. You take everything dry cleaner. If it hits that point, this is, this is a man that does, I mean, what do you, what do you, why don't you just piss on the money?
I mean, you bring 10 shirts down. It costs like $25 and you got a beautiful nicely pressed shirt.
look like a damn uh what about your t -shirts GQ model don't your t -shirts ever get
wrinkled and you gotta iron them or your pants I don't really wear t -shirts pants I don't care
I'm a casual man god bless you you know what you want and you know what you like it's true
and you'll indulge in both and I don't have a problem with that patty pat let's let's let's go
down let's go down what do you say we take a stroll down to Pat's movie corner oh all right
I haven't really so much just turned on my television I'm behind on my stories about nothing but
just like last week I told you I wanted to turn off my brain and watch the movie from my youth
problem child one and two I did it again this time with a film called kindergarten cop
And I gotta tell you, I understood completely why I loved it when I was a kid, but that's
a bad move.
Yeah, I, I, I don't, I don't, I've never recalled thinking it was a good move.
I mean, it almost seems like I made for NBC movie.
It's lit in that way.
Yeah.
It's acted in that way, Arnold, with the kids is funny, but they do it like four times.
So the entire movie you're watching like a Z grade Arnold action movie. Yeah, because they couldn't make it to intense because the movie's for fucking children
Then at any time you start getting two board with that then Arnie teaches the kids for like three minutes
It's hilarious and then they move back to this boring like a jewel heist plot. Yeah, I remember that as a kid
In the fucking 80s and early 90s movie jewel heist three minute a baby has a fucking jewel heist. It does. Yeah, isn't that well? Maybe I'm wrong
I don't think so, 80s movies are, well 90s, that's early 90s I guess, right?
But those movies had unnecessary crime devices planted into all them.
I don't know why that had to be a part of anything.
It would always be like you're watching like 40 minutes of baby boom and then all of a sudden
they're like walking on the outside of a building with a gun in their mouth.
Yeah.
Pick a lane.
Yeah, I agree.
I try to walk the baby boom.
I thought all the crime elements ruined Roadhouse. I just wanted to see a fun romp
Yeah of Patrick Swazie and Sam Elliott beaten people up. Jesus Christ. Sam Elliott gets murdered halfway through the movie
It's like what the fuck is going on right now? I had a Sam Elliott siding up at WB because he works on that the ranch the Multicam
Yes, I've not seen
But I'm not great. I mean he was walking across the lot as if every bone and his body was shattered
like he looked like he had been like run over by a tractor very recently legs were all like a
Kimbo and I hope he's doing all right maybe from riding horses or something where do you think he
was headed on that lot what do you think he was going to do shitter how to imagine shitter he calls
it I'm sure you get me to shitter through a damp mustache oh yeah we used to do Sam Elliott on
this show I forgot yeah Sam Elliott ordering food ordering food yeah wait let's do one of those
right now. Give me a restaurant. I noticed the establishments called Shake Shack. Am I
to assume the best dish on the menu then would be the shake? Now let me tell you this
there, partner. I don't see a damn shake or a shack in this place. Just give me a cheeseburger
and some and one of those sausage patties. What's the 4 -1 -1 on those cheesy tots?
They have popular item. They have popular item. I suppose you think a fellow like me
order that Western omelette. You're wrong. I like a Spanish omelette myself.
Always did. Speaking of Spanish omelettes, here's a photo of her, my first wife,
Dottie. She came with her own bottle of hot sauce. If you catch my drift. Yes,
I'm talking about that tight Mexican hole. You're slipping into an almost an
I didn't feel great about it, tried to lighten it up with the Ebenezer Scrooge bit.
At that point it seems like we're trying to avoid it, which maybe makes it worse.
I was playing the character of Sam Elliott who I assume is a casual racist.
It's the way he walked across that lot.
I didn't find anything racist about what you said.
I found it just extremely misogynistic.
I didn't think it was racist.
No, it was I guess it was all of those things
Pat I saved a couple movies for this week because I as you know, I was flying back and forth between continents and countries last week
Where is Armstrong and I I saw quite a few films I saw Dracula untold
Which I didn't wait not dead and loving it
It's as far as I could tell there was no connection to dead and loving it which I was upset about
What who is it untold that Jason Jason's staph him?
uh...
it now it was uh... should have been
it's the guy from
well the one guy in it is the guy from last action hero
Arnold Schwarzenegger
not arny and not the kid and not the old man that runs the theater the guy with
the smiley face eyeball
like the bad guy
okay
rufus seul
with like the red hair
There's also Woody Allen's scoop about scoop is Woody Allen's worst movie I couldn't
disagree more.
I love scoop.
I've got a you love scoop I think it's a wonderful film holy shit I find it incredibly
funny and I can and I can show you worse I mean it's have you seen did you ever see a Hollywood
ending the movie where he's directing a movie one of his worst goes not his worst which
Scoop. You think Scoop is worse? That's right. Are you talking about Michael Rappaport?
No, Pat. No. The bad guy playing Dracula. He even has Michael Rappaport playing Dracula.
What is a good blood? It's all I wanted. What is a good blood?
This guy doesn't play Dracula in it. He plays the guy that gives Dracula the vampire curse.
okay the guy that plays Dracula oh oh he was in a I remember now he's in the
hobbit he's in the second hobbit Sean Bean might be he plays the archer that
kills smog in the third I like smog I hate it all those hobbit movies but for
some reason I I enjoyed smog I love desolation of smog it might be my favorite of
all of the lord of the room yeah yeah by the way I'm not a big fan don't write
Let me offer some fucking nerd out.
Yeah, I know.
I hear you.
I didn't really care for the first three
Lord of the Rings films.
I found them a little very boring.
I mean, excruciate.
Very lucky.
Here's an eight -hour version of them.
Yeah, watching some, you know,
Midget's Walk for May to Be.
And as you know,
other people, I'm sorry.
So Dracula, wait,
I got to give my mini review of this.
Dracula until,
the salad movie.
All right.
You know.
Dominic Cooper, huh?
Dominic Cooper.
Yeah, so that's who it is.
Okay, he played the archer and...
I mean, I couldn't have less interest in this thing.
I didn't have any interest in it, but I got on a plane.
I saw it, our old friend Ken Hanley from Fangoria.
Yes, love.
He tweeted one night about, I don't know why I ever doubted
this being a good movie, it's a good movie
and that made me think, okay, well maybe I should see it.
I'm on the plane, they got it there for free.
I say I'm watching it.
It's an enjoyable action -harm movie.
All right.
That tells a cool origin story of Dracula and and I enjoyed it. Remember how shitty American Werewolf in Paris was
It's I mean there are a few sequels have dipped off harder than that one did from the from its predecessor
As you know, I watched Jurassic Park 3 I do on the plane and this is a good time as any to tell our fans fans
We are gonna be launching a patreon site very soon
and we're gonna release special commentary episodes
on the Patreon site.
And when we get of one end three.
The first two episodes will be Jurassic Park one and three.
Those will be the first special sort of donation.
I don't know how Patreon where you donate and you get some.
You should, if you wanna help out the boys
and say thanks for the laughs, thanks for the memories.
Yeah, thanks for getting me through that particularly rough patch where I
Yeah, I might have found solace in the bottle one too many nights
Maybe I hit my wife
Maybe I hit her again
You two were there for me and here's here's four dollars. Yeah, it'd be nice
That's always it would be and I know we do it for free
I know it sounds like we're sitting high on the hog when I tell you we've made
125 dollars each
each, which I still have not seen in a, I mean, we got to be into the goddamn 60, 70,
5th episodes of this thing.
Yeah.
Oh, 100.
We're the only people to have not monetized podcasting and we do well, you know, we, although
I will say when Joe said he doesn't want to seem, seem high in the hog.
We are both sitting atop fat hogs at the moment.
literal pigs Joe rented a couple of pigs we've been jousting I guess you could
call it for most of the night the pigs are weary we're all gonna kind of
sleep in a pile here after the pod but it was a fun night I might fuck my
pig I did is that is that okay to say is a joke your beast reality jokes still
Okay, they're they're always in fashion Rose on a serious radio. I can't remember the show
But I was on some serious radio show and I go I
Go I made a BCL you joke and the host goes just so everybody knows at home
We hear it serious are sternly against beastieality. What's your joke pro?
Yeah, it was it was an absurd and I was like thank you for clearing it up with the audience that serious this major
is, in fact, against beastieality.
Who's sitting at home confused by that?
Yeah.
That's what we live in.
It's a shit show.
Anyway, so the Pixies last week was a fantastic show.
It was.
And I told you another story about, I would say perhaps even worse
than Beastieality really kind of chilled me to the bone.
There's this big fat dude in Philadelphia and his wife
and they get stuck in the elevator of their building
And neither of them have their cell phones on them. They look like, you know, pretty trashy folks. No offense
They're sitting there in the elevator
And when they find them when the cops finally get the door open because they couldn't call out
It had been less than 72 hours less than three days
And the man had murdered and eaten eleven pounds of his wife's body
11 pounds of flesh in three days. I couldn't eat 11 pounds. You'd be sick to death.
It's literally the Mr. Show sketch where they find Bob Odenkirk in the plane crash and
he's eaten everybody and it's been like not even a week. Yeah. If you look up this news
story, it was insane and they're like, you can tell he felt really bad about it, but like
we're obviously going to charge him with murder, but like what an interesting case to be
So he got so hungry and scared he just snapped the murderer that was there and just started eating god damn
And I guess I assume didn't cook it or anything. He's eating just raw globs of flesh
Well, how could he have cooked he couldn't he's in a dead elevator
Chilling tail only in Philadelphia folks or perhaps also Florida
But hello listeners
Well, the only reason I brought up Jurassic three a minute ago was because I got on a Sam Neal tear when I was on the plane. Yeah. Watch the film called the dish. Have you ever seen this film? No heartwarming romp.
Wait, no, I saw the dish like 99 or so. Yeah, the lovable folks and I'll show you that ran the the satellite dish down there during the first moon landing.
saw it. I enjoyed it very much, very lighthearted. Yeah. Very playful. Your boy Patrick Warburton's in it.
My boy Patrick Warburton. He's in it playing a NASA representative. It's odd to see that man go
from putty to a NASA rep, but he played both very convincingly. And I'll tell you, I was in goddamn tears
at the end of that thing when they showed all the moon landing footage and I thought this must be how
people felt when this happened. Yeah. Last but not least, band of robbers. Can't
recommend this movie highly enough. Not familiar. Band of robbers, modern day
retelling of Huck Finn and Tom Sawyer. It's a crime comedy. starts with Huck Finn
getting out of jail. Tom Sawyer is a cop. He's like, let's have one last ride.
Let's get into some shit. I know where there's a treasure. And it's it's a
really it's almost like a it's almost like a what was the what's the first
Wes Anderson movie bottle rock bottle right it's like it's very bottle rocket a
new movie yeah it's probably two years old our friends Hannibal Burris and
Johnny Pemberton are in the film sure that was a nice surprise and it was it was
it was a thoroughly enjoyable film and very very funny I want to check this
betcha out. You should. Band of robbers, folks. And with that, let's move into Joe's scary stuff.
Oh, sure. Which I keep forgetting to do everywhere. Back. I'll make this real fast. There's a DVD company
out there called Cinemacolt. They are an Australian based company, but you can't get their stuff on Amazon.
on, I have folks, I cannot, I can't, I'm not trying to sell you on this thing because they
don't sponsor us, but I can't tell you, if you're looking for really, really brilliant
restorations of really great cult films, go there by yourselves. Some I bought every copy
of every movie I could find when I was in Australia because the prices were significantly lower,
But they did a really wonderful restoration of last man on Earth, the events in price version of I am legend
While it was in Australia picked up the town that dreaded sundown. I picked up the fury. I picked up
I picked up the beyond I picked up black Sunday and I think one other one that I can't remember at the moment
But it's a really great company. They do nice work. Not not heavy in the bonus features of department, but that's okay
Okay, it's an affordable way to get a nice blue ray version of a classic cult film.
Pat, I urge you to go check these guys out.
Yeah, I'll just slide on down to Australian scoop it up.
Well, as I said, you can go on Amazon and get them.
Amazon .co .os.
Something like that.
I got it on regular Amazon.
All right.
I don't need you sharpshooting me, watch.
I'm just trying to do a second.
Sacking a valid follow -up question is all I'm doing.
Hold on one second here.
I'm just going to take a brief pause, sorry about that folks, as you can hear I've
got shit in my mouth, not from the pig, now, I suddenly got a wave of low blood sugar
and I had to pause the podcast and go to the fridge
and start shoving carrots into my mouth.
It was a real scene.
Yeah, but we're all back online now.
So anyway, we saw Guardians of the Galaxy volume two night
together and a quick stop of the cheesecake factory prior.
Yes, for real dream evening.
In fact, I don't mind saying this right now, this is one of the things we're going to offer
on the Patreon.
Let's give the people a little taste of what's to come.
We're going to figure out merch and that kind of stuff.
One of the things Pat and I have discussed, we're not sure what the donation amount will be.
But for a certain donation, a large donation to be honest, you will get to meet Pat and
I at the Cheesecake Factory.
right. Our treat. Our treat for a couple of drinks. I mean, reasonable. Within reason. Yeah, you know,
it's kind of your treat because you're going to donate a big sum of money. Yeah. And then we'll
take you to see a movie next door at the Pacific cinemas at the Americana here in sunny LA.
Well, let me make this abundantly clear. This isn't like, hey, can you wrap up some some Asian lettuce
wraps to go because it's all in these guys. You're getting one dinner and one
alcoholic drink perhaps too. I say get the dinner part. Let's just let's just
drink. Well buy you a few drinks. We'll get a little loose and we'll go to the
movie. Water, bread, their complimentary. Feel free to fill up on both. Maybe we're not
made of money. Maybe an app. Have an app. Keep it light. Who knows where the
night could go. I don't know. You could wind up nude by the end of this thing. By your choice.
It'll be just a real fun evening. So anyway, to see the beautiful downtown Armania
grove. The Americana. Did you just say the downtown Armenia grove? It's well, it's the Armanian
growth. It's very like Armenian. What? The the Americana? What
Americana? Yes. It's in the center of Glendale, a little
armania area. Little armenia is like Hollywood.
You know, Glendale is largely Armenian. Is it? I don't you
must know that. I don't see color. I don't color. I honestly
I didn't know that. I've never, I don't think I've ever seen an Armenian on set foot on the soil of the Americana.
It's, it's, it's very, very heavily. Like Heather, my girlfriend, fiancee, is
pretty Armenian. So there's this movie out with Christian bail about the Armenian genocide
and her and her family went and of course they went to the Armenian Grove, which is the Americana,
where it was hailed as like the biggest premiere in Hollywood history because it was the,
I think the hundred a year anniversary or something or the Emanuele genocide that number is probably wrong. It's definitely wrong, but
Well now I get why the why the sales girl at the Urban Outfitters screamed our wounds are still open at me. I
Didn't understand why she did that. Yeah
Let's get into let's get into clarity. We're scurting the edge of good taste tonight a little riff on the Emanuele genocide
That's fine. It's late as we said
Smash cut to them pulling the pilot out of my hands because I talked about the Armenian genocide
Folks
Gardens of the galaxy was uh extremely entertaining
It I like what Marvel does in terms of visuals. I think that
They have to be this and dr. Strangin particular it seems like they are making movies for
People on drugs and I appreciate that because I I sometimes am
I just thought it looked great. It had its tongue in cheek, but also like had big swings
of emotion that were kind of kind of worked. It was corny, it was stupid at parts, but
way more of the comedy attempts than normal were funny. Or at least you were like, I get
why people are laughing. You know, they weren't bad ponds and shit. They had some good sort
a character comedy in it. I heard you laughing yourself Joe. I laughed a few times. I thought
there were some funny moments. Yeah. I did not hate this movie as much as I thought I was
going to. I actually enjoyed the first Guardians of the Galaxy quite a bit. I did as well.
And I thought that I was going to hate this one because as we all know, I've grown to really
have a bad taste in my mouth about the Marvel Studios Marvel movies much more so than the
Sony Marvel movies, but this movie I felt maintained a significant, significantly larger
amount of heart, honest heart than any of the recent Avengers related movies have.
I think it's far far, this movie was, to me, far, far better than the second Avengers
movie. It was better than any of the solo movies that they've done since then. It was better than
Civil War or any of that stuff. And you didn't mind the joking. Well, I'm gonna get to that.
The great soundtrack as well. I like it. It also has a nice time. It also is supposed to be a
funnier movie. Correct. So the joking didn't bother me that much. I will say this. They do it at
the expense of the film's quality. A lot. Yeah. A lot. Now, this is going to be riddled
with spoilers, everybody. So, you know, if you haven't seen the movie, well, Chris, you
probably haven't. It just came out. But I'll try not to ruin major plot points here. But
these are going to be spoilers in the sense of, I'm going to talk about gags in the movie.
There's one thing they do repeatedly with this, you know, villain guy who's this hideous
like mutant alien, and his name is Taserface, and they keep doing this gag where he tells
somebody his name, and then they start laughing at him.
And you're like, this is absurd, you're ruining, like, I'm not taking the villain seriously
anymore.
right? Like, and so, so the point I'm getting it, and I get that that's the point and that's
the joke and everything, but what I'm getting at is, is when you take the ass out of everything
like that, there then becomes no real tension or fear for the characters themselves.
Sure.
So, I didn't give a shit about anybody on it. Chris Pratt had, it seemingly no dialogue, like
he made no impression. He, he talked to his dad a few times, but other than that, it was
like they're focusing on these animals and trees is who gets a lot of the
material. I will say this, I found baby Groot devastatingly adorable. Did you
see? I thought you would hate that too. It was real cute. I was having a hard
time coming to terms with how cute I found it. It made me think of my dog the
The whole time.
people do things at the, look, one of the lessons I learned early on when the first script
I ever wrote, and I believe it was the great Dave Keckner who gave this advice to one
Bill Burr, who then passed it to me.
He said, look, because we made a short film called Cheat, Bill and Bobby Kelly and myself, and
David Keckner actually, Bill showed it to him, and David Keckner said it was good, and he
He said, listen, you could tighten it up.
And Bill said, how do you mean?
And David Kekner said, look, you can joke anything to death,
but you need to cut out the stuff
that doesn't need to be in there.
And again, there's a lot of stuff in the movie
where I'm like, everything doesn't have to be a swing
for a gag.
I don't need to see the sentient,
or not the sentient, the sovereign being
who are supposed to be this like regal perfection race
that were engineered perfectly and everything,
saying lines like, you suck man,
and don't screw with the soft,
it's fucking stupid, it ruins the characters.
It's just too much, it's just too much,
I don't know if the kit is the right word or whatever,
why are multiple characters in the film said go to hell?
Well, how do they even have a concept of hell?
What what where is that coming from why are people saying I got to take a whiz
Why are they why wouldn't that what do you mean?
It's not like it's a
Revolutionary war period piece. Why can't they say these things?
This is American slang
It's not just it's not or it's not even earth slang. It's American slang
It's like you you know what I mean like do you want them to talk like people on Mars do I'm not
saying that I'm saying you're already having me suspend disbelief that everybody in the galaxy speaks
perfect English nobody ever speaks another language. You want to speak in fucking Naboo like in
Old Avatar you want subtitles. Yeah, but I can't have that listen I'm saying I will go with you on
this everybody nobody's got an accent everybody just speaks regular English it's fine whatever whatever
No, that is fine. What a that is completely fine, but here's everybody in this action movie speaks English. Well, they're from multiple planets across the galaxy. It wouldn't be the way it is, but listen, it wouldn't be the way it is folks. I wasn't aware you had intimate contact with aliens from other planets. They'd have a different language. They'd communicate. What if they don't? All right. Fine. I'll accept that. Starman didn't I'll accept that was a documentary. But how about it?
instead of who what's the big guy's name? Who's Dave Batista packs gas with the fuck's
his name in it? I don't know. Josh Gad. His name is Josh Gad. Yeah. How about instead
of having him saying she's disgusting, which is a 12 year old slang word from America?
Have him say revolting. Just make it a little believable. This guy, which is one of your
most insane lines of thought that you have ever seen either on or off of the show.
It's not insane. It is insane. Have them say revolting instead of disgusting because that's what an
alien would say. What you're saying is what an insane person would say. You don't think it would ruin.
Let me just ask you this. If you're watching Star Wars, okay. Sure. New Star Wars comes out.
Looks great. So I'll try out tonight. Yeah. I'm excited about it. New Star Wars comes out.
Uh, there's a scene where Luke is training Ray and he goes, uh, hey, don't go in that
cave.
It's gross.
You know, you know, you know, it's a whole different franchise made in a different time
like, and they might say gross.
I don't know.
They would not say gross.
It would be absurd.
I'm saying, but that is the world of Star Wars, which is not the same world as Guardians
of the Galaxy.
Fair enough.
But here's my also listening to pop it's here's my point.
You could you could still make the joke without having to go for the catch factor
It doesn't I don't need the green alien or the blue alien to say gross
He could say a more believable word and I would go that's still funny. Do you see what I'm saying? No
Oh, and for just to be real clear. No, I don't you thought it was fine when when when the last ship got blown up
And one of the the sovereigns goes you suck Zarnak. It's terrible
The whole movie was like that.
The whole movie is an agronistic and slaying
and dancing and music.
Did you mind that the sovereign,
like when they had those remote controlled spaceships,
that the control, like the control portals
or whatever the fuck you wanna call them,
that they were controlling the ships from,
made fucking like Pac -Man noises and shit.
Pac -Man came at him at that one point.
No, no, no, like I'm talking about,
remember the gold people they could control
their ships remotely?
And and it made like arcade video game noises. Did that bother you it did not
God because that's what the movie is what the whole tone of the movie is so the whole tone of
It doesn't it doesn't fuck up any tone they have because it's completely in line with everything else
It's something you liked less than the other stuff
Doesn't make it unless that but here's the thing. It's not the tone of the Marvel universe
first. Hold on. These movies all have their own feel, which is why I prefer them to your
DC shit, which all has the feel of being drowned in a lake. Don't bring it up if you don't
want me to go down that road. Here's the thing. This, this is going to cross into the Avengers
movies. Yeah, I know. So I thought the new Thor looks sweet. It looks pretty good. I like
that they are, they're not also fucking serious. I like that. It doesn't have to be also serious,
But if you want me to believe that the work comes from a planet where Anthony Hopkins
This regal, you know, it's like come on like like like like
I don't believe that every and god in the future is regal everybody talks like a valley girl and guardians of the galaxy
You're just like okay every alien. Yes, stupid
Well, they do all have different voices that that's stupid, but
Yeah, that's the style of the movie every
Some fucking rock creature from the planet Nebula or whatever knows the word dude. It's absurd
He could have learned it from the fucking Star Lord. I think the Star Lord says dude and he hasn't picked up on get the hell out of here
It's true. That's how people pick up things the only the only bizarre thing to focus on or think about at all
I thought the movie surely had flaws and then you're just like hey, let me just make up something no
No, no, that bothers me.
All right, it's bad writing.
It's the marble thing.
Every character's written the same.
That bothers me about, I've said it many times.
Every, any wine that any character in this movie said tonight,
you could have changed it with another character.
Not one character was written differently.
Even when Kurt Russell, who's a spoiler alert,
who's part God, who's literally part God,
or is it God? He's a God. Even his character, when he got angry, he goes,
I suggest you stop pissing me off. And it's like, can one person speak differently?
Does anybody have a better education than anybody else in this film?
Okay. It's stupid. Now, let's get into this Kurt Russell thing.
I thought he's absolutely stunk in the movie.
It wasn't his best performance, he seemed a little confused.
But he was certainly better than Mr. Sylvester Stallone.
Stallone, that was, I don't even think Stallone knew it was right.
It looks like he was remembering him as he was saying him.
I thought that perhaps in tone with the movie being pretty campy, that he was direct, I'm
cheesy Stallone performance. But you know that's not the case. Stallone was embarrassing in this movie.
In a way he hasn't really been since like the old, you know, over -the -top rhinestone.
He was really bad. You can't put everybody in every part. Stallone and Kurt Russell were miscast
severely in this film. Kurt Russell was not coming off good because you don't buy Kurt Russell
as a God. Kurt Russell looks like he was an overboard for Christ's sakes. That's what they're
making. Yeah. But that's who Kurt Russell is. He's the guy that fixes your car, shoots
his way out of the case of overboard. Yeah. Shoot his way out of the crazy. He's Star
Lord. Make him start and run. Don't. Yes. He's captain. Run. Don't make him a God. Give
Give me a book.
John Q.
Backdraft.
Which I thought was a little on the nose character name.
Dia.
Stallone.
Can be a great actor.
Copeland.
Rocky.
We aren't.
Look, let's just say it.
We're all thinking it.
Let's just say it.
Stallone's great in a part where the guy's not too sharp.
Yeah.
That's exactly right.
He got to put it.
He's supposed to.
They got him in this thing as the leader of the ravager.
He's supposed to be leading this entire.
Very sharp and intelligent man, and then he's yelling at one point about that you've broken the code
I can't even believe stolen could remember what the code was you broken the code
Very poor act
Uh, I did I did not see Miley Cyrus David Hasselhoff a bit was pretty funny. I thought the David Hasselhoff cameo was funny
Who was Miley Cyrus an alien?
I don't know her voice was entered or something somewhere I did not one more actor in this
I didn't care for I can't remember her name but the girl from doctor who who plays the
Blue and Gillen Nebula or whatever yeah I wouldn't feel in her I felt like I thought it
was Rachel Lee Cook the star of she's all that I really did until we looked her up at the end I
was glad to see her again I love Rachel Lee Cook Jozy and the pussy cats underrated comedy where she
been. She was just, she was the original person and that this is your brain on drugs commercial
when she was a little girl. So she just did it again. With the eggs. Yeah. So she just
did an update of it where I was like, this is your brain on drugs, but the twist on it was,
and the simple marijuana charges, why we have tons of African Americans in prison. Uh -huh.
She's using her moderate fame for political gain. The audition for my show, she had a good
audition. This is your brain on drugs. The one I remember is the close -up of the frying pan
in the eggs and the male the man voiceover. Well, I guess they they did want to
some point with her as a young girl and she updated it. Who the hell wants to hear about drugs
from a young kid? The fuck's a kid though. I don't know shit. You haven't experienced the pain
that makes you need the drugs. Yeah. You little shit. Dare. Remember dare? Yeah. Keep kids off drugs.
was dare drugs or was dare drugs? It was drugs. Oh, man, I'm thinking of moms
against drunk driving and they got a point stupid. Sure. Why's it gonna be moms
against it? Why can't we all be against it? Where are the dads? Speak loud dad
speak proud and loud. This sounds like a side felt bit. Mothers against drunk driving.
Are there mothers for drunk driving? I think pretty much every mom is against
strong drive yeah uh okay so we talked about the that's gonna start on the
fathers against drunk drive where are these man why aren't they backing up that
wife I'll tell you the these mothers were a man of drunk drive and should be
mad at their husbands we should call an M .A .H. hey hey you want to go down a
March today, man, M -A -H.
I was watching Seinfeld today and he, the opening stand -up thing was about how they
sent monkeys into space before anybody else, it leveled me, it leveled me.
This is clearly the next step for the monkey.
It's a very, is it funny, man, I've seen him do stand -up live a couple times, it was a
real treat, both times.
Uh, one other thing I wanted to talk about with this, again, overall, like the movie,
it had me by the end.
I overall enjoyed it.
I felt for the characters by the end.
I did like the film and much to my sugar and I didn't want to like it.
I went to hate it so I can come on here and make fun of it and I, you know, I, I saw you
doing a lot of typing on your phone, so I thought you were going to hate it and have a lot
to make fun of.
Most of it was the language issues that I had with it, sure.
I wasn't thrilled that they just kind of jacked the asteroid scene from Empire Strikes Back. I thought that was kind of weak
But whatever
Also why can Gamora pick up like a two -ton gun?
Remember that part who's Gamora the green lady. Oh, I mean just the same normal
Does she have super strange better better than average strike? She's a mutant
Is she I don't know. She's a something ghost. I don't know all right
Well, I was just curious about that last but not least
There there was a lady sit next to you in this thing
Oh, yeah, it was a DVD commentary through the goddamn movie her seat was drenched by the end of this fucking thing
She was like oh, like I mean the brute every time he came on was like oh
I like so adorable
I learned Joe was saying as well, but he kept it to himself.
I kept it to myself like a decent, dignified citizen
in this fucking society we have to live in.
Let me just laughing at every joke, a lot of all.
It was like being in the full house audience
and sitting right next to me.
I will say this overall, that ladies enthusiasm,
the enthusiasm of the folks around us,
the applause at the end of the film,
that was what got me the most.
I thought people really like this film. It made a lot of people happy. Yeah, there are people where this is their
Star Wars. I know Star Wars makes me feel and
Overall Pat, I'm gonna give it a thumbs up
It too. It was fun. I did kind of doze off here and there. It's too long. They're all too long
But they're all too long. I owed ten dollars in the way out. I had a four -hour validation. I would eleven ridiculous. Yeah
Um, but you know folks, it was uh, an entertaining film if you like the first one you're gonna like the second one
So I can say I prefer the first I think the story of the second one is better than the story of the first one
Okay, all right the story the first one is I didn't like all the prison stuff in the first one
That's for sure. Yeah, that was kind of boring and then the story of the first one is just the infinity stone bullshit
Where it's like enough with these goddamn fucking infinity stones every movie
This was was him finding his dad and the twist in turns of all that and I thought the story
And this was way cooler. All right. This certainly was their empire strikes back. I think yeah, yeah, I liked it.
I also
The trailer for Dunkirk looked awesome. It did look pretty insane. Like we haven't had a move like that in a long time
Well, and we just probably had one. I mean, it's a World War two movie when the last World War two movie
It's been a long time.
How long?
I don't know, but in my sense,
there's a big one like that that came out.
I don't want you to get mad at me about it.
Well, I don't want you to know your stuff a little better, I guess.
The Doug Kirk, I'm a little disappointed
that it's only a PG -13.
Sure, because, you know,
but you can push it in those,
if it's a period piece about a real war, they don't care.
You blow somebody's head off.
I
Nothing's ever gonna equal that that opening save in private Ryan. No, of course not Jesus Christ almighty rough stuff. Yeah, really rough stuff really rough
Well Pat I think we've come to an end here. You look like you're about to fall asleep. I mean, I almost did in the movie. I'm tired
Folks, I am on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh something I forgot to plug last week, but I urge you to check out
Well, is that I was a contributing rider to the White House correspondence dinner this
year, hosted by Hassan Manage.
I sent a bunch of jokes and then I got a bunch of jokes and it was very cool.
And I urge you to watch it not just because I have a couple of jokes in it, a few jokes,
but because I think it's an important piece of entertainment.
It's Hassan Manage talking about, you know, how bad things are on our country, how bad things
are with the press, how bad it is for immigrants and the people that he's trying to throw out of our country,
etc. It's a good, you know, a good 20 -minute chunk of comedy and has something to say. I urge you to
check it out. Yeah, he did an outstanding job and it was a nice piece of work and grads on that
for being a part of it. Thank you. Fuck Trump for not even showing up. I mean, come on, dude. Yeah,
it's pretty fucking perfect. The last president to not show up was Ronald Reagan in 81 and it was
because he was recovering from an assassination attempt.
That is true.
And he sent in a video of remarks from his hospital, but like comedic remarks from the
bed.
Well, I'm not doing too good.
I mean, that's what you mean.
Say what you want about Reagan.
I wasn't a fan of his policies or his viewpoints, but you do something like that.
You like the guy a little bit.
I agree.
You know, you got a little W Bush on Kimmel.
Again, that was never a fan of the guy goes on Kimmel. He's fucking killing. Oh boy. He's killing. I don't think I want to see that
He's well
She's the guy off when when he was trying to talk to the guy from 60 minutes about
He was asking about the wire taboo so then Trump was like well, you know the big story what we should be focusing on is the whole thing with
Wire tapping and everybody knows there's wire tapping and the guy was like mr. Trump. That's
been completely disproved.
And he's well, many people are saying it.
So, he was right, but it's been completely disproved.
Well, hearing it a lot seems to me
that what's happening is why it's tapping
and we gotta go after the real enemy
and he goes like, are you really saying?
He goes, you called this man crazy and sad
and on and on.
Do you feel the way?
And he's like, I think we're done.
I think we're done.
I've answered your question.
Like you seem crazy.
Strong arms, the guy out of the oval office.
He walks over to his desk to get away from him.
It's the president talking to a guy from CBS and he has a complete meltdown being asked
a simple question to where he has to walk away from the interview.
I gotta tell you, I can't peek my head out of the hole anymore these days.
It keeps me at just a always permanent simmer of anxiety and addition to everything else.
I don't know how much time we got left and I don't know if I can give a fuck.
We got time. We got time. I don't think anything
Like that drastic will happen. I really don't and I know a lot of people would disagree with that
But I just yeah, I mean he is taunting our enemies
Yeah, yeah, you don't like to see that. I don't I don't care for that. No
Well anyway, folks, so I'm sure he thinks if if they blow up
America, I think it doesn't have to do this fucking job anymore. It's clearly he can't stand it
Yeah, he doesn't seem to be enjoying it, right? No, no dad at work just aggravated he said the other day
I didn't know it would be this hard
He was like I you know I liked my old life very much and this is a lot more challenging than my old life
I miss it at times. What did he think it was gonna be? I don't know. I don't know. It's a shit job
Yeah, it's not a fun job for anybody. I feel like it's like it's like you do it like
It's like becoming a war hero or something.
Like when you look back on it, you're like,
I'm proud of myself, but when it's happening, it's hell.
Yeah, I don't know.
I feel like it's like when you get a riding job or something
or whatever job and you realize like day three
it's gonna be like, you're there till 11 p .m. every night.
Then he's like, fuck, why did I take this?
Why did I accept it?
In this case, he's running our nation.
Well, I say, I like to say he's running it into the ground.
Whoa, whoa, and I believe I am the first person to do that play on words.
I think probably so.
So I'll send you off on that gem of a joke.
Do you have a plug, John?
Do I? It's a great question.
No, not really. I have some stuff coming out soon.
I don't know if I'm allowed to announce it yet or not.
So coming soon there will be some things as far as live dates cluster fest in San
Francisco in early June. I will be performing at that on the third and fourth of
June amongst many other fantastic acts including one Jerry Seinfeld and
another Mr. Ice Cube. Good also. So very excited about that. And I've got the other
podcast on the other network, which is Farrell with my buddy, Kurt Brown, or we're called
emotional hangs.
Go check that out.
It's a completely different thing.
And is it true that ISCube will be doing haircuts at the festival in his barber shop character?
I heard that he will be, in fact, doing that, and then all press he does, it will he'll
be in character.
Great.
That sounds fun.
yeah all right well folks I'll tell you on Facebook what our next movie will be
we haven't decided yet I do notice several of you being like where's the new
episode it's already up we've already put up prisoners go go give it a
listen sometimes you got to hit a refresh you know what I mean and again I've got
to hold your hand every step of the goddamn way now people it wasn't shown up on
the app for people okay guys we're trying to figure out these I'm sorry I snapped
I didn't realize.
Ins and outs.
I'm not quite sure what's happening,
but we're figuring it all out.
But again, the Patreon's coming soon.
We will settle this Jurassic Depart,
Jurassic Park debate by watching the films.
And I think all of you, by the way,
for the just venomous lashing that I've just seen.
Nobody agreed with you on Twitter.
Couple people did.
Well, it'll probably turn to a roast of what we'll do
a commentary for one and three.
and each will probably wind up roasting slash defending each other's choice.
Anyway, uh, alright, that's the show.
That was a hitgun podcast.