Summer is here, and Bed MGM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MGM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Waiter, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only, games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as non -mustrable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning, or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Monthly 21 -plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberer, offer not available in all states
terms apply, see Fanatic's fourth book app.
Howdy folks, welcome to we'll see you in hell.
Your favorite podcast about horror sci -fi and fantasy films and sometimes let's be honest
other genres that we just decide to squeeze in.
Now you might be wondering why I'm delivering the intro with these pauses today.
It's because I realized just now if you do it that way, you don't have to talk as much
for the entire show.
It eats up a nice, Christ almighty, we're at 40 seconds already, I'm still in the intro.
Even if this is what you're doing, I don't know if I would tell them that's what you're doing.
It feels a little lazy, a kind of a low energy to start the show off.
I am a little lazy.
Okay.
I'm a little lazy.
I also think I'm a little teapot, short, stout, maybe not stout, but short, you know.
Stout means fat, is that what stout means?
Stout is like, round, like if stocky's a nice word for fat, stout is a nice word for
stocky.
Stout means like barrel chested, kind of.
Okay.
So it's like strapping.
So Shirley Temple was talking about her chest size when she sang that song bust. Yes. That's disturbing. I never knew that her little bust. Okay. That's enough. Pat, how are you, Pat?
Uh, I'm fine. I'm fine.
We're talking today about the movie Fire Starter, so I'd like to get on with the show and at the same time on, with the Joe's the Fire Starter.
Joe's the Fire Starter.
Remember Prodigy?
I do.
Was that even the right melody? I barely remember that one.
Yeah, that was it.
Liquid Fire Starter.
You know, for a band named Prodigy.
Yeah, some of the dumbest fucking music I've ever heard my real stupid. I feel like the lead singer was like looked like pinhead
Is that correct?
Maybe he did a video where he was dressed as pinhead. No, he looked like he looked like a
Hot topic jizzed all over his face. Yeah, that's basically what he looked like he had like a weird like
Yeah, hair cut like the guy that answers the door at the Emerald City. Yeah in Wizard of Oz
And then he had a bunch of shit in his face like a bunch of piercings and stuff
What was there other songs smack my bitch up was one smack my bitch up smack my bitch up. Yeah
What was the original single the big original single though fire starter and and that one we're later, weren't they?
Firestarter smack my bitch up was later hits
That's it. That's all I remember I thought they had a third
Third, I bet you they have like 18 fucking albums, man
They really know those two songs. Well, maybe those prodigy heads out there can
Give us a shout out. Now, do you think our fans would hang your head and shame play around it?
Do you picture our fans as prodigy fans? I?
Think some there's some overlap
There's some overlap. They probably is when we talk 90s rock it brings out these people I
Wouldn't I wouldn't call them 90s rock?
I mean, prodigy, I mean prodigy.
2000s?
Well, they're not rock.
They're like, dance.
Just real.
Whatever that truck was.
It was like, right, when, it's like, right,
when everybody thought nine inch nails was awesome,
I fucking hate nine inch nails.
You know, I tried to convince myself
at three different times of my life
that I enjoyed them, and I don't.
It sucks.
And finally, I was like, all right,
I'm going to sit down with this downward spiral
and really lean into it, experience the emotions.
I barely made it through this thing.
All the albums are 75 minutes long.
Yeah, he's whining like a bitch.
Yeah.
You know, a couple of good cuts.
I like fuck you like an animal.
But closer, it's called.
Yeah, I saw him at a festival and I left early, you know.
He's a talented guy.
I mean, the scores he does for things are usually really good.
Yeah, he did the score.
Well, he works with another guy when he does them,
but he did the score for the social network.
And it was very good.
But his music is, oh my God, head like a hole, down in it.
Yeah.
What's the one that goes, well, well, well, well, well,
by the way, that's a Stevie Wonder song, I believe.
But there's no song that kind of goes like that.
It was definitely not Nine and Snail.
There's the one that goes, well, well,
You're you're doing superstition did not maybe nine inch nails covered superstition
Is that what I'm thinking no definitely not
What you take on why we're talking about this here's another real polarizing band with people
Okay, what do you think of the red hot chili peppers? I thought we'd talked about them on here. Did we I mean maybe they
he's heavily auto tuned. So when you see him live, they auto tune every note, especially
on their two good albums, the California Cation, and by the way, the one after it, which
I don't think would be good if I listened to them again. And blood sugar sex magic I liked
at a time. Can't listen to those songs now. Oh, God, what trash like that? Yeah. Funk rap
when you see them live the man cannot sing to save his life. He's a terrible singer. So he's got
these songs with these great melodies and he's not hitting them at all because they're written by
other members of the band or Fruciante or whoever. You know, I see him and I think every time I see
Key this and like an interview or something, I go, I want to like this guy and then I realize it's
just because he looks like Justin Long and it's my affinity for Justin Long that I'm feeling.
just like the drummer looks exactly like Will Ferrell.
And it makes you think you want.
You want to like him.
Yeah.
I want to go on record, by the way,
saying I was the first person to notice that.
Long before it was ever, it's probably not true, Joe.
I think it was true.
I just didn't have the outlet platform to get it out there.
But I do believe I thought of it before anybody.
Somebody else made the up.
Nobody said the Justin Long thing.
I'll tell you that much.
It's true.
I don't see it as much.
Oh, look at look at the two of them. They look like identical. It's weird. All right. Now key to snow with like his bob cut and the mustache. Yeah. No, I know. Yeah. He's trying to be Iggy Pomp.
Trying to age like Iggy Pomp. Well, I mean he's he's aging very well. They're very well not going to be Iggy Pomp. No. Well, maybe he will for some people. I don't know.
There's no accounting for taste. You know, you know, I've never agreed with that.
I think there is I think there is some people have bad taste. That's true. What does an expression mean? There's
I mean, you can't say things are bad and good taste
No, it's saying like it's a like hey, you can't you know, you can't account for taste
You can't you can never tell what people are gonna like
Okay, you know, it's people like what they like, you know, regardless of what you think and
And I have a problem with that expression, I think some people need to be
reprimanded for what they like. I don't disagree with that. Right, I hope you
didn't. No, you know, you'd say we have the same taste then when it comes to this
subject. Yeah, Joe. Just trying to pull something out of you over there. I'm here. I
know you're here. I'm here. What's going on in your life, Joe? The latest is we
went to the, it's always sunny premier. Yes, we went last night. By the time this comes
out, it's going to be a while, but I was over served. The new season looks to be fantastic.
We saw the first two episodes. Really great. Very funny. Really great. Well, you guys have
probably seen them by now. So yeah, they were really funny. The first containing, I'm just
truly awful performance by Mindy Kaling that I think it's just she was unquestionably bad
on it and I was a little shocked at how big her role was in the episode was very relieved
it was not some sort of arc and they I mean not to spoil anything even though the episode's
aired she's gone by the end of it but I mean she brought zero comedic chops she didn't
sell a joke. She looked like she was struggling to remember her lines visibly in takes.
I was embarrassing. I'm happy to hear you say it because when I was, when we were watching
it, I thought I was being too judgy. And then as soon as you said it, I was like, no,
right. She's like bad at it. Like it was bad. I don't know how she had a show for so long.
I mean, I guess maybe she put more effort into her own show. I don't know. Maybe she was
stressed. I think she just had it catered something. So maybe that was, maybe she was
just like overworked on the office she was funny I mean she wasn't didn't have to
exhibit a great deal of range I guess but I was I was pretty shocked by it I don't
know she just seemed like she wasn't present or something yeah which but I will say
this and we can we can talk freely now because again the episode's already
aired and this is a spoiler her awful performance made the return of
Of Dennis Reynolds all the more glorious like when he was great came a very nice moment
Yeah, and basically like remover from the gang mm -hmm and takes his mantle up again
It was pretty fantastic. It was the yeah when he replaces the sex doll
The theater we were at applauded and rightly so it was delightful now. Do you?
My theory is that you don't like Mandi Kayleag
because you originally had a Kickstarter called the Paddy Project where you were
trying to find love online and stuff and then you felt that they took that idea
from you and kind of ran with it. Yeah I mean I see a lot of similarities
between the two of us are upbringings and I think she borrowed liberally from that
childhood of mine for her for her own. I don't know. I don't know enough about it. I have a
strong opinion. I know she was bad in this episode of television. I don't have a strong opinion either.
I just thought she wasn't very good in the episode. But I love both episodes. She didn't she wasn't
enough to ruin it. I will say this though, too. I feel bad for people that guest are on that show
because they're so overshadowed.
Yeah.
People love, including myself.
You love the regular characters so much.
Yeah.
And they've got such a tight rhythm
and they just, they know how to do it with each other.
And it's like, when you throw somebody else
into the mix, it often sticks out.
When they had Jason Sidacus on, he wasn't bad,
but he didn't make me laugh.
And I feel like a lot of that had to do with the fact
that I'm like, I don't care about Jason Sidacus on this show.
Right.
I like him otherwise. So maybe I would feel the same way about Mindy otherwise. I mean the Mindy project really wasn't meant for me
No, it wasn't really geared towards a guy like me. It's not Charles and charge. I
Like Charles and charge. I know and I'm not gonna apologize for it anymore. All right
All right, what are the stories he's going on hot dates? The kids have homework problems. He cares about those damn kids
And he puts them in front of himself quite often. Are they getting bullied?
He's got pressure from the parents to not fuck up with the kids, he's got pressure from the kids to be cool and let them slide on stuff, but but everybody loves him, but he's sort of is running this household and keeping the piece in the balance going between everybody, that's why it's called Charles and charge now Willie, and he's got pressure from the parents to not fuck up with the kids, he's got pressure from the kids to be cool and let them slide on stuff.
games comes in. Sure. More or less showing a boner through his pants every fucking week.
He's the one that comes in like, we got to go bang these Asian stuartuses. I just met,
you know, this is Asian. I wouldn't be surprised. Okay. But I mean, it gets, he gets pretty
specific about like what the women do for a living. Okay. Where he met them. Yeah. How much
she wants to have sex with them, it's, it's, it's, it's a, like, really a virgin deep
down.
No, he's just like, he's just like his dumb ass friend.
He gets it done.
As far as I know.
He lays the pipe.
Charles, I think, is more of, uh, of, uh, sought after ladies, man, that, but he's responsible,
but he's more of, uh, of, uh, of a hungry ladies man, but, but he's less responsible.
I'm listening to the audiobook of the game, not to use its techniques to meet women, but just because it's a memoir, which I didn't really realize.
It's not like a guide to pick up chicks. It's like about this society.
Yeah, so I'm finding it interesting. It's a gross book. It's like the dirt, the motley crew book, just makes you feel very unclean.
But I'm enjoying it and Scott Beo just made an appearance because mystery in one of his
protégés went up and got Scott Beo's girlfriend's number as a challenge.
I think you're drifting a little off the mic.
Just be careful.
All right.
Yeah.
That's fine.
We can keep going.
All right.
I like to let the people here behind the curtain a little bit.
Maybe I wasn't even drifting off the mic.
I could tell by the wave form, tech talk.
No, you were turning your head and your wave form was going down.
I didn't want people to be like, I can't hear Pat that well or something.
I don't want that either.
You're an important part of the show, Pat, whether you believe it or not.
I am.
So, Bayo comes in and what happens?
The mystery, who's one of the society's leaders,
In a challenge with the author of the book, get Scott Beos girlfriend's phone number in front of Scott Bea.
It's like an act one high point of the book.
They get Scott Beo's girlfriend's number and when they go into such detail on it,
that only then that I start to feel stupid for listening to this book.
But I've been enjoying it.
Now, do you listen to it like American Psycho style, like while you're working out, you know,
trying to roll walking around the neighborhood, but nothing serious, no?
No, and it's read by the author who's Neil Strauss, so he's like, I was drowning in pussy.
I couldn't get enough pussy.
It's like, all right.
He's just got, like, not the most lethario voice.
and it's all disturbing to me.
What else did Neil Strauss write?
I think he also wrote The Dirt, which is an amazing book.
And then you can tell he's trying to cover his tracks now, so he'll be like, I thought
two sisters on the same Wednesday afternoon.
And then I'll be like, but when I got home and looked in the mirror, I didn't like what
I saw.
So that like now when he meets a woman, she'll be like, oh, he's changed
So that part of it. I don't care for he keeps trying to cover up his bad behavior by being like I was too deep into the society
Well, I think that's what the arc of the book is. Yeah, I got this
Supposed it was a trophy. And I felt terrible. Yeah, exactly. You said I won but I lost but at what cost? Yeah, uh, I
Jumped ahead. Yeah, then he goes
was you're so eight no price tag higher than the one on that baby. Yeah. Yeah. Like that's
like a way the Sinatra would maybe say it. Who probably also had fucked two sisters
on many Wednesday afternoon. Yeah. He's one up to a hotel room with what he said is the
most beautiful woman he's ever seen. And he's about to make love to her. And her feet smell
so horrible that he has to run out of the apartment.
It's the book's just trash.
That's a weird, uh, her feet smell so horrible.
Not mad, sir.
You think that was...
He tried to class it up.
Yeah, do you think that's what that was?
And the publishers were like, look, dude, this is...
Come on.
I'm gonna just pray it was her feet.
I feel bad for the lady either way.
Yeah, I mean he uses names. I assume they're fake, but they'll be like gotta be right, but he'll say things like I mean
This was missed December 1986 like you can Google it
I couldn't believe I was on a date with Scott Beos ex -wife and you can find out who she is
Not anonymous sources
Oh boy, a lot of bio material in the book.
What is the obsession they have with bio?
I mean, it wasn't even written that long ago, but they talk about him like he's the toast
of the town or something, like Estevez and not at the Roxbury.
Look, he probably wasn't one point, right?
Yeah, but I think it was the Charles and Charge days, or the Joni loves cha -chi days.
I feel like after Charles and charge, he still had a,
remember when they did Scott Bale was 50
and not matter 40, whatever the fuck that show was called.
Yeah.
I feel like between Charles and charge and that,
he probably still had a nice run around town
where people were like,
Charlie's here.
Yeah.
You know, he was like the guy there.
How are you, Mr. Bale?
Yeah.
Block your calm, Mr. Bale.
So, no, no, is it a day, Mr. Bale?
That's a paper boy.
Yeah, because you would get suck your dick, Mr. Bale.
Hey, oh, Mr. Bale.
Mr. Bale, please let me suck your dick.
Mr. Scott Bale, look at me.
Look, look at me.
Let me suck your dick.
The paper's just ain't selling no more.
The publishing industry is crashing.
Yeah, I'll suck you dick for money, Bayo. It doesn't even have to be much money. I
Know you're good for it. Also now the the boy from Charles and charge came out and said that
Bayo had like somehow done something terrible to him. Well, I think it was a molesting thing was more like he like
Pulled his pants down to hookers. I'm something crazy
Which reminds me Joe why did you ask got got Bayo to do what he did tell him
to do what he did. Smooth as silk. Smooth as silk. He lives, he leaves it on the
writer's room. He comes here and gives me his leftovers. I do, I, I, yeah, working
thinking that much on a hangover. I am pretty spent. But how'd you feel today? I
I'm not gonna lie to you. I had a glorious day today. Now I leave town Friday as you
know for a month. And while the cats away, the rats will pray. Yes. I leave safe return.
town Friday for a month so I kind of cleared today and yesterday so we could
get the episodes done we need to get done yeah today and tomorrow excuse me
yeah so we get the episodes that we need to get done so I can also do my laundry
get my haircut get everything packed run any errands you know all that bullshit I
had to get conno certificate to fly from the vet all that crap but today I had
gotten much more of it done than I realized.
And I woke up and I was like, it was overcast.
That I liked.
It was beautiful.
And this apartment's great too.
Because if I shut my blinds and turn just the kitchen light on,
it creates an illusion that it's just overcast outside in here.
So I did that anyway to really amp it up.
Sure.
And then I just laid around with Con, man.
And we watched TV.
I went to the supermarket at like eight a .m. Okay. I was up at seven thirty. So I wasn't hungover
But taco stuff
Okay, baked a chicken
Made con is food for the next two days some of the chicken folks. It was delicious
Now was it because when you were eating it you seemed underwhelmed and it hurt me a little bit. I was well
Who's saying I'm not well?
Well, I mean, I don't know if I'd say I was overwhelmed, but I'm certainly well. I
I was thinking of a great, that's a great Seinfeld thing, type style thing.
Here's a great Seinfeld thing, and I thought of this last night, because when they were
given the speech before, they showed the first episode, like a couple times, I guess it
was Rob McLeanie during his speech about like what the show means, I mean, everything, a
couple times he said, so without further ado, right, episode one, and then he'd be like,
Oh yeah, he talked more. Yeah, and I just was picturing Seinfeld going, this is a do
You promise there wasn't gonna be any further. I do
Do you know what that word means? I
Don't think you a do
Calls it back at the end. Yeah, it's it
Well folks, uh, I bid you do walks off comes back. Yeah, here I am again
Yeah, see you feel jaded, don't you I said bitch you do the light bulbs start exploding over the stage
Oh shit, why don't you take us on down to
To pass movie corner Joe. Yeah
Well, I
Want to single out a show I mentioned last week. I want to single out Jenny McCarthy and Chris Harbick. Why'd you tell him to do what he did Joe?
I
Want to talk that you were really saying you watched single out again? No, no, no, no, no, I
Jesus quite finished. I'd like to single out the show
Sharp objects, so I've mentioned it last week that I had seen the first four. I've now seen the final four and
Not only was it fucking great
But by the end I would say it applies for this podcast
I won't reveal much more than that.
I'll just say this thing was darker than I even expected.
So for four hours it's basically a woman driving around drinking vodka.
Then things get like super thrillery and interesting and good and fucked up.
Great.
Really loved it.
Like it was impossible for us to stop watching it.
Amy Adams was killer in it.
I love Amy Adams.
Chris Messina again not great also did not need to see your erect penis or whatever the hell was going on
It looked like some sort of fake machine and who plays the Amy Adams mom when she's young
Isn't it somebody famous they grow from it? No, no, no the mom who plays the mom. Oh, Patricia Clarkson
Yeah, there you go. Wow. That's a fucking killer cast man. It was a very very good show. I liked it quite a bit
Patricia Clarkson was on
What's that show with the guy plead the fifth that YouTube thing plead the fifth do you
don't talk about sounds made up it's like some YouTube talk show with celebrities and
at the end of it is like it's time to plead the fifth and he asks people like racey questions
okay and then what if you don't want to ask him to say plead the fifth you can plead the fifth
to one question okay but that's the one where I believe it was Bert Reynolds they go who do
think the most overrated actor is and he goes Clint Eastwood. Like they kind of say some shit.
Yeah. Like, whoa, all right. Right. But she was on and he was like, who was the best kisser you
ever had? And she was like going off about this young dude that she made out with on a recent project.
Yeah. And she's like, he was so good. Oh, he's going to see this. He's going to hate me for saying it.
She's a saucy, she's a saucy lady. I like her a lot. All right. But then he also asked her who was the
worst. And he's, man, fuck, that was the good one because that's the gossip. But I can't
remember who she said, but that was actually a famous person. Well, at least there was
a lot of build up to no punchline at all. Well, I like to do it. David Lynch style. All
build, no payoff. Speaking of which, I, uh, I'm nine episodes into Castle Rock. By the time
this episode airs I will have finished the series. It's only 10 episodes go on. I don't know,
man. I was really on board as I said when we reviewed the first four or five. They started
to take a real dip. Some very, very self -indulgent episodes that kind of didn't further the story
by much.
Look, if they took a dip, I know I'm out because I thought they were boring as shit for the
first five. You'd be out, dude. Yeah. You'd be out. And now at the end of episode nine. Yeah.
There was a pretty cool reveal twist thing that happened with the story that made you kind
of understand what was happening. Right. But it was just two twin peaks. It was twin peaks.
It's getting too into like, there are many realities and they're this and it's like, that's what they
did on the new twin peaks. Yeah. And it's like, you know, I thought it was kind of interesting when
they did it on Twin Peaks. I thought it was much more appropriate. But you've got a show
called Castle Rock. Stephen King is executive producing. You've got the right to cherry
pick this guy's fucking amazing catalog of work. That's exactly what was frustrating.
Why are you turning it into like a David Lynchy and kind of thing? Make it a fucking horror
show like it's I think comparing it to David Lynch is too generous. I mean, it was just
slow. Well that's but that's exactly it was it but at this point it feels like I'm watching
the old twin the new twin peaks right where you're just like man parts of this were cool
but what the fuck guys we have one episode left what what where's this going yeah so I mean
obviously I'm going to finish it because it's only one more episode maybe they'll redeem it
in the end but I got to tell you to when I hear there's a castle rock anthology show coming
out. I get excited because I think every week it's going to be a really cool twilight zone
tale from the crypt type of horror story that happens in this weird town. Yeah. But now
because for some fucking reason anthology means an entire season, which is stupid. Right.
That's not anthology. I'm sorry. It's not. It's, that's what this was. So I'm like, okay.
I don't know. I got so people I'm disappointed. So you've seen 9 of 10 and 9 was
very good because it finally answered questions but the answers to the
questions I was like God damn it man this is all this was the whole time like
like that that's kind of cool and clever but like it's not Stephen King to me
there was one thing that people got very excited about and it didn't pay off
and I doubt that it will.
He says, they established that they think,
scarred scarred, pill scarred scarred is the devil.
And when, who's the guy that played the sheriff
and Sissy Spacex boyfriend, the old guy?
It's like, you're fucking mother is in a bad shape.
Why can't I think of the man's name?
I don't know. I never knew his name until this show. Oh, uh, Scott Glenn. Yeah. So the right stuff. Jesus Christ
He meets Bill Skarsgard's character in the in the woods. Yeah, and he's like, I remember you
Yeah, I remember that and he says
27 years went by and you have an age today and then all these theories popped up online 27 years
It's Bill Skarsgard. He also plays Pennywise. Is this gonna be a huge fucking it tie in bread? And I was like holy shit
That's why I would have gotten back in.
That would have been awesome.
Yeah.
But it doesn't appear to be.
Yeah, okay. Just a coincidence.
Well, I mean, I guess they could tie in
that it's the evil occurring every 27 years.
It's just not it, whatever the fuck.
I don't know.
Because they do keep hammering home this idea
of the tragedies of this town that have happened.
Right.
So maybe it'll sort of tie into it,
but I don't know, man.
I don't know.
Anyway, I saw black clansmen finally loved it. It's a great film. Great film. I thought the
only bit that started veering into cartoony care territory from me was the guy from
Itanya playing the fat clansman.
Yeah.
So I was like funny, funny, funny to a point
and then there's like scenes of such tension
that we don't need this guy farting
and falling out of a chair.
I was like, why are we letting this go on to this extreme?
In a few spots.
And I'm talking about one very minor criticism
of a otherwise fantastic moment.
That's interesting.
He didn't bother me.
My friend Theresa and I saw it and she said,
we both have the same opinion.
I mean, we were like, that was a very sad character
because you could tell it was a guy
that just so desperately wanted to impress
any group of people and be accepted
and this is the one he fell into.
So I just kind of took it like that,
but that's a fair criticism.
I'll have to keep an eye out for that the next time I watch it.
I even liked it most of the time.
I just like near the end there were spots where I was like,
all right, we could have rained that in a scotch.
Now did you also find the casting
of Nick Tutoro confusing as baffled even though I was prepped for it by you. I was baffled by it.
Just didn't make any sense. It makes no sense. Like put him on the force. Obviously you promised
this guy you'd give him a part for money or something, but yeah, put him on the police force.
He could have been the supervisor. The guy's like, I wouldn't go to that meeting. You know,
he could have been that guy. They had the old cop that was like the smart mouth guy. He could have
in the dirty cop. That was the racist. That was good though. Huh?
I think I was good though. I really was really good. Great casting. Great.
Great. I'm a fan of that guy that plays the chief. Yeah.
And I don't remember even what the fuck I've seen him in. But I just know that
I'm not your face. I was a big fan. Adam driver was great. Washington was great.
Great. I'm glad. Great time. Great time. Just it made me feel like it had
been a year since I had seen a very good movie.
Well, that's, yeah, and I felt like that, and that's why I was just really trying to drive
home the point of, to me it's the best thing he's made since like, it's up there with
like Malcolm X and do the right thing.
It's like one of his really great entertaining and challenging movies.
Sure.
And it was classic Spike Lee and I forgot how much I missed that because I hadn't seen it
so long. I really wanted them to kick the heavy woman, the wife and the butt at the
end. Wow, she's, I really wish somebody would have kicked her in the butt. That
character, she is as unlikable as every clansman is in that movie. She was, yeah, she was
the awful. Yeah, but she's a great actor. Obviously, it's the clan. They're all awful, but
they really like spent time making her hateful. The, she's a great actor. Yeah, she
That was like one of those performances where it was like if I was casting something I'd be like I would cast that lady on blind faith
Yeah, I and I didn't know where I'd seen her either. It's the first time I've ever saw her used to be
I'd look something up on IMDB now. I just go. I've seen her and something
Keep staring forward
Let me I think I have one guy evil speak as a horror movie from 1982. I believe
starring Clint Howard
Yeah, Howard's younger brother
The loose plot also the star of the ice cream man. I never saw the ice cream man. It's a really bad horror movie
It's had its moments. It started with a lot of promise
It's your typical kid gets bullied makes a deal with the devil to get revenge
Mm -hmm. I'd love to write one of those kind of horror movies that though, but they're always fun
I really like 976 evil. It's not a good movie, but I like it, but
But this is the same thing, basically, it preceded it, but it opens with this satanic cult
led by Richard Moll, bull from Nyquorn.
Yeah, okay, which, it's funny, I grew up on Nyquorn, so I always thought of him as a
comedy guy that sometimes did dark stuff, it's the complete opposite, like everything else
I've seen him in house Dungeon master this he's always playing like a fucking creep right, but but he's good at it
Anyway, I've always found bull a creep. I never liked bull a creep
I just I liked everyone on on that cast and bull was always kind of a
I didn't he didn't sit right with me. Freak me out a little bit. He was just dumb
I wasn't a fan. I didn't like his face if I can be honest with him. Oh wow
It looked like a thumb. Didn't like him. Wow. Sorry. All right. Well anyway, there's the Satanic Colton,
you know hundreds of years later at this prep military school,
Clint Howard discovers like the sort of remnants of this cult underneath his school.
They're old author and they're their old book of black magic and all that. And somehow,
Now, gets the computer that's been sitting down there to be part of the ritual to start
asking the computer, commanding it to answer him questions about Satan's stuff, and then
it starts to.
I kind of missed how that happened, but anyway, eventually he wants to get revenge on everybody
and he does, the kids are puppy at one point and they kill it.
That was enough for me.
I was on the devil side from that point on.
Sure.
Some very, very dark moments in the movie,
some very scary moments, freaky moments, I should say.
But overall, not a very good movie.
Yeah, kind of boring.
It was sort of like Prince of Darkness.
It's a lot of time in the basement with the computer
and the devil's gonna show up or is he and you know but anyway does the devil show up that
what's that does the devil show up I think I think yeah at one point Clint Howard's face turns
into like the devil's face and then it turns back or something okay we're at the 37 minute mark yeah
Well, why don't I shuffle us over to Joe's scary stuff?
Please don't.
And then we can get to our review.
Well, people.
Do I have one this week?
I thought I did.
What was I gonna do this son of a bitch?
What the hell was I gonna do this week?
Oh, I know what I was gonna do.
So I'm going to Japan, and Japan is a huge, huge video game district, and I'm very excited
about that.
And there's a game that I'm going to try to buy while I am there that was never made
available.
Well, it was recently made available in the States as a reproduction, but I, for the Famicom,
which is the Japanese Nintendo Entertainment System, and I have one of those coming in the
mail. As we speak, but there is a horror adventure game in the vein of Castlevania called Holy
Diver. I can only assume named after the DO record, which is pretty sweet and awesome. Hold
tiny dancer. See, I get you mixed up with private dancer. I'll be a private dancer, dance and
film. Do what you want me to do. My friend Nick used to do that at karaoke in college and it was,
it almost killed me. It was one of the funniest things I ever seen. It's a hot song. He would dance
around to it, too. He'd get into it.
Anyway, I'm super psyched. That is my mission when I'm in Japan, to find this old horror
adventure game, Holy Diver, and to buy it, and then bring it home and play it on my
Famicom that will be waiting for me because it came in the mail and
That's your scary stuff look up clips of it. It's pretty cool. There's also a new game out called the messenger
That's like sort of a nod to ninja gate and and the fantasy ninja type games on the NES and that just came out
I'll be purchasing that for the flight over to Japan to play out my switch, but that game looks pretty fucking excellent. So there's your scary stuff
Well, as always, I don't play video games that segment to meet drags a bit. Wow. I have
a scary stuff thing and maybe if I just keep doing the actual DVDs, we're talking about
on this show. I'll keep doing the segment correctly, but I watched the Firestarter documentary
on the screen factory addition, a fire starter,
which I will be selling immediately.
And you're doing the segment wrong, but okay.
It was like a 90 minute documentary
about the making of fire starter
and it contained this nugget that the director
who is featured all over this thing,
they don't really get any of the stars,
but they get like the stunt doubles and stuff like that.
Stone doubles actually had the best anecdotes of anybody in this thing.
It was a very boring documentary, but this guy Mark L. Lester, who directed it, he goes,
yeah, you know, I had met this lovely writer. They said, you know, a writer I said, I do.
And I gave him the book. And within three weeks, he had finished reading the book and had written
a 300 -page script. And he said, he included every moment from the book, basically just transcribed
the book into a screenplay form. And I said, we can't do this. We simply can't do this.
So he whittled it down and I said, now let's hang on to it and not turn it into the studio
for about a month. So it seems like it took you a long time. Or they won't think you even
tried on it and then you watch the movie and it's like yeah he didn't maybe he
could have used that month you were pretending to write the script to write the
fucking script and what a perfect segway it's it it was it's such a bad movie film
of this week firestarter which Pat and I only thought as we've discussed off
Mike that this was like a classic I thought it was like kujo or you know like one
that's not a classic, but one that, you know, is a really entertaining horror movie.
And then you also have the 80s, like, cheese factor that makes these movies really fun.
The music. So I think Tangerine Dream did the music. I'm like, oh, sweet. The score sucked.
Yeah, you want to have no fun costumes in it. I got one for you on that. When I first moved L .A.
I bought that fucking Tangerine Dream soundtrack, having never seen the movie for $30 on vinyl.
Yeah, having never heard it just thinking it's not good. How could it be bad? It fucking sucks
I sold it within two weeks. Yeah, it's not good. This movie fucking sucks. I
Couldn't make sense from the jump. It does not work and it does not make sense now
Let's start with this killer cast
You got Drew Barrymore. You got George C. Scott
I my jaw hit the floor when I saw George C Scott you got Martin Sheen now
Let me put a quick pause on George C Scott
Because I texted you when I saw it. I looked up ebber to review a fire starter, which was not a positive review
But he at one point he goes this movie has and he lists like 800 things and he goes and somehow it's still boring
One of the things he mentions is
George C Scott as a Native American child molester
And I watched the movie and I was like,
they don't mention he's a child monster.
So I googled the book.
He's not a child monster in the book.
So what?
Also, he's not Native American either, is he?
I don't know where Ebert got this,
but it was kind of nuts.
He is wearing a ponytail,
which can sometimes lead you to believe Native American.
The, look, you want to talk weird child monster vibes.
I texted you 20 minutes into watching this thing.
I was like, seems like the dad is flirting with his daughter the entire time.
I didn't pick up on that even watching for it when you said it.
So you might have been in a mood.
I was a little tipsy when I watched it.
But that scene was odd to me when he goes, I'm crazy about you.
And she goes, I'm crazy about you daddy.
And then they kiss on the lips. It's weird.
Okay. That's a weird thing to say to your kid.
I'm crazy about you.
And then she says it back.
I agree.
I don't disagree.
this this fucking movie all right let's obviously it's about a little girl
that can start fires pretty cool concept and there are one or two cool scenes
where Drew Barrymore does kind of go bat shit whatever but I mean it's
basically just carry it's carry though the ending is just pure it's carry
outside which is a less interesting carry because you're not and confund and
people you know aren't dying it's all these strangers dying and I am a Stephen
King fan. But this movie has my number one Stephen King pet peeve where he feels that he has to explain
it through some sort of government project. Yeah. Immediately takes you out of any horror realm you
could have been in. Now you're into sci fi. Yeah. There's like there's a method to the madness and
it's not just this freaky thing that's that's weird and confusing and it's the explanation just sort
makes the like so she can start fires with her mind her dad can control other people's minds
her mom can what was what was her thing Heather Locklear I can't even remember Heather Locklear
is in this thing for like six minutes on the case she's got uh oven myths lit on fire so maybe
she started oven fires or something but I'm like they all got sort of different powers
in the same family. Just like right there, it's stupid. Why did you read this book? No, I didn't
either. It's one of the few I have not read. But it just was stupid. Like nothing made sense seen to
see. Um, why did George built zero tension throughout except if I read that review, I kept waiting for George
he's got to molest the girl. Why did George, he's got want her to kill him at the end.
And he says that at the one point, like Martin Sheen's like, what are you going to do?
And he talks about how he's going to like, basically try to break her neck and kill her.
Yeah.
Because they're afraid she's going to get out in the world or something.
Which, that's like, if I, the only way I can kill her is to break her nose or there was
some weird, yeah.
He's going to shove her nose up into her brain.
And he said, as I will do that, she will like, set me on fire.
Hopefully my death will be quick.
And then I can bring her power into the next one.
I was like, what the fuck is this guy talking about it?
He just knows. He said in their explaining what he knows will happen. It was terribly written.
That's why when I saw that anecdote from the script, you can say I couldn't believe he turned in
the draft for the script in three. If you made a masterpiece, don't say it about fire starter,
everybody will be like, yeah, take the time. Also, why did they want to kill her? I thought they
wanted to use her as a weapon. I guess she got out of hand. I mean, she was blowing a lot of
shit up at the end. No, but this was before that. I don't, I, I, I stopped paying attention
to be completely honest with you. It's, it's, it was an insult movie. It was, it was
insultingly bad. And that's saying a lot, when everything you're discussing drew Barry
more movies. Yeah. She's been in some real doozy's folks. Yeah. A lot of directive video stuff
in the 90s. When everything is blowing up at the end, that was a well done stunt sequence.
there were some cool fireballs.
But yeah, that's all I can give it.
It's unfortunately early 80s though.
So every time you see a guy that's caught on fire,
suddenly he's a six foot five, 300 pound man.
Right.
Because they've got him wrapped in all the fucking,
you know, the flame protect retard and shit or whatever it is.
Sure.
But yeah, that sequence at the end was cool.
See in the fire, come up out of the ground.
Like the part where she was making the cop cars explode.
was pretty cool. But to me, it would just be so much more intriguing if it was just,
I have a daughter and we're drifters because she has this fucking weird power
that she can't control, and I have to protect her. And we don't know why she has it
or where it came from. That to me is so much cooler than it's kind of like Logan.
Yeah. A bit. Yeah. Well, that's what, and that's what Carrie is. Right.
But in this you I guess he was like well I already did carry shit all right
Well, this one she's from she's from the government. She's a girl little girl younger than Carrie
Yeah, this is up there for me with like maximum overdrive. This is this was bad
Stephen King's story. I have no interest in I just don't give a shit
You know silver bullet kind of has some camp value to it silver bullet is better than this movie. It's one of the worst
Stephen King adaptations
Uh, yeah, it's up there.
In fact, hey, what, or did we blow it out on this?
I was gonna say, what if for our next episode
is we discussed the worst Stephen King adaptations?
We've been doing that.
Did we already kinda do it just now?
I think so.
All right, I already got a Q and A setup.
Oh, okay, sorry, I forgot about that.
So our next one will be a Q and A folks.
Well, this bonus app will be a Q and A.
Yes, we might be one episode short in October guys. We apologize if that's the case, but we'll try to double up one week or something, but
My I'm just gonna be away. Oh
No, that's after this. Okay. Yeah, see I don't even know when the this comes out in like
Oh, Christ. I don't know what's happening October. I think I don't know I don't know God damn it
I think this might be the last week of September if this is if this
If this comes out before the last week in September and you live in Atlanta, please come watch
me tape my new hour. I'm shooting and recording my new hour. I'm releasing it as an album
exclusively to Sirius XM. And we're doing it in Atlanta at the Earl on the last Sunday
of the month. It's the, I believe it's the 30th or something of September two shows seven
and nine thirty and it's going to be a hell of a lot of fun. It's for the red clay festival.
Please come out if you live in the area and be a part of that. If this came out, if this
podcast comes out after the end of September, well, I don't know what to tell you, but just
in case I want to get that plug in.
Joe DeRosa comedy on Instagram and that's it for me.
I am at the Patrick Walsh on Twitter and Instagram.
I am running the television show Cool Kids, which is likely airing now on the Fox Network
co -created by Charlie Day of its always sunny in Philadelphia fame, starring David Allen
Greer, Vicki Lawrence, Martin Mull, and Leslie Jordan.
It's a very funny show, it'll be on Friday nights, 837, 30 Central.
I also appeared on the extremely funny podcast, Hollywood Masterclass, which is a spin -off
of Hollywood handbook hosted by my friend Sean Clements and Ben Rogers.
I listened to it on the way over, I was cracking myself up.
it's nice to be with an equal sparring partner in a podcast, you know, just a comedy equal, you know,
for once. Well, that's good that you found somebody that could dumb it down for you.
Oh, but Hollywood Masterclass is a spoof of like these Judd Appetite and all those different
masterclass things. That's great. And I got to come on and be like the comedy expert and the whole,
The whole guidance you get is basically like be condescending to this aspiring
comedian and
Tell you it was a real good time and I was I was I was really laughing you can get a free trial of stitcher premium if you want to listen to it
They got great stuff in there. I think are we on stitcher? We are I have no idea. I think you can find us there too
so anyway
Okay, Hoghouse page on Etsy for the merch.
Our live shows are October 20th.
To that night.
But hold on there, Patty. Don't think we forgot your shout outs for the month of September.
Here they are. Anthony V. Manito, AKA part of McFly chuck egg Sean Florent, Danny Rudd,
Natalie Hartline, Scott Connor, Leo Lopez, A. Ali, Catherine Russell, Emily Rock, Scott
Matthew Nick Mascara, Dave Del Greco, Kurt Ziegler,
Tegan McLeod, Chloe Paggett, Michael Wizard,
Whitset Parton, Matthew Ross, Scott Birchett,
Dennis Ormston, Travis Hines, John Wyzengruber,
Matthew McGuire, Angela Piccaro, James O 'Brien,
Kamani Claude Felder, Claude Fielder,
Claude, Kamani, Claude Felder. Was that right? Let me know. Let me know if it was right.
Your mic's off. Pat just said, uh, why did you tell Claude to felt, Felder felt, oh,
I get it. Feel like, felt, Pat's mic's off. But he's, people, even when the mic's off, he's
on Matthew Moon, Jay Fisher, Sean Lyle, John Hollywood, Jake McAlvane, Meredith McWilliams,
Gregory Hassel, Jesse Janicki, Mike Greenwood, Brianna Alcourt -Kyre, Alcourt -Kyre, Cole Rothacker,
Matt, supportive guy, Martin Brent. Oops, I said that last one wrong.
to Shay, Anthony Rodriguez, Chris Pazmore, or Passmore, whichever way you like it.
Casey Jones, Syngy, Dermott, Fuck You, Blade Runner, was a great fucking movie.
It wasn't, but I appreciate it.
Robert Haynes, Natalie Hatley, Will Pittman, Kevin McNanny, Kevin Driscoll, Jen Wessels,
Lewis Bell, Joe Hoffman, Scott Sweeney, Jay Miller, Clayton Stamper, Amanda Lancaster,
Michael Bolis, Ethan Gammage, Gammage, Gammage, James Gil -Rolamo, Derek Adams, Sean
Hall, Adam Loundsbury, Brett, Fran Gella, Toby Bell, Vincent Franks, Joseph Regoz, Steve
Burton, Anna Demario, Bo, just plain Bo. Just plain Bo. Aaron Roberts, Scott John, Ben
Tillman, Sarah Catherine, Paul Merchie, Scott Sweezy, Kara Konini, right?
Joshua Taj Bozeman, Chuck Andrews, Neil Dolby, Tom Laverick, Tucker Rouch, Rouch, excuse
me, Tucker Rouch, John Smith, Edmund Agabo, and Andrew, Brian Belaurier, Belaurier, that's
it, Brian Belaurier.
Guys, by the way, if I fuck your name up, it's please know that I'm not like making fun of your name in any way.
Uh, I just, I just have a hard time reading names sometimes.
Uh, Will Helms, Jennifer Anna, Bryce Buckmaster, TJ Mon Holland, Melissa Alvarez, Jake Bullock, trans...
Trans, what the fuck? Trans just religion, zero fuckstrawt .com, you fucks.
Hashtag Trans just religion, zero fuckstrawt .com, you fucks.
I guess go to that website if you want.
Matt Crawford, Jenna, Richard Deming, Brian Callis, Tim Drain, Michael Madrigal, visit Mr.
records in Lancaster, Pennsylvania, Richard Howenstein,
Britain, Fraser, Sean, Luke Physiock, Karen Kogariff,
listen to her podcasts, my favorite murder, and do you
need a ride? Tyler Sanderson, Joey Mueller, Shelby L, Nathan
Baskett, Gary Myron, Saira, Dylan Lar, Phil Borel, Edmund
Dillon, the Blackmagic Ninja, Scott Pauline Sirell, Patrick
Baxter, Daphne Kellogg, Ryan Martz, Tristan Avery, Hunk
McMasterson, Richard Ironman, Matthew J. Brown, Julia Gwire, charity Ferguson, Hank
Gustafson, Nick Walther, Alex C. Alexander Stein, Tyler Keatley, Emily Marvel, John B.
Wat, go to Johns, what the hell is that place called, Etsy store, Mory Benjamin, Nicholas
Burns, Alex Nelson, Jeremy Cool, Derek Clark, Alex Shipley, Sean Pinock, Amanda Leaves
and Timothy Letzo, Shane Nazarene,
Smelly Bubbles, Samantha Kiefer, I love you.
David Belinger, Hunter McDonald, Justin Bohagger,
Adam Benbenek, Mani Rios,
Demani O 'Rubio, Brandon Gash, Jake Farot, Rob Lines,
Jacob Barra, Jordan C, Maxwell Ashcroft, Ryan Kohler,
Barb Allen, Jonathan Face, Rebecca Cohen, Chris Bowen,
Mike Gibbons, Donnie Joyce, Michael Dawson, Jennifer Smith, Connor Denney, Steven Kapa,
Kaupa, sorry, Steven Kaupa, Kevin Swisterwitz, Anthony J. Guajardo, Annie Johanison, Timmy
Kay, Megan Leibbrand, Scott Blickensturfer, Alec Walker, Brett Wemmer, Tristan Carlson, Laura
Weston Thomas V. Hill Jared Blair Josh Small Ridge Ricky Verdugo Chris
Hooper Emily Florence everybody show Emily a lot of love for all she does
through the show because without her we'd be not dead and Sean L Dave
Comerick I'll be manual Kim D 'Angelo Jonathan Gillette Michael McBee Stephanie
power Sterling Abrego Diego Campos Stefan Stefan Musau Zoe Blascavick
Hazel Kivinslin, Dan McLeod, Lorenz Bunganiers, Alejandro Salgado, Papa Spusch, Tracy Reddington,
Sean Thomas, Amanda Alzamora, Jason Weibel, Mike Curry, Drew Spindler, Andrew Coveau,
Sam Mitchell, Aaron Millinowski, Scott Nolan, Jack Gertz, Ben, Misty Zavar, Molly Russell's
Dajne Wilford, Johnny Ferg, Mathias, Paljo, Mike Michelle Gold, Danielle DuWare,
Eric Lamora, Kevin Marcenek, Lawrence Anderson, Jared Smallridge, Will Pottoff, Natalie
Craig, Kyle Kinsland, Monty, Monty, Monty, Adi Babiduk, Scott Patton, August Raidel, Paul
Rage last name sounds Asian, was that one that was a new one? I don't know. Beth
Gaston, Julie Bailey, Michael Ayello, ILO, read aesthetic, and Max Unrath. You guys
are amazing. Thank you for your support. We love you. We'll see you next time. We'll
It's cool, isn't it?