Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer, or check out
our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz, only available at Bed
MDM Casino.
Spin on Spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as non -mustrable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning, or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 -plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberer, offer not available in all states
terms apply, see Fanatic's fourth book app.
Hello everybody and welcome to a brand new episode of we'll see you in hell now hosted
on the head gum podcasting network. Look, I could bend your ear off all day folks but
but it really seems like we should get on with the show
and in the meantime, on...
with a jump. I kind of missed the high pitch ones now. I know you're trying to
diversify it. I know. I don't give it any thought. It's whatever comes out of
me. I'm feeling a little lower than normal. Um, perhaps it's that we're
recording at 3 p .m. instead of our usual 10. You know, look at that wave form up
there. Look how big that Joe is. I think people like a variety. Yeah, I mean the wave
The wave backs me up. We're looking at it. We look at our sound waves up on the TV and that was a powerful Joe
Whether you liked it or not. I didn't dislike it. I just I just I start I'm starting
I'm noticing I'm anticipating the higher pitch one. Yeah, and then it doesn't go back through the archives Joe
You'll you'll find plenty there
I'm just gonna get right into it folks. I
As a homeowner, I have to pay property tax
It's probably not as well, it's probably not what you expected me to kick things off with.
Well, no, this is the new direction of the podcast is talking about business.
Yeah.
This isn't an ad.
I'm telling you about something.
So, look, it's Los Angeles.
Things are crazy.
I'm just going to give you the figure.
It's shocking.
Here's what it is.
I'm required every year to pay two installments of roughly eight grand.
It's a lot of money.
It's a lot of money, but you know, tax reductions, ideally, it kind of comes out in the
to wash, it doesn't, but whatever.
So, I pay them, the second I get the bill,
I'm like, all right, obviously I'm paying this immediately.
You don't want to get in trouble with the government.
So I paid both, you pay them on two different shifts,
about six months apart.
I get my confirmation on each.
And I get in the mail the other day,
notice of delinquent property tax, pink slip, whatever.
and it says that I didn't pay it. There was an issue where, as everyone has done a million times,
my account number and my routing number were switched. Okay. You know how you just don't know
which is which on a check? Yeah. I've never known. I always look it up and I always fuck it up. So
they are claiming we sent you an email to tell you you messed up one email. You did not fix the error,
and now you owe us $1 ,000 additional dollars as a fine.
Yeah, that's your...
A thousand dollars.
That's your government, there's your government.
That's not my government, Joe.
It's not mine.
But I was furious and I send out an email to people
and I place a call.
I'm just like, look, now that I got you on the phone,
which took hours, of course.
Yeah.
It's like Teresa.
You have never made this mistake
Where you switch the accounting number and the routing number. Do you feel that that's a thousand dollar mistake?
Right. You have a record of me attempting to pay it on time and in full. Right. It's not like I'm dodging it.
You don't know that I tried to pay it on February 10th or whatever. She might have thought you were pulling a castanza.
I sometimes forget to sign the check. Yeah, I mean. Rosanne did that as well. Yeah. Yeah. In the day.
Um, and
You know, I knew full well, even though I waited on hold for four hours, even though I sent these email.
I know full well. I'm paying that thousand. I know it. I know it. This woman can't give me a sir
I do understand but that's our path didn't even give me an understand she goes right into anger mode
We sent you an email. So you got the email I said well, I'm telling you I didn't get it and I searched my junk and I searched
Everything else and I don't have it right so
There was no
No warning given to me, no second warning.
You think there'd be a couple warnings
in the situation of $1 ,000 fine.
And in addition, I received a confirmation email
telling me my payment was accepted.
So you have to see why I'm confused.
Sir, just kept cutting me off,
wanted to get off the phone.
Not an apology, not an I know it sucks.
Not an anything to just make it better.
Right.
I said, is there anyone I can talk to who could help?
She goes, you can appeal it.
It's gonna take a lot of time.
It's going to have the same result. Now, I'm going to let you go. Thank you, sir, and hangs up the phone.
That is your government for you. I'm just disgusted with everything.
You saw the guy who got hired who body slammed the reporter. Yep. Got elected to governor. Yep.
Yep. You saw Trump push push the man out of the way so he could walk ahead of him.
So that I'm checked out, Walsh. I'm just I'm just I'm not it's not my world anymore. I don't live in it.
It's not, it's not our world. It's not, it's not ours and the whole thing about California starting its own
Country, let's do it. Who's arguing? Who's fighting this? I don't know. I know people with pride in America, I guess that's not anyone here
Texas has wanted to secede for many years
But they want us to see it to be like racist on their own or they want to have a
Wow, how do they want to do it? I know. Well, that's a good question
I don't know if they want to secede for the right reasons or the wrong reasons right Texas is a pretty conservative state
Aside from Austin, but I just know that they want to secede or there are many people who want to secede there
You know
This is you know
Well, what is when is a unified country ever gotten you anywhere?
It's never a good idea. I've never understood having pride in your country or America
Oh, I mean it's it's stupid and anytime a change happens somewhere
It's a revolt took place or something. Yeah, it's never because of a unified country. No. Yeah. Well, this was thing, you know our mutual friend Kumail
He was to Twitter like
Who can I just say something sure and this might be a little tabloidish. This might be a little sensationalist
He did that commencement speech at that college didn't see it
I saw a nice chunk of it
I texted him last yesterday. I texted him. Uh -huh. Hey, man, saw a bit of that commencement speech. Really nice work, buddy. Yeah. No response.
No response.
Now you were talking to me before this podcast started about another person not responding to you.
I mean, you're really kind of getting to be persona non -gover. I gotta be honest. I texted you yesterday at about 11 a .m.
Didn't hear back till 9. I was like, does everybody just hate me? I didn't know what was going on.
Well, I was truly busy, I don't know what their excuse is, but yeah, I mean, come out,
tweet it and come out lately and it's good that he's using his celebrity for good and
not just, you know, dick jokes, but he tweets out, real men don't body slam people.
Real men are confident enough to use words and ideas.
You know the things that separate us from animals, it's not a joke, it's just a true thing.
I get home, I've had a few, I had a real rough week, it's all the clouds are finally
lifting, I've been trying to staff my show, it's very stressful with riders, and I pop
off a tweet to Camel and I go, hey, here's an idea for you, Camel.
You got a body slam coming your way, buddy.
Very funny.
Send this, immediately racks up, racks up like 100 likes, people that know that we're friends
and we banter on Twitter now and again.
Yeah, that's very funny.
Kumail doesn't respond to the tweet.
Kind of leaves me hanging on it,
but he's made a dramatic statement
and he doesn't want to engage in cheapening it with jokes.
I assume he could have not even seen it.
I don't see my mentions till two weeks later.
Leave it as all hanging.
He left it, yeah, let me hang it.
That's fine.
But, and by the way, I don't care about that at all.
What I did care about is that for the remainder of the week
until I took it down and then beyond
because now I get DMs.
I want to back up for a minute.
Yeah, you said I don't care about that at all so you say and you're like better than me like I care about it
You don't care about it. Is that you sharp shoot me?
No, and and if I'm being honest, I did care a little bit
All right, sorry, go ahead a
Hundred mentions DMs etc. From people coming to Camille's defense
Then that's a threat, Camel, you don't have to take that threat.
Somebody should report him.
I hope you're not scared of this deplorable Camel.
He couldn't beat up an old lady.
God.
Then the things, so wait a minute.
An actor says something he truly believes in and you threaten to body slam him.
Do you think you're better than him?
And I was just reading this and I don't, I mean, forget living in America.
It's hard to even really want to live anymore.
It's listen all of you all of you shut the fuck up if you want to get involved go get involved
You're doing nothing on Twitter. You're preaching from your couch shut the fuck up all of you
Shut the fuck up. I
So tired of it. I start to to respond to like
Dick lick 69 at Twitter .com
You know with an avi of him, you know, sitting in a kiddie pool with a sprite
Hey, man, Camille and I are friends. I'm not serious. They're gonna beat him up
I'm also not gonna make jokes if Camille had been like, hey
This Manchester bombing is a bad thing. Yeah, I'm not gonna go in and be like hey speaking of bombing
I just saw your latest stand -up spec. Yeah, you know
It is a maniac who threw a reporter on the ground and everybody is okay
it's so and by the way everybody does it suck that a guy that became the
governor whatever the fuck through a reporter on the ground yeah that sucks that
shitty and we that's not when our leaders to be doing guess what there also was
a time where people fist fought it's not that big of a fucking deal Jesus Christ
people used to fight regularly it was a regular occurrence in bars at parties
at weddings, at funerals, people, fist fought.
It's not that big of a fucking deal.
It's an isolated incident.
It sucks.
Get your fucking pants out of the crack of your ass over it.
Where the only way I'll differ with you here
is that it is truly troubling
that he was then elected the governor.
Well, sure.
I think that that sends forth a pretty dangerous message.
Sure.
And then Trump the next day like, wait, wait a mug, baby.
Let's do it to get like the president approving of it is another kind of odd move
Not like in but not saying it's not saying it's not troubling. Yeah, saying it's not it's what you want to see your leaders to do
Whatever but let's stop fucking acting like it is it's it's it's the end of the goddamn world. Jesus Christ almighty
People think we're gonna live in this fucking utopia or nothing bad ever happens to what end guys
What do you want? What do you want to live in the fucking demolition man world where nothing goes wrong?
And then even the cops don't know how to react when a crime happens fucking Christ
I'm sick of it. I don't even want to live in a zoo topia, frankly
And the only one who didn't like that movie
Boring everyone was like, but did you get that it was about racism? Yeah, it was thuddingly obvious from the first moment of the movie
You know that's what kind of irritates like if an animated movie or like a dumb
comedy has the slightest trace of social commentary no matter how obvious or
poorly done everyone nuts their pants yeah did you get did you pick up on the
subtlety I did it's because it's because I'll say this again to all of you and I'm
not necessarily saying our listeners I'm just saying the people that fall into
these category if you're listening you have great taste and are probably excluded
from that. The people that do what you're talking about, all of you people, you think you're smart.
You're not smart. You're fucking stupid. And somebody did a stupid thing in a movie and it made you
feel smart. Well, you think you're special now. You're not fucking special. You're not special. You're
not smart. You're not insightful. It was made dumb for you to feel smart. You were duped. You were
tricked. You're a fucking moron. Go back on Twitter and fucking tell somebody making a joke that
That they should be banned from fucking social media. You fucking shits a joke to to my friend also. Yeah, exactly
To our friend. Where's my text back now?
These are busy people. I mean
What am I just sitting around here all day now disregard the fact that I am
I was gonna say I think so, but that's fun
Folks, our topic today, and we're not quite there yet, but we are going to get into
all things Twin Peaks.
And we're focusing specifically on Firewalk with me because it's been out, and a lot
of people have recently watched it because they are preparing for the new Showtime rebirth
of the show.
What has been launched?
I mean, it's premiered.
I didn't say it hadn't.
Or you said they were preparing—oh, oh, I'm sorry.
I thought you meant like show time was preparing for sorry. I misunderstood you I apologize
No, but they they put a lot of my friends have been like if you've seen this fire walk with me
I finally saw for the first time because show time put it all on their app. I see
Series in the movie
We're not gonna spoil anything although it's fairly difficult to spoil things from the I've only seen the first three
Joe's seen the first four, but we'll be spoiling fire walk with me because that's been out. Yeah fire walk with me
We'll be spoiled but not the new show
Before we get there, let's go into Pat's movie corner.
I have again been extremely busy.
If you can start, I'll try to think if I watched anything.
I've seen one or two things, I watched, oh, and I have something for Joe Scary stuff
today too.
I watched a wonderful documentary around Hulu called Batman and Bill go on it is about it is a
documentary about Bill Finger the co -creator of Batman that never received any credit
or money for the creation of this global sensation brand product whatever you want to call it how so
Bob Kane never gave him credit.
Bob Kane were orchestrated a contract where he could just say that it was always him getting
the credit and he never bothered to go back to the guy that he co -created with to try
to help him out.
So you got to read contracts, folks.
Yeah, after that founder and after what I'm hearing now, you got to read those contracts.
So it's a wonderful documentary.
It's very moving.
It's heartbreaking and it's basically about a filmmaker's quest to figure out how to get Bill
finger's name on Batman forever. Not Batman forever. Just the movie Batman forever. That's the
one he particularly enjoyed. Yeah, but so it's a really really wonderful film. I really enjoyed it.
It's like I said, it's a lot of different emotions, but there's a lot of hope in it. Not a word you
hear me use quip frequently. No. A lot of hope in it. And I enjoyed it quite a bit. I also recently
watched. Well, I purchased it best by the complete series of the original Flash TV show
from 1990. Who's in that John Wesley ship? I believe that is his name. You psycho. How
do you know the guy's name? It's a recurring joke. There's a guy who calls into the best show
with Tom Sharpling and is obsessed with John Wesley ship. He's a real, it's a, it's a real guy.
It's not a bit and it's he's obsessed with the work of John Wesley. All right. Well, this is John Wesley ship and he plays a great flash
And I bring this up not I know it's TV show, but the pilot for the TV show is a movie
And I thought it was a very cool flash movie was the first live -action adaptation of the flash
You all know how I feel about DC
I think it's worth checking out
I got the whole series at Best Buy for ten bucks, so you can't really beat that
And in interesting DC and news, Zach Snyder, on very unfortunate reasons, his daughter's
suicide has exited Justice League, and Joss Whedon is now the director of the Justice
League film.
Zach Snyder's daughter committed suicide?
She apparently committed suicide.
Just came out.
Jesus Christ.
So he had to exit the project, and Joss Whedon has now taken over.
So the guy that in my opinion made the last great Marvel movie is now at the helm of the Justice League
What do you think was the last great Marvel be Avengers the first Avengers? All right, so
So yeah, I'm excited about that. Okay
Yeah, I now that I thought about it aside from watching those first three Twin Peaks I have seen nothing and
and accept, I watched several episodes each of,
I watched several unbreakable commitments.
I have some friends who ride for it.
I just think it's a, I like jokes people.
It's a relentless joke machine
and I can't recommend it enough in that regard.
It's a very similar to a 30 rock.
If you don't like a joke, you know,
like just wait five seconds, and I respect it.
They do great, funny stuff, and I think it's a great show.
I watched the first Master of None, and you have to,
on the flip side, call that show a drama, I think.
There was no attempt at humor in the premiere,
and it took me a while.
I finally showed off my brain and just say,
I'm going to watch something.
I don't need to be angry if a comedy isn't funny.
Sure, I'm just good because that's the world we're living in now as well, but it is strange.
It is strange that these things are praised as like the best comedy, your transparents,
your master of none, but this has been discussed before. I'm not breaking new ground.
The Martian winning best comedy, you know, comedy is an art and I feel like we're cheating and we're
not being fair. That's all. I agree. I would agree with you. How about that?
I also saw, for the second time, I hadn't seen this since I was in college and I was very
high when I did see it in college, but I purchased the criterion collection, actually
I got this for Christmas and I just had finally watched it.
The criterion collection, Blu -ray release of Island of Lost Souls, the original adaptation
of the Island of Dr. Murrow, it is on Blu -ray, it looks pretty phenomenal for a movie that
it was made in 1932.
You're only gonna get so many pops out of the print,
but it looks great.
And Ion and Ion and I, I'm a big fan.
Yeah, I love an old movie.
Very, very cool movie.
H .G. Wells hated it, said it was a bad adaptation
of, you know, it was just a shock adaptation of his work.
Fans of the book agree that the movie,
the book is never improperly adapted.
However, that this is the best adaptation.
Look, it's 70 minutes people. You're in and out. It's an hour and 10 minutes. It's a black
and white. It's Bellalagosi. It's creepy. And if you read in the booklet that comes with
the film, you find out some interesting history about the movie, including the fact that during
original screenings people were vomiting. Boy, things have changed. Yeah, so that's pretty
A recommendation for a good buddy Ken Hanley, formerly a fangoria.
Ken, hello, we miss you.
He recommended I buy the screen factory edition of Black Christmas because I was saying that it was one of my favorite horror movies.
Per his save so when I was in a very drunk state, I did buy it.
I received it in the mail for getting that I purchased it and it is a beautiful 2K restoration of the film.
tons of very cool special features with interviews with the old cast and
everything like that. Scream Factory really does it right. If you still haven't
checked out their stuff go check them out. Great. Yeah. And now I wish I'd have
a thing for you like like somebody suggested one that was good and I'll have to
look it up and find it. It's on the Facebook page. But it's all right. We'll just move
on. Well this is where it would go. Yeah. Then I could kick off this part with
your thing. We're little by little finally landing on kind of a format of the show. Like the way we
just did it by accident actually makes sense as a format of the show. Yeah. A little talk,
movie corner, scary stuff, into the discussion of the film, but somehow we've never done it correctly.
The last couple times we have, we just forget sometimes. Yeah, that's true. We are going to talk about
all things, Twin Peaks. People, at least if I'm looking at Twitter, hated it. The
new one? The new one. Well wait, let's wait for the new one. Let's start with Firewalk
with me. No. All right, do you think? Well, I mean, yeah, I mean, I think we've discussed
the show on here before. My thought of the show itself is you have a pilot that ranks with
some of the best of Lynch's movies,
especially in its unedited version.
You got a first season that's pretty phenomenal throughout.
Lynch leaves and the whole thing falls to shit.
I mean, I didn't feel they had anywhere to go but up.
The finale of Twin Peaks is pretty good.
But I mean, they just completely lost the way.
There was a six episode arc
about installing Venetian blinds in season two of Twin Peaks.
Isn't that in season one where it's the eye patch lady
keep talking about our Venetian blinds. I believe that's that's got to be two but maybe I'm wrong.
I think that's one man. But look season two has the multi -episode arc about mis Twin Peaks,
the beauty pageant, you're like, what the fuck is this? The thing with season two at Twin Peaks,
it's not without any redeeming qualities. It's just very apparent that the guy that was behind it,
the mastermind has left. And now it's a bunch of people trying to figure out what they
think David Lynch does. And it doesn't work. It's not. He is the only one. I mean, there's
been lots of attempts throughout the history of movies and TV for people to emulate it.
And it doesn't work. I mean, the man seemingly so normal is insane. And I always wonder like
what is his day -to -day life like? He's into meditation. Is there a drug element that we
he don't know about David Lynch.
He seems very innocent to me.
And he looks great.
He was in this new one.
He looked like he looked 20 years younger than he is.
He's a big smoker right now.
Yeah.
I mean, I should say big, but like in the bonus features
on the Blu -ray, he's smoking really consistently.
Which makes it even weirder that he looks so great.
I'll tell you this, the Twin Peaks television show
in its original form, for the most part,
worth checking out, it's got its highs,
it's got some very low lows.
But overall pretty good loses its way. I would say nearly impossible to get to the end of season two and eventually
You know my girlfriend just rewatched it or watched it for the first time for her and I was with her
Until we got into those season two lows and I basically told her you know
You're fine just watching the finale and watching the movie and that's what we did well
Yeah, that's the unfortunate thing and it's and it's only an issue
It's more an issue or not just an issue of people trying to emulate Lynch
It's an issue of bulk. It goes from an eight episode first season to it like a 22 episode second season
These are hour long episodes. I mean, it's too much. Well, I mean this showtime Twin Peaks is 16. I believe I
Love it. I do too. I do too. I love it. It's so far
So but then so that brings us now Lynch returns at the very tail end of the series and then says folks
Rest easy fans the show there's a movie coming fire walk with me
Oh, it's a reference to the poem in the thing with the Laura Palmer and Bob. Oh, this is exciting. It's gonna be a prequel
It's gonna tie up all the questions and loose ends and he drops this movie a movie that and I've mentioned this recently
The day in a ghouls podcast Quentin Tarantino said after I saw firewalk with me at con
David Lynch had disappeared so far up his own ass. I never wanted to see another David Lynch movie ever again. Yeah
Yeah. I don't think Tarantino was at a point in his career where he should have been taking
shots at a master like Lynch. Sure. But um, but I don't think that's a far off statement.
No. No. Uh, I watched, I rewatched Firewalk with me again recently. I did too. Uh, I remembered
it being frightening and interesting when I saw it when I was younger. Again, probably in
a drug -induced state of some kind, what were your initial thoughts upon rewatch?
It's a flawed movie.
I watched the deleted scenes which were cool and almost, you know, almost a whole other
movie in themselves.
I think Lynch, my buddy works at Showtime and no one at Showtime had seen the new show.
They just knew like his original thing was something like 40 hours and he was like,
I'll edit it. You'll get the episodes. Just leave me alone when they left him alone right shoots way too much.
Um, I don't know if he thinks things make sense. I mean he he's had movies that do certainly.
But they're challenging fire walk with me to me makes sense and I think it's gotten a lot.
Uh, better treatment by critics as the years have gone on because it is like a frighteningly
the accurate portrayal of like what a woman must go through when her father is routinely
raping her.
If you look at it as just a portrayal of that, it went to places.
The show kind of only hints at that.
The show was always this weird mix of comedy pasted over this story of a teenage girl being
raped by her dad a couple times a week.
It was that.
It was, it was schmaltz.
Yeah.
It was mellow drama.
And I felt that all that had been taken out of the movie when we talked about it on Dana Gold show
Dana Gold said it went from being the show that was weird and funny and scary and the thing that you felt like
It was just for us if you got it you got it if you didn't tough shit to a movie
But it was two hours of hearted
That's pretty much
What it was I mean what I always like the most about David Lynch is
the darkness I think that
He goes to places that no one else does so fire walk with me especially in watching it again
I mean there were several moments like and in the reboot by the way where Heather and I would be sitting in the couch
And just look at each other after a scene like Jesus Christ
Like it's really unsettling stuff. There's about a 30 -minute scene in the Roadhouse bar where that fat guy is like, you know
Trying to fuck her and this yeah that to me is is
It's unbelievably strong, powerful, great filmmaking, it's not something I want to sit
and watch all the time.
That brings me to one of my problems with firewalk with me.
Because if you'll remember when we were shooting the pilot, you're a pilot, yeah.
Which I think critics will compare to firewalk with me.
Right, right.
It's sort of a multi -cam sitcom version of firewalk with me.
Right, yeah, I agree.
Well, they're laugh with me, I'll call them.
When the first or second day of rehearsal, I came in and I said, I rewatch Firewalk with
me last night and I said, I'm done.
I'm done.
I don't think I'm going to watch the new Twin Peaks.
I said this to you.
And you said, why?
And I said, the God damn fucking movie, it's too much.
And it was just too much.
And that brings me to one point that I had, nobody was want to do respect to the character
in the actor. Nobody was watching Twin Peaks going, I want more jock. I want more jock.
Can we have a storyline that really is jock heavy? That's true. And then they make
the storyline and then it's him like fucking Laura Palmer and red lights and it's just
like, whoa, it's like, I don't want to see this. It's disturbing me. And then they didn't
get some of the biggest names from the show. You know, that was the other thing as, you
know what's her face wasn't in it.
Lara Flynn walked.
Lara Flynn boil.
I mean, I didn't care.
Why wasn't she in it?
I think it was, she just was like, yeah,
I'm gonna go be in like men in black too
and all this other big shit.
I, she was in like the temp and doing her own starring.
Remember the temp?
It's like basic instinct, but with a temp.
Oh God.
It was one of those early 90s erotic thrillers.
Sounds terrible.
It wasn't great.
She's in Wayne's world as well.
She is in Wayne's world.
Runs into the car.
Yeah, I think it looks that they're long been rumors that Larathon Boyle is not the easiest person to work
Yeah, so I feel like the fact that she and Michael Anderson are not back in the new series is
Proof of that, you know, I feel like the only way Michael Anderson is not in that know who's Michael Anderson
He's the the the little person that talks backwards. Oh, okay
I mean the only reason that I can do so he is not in that is because of some kind of contractual dispute or something
Is he alive?
Yeah, he took the Facebook to be like,
yeah, well, people were being like,
you are Twin Peaks, why aren't you in it?
He's like, the producers seem to think differently.
Wow.
And I was like, how no offense, how stupid do you have to be
to not just go do the fucking show?
What is he doing?
Is he a realtor now?
I don't know.
So I'm just like, this has got to be,
that he probably has for like a million dollars.
We're not this isn't really spoiling anything about the new show, but they they spend a good amount of time in the black lodge
And the fact that he's not there is like you're like, why is he not here? It clearly wasn't a writing choice
Right, he's not here for a reason anyway, and you know, I saw
Bob who they cast Bob so in the movie we learn that and it's sort of
Up to interpretation in the movie right. I think Ray was
Should have been nominated for an Oscar for Firewalk with me. He's incredible
She's great.
And what's her name?
Cheryl Lee, for God's sake.
She's great in it too.
Just a nightmarish state of mind
to have to get into every day for both of those actors.
But, no, what do you think?
Do you think that Bob truly is a demon
who possessed her father and raped her through him?
Or do you think it was an excuse?
No, I think it was a demon that possessed
her father and raped her. And not that they have said anything in the new show. Yeah. To say that
that's what's going on. Right. But I will say the new show is going to such crazy areas that I'm
like. I'm like, yeah, that's that's what happened. Like, like Bob is some kind of, yeah, Bob. Well,
it's, I mean, look, you're going to watch the show. You're going to know this five seconds in. Bob
No, I Didn't get that at all. Okay, maybe I just missed it. I thought the kind of tan Bruce Campbell looking
Dale Cooper is in a way possessed by Bob. Well, he might be I think that's what we're supposed to take that's most what I tell
Let's revisit that. Let's finish fire walk with me and let's revisit that because Bob is this is the good part about fire walk me
Bob is a big part of it
He's very scary. Yeah, he's very creepy and Bob was like a sound guy. Yeah, that David Lynch was like you look creepy
You should play the part now. I was I was bothered. He was not in the reboot and I learned that he is dead
Victor Silva. He died of AIDS. Oh, boy. That's terrible. Yeah
In fact, right like right after Firewalk was me. Yeah. I mean, he
I there are still times when I close my eyes and see Bob approaching the foot of the bed in Firewalk with me
Yeah, and this is my hats off to David Lynch even though I'm not a big fire walk with me
fan the man is a master with the camera and sound absolutely I mean he can make
and he can make any shot horrifying well I was gonna say it's literally like
16 year old girl's bedroom right and it's just this guy behind the dresser no
makeup he's not like creepily misshapen in somewhere it's just a guy behind the
dresser. Yeah. And for some reason it's fucking horrifying often discussed on the show the the
Winkies diner seen in Mahal and Drive when the homeless man comes out in broad daylight from
behind a dumpster. Probably the scariest thing I've ever seen. Showed that to two of my
my friends Brian and Crystal who you know showed that to them the other night when we were
quite a few in the bag. We had a few drinks and neither of them had seen it. And I thought
Crystal was going to run through the wall like an old cartoon character.
You showed him the movie or the scene?
We were just in their living room and it was late and I was like, have you ever seen
this scene?
It's the scariest thing I've ever seen in my life.
And they were like, no.
So we put it up.
We found the scene on YouTube and put it on.
It was nice in the reboot to see that guy who tells the story at Winkies.
Yeah.
A lot of old faces back, a lot of new faces in the reboot.
that reminds me of the old Oscars joke of Johnny Carson. He was hosting the Oscars. He goes,
nice to see a lot of old faces on the crowd tonight. A lot of new faces too. Hillers,
a lot of new faces on the old faces, frankly. It's great. Now, let me ask you a question. How long
If you've been working on that Carson impression. It's just just now just now. I used to do it all the time
Was it great? Is that what you're saying? No, I was making a joke about I was hoping you'd be like every night
I stand in the mirror for 20 minutes. No, no, I've done it before I used to love doing with my my dear friend Dave Feeney was my
co -worker years ago
We used to love putting three like 70s names together to do that car and act thing
So we'd be like Lonnie Anderson
I don't know why it was funny, but it was funny.
Would you have the punchline too, or would you?
No, just the setup.
Just the setup, yeah.
I'll tell you, I often go back and watch those old Carmac things,
and on YouTube and stuff, they're so expertly written.
Yeah.
It's enviable.
You're like, Jesus Christ.
These are so tight.
Yeah.
Anyway.
The end of fire walk with me wraps up in my opinion, especially for something like twin
peaks, a little too perfect of bow.
All the hints and weird clues that you had seen through the series, the talking bird and
who was in the cabin and how was Shelley's husband involved and all these things.
It all just kind of finally is laid out.
This is exactly how it went down.
This is where she died.
This is why the body washes up on this shore.
blah blah blah. My question is this. Do you think that Lynch knew all along? This is exactly
how it's going to end? Or do you think he, as he went, he's like, wouldn't it be weird
if we put a talking bird in? I'll figure it out later. I wouldn't be surprised either way.
I think that he probably did not know what was going on. But most people's grievance with firewall
with me is that we finally thought we were going to get some answers and we didn't. But firewall
What more with me does answer quite a few questions.
Well, it shows you killed her finally.
Yeah, but her dad.
But they also get the dad in custody
in season two at some point.
Yeah, so I don't know.
I'm confused.
I mean, I think most people who don't like David Lynch
are approaching it from a, tell me a linear story
that I can understand at all times.
Most of the tweets I saw on Twin Peaks,
I was like, well, you're dumb.
Or this isn't for you.
Like, I sit down just expecting to have a time,
almost like I'm in a dream.
That's really what he's doing.
He's kind of recreating that feeling of a dream.
You lurch from one thing to another.
Maybe it will make sense.
Maybe it won't.
Maybe it does make sense.
Maybe it does.
I describe every Lynch movie as a fever dream.
That's good, Joe.
It is good, isn't it?
Yeah.
That's how I describe them.
I'm serious.
Yeah.
I mean, I even even even the the one about the guy on the tractor. It's just a wild. I love a straight story
I never saw it. I'm just kidding. It's pretty straightforward, right? Oh very much. It's just rated G
It's rated G but that guy Richard Farmsworth who shot himself
Not in the movie
He was in like unbearable arthritis pain
I mean, it's not like, I don't know why you why you were just laughing about it, because it's this beautiful
This this man who has just a hellish brain creates this beautiful
G -rated film that's like uplifting and then the guy got you to self right out
No, Farms with also great and misery. Oh, yeah, it's like the old sheriff, but
Yeah, straight story is an amazing movie that two few have seen. I love that movie. I
I will check it out.
It's on the David Lynch collection on my Showtime app,
which, by the way, consists of fire walk with me
and a straight story, it's its own tab.
It says the David Lynch collection.
Yeah, Showtime seems to kind of just kind of cobble
together whatever they can get.
I watched the premiere, that is another thing
I watched the premiere of, what's the new show
about dying up here?
I'm dying.
Is it any good?
Not really, man.
And I mean, it's the opening is, is the buggy nights rip off.
They're walking it, walking a drink through the club.
And then like if they didn't ride in the script,
we're ripping off buggy nights, they're not playing fair.
It was the exact same opening tracking shot,
introducing people in the 70s club.
I don't know if I can sit through another show
of like comedians going, when you're up there,
it's the greatest feeling in the world.
Like it's like, for Christ's sake.
And you're a comedian.
I haven't done it in too long.
I can't even really refer to myself as a comedian anymore.
I go in and out of it.
I've been out for too long.
But you're a comedian who is sick of it.
I can tell I make my bread and butter.
I know.
You know, I don't mind saying.
Comedians are sick of these shows.
So what, how in the world could people across America
not be like, I'm not watching another show about comedians?
There's more shows about comedians than doctors
or lawyers or cops.
Now I was sort of, I think sort of close for a role in that show.
Okay.
Which one?
I'm dying up here.
Which role?
Oh, there was an asshole comic and I was pretty close on.
Andrew Santino role?
I don't know, because I haven't seen the show, but you know, and reading the excerpts from
it and stuff, I enjoyed what I read and I met some of the producers that were very nice.
My friends are in it.
I'm friends with Andrew, I'm friends with Al Madrigal.
So, you know, I wish everybody well with the project.
I hope it goes well for them.
And like I said, what I read seemed pretty good,
but I will say this, comedians are ego -fucking -maniacs.
The last thing they need is something else celebrating them.
Their whole life is celebration.
Yeah, you get on stage, you're celebrated by the audience.
You're getting laughs for saying things
that people would get fired from their regular jobs
for saying, you're hooking up with people
that are so far out of your fucking league,
it's laughable.
You're getting overpaid to do essentially nothing.
Like, the last thing comics need
is another one of these fucking documentaries.
Like, it's just so tough out there on the road,
and you don't know what we go through in it.
Shut the fuck up.
Seriously, I mean, Jesus Christ.
The truth is, you don't know what anyone else
in the world goes through.
Like, what are you talking about?
Is it tough on the road?
as some lady wakes up at 5 a .m. to take three buses to our 7 a .m. Walmart,
clocking, to feed her six -kit, shut up. And you sit in a hotel room for 18 hours
and then talk for 20 minutes and leave. And here's the thing. If you don't want
to do the road, fine. That's fine. I get it. If it's not for you, fine. Yeah. Stop.
It doesn't have to be committed to tape. You're polite. Yeah. I mean, this is
the real thing of like this girl can't quite connect. And then they're like,
but why don't you talk about yourself?
So then she's up there and she's telling a few jokes
about this and that and then she's like,
let me tell you about what's really going on
and then everybody's howling laughing.
I mean, I've seen that scene 40 times in the last year,
probably on television shows.
It's not a bad show, it's well made,
I wish them well as well.
I'm gonna watch episode two.
I just kinda feel like we've hit a real saturation point
with comedian shows.
Can I share this real quick?
Yeah.
They did this to, I showed this on, I was on a date recently
and I showed this to the girl.
I said, uh, this is one of my favorite things
ever to see in a movie.
For those of you at home that can't see me,
I'm miming a phone right now.
It's really convincing.
Yeah, I love this gagging movie, ready?
Baby, baby, I love you.
Everything is gonna be all right.
We're gonna sign the deal and it's all gonna be great.
Okay, come on.
Would I leave you hanging?
Absolutely not.
Okay, kiss kiss. Bye -bye. Click.
Shmuck.
Yeah, yep. Now she said that's only been like in three movies. I'm like, no, that is like a classic.
It's in there all the time. Yeah. Yeah. All right. Well.
Anyway, new Twin Peaks, like we said, we're going to keep it spoiler free.
This is the best spoiler free review I can give of this new TV show.
I've watched all four episodes, Lynch, not only Lynch, but Twin Peaks is back.
I ruled the day that I said I was going to tap out.
I regret saying that the show is fucking phenomenal.
The one thing we will say because Pat sort of gave it away, and again, this is something
you learned very quickly.
There are multiple agent coupers who are very, very different shades of personalities.
One of them might be possessed by Bob, apparently.
I need to go back and rewatch that now.
I think so, by the way.
I don't doubt it.
I might have just missed it.
Yeah, there's also, this hasn't happened to me in many years.
There's also a nude scene that got, I mean, the woman's body was magnificent.
It burned into my mind that coffee girl.
I had to, are we talking the white girl or the black girl?
Well, both are astonishing, but they did.
I love that Lynch is still doing it.
I mean, when, so when you're seeing that, let's just be gross.
That coffee scene because she comes in all nerdy and everything and then she strips down and you're like holy shit
The the girl in the in the glass room. Yeah. Yeah, I don't know why you're calling it because she brought coffee
She brings the coffee, okay
I wouldn't I wouldn't watch that scene and refer to it as the coffee scene no the coffee girl
I'm saying okay, she always brings the coffee. You know, she can I freak you out? I know she's like a child actor
She was the little girl in the hand that rocks the cradle. I never saw that so I thank God
I never saw it. This was my first introduction to her. I had to look her up and see that but that the
The the nudity in that scene was really something spectacular
It and Lynch really always takes me back to like the the junior high days where like you're seeing a button a thong
Then you're quickly seeing the butt then you're seeing a side boob and it's all just planned beautifully
like, it's way more effective than if she had just stood there full frontal
mood. I agree. The rest of the reason it's staying with you. It was like, I agree.
It was just a, he does well with, I mean, who hasn't cranked it out 45, 50 times to
that scene in Mulholland Drive between the two ladies? That's a rough one to just sit
there with the pants on through. But yeah, and then there's the, there's the black
girl. My was ridiculously hot, but she does play a prostitute. So it's a little less
of a switch. Yeah, but I mean, but she's that's the thing that's the thing is that you see you're seeing
her and I was like, wow, and I was just like Lynn Lynn, she'll indulge that like 80s teen movie
porki side of you. I was looking at her and I was like, look at that butt from the side. Yeah. Oh my
God, Becky, look at her butt. I was very into it. And I was like, I'd like a better look at that butt,
But I probably won't get it because we're in a modern day and nudity isn't really in movies and
TV. Right. And also your fiancee sitting next to you. You can't pause it. Let's go out of
microscope. But then Lynch cuts to her walking down the hall full frontal naked because he knows
people are going to want to get a better look at this butt. Yeah. It's right. And I said thank you
And then we cut back to her in the shower and, you know, I say once an episode, Joe and I
get a little gross. But it's a celebration of the female form. And Lynch makes you not feel creepy
about it. Except, you know, he was very criticized by Cisco neighborhood and blue velvet for having
Rosalini walk in completely naked. They found that exploitative. But I just, he's a man who knows
what he's doing with with sex and nudity and with everything else. It just feels good.
The best review I read of the show is this is not or this is not an effort in nostalgia.
Twin Peaks, the revert, the return is a celebration of Lynch's entire career. You're not just seeing
elements of Twin Peaks. You're selling elements of everything Lynch has ever done, including a race or
head, which I agree. A lot of eraser had. A lot of weird eraser had moments in it. The show is
terrifying. It's funny. Yeah. It's erotic. It's unsettling. It's confusing. It's everything
that made Twin Peaks good. I would say I would dare say it's better so far than the original show
only because now they're on showtime and they can push the limits more and get even
and fucking crazier.
So I do really love it.
I mean, the Lynch is still using like music
that would be, you know, like Nicholas Wyending Reffen,
who we have disagreed on a great deal.
Who?
Nicholas Wyending Reffen.
He did drive.
He did, you know, I like his music.
Well, yeah, I'm saying it.
Wait, is he the director?
Yeah, he's the director.
I don't know, sorry.
No, I like his directing.
I don't like, I think even the guy that did the music
and drive, sorry.
No, well, I mean, that guy is a big Lynch head.
Like, there's a lot of David Lynch in his movies, the way he sets up a shot, et cetera.
Um, but, you know, he's always got the coolest, hippest music in his movies.
And Lynch, who's like 70, just does the same thing.
Every, like, incredible music, there's, like, weird, like, metal in it.
There's weird, uh, you know, of course, like, Beverly Brothers type shit, the chromatics
play a song.
I think that was the chromatics at the end of one of them.
It was.
Every episode ends in the bar.
What's that bar called?
The Red Hook or whatever.
Yeah, I love those those two they were basically ripping off the Eveline brothers, but I just love the full song
They were great. Yeah every episode so far at least ends with a band playing in that bar
Yeah, and they just it's they're performing in the bar for the characters in the show, right?
But he just ends with the actual performance instead of just going to black with
He lets the credits roll over in actual it's a very interesting choice. Yeah, it is those sad though because as soon as you see the band
and you're like, God damn it, it's over.
Yeah, well, but we have so many to go.
I still have one waiting on the DVR
that I'm dying to watch.
Yeah, and the reveals, some of the reveals
of the original characters are just so great and it's great.
Yeah, it is.
I loved it.
I can't really tell you what's going on.
The room, with the glass box,
that when that thing started talking on the stick,
yeah, that was very eraserhead -ish,
That kind of like almost like a pod speaking to him those those were the scenes where you know Heather and I were like
Like it just makes you feel like should I be watching this? I
I'm terrified and I will say this. This is not a spoiler in any way
And I believe it does take place in episode four, but when who's the secretary in the police station?
The blonde you know poor man's Victoria Jackson. I don't know the blonde lady that's married to the dumb cop
Dotty when there's a scene where their son shows up in episode four and it is is my favorite scene
So far in the series and I was howling laughing. All right, I haven't seen that yet
So now you told me though that a friend had told you that the scariest thing he's ever seen was in like the first or second episode
Oh, critic wrote that what do you think that it that way?
I don't want to say because it's a very cool thing and I think the the listeners should just experience that because when I saw it
And I think I know what it was. I was like, oh shit, I think that's what he was talking about because that it there's a I don't want to ruin it
There were a few really horrifying moments, and I just didn't know which one you meant or he'll tell you off off the air
That's fine folks
That's our show catch me at joderosa comedy on Twitter and Instagram
Thank you all for your five star reviews of this show and my albums
Thank you for helping me pull up the album ratings for the drags of those troll reviews. I appreciate it
I got a lot of tour dates coming your way. I will be in June in San Diego the American comedy company
I will be also at the cluster fest in San Francisco. I will also be at the stress factory in New Brunswick, New Jersey in July
I will be at
The punchline comedy club in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. I will be a cap city comedy club in Austin and in August
I will be in Amsterdam at the something festival it's escaping me right now
But I believe Kyle Canadian myself will be co -headlining shows. So I'll see you out there. I
Am at the Patrick Walsh on Instagram and Twitter. That's all we really got folks. I think
As I said coming up, I would expect a Kingsman secret service episode. I would expect a
What's the big movie coming out?
we're not neglecting your request. I keep seeing lost boys come up. I think that's one
that we'll do soon. But I'll keep you updated on the on the Facebook page. Thank you guys
very much. We'll see you next week and we'll see you in hell.