I'm here for Bet Rivers online casino and sportsbook with poker icon Phil Helmuth.
And now thanks to the excitement of Bet Rivers, I'm also a slots icon.
That's great! And a same game, Parley icon. Cool, cool. A Blackjack icon, a moneyline icon,
a roulette. Take it from Phil Helmuth. If you love games,
Bet Rivers is the place to play in Bet. Bet Rivers.
Games on.
Must be 21 plus in present at West Virginia. Void were prohibited. Terms in conditions apply.
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gambling.
The football season is full of guarantees. And here's another.
Know whether sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October.
If your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan cash.
Guaranteed. Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here. Must be 21 plus. Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gambling.
Offer not available in all states. Terms apply. See fanatic sportsbook app.
Welcome to We'll See You In Hell.
The podcast you go to when you need information about horror,
sci -fi or fantasy films. And let's be honest, sometimes action.
And once in a while, a comedy holiday, a comedy holiday flick
like Plains Chains and Automobiles, which we did recently.
And today might end up being about love actually.
It also might end up being about the movie Cam, which is the new Blumhouse film on Netflix.
But we're just going to have to see how it plays out people.
If we don't get to Cam today, we'll get to it next time we promise.
I'll tell you what it's going to be about right up front.
And I'm not going to say his name.
I blocked some piece of horror shit today on the Facebook page.
Some big old chunk of horror shit. I'll say his name.
No, that's a given a school shooter credit.
Well, no, but I really like
sinking to the level of calling out a specific part.
Because this guy really about two months ago, I send Joe a thing.
And it's like somebody put a picture of me and Joe up at the live show.
Yeah, great. Really having a nice time enjoying Joe's company.
Yes, he's like, uh, I wish I'd never seen this.
They're ugly. Blah, blah, blah.
You get you get to come on our our shows page to call us ugly.
That's why he's like the last episode sucked, boring, blah, blah, blah.
You know what? You're out of the group.
And I hope you never get to listen to the show again.
You piece of shit.
That's right, Mr. Giles or Giles Evans.
Sorry, let's get you your money back.
Oh, wait, it's a free fucking show.
Giles, is it Giles or Giles?
I would assume Giles.
What a miserable prick.
Yeah. Oh, they, they were high last episode.
I didn't like, we weren't high.
We weren't fucking high.
We were tired because we were goddamn talking for two hours.
But if, if it's clue you're talking about,
a lot of people fucking love the last couple episodes.
I thought me and Joe did a great job.
I know everybody loves a live episode.
So maybe if you cough a little money, you could hear us on Patreon.
But if you want to sit in bitch about a free show,
Giles or Giles.
Shut up, bitch.
Giles, slash Giles Evans.
I will say to you.
Well, this is the thing.
Everybody, let me see it.
Everybody saw us do it with, with the other guy who did this.
And then I think this guy's like, maybe they'll shout out my name.
No, because he was, he was shitty before we did that.
So guys, and Giles, listen to me.
Please don't say mean shit just so we do this.
Because we can't take the time to try to differentiate
between who's doing it ironically and who's not.
That's not it.
This guy was not being ironic.
And I want to be off Facebook and I'm just like,
I'll stay because I like reading about the show.
Again on this morning after a real rough week and I'm like,
really?
And I know 99 % of it is as positive as can be.
And I know we only talk about the negative people.
But that's who we are.
I'm going to mention a positive in a minute.
But I want to, I really want to say this.
And you've, you've, you've cut me off twice now.
Giles.
And here's the other thing.
Evans, okay.
In the words of the great Delta Reese,
Deli Reese, Deli Reese, excuse me.
Deli, when I got mixed up with Delta Burke for a second.
Deli Reese is who I'm talking about.
Kiss my entire ass.
Yeah.
Which is what she says in Harlem nights.
And it's a great line.
It's a big ass to fuck this fucking guy.
What a fucking asshole.
Wish I hadn't seen him.
They're ugly.
Yeah.
What are you?
Some fucking show girl?
No.
Well, what the fuck are you?
Are you a stud?
Get the fuck out of my face.
They're ugly.
So I can't listen to them.
Then don't listen to us.
You dip shit.
They sound high.
I'm worried about Joe.
Pat's got a woman to reel him in.
He actually wrote that.
Pat's wife will reel him in.
But I worry about Joe.
Don't worry about me.
And let me just say.
When I die, you're not invited.
Let me just say for the record.
My wife is not interested in my shit.
She's not.
In fact, she's used the exact phrase,
fuck him to me.
Fuck him, she'll say.
Many times I'll be at their house for dinner.
Pat will go to the bathroom.
She'll lean in.
She'll go fuck him, Joe.
That's right.
And honestly, I don't disagree.
Now, a positive note.
Real quick, a positive note.
I need to thank.
This is very positive.
Mr. Edmund Dillon.
Sir, thank you.
Why?
I'll tell you why people.
I get an email from our dear friend.
What would you call Emily?
Our squad leader.
Almost, you know?
Guru, yes.
She sends me an email.
She says, hey, this guy Edmund,
Edmund, is it Edmund Agaba?
Well, Edmund Dillon is the name I have.
Okay.
Because I believe Edmund Agaba was the lovely gentleman
who said he donated twice to the patron.
He was dressed like Wayne.
His lovely girl from his head dressed as Garth.
I do believe so.
And thank you, Edmund.
Hello.
A lot of Edmunds on the show.
Which I didn't expect.
Edmund, have you ever seen that movie?
I have.
Whoo.
Rough stuff.
It is.
I saw that in a theater and a crowded theater in New York.
Looking over my shoulder, like I was with a guy telling
racist jokes at a party.
It is, you kind of work.
It is a rough, it is a rough movie, man.
Like there is a lot of inflammatory language.
If there was, in that film.
Anyway, Edmund, I get an email from Emily Simpson the other night.
She says, this guy Edmund sent you a video.
I want to make sure you got it.
I hadn't gotten it.
So thank you, Emily, for getting it to me.
I play, I hit play on this thing.
So hand some gentlemen on the cameo service, which is the service
where you can pay celebrities to send videos to your friends,
whatever.
Yeah.
I'm looking.
I go, God, David, I think that Zach Galigan from Gremlins,
who I've talked at length about on this podcast.
In fact, it was, and it was him giving us this message of like,
don't be down about the guests that have said no.
The third time's a charm.
Maybe the third guest will say yes.
Which I think was like a cheeky way of him saying,
hey, maybe ask me, I think, I don't know.
But in any case, it was a video from Zach Galigan, who I'm a huge fan of.
Not just from Gremlins, but quite frankly, more importantly,
from wax work.
One of my favorite are movies of all time.
But more and much more importantly from Gremlins.
Well, for me, it's wax work.
Come on.
I love, listen, I'm not saying Gremlins is worse than wax.
I'm just saying like, as a horror fan, wax work is one of the unsung classics to me.
Julian Sands.
Who the hell is Julian Sands?
He's in wax work.
I don't know who that is.
He's in Boxing Helena.
You know who's in wax work?
The guy that plays the bad boy in the first season of Twin Peaks,
the dates Laura Palmer.
Oh, fried!
I ain't afraid of no feudal.
Yeah.
He's in it. He's great in it.
Okay.
It's a lot of fun that movie.
I've never seen wax work.
The bad guy from the, you know, like the King Demon guy from Time Bandits.
Okay.
Is the guy that runs the wax, wax?
You've never seen wax work?
Never seen it.
Dude, it's awesome.
And Julian Sands is not, I don't know where it is.
I was thinking of Warlock.
Yeah, no.
This is much better than Warlock.
All right.
Anyway, thank you, Edmund Dillon.
And thank you, Zach Galigan, for the video.
It was really sweet.
Yeah, give us a nice little pump up.
It was cool to say.
It was directed more just for me,
but sure, you can get it on it if you like.
To it was really addressed to me.
Folks, if I may, I'd like to get on with the show
and at the same time on,
with the Jungle Bell, Jungle Bell, Jungle Bell Rock.
Jungle Bell's chime in, Jungle Bell Time.
Jungle Bell?
Joe, Jungle Bell.
It's, it's, you're saying, Jungle Bell.
I'm saying Joe.
Which, by the way, we should pitch that to Weird Out.
Jungle Bell Rock, and it's all about living in the jungle at Christmas.
No, it's the holiday season.
It's December 1st or whatever.
Happy holidays to you.
Second.
I got a tree last night.
And just as I expected it,
bumped my holiday spirit from a 0 .0 to a 1 .0.
And honestly, it was worth it.
I hung all the ornaments with care and hopes
that saying Nicholas soon would be there.
And folks, it wasn't the only thing in my house
that was well hung.
All right, folks.
No, we got the tree up.
It looks nice.
The cat likes the tree.
It's cute.
All right.
Is the cat
sort of playing and laying under the tree?
Yeah, the cat likes to get out of the tree.
It makes it feel like it's outside.
Okay.
Because you don't let the cat usually out of a small closet in your house, right?
Usually keep it.
I keep it in a hutch.
And when I poke it with a barbecue poker,
folks, could I take you down to Pat's movie corner?
Because I've been deeply depressed.
I got to point something out.
And I've watched hundreds of things.
Go for it.
Pat and I have had a few drinks today.
As we always do.
Yeah.
Before we do the show.
Sorry, Giles.
Yeah, sorry, Giles.
I'm tipsy enough that I almost just said to you,
you got to get on with the Joe still.
No, I just did it.
Yeah, no, no, completely.
Yeah, we had a full interaction about it completely forgot.
Yeah, actually, just in it.
Juggle Bill Rock, yeah, never.
But I worry we're going to sound pretty fucked up on this one, but it's fun.
Hey, we went to the drawing room, which closes at 2 a .m.
It opens at 6 a .m.
And Joe was telling me, within the month he's been over there at the drawing room at 6 a .m.
I was there one time in my life.
At 6 a .m. it was over the last month.
And a lady screamed at me that I was the reason Trump got elected.
Yeah, which obviously I agree with.
I don't know what I did.
We don't cam on the show.
We talked about this also at the top.
Now you're also forgetting.
We might do cam, but I want to discuss this Lindy West
review of Love Actually, where she takes just a wonderfully spirited film
and reduces it to some sort of socio -political thing.
I was telling Joe and it's a very popular piece.
It was on Jezebel, I think, written by Lindy West.
And it's called, yeah, Jezebel, it was released five years ago, December 18, 2013.
I rewatched Love Actually and I'm here to ruin it for all of you.
I got to tell you folks,
this piece I watched Love Actually last night with my special lady.
And I laughed throughout at this like running commentary.
And did I agree with every point she made?
No, but I like hearing what people think of movies.
It's like when Joe's mad at aliens.
I'm like, well, Joe's wrong, but I can certainly enjoy what he says.
She's not mad at this movie.
She's mad at everything.
This is Lindy West's entire career is,
I'm going to take a thing that somebody else did and be mad at it.
That's all she ever does.
Remember the speech at the end of Planet of the Apes,
where Zeus is like, be where the beast man,
for he is the harbinger of doom.
It's, that's the speech I hear whenever I hear Lindy West's name.
She's just, just, just joyless.
She's a joyless person.
She, she, everything she does is, and sometimes she makes some good points.
Sometimes she makes some, I feel here in this Love Actually article.
Sometimes she makes a very valid points about the gender roles in society
and about rape culture and things of that nature.
She's made some very, very good points over the years.
But a lot of the time, it's just her finding a thing to be mad at,
and it's this bullshit 17 year old angst.
It's like get over it Lindy.
Joe, that's what an article is.
If you want to write an article,
you got to take an extreme stance and call attention to yourself.
I disagree.
I think you can take a more balanced stance and have some,
but I don't want to read it.
I wouldn't be reading the article five years later
if it was some balanced stance.
I think you can have, I think you can have a valid way to do it.
Do you want somebody to go?
I love the story about the rock star and his manager.
No, what I want somebody to do is say,
there are more important things to write about than Love Actually.
Create your own Christmas story than a fiction story
that you think is worth people reading.
Or do a commentary on something
that's not a fucking stupid romantic comedy
that has no effect on the world whatsoever.
It's just stupid.
It's a waste of time.
I completely disagree.
It is a Larry David,
and I mean the character,
level of specificity.
It's a sign -filled plot level.
It's a castanza shit.
I don't like Love Actually.
I completely disagree.
I thought it was very well written.
It's a massive font.
It's crazy.
It's because it stands a level like nuttiness.
I didn't agree with it throughout,
but I thought it was very well written and very funny,
because I've opened my mind because I don't care now
about if I live or don't.
If that was the one thing that she ever did like that
or one of the few things she ever did like that,
I go, okay, fine.
I don't know who she is.
You've made some decision about it.
Listen, I made a decision about it all.
She's made a decision for me.
Everything she writes
is I'm mad at this
because I find it offensive for this reason.
And when it finally gets down to the level of Love Actually,
it's like for Christ,
it's like watching the three stuages
and being like, this promotes violence.
It's like, oh, really?
This is the fight.
This is the fight we're going to test for the same reason.
I like a debate team or whatever else.
I like somebody picking a side
and arguing it to the fullest.
And that is what this piece is.
Joe has not finished the piece.
I read most of it in the area over here.
It's very angry.
Well, she also says things that are accurate.
She goes, she goes, so Liam Neeson calls Emma Thompson
who I guess is just some woman he knows.
And then in parentheses, she goes,
relationship never explained in all caps like,
no, it's his sister and they do explain it.
And that is a thing you know if you watch the movie
without screaming at it over the details.
She actually at one point says, too,
she goes, no woman is allowed to speak in this film.
What are you talking about?
What the hell are you talking about?
It's not just, it's just not true.
It's not a factual account of this film.
And then she'll go, this would be her defense, right?
Because this is every humanless person's defense
of anything when they do like some dumb specific thing
over something this trivial.
They go, and by the way,
I know there are people out there now going,
Joe, if her argument is so trivial,
why are you getting so upset?
Aren't you shut up?
Shut the fuck up.
My point is this.
This would be, it seems like a valid point.
It's, it's, I'm two steps ahead of you
and I already know the point.
Here's the point is her defense to this
is whatever humanless person does.
They go, they go, it's a joke.
And it's like, no, it's not a joke.
I don't, I didn't read this.
It's a joke at all.
And I don't think it's a joke.
When you take a thing and you represent it incorrectly
and then you act like it's a reason for people
to be rageful.
Do you like the character who is secretly plotting
to steal Kira Knightley away from her new husband?
No, I don't like that character.
All right, then I think you'll find points of agreement
in this article.
You're not going to agree with everything,
but you don't have to.
Somebody, somebody says one thing,
you don't agree with, you shut them down.
I think it's crazy that she depicts
the Colin Firth relationship
as when a woman doesn't talk, she's more likable.
Well, he's attracted to her based on nothing.
That is true.
It's not true.
He's attracted to the point of that story
is that love transcends all barriers.
He falls in love with her even though they can't communicate.
That's the point of the story.
Now, if you want to be a fucking miserable asshole
and just go,
oh, it must be because she's mute.
It's like, okay, so then the piano is in a love story.
She is just as you are doing with your stand -up.
She is supposed to be taking a point
and running with it to a comedic fashion
which she does beautifully throughout this entire world.
I beg of you.
If I ever put that amount of time,
if I ever put that amount of time,
she's been paid and hired to write a love and shame
on Jezebel for that.
If I ever take that amount of time
to create and craft a piece on love, actually,
whether it's in stand -up or in writing, please shoot me.
Please, this is the amount of attention the movie deserves.
This right here right now, off the cuff, off the top of the head,
knee jerk responding.
I have a feeling a lot of you are going to enjoy this piece
if you go look at it.
Okay, go read it.
Go read it.
Yeah, very fun.
Because that's fun when somebody ruined it.
Let's all boycott the root off the red nose reindeer.
Rankin and bass stop motion animation classic
because it promotes discrimination
against a red nose reindeer.
I mean, it's just fucking miserable, man.
But Joe, I watched love actually last night with my wife.
We enjoyed the hell out of it.
And I also enjoyed this person's critique of love, actually.
I've said it for years.
You have no backbone.
You play the game.
You won't take sides in this business.
How am I playing a game?
I enjoyed something twice.
I'm joking, actually.
So that was a joke.
I mean, I've never seen it so hot.
I just, this is all she does ever.
Every fucking thing is like I'm offended
and I have somehow derived sexism from this thing.
And it's like Jesus Christ.
It's this like beautiful movie
that depicts people falling in love.
But I've seen a lot of people talk shit
about love actually in recent years.
And it's, no, I tell you where you've seen a lot of people talk.
You've seen about 20 people talk shit about it.
And they all live in Los Angeles.
Because they are so fucking precise with their horse shit.
They have nothing better to do
but try to continually find a target to be angry at.
And it has become so enane
that they are now down to love actually
as a fucking target.
As a target.
Love actually.
A Hugh Grant movie.
But this is what we need to be bitching about.
You are this, this was five years ago.
But you are disgusted by the guy
who sets up a whole church.
So they all play all you need is love for her.
Right.
So some of this, some of this article
is her sister's got to buy that guy.
That's her husband that does that.
No, no, no, it's her creepy friend
who's a creepy friend is the guy that comes
and pulls out the cards.
Yeah, but he sets that up.
The front, the guy who she's marrying
is looking around like what's going on.
I watched this last night.
I'm not, I'm not, I'm sorry.
But she had a big part of this article
is her saying like nobody noticed
the six guys with trombone sitting next to them
at the wedding ceremony.
And that's unquestionably a funny commentary
for watching the movie during the balcony, by the way.
No, they're down on the floor too.
No, they're also on the balcony.
But they're also on the floor.
Maybe they did notice
and they didn't say anything
because they were like, this is a surprise.
My point is, what are you nitpicking here
with this article?
She's, she's taking it to a comedic extreme.
I thought you would just enjoy it.
I don't, I honestly don't understand the anger.
She's not funny.
She's angry.
Well, no, I do understand the anger
because you know this person
and have a specific issue.
She does.
I have no idea who she is.
And again, I thought the article was very fun.
Again, she's made some great points over the years
when she's, when she's serious
and focuses about, about cultural epidemics.
But when you start to let it bleed
into love actually,
and you start saying that this is somehow
a representation of discrimination in America.
I think you're fucked.
I'm sorry.
I just think you're fucked.
It's like watching scrooge
and being like, what an asshole, huh?
I'm supposed to like this guy.
It's like, Jesus Christ.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
There was a flawed character in a movie.
Remember when that's what movies were?
Remember when stories were about characters,
just normal characters.
And it was like, yeah, some of them are fucked up.
That's the point of the story.
And we didn't have villains
being bleeding hearts and agreeing with one another.
It's like, come on.
It's just nuts.
But it is from five years ago and I, you know, whatever.
It drives me nuts.
I'm sorry.
I mean, folks, the article is very funny.
I don't know what to tell you.
All right, go read it, guys.
And tell me how funny it is when she,
when she inaccurately describes
many aspects of the film.
There's like, yeah, there's a couple of mistakes in it.
There's literally a thing where she's like,
I gotta, who's the old guy, Bill Nahi?
Yes.
She's like, he's got to be sitting down while he records.
I'm forced to think about the position of his nutset.
It's like, what the fuck are you?
You literally just took a chair.
She's got offended at it.
She's taking it to a comedic extreme.
Okay.
Well, that's what she'll say.
But I got news for you.
She takes everything she says to that extreme.
And when you put it on that same, under that same umbrella,
I don't think that that's what you've taken
into a whole other thing.
I don't know who this woman is.
And I've taken it too.
I thought we could have a nice discussion about an article.
You've got some crossfit.
You know we wouldn't.
You said right before we started recording,
I'm happy you want to talk about this.
You didn't finish it.
You're going to get all worked up.
And it's going to make me happy.
You said that before we started recording.
I laughed from start to finish at this insanely long article
about love, actually.
And I think she knows how funny it is.
Okay, well, like the kid.
If you had wrote it, she says here,
to be honest, Liam Neeson is acting the hell out of this movie.
She acknowledges positives and negatives.
But it's like, she said it's creepy
because his wife died six years
after they made the movie.
You have to read the whole.
I really wish you just read the whole article.
I read about 70 % of it.
I don't know how much.
If there's some shaman on twist at the end of that thing
that in one last sentence, who writes their novel
on loose pages on a typewriter
in an open air shack next to a pond?
Lots of people.
That's kind of a funny option.
Sorry, miss.
Lots of writers do that.
Lots of writers talk frequently and publicly
about how they still love the typewriter.
That's very common.
Go ahead.
What else you got?
No, I'm not going to read the whole thing to you, Joe.
You haven't taken the time to read it yourself.
I read 70%.
That's all you need to read.
You didn't even get halfway done.
It's way longer than you think.
Well, then that's even more ridiculous.
It's more ridiculous.
I'm a big fan of it.
Be a big fan of it, you know?
Folks, no way.
By the way, just to let, you know,
Lindy West is exactly the type of critic
that would watch your sitcom
and say that it was offensive
and part of the problem.
She's that, she that's who she is.
That's fine.
Oh, God, it's not fine.
It's stupid.
If it was funny, I would read it and enjoy it.
I don't give a shit about anyone's opinion about anything.
All right.
Well, you care about this.
You want to marry...
You want to go marry Lindy West?
You want to go on a date with Lindy West?
You love?
I honestly didn't know who wrote the article
until it snapped something in your brain.
And, guys, just so you know,
I didn't know who wrote it either.
I wrote...
I read the first two paragraphs
and I go,
this is fucking abominable.
Who wrote this?
I scroll up and then I go,
oh my God, Lindy West.
Of course.
You're gonna enjoy it.
You're gonna read the article
and you're gonna enjoy it.
I read most of it.
Sounds like Pat's got an old crusheroo.
I don't know who she is.
It's possible to love someone without knowing them
as proven in love, actually,
by the mute woman storyline.
Lindy West.
Go away.
Oh, man, we got some juice out of that.
All right, we got some traction.
We're good.
I mean, just exhausting.
It's not ex...
You wanted this.
You told me you wanted this
before we started recording.
You got it.
You got your Christmas wish.
I'm gonna take you to Pat's movie corner.
Last night I watched beautiful boy.
I'm gonna tell you this.
And then he watched a movie.
Steve Carell.
Here's the thing.
Steve Carell is a brilliant comedic actor
who got too much respect
for being able to land brief dramatic moments
in comedies, brief, dramatic moments.
He would land them well.
He made you care about him.
And now he's doing these parts
where he thinks he's fucking Sean Penn.
And I'm gonna say it.
Steve Carell is miscast and beautiful boy
and he sucks in the film.
He's got these scenes.
I know a little thing here.
Yeah.
He thinks he's Sean Penn.
Brother, I'm gonna tell you, you ain't Chris Penn.
That's correct.
There you go.
He's supposed to be playing like an every man,
dad and his son's addicted to drugs.
The movie for two hours I assume plus
because it seemed like an eternity
is trying to put you in the shoes
of somebody whose child is slowly killing themselves
through drug abuse.
Watch them on them.
My wife, she's got a cousin
who's having similar issues.
I'm just kind of like,
what are you trying to torture me?
Like it was joyless.
It was miserable.
Timothy Chamolet was fine in it.
You know who wrote the movie?
No, Lindy Webb's.
That's not true.
It's not true.
The movie relies on music
to sell every emotional beat in it.
So like at certain points,
I almost got full.
They're playing stay away
by Nirvana at one point.
You never hear Nirvana in movies.
And the guy is like puking
because he's overdosing on drugs.
And it's like,
gotta find a way,
a better way.
Where to live.
I was like, shut the fuck up.
I would have gotten it without this
over the top
ham -fisted musical cue.
And there's also that terrible scene
where he flushes his drugs
down the toilet
and it plays Michael Jackson's beat it.
Just beat it.
The movie
is lame.
It's pulling the heartstrings
in a way that never felt legitimate
to me.
Steve Carell when he's yelling at his son
like, you gotta get yourself together.
I didn't buy it.
I laughed at a few points.
It's that's always thought
that deep addiction was funny.
I never agreed with the point.
It's a movie of the week
and they tried to put some stars in it
and kind of fool you that it's not
but it's not well done.
It's not interesting.
And the reliance on music
to celebrate, you know,
they're driving along
that the son and the father
kind of patch it up for five seconds.
And we hear the entirety
of heart of gold by Neil Young.
Oh, good.
It's like, no, just let me
make my own decisions about the movie.
The only worse choice would be
and the cat sitting the cradle
in the sill of a spoon.
There's 900 music cues in this movie
and everyone you're like,
could that have been more of it?
It's like suicide squad.
What drug is he addicted to, by the way?
He starts with weed, he winds up
being heavy into crystal meth.
Then at one point he does heroin
and like, fucks his girlfriend.
Am I mistaken that you do heroin,
you end the gal and you're not fucking?
Can you fuck on heroin?
Now I used to fuck my dealer
so I don't, it's a tough, it's a tough,
weed weed get all hot in the vein.
We called it.
Well, yeah, they,
well, they do heroin, they get in the shower
with their clothes on.
That's how crazy they are.
Oh, good.
It's like Julius is saying,
you took your, you took your coat off
and it's still in the rain.
And that's seeing it plays blame it on the rain, does it not?
Yes, it does.
This is terrible.
They get in the shower with their clothes
on and start begging out and then they fuck
and I was like, two people who just shut up with heroin
are not fucking.
I'm sorry.
Well, I, I, maybe somebody can correct me,
but I've never done heroin.
I don't know, maybe.
I feel like your dick's not hard.
Well, I mean, ecstasy you step heroin in it
and it would make y 'all horned up
so maybe heroin makes you more.
I fucked on ecstasy, you can't come.
It takes 45 minutes, but still.
I'd like to put that to a test right now.
Pat, I've got some ecstasy over in the drawer over there
and let's, let's, let's see how long it takes us.
I'd be happy to.
I can fuck forever on ecstasy.
I just can't come.
I probably revealed too much.
Which is why I said I wanted to chat with you.
Pat, I want a beautiful boy.
Can't recommend it.
Sorry.
I want the title is just terrible.
Beautiful boy.
Do you know what song they play in it?
Beautiful, beautiful, beautiful, beautiful boy.
And all these people who act like John Lennon
is this edgy fucking genius.
And Paul McCartney is the sappy one.
Listen to fucking beautiful boy.
And as the great Elvis Costello one sang.
And I saw him in concert this weekend
who was fucking incredible.
He played for three hours and he just beat cancer.
He sang, wasn't it a millionaire
who sang, imagine no possessions.
Beautiful fucking line.
John Lennon, beautiful line.
Pointing out the hypocrisy of John Lennon.
John Lennon, I love the Beatles.
I love John Lennon, but beautiful boy.
Also, they used it better in Mr. Holland's Opus.
Because it was one song.
It wasn't a song where there's a song every five seconds.
I don't like the Beatles as you know.
But I am a Paul McCartney fan.
I think a lot of Paul McCartney stuff.
He's great.
John Lennon is one of the biggest fraud hacks of all time.
I'm so tired of people talking about what I can't go with you there.
I just hate everyone calling McCartney sappy.
Now, John Lennon, like Kurt Cobain of his day.
Every Lennon is so beautiful boy.
Listen to Lennon's entire solo catalog.
It fucking stinks.
I like some of this.
So, they just Christmas.
That judgy shit.
And what have you done?
What did you dub, John?
But he's got some good songs.
Mother Colterkey.
Give peace a chance.
Colterkey is great.
The studio version of Colterkey is great,
which he has made unavailable on any of his releases.
He hasn't done it.
He's dead.
He doesn't have any sense of anything.
He goes, hey, John, can we get a studio version of Colterkey?
Now, going to give the other side to Oh no.
I'm a Yoko guy.
Oh my God.
He sucks.
I went to the premiere of Lennon,
the Broadway musical about John Lennon.
There were so few people there.
I bought a student ticket for a preview,
which was always a $20 ticket.
And I was like, yeah, I'll see a musical about the life of John Lennon.
I have no friends in New York.
And you know who I sat next to?
This is how a few tickets were sold.
Yoko Oh no.
I sat next to Yoko Oh no.
I was joking.
I'm looking at my ticket and I'm like,
please God, tell me I'm not sitting next to Yoko Oh no
for the life of John Lennon musical.
And it said you paid the extra five bucks.
You can sit next to Yoko.
I got a $20 like free ticket.
I'd rather wind up next to the the the the widow.
I'd rather see a musical about Pete Best.
Then a musical about John Lennon.
It wasn't great.
Oh, good.
Oh, love.
So I've done one of three.
You've done none.
Take it away.
What have you seen?
Why are you coming at me today?
Why I've seen a lot.
Didn't take it away.
You don't want to you don't want to know this site's actually.
Beckham away toys.
What have you seen?
I watched you guys.
I didn't believe you how bad it was.
I watched the bow to Buster Scruggs
and holy Christ on my love for it on the.
Yes, fucking.
We'll see you in hell, page.
I don't even understand.
This thing is terrible.
It is terrible.
I thought it had it had decent segments and bad segments,
but yeah, not by by and large.
And I rewatch and tell our book,
you old cruelty this week.
I think it's maybe one of the coins very worst.
Because I liked intolerable cruelty.
The hands down best story is the Tom Waits story.
And it comes four stories into this thing.
Yes.
And that is four stories too late.
And when I tell you that it is the best story,
I don't mean like, oh my god,
did that Tom Waits one really rock me?
I mean, Tom Waits one was good.
That was the first one where I was like,
this is the only one that has any,
as far as I can see, point or anything.
I give a shit about, but it was still,
if it was in an anthotic, and I love Tom Waits.
I'm a huge fan.
If it was in an anthology of better written stories,
that would have been one of my,
the ones that I thought was kind of boring.
Like, this thing makes, in my opinion,
has no point, makes no sense.
It's the, it's the Cohen brothers
reaching into their grab bag of goodies
and just kind of doing a bunch of shit.
Well, I think most tellingly,
it was supposed to be a weekly half hour series.
I mean, could you, and they made it worse?
No. Thank god, they truncated this thing
into a fucking two and a half hour movie.
Could you imagine sitting there
for a half hour every week?
So this first one with, what's his name?
Tim Rutherford, what the fuck's the guy's name?
No.
Tim Blake Nelson.
It starts charming and interesting.
And you kind of think like, okay,
Tim Blake Nelson is going to sort of be
the narrator or the sort of, you know,
the storyteller of this journey,
which would have made sense.
Sure.
And instead, it's not.
It's just, he's the guy named Buster Scruggs.
They do this kind of funny joke
where it's like, he's a singing cowboy,
but he kills people.
And then that segment, as a quick little,
like a sketch funny.
I mean, I didn't laugh out loud,
but it worked for me.
It would have been like seeing Dave Fumel.
Listen, it was, I love seeing criminals.
It was, I love seeing,
fucking Tim Allen Greer.
Tim Blake Nelson.
Yes.
It was, it was, it was a, it was a funny sequence.
Fun kind of fine.
I wouldn't, I wouldn't die in, but it'd be a LOL.
But it was funny.
But even like when he gets killed,
I was kind of like, oh, is this going to be
now that he becomes like the sort of ghostly narrator
of the West or whatever?
And they just do this dumb thing
where he floats away singing like the,
the weasels in Roger Rabbit.
Yeah, it's just not playing a heart.
It's just like, I get it.
I don't think it's that interesting.
I don't think it, the second story with James Franco
starts really interesting.
Franco sucks in that movie.
He does suck in it.
And then just, he's been rude.
Kills it, but he's being hammy.
It's literally just this thing of like,
he almost got hung once and then he got away
and then he gets hung again.
And that time he doesn't get away.
And it's like, what, what is this?
Like, what is the point?
It's, okay, create some stakes.
Create a story about a man that has narrowly
and arrogantly escaped death so many times.
And then it comes and bites him in the ass.
Or create a story about a man
that shouldn't have been hung once.
And then the second time was unfairly hung again
and you say, oh, the tragedy.
Instead, it's a guy that should have been hung
because he was robbing the bank.
And that's what they did back then.
And he gets away by the skin of his teeth
and then he gets hung again.
And that's it.
The third story, Jesus, fucking Christ.
That only amnesum story.
I'm like, am I supposed to be his board
as the people watching this limbless poet?
I thought you might like that one
because I believe it was a commentary
on the entertainment industry
and how a flash in the panic can be.
But yeah, it was 20 minutes too long.
But it wasn't, but here's the thing.
It wasn't a commentary on the entertainment industry
in my opinion.
It's how I took it.
Because the commentary to me would have been
if this limbless kid was happy
and doing great.
And then all of a sudden it tapered off
and Liam knees him dropped him.
That's not what it was.
It was show after show
of people being bored by this kid.
And the terrible sad tragedy
of this kid relying on Liam knees
and those scenes are so sad
where he's got to feed him and stuff.
Sure.
And then he just dropped some
by killing him, by murdering him
and goes out with a chicken
and then that's the end.
There isn't even the moment of like
Liam knees him being like, what have I done?
Yeah.
What did I do?
It's just terrible.
The time -weight story is the fourth story
there's finally some works
point of plot here or whatever.
But as I said it was too little
too late at that point.
I was just kind of done.
I don't know why it's called
the Ballad of Buster Scruggs
that doesn't seem to have any sort of
through line.
My least favorite.
I learned most people is their favorite
which is the 45 -minute segment
with Zoe Kazan
where nothing happens really.
Right.
She falls in love with that guy.
Did you like that one?
You didn't make it that far.
I think I turned it off halfway through that one.
I just was, it was at a point
where I was like, there's two stories left.
The last one is the most slow.
They're not picking this up.
They're going to heaven.
I get it everybody.
I just thought I was boring and not well done.
Also, but that's like such a hackney,
I'm sorry, it's a hackney premise like,
we're on a stage coach going to heaven.
It's like that's been done a million times
on the twilight zone,
all these other shows and whatever.
It's just not interesting.
It's boring.
It's, come on man,
the twist is they're going to heaven.
Who cares?
So I just, my least favorite episodes
of the twilight zone are the ones where,
and it's my favorite show of all time.
But it's the ones where there's like some sort of like
caravan on foot in the old west
and like a woman that doesn't understand
why she's there is talking to Abe Lincoln magically.
And then she realized she's died
and they're all walking to heaven.
Yeah.
I mean, it's like the, it's like the fourth story
and tells you the hood too,
where they just bring back all the iconic
civil rights people and it's like,
it's just the story about a guy
like transcending to head.
It's boring.
I'm sorry, it's just not a fun thing to watch.
I agree.
I will do a good one before this is over,
but another one I did not like,
folks, was crazy rich Asians,
which was sent to me as
for my consideration for Academy Award.
I've got a copy.
I haven't watched it yet.
Folks,
Louis was a huge hit.
I'm happy the Asian people are having their day and the sun.
It's movie sucks.
It's bad by romantic comedy standards.
Well, get Lindy Wester write an article about it.
They have Ken Jiong make like tiny appearances in it
and he's hamming it up,
but you can tell he's doing it because he's like,
somebody's got to bring some fucking life to this shit.
And he provides the life.
The jokes, I mean, they're walking into the wedding
and there's a guy wacky sidekick
and a girl wacky sidekick who was Aquafina.
The guy wacky sidekick was on two broke girls.
I don't know what his name is, but he was on it once.
They're walking into the wedding
and she goes, I heard that girl is a porn star
and he goes, oh, yes, an Asian porn star.
I heard her first film was called
Two Girls, One Couple Noodles.
Listen, I need you to listen to me for a second.
But did you hear me?
I need you to listen to me for a second.
That's the key joke of the movie.
I don't want to throw this mic at your face,
but I will.
That's one of the key jokes of the film.
Just for putting that joke in my head.
I'll throw this mic at your face.
Somebody's got to pay.
I had to stand up and pace knowing this movie made 300 million
to eyes like I have to get up and pace my apartment,
my home, my other house.
I was traumatized by some of the jokes in this movie.
It's bad.
The story is boring.
I wasn't that interested in, there wasn't really enough
culturally.
It's like they've just leaned into the Tiger mom stereotype.
There was no new information culturally.
Like my big fat Greek wedding is not an amazing movie either.
But you feel like you learn a lot about Greek culture.
I wouldn't say a lot.
You learn so.
You learn that they go,
WAPA!
You learn so.
That's your main takeaway from that film.
This was just like Asian moms or a bitch was like the takeaway.
I didn't, I don't know.
It bothered me.
And I'm going to bring up something very sensitive.
Oh boy.
But please know
that I'm coming from a place of how did they miss this?
The emotional climax of the movie for five minutes,
they play a Chinese cover of Coldplay's song Yellow.
And I for the life of me don't know if this was some sort of taking back the word yellow,
which is a Asian American slur.
Right.
Why would the film Crazy Rich Asians play the song Yellow over its emotional climax?
Well maybe they weren't thinking of it that way.
How?
Yellow was a hit 15 years ago.
It's not in the cultural and it also doesn't apply to it.
Yellow was kind of a sad song.
It's playing over the end of this movie and I'm like,
no one has thought about how uncomfortable this is.
I got you.
There's a zap a song called Keep It Greasy.
And it's if you're doing an Italian movie,
the emotional comedy, you don't want to play Keep It Greasy over it.
It's going to be a stretch.
Sure.
All right.
Yeah, I hear you.
I mean, yellow, like that song was a hit in 2003.
Sure.
Like why would you pick it?
I couldn't wrap my head around.
It's still a hit in all of our hearts.
I've always loved the song.
I don't even like Coldplay.
It's a beautiful song.
But that's remember that that's back when you thought Coldplay was going to be like a good,
like indie band.
Yeah, they're first band.
I like, you know, like Snow Patrol, like a decent.
Oh, they suck.
Yeah, they suck.
Anyway, I can't recommend it.
Like, you know, it had a lot of like great costumes and shit.
But at the end of the day, it's not a good movie.
I'm looking for positives.
But it's not a great movie.
I watched the Kaminsky method on Netflix.
The new Michael Douglas.
It's all the first two.
You know, look, folks, it's, it's, it's not reinventing the wheel.
It's, it was written and directed by what's his face?
From Chuck Lorry.
Yeah, Chuck Lorry.
One of the only men worse than my former boss, Michael Patrick King.
One of the only worst bosses.
Really?
It's supposed to be a scrimary of what's a shame.
One of the absolute worst people.
My buddy got a job on mom.
And they pulled him into a side room and were like,
you got the job.
But now here's the truth.
And for 10 minutes, they were like,
here's what you're going to have to put up with if you take it.
And at the end of the conversation, he didn't take the job.
Guaranteed money in the bank.
He was like, yeah, I'm not going to do that.
Wow.
All right.
Legendary monster.
Well, fuck, man.
Then I hate to give any credits to the show.
But, uh, you know, look, it's, it's, look, it's not, as I said,
it's not reinventing the wheel.
It's not breaking much new ground.
But I did enjoy it.
I like anything that revolves around older characters,
which is why I like your show, Pat.
Yes, thank you.
It's why I love the golden girls.
It's why, uh, you know, I love grumpy old men.
Sure.
I just like stuff like that.
So, uh, I enjoy there being a show out there about an aging, uh,
actor slash acting teacher who's best friend is his agent, uh,
who's also an aging man played by Alan Arkin.
Love Alan Arkin.
Uh, and they're going through the, the, the sort of trials and tribulations of,
of, of sort of reaching the end of the September of their years, so to speak, um,
December, September, well, September is the, September, it'd be like 45.
Now, I think that's like when you're in your 60s, that's the Sonatra record,
September of my years.
All right.
December is like 90.
Um, anyway,
it's got some very cute, funny moments in it.
It's, it's an enjoyable show to watch.
I do like that.
It shows, uh, respect to the notions and perspectives of the younger generation,
but it also wasn't so precious that it doesn't also make jokes about it and stuff.
It's a good generational depiction of, of, of, you know, sort of the older folks and the younger folks
without it being like ones right and ones wrong and, you know, it's, it's very balanced.
So it's, it's an enjoyable watch.
It's an enjoyable watch, you know, I watched two, maybe three.
I found it to be solidly written, never laughed out loud, funny, kind of dull,
but well -acted and I didn't hate it.
Yeah, basically, I laughed out loud when Alan Arkin went.
When I pee, it's like Morris code.
I, you know, he's got, Arkin's got some good lines.
I like that they made fun of, you know, um, uh, my buddy Bill Burr and I were talking about how,
like, you know, a great restaurant in LA by career waiters. Uh -huh.
Moose on Frank's.
Moose on Frank, you go to Dan Tannis.
It's like, you'll get a guy who's like 68, you know, like, this guy's a career writer.
Like, this is like a real deal spot.
I like that they made fun of that where they're at Moose on Frank's and the waiters like 89.
Right.
Waddling to the table to drink and I only finally get there and Alan Arkin goes,
congratulations.
You know, it was, they made fun, it was some inside jokes, but I enjoyed it.
I'll probably eventually finish the season, but it's not, it's not something I was blown away by.
I feel like we've been very negative this episode and I want to turn it around with one of my
favorite movies of the year, even though it may have come out last year.
Documentary called Dina.
It is available on Hulu.
Is it about Dean Martin's daughter?
No.
This movie.
Genie Martin, you know, I do.
It charmed the fuck out of me.
I loved it.
It is a movie about a severely autistic 45 -year -old woman.
And she's about to marry a severely autistic in a very different way, like 40 -year -old guy.
And she's been through a lot of trauma.
Her last or ex -boyfriend stabbed her.
There are big twists and secrets in this movie.
I saw it be, it was, it was well -reviewed, but it was a little controversial because
it feels like just being a fly on the wall in this relationship with these two severely autistic
people and they were like, well, you're taking advantage of them.
Truth is, you don't know what went on.
You don't know how this happened.
Granted, if you're having that much access to an autistic couple, there's probably a bit of
exploitation there.
But I learned so much about this illness and about these people and about where my own issues
but with these issues because I have OCD and I would assume some sort of mild autism,
nothing like these people have.
But I related to it a lot more than I expected to.
And I thought it was just a beautiful love story.
It's a documentary.
She tries to talk to him about like, she buys him the joy of sex.
She can't get him to sleep with her.
He's either a virgin or they've just never had sex, right?
And he just can't calm down enough to do it.
There's a scene where he goes and talks to his dad who was like,
Bert Young.
And he's asking his dad, like, I don't know how to do it.
And I'm scared of everyone.
His dad's like, you're going to be great.
He's like, don't worry about it.
Once you get there, you're going to, I know you're thinking you can't do it,
but once you get down to it, you're going to be able to do it.
I guarantee it.
Oh, that's sweet.
And the mom comes in and is like, you know, all my friends always ask me,
you know, how's he doing?
Because he's so handsome.
They all say how handsome.
Oh, that's sweet.
This sounds very touching.
You see how he's not, they're not severely handicapped,
but they have really serious issues.
And you see how his parents kind of give him his strength,
his self -esteem, and her mom is a severely plastic surgeryed bitch, frankly.
Disaster as the dead Kennedy's once had.
Yeah, she like, they go to get a, get a man he petty.
And the daughter who is, again, highly autistic is talking a lot.
And the mom's like, oh, well, she shut the fuck up.
Well, she shut the fuck up.
And much like three identical strangers,
which is another great documentary.
It's a great story amongst everything else that it is about how good or bad parents can really
fuck you up.
Sure.
It'll make you make your life much better.
Yeah, man, I saw that in a department store last Christmas.
Yeah.
This woman had a mentally handicapped daughter who was an adult at this point.
She was probably 30.
And the woman, the mom was like this sort of plastic surgery dolled up, whatever.
And was just being, and the daughter kept talking to me and my mom and being like,
how are we, what are you doing here?
And like, what are you doing?
Yeah, it was very sweet.
And the mom just ignored us, wouldn't talk to us.
And then was like yelling at the daughter to come, it was really gross, man.
Nobody is saying, you know, raising a child like this is not a difficult thing.
But it's like this far end where your daughter is like 45.
And the mom's still being a bitch to her.
The dad's not even around.
So clearly like, he's like, I don't want to be seen on camera having this girl as my daughter.
So even though it is about Dina, who is the woman, and she is a very
difficult partner.
Clearly, she talks a lot about all the guys she used to fuck and how they used to
fuck to this guy who was having big issues.
That doesn't help you.
But she doesn't know that what she's doing is wrong, yeah, yeah, sure.
I was so fascinated by everything about it, and I couldn't recommend it enough.
I was a baby crying by the end of it.
I just think it's a beautiful movie.
And it's structured a lot like a romantic comedy, but it's a documentary.
So I recommend it very much.
If you have Hulu, it should be the next thing you watch.
All right.
Now, Pat, I'm going to propose we do something unprecedented here.
We'll see you at hell.
Yes.
We're at 51 minutes.
Yeah.
Haven't even started on the movie.
I say we cut it here.
Cliffhanger style.
Well, then what have we reviewed?
Love actually.
Look, the audience knows our stance on love actually.
I think it's a fucking wonderful film.
I like it too, but I urge you to read this article about it,
because I think it's a great side history about the movie.
Well, I'd like to know what you think.
And I have issues like the friend who, the friend, the guy who basically hijacks,
should we tell Eddie Afor's wife here and nightly?
That's a fucked up story.
He doesn't hijack her.
He goes to her and says, I know how you thought, I hated you,
because I never talked to you.
It's not that.
It's a fucked up story.
I'm not saying it's not weird, hold on.
But he goes, it's his way of saying, I know you think I don't like you.
But I'm actually, I think you're wonderful,
and I would never interfere with this, and I couldn't figure out how to just
be normal around you.
There's a beautiful side to it.
There's also a dark side to it.
That's what life is.
And doing the flashcards, you like that part?
Well, look, a lot of people have paraded that flashcard scene.
To me, the whole movie is about Rickman and Thompson.
That's a beautifully told story.
Alan Rickman and Thompson, that's the one where I kind of agreed with Lindy,
that he's kind of a prick.
Of course, he's a prick.
I thought there was a beautifully written story.
It is.
It is saying I enjoy, when people are talking shit about a movie I love,
and it took me a long time.
It used to anger me, but now I'm like, I've enjoyed hearing this opinion.
The most beautiful story is the Bill Nye, he with his manager,
and he always makes fun of his manager for being fat and stuff.
And then he goes to his manager and Chris Prasey even says,
I know, buddy, that I always make comments about you're the one I want to be with.
You're my best friend in the world.
I love you.
Yeah, that makes me cry.
There are fantastic parts in love, actually.
There are embarrassing parts in love, actually.
It's a delightful movie, but I also think this article is very funny and interesting.
Well, Pat, I find you delightful.
Thank you.
I also think that you're moronic and stupid.
Agreed as well.
So it's, you know, there's a duality to all of us.
And that's the point of love, actually.
There's a complicated side to all of us,
which it's not just black and white.
So if we're doing love, actually, do you have a scream in a new psycho?
Do you have a Joe scary stuff?
About love, actually?
About anything.
Now, I'll save it for the next episode.
We're talking love, actually.
We're going to close it out next.
We gave the people what they came for.
We did.
This was 55 solid minutes of screaming.
True.
Love, actually, I give it a big hogs up.
I give love, actually, a hogs up too, but I'm open to interpretations,
because I think big chunks of it are stupid.
But it's undeniably entertaining.
I think big chunks of you are stupid.
I couldn't agree more.
I think it's undeniably entertaining.
But I also recommend you read this article.
We know.
You keep saying it over and over.
They'll read the goddamn Lindy West article, all right?
I don't know what this Lindy West did to you, Joe.
You should do anything to me.
Nothing.
But it's like, you know, it's like listening to a Trump speech
and going, is this accurate?
And you go, no, it's idiotic.
It's too much.
It's stupid.
That's my point.
Anyway,
this is one of the most divisive movies of our lifetime.
I don't understand what everybody's so goddamn mad about.
It's a movie that really pisses people off
and also that people love.
He puts Hugh Grant beautifully puts Billy Bob Thornton in his place
when Billy Bob Thornton is portraying like the sort of clinton -
But no people don't love how much material there is
about how fat this girl is who is at best two pounds overweight.
They talk a lot about how fat that girl is.
Who does?
It's her father.
It's discussed throughout the whole movie.
And I, but I don't think the, here's my thing.
I don't think the point of that is you to watch it and go,
she is fat.
I think the point of it is for you to go, no, she's wonderful
and beautiful and these people are being unf -
Hold on, hold on, yes.
It's a Cinderella.
It's literally Cinderella.
Everybody is needlessly mean and critical of her
and then she gets to be with the greatest prince guy.
She gets the prime minister and he's like, no, you're wonderful.
I love you.
What are you talking about?
Why can't people look at it that way?
People don't like the jokes about,
so the girl calling for her likes, who doesn't speak English.
The dad thinks they want her ugly fat sister.
There's a lot of jokes about her ugly fat sister
and how impossible it would be for her to get married.
There's a lot in the movie that's a little odd in today's world.
Fine, and again, I'll say this.
This article's written five years.
Again, I'll say this.
I don't think you're supposed to be cheering and hooting for the dad.
I think you're supposed to be like, this poor girl comes from this awful family.
Sure.
And she found love, like it's a beautiful thing.
She found some, here's my point.
Nobody ever looks at it like this.
Oh, here's a story about a woman who's got a horrible man in her life
who doesn't appreciate her and treats her terribly.
And then she meets a wonderful man that says, no,
this is everything you deserve and I do appreciate you.
Look at it that way.
Oh, I'm saying Joe's, that's a boring article.
Well, you know what, Pat?
And stand up.
Then go write for the choosing a POV.
Then go write for the national inquiry.
She's not a stand up.
Don't you fucking dare.
Don't you dare.
I don't know who she is.
She's not a, I'll call her a TV writer if you call her stand up.
Don't you fucking dare.
If you're an article writer or a stand up or whatever else,
you're choosing a point of view and arguing it to the dad.
No, no, that's what she's doing.
An article writer or a stand up or whatever?
No, she's arguing that it's a bad movie.
If she argued it very well of writers,
Joe, she's not a TV writer.
She's not a stand up.
She writes blogs.
Okay.
How do you know who she is?
Big difference because she's a famous blogger.
I can't believe you don't know who she is.
Never heard the man.
The man.
I want to give a good shout out to Mickey to Mick Mack.
And we'll see you in hell because if we're going to shout out
somebody who sucks, I want to shout out somebody great.
He said last night.
Got to give a big shout out to my brother
of another color, Patrick Walsh.
After ordering a third round of Moscow mules for the lads,
Mick Mack might be British.
I don't know.
I used one of my favorite Pat Walsh lines from the pod
on a lovely lady tending bar.
He ordered the round and he said,
that's the kind of life I'm living, baby.
The world is my oyster, comedic pause.
And I'll have a baker's dozen.
Folks, she laughed.
We banched it all night.
Got the number and we sexed until the sun came up.
Yes, folks, sexed it.
I expected to get laid but she's 26 and apparently
this is what passes for intimacy amongst younger millennials.
This story took a turn.
Anyway, yeah, look.
But a line that certainly never got me anything.
I'm glad it helped you out, Mick Mack.
I assume that's not your real name.
And Pat, I'm glad you took a moment at the end of this thing
to pat yourself on the back.
No pun intended.
I get so few opportunities to do so.
We'll be back next week with Cam.
We are talking about Cam on Netflix.
We are talking about hold the dark on Netflix.
We are talking about Texas Chainsaw Massacre.
The next are all coming up.
All right, all right.
I'm not giving you a dead schedule.
Hold the dark might not happen.
But the next three will probably be Texas Chainsaw.
Texas Chains.
If you get to watch it on the Shutter Joe Bob Briggs, do it.
Also reanimator.
If you get a chance to watch it on the Joe Bob Briggs Shutter, do it.
Cam is definitely next week though.
My highest of recommendations for anyone with an interest in horror
is to watch these two Joe Bob Briggs marathons
because they're an absolute blast.
I'm almost done with them both.
We'll be back.
We're sorry this one was so heated and all over the place.
I hope you enjoyed it.
We'll see you soon.
I'm on Instagram and Twitter at the Patrick Walsh.
Joe DeRose returns with new episodes this Friday night.
Joe DeRose is a comedy on Instagram.
I'll be headlining Gotham Comedy Club on January 5th, 6th and 7th.
January 5th is my birthday.
I wouldn't hate it yet.
Oh, we'll see you next time.
We'll see you in hell.
It's a good show.