Summer is here, and Bet MGM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz, only
available at Bet MGM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from Anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Bet MGM game sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia
only, games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal, durable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided in
applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamber.
Firestone Complete Auto Care's epic savings advantage is a sign you need to stop putting off
your car's maintenance, and you can save up to $100 on tires and services while you're
at it.
Don't wait, call Firestone Complete Auto Care for an appointment.
Hey folks, it's Will See You In Hell, your favorite movie podcast.
How about that?
And today we're talking about the Oscars.
We talked about them on the bonus episode in our Patreon for the January bonus episode, and
we were going to do this second half as another bonus episode, but you know, we said, why
not give the Patreon people a different kind of bonus episode and cover some of this Oscar
talk on the regular show.
So if you're not on the Patreon, you can hear it.
And if you want to hear the other part, you can go join the damn Patreon.
How about that?
Yeah.
For the bonus, Joe and I discussed the Oscars at large, the history of the Oscars, the best picture
nominees, all nine of them, and the best director nominees.
It's a great discussion to available on the Patreon.
Today we're going to be talking about everything beyond that, the acting categories and et cetera.
And I have seen, I think all of the films Joe has seen most, and let's kick this thing off,
with best actress.
Well, we'll hold on, you're forgetting something to, oh, we're doing the whole thing, segments.
Well, I think you should at least get on with the show.
All right, let's get on with the show.
And on with the Joe.
His heart's in it tonight, folks.
You told me that's what you wanted.
Me talking.
You got it.
I like to, I like, I like, would you put a little salt on it?
You know, that's all good.
Well, I got to build to something.
We're doing thousands more of these, I assume.
All right.
So it'll slowly transform over the years.
Like a transformer or a bumblebee.
Bumblebee got rave reviews.
Did you ever see that coming?
I ain't going to see Bumblebee, folks.
I'm not going to see it either, but it got 90 some percent.
The first one was a D, and I assume they only went downhill from there.
They did, but the Rumblebee is back.
The reviews of Bumblebee were like, this is the Transformers movie you always wanted.
I never wanted one, so I'm fine with it.
You didn't like the Transformers as a kid?
I wasn't into them at all.
No, not my thing.
Really?
No.
All right.
Well, let me just, I mean, if we're going to have this big Oscar talk, let me get you
quickly over to that corner, the movie corner, because we got a lot to discuss on today's
episode.
And I'll skip movie corner this week, so we can keep it moving.
I'll discuss three movies that are, you know, right outside the Oscar realm, you know,
like movies that were in the mix, but maybe didn't get nominated.
I would like to discuss a picture called Destroyer, starring Nicole Kidman.
This was so clearly designed to win her a best actress nomination.
It seemed to be her only interest.
They have made her down to look like Officer Tignotaro.
She looks exactly like the comedian Tignotaro in the movie, you know, no makeup, short hair,
whatever, except with major plastic surgery.
That's the thing.
She's trying to, it's trying to be her Charlize Theron monster, but she has had such work
done, no judgment at all, but she looks like a woman who's dropped a ton of money into
her face.
And that is not this character.
And, you know, it's not fair, maybe it's not right to comment on, but it took me out of
it.
Not that.
Why can't you comment on it?
The plastic surgery looks weird on anybody.
Sure.
It looks weird.
She, you know, is trying to do the no makeup thing, but when you, you've altered your face
to that degree, no makeup doesn't have the same impact.
It's just basically I wasn't buying her.
I didn't think her performance was very strong.
She talks the whole time like, I'm a tough cut.
Like literally that kind of voice.
That was just from the surgery.
Yeah.
It's like, I'm on the beat, you know, like opening scene, you know, there's a dead body
and Nicole Kibben comes walking out, like throws the police caution tape, you know, walks over
to it and she's like, whose body is this?
Like shoves her way in.
Like, I'm going to find out who did this and they're like, wait, have you even been to bed
yet?
You got to clean yourself up.
Stop the drinking.
And I'm like, she's, wait, she's yelling at crooks like this about making the other
cops are yelling at her.
Like, you got to pull yourself.
Oh, sorry.
She's like, fuck you.
But I'm like, I'm like, guys, come on.
If this was die hard with a Vengeance or something, fine.
Now is this entire film voiced by Cartman?
Yes.
Cartman plays a key role.
I mean, the picture is not convincing.
There's a midway twist that leads to some action scenes that are pretty exciting and well
done.
Beyond that, it just doesn't ring true.
It's like when they tried to do training day again, that movie Harshtimes with Christian
Bale.
I like Tarshtimes.
This is kind of another step down like you can tell nobody involved with it had anything
to do with the police aside from maybe a ride along one night or something.
It just doesn't feel legit.
And I love LA cop movies.
I love them even when they're bad, but this just didn't, didn't do the trick for me.
All right.
Plastic surgery doesn't always look weird, by the way, just usually.
True.
It can look great.
Oh, yeah.
There's a little bit, though.
You got to go, you know, that stuff's like salad dressing.
You can't go pouring it on, man.
Sure.
Yeah.
Another movie that got a little bit of Oscar buzz and there was talk of it maybe being nominated.
It did not get nominated.
Norted Gosling, Norted Damien Chazelle, who got nominated for a law of land, of course,
and Whiplash, which is an incredible movie.
First man, I'll be God damned.
I thought it was panned.
I look it up last night.
It had great reviews.
I sit down.
I'm like, I should have seen this fucking thing at the theater.
The first 20 minutes are like putting you almost in like a, like when you go to Disney or
California adventure and they show you like, like you're flying over the city.
It's actually pretty awesome and realistic, it's like planet earth kind of.
And that's what this felt like.
It was like you're in the cockpit, which all these astronaut movies, they never really do.
They never put you in the cockpit, make you feel the claustrophobia of it quite like this.
It was awesome.
And then the stuff when he's at home was just kind of like a, a very slow madman episode.
But it's about a topic I enjoy, a guy having difficulty communicating, a guy having trouble
connecting with his wife and kids, and his work is so all -encompassing that he just doesn't
have the juice when he gets home, he's so addicted to his job that it affects, of course,
his relationships and his personal life.
I can relate to that a lot right now, not that I'm having problems, but it's hard to
make two things work.
We should talk.
Well, she called me.
We just don't get to see each other, you know, and it puts a strain on things, and I am
always sort of in my work and have to be, and that can take its toll.
This movie makes you a lot of fun, a lot of the time.
I'm very fun, I'm very fun.
But you know, it's a movie about the line you walk between work and home, and that really
is the movie.
However, the space stuff is awesome, it's way beyond like what Apollo 13 did.
I think the movie has a whole, if you talk about how successful the space effects and the
moon effects are, and how fairly involving and interesting the home stuff is, it averages
out to a B+.
But it's a great movie, and one I would recommend, and I think Damien Chazelle is an awesome
director.
Okay.
And my third, folks, I got to talk about that mule.
You know.
I don't know if about my dick.
You know I got to talk about that mule, directed by Starring Mr. Clint Eastwood.
This thing is completely insane.
I looked up and actually laughed out loud when I saw that it was written by the guy who wrote
a little picture called Grand Torina, which ends with Clint Eastwood singing, there's a
grin, Torino.
We've discussed the film, the man, the man makes some mistakes in his life.
When he's on, unforgiven, et cetera, man, the fucker is on, and when he's off, he's way off.
And now he's playing a 90 year old man in this movie, and it's a true, based on a true story
about an old man who ran drugs for the cartel.
The story is pretty entertaining.
What they sprinkle it with is just what they sprinkled Grand Torino with.
Long scenes of Clint being racist, people point out to him that he's being racist.
He chuckles, and you move on to the next scene with no repercussions.
I don't know how this thing got made in this time.
He walks up to help a family, or it's a black couple, and they're like, thank you so
much, he's helping them with their tire, and he goes, yeah, it always makes me feel good
to help the Negroes.
And this is, of course, set in 2018, and the woman goes, excuse me, she's like, we don't
use that word.
And he's like, really?
I'm sort of helping you with your tire here, chuckles, fix the tire, and he's like, all right,
I'll see you later.
It gets back on the road, it's never mentioned again.
Wow.
So that scene, and I assume if I had seen it in the theater in Missouri, while I was home
for Christmas, would have played this way, was designed for comedy.
Just like Grand Torino, you know, Philip Simmer Hoffman, I always tell that story about him
dying, laughing, while wasted, and in sweatpants, and a screening of Grand Torino.
The movie is funny, but it's funny in a way if you're like, is this okay?
Is this supposed to be making me feel this uncomfortable?
Does Clint just think this is how people act?
And I think a lot of the people who watch these Clint East would movies now and get excited
about them, it is the way they talk and act.
So maybe they appreciate being seen, but to watch Clint East would make kind of like racist
remarks to person after person, and then chuckle when they get offended is weird.
It's just weird.
It is weird.
I just hope we don't get in trouble for you just saying that.
The word?
Yeah.
Well, today I tried to tell the room about it, and I said N word with an O on the N, and
nobody knew what I meant.
Do you see?
Do you see what I mean when I say context?
You got to be able to say things in context.
But then everybody was like, well, you can say that word, which is why I said it here.
But yeah, I didn't want to.
I'm telling you what was said in the movie, the Mule.
I don't think Vigo Mortensen wanted to either.
Well, he said the actual word, which I would never say.
Anyway, all right, I got to check that Mule out.
You said he had a few threesomes in it, right?
The Mule, a half hour into this picture, Clint Eastwood has had two threesomes.
Why?
I mean, with hookers.
See calls hookers the other time, the cartel sets it up, but you get kind of into it.
You don't see penetrates, but you get kind of into it.
Clint Eastwood also, you picture in behind the camera, panting, gasping for air.
There are scenes I get at Andy Garcia's playing the head of the cartel, pretty on the nose.
And they, like, he's played that role eight million times.
He's so like 70.
Yes.
Well, it's got to be somebody who makes Clint look like he's a movie star.
So they go into this cartel party and it's like an entourage shot of like the pool and the women and everything.
But the camera makes such a clumsy dive into this woman's ass and just like stays at a bad angle
on this woman's ass for like 15 seconds and you just imagine Clint filming this thing.
And I really do feel like he's like, I'm going to make a movie for my base, my people, a movie like the old days,
where there'd just be a long close up of an ass, a movie where you can call people racist slurs.
And sure enough, the movie received pretty good reviews, it did well at the box office.
Maybe there's been discussions elsewhere about the racism, but I was shocked by it.
I haven't heard it mentioned once about the movie.
Yeah, me neither.
Like Grant Tarino, that was kind of the, that was the point.
Right.
Was that he's a racist guy that ends up denying on behalf of people he was racist towards.
Yes.
This doesn't sound right.
I mean, look, well, the whole movie was, he's trying to make up his, his marriage hit the skids with DN Weast,
who I always like to see.
This is not her best performance by a long shot.
But he's trying to patch it up with her before she dies, but he's a mule, Joe.
He's stubborn as a mule, but he's also a drug mule, Joe.
Oh, I didn't get the double thing.
And the whole movie becomes about his redemption and like making things right in the eyes of his
wife and kids, but you're like, but what are we going to do about all the racism we've seen
that you realize in the end was there for comic relief?
And that doesn't sit well with me, I must say, in 2019.
It's a little upsetting.
Yeah, yeah, it's that's upsetting.
All right, well, maybe I don't know.
Maybe I won't watch it.
I don't know.
I have no interest in it.
I just didn't, that's why I haven't seen it yet.
It ain't great.
If it popped up on HBO, it could kill an afternoon, but it's better than trouble with the curve.
I'll tell you that.
First man.
What's it really is a lot of ladies, you help review about my penis, folks.
They had a little trouble with the curve to dick jokes.
Two dick jokes in tonight.
I got that mule one out.
You got the trouble with the curve, what out?
What other Clint Eastwood movies could make dick jokes about?
Grand Torino.
It seats five comfortably.
There it is.
A mystic river of cheese, right?
Yeah, the fighter.
It's ready to go another round.
The fighter's David O 'Russell.
He's a million dollar baby, which is a million dollar baby for my penis.
Let's get to the Oscars.
What do we got first?
Best actress, best actor.
The people who did actually get nominations.
Not those losers I was just talking about.
Yeah, we'll start with actress.
First up is the favorite, not the movie the favorite, but the favorite to win
won the Golden Globe and all that.
Ms. Glenn Close and folks, if ever there was a case of somebody being awarded
not based on current merit, but on a lifetime of work, this is that again.
They do it again and again at the Oscars.
People get awarded for the wrong performance.
Martin Scorsese won best director after all those years for the departed.
I love the departed.
Martin Scorsese has made much better movies than the departed.
And it winds up kind of being unfair to the people who did give better performances.
Because the wife in my opinion is one of the weaker Glenn Close performances I've ever seen.
It is not her best and it doesn't go both ways because Spike Lee is not going to win this year
even though he's never won best director.
But they'll give you to this old white lady.
I don't know why I'm talking about race so much tonight.
I guess it's because it's all you see everywhere.
But this is one particularly, particularly notable case where Glenn Close does not deserve
a football.
And it is strange that you're this race woke as you sit there in a sombrero.
Folks, I'm not wearing this.
I do have cast on that, but I'm not wearing this.
Glenn Close, you didn't see the wife, right?
No, I heard it sucked.
Yeah, I talked about it on this spot.
It's laughably bad in spots.
And she's fine in it.
She's been better in everything down to damages, the AMC show.
Now this I did see.
Can you ever forgive me?
Melissa McCarthy, now I had to read this.
I thought maybe she was nominated for her work in Life of the Party, which I talked about last week.
Can you ever forgive me?
This is a film where Melissa McCarthy plays the most disgusting person that's ever lived
in the world.
Who's a struggling writer and keeps cat shit under her bed and drinks all day and then yells at her
agent that she can't get a break.
And then she's like, hey, try wiping your ass.
Maybe I can get you a meeting with a book agent.
Basically.
And then she starts the four.
Agent beautifully played by Ms. Jane Curtin.
I love Jane Curtin.
Yeah, I love Melissa McCarthy.
She's very good in this movie.
You know, it's one of these like sort of chester flicks.
You know, it's a con, con woman that's, you know, turning, not tricks.
That's the wrong term.
But you know, she's running forging books.
Forging letters.
And then she gets caught and you know, and then she later in life, I read about the real lady today,
Lee Israel, who wig went on to say she was proud of her forgeries.
You know, it's like kind of taints the movie a little bit.
You know, like you're like, you're kind of an asshole for doing that.
I get it, you were desperate.
You could have also gone and worked at fucking 7 -11 or something.
But you know, anyway, she, she's great in the movie.
The performances are all very good.
It's very well directed.
And I think, you know, I think McCarthy deserves the nod.
You know, the comedian Emily Heller.
Yes, her older sister directed this movie.
Oh, really?
I really liked, can you ever forgive me?
I thought it had a lot of really nice little moments, especially I really liked the moments
between Jane Curtin and Melissa McCarthy.
And Jane Curtin, even though she's the man in this exchange,
like just being completely right, like you're almost asked to side with the man.
It's like get your shit together and maybe I can help you out.
I love any movie about a character who can't get their shit together.
I always feel like I'm one minor decision away
from being a character like this, Melissa McCarthy.
But I liked the movie.
I liked the two lead performances.
And I thought Melissa McCarthy was great in it.
I always knew she had a drama in her.
But she really, I think, inhabits this role in a way that makes you forget Melissa McCarthy.
And it's not like heavy drama.
You know, it's still been too funny.
There's a joke here and there, yeah.
I thought she was great.
Joe, quick trivia question.
There has been only one tie for Best Actress in 1969.
Who were the actresses?
I'm going to go with Helen Hunt in 69.
Julia Roberts.
Joe, they were tadpoles.
Okay, I'm going to go with Shirley Temple.
She would have been a hundred.
And the girl that played Heidi.
That's Shirley Temple.
Oh, well then Shirley Temple tied herself.
It was Barbara Streisand for Funny Girl and Catherine Hepburn for the Lion and Winter.
I always get the Lion and Winter confused with the Lion and the Witch and the Wardrobe.
Sure.
That's a real disappointing mix -up.
Who's next?
Next is everybody's favorite actress.
Easily one of the greatest actresses of all time.
Lady Gaga.
I folks, I mean, I don't think she's kicking off some acting career.
That's going to stay on the test of time.
I think to award an actress for, I'm sorry, a singer for playing a singer adequately seems
like a bit much, especially since she's never acted before.
Ridiculous.
I did like Lady Gaga in this movie.
I can't be mad at her for her peers thinking she was great in it.
But she was good in it.
And I think, but really, for me,
she only came to life in the moments where she was singing, which makes sense.
She had beautiful performances of things.
She was good in her romantic scenes.
But, you know, for me, she doesn't have my phone.
It's Frank Sinatra all over again.
There is no bigger fan of Frank Sinatra than me.
I love his music and I like his movies.
I do not think he ever deserved a best actor Oscar,
a best supporting, whatever he won from here to eternity.
I liked him from here to return to my career.
I liked him in a too.
I like him in a lot of things.
I'm just saying, like, come on, man, there are like craftsmen out there.
Right.
It's like, give me a break, you know?
So I think it's just the same thing as that.
Nothing against her.
No, and she's good in the movie.
But, come on.
Yalitza Aparitio for Roma.
This is her first movie ever.
I believe she's like, yeah, she's 25 years old.
You know, plucked from obscurity.
It's a good story.
I think she's good in the movie.
It's a largely silent performance.
To me, this movie is all about the way it was shot,
which is genuinely impressive.
But the other things to me are not as great.
And I thought she was good in the role.
But again, I'm not thinking about her when I think about Roma.
Olivia Coleman is our next nominee.
My money's on her.
Olivia Coleman was incredible.
You know, I haven't seen all these movies, but I think she's,
yeah, I think she was just tremendous in that movie.
Yeah, we discuss Roma in the favorite and all these over on the Patreon.
But she was amazing in this movie.
And I think really got the best of her scene partners,
Rachel Weiss and Emma Stone.
I think they really came up around her because she's just that good.
She's great.
It's by the way, surprising boob shot from Emma Stone in this movie.
Yes.
I was not expecting that.
I wasn't either.
And I, folks, I like to, if I can be honest with you.
For me, the will win is Glenn Close.
I think the only person who stands the chance is Lady Gaga.
My vote would be Coleman.
And my second choice would probably be McCarthy.
My vote is for Coleman.
I think McCarthy might take it.
This, the odds in this entertainment weekly,
give Melissa McCarthy a 3 % chance.
Well, but they give the Roma lady a 1 % chance.
I don't know.
I think it's going to be close and there could not be,
I mean, the woman has been incredible in many things, not the wife.
For best actor, we're talking about Christian Bale for Dick Cheney.
To me, everybody in this movie was doing an SNL impression with the comedy removed,
or turned way down.
And I just never, I never liked biopics.
I never liked movies where you just feel the person doing
an impression of somebody as opposed to inhabiting that person.
Christian Bale is good as Dick Cheney.
I mean, he disappears in the role with the help of makeup,
but I mean, man, he's the front runner for this award,
and I just think it's ludicrous.
I would agree.
Talk about the movie on the other pod.
I would agree with that.
Rockwell, I believe, is also nominated for best supporting.
And Amy Adams is also nominated for best supporting.
I think off, I'm a fan of all three people.
I think all three nominations are off base.
First of all, Rockwell is barely in the goddamn thing.
Right.
He shows up in a couple scenes as a few lines here and there
is not pressed in any way to do anything
that crazy, right?
It's slightly less funny, Will Ferrell.
Yeah, and the same with Adams.
Adams gets to show a little more emotional range,
but she's kind of just playing that typical,
you know, the like dragon lady wife behind the politician.
You know, it's like, you've kind of seen it a million times.
I thought she was good, but I caught her acting too.
You know, it's just one of those movies where you're like,
sorry.
It is harder, especially working in the biz
to not just see people acting, but like to me,
as I said at the beginning, I have a performance that is so much more
interesting to me than these flashy showy performances
is Gosling and First Man.
He plays it all close to the vest,
but you see that he is like dying inside and doesn't know how to deal with
loss and grief and et cetera or talk to people.
And to me, he acted head and shoulders around these people
and didn't get any mention at all.
Who's next?
Next is
Rami Malik.
Now that's somebody who is acting with a capital A.
I, as we've discussed on the show, thought he did a really good job.
I would love to see and at least have the chance to compare
what Sasha Baron Cohen would do with it.
Rami Malik annoyed me in spots and I couldn't tell if that was an accurate portrayal
of Freddie Mercury or if it was just Rami Malik being annoying
because if you've seen him win things this year, he's an annoying dude.
I thought he was tremendous.
I think he absolutely deserves a nomination.
I do not think Sasha Baron Cohen could have done as well.
He wouldn't have got a part, that's for sure.
Sasha Baron Cohen, I think, would have traipsed into the territory you're talking about
with Vice.
I felt like it would have been an impression.
He would have figured out sort of character traits and mimicked them very well.
But Rami Malik, the emotion was there,
the struggle of a guy being gay and not being able to be openly gay
because of his background and the times he was living in and his confusion
and everything, it was all there.
I mean, he nailed this fucking part.
Without Rami Malik, that would have been a bad movie.
I agree.
I mean, he held together a two and a half hour biopic really well
and you always sort of were able to believe you're watching
one of the most charismatic people of all time.
That's no small feat.
It's a really good performance.
Willem DeFoe and At Eternity's Gate, not only have I not seen it,
I don't know anyone who's seen that movie.
What the fuck is that?
I believe he's playing Picasso, so that's a movie that I will never see.
Although Julian Schnabel directed it, who did,
what's the one where the guy paints with his mouth?
That was a good movie.
Diving Bell in the Butterfly, that was a good movie actually.
And Julian Schnabel's a good director, but folks,
I got no interest in another biopic of a painter.
I'll tell you that much.
I'd watch a movie about Picasso with DeFoe.
He's probably real crazy in it.
I mean, I bet the movie's so boring.
It's like watching paint drive.
Full.
Next up is Bradley Cooper and as Andrew Dice Clay said,
hey, you know, maybe next year you get something for the directing thing.
Tank.
This year, it's all about the acting.
That's what you're known for.
Be happy.
Bradley Cooper is good in this movie.
He is.
That picture makes me sick.
And the picture is why I'll never truly respect Bradley Cooper.
I'm looking at a picture of him,
like biting his fist, like Blanche Dubois,
or Blanche Devaro, excuse me, on the Golden Girls,
and staring off into space.
He's doing like the thinker, isn't he?
He's like a pensive actor and it's really gross.
God, fuck off.
Hearing him and Lady Gaga talk about acting and their connection
and everything is pretty sickening.
The truth is, for a directorial debut,
it's a really well -directed movie.
I heard it was saved and editing, but regardless,
what's on the screen is great.
And he's really good in it.
At some points, you catch him doing like a intentionally deep voice,
like Nicole Kim and was doing in the other movie.
It's like, no, talking in a deep voice doesn't make you more serious.
It makes you look kind of silly.
But Bradley Cooper is good in this.
I wouldn't get him anywhere near the best actor award,
but he is good in the movie.
And the movie, again, is good.
It'll surprise you if you think you know what it is.
Quick trivia question, Joe.
Quick Oscar trivia question.
Daniel Day Lewis is the only actor to snag three best actor wins.
What are the films?
Phantom Thread.
There will be blood.
My left foot.
There will be blood and Lincoln.
Oh, fuck.
Lincoln.
That's right.
It was Lincoln.
Shit.
But, you know, it was fun.
He's been nominated six times for the honor.
Veejo Mortensen is nominated for Green Book.
Veejo Mortensen is really likeable in Green Book.
His role consists largely of being kind of dumb and eating a lot.
He folds up a pizza at one point.
A large pizza like a cow's own and eats it
in a wife -beater.
You know, you want to talk about how subtle this movie is.
Why does he, why does he, why does he, why does he, why does he do that?
He's just a big eater.
His like, he goes like this.
He goes, he goes, wow, the sauce.
One of his biggest character traits in the movie,
like probably his biggest.
He basically, he's a racist guy who eats a lot.
Veejo Mortensen has been better before.
He'll be better again.
If you want to see some really choice underrated Mortensen,
I would recommend Captain Fantastic that came out a few years ago.
I think he got nominated for that too.
I thought he should have been nominated for Sahara.
I don't even remember Sahara, but I think it might have been McConaughey.
I don't know if it was McConaughey, but he might have been in there too.
I think Mortensen was in it.
It was Steve's on McConaughey and I think Kate Hudson,
but maybe Mortensen had a support.
It was in after the Lord of the Rings movies.
He's in some like desert movies.
He was.
I love him in Eastern promises.
I love him in history of violence.
I think he's a good actor, but Indian Runner,
if you want to go way back, Sean Penn's movie,
but Veejo's super likable here, he's basically playing the role as good
as the eight lead on the sopranos, which is what he is doing.
He's playing that kind of role with that level of subtlety.
Look, I don't think the guy deserves the award by any stretch of the imagination,
but he's a good actor and I like him in this spot.
Are you excited that they cast Young Gandalfini as the young Tony soprano?
I hope he can act.
I mean, look, no one's more excited about this movie than I,
however, to see it with none of the people from the show is,
I can't get that excited.
Nobody from the show is in it?
I don't think so.
Well, I guess not, right?
Because Tony's like, it goes way back, yeah.
It's going together a good little cast, but like, I don't know.
I mean, who was he?
I never thought even on the sopranos when they'd go back to his childhood,
it was never my favorite part of the show.
Who wants to see a children prequel of the sopranos?
I kind of, well, it's Uncle Junior who's like, you know,
80 on the show.
It's like him and his prime and Tony's dad and his prime and stuff.
And, you know, to see the mom, Livio, when, you know,
when she's 40, he'll be fun.
I'm excited to some degree.
It is the cat, I bet you the tag phrase is,
watch this family rise to its high note, the sopranos.
Look, I'd submit it.
That's better than probably what they welcome up with.
Well, before we move on, let us throw to our sponsor.
We'll be right back, right after a word from our sponsor.
All right, we're back.
Best Supporting Actress.
Regina King.
Right, for Best Supporting Actress, I'm very excited for her.
Regina King has long been the best part of a lot of movies.
She's a great actress.
And she's nominated for if Beale Street could talk.
Beale Street could talk.
I really enjoyed.
It's from Barry Jenkins, the guy who made Moonlight.
It's nowhere near that good or important.
But it is a very well done and kind of moving love story.
Told out of order to sort of make it seem a little more
interesting than it is, I would say.
But it's shot really well.
And it does something that's very difficult to do in movies,
which is make you really believe that the two people are in love with each other.
Regina King plays the girl's mom.
She is really great in the movie and deserves all of her claim.
I'm excited for her because this is an actor that started out on 227.
Great show.
Jack, okay.
And then, you know, bop the long into some movies and stuff.
And then showed up on TV shows here and there.
But I got to be honest.
I thought, I actually met her once.
She was very nice.
I thought she was kind of like in that position of,
this is, she's going to be a character actor.
She's going to pop up on TV shows in like five episode arcs and stuff like that.
But that's it.
So to see her now stepping into the biggest spotlight she's ever stepped into is exciting.
I'm very happy for her.
It's a very good movie, really kind of impossible not to like.
And she is really good in it.
As is everybody.
It's a very good movie.
Terrible title if Beal Street could talk.
It's like, that's not a good title.
I'm sorry.
Emma Stone.
I don't know what it was.
I like the title, I don't know.
The title really says to me, don't watch me.
It took me a long time to watch it.
All right.
Emma Stone for the favorite.
Emma Stone was great in this.
As was Rachel Vise, who I assume is also nominated.
And I'm going to just double check.
Yes, she is.
They're both nominated.
I thought they were both great.
I don't know that either deserves a supporting actress.
Not, but they were both very good.
To me, I thought they were both great.
Emma Stone's got some growth to do as an actress,
but I always like her.
Vise kills it in this movie.
I thought Vise was incredible.
And really, would they give V?
I think that's how you pronounce it, right?
Really.
Rachel Vise.
I thought she was great.
I thought they were both great.
I just didn't.
Compared to Coleman is given so much to do, first of all.
It brings so much into it.
It's pretty incredible.
I would actually give it to Stone over Vise.
Not the movie, the actress.
Because Stone's character goes through
an actual pretty large transition in the movie.
Rachel Vise is pretty much the same person in the entire time.
Not that she's bad,
but she plays who she plays the entire time.
That's true.
Stone by the end of it is completely unlikable and just awful.
Yes.
Yeah, it's really just a preference.
I just like Rachel Vise more.
Black Swan.
That's a great fucking movie.
Just saying.
All right.
Her ex -husband, Darren Aaronovsky, I love Black Swan.
Great, great movie.
Totally.
Joe.
Isn't it weird too that she's Hugh Grant's
boyfriend and about a girl.
And Nicholas Hout is also involved.
And then in this.
That is weird.
I wonder if she'd recommend them.
You know, it's just weird seeing them play like peers
now when they were in a movie where he was like a little kid.
Right.
She looks the same exact age.
Anyway, go ahead.
Only two actresses have one best supporting actress twice.
I want to ask you that.
It's kind of hard.
Shelly Winters and Diane Weist.
Diane Weist won in 1987 and 1995.
What were the movies, Joe?
And I know you've seen them both.
Han and her sisters.
Yep.
Deserved.
1995, same director.
Hold on.
What the hell movie did he do in 1995?
1995, he did a...
Wait, that was in high school.
It's a funny one.
Hold on.
Mirror Max.
I know it's...
Wait a minute.
Give me a second.
Hold on.
Just give me a second.
I'm just thinking about the listeners.
Mad Hatton, murder mystery.
Bullets over Broadway.
Oh, shit.
That's right.
Amy Adams also nominated for Vice.
I found her good as always, but kind of hammy
and did not really inhabit that part very well.
And then Marina De Tavira,
who is supporting in Roma
and to me makes quite a bit less
of an impression than the lead.
So I would not vote for her.
What's her percentage to win?
They've got her at 4%,
but Emma Stone below her with three.
They're picking Regina King and Amy Adams
in second, which to me says
Regina King's got it in the back.
I'd like to see King get it.
All right.
Who do we got for best supporting actor
or final category?
We've got...
By the way,
what's the least amount of screen time
someone had for and one best supporting actress?
Christal, I don't know.
Beatrice Straight for Network.
Eight minutes.
Really?
Best supporting actor.
Give it to me, Daddy.
Mahershala Ali,
which I realize as I read it,
I've been mispronouncing for two years now.
Mahershala Ali in Green Book
is, I would say, exactly the same thing.
I said about him.
That I said about...
Where you go?
Extremely likeable performance.
They both seem like roles that come very comfortably
to these two and not like some sort of stretch.
But they're likeable
and they have great chemistry together
and that ain't nothing.
I like the actor a lot.
Sam Rockwell is George W. Bush.
I love Sam Rockwell.
I think you'd agree.
Not quite deserved.
Yeah, and I already talked about it,
but it's...
Sam Rockwell was arguably my favorite working actor.
Yes.
And I feel like this is just a publicist
being like, this guy should be nominated, guys.
He does a lot of good work.
Yeah, he won Best Actor last year,
so maybe take a year.
Oh, he did?
Yeah.
Oh, that's right.
Best supporting actor or Best Actor?
I think he won Best Actor for that.
You know, he's perfectly competent in the movie.
It's just not an interesting part
and it's a thing we've seen many, many other actors do.
We've seen a lot of George Bush portrayals at this point.
I got two great trivia questions for you here.
Who was the first black man to win Best Supporting Actor?
It was 1983, and I'll give you a hint.
Mayo Nays.
I don't know.
Lou Gassa, Jr., Officer in a Gentlemen.
Awesome performance and an awesome movie if you haven't seen it.
I've never seen it.
It's a great, great picture.
Love it.
Deb Winger and her prime.
Here's a great question that I got last night in the treadmill,
but it took me a while.
The only two brothers ever nominated for Best Supporting Actor are.
One was nominated in 1989, and one in 2001.
It might take you too long.
I can't believe it.
I got it, but it took me a while.
Give me a hint.
Arizona is your hint.
Is it raising?
I'm just saying Arizona is your hint.
Nicholas Cage and Johnny Cage of Mortal Kombat thing.
No, it is River Phoenix for running on empty
and Joaquin Phoenix for Gladiator.
What's the Arizona?
That's where they lived.
Phoenix, Arizona.
Okay.
Well, kind of a fun clue.
Richard E. Grant, who I love from With Nell and I,
and was very good, and can you ever forgive me?
Yeah, he was terrific.
I think he's got a shot at a driver.
A driver is great.
I would love to see him take it.
He ain't going to get it, but he was really good in that movie.
And Sam Elliott, your stool Mavuis for a star is born.
They are calling this for Maharaja Ali.
I think it was a strategic move to put him in supporting
because it's a lead actor performance.
And I think it's crazy to say that
Mortensen is the lead of that.
And Ali is supporting.
They're in every scene together.
That is strange from start to finish.
It's not fair and it's weird.
I also thought it was strange that Emma Stone wasn't considered a lead in
favorite and Olivia Coleman wasn't considered supporting.
Yeah, he's in the movie significantly less.
Coleman, Portman, and Vice should have all been nominated for supporting,
but there's no really got to have a lead to that movie.
No, I mean, I don't think I'd say stone.
It's stone story.
Maybe.
You know, it's her character story.
They're calling this for Ali.
I think the award goes to probably Ali.
But I think Sam Elliott and Richard E. Grant have chances.
I think my pick.
My pick would be Richard E. Grant.
I'd love to see Sam Elliott up on that stage.
And I think a lot of voters would.
I'd like to see Grant or Elliott just out of the prestige of their careers.
They've had a lot of careers and, you know,
but only post -post -umus Oscar for Best Supporting Actor.
You know, that's the guy from Network.
That's Heath Ledger.
But the guy from Network won posthumously.
He got best actor.
This is for supporting.
That's what I'm saying.
The guy Network got best lead actor.
Peter Finch.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, he did.
I thought he was supporting in that movie.
No, he's mad as hell.
Um, what's real quickly run over the other,
not every one of the categories.
If he was alive, I bet he would have said,
I'm not mad as hell.
And I will take it as he took the statue.
Yes, uh, cinematography, cold war, the favorite, never look away.
What does never look away?
I've never heard of it.
Roma and a star is born.
The surest thing to unlock if you're doing these pools,
Roma will win Best Cinematography and definitely deserves it.
It's incredibly photographed.
What do we got in the screenplay category?
Screenplay.
That's what I'm curious about.
Always my favorite.
There's original and adapted or best original screenplay.
The favorite.
Okay.
First reformed.
I fucking love Paul Schrader's movie.
Green book.
Which, how was that an original screenplay
when it's based on a true story of this guy's life?
What's the favorite's based on a true story?
That's true.
Roma and vice.
Vice is the worst of these nominees.
That's in there.
Uh, I, well, I'd love to see the favorite get it.
I didn't see, was it all best dressed?
The priest one?
First reform.
First for four.
I'd like to see that win just because I like Paul Schrader
and I, I really want to see that movie.
I didn't get a screener, nothing man.
They didn't send a screener and that's why they're
shut out of more like Ethan Hawke would have been nominated
if they had sent out a screener.
And that ain't fair.
Paul Schrader didn't have the money to do it.
First reform has zero chance of winning this.
It goes to Roma or the favorite my money's on Roma.
But in terms of screenplay,
you know, yeah, I think I'd go with the favorite.
I'm going to call it now and this is going to contradict
what I said, some of what I said on the other first part
of this two -part Oscar podcast.
I think Roma's going to sweep the whole thing.
I think Roma's going to win a lot.
I think that's going to be the big like sweep movie.
Yeah, for sure.
And they'll see it as a fuck you to Trump
because it's about Mexicans and etc.
They'll make it political like they do.
That's adapted screenplay.
The ballot of Buster Scruggs.
You've got to be fucking kidding me.
Let's pit stop here for a minute.
This fucking movie.
Yeah, I mean, are you out of your fucking mind?
You'll find no bigger Colin Brothers fan and apologist.
I can go to bat for intolerable cruelty if you want me to.
But no, I can't go with you on Buster Scruggs.
And if anything, I like to, because it looked great,
the stories were not holding my interest at all.
Ridiculous.
I got to be honest.
I didn't know that was adapted.
That's adapted and that's as good as they could do.
I don't.
I think it's adapted.
It's one of these things where they wrote a novel or something.
All these things have terrible loopholes in them.
But I think it's an original.
It should be an original, but there's some loopholes.
Buster Scruggs, Black Clansmen, which is a great screenplay.
Absolutely.
I guess that's adapted from an article or something.
Can you ever forgive me if Beale Street could talk and a star is born?
Great screenplays across the board.
You know, those are great nominees.
My vote is Black Clansmen.
Sure, sure.
Visual effects.
Avengers Infinity War.
Christopher Robin.
What do they do?
Animate Winnie the Pooh and they're in the visual effects category.
Well, he interacts with Tigger and all those guys for the whole movie.
Well, pardon me, all to hell.
Well, I mean, that's a pretty big visual effect.
I didn't expect you to go to bat so hard for.
I'm just saying it says Robin.
He's talking to a goddamn tennis ball and you think a bear is there.
Chose fired up about CR.
First man, which had incredible visual effects.
Ready Player One, which while I didn't like it at all, certainly had great effects.
Look, I would have I would have put solo in there over really good.
Solo is in there before you go on your high hole.
Okay, good.
All right.
Solo's in here.
I mean, for me of these, I got to go with first man.
I thought the effects were really great.
I felt like I was in the fucking spaceship.
We don't need to talk sound and all that.
Song.
I don't even know most of these songs.
Animated Feach.
Incredibles 2 didn't see it.
I love dogs, not good.
And I didn't I saw Spider -Man into the end of the Spider -Verse.
I'm playing it close to the Vest folks, but I didn't like this movie.
All right, I'll see it at some point and then we'll do it.
Ralph breaks the internet and Mariah.
I mean, Spider -Man's going to win that.
There's no question about it.
I don't know.
I wouldn't be surprised if Incredibles 2 won.
That was that was a long time coming sequel, dude.
All right, like that was that that movie was that first one was huge.
Documentary, so they don't nominate the absolutely incredible Won't you be my neighbor?
Mr. Rodgers movie that made me weep.
They don't nominate it, but RBG isn't here.
I'm sorry folks.
RBG was a paint by numbers CNN documentary of an interesting woman.
Don't get me wrong, but that should never be nominated and they should be embarrassed.
That's the only one of these that I've seen.
That's all I can really kind of.
What are the other ones?
Free solo, which is supposed to be like a cool mountain climbing.
Yes.
Hale County this morning this evening.
About a nice storm.
It didn't sound pretentious, does it?
Hale County this morning this evening.
Minding the gap.
That's about about vaginas.
And of fathers and sons.
I'm glad you said it.
I was going to say it and I got nervous.
No, it's fine.
Fathers and sons.
Cinematography, the only other one I'm really interested in.
Cold War, the favorite.
Never look away.
Whatever the hell that is.
Roma and a star is born.
I already did this.
Roma.
I'm trying to give you a few that are like easy free ones, but that's all I really got.
The Oscars is ridiculous.
They're going to watch.
Almost never get it right.
I've watched it every year since I was five years old.
I used to do a trivia game with my friends like a pool.
I would have a whole party for the fucking Oscars.
You couldn't nail me down to watch this fucking thing.
I'm way less excited about it these days.
But folks, I mean, come on.
If you're into the movies, you're into the Oscars.
That's true.
I'm into the movies.
I'm not into the Oscars.
This year I think it's going to be a real rough ride.
Whether they get a host or not,
I think it's going to be a uncomfortable night to watch.
And that intrigues me all the more.
I'd rather see a show that's a train wreck,
like the great Franco Hathaway disaster of a few years back,
than see somebody do a pretty funny monologue and leave.
I don't know if it's just that I'm older now,
but I don't know, man.
I can't watch these things anymore.
And I don't know if they were just always like this.
And I just now notice,
or if it's just deteriorated,
but I can't watch these fucking things, dude.
Oh my god, I want to blow my brains out during them.
I think what it is when we were outside of the entertainment industry,
which sometimes it feels like we are.
I mean, you sit and you're like,
oh, what a dream and these people.
Like, you believe everything you see.
And then you come out and start working with actors
and meet these people and you're like, oh, it's all horseshit.
And, you know, you can't go back to the old innocence.
But I still find some fun watching it.
I like to order up some food,
to bottle a wine with the misses and chill out.
If you want to join us, Joe, here's your invite.
Come on over to the house.
We'll watch the Oscars. We'll have a few drinks.
The only thing I could think more depressing than watching the Oscars
is watching them next to two people in love
as I sit there alone drinking wine.
Maybe we'll invite someone over for you to pray upon.
All right.
Dude, why do you always make me sound like a great prey in a bad way?
Oh, you mean, you mean,
pray over?
Like, pray over?
Yeah, pray over, religiously.
Pray for her life.
Oh, right.
You know,
wash.
Uh, we all got to ask your fever.
Thank you, folks, for coming out.
And I hope our picks help you a little bit.
I will say this, when I used to do the pool,
sometimes I'd go off of my own,
and that's always when you wind up winning big
is when you pick what nobody else picks.
But in terms of their choices,
entertainment weekly is always very close.
They are a good magazine for that.
I would recommend them for that.
If you want to hear the first part of this,
where we talk about the history of the Oscars,
that's picture best director.
It's over on the Patreon.
That's not, uh,
let's set over sell the history of the Oscars.
We got into it.
We, we talked a little bit about past.
But I mean, it's, we're not on there.
There'd be like the first ceremony was held in,
in a tent.
It's not Ken Burns,
but we put a little more research into it than normal.
Yeah.
And, uh,
the hog house,
we haven't mentioned in a while over on the Etsy page.
If you want to check out the merch,
uh, thank you to Emily Florence for keeping that running so well.
Uh, Happy Birthday to Emily Florence.
A little late.
I think your birthday is today,
but you'll be hearing this on Monday,
so it'll be late.
Happy Birthday to you.
The cool kids
is on the Fox channel.
It's also on Hulu.
You can catch up on Hulu.
You can watch the new episodes on Fox.
Uh, DVR it,
watch it within three days,
whatever.
I got to get this thing renewed, baby.
Uh,
I'm on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh.
Joe, what do you got?
Joe DeRose a comedy on Instagram.
Joe DeRose a comedian on Facebook.
You can go to the Facebook page to see my new sandwich videos.
Hogi's heroes, uh,
two were up now.
There's four more coming fairly soon.
Um, oh, and I guess you never need a guest.
We haven't had guests yet, but we might.
All right.
You're at the top of my list.
I don't know how to make any sandwiches,
but I would just feed you the sandwich.
Oh, great.
It'd be more like a, like a Mario battale,
like when he cooks for the person sitting across the desk.
Great.
And then I, and then I would also whip my dick out in front of you.
Oh, like battale.
Did he do that?
He did something like that.
He did.
Anyway, I, uh,
if you're in Tampa, Florida,
and just happen to be going on
the impractical joker's cruise this week,
I'll be there.
So come say hi if you're on that boat with me.
Let's have a drink.
Uh,
and I guess that's it for plugs.
Oh, and head over to patreon .com slash burr.
B -U -R -R.
Brand new episodes of The Unformed Show
with Bill and myself two per month
for five bucks.
Uh, that's it.
Thoughts we'll see you next time,
and we'll see you in hell.