Summer is here, and Bed MGM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer, or check out our
exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz, only available at Bed MGM
Casino.
Spin on Spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp, Raken Bacon,
Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from Anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bed MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bed MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Bed MGM game sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bed MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia
only, games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal throwable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamber.
The football season is full of guarantees.
And here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if your
football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 plus.
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamber.
Offer not available in all states, terms apply, see fanatic sportsbook app.
It's a good show!
Welcome to We'll see you at Hell, it's your podcast for horror movies and the sci -fi
pegs sometimes.
We do the action shows once in a while.
We'll do some drama or a comedy.
Why that song?
We can sing anything we want.
There's no rights issues.
That's always my joke on the show.
We'll put somebody to love by Queen in the scene and then we're like you know by the time
this air is it's going to wind up being a camp town ladies, which is one of the free songs
you can use.
But I hate that song and I hated you singing it.
I did.
Good to see you too.
Sorry.
I didn't tell ladies a terrible melody.
I don't like it.
Can't tell races first of all.
Camp Town ladies.
It's not Camp Town ladies.
To me the song's all about those Camp Town ladies.
I didn't say I liked the song, it's with the mood struck me and I ran with it.
You think I love every goddamn song you sing?
No.
Thank you.
Folks, this week we're talking about Wes Craven's Immortal Classic, The Hills Have
Eyes, babe.
The fucking Hills have fucking eyes.
Okay.
Yeah.
What are the, what are the, does the fuck do the planes have fucking ears?
Power.
You think you think your vacation was bad where I'm at the Hills have freaking eyes, babe.
Okay.
You got anything worse than that?
We'll talk about it later.
Much later.
We're here.
We're having fun.
We're talking tonight about movies, we're talking about life, we're getting on with the
show and at the same time, on with the Joe, very nice little song, not the only one that
can sing.
I liked it.
Joe, what's happening in your life?
Pat, I bought a scooter as you know, I know about the scooter, I know about the cruise
you're going on in.
I also bought a car too.
When did you buy a car?
A guy was selling a jag, a mint jag, cherry, babe, three days ago.
You buy a scooter so that you can get around, three days after that you buy a car.
Here's why I bought it.
A guy selling a classic jag on the street privately.
The price was insane, it was a mint condition, it was too good to deal to pass up, I snagged
it.
Did you run any sort of tests or I could test drove it, I ran the van, I did all that shit
yeah.
About a Saturn once on the drive home, the side view mirror fell off.
I said promise, I said I got $1 ,000 to my name, I'm giving you $1 ,000, please tell me
if this car is going to work, I need this car to work, I got to get the job interviews,
I'm new to LA, please don't lie to me.
He was like you got it man, give him $1 ,000 on the way home, the side view mirror falls off.
Oh he saw you coming from a mile away, didn't he?
Might as well have a piece of wheat in my mouth.
It's wearing a barrel, it probably didn't help that you walked up to him holding two
suitcases, the bus ticket, you're welcome to the jungle playing in the background, I got
a scream in and for you, want me to hit you early with it?
Sure, I mean congrats on the car, so what are you going to do with the scooter?
I'm still going to ride the scooter, I still don't have a driver's license right now.
So I bought the car from when I have a driver's license.
You bought a scooter in a car you got no drivers license.
Well I can drive that you don't need one for the scooter, that's why I got the scooter.
Do you ever try to reinstate your license in this fucking state?
It's a nightmare deal.
These fucking DMVs are a nightmare, it's like two month waiting period.
I explained all this to you last night, but this car was so cheap and so beautiful
and I thought I'm going to have a license sooner or later and I'm going to need a car when
that day comes, why would I not just grab this?
I have a space to put it in and I feel great about the investment.
Looked it up, got it for, whoo, it was a deal, I don't want to talk numbers, but scream
and add a little film directed by Steven Knight, starring Matthew McConaughey and Anne Hathaway.
Oh yeah, what's that thing called?
Serenity.
I've heard it's among the worst films of all time.
It's an American thriller.
Here's why I want to see it.
Now it's already outdone, it's budget.
Oh no, it hasn't, sorry, that's in 48.
It's made 4 .8 million in the box office.
It's budget was 25 million, president.
People are running to see this thing now because there were several reviews coming out saying
there is a twist that is so bad shit.
We got to go see them.
That the critics are like, we can't add of you needing to see this, I don't want to ruin
it for you.
We got to go see them.
So, I'm in.
Be the next Goddy.
I'm in.
Well, Goddy had no twists.
Well, we're going to have to move real fast on this movie if we're going to see it, but
I'm down this weekend.
Well, you're going out of town.
We're never going to see it.
We'll never see it.
Maybe it's on one of those, it's on demand or something.
Yeah, I just saw a preview of Matthew McConaughey in the new Harmony Karin movie.
I am a massive fan of spring breakers and it looks to be along those lines, I can immediately
shot to the top of my list because I really love spring breakers.
I want to see it.
It looks much funnier than most Harmony Karin movies, but I'm sure it'll turn disgusting
and tragic at some point.
I'm sure it will.
Is that the screaming in?
Yeah, I just, you know, I think that's fascinating.
That critic reviews about this movie and how crazy the twist are is what's making the movie
be seen now.
Sure.
And I want to see it real bad.
All right.
Man, the McConaughey in half the way, those two, dude, they do some amazing films and
they make some bad fucking choices.
No question.
Flexing choices.
Wild.
Some of the choices they make.
Wild choices.
Who's going to tame your world choices?
Who's going to ride you?
Wild choices.
Folks, let me take you over to Pat's movie corner.
I saw a picture, the directorial debut of Jonah Hill mid 90s.
I was really hoping we could get more product out of Jonah Hill in different ways.
Thank God.
You want to see him kind of spread his wings.
Yeah, I'm hoping he puts a band out at some point.
Sure.
That's coming.
Yeah.
Mid 90.
Jonah Hill.
All right.
Look, I played poker with the guy once.
He was an asshole.
He was very funny.
He was very, he was an asshole.
He was an asshole, but what he was saying was very funny.
It almost felt like being with, you know, like Don Rickles or something.
Great answer.
All right, all right, fair.
Leveled everyone at the table.
But you know, I don't know anything about the dude.
I like him enough as an actor, depending on the role, I think he's kind of limited, but
I like him in some movies.
I don't like that he lost weight.
I'm going to say it till the day I die.
Then just wait a week.
I don't like theater.
It'll be back.
But, you know, mid 90s, he's not in it.
It's his writing directorial debut.
It seems inspired by Harmony Karin so that makes him for a nice transition, but it's got
that kind of kids feel to it.
The movie kids that was so scandalous when I was in high school.
Basically, it's like a 12 year old kid who I guess is supposed to be the stand in for Jonah
Hill.
It feels autobiographical.
He's a big skater.
The whole time you're watching it, you're like, was Jonah Hill really a hardcore skater into
the punk scene?
I don't know.
There's no way.
The first movie he's in, he's like 16 and he's a house.
It's very possible that it was not autobiographical.
I don't know that much about the process behind the movie.
I will say it felt like it was going for that sort of personal thing.
It's a young skater.
He does something very dangerous and aligns himself with a older, more reckless, experienced
crew.
He's got a strained relationship with his mom, a super strained relationship with his
older brother, played by the hedges kid.
What's the hedges?
I don't even know if he'd heard hedges his dad, but Lucas hedges, the guy from Lady Bird and
Manchester, I see.
Oh, I like that guy.
He's a good actor and he's playing like a bully older brother, yeah, bully face.
Yeah.
He's like the bully older brother.
And, you know, it's all unknowns.
He's a delinquent.
He gets worse and worse as the movie goes.
At one point, a seemingly 18 year old girl takes him into a room and you're like, please
don't show us this 12 year old boy fucking this older woman.
And they kind of do, she takes her clothes off.
He's like shirtless and like she moves her hands on him and stuff.
I was just kind of like, why, why do we go in the room here, Jonah Hill?
I don't know that we needed to.
It makes some odd choices.
It feels like it lasts about an hour.
I think the movie's like 75 minutes long.
And it just feels like something you've seen a million times before.
It's very meandering.
It feels like a student film.
It does have a great 90s soundtrack, you know, some pixies, some great stuff.
Stuff that you feel like every time your song starts in, you're like, you weren't listening
to this, Jonah, you were listening to probably smash mouth or something.
You know, like, he moments like that.
I think the soundtrack was a huge part of it for him.
Yeah, well, look, I don't know anything about the guy.
The movie, even though I'm giving it a pretty bad rap here, it's entertaining.
Yeah, you took a real left turn on that one.
I thought you were going to say you liked it.
No, it's entertaining enough.
That's what I'll tell you.
It's nothing great.
And there is a car crash scene in it, which does not really be spoiler that was shot in
such a way that I gasped.
I was horrified by it.
And it's hard to make a car crash carry when every movie does that gag of a guy walking
into the street and getting hit by a car.
This one was really upsetting.
But the movie as a whole, not entirely successful, I thought it was pretty good, Joe.
Yeah, I saw my three this week are documentaries.
First is called Perfect Bid.
Never heard of it.
It's a documentary about a lifelong price is right, fanatic, that was so into the show.
He had watched every episode.
He built his own computer programs, he was a mathematician.
And he built his own computer programs to play the prices right at home in order to
memorize the price lists of everything.
Because he noticed after being a fan for a while that they would repeat products.
So he made a huge database of products and memorized the price of every single product.
And then started going to the tapings and you know, you can yell out from the audience and
getting people like, they would say, like if they listened to him, they would get it
like literally on the fucking dollar.
And then he got in trouble, not in trouble, but he got banned from the show during the
Drew Carey years because he went in and helped a couple bid.
And when they bid, the guy beat the entire show, like the final whatever the fuck it's
called.
Yeah, on the exact dollar.
And he was trying to tell the guy not to do that because he was like, it's going to be
weird.
And that made people think that he was cheating, which he wasn't cheating.
He just had the savant level knowledge of memorization.
And then the guy that got the number from him became kind of famous for a little while.
Like the man who beat the price is right.
And then went out and did all these radio interviews and was like, I did my homework.
I watched the show and like didn't give the guy any credit whatsoever and got all the fucking
glory.
And and then Drew Carey says in an interview at the end of it, like we've we pitch products
so much now that'll never happen ever again.
Like we have made it our goal that that will never happen.
Yeah.
So it was a fun documentary.
I mean, it wasn't fantastic.
It had its moments.
It's a lot of the guy just kind of telling his story.
And it doesn't veer off of that quite enough to be sort of visually intriguing.
It gets a bit repetitive, but but I thought the story was fascinating.
Okay.
And I thought it was cool to see a guy who did all this work and memorized all this stuff who
at no point comes off like a weirdo or a creep.
It's weird.
You're kind of waiting for that turn where he's going to be with, but even says at one point,
like how like his favorite woman on the price is right was a forget her name.
How like he got a chance to talk to her and he didn't overdo it.
He's like, I didn't want to be that guy.
I didn't want to ask her for an autograph.
And he's like, and then she ended up just bringing me one out of the kindness of her heart.
It's odd how regular he seems for his fanaticism about this show.
There's a Hulu duck.
I think I saw it on Prime.
It's the first time I duck.
Folks, I saw a picture called Bad Times at the Ele Royale.
How was that?
But starring Jeff Bridges and the girl from 50 shades of things and also who's the pretty
boy from Ghostbusters?
Is it Chris Hemsworth?
Thor.
Look, the movie's directed by Drew Goddard.
He sent it out like in some top secret box and it led to this big bidding war.
You know, it sounded like what they used to do in the 90s when they really put a lot of
panache into these sales, trying to sell them.
I like Goddard.
I like Cabin in the woods.
I thought the Martian was kind of entertaining.
I really like Cloverfield.
I love World War Z.
The guy does good work.
This movie for my money was not good.
It was Tarantino -ish, which I had heard, but it's like a bunch of strangers come to
this hotel, the Ele Royale, it's mysterious, and a bunch of bad shit goes down.
Basically, the movie was kind of a clever gimmick, but they don't pay it off, so like the
whole time you're waiting for this twist that doesn't really come.
The twists that are there are either shown in the trailer or happen very early.
It's very violent and it ultimately leads to nothing.
It's kind of this cool thing when you realize that like the bell boy, this is a half hour
in, but he goes around in this tunnel in the hotel and he can watch into everybody's
rooms.
That's a cool gimmick.
He also makes videos and sometimes pornographic videos that he sends to like this big boss who
gets his kicks from him.
That's kind of some sick, interesting twist in that region there.
But as soon as you realize what's going on, you're like, oh, this would have made an awesome
half hour twilight zone or an awesome hour -long black mirror.
This movie is 2 .30.
Oh, come on.
It's 2 .30 for no reason, and at about the time when I was like, can we wrap this up?
I realized Chris Hemsworth hadn't even been seen yet.
Oh, good.
Then he comes in and starts a whole new story.
There's flashbacks to him.
Anytime you're doing flashbacks at the two hour and 10 minute mark, you haven't constructed
your screenplay well, in my opinion, unless you're revealing something.
To me, every scene in this movie was too long.
The movie as a whole was too long.
I like the actors.
I like bridges.
There was enough in it to say like, I guess it was kind of cool if you're on a plane
but beyond that, I can't recommend this movie.
It left me very cold.
I just didn't want to see it.
Anytime they show a trailer for something like that and they're like, the coolest movie of the...
I like to shut the fuck up.
Yeah, it felt like that.
It felt like...
What it felt was all those movies that came out post -pulp fiction, like a thing to do in Denver
when you're dead or something.
I love that movie.
I'm just picking an example, but it felt sort of like a paint by numbers retread
of the...
It's not the dialogue feels Tarantino -ish.
It's just something about the setup.
It all feels kind of like a lot of smoke and mirrors that don't amount to much and all the
secrecy and all the...
I think they sold this thing for like a million bucks.
It's like...
Really?
It just shows how easily people are swayed.
The motley crew of characters and the priest who's a thief, it's stupid.
It's been done.
All right.
My second docu -thing that I watched was a docu -series called America's Monsters.
It's only like four episodes and each episode, they cover two...
They're an hour each.
Again, this was on prime and they cover two of America's famous, fabled monsters.
So like the first episode I think is Bigfoot and the Mothman.
Okay.
You know, and then there's like a Loch Ness monster one and another whatever the fuck.
You know, so...
Or no, first of all, it's Mothman and the Bellwitch and then there's like a Bigfoot and Loch Ness
monster and then, you know.
You get it.
It's like a little...
It's got the feel or vibe that like a travel channel show would have.
Right.
It's not super dark.
It has dark moments, but some of it's very light and almost playful about like the history
of the lore and how the town celebrates it and that sort of thing.
But I love stuff like that.
I want monsters to be real, really bad.
And anything along those lines, I'll watch it because it gives me hope quite frankly.
Okay.
I watched another one of my Oscar screeners called Widows.
This was a decent hit at the box office over the holiday season, Star's Veola Davis directed
by Steve McQueen who did 12 years of slave.
Look, this movie is incredibly entertaining.
I hadn't talked to anybody who had seen it, but it's like really fun.
It's a fun, heist movie.
It's got a fun gimmick, you know, these women's husbands all get killed in a heist gone wrong
and the women know where the spoils of the heist are located.
So the women join forces to get the fortune, the wives, kind of like a set it off feel,
if you ever saw that movie, which is a great action movie by F. Gary Gray from the 90s.
Widows has an incredible cast, probably overqualified cast for the story.
It's telling, but Veola Davis, Daniel Kaluya from Get Out being like a very threatening villain,
a really good performance.
Liam Neeson as Veola Davis's husband is great in it.
Michelle Rodriguez is pretty fun as always.
Colin Farrell doing a terrible Chicago accent, but he's fun to see in it.
Lucas Haas acting again after like 10 years off, also in first man, but a good actor.
Brian Tyree Henry from Atlanta, Robert DuVal shows up for a ludicrous scene or two.
It's just a super stack cast.
You know everybody in it, and it's one of those movies where you're like, yeah,
this is exactly what I wanted on like a Sunday afternoon.
It's a good heist.
It's not as good, maybe it's like an inside man, but it gives you that kind of feel.
Just a heist where everything's thought out well, everything makes sense.
And it's, you know, it's not so convoluted you don't know what's going on.
Good acting.
It's well done.
Set in Chicago, which I always like, I recommend it.
OK, my final pick is a documentary called The Flatwoods Monster.
Again, another monster documentary.
Yes, there's a company called Smalltown Monsters.
They're producing a bunch of documentaries about this sort of thing.
You know, Smalltown American Monsters, the Flatwoods Monster.
I believe took place in Pennsylvania, so I was attracted to it because I'm from there.
These things are really, they didn't do the other series I was talking about,
but they have a few of these docs that they did on prime.
I watched a bunch of them.
I really enjoyed them.
They're very, very well shot.
They're much more sinister feeling than American Monsters is.
They definitely lean into the darker curve of this whole thing.
And I would recommend checking them out.
They're a lot of fun.
All right, great.
I'd like to, if I could talk about scary stuff for a moment, I got one too.
Take the reins.
I presented Joe tonight with a small token of my affection.
A blue ray copy of whose hairy crumb dolled up to look like a rental VHS.
I thought this was a great gift idea that Joe would appreciate.
A man who's always buying older and older games.
Which is why I feel bad for spinning on it and throwing it to the ground.
I didn't love that either.
Yes.
But there is a small selection of these on Amazon.
And that's where I got it.
To me, the only one I really wanted to get was whose hairy crumb.
But they offer all kinds of horror movies and really kind of cheesy bad stuff.
It's worth adding to your collection, I think, just for the packaging.
And I recommend you check them out.
That's all I got.
I'm going to go video game, Pat, as I usually do.
Ooh, she's got a headache.
Oh, ow, ow.
Is that bad?
I mean, headaches are bad, yeah.
It hurts on the side.
Do you think I have a brain tumor or something?
I don't think you have a brain tumor.
Oh my god, that hurts.
Well, let me tell you what to search.
Well, Joe's going through this.
Blu -ray retro VHS.
Those are the boxes.
They offer last action hero, Sheena, which is softcore porn, if I remember from my childhood.
Sheena.
Neighbors with Acroid and Blue Sheat, not a good movie.
Neither's the Randy Quaid one.
No.
Cruel, which Joe said he loved, I've never seen.
As a kid, I don't know if it's still good.
Hard bodies, which I used to crank it to all the time, even edited.
What was hard bodies?
It's one of those softcore deals from the 80s.
And that's about it.
There's only a select few.
For me, you got to get who's Harry Crumb.
I wouldn't mind that last action here, to be honest.
I like last action hero, underrated.
Video games for scary stuff, Injustice 2, I finally got it.
It's been out for a long time, I know.
But if you like fighters and you like superheroes and you like superhero fighters, you
are not going to do better than Injustice 2.
It's the DC fighter created by the same people that make, developed by the same company
that does Mortal Kombat.
So it's got a very similar look to the new Mortal Kombat games.
Speaking of bonus scary stuff, Mortal Kombat 11 has been announced.
Some new characters are coming in.
It looks like Pennywise is one of the horror characters this time around.
And Michael Myers.
And it looks fucking awesome.
But anyway, Injustice 2, really great, terrific character roster.
I'm going to read it to you now.
You got Batman.
You got Superman.
You got Wonder Woman.
You got Supergirl.
You got Aquaman.
You got a trust, a tracetus.
I don't know who that is.
He's a bad guy, though.
Gorilla Groud.
So fucking cool.
One of my favorite flash villains.
Deadshot.
Harley Quinn.
She's always in these games.
And she's great.
The Flash.
My favorite guy to play with.
Blue Beetle.
Bane.
Always very cool.
Poison.
Ivy.
Brainiac.
Very, very, very cool addition.
Dr. Fait.
Very cool.
Cyborg.
He's usually, you know, Batman.
Those guys, they're usually standards.
Cheetah.
Who I don't think was in the last game.
Catwoman.
How long is this going to go?
Swamp thing.
Which I am very excited about.
I love the Swamp thing.
Black Canary.
Should I step out?
Robin.
I'm just reading the character list of the people.
Can I, is that okay with you?
The, uh, and you maybe miss, oh no, I got it right.
Green Lantern.
Excellent.
Dopey.
Joker.
Red Hood.
Firestorm.
Green Arrow.
Starfire.
Black Adam.
Any of these names?
Do anything for you, Pat?
Starfucker.
Stubb sub zero.
Shutter combat.
Captain cold.
Awesome.
Black Manta.
Scarcro.
Awesome.
Raiden.
For Mortal combat.
Dark side.
Awesome.
Adam.
TMNT.
How fucking cool is that?
Enchantress.
Unless but not least.
Hellboy.
That's quite a roster, people.
Donner.
That was like when I read some comment.
Cupid.
You just can't turn it off, can you?
What makes me wonder if you ever had it turned on?
The fans don't want it off.
Folks, we're going to take a quick break for a word
from our sponsor.
I'll see you next time.
All right, we're back.
Folks, I guess we'll get to our picture, right?
The hills have eyes.
We've never gotten to a movie this early into the show.
I mean, look, I watched it on Shutter.
I assume it's still up there.
I watched it with the Joe Bob Briggs.
It was part of the Thanksgiving marathon,
which was called like dinners of death or something like that.
Yeah, it was all cannibal movies.
Look, he had one of the, he had the guy
with the big crazy eyes interviewed.
It was a very sweet interview.
I'm glad I watched it.
There's nothing brings me more joy these days
and sitting down with a Joe Bob and a horror.
And I still have something to go through.
That said, this was one of my least favorite he's shown.
I know I saw when I was a kid when I was trying to check off
this book of like the hundred greatest movies
ever made in each genre.
And this was on the horror list.
And folks, in my opinion, not deservedly so.
I think the movie, I remember more
and had more of an impact on me,
not that I love this movie either,
was the remake, Alejandra Ahaz version.
I own that, I've never watched it.
It was really scary and disturbing.
And I don't ever want to watch it again.
But it stuck with me a lot more than this legendary movie,
Wes Craven's The Hills Have Eyes,
which to me was dull.
Just long scenes of people walking through the desert, you know,
like I don't really remember any great scares in it.
The cannibals were not scary to me.
The people they were stalking were unlikable at best.
I just wasn't into it.
It's an okay movie.
It's not one of my favorites.
I mean, but it is a different type of horror movie.
It certainly is more of an exploitation film.
Sure.
That's supposed to sort of rattle your cage, you know,
we, for instance, when they fucking take the baby
and you think they might murder a baby, right?
That's nerve -wracking.
Well, apparently in the original draft,
they ate the baby and the actor was like,
no, I'm not doing the same.
You can fire me, but I'm not doing the same.
So they cut it.
They say they're gonna eat the baby in it,
but they did in the original apparently.
But not, but it was fake, right?
Yeah.
I mean, human didn't eat a baby on, no, no.
Thank God for that.
I mean, this came on the heels sort of
of last house on the left, which is also remade,
was also remade, which that remakes sucked.
It's 1977.
Interesting fact about, so first of all,
it coming after last house on the left,
it's interesting to me because it seems,
there's a lot of it to me mimics that movie, you know,
it's kind of the same thing, like a pack of brutal people,
prey upon a pack of innocent people
and do horrible things to them.
But there's some interesting trivia
with this movie.
I'm reading from Wikipedia right now,
and I wanted to make a point to do this
because I learned some stuff.
Craven based the film script on the legend
of cannibal Saunee Bean, which Craven viewed
as illustrating how supposedly civilized people
could become savage.
That is sort of in there.
I don't really see that.
No.
This is when they always want to put in those documentaries
whether like horror was so much more about the scares, man,
like in the 70s, it was a commentary on Vietnam,
whatever, this movie is just a cannibal in the desert movie.
I didn't get much else out of it.
Other influences for this movie, you ready for this?
Yes.
The grapes of wrath.
Okay.
Fuck.
Yeah, some critics interpret the film
as containing commentary on morality and American politics.
Yeah, if you mean like the morality of cannibals are bad,
sure, yeah, it addressed that theme.
And it does, I understand it was supposed to be like,
look what it drives the civilized people to do.
Right.
Well, it's more like they're just trying to survive.
Yeah.
Like in the last house on the left,
doesn't she like bite a guy's dick off or something?
Like it's way.
I think so, yeah.
You know, where's the thing I'm looking for though?
Hold on, development.
West Craven, in 1977, desired to make a non -horror film
following his directorial debut last house on the left
from 1972 because he saw the hard genre as constraining,
which is interesting because as we talked about
in a previous episode, I think it was our bonus app.
We talked about how guys like Adam McKay
are so good at comedy, yet they demand they do this other thing.
Right.
Instead of just utilizing their gift,
and it's interesting to me that West Craven kind of wanted
to do that too, he, I guess looked a little bit down
on horror, not, you know, maybe downs are on word,
but he couldn't find producers interested
in financing a project that did not feature bloody violence.
So Craven's friend producer, Peter Locke,
was interested in financing a horror exploitation film
and Craven decided to write the project due
to his monetary issues.
Craven considered collaborating with Sean S. Cunningham
on the horror children's film based on Hansel and Gretel.
That would have been fucking awesome.
But Locke wanted the film to be more in the vein
of last house on the left.
What the fuck would that have been like?
Hansel and Gretel, why has that never been done?
There's been a Hansel and Gretel horror movie.
I think it just sucked, but the only one I know
is the witch hunter's one.
Right, but I think they have made it.
Look, I, to me, this was a below average horror movie.
And when I was that night, part of the fun
of watching these marathons live is you actually
do the hashtag, I so rarely do that shit,
but you see what everybody's saying
about the movie in real time.
And that one man, like people, as pumped as they were
about Joe Bob, they were just kind of like,
oh, this movie's not great.
And it isn't.
Well, and I think it played second to Texas Chainsaw, didn't it?
It did, correct.
And it's a huge lot down from that.
You can't, how are you going to,
because that was an influence on this movie,
but I mean, how are you going to follow Texas Chainsaw
message? Yeah.
What else was in the dinners of death, by the way?
Blood feast or blood rage?
One of the two, okay.
You know the one that you talked about on here,
the really old one?
Yeah, the one from that set over there,
what's his face?
A brain is mush right now.
And also the other dinner of death was...
Hershel Lewis, that's...
Hershel Lewis, yes.
And let me look, I watched all the dinner of deaths,
and I'm still working on Christmas,
because there was 13 movies.
Dinner of death, Joe Bob Briggs.
Oh, Christmas was just fantastic, wasn't it?
Christmas is fantastic, but he had the first one
where he came back.
That was the 13.
Oh, that was the Halloween one, correct.
Okay.
You can't find anything online anymore, God damn it.
Chainsaw hills have eyes, dead are alive,
the Takeshi Miyake, which was super fucked up,
but crazy Japanese movie.
Was it good?
Yeah, it was really fun.
I mean, good, I don't know, but...
Is that also about cannibals?
No, I wouldn't say it is.
You do see dogs fucking it, if that interests you.
Where do I sign up?
Blood feast was actually on his first marathon.
Okay.
And what showed was 1987's Bloodrage,
which was a pretty good Thanksgiving horror movie.
Bloodrage, definitely like a second tier,
but it was like really fun and trashy.
I'm unfamiliar with Bloodrage.
Yeah, it was new to me as well.
That's what I like.
He does some classics, you know, Hellraiser,
or whatever, he also throws you some you never heard of
and they wound up being really cool.
I googled Bloodrage and what came up
is a Viking themed board game.
Okay, scoop it up.
Bloodrage, 1987 Slasher film with Bruce.
Wow, you know, it's always a bad scene
when the director's name isn't in blue on the Wikipedia.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, gosh, poor bastard.
Oh, but it's set on Thanksgiving.
You got a Wikipedia page?
Yeah, yeah.
I don't want one, don't make me one,
but, you know, my name's on Wikipedia
and then I'm also like a notable alumni
of Francis Hall High School.
That's nice.
No matter where I mentioned, I ain't blue
because I don't got my own page.
I'm fine with it.
I don't want people to be able to be like,
oh, he smells like farts, you know.
Pat, I didn't want one either
but the fans get what the fans want
and the fans made a page.
Yeah, yeah.
I just don't like that you can change it,
you know, there could be horrible things written about,
you never know.
No, they, but they put, it's police for that.
That happened to me and it gets taken down.
I would imagine it happened to you.
Oh, you know, you got a bastard
and you're bastard people.
I mean, because you had all those haters for so long
and I assume still do.
Pat, I got to tell you something.
I am digging deep to try to think of something else
to say about the hills, have eyes.
I had another goddamn word to say about it.
Well, it was okay.
And you haven't seen the remake to compare it to.
I don't love it.
I didn't, I didn't love it.
You can't see the west hill, you can't see the west hill.
What, what's your take on hills in general?
Are you mean boobs?
Did you ever watch MTV's the hills?
I did.
I never saw it, was it addictive?
Did you watch a bunch of it?
Uh, I fell in love instantly with Lauren Conrad
and wanted to marry her.
So I was going to watch it for that reason.
but yeah, it had an addictive quality to it.
I understand why people got into it.
I mean, it was the first, the hills,
I believe was the first reality show
to be shot like an actual show.
Right.
You know, and I had never seen that before.
I'd only seen like the real world
where it's like, you know, it's very obviously a docu -series.
Yeah.
And they shot the show, the hills, like it was
a fucking scripted show, but it wasn't.
I mean, I'm sure it was, you know, nudged.
I've seen small moments of it.
It never interested me.
I was always a temptation island guy.
How do you just, you're just a horny bastard.
I would do Jersey Shore.
Temptation Island is back now on USA
and I might watch the news season.
Now let me ask you a question.
The show was sick.
They put you on an island with people
that are your exact physical and emotional type
and try to get you to cheat on your husband
or wife or girlfriend or boyfriend.
It was crazy show.
And they all did.
Did you like cheaters?
Cheaters I could give or take.
That often seemed set up to me.
Yeah, the older I got the more, you know what?
It was a real let down was a,
I remember being so excited for scare tactics
and then you work in the business for like two minutes
and you're like, oh, that's all fake.
Right, yeah.
There's no way that's real.
That was a bummer.
Yeah, I mean, Temptation Island was in that early
like Fox Lee's reality.
They'd do anything for a rating days.
The Fox they were pigs when they came out sick.
They had that show where the guy was like
putting the laser light pointer on the cellulite
on women's legs and stuff.
Remember that, remember their first two sitcoms
were married with children
and then the other one was Herman in prison.
Oh, I was like in Herman's head.
I guess it was.
I remember women in prison with Mary Joe,
what's her face from back to the future?
Sperber.
Wendy Joe Sperber.
Yeah, it was about five women in prison.
It was a multi -cam sitcom.
You know, I pitched and was turned down
a multi -cam sitcom about prison
because it seems like why wouldn't you?
Those shows have to exist on a few sets.
It gives you a reason to not leave.
Then I think, you know,
orange is a new black Camelot.
Not that it was down to me or them,
but nobody wanted my idea.
It's always been between you and them.
Yeah, I would you feel about how do you feel about eyes?
I like eyes.
I don't notice them.
I don't, I feel like almost nobody in my life
what I know what color their eyes are.
Would you say they're my best feature?
What color are my eyes, Joe?
Brown.
My eyes are blue.
What color are my eyes?
Brown.
Blue.
So that we don't know each other at all.
I mean, Joe and I have spent,
you don't know me by now.
If you don't know me.
I mean, that's how little, like, you know,
women always do it.
Like if my wife tonight was like,
you don't know my eye color, it would wound her.
Guys can know each other for five years,
spend days together.
What is this?
Tim Allen routine.
And have no idea what they're like.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
What color the eyes are?
No, we don't care.
Good Lord.
Right out of a home improvement script.
I mean, guys don't care.
Yeah, that was feeling very 80s stand up.
Little Paul Provenza.
Provenza, I know he would never do a bit like that.
All right, fine.
He gave Provenza credit.
I was just talking.
I wasn't trying to do a damn bit right now.
You are right, though.
But I'll tell you, ask a fellow
what a woman's cleavage looks like.
He could describe it from memory.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
That's, uh, do it as Woody Allen.
Often men are completely unfamiliar with the details
of a woman.
Oh, it's being, of course, not about the cleavage.
Ha, ha, ha.
That was good.
I like to tell you included the dry mouth,
like cat food, uh, tongue lick.
Yeah, he's always like belching or something.
Yeah, some sort of gas thing going on.
Yeah, I, I, I, I, I, uh, well, folks, that's our show, I think.
I think so.
It's a little short today.
We cut today's a little short.
Joe's heading back out of town, you know, well, I'm,
I've already the, the marriage is a shambles.
When this, when this comes out, I will already have returned
from the trip, but I have to, but as we record this,
I have to go on a two week run, which we talked about on one
of the other previous episodes.
I leave tomorrow.
I didn't know I was leaving for that long until, uh, basically today.
Right.
And, uh, so we had to squeeze three episodes together tonight, uh,
and this is the third one.
And we're not trying to cheat anybody.
We want to, we want to give you your free podcast worth.
And I, I think you got it.
I do too.
I hope you got it.
And if you don't, I hope you get it.
Yeah.
I mean, we're trying to not have to skip a week.
We, we wish we had a more exciting movie.
I mean, it just doesn't inspire a lot of, a lot of chatter.
I think this might be one of those cases of like a super influential
movie that, when you go back and check it out, you're like, yeah,
this has been doubled and tripled a thousand times over.
I thought it was going to carry us a lot farther.
Also, and for some reason, I'm so dumb.
I didn't think like, I should watch the remake too.
And then we could talk about that.
Sure.
The remake is very intense.
And, uh, you know, I would say not, not a fun watch.
It's one of those, you know, that, that kind of horror movie that's just sort
of like rubbing your face and depravity kind of thing.
Well, I watch it and we can do that on a later app.
Okay.
I don't want to watch it again though.
You don't have to.
Don't make me watch it again.
You've already seen it.
I'll just watch it.
All right.
Plugged.
Jotaro's a comedy on Instagram.
Jotaro's a comedian on Facebook.
Go to the Facebook page.
Give it a like.
Check out my Hogi's heroes sandwich making videos, uh, and upcoming gigs.
I will be doing bonkers comedy club in March.
In Las Vegas.
Good, good chance.
Patty Walsh will be with me.
That's right for your emotional support and booze drinking after the shows.
Um, I think it's just two shows, uh, and I'll get you more specific details soon.
But Helian's come on out and enjoy yourselves.
I am the Patrick Walsh on Twitter and Instagram.
Cool kids.
There's Friday nights on the Fox Network or you can watch it on Hulu as well.
Folks, thank you very much.
We'll be back.
Joe and I are still planning that Aquaman watch.
So you might want to check that out in preparation.
Um, but thank you for listening.
If you want to check out our Oscars podcast, get the Patreon.
And we will see you next time.
We'll also see you in hell.
We'll see you in the next one.