I'll you another episode of We'll see you in hell in today
Hey, we're talking, oh boy, we're talking about the end of an era, aren't we, Walsh?
We are.
We're talking about the end of the latest Halloween franchise, Halloween ends, which
technically, yeah, is the end of the franchise as we know it because these are, do you think
some of them?
Well, these are continuing, this is the end of the original franchise.
Yes.
All right, because they were considering this a sequel to the original Halloween, this franchise.
Okay.
And everybody knows that when you want to end a horror franchise the right way, you patches
got up and walked.
It looks to turn off lights.
He literally just stood up and walked away as I was speaking.
I've seen a light go on and off.
The light is back on, pad is sitting back down.
Sorry, it was blinding me.
That's okay.
Everyone knows that when you end a franchise that the dice are loaded, but in news that the
dice alluded, I was just going to make a crack about you handed off to the guys
that did Eastbound and down.
Who I'm a big fan of those guys, but their comedy work is impeccable.
Yes.
Quite a bit of David Gordon Green's directing stuff.
What else is he directed?
Well, he did all the real girls, which I mentioned, he had a great indie career.
He did a movie called Snow Angels with Sam Rockwell that I thought was excellent.
Okay.
And then he directed, you know, a lot of huge big comedies.
He did your highness was kind of his big bomb.
Yeah.
He did a Pineapple Express, which is a hilarious movie and a good action film.
I do as far as to say a masterpiece, a comedic masterpiece.
Yeah, I mean, I love that, mom.
Front to back.
That's great.
And it's well done with the action and suspense.
Maybe that's where he went wrong with this was like, if it was a comedy horror, it would
have been perfect.
But well, he does action really well on gemstones as well.
He's been down.
He's pretty much a straight comedy, but gemstones brings in these big kind of tron style action
sequences sometimes and he always shoots the hell out of them.
We'll get to Halloween.
I thought that we discussed the last Halloween kills, of course, which I thought was one
of the more sloppily directed big films I've seen in a while.
So I feel like maybe that was rushed, obviously, to meet a deadline.
That was the one in my opinion, the worst Halloween movie ever made, which I said I said on
the podcast.
And I, to me, I don't know, but to me, it's the worst of the recent years, for sure.
Yeah.
I went, I put my money where my mouth was on that one.
The listeners might remember and I went back and I rewatched the worst of the Halloween films.
Right.
And I was like, I can't believe this.
I can't believe this is worse than Halloween six.
Yeah.
Where they claim that Michael Myers is a vessel for inspiration.
Yeah, but all right, evil entity or what a big swing and a miss on that one, but we'll
get to it.
We'll get to it.
So I'm sitting here watching a little bonus movie corner.
Ready for this?
Yeah.
I'm sitting here wide.
I'm in the mood for.
It's been a long day.
I said, I'm in the mood to watch a classic horror movie while I dinner.
So I put on my arrow collector's edition Hellraiser.
True.
Blu -ray.
I hadn't opened it yet since I bought it.
I bought it when I was with you, actually.
Yeah.
And that our Helian friend gave us.
Helped us out at Barnes and Noble.
Yeah.
Anyway, I put it on.
And I'm watching it.
I go.
I love this Ashley learns.
I love her in this movie.
I love her in Hellraiser 2.
I'm a fan Ashley learns.
I go, I should follow her on Instagram.
I don't follow her.
I should, I bet, you know, do one thing.
I go to follower already following your boy.
Wow.
Dominic dropped.
Have you mentioned there before?
Like what brought this on?
I don't know.
I DMed her and I said, hey, weird thing.
I'm sitting here watching Hellraiser.
And I thought to myself, I should follow Ashley Lawrence
on Instagram and I go to your Instagram
and I see you're already following me.
Huge surprise.
I'm a big fan of your work.
This is so cool.
Thank you and nice to meet you, sort of.
Yes.
And I see that the message has been seen.
Oh, not responded to.
All right.
Well, let's check.
It's only, it was only seen 10 minutes ago.
But let's, let's.
Rosa has been blocked.
Nope.
Nothing.
All right.
16 minutes ago.
Maybe she's trying to say it.
Cool.
Either that or she's like, she's got a serenose.
Somebody writing the perfect response.
She's like, I can't blow this.
I've been waiting for Joe Dross that you noticed me.
Blow these many years.
What would you do?
Somehow through some, the chain of events.
Yeah.
I ended up, Ashley Lawrence ended up being the woman of my life.
I'd love it.
I'd love nothing more.
You go to conventions together.
Have you seen the hell Frazier memes that are going around?
No.
How did I miss that?
I mean, you, you can guess.
It's, uh, it's Frazier as pinhead basically.
Sure.
You know, I, I don't know any of them off hand, but it's like,
I've got so many sites to show you.
For example, the opera, you know, stuff like that.
Okay.
There.
You'll, you can find them on Twitter.
They're pretty easy to spot.
Um, I actually just got back from.
Las Vegas.
I went with, uh, a woman who was virtually a stranger to me.
The one from getter.
I was a getter done.
And make it with you.
That, that lady.
Yeah.
Okay.
Um, so yeah, we just went to Vegas spur of the moment.
That's how I'm living my life now quarter mile at a time.
And, uh, we had a really, we had a really good time.
I don't know what to tell you.
We saw.
Yeah.
How do I say this?
No, nevermind.
It's an Eddie Murphy joke.
I thought that was original.
I'm not even going to do it.
Go ahead.
You went to Vegas.
You can quote it to him.
You know, he's that joke.
I put my dick on the craps table many a night, where he talks about having a six.
Yes.
That's a very funny, uh, phrasing.
You're asking if I put my dick on the craps table?
I was good.
Yeah.
I was going to get unprotected sex joke.
And I couldn't.
I couldn't get to it.
That was Eddie Murphy.
Yeah.
I don't know how to play craps.
I always say I'm at capacity with my vices.
So I never learned a new one.
I hear it's fun and a good bonding game.
And everyone always seems to be enjoying themselves.
But I just don't get involved.
Eric Griffin from workaholics.
He was also at Skankfest when I was at Skankfest in Vegas.
And I.
The first time I saw him at the entire festival was at 3 a .m.
Playing craps at the gold nugget.
Alone.
And I don't mean without friends.
I mean, he was the only one at the table.
And I went up to him two times.
Both times I went up to him.
He immediately rolled the seven.
And I was like, this is like the cooler.
I'm so sorry, dude.
Right.
But I went up one of the times.
The first time I went up to him and I was like,
I was like, you're a fucking sociopath.
Like I've never seen anybody do this.
You're playing craps.
You're the only one playing.
Yeah.
And he was like, I like it.
I like to do it like that, man.
It's fun.
It's just me.
That's a comedian mentality.
I like it like a blackjack alone table and etc.
Yeah.
But it was good.
It was a good trip.
We saw.
I got to say I always stay at Cosmo.
I'm not giving them a shout out of who cares.
But they got this show called opium.
I've been going there for 10 years.
And I've always like, I can go see whatever I want there.
You know, I'm a bit of a baller.
And I said, hey, what is this opium show?
And the guy's always like, yeah, it's some like improv thing.
And I'm always like, okay, well,
I'm not going to go to that.
But this time, you know, yeah, I was I didn't need to impress
this broad.
I just met her.
She was already impressed enough.
I'm like, yeah, let's go check out opium.
You know, I'm not dropping the usher money.
So we go over to see the show.
And I had an absolute blast.
It's small.
It's intimate.
People doing like incredible human feats,
but like on a modest scale, I guess, if that makes sense.
So like there's these two guys who were doing acrobatics
just on each other.
But when you're in a tiny like theater in the round,
it's just it was incredible to like see people do this shit.
There was a husband and wife team two of the best looking people
I've ever seen, half naked.
There is nudity in the show as well.
They're both on roller skates.
And he starts spinning around holding her by the feet.
She's just whipping around and around and around
into the audience.
Like skates just like skimming people's glasses in the front row.
Very dangerous shit.
And then he spins her around and starts twirling her by her ponytail.
He's holding her ponytail.
And she's spinning around in circles around his body.
I've never seen anything like it in my life.
Wow.
It's wild to show.
You think you're not going to like it and you love it.
I was out with Brian Quinn one day.
And we were just out day drinking and we met kids from stomp.
And they knew they knew him from in practical jokers and they were like.
Talking to him and then they he was like, what do you guys do?
And they're like for us.
Yeah, he think a word stomp.
It starts in 10 minutes.
Do you guys want to come?
We're like.
Yeah, I guess so.
And we went and I loved it.
And I was like, this is a show I never thought I would have like loved.
Not that I thought it was going to be bad.
I just didn't, you know, it's like blue man group.
It's like one of those shows you hear about.
You go, I don't know.
Yeah, I guess so.
Yeah, you think you're not going to have the interest in that.
If you go, I recommend that it was great.
They do some comedy in it that was like, you know, dirty and funny.
And the performers give it their all.
My favorite was this woman comes out with two different trays.
And each one has like 18 cocktails on it like martinis full of liquid.
Right.
She they're going to do a limbo bit.
So you figure, okay, she's going to try to do it with the glasses.
Okay.
So this guy is going down and he's doing like the lowest limbo under the bar I've ever seen.
And their place is going nuts.
He's basically parallel to the ground.
Okay.
The girl who we've forgotten about practically at this point.
Goes under his legs.
So not only under the bar that we were already impressed with.
But under the other guy's legs holding two trays of martinis.
She emerges holding them up.
Like didn't spill a drop.
Yeah, people jumping to their feet in a pause.
It was incredible.
I was I really enjoyed the show.
Go as long as Bert Young isn't in the show that you're being asked to go see.
You got to just give it a shot.
You never know what you'll find.
The only thing worse than watching improv is a man describing it to you on a podcast.
It wasn't improv.
That's my point.
I was wrong.
Hey, I'll just show you.
Although it's not fun either to hear about amazing feats that you're not seeing.
But you know, they were amazing.
It's a huge day on the on the we'll see you in hell pod right now.
For your boy.
Yeah.
I just followed earlier.
Damien Leon director of terrifier.
Terrifier too.
Just checking his Instagram.
Well, I'm looking.
I'm trying to give the live update of the Ashley Lawrence response.
Uh huh.
20 minutes.
I'm about to go into five roads.
Winger's mode.
Uh huh.
I got to follow back from Damien Leon.
We've connected here now with the terrifier crew.
Have you seen terrifier?
I've seen the first one.
I haven't seen the second one yet because it was playing.
It's been playing.
It's just went to a thousand theaters now.
So it's like it keeps getting bigger every weekend.
It's not the fucking AMC here.
Yeah.
But when it first got released, it was, you know, it was playing like.
One one like nine p .m.
Or so, you know what I mean?
I'm showing you day.
I want to see it.
I asked a friend.
It was a comedian.
Any letter.
It was very funny.
I said, she said, did you see it yet?
It's amazing.
And I said, I haven't seen it yet.
I want to see it.
But I was talking to Pat Walsh.
About it.
Oh my god.
Is he single?
And you were like matter of fact?
Yes.
Yeah.
That's exactly how the convoy went.
No.
I find her attractive as well.
Even though none of this happened.
She's, she's got a significant.
When I hear he's not so significant.
Tell her, tell her I said that.
So anyway, right?
Any letterman?
She's beautiful.
And very, very, very funny.
I'm thinking of the right one.
But I knew it was her or Annie Lennox.
The Annie Lennox never did it for me.
Not an unattractive woman, but doesn't do a form.
She looks identical to my aunt.
And that's why I never was interested.
Anyway, Annie said.
I said, I said, Pat and I were talking about it on the show.
And we were a little.
Like we want to see it.
But we were a little nervous because.
You keep hearing like people are barfing and stuff like that.
Yeah.
And I was like, I'm just trying to get ready for it.
And she was like, dude, that's both.
She's like, it's like Chris.
It's fun.
Gory.
She's like, it's not like.
They're doing the old like William Castle.
Where they put.
They think they kind of are pretending that people are puking.
It's probably.
Yeah, probably.
But she said it's very, very fun and wild and over the top.
And like so.
I want to see it.
And the.
I think that clown is dark.
The clown is genuinely freaky looking.
Did you like the first terrifying?
I did.
I enjoyed it.
The disturbing jersey.
Not neither one.
Oh, there's a disturbing.
Thing in it that I that they.
Well, they cut a woman bone tomahawk style, right?
There.
Yeah, there's that.
But but the thing which is disturbing.
But the thing I found most disturbing in it is.
It opens with a woman.
On a talk show.
And I think this is sort of based on like when the monkey lady went on Oprah.
And like reveal her face.
Right.
And she's like talking about how she survived this serial killer.
Yeah.
And her.
It looks horrible.
It looks horrifying.
Like her face.
And like that was.
I was like.
That's like the fucking almost like cold open of the movie.
So I was like.
Alright, we're in for a ride here.
Like this guy's not fucking around.
But it's that guy that plays art.
The clown is great.
I don't I don't remember his name, but.
He's right.
I think you gotta.
Good shot.
It's giving me.
And maybe it is just the puke reports.
Is it is not appealing to me?
And there's so many other movies I want to see right now.
But I'll see it at some point.
I want to have our slasher movie.
I mean,
that's long.
I think if I think it'll be like to horror.
And gore and horror the way like gore.
And action is like with like.
Brawl and sell block 99.
I would say it like that.
Like the violence in that movie is horrific.
But for some reason it doesn't bother you because of the way it's done in the style of the movie.
Right.
Alright.
That's my analogy.
Amen.
Folks, I would be remiss.
I didn't give a little shout out at the top of the show to a former co -worker of mine.
The great hilarious.
Leslie Jordan.
A regular presence on on your television and occasional film.
You see him in Jason.
Goes to hell.
Very briefly.
It's where he crosses it at the horror world.
Not not his best performance.
Not something he's proud of.
I'm sure.
But American horror story.
Yes, he's in a bunch of those.
Yeah.
But you know,
just on a comedic level, the man in person.
I saw as one man.
It's kind of stage standup show.
And then of course when he played sit on the show I ran.
I just thought he was unbelievably funny.
Always found the funniest way to say everything.
Always got the laughs.
And in a extremely toxic work environment.
He had a smile, a joke, a laugh every day.
He'd come over, tell you a story.
He sensed if you're at the end of your rope.
And he made the point of coming over and like cheering you up before he went off and learned his lines.
Just one of the greatest people I've ever encountered worldwide.
But then, you know, you put that into Hollywood in the entertainment industry.
He was a true diamond in the rough.
A great man.
RIP.
Leslie.
Yeah, it's sad news, man.
When you texted me that he died, I was like, what the fuck?
Well, I heard car crash.
I mean, he had so many funny stories about being a meth head.
He was a meth head for like 10 years.
And now completely clean and sober.
But I just, you know, darkly assumed that he relapsed or something.
Because it said he had a big car accident.
He was the only driver.
But I guess he just had some sort of health incident.
Some medical.
I would assume a stroke or a heart or something.
And he crashed into the side of a building.
To freak.
It's a freak thing.
It's tragic.
And as Joe was pointing out.
It can happen to any of us.
You got to live your damn life.
You want to go to Vegas with a virtual stranger.
Go to Vegas with a virtual stranger.
Play the crap.
Add a voice.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's sad news, man.
And I will.
I'm just a fan.
I never met him or anything.
But I will miss his.
It's, you know, his Instagrams were always great.
Well, shit.
Yeah, he was especially early days of the pandemic.
He was a dream.
And one of the most.
Yeah.
What are y 'all doing?
One of them.
Everybody in the room used to pitch in his vote.
You know, everybody's scared of like.
It's like if it was David Allen Greer, we're pitching jokes.
We wouldn't do it in a black voice, you know, but like.
Every single person in a room would pitch jokes in his exact voice.
In a, you know, it was a feminine, Southern, whatever.
Right.
Nobody worried about being told they were insensitive because you have to do his voice.
It was an amazing voice.
Funny.
And an interesting home decor.
Well, odd.
Like, like Joan River style where it's like, look at my, this is my vase collection.
You know, I mean, like wild shit.
Like.
Yeah, I think, I mean, he was just in poverty for a long time.
People are like, well, he's been on TV forever.
But if you come in and do like a guest spot on Will and Grace twice a year, you know, that amounts to very little money.
So I think only in recent years was he's starting to make money.
And clearly always wanted to live the life of like a.
You know, like a Nashville country star or something.
He's always had like crazy rugs and.
Yeah, all sorts of weird shit in the sounds.
Liberace style.
Kind of thing.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
And on an apartment budget.
I know he never had a house to my knowledge.
No, it was like a.
You could tell the video is like a ground floor apart.
Yeah.
Very cool, dude.
All right.
P.
Lesson.
I.
Would be remiss.
Again, I don't know why I'm starting every sense with that would be remiss.
If I didn't bring up a little.
Scream and then I told this to Joe earlier today James gun is now the president of DC.
Now since Joe gives a shit about DC, I thought he might have something to say.
Do you think giving the creatives the key is good to me.
They need to do something different.
Maybe it's this.
That's probably what led to the decision.
Well, you know, DC is.
I, I barely give a shit about DC.
I, I've always preferred it to Marvel.
Right.
I couldn't care less at this point about Marvel.
And Marvel seems to now finally people are going.
It's so funny.
Marvel's like.
Marvel's like Kanye.
It's like, it's like.
She Hulk was like when Kanye started saying crazy anti -Semitic stuff.
And people finally went.
Well, this isn't great.
And you're like, it took you this long.
It's like.
I remember when the guy was saying he was Shakespeare on morning radio six years ago.
Nobody seemed to.
You didn't notice then that maybe something was a little off.
He was having some kind of a break.
You know, I can't tell you how many people told me like Pat, you know, you can't.
He got to give him.
He's got mental illness.
And I'm like, this has been going on for a decade.
And he seems pretty together aside from everything he says.
You can.
And I don't say this to make fun.
It's like you can have mental illness at that stage of celebrity.
And nobody around you was going to help you.
You know, yeah.
Because the second you start saying, I mean, look at Donald Trump.
You can go no.
And then if you get pushed back, you're like, I'll fire.
You're done.
Right.
I can rehire any person on my team that I need.
Yeah, that's not only a guy you can't hear.
No, that's a guy who fires you if you say no.
So that leads to a very problematic.
Support system.
What's that?
Right.
So.
But anyway, Marvel, I prefer DC to Marvel.
And I do like some of what DC is doing.
I actually thought black Adam looked pretty cool.
It didn't get really great reviews.
But.
Now they're bringing Henry Cavill back to do another Superman,
which I think is smart.
You know, I think DC.
Panicked.
And started flailing because they were getting kicked so hard
and they asked by Marvel.
And it's like, no, I see your plan through like stick with your universe
that you started creating and just make it good.
And I think they're writing some of the misfires that they made in,
in, in veering off that course for a moment.
Look, James gun.
To answer your question, I don't know.
I.
I don't know if it's good to give the creatives the.
The wheel.
You know, I feel like creatives always seem to have better fixes for things
than what the executives are doing.
So I think that that's, I think that that can be true.
I also think that putting a creative in that kind of position can corrupt the creative.
Yeah.
You know, but also too, there's another take and,
and which is interesting, which is sort of along these lines.
But there was a zap interview where he said like in the 60s,
he's like, it really sucked in the 60s when they took the record labels away from the,
from the guy, the old man in the shopping, the cigars and the suits.
Right.
He was like, he was like, they replaced all those men with young hip people.
And they thought that was a good move.
And it was a terrible move.
He was like, because the, the old man didn't know what hip was.
Right.
They didn't give a shit.
Like they threw anything against the wall.
And if it worked, they didn't fucking care.
It just worked.
Once they put people that quote new unquote into the positions,
that's when all the selectiveness and the cool kids bullshit starts.
So I think that you run that risk with in, in theory,
I'm not saying James gun is that guy.
I'm just saying you do run that risk in theory when you put an artist in a,
in a curating position and a development position.
But he gets this stuff and he knows how to do it.
I mean, he proved it with.
I thought more so than anything with suicide squad to jump.
To jump.
Outlets and brands and tones and whatever and go over here and like,
not only make a great DC movie, but make a DC movie that fixed.
Yeah.
All the shit that was wrong with the original suicide squad movie.
You know, I don't know, he, he might be good for the job.
I mean, look, Favreaux doing it with Star Wars and he's fucking great.
So why not put James gun in that similar position?
Between that guardians piecemaker show.
Sure, you know, that's, that's as good a run as you're going to find in this business these days.
Um, some mausole to Mr. gun.
Let's take us over to the movie corner where I have been watching a tremendous amount of Halloween films and scary spooktaculars.
Yes.
I would like to start with a rewatch of the ring starring Naomi Watts.
You know, I remembered next to nothing about it.
I saw it theatrically.
I always was like, oh, yeah.
In my mind, it's thought of as one of the best horror movies of the 2000s.
It's a really great horror movie.
Um, and, you know, it's a little ridiculous at spots.
You could probably easily poke holes in it.
But it just, it's, it happens to me every time for the most part when I go back and watch a movie from 20 years ago.
I'm just like, no, everything kind of works.
Everything kind of makes sense.
For the most part, this is holding together scene to scene.
The mystery is fun, compelling, interesting.
The scene where the horse jumps overboard into the water because he's scared of Naomi Watts is great.
The cold open is great when you think it's going to be scream because it's the two kind of.
Yeah.
The teenage girls, you know, that opening with them is great.
And that's not the tone of the movie at all.
It's actually a very somber, serious movie.
I think Gore Verbinski, who went on to Pirates of the Caribbean.
He did the weatherman with Nick Cage, which is a great, great movie.
Yeah.
He always does different shit, you know, very different kind of movies, but they always look amazing.
And I think this movie is shot incredibly well.
Brian Cox is great and spooky in it.
Naomi Watts.
Right off my Holland drive.
Just looking absolutely stunning.
And I always like Naomi Watts.
I like the movie a lot.
The seven days thing.
The video, you know, I love that they undercut it right after you watch the video and the guy's like,
Man, it looks like kind of a student film bullshit or whatever.
But it is actually unsettling and scary.
And I don't know.
It's a great horror movie premise.
I didn't see the original.
I don't even know if I saw the ring two.
And I was unaware there was a third ring movie called rings starring Johnny Galecki.
No, you even know that movie existed.
You, you're forget.
No, you knew that existed.
We talked about it when we were working with him living biblically.
Like rings.
We a hundred percent.
But you and I talked about that.
I remember us talking about the cleanse, which was the horror movie he did.
Right.
Not rings.
Yeah, he did both.
Because I remember saying to you.
Like talking saying like, oh, man, I feel bad for Galecki.
Like the ring.
That rings thing is getting.
Okay.
Like.
Yeah, we, you knew you just forgot.
But, but, um, but whatever it doesn't matter.
Um, all right.
I, uh, a fan of the picture.
I'm a fan of the picture.
I actually, I'm gonna.
I already did hell raise it.
I'll do two rewatches.
I said, you like the ring Joe.
Have you seen the brain?
I'm not a fan.
Um, it's.
Whoa.
It's not a bad movie.
It's just not for me.
It's way more of a mystery.
Okay.
In a horror film, my opinion.
It is.
I'll grant you.
Um.
Yeah, that's fine.
I don't, I really don't like the.
I, I've talked about this before on the show.
I have a big problem when ghosts use technology.
I don't like it.
I just don't like it.
It bothers me for whatever reason.
So, um.
I gotta, this is not a horror movie, but I gotta bring this up.
Because you've often stated that it's the worst of the franchise.
Yeah.
I rewatched it.
I think I'm gonna.
No, I watched it in my bed the other night.
Um.
I just wanted something easy to put on before bed.
I put on national ampones European vacation.
Now.
It, it's not compared to the first and the third.
It's not great.
It's better than Vegas.
Um, but it's not great.
Yeah.
However, the reason I want to talk about it is there are two things about it
that I want to point out.
Number one, it does have some amazingly funny Chevy Chase moments in it.
Like, like, like some of the biggest laughs.
It's got like four or five laughs in it that are so big.
That would be on your top 20 vacation movie laughs.
The first being.
When he catches the phone call that Audrey makes the Chicago from England.
And it's like $400.
And then it cuts them in the car and Audrey's crying.
And Beverly, Angela goes, Audrey, stop crying.
Your father didn't mean what he said.
And she's like, yes, he did.
And she goes, no, he did.
He's not going to cut your boyfriend's balls off.
And Audrey keeps crying.
And then Beverly goes, you're not going to do it, Clark, right?
And it just cuts the Chevy Chase stowed face.
And then he just finally goes.
Finally, I won't.
Which is great.
That's very funny.
And then the thing in the circle is like.
Yeah.
Jesus Christ.
Well, I mean, John Hughes is always a master of finding like a thousand things.
Like Christmas vacation checks off a thousand things that everybody can relate to about getting your family together for Christmas.
Yes.
He's a master of it.
And you go to Europe and he's like, here's everything that's annoying about Europe, plans, trains, everything that's annoying about travel.
He just had a really kind of a standup comedian's eye for what unites us all.
When there, when they're in that big band parliament, like drive around thing, whatever it's called.
And the car almost hits them.
And he's like.
And he, and he, it's like the fourth time he's going to say kids big band parliament and the car almost hits the.
And he goes son of a bitch.
Kids, forget it.
And he's so flustered and it's so funny.
Yeah.
And there are other moments I don't need to him jumping onto the bed bouncing off falling onto the ground like classic like there's some classic Chevy Chase physical humor in it.
But.
The strongest accolade I can give the movie.
And again, this doesn't make it one of the best vacation movies, but it is a very big compliment to give it.
Or it's a big attribute.
I think it's the best version of the kids because it's the only one that gives the kids something to do.
In the other movies, the kids, they have their moments, but they're ornamental.
They're there to roll their eyes and be like, oh, dad, this gives the kids a storyline.
Audrey misses her boyfriend, played by the great William spot.
Who's apka or is apka who's awesome in it and for four minutes and plays an absolute.
Fucking asshole.
It's wafting off of him.
The kid has of course for it.
And that's and then she's on the diet.
She's starving herself the whole time.
And then she finds out that he's cheating on her and then she starts gorging herself.
It gives you, it gives you, it gives you something to cling to with Audrey, like you feel bad for her and you, you're rooting for her.
And then the whole thing with Rusty just wanting to get laid and like the foil after foil of like his dad fucking that up.
Right.
I love the actors that play the kids in the other movies, but this was the only one where I was like the kids have like an actual B story.
Instead of just kind of being there to be like to be like, oh, dad, you're an idiot, you know, it's weird because I think performer wise, you have the weakest two kids, but they do have the better stories.
I mean, Juliet Lewis, Johnny Galecki, the great Anthony Michael Hall.
Dana Baron, whoever's the other one, these are way better actors are funnier actors, but they didn't really have stuff that is true.
I disagree with Audrey.
I think she's the funniest Audrey.
Juliet Lewis just kind of stands there and rolls around and doesn't say anything, which is not a comment on her acting.
Again, it's just she has nothing to do.
I like Galecki and Anthony Michael Hall better and that age range of actors.
Yeah.
But the kid in this is no slot.
She's the kid from night of the creeps.
And he also, by the way, he's, what's her name?
From Gossip Girl.
The blonde from Gossip Girl, the hottest woman that's ever lived that's married to Ryan Reynolds.
Blake Lively.
Yeah, Blake Lively's brother.
Who's Blake Lively's brother?
Rusty from European.
Interesting.
I had no idea.
That's a big family.
Her sister is the worst witch lady.
The redhead with played the worst witch in that movie, the worst witch.
I never saw the worst witch nor have I heard of worst.
If you saw the actress, you would be like, oh, that lady.
Anyway, European vacation.
It's, it's a fun enough watch.
Oh, and then you got the great John Aston as the pig in the poke game show host that makes out with doing the murder riffing thing where he makes out with all the women.
And that's very funny.
Anyway, that's not for me.
I don't like, there's a nastiness to the movie.
I don't mean like crudeness, but there's just like a.
I don't know.
There's something about the movie, the meanness that I didn't care for.
It's very.
You got Eric Idol in there.
Yes.
The England sequences.
My favorite.
They really make the English look not great.
Yeah, they seem to hate all cultures really.
Well, that I went and read reviews of it.
For what it came out.
And the reviews are like, could you stereotype one more coach?
Like, you know, they.
Yeah, the reviews were not kind to it, but.
But, you know, it's, it's, it's an enjoyable enough film, I guess.
It has its moments.
I rarely read this.
I rarely.
I saw.
Well, hell, folks, I saw bros.
And.
I don't know.
I obviously love the work of aptal.
Have been a big fan of Billy on the street.
I like Billy Agner.
I think Billy on the street is a hilarious program.
But then I don't know.
Billy Agner being on Twitter all day every day, being like you homophobes,
not seeing this movie.
It was a really bad look, I think.
And a lot of people did not like that.
It's also like the trailer for bros makes it look like medicine.
And like you're seeing the first gay romantic comedy,
which is also not true.
There have been several even mainstream gay romantic comedies,
like getting out.
That I love in and out.
I love in and out too.
But, you know, as I told Mr. Apital, everyone walked out of that movie in 1997.
And I saw it with my friend and the entire theater left when Tom Sellett kissed Kevin Klein, the entire audience.
So.
I would say the birdcage is a gay romantic comedy.
Birdcage is a gay romantic.
It is.
It is much about Robin Williams and Nathan Lane falling back in love.
They're the stars.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
So I don't know the whole sort of preachy side of the movie makes no sense to me.
I think it's great that it's a gay romantic comedy and that it was released in a mainstream fashion.
And all the performers in it are played by actual gay actors.
I think that's all fantastic.
But ultimately the movie left me really cold.
I was excited to see it.
I'd actually been saving it because I was like, I need a good laugh and I'll save it.
And then I wound up not really laughing.
Well, they make fun of Schitts Creek a couple times.
I know everybody loves Schitts Creek, they roll their eyes and all that.
But Schitts Creek also built to this really sweet moment where the Dan Levy character sings a song to his boyfriend and etc.
So in this movie, it's all building to a allegedly sweet moment where Billy Agner sings a country song to his boyfriend who likes country music.
And it's like, okay, well, if you're going to shit on Schitts Creek, you've obviously seen Schitts Creek and you're stealing.
It's ending.
It's not the most original ending to begin with.
So it really just kind of follows the beats of like a real paint my numbers, 90s romantic comedy with gay guys.
And then you got, instead of them talking about, oh, isn't it embarrassing when, you know, your pussy does this.
It's guys talking about their dicks and gay sex stuff.
So that makes it different.
But the jokes just weren't strong.
I just belched into the mic.
I'm very sorry for that.
I saw it.
I didn't, I don't know what came over me.
I don't know why I just did that.
I'm sorry.
It's odd.
It's, it's our rated, but it doesn't go the raunchy route of like a something about Mary, as I thought that it might because, okay.
Now, in my mind, we've got all this new sexual terrain to cover in a gay sex romcom.
So we can see all sorts of stuff that we've never seen in a movie before and hear about it and hear about.
You know, but plugs and, and, and, and the wide variety of prep, you know, tops, bottoms.
I think a lot of straight people have questions that they don't feel comfortable asking their gay friends.
But that's not really what this movie is.
It's not really a sex comedy.
It's a very chased almost puritanical type look.
You know, he's on Grindr at the beginning and stuff, but I don't know.
It never really picked a comedic take or style on the material.
It just sort of was like, we're going to be a romantic comedy like you've seen a billion times, but with two guys.
And great.
I mean, yeah.
But that doesn't mean I'm going to say it's a better movie than your average generic romantic comedy.
It's not.
I think.
Well, I look, I think when it's when something is build.
In the way that bros was build, you're almost nervous watching it, because you're like, well, what if I don't like it.
Yeah, exactly.
I don't want to look like an asshole.
But also too, this happens with these with these movies that are breaking new ground in any direction, or culture, whether it's a new cultural, well, it's always a new cultural direction.
But whatever that is.
That it's just, you know, it was like it was, it's kind of you go back to the, the, the Ghostbusters reboot argument, which is.
But you just made a bad movie that guys would have made.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
It's just, it's like, it's not good.
Like I don't, I wouldn't like this if it was guys either.
Like I want people, whether it's men or women or trans men or trans women or black or white or male or whatever it is.
Right.
Straight.
I just want people to be making a better product.
That's it.
I mean, couldn't agree more.
It's not only did I want to like it, I fully expected to like it sounds like you want it to like it.
No, I, I wanted to like it.
I expected to like it.
And I just didn't it sort of pleasant enough.
It builds to, you know,
I bet I could probably dial it back on the celebrity cameos like you're.
Did he direct it?
No, he just produced it.
Okay.
I think in order to get these movies kind of over the finish line, you know, because it's hard to get a comedy made these days.
I think he calls up his buddies.
So you got like Amy Schumer and Ben Stiller are like presenting exhibits in this game.
You know, you're, you're an hour and 50 minutes into the movie and it's like, I don't need to see Amy Schumer playing, you know, Betsy Ross or whatever they have going on.
It's just, it takes you out of the real life of the movie, I think, when, when stars are popping by.
But it's a, that's a minor quibble.
I think in general, it's an average romantic comedy with guys.
It seems like a bit of a missed opportunity.
But and you know, what sucks is that it's the first comedy released in theaters in a long time.
And it's the first game movie in a while, whatever, which means they're going to take less chances on game movies and comedies.
And I think that kind of sucks.
What we are going to see a lot more of guaranteed is cheap horror because horror is destroying at the box office this year.
I talked about watching Hellraiser, but I didn't really give a review of rewatching it.
By the way, I got a response from Miss Ashley Lawrence.
All right.
I want to see what this says.
Of course.
Hello.
Strong start.
Oh, that's it.
What do you do with that?
What do I do right back to that?
No, no, no, no. You can't write back to Hello.
Should I just like it?
Like hard it?
Like.
Just leave it.
If she wanted to start a discussion.
I don't know why she's just saying hello.
But maybe she, she might be married and is like, I don't want to be DMing with a guy, which I understand.
Yeah, but she's a fan of my comedy, I assume, or something.
I mean, she's not following me just for the shits of it.
What if you plow her in a bar bathroom, not knowing who she was, and that's why she follows you.
And that's why she's showing.
Plow in bathrooms, baby.
All right.
Is Sinatra once said.
One of his albums, right?
One of his theme albums.
Yeah, yeah.
It's him sort of for loan for lonely flushing a urinal while he smokes a cigarette alone in a bathroom.
All right, so I leave.
Yeah, because I wrote a message then she responded and that's it.
You go, all right, I guess if she didn't want to.
Yeah, no, if you want to talk because I've been doing a lot of online dating.
If somebody wants to talk, they respond with a question.
Yeah, they don't end it.
They don't put something that ends the conversation.
Or maybe she wrote hello and got sidetracked and was going to like follow up with that later.
I think you just got to be patient and wait.
All right, I got to stop talking about it.
Anyway, yeah, hell razor.
Hell razor.
I rewatched because like I said, I was in the mood for a classic comforting horror film.
Yeah, like hell razor.
And I also rewatched because despite all the new things I have to watch on my shelf, I thought.
You know, we just reviewed this remake.
Let me, let me review this.
Let me look at this again.
And dear God, like it only shines even brighter after this.
It does.
I mean, it's like it's so good.
It's so well done.
And it doesn't make any real sense.
Like there's no real logic to any of it.
It's just sort of this experience.
They never explain why the blood brings Frank back from the dead.
They never really explain why the center bites betray Kirstie and the pack they make with Kirstie.
But now do you think if you were reviewing that if if night, if you could watch 87 hell razor now.
First time on the show as if it was a new movie coming out.
Do you think you'd be on this podcast going, wait, so we get no explanation why the blood brings them back.
I thought very much about that as I was watching it and I very well may.
Yeah, or would.
But I don't I don't know because it's so hard to to determine.
There's just such a difference in the experience of the movie of a movie that was made.
I mean, I'm watching this thing on 4k Blu -ray.
And it's like, you can still see all the grain.
It's beautiful looking.
There's a texture till it.
Like, and there was that texture back then.
I saw this movie with my parents, which is a weird one to see with your folks.
Because for some reason my dad wanted to see it like we the bottom.
We saw the box in the video store a few times and he's like, I want to see that hell razor.
And I remember not liking it as a kid because I kept saying to my parents.
I was probably 12, but I kept being like, I want the guy with like the needles in his head to show up more.
Why isn't he in this more?
Because it was like before I knew his name was I think was before he was called pinhead right anyway.
But yeah, every part of it like it's it's very much a movie that that is based on the concept of exploration and experience like every character is on their own little journey.
Claire Higgins who plays the wife, Julia, you know, she's trying to bring Frank back because this guy fucked her so good.
Yeah, that she wants to murder people to bring his corpse back so he can fuck her again.
Right.
So she's on that journey.
Andrew Thomas, I think his name is or whatever whoever plays the dad, he's trying to keep his family together in this new home in England and you know, being a guy from the States and he knows that his wife is becoming more and more strange from him.
Ashley Lawrence is trying to remain close with her father while the she despises her stepmother.
And then also falling in love with this guy that she meets.
The set of bites even are on a mission to get Frank back because he's alluded them and and and and that's never it's insinuated that that doesn't happen to them.
So everybody and then Frank is trying to bring himself back from the dead.
So like everybody in the movie is is on new terrain like and that's kind of what the movie hinges on it's like it's about people exploring new experiences be them good or bad.
And I think that Clive Barker kind of just puts that in the driver's seat and says I'm going to have a lot of sort of a femoral I guess would be the word.
Or even fleeting concepts that surround this journey that each character is on that that create mood and add to the experience of what's happening here.
But I'm not going to really worry about if it all adds up or not it's just kind of you're going to take some things for granted so.
But even with that all said it's the so so it's the exact opposite of what this new one is we talked about the new one and the thing I texted you was there's way too much plot here why is this so complicated yeah they're like putting all of these things in to try to get you to understand the story and then it's still confusing in the end.
But whereas this is like here you go guys 90 minutes you're in your out you know things are happening that aren't explained why did the sink explode as Julia is remembering the first time she met brother Frank in the rain.
You know why are these events in the house lining up with the events of Frank coming back from the dead there's no real explanation to any of it other than it's eerie and it's weird and there's a presence at work here.
Yeah you know why does this guy who's homeless you know reclaim the box at the end and turn into a flying demon what is he who is he you know blah blah blah.
And it's an awesome movie it's just really really well done it's Clive Barker's best work I think for sure.
You know and he stepped into producer role in the second third and fourth films but it's just a great movie it's just great and then you know and Doug Bradley.
You know he hits a legendary stride with pinhead like it's just it's it's up there with Robert England and Kane hotter and.
And the nun from the nun and Chuckie and Brad Paisley what the fuck's the guys I hate Brad Paisley more than any of these people you mentioned.
Chuckie Brad Dura Brad Dura if you know it's the thing you don't often see you know so it's pretty cool agreed.
I saw a picture called Lake Mungo which I had never heard of so on this Bravo 100 scariest moments are sorry shutter 100 scariest movie moments pretty high up on the list was a moment from Lake Mungo.
The guy Mike Flanagan who does you know house on haunted Hill and all the Netflix type shows or shows leap doc sleep.
Gerald's game he talked almost the entire segment about Lake Mungo and how incredible it was and how he recommends it if anyone ever asks him what's a horror movie they should watch he says Lake Mungo his number one scary movie moment of all time is from Lake Mungo.
So I look it up and of course it's on to be like everything else sitting there on to be ready to be watched for free and it's 84 minutes it is a mockumentary or fake documentary that really has no scares it's an interesting ghost story the big scary moment didn't work on me because I had just watched the show when I saw the moment.
But I don't know that it would have worked on me anyway.
Where it shines is that it's one of the most meticulously put together fake documentaries of all time it works as well as Blair Witch in terms of convincing you that this is a real thing and these people are real.
And it's really cool you know there's there's twists and turns which you're not really expecting it's a great sort of Halloween creepy vibe to it but don't go in expecting this thing's going to freak me out I'm not going to be able to sleep again it must work on some people there's a lot of talk on the internet about this movie fucked me up and all this other stuff.
Look people are scared of different shit so maybe it'll really get to you I don't know I think it's well worth watching as kind of a lost horror gem that I had not even heard of and it's sitting there free on to be if you want to watch check it out God bless to me yeah.
I'll close it out with another re watch I want to plane coming back from Vegas.
I put on so you weren't there this weekend where you know two weeks ago yeah.
I put on something quiet something familiar something I'll be able to just kind of not off to end up watching the entire thing front to back.
Unforgiven starring Clint Eastwood masterpiece holy God what a goddamn movie they don't make them like that anymore they just don't know she's this Christ this thing I mean I don't know I never made movies like that before.
I mean that's about the that is the best western there's ever made I think it made me want to start watching Westerns yeah that look there's plenty of great ones but I think that is the ultimate.
It's you know what is there to say it's Morgan Freeman it's Clint Eastwood it's Gene Hackman yeah there you go and it's in it's in it's in a great Dick Harris in a supporting role the English Bob referenced in Pulp Fiction.
It it what is it what's the reference the English Bob for all I care Samuel Jackson says oh wow yeah um and you're getting the three of them at their best like oh yeah it's it's the quintessential version of the three of them yeah Clint Eastwood as the troubled badass who is a hard man but you like him still.
But not yet decrepit his you know perfect age for him same with Freeman Morgan Freeman as like the heart and soul and endearing like God if I had to go through this this is the guy I'd want next to me the entire time and then Hackman as a complete prick like which is the best Hackman like Hackman is so good at playing a fucking prick I was building a house yeah.
You got you got Saul Rubenstein Rubenek with Rubenek yeah right in the memoirs from a Frazier fame and true romance as the agent as Joel Silver right just playing a fucking warm he's great at that God he's good at that he's great everybody's great at it.
Um and the the entire cast of the the the the the the is a menagerie cathouse whatever the hell you call it yeah um that whole crew there are all amazing the whole thing is just amazing man seeking revenge man nothing better than a man brought out of a good life to force to do horrible things again.
Starts drinking again casually my favorite moment of the whole movie give me that bottle yeah starts to shot an unarmed man he should have armed himself yeah he's gonna decorate his saloon with my friends I thought um I I wanted him I really wanted him to kill Saul Rubenek and I was bummed that he didn't know which because he's Jewish well I was talking to Kanye and it isn't fashion.
And why did you tell Mr. West and why have you been telling him to do what he's done for the last 14 years.
But he tells Rubenek to load the gun he goes pick up the gun and I thought I always forget I always every time I only watch this movie every seven years I always think that it's going to be he's like he's making him arm himself so he can kill him.
Yeah me too a weasel and he doesn't but um but it's it's it's kind of cooler that he doesn't kill him because you realize like he has he he's got his lines he's got his boundaries that he's got you know his rulebook that he's going to follow right.
Yeah it's almost comedic in places like when he does take the bottle it's it's kind of funny yeah because you realize like he's like I have to go down there and kill everybody now so I'm just going to have to start drinking right you know when he's wrestling the pigs at the beginning it's kind of funny.
That the turn of that younger character from being like the loudmouth to being like when he finally kills the guy and he admits he never killed anybody and he's he's mortified and yeah he's like sick with himself like it's just a it's just yeah they don't make him like the you know the comedic thing of like he turns into a whining cry baby or something he like actually seems sickened with what he's done so there's so much great stuff in that move so much.
And then you're written by oh yeah believe it or not the gentleman who wrote blade runner oh all right well I mean it makes and lady hawk lady and soldier with Kurt Russell that movie suck I guess I just don't like his sci -fi work lady hawk lady hawk's not terrible but it's not great it's broadrick fiver yeah I know I just just Christ I mean it oh wait he was the fifth writer and he was uncredited so we can.
Can't really blame lady hawk on him right he probably was brought into make it shootable and I love by the way I love that it doesn't have this perfect little buttoned up ending on it yeah you you think that he's going to take the the the prostitute that gets like cut to pieces right that the whole movie is about you think he's going to take her and like make her his wife because he they have that scene where he's like if I were to have a freebie yeah I like it if it was with you you know that the big.
And he doesn't the end the end little text crawl says you know the mother of his dead wife went to find him and he was long gone with his children so say he went out west to look for gold and San Francisco and did well for himself and and it's just a perfect ending like there's no bow on this he had to keep moving because he did something horrible again and he evaporated and became a legend like he was before they found it at the beginning of the movie.
It's just a it's just a fucking masterpiece man it is the best and all that movie all those movies in that run were great I love in the line of fire I love a perfect world with Kevin Kossner maybe his most underrated I think the funniest line of his in the line of fire him and Renee Rousseau have this sex scene and there's the really funny thing where they get in the hotel room and you see all these guns dropping to the floor and like holsters and like stir ups because they're got their happy eyes and so then after they've fought.
And he's like he's a grumbling and Renee Rousseau is like what what happened did he kill again it's not what I'm upset about and she's what's the matter he goes I got to put all that shit back on again God damn it always just made me laugh he's a funny man I'm maybe I'll rewatch grand terino maybe the funniest racism has ever been.
It's funny I thought about watching grand terino after I watch this because I was like I want to watch another movie where he's an awful man yeah but then he does something nice at the end he's way worse he went to Rina yeah well no and in this they say he killed children now that's true that's true and then he admits to it he's like I killed when we did you know like you know like kills damn there everything that ever walked a crawl to one time or another now I'm going to kill you a little bill yeah what a great what a great.
movie and speaking of the opposite of great movies we come to today's film Halloween ends the end of and it's completely unnecessary trilogy that sort of seems to have kick started in a way and a new I wouldn't even say genre I would say it's fully half of horror movies are about trauma trauma of something that has happened to you in the
past coming back and the present is the premise of the latest smile it's the I mean it's the premise of a lot of horror shit lately things coming back to to kind of haunt you as Joe pointed out they did that in H2O with Jamie Lee Curtis's character being an alcoholic and having trouble they already kind of had done that and I think done it better and that's the only trick up this new trilogy sleeve is let's deal with Jamie.
Jamie Lee Curtis's trauma and they don't they just didn't do much with it you know for having complete rights and freedom to do whatever you want with a franchise that is run out of gas a hundred times over to just kind of give us another serving of the same shit is sort of unforgivable and for me that is why I think I enjoyed this I know I enjoyed it more than Joe and I know I enjoyed it more than most while still thinking it's a bad move
I thought the central gimmick of this new one that it's a kid named Corey who's pretending to be Michael Myers was at least something new and for that reason I admired it because I couldn't have taken Halloween kills again but it's not a very good movie don't get me wrong
fuck you fuck Corey the the audacity for them to do this in the in the eleventh hour of a of a franchise like Halloween for them to introduce a new character yeah and give him most of the kills yeah it is insane I don't I don't
understand it I don't know what they were thinking it led to nothing it didn't even set up this concept of there will always be a Michael Myers because in the end there's not Corey dies they go out of their way to show the entire town that Michael is actually dead right
higher town celebrates in destroying his body and they make it quite clear that the trauma has ended with the most lackluster line in movie history where will patent oh god what a terrible character by the way it's gonna be the first time
I've ever seen this man smile in my life yeah you know he's walking away from Jamie Lee
Curtis and Jamie Lee Curtis says so tell me about those cherry blossoms something that is unrelated to the entire franchise now when this fucking movie oh my god I'm
disgusted with it did you sign the petition to have them redo it there is a petition I know that's also making me
furious but I mean they did with this what they did in Rise of Skywalker which I know I like to
initially and now I don't like it but it's like why are you adding questions why are you adding characters you have a
million loose ends to tie up in this franchise in a third movie tie them up you're opening new doors the last movie
ended with Michael Myers as a 70 year old man taking down six people attacking him all of them
brawny men right and surviving stabs and gunshots and being beaten with blunt instruments to conquer all six men and walk
into the darkness they explain at the end of that movie Michael is beyond any evil we can understand he is
something bigger than we can imagine he is powerful all this stuff they set all that up so you go okay and the
third movie I guess they're gonna explain what all that means is he gonna be supernatural is is there
gonna be a plague through the town where it turns out there are several Michael Myers and that's how they seem to
keep living on and what is what is what is this going to be and instead they flash forward four years
they make Jamie Lee Curtis's character a functioning normal woman again and the bulk of the movie is
focused on a kid who for no good reason becomes obsessed with Michael Myers who Michael Myers when he
encounters the kid by the way Michael Myers the the invincible Superman from the last movie is living in
a sewer and is now weak which okay fine he spares the life of this kid because somehow by looking into
the kid's eye he knows that the kid is a killer it is the dumbest lazyest thing I've ever seen yeah that's
dumb and then the kid becomes Michael Myers only two immediately be killed and fail and not even be
killed by the town he kills himself just to try to set up Jamie Lee Curtis and that goes nowhere and
means absolutely nothing and then Michael Myers comes in this man who we watched in the last movie and I
do not this has nothing to do with gender people but if you're going to show me this guy fighting six
broughty man in the prime of their lives Jamie Lee Curtis is not overpowering him I'm sorry stop it
with this I guess unless you're saying but he's weakened from the last movie but the whole thing in
the end of the last movie was that he can't be weakened because he's invincible so what is it and
Jamie Lee Curtis has been weakened by time as well we all have but at no point in Jamie Lee Curtis's
life could she have beaten any version of the Michael Myers that we've grown accustomed to it just
wouldn't happen at this point she's a frail woman in her late 70s you know and you could say well he's
a frail man in his late 70s right he's stronger he's much taller and bigger but here's the thing if
you want me to believe that she can fight him don't have him fight six men in their 40s at the end
of the last movie it I just was fighting firefighters at that point it seemed like more than six to me
took on like a the town I just I just don't understand how we kills should have been this if you're
going to do this story you do it as the second one and get people upset and then for three you bring
it back home to to to Michael and Jamie together again but I do agree you're not setting anyone up to be
happy if you are ending this 40 year horror franchise although it's definitely not the ending they'll be
more folks but if you're gonna end it with a made up character literally named Corey I mean it's
absurd the kids frail why do you say literally named Corey what do you mean named Corey like the
most in like unthreatening generic like teenage dude I think that's the I think that's sort of what
they're trying they're trying to say like it could happen to anybody this monster lives in all of
us and it's like but that's not in any way clear I don't give a fuck about this kid but by the way
the kids in like his 20s and he lives with his mom still because at the beginning of the movie he has
an accident where he accidentally kills a little kid which by the way it is the most let's talk about
the writing of this film this film is written like it was supposed to come out in 1986 it's like
guys you can't you you can't write characters like this they don't exist like it's not commonplace
enough you can't have a dad that in front of people goes because you're a fucking idiot that's why
you're an embarrassment you know what I mean it's like people say things now yeah like like
the that that's seen at the top where the kid is like a sweet scared kid and then as soon as the
parents leave the kid becomes a complete prick it's just such cliched terrible fucking writing
oh oh god you want to talk about cliches and terrible let's insert one of the most racistly portrayed
black characters I've seen recently in cinema a guy with an afro who by the way forget the hackney
trope that he's narrating the movie through radio right like when has that happened since 1985
what do you do the right thing like what what what what fucking world does this still happen in in
2000 the black characters throughout this entire franchise yes are weird there there is a
weirdness to what's going on here the what the black guy with the with the sheriff's hat who kind of
goes through each of the movies you know there's a lot of strength and then in each there is a brutal
murder of like it letting the last one there was an elderly black couple and you're just kind of like
what's going on guys this is something I've noticed about it is yeah and this character and this one
is very bizarre the first one had the little kid that like cursed and it was supposed to be like so
fucking hilarious and you're like I guess man like I don't know but this one this character where
the guy literally has an afro and literally plays like like does like a night tunes kind of
fucking radio show and then on top of it like you then you make them and you don't just write a
cliche character that's that's in its own way unsettling and it seems inappropriate and folks you
know me I'm the least fucking low guy on planet earth telling you it's fucking weird and and
and then on top of it you make the guy a complete asshole
like what and then and then he gets the most brutal kill because Casey cuts his tongue out
and which again which has been a problem through this entire franchise they said they were going to
redignify the Halloween franchise and it had just become about gratuitous kills and there was no
substance to it anyway this entire fucking three movies was nothing but gratuitous kills yeah each
one was worse than the predecessor the first one had a chance at being good it ended up being very
whatever the second one fucking sucked and this one to me was just an abomination uh this to me felt
like they took a fucking script of another movie and went we'll we'll just call it a Halloween movie
or it's at a point where they got so many cooks on this thing that Jamie Lee is demanding they do
this carpenter is demanding you do this plum is demanding you do this David Gordon green is
demanding you do this and you know because that happens too where where everybody starts to put
their fingers in the pie and you end up with a mess and it's just this movie it's terrible it's
just fucking terrible it was better shot than the last one it was better directed yeah it wasn't as
frantic and like it honestly it seemed like they rushed that last one to the lab you know like it
seemed like I was gonna start seeing like slips of film on the left and right side of the screen because
it was so rushed together this to me is comparable with the first David Gordon green Halloween by which
to say it was a letdown I liked that they tried something different but it didn't work and uh you
know this is especially considering how many movies are in this franchise the the batting average for
this franchise is just pitiful it really is if we're gonna count zombies and the originals I mean there's
a lot of shit in this franchise um well the mean three the funny meme going around is like the one
with Rob Zombie being like that you never thought you'd want me back or it's something like that it's
like yeah yeah I gotta say Rob like even after the monsters I'd rather see you handling the Halloween
right now this is this trilogy was a letdown and a half I mean it's just it's and I'll say what I've
said from the beginning I don't buy for a second that Michael Myers by the way that question was never
answered and they tease that it would be they tease that it would be answered in this third movie that
there would you would finally understand why Michael was obsessed with Jamie Lee Curtis it's not
enough to just say she's the one that lived it's not enough it's just not enough and they tease that
they were going to explain that they tease that it was going to be that once she died he could stop
yeah and then it was going to be the two of them dying together and then and then David Gordon
Rienkeman goes we tried several endings we shot several test audiences didn't like the grim why the
fucker audiences dictating what the end of the movie is going to be what the fuck is going on anymore
man it's a goddamn horror movie yeah letting an audience tell you it's two grim what yeah horror
movies are supposed to have grim that's some of the beauty of them you don't have to have the happy
ending people like that they don't have the happy ending yeah have Jamie Lee sacrifice herself to save
her daughter or granddaughter and and that also is what stops Michael finally from killing or whatever
it does this pointless fucking montage of jump cuts after the whole thing oh my god that book by the
way she's writing it's like a 12 year old is writing it couldn't believe it doing the sex in the city
thing at the beginning of this well I told Joe they do a recap at the beginning at like a previously
on Halloween and they do sort of tie it in by making it Jamie Lee writing a book but it doesn't change
the fact that it's super awkward and these movies made a ton ton of money but you don't ever in your
day to day life hear people talking about these new Halloween's being great you checked out that new
Halloween wasn't it cool I haven't heard a single piece of positive feedback on these movies
but all three of them made a huge amount of money and and I guess I don't know what the lesson
Hollywood is taking away except the script doesn't matter and it's a bad lesson to be teaching them
and slid right out of this into the exercise legacy trilogy doing three more exercises with Burston
no less it's like what what is this gonna be with no no you know Linda Blair's like they haven't
called me it's like yeah guys why would you why would you call the star of the original movie
and maybe they're just doing a secret thing you know whatever but like you know that
plum came out or not plum but whoever came out the other day and they were like
William Friedkin is definitely not involved it's like oh no shit it's like
what are you proud of that guys yeah that's good like like you know bladdy's dead it's like
it's just like what are you doing like it uh god damn it
fuck yeah that's not gonna be good that's not and you know it was just like they said let's
do the exact same thing with Burston let's just do the exact same thing and it's going to be
dealing with the trauma of the exorcism 55 years later yeah my daughter doesn't speak to me anymore
we went through hell and back well literally yeah I can I can write the dialogue yeah
off the top my just riffing I could riff this dialogue the uh well
as my tweet said folks Halloween couldn't end soon enough
hog waitlines way down on this one hog is down as well uh I don't know what to say I'm glad
the franchise is over for now I don't know I don't know if we're going reboot or if we're going
another in the David Gordon Green trilogy but we're gonna get more I assume that Corey was
going to be the new Michael Myers I thought they were doing the training a new one but thankfully
that's not happening yeah no I think I think it's done and I think when it comes back
it will I'm gonna predict it it's gonna be a mask that looks different that's nowhere near as cool
and it'll be Michelle Myers that's my prediction yeah that sounds about right um anyway folks we'll
be back with uh smile we back with smile uh I am on my buddy's new youtube talk show up all night
with Bob my friend Rob Sheridan hosts it he's had on Mark McKinney and a lot of cool comedy people
uh so I did the Halloween episode with him that's available on youtube I am on instagram a twitter
at the patch of wash and that's all I got folks uh I am Joe DeRosa comedy on all of your social media
come to Joey Roses NYC uh the website is JoeyRosesNYC .com we are open seven days a week
I would love to see you there uh we're opening now earlier 11 30 a .m every day uh thank you for all
the support it keeps getting better which is why we're expanding hours uh we hope to see you soon
um also I'm on the road my big show coming up that if you're in New York I'd really appreciate
you coming I'm at the black cat again uh doing my new uh I'm calling it a one -man show uh I never
promised you a Rose Garden that's November or Tuesday November 8th I think is the day
it's it's that Tuesday the I think the 8th is the number um anyway one show only after party at
Joey Roses just like we did for the podcast uh Pat and I will be down in Florida in December doing
we'll see when I'll live at Coastal Creative in St. Petersburg and then the two nights that follow
that I'll be doing the show down there uh my the one man uh Austin Texas at the Vulcan in January
governors in Long Island in January go to joda rosa info dot com for tickets and show times
uh I guess that's it we'll see you next time and we'll see you and hell