Welcome to we'll see you in hell folks. It's that movie pod with the movie buds
And by buds, I mean the hard buds of myself and Mr. Patrick Walsh.
Joe, thank you for that. And I believe it's an accurate assessment.
Good morning to you. Maybe the earliest we've ever recorded or did we do one like we're trying to beat
a vacation like 7 a .m. thing years ago. This might be the earliest. It's 830. It's 830
year time. It's 11th. I'm on the East Coast now. I'm actually sitting in the home. Yeah,
of one James Pinkstone, our friend James. He's not in the room with me. In fact, he's at a real
job like most normal people have on a Friday. Yeah, he's not sitting here fucking around. That
was one of my favorite Mr. Show sketches where Odin Kirk is calling the blind guy. And he's like
he like gives money to like a blind thing. And he has like a blind sponsor. And he's like, I got
to call this guy. He is so little in his life. Yeah. And then it's David Cross is the blind guy.
And he's like, Hey, Bob, I don't got time for this. I'm gonna spend my day fucking around some TV show.
Yeah, really funny. That was funny. Yeah. How are you doing?
Look, personally, I'm doing night and day better. I'm on top of my game. I'm out in these streets.
I in the home, I have a massive ant infestation.
That, but what a, and a few uncles too.
Folks, no, that's an incestation is what happened with my uncle folks.
No, I am here. I have two two uncles that I like. Don't take that. That's not true. Nobody
incested us. Yeah, when Joe was here, Joe stayed with me for a week, which was a blast. And basically,
I returned home from Atlanta to an ant infestation. And the only way to do it is you buy these,
look, maybe this will save somebody's life. I know a lot of you won't care, but listen to me for 30 seconds.
You get these traps that have liquid in them. They're, it's an orange box. And you set them out.
And that can work. But what I do is I wait until you get a big glob or a big glob of ants. Like Joe saw
this a couple of times, like a softball size hive of ants, like swarming. It's terrifying.
It really is unsettling. But you drop a little of the bait goo out of the bait onto the pile.
The ants don't scatter. They just go nuts. They're like, what is this? What is this? But they're
being covered with a sugary, delicious substance. So a few of them die instantly. The rest of them
start greedily feasting on the goo. And you set the trap next to them. So they're like, hey,
there's more of this over here. They all go into the trap, eat it. They disappear. And what they're
actually doing is taking the poison within them on their skin, if ants have skin, which I don't think
they do. But on their person and inside of themselves, they take it back to their base, their hive.
And then everyone gets poisoned. The whole, the whole lot of them goes down.
The only way to do it. This is also how you mate. Yes, that's true. You'll say, take some of that
goo back. Good Lord. Take some of that goo back and share it with your friends. Tell them how it's
how it tastes. I throw a damp rag at them and shut the door. We had to do this because New York
City, sometimes you have to deal with rats around your establishment. We didn't have any inside
when we were building the place. Thank God. But there were some outside. And we had to do the same
thing. There are these pellets you put down. And my partner Paul was like, this sends a message back
to their friends because like they eat it and then they go home and die. Yeah. And somehow the rats
know like, oh, I shouldn't go to like wherever they just came from. You know, exactly. And why didn't
they teach us this in ants, starring Woody Allen and Sebastian Stallone? It was a sugary goo.
Now, of course, I'm carrying a hundred times my body weight, which for me is, you know, about a hundred
pounds. That's being honest alone. That doesn't make sense with Woody Allen as an ant. That was Woody
Allen as a person. It was perfect casting. They're like, we need it. We need it. We need a neurotic
ant. I mean, you wouldn't cast him today. You just wouldn't. I know. I'd be a different thing.
But yeah, I just speaking of Stallone, I just watched the trailer for Samaritan, which is,
so Samaritan is a new movie coming out starring Sebastian Stallone. It's a superhero movie
where he plays an old superhero who the public thinks is dead and he has stepped down and he's
now a garbage man and a young kid figures out that he's Samaritan, which is a really cool superhero name.
And then like, you know, it's Stallone being like, oh, dude, I had to walk it, you know, and then
like him slowly coming out of superhero retirement as an old man. Every movie he's ever done.
Yeah. So it doesn't look bad. I like that Stallone is back in the spotlight because I don't know,
for those of you old enough to remember the 90s, it was dark for me. I thought we lost him for a while.
I was like, he was doing direct a video at one point. And I was like, oh my God, like, what's
going on here? The 90s. He closed the 90s with like, get Carter, which is awful, but got a theatrical
release. You're talking last 10 years before that. No, no, no, no. I'm talking like, before Rocky
Balboa came out, I'm talking like 90, yeah, late night, because get Carter's like 94, 95 somewhere in
the US. I think it's 2000. That was the, right, right around 2000. Is that I saw it on a double
bill with Meet the Parents, which was 99. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. It was the worst double feature
I've ever seen. And it was get Carter. And I'm going to text my friend and find out what the other
movie was. Get Carter should have been great. And it sucked. Awful. The Michael Cain one is fantastic.
Michael Cain is in the remake as like a different character. I'm never a fan when they do that.
No, they're like, they're like, it's a new Star Wars, but this time Mark Hamill plays
Jabba, the Jabba's cousin or whatever, you know, you're like, I don't want that. Just having
be Luke. Yeah. But uh, get Carter, oh, so still, sorry, it's nice to see him doing okay.
Okay. But I got to say, man, his draw like he's getting real tough to understand because he's 75
or 76 now. Right. It looks amazing. He looks fucking amazing. But his, he still has the voice of a 75
year old man. So it's 75 years old into the Stallone like draw. So it's kind of getting hard to, you know,
what was I? Like it sounds, it sounds, he sounds sort of like an impression of him now. Yeah.
Yeah. For sure. You know, does he, when he, when he makes the flip from garbage man to superhero,
does he go, it's time to take out the trash? I'm sure that line's in there somewhere in the trailer,
which maybe think maybe it's a decent movie. Yeah. All right. You know, who knows? Well, if that was
the last line of the trailer, you know, you'd be like, Oh my God. That's good. And I wouldn't have
been surprised that that's the fire. We talked about fire starter. You know, liar, liar pants on
fire. That was the big like payoff line in the trailer. And you're like, what horror? And I don't
mean horror in a good way. Are we in for with this thing? Yeah. I wonder if we're the only two people
in the world who saw that fire starter. I certainly have never met anyone who saw it. I never saw a review
of it. Did, did we dream it? It was so horrible. Um, I, yeah. I don't, Jesus. Cripe. Yeah. I don't know.
But, um, I asked my friend what we saw with get Carter. And he said antitrust, which I know is wrong,
because I never saw antitrust. The fuck is antitrust? This was the dark period, but me and my friend saw
every single movie that came out for four years, probably not a lot going on in college high school.
And antitrust was Ryan Felipe. And Tim Robbins, I want to say.
But, uh, they all really hated that one. I think I, it might have been get the Carter get Carter.
And maybe we all hated extra because we all love meet the parents. I think is what the double
feature was. I'll tell you this, you make a movie called antitrust. And it's not Martin Lawrence
in drag as an ant antitrust. Yeah. You know what I mean? Whose last name is trust? I'm not interested.
Get it away from me. What the fuck are you talking about? I actually want to see that right now.
I saw a big mama's house alone at the theater and I laughed so hard throughout. And then I saw the
sequel and laughed quite a bit in that one too. I did not see the third one with like Nick Cannon,
but it's a funny franchise. A lady in a dress always good. Yeah. Always good. I'll take Martin
Lauren in antitrust. I'll take Eddie Griffin in antitrust. Sure. If we're sitting here talking about it.
Lady Bugs with Rodney. Oh yeah. Terrible movie with some great lines. But it's a
she's just his friend and she coaches the team with him. And the running gag is like she's
like eating like hoagie through the whole movie or something like that. But it's got the greatest
Rodney Dangerfield side gag of all time in any of his movies. And it's the only funny part in
the whole movie is when she goes, why would you think you could coach a soccer team?
And he opens the back of the minivan and it's filled with soccer balls and he goes, I don't know.
All I know is I got a lot of balls. That wasn't the trailer if I'm not mistaken. It works. It plays
100 % like it works. And then everything around it is so fucking bad. The guy from
Not necessarily the news. Do you remember that show? You're old enough to remember that show?
No, I've never seen it. Just before your time HBO. I think Conan wrote for it because the reason I know
it is when I gave a tour of the NBC studios as a page when we got to the Conan set that was part
of the spiel yet to say he got his start as a writer for HBO is not necessarily the news. But I've
two casts. It actually was fairly succinct. That's where Snigglets came from. Rich Hall.
But anyway, they the second cast, the main male, there was a male and female anchor and the
main male anchor, I forget his name, but he played the bad guy in ladybugs, I remember.
I don't want to look up his name because I'm afraid that I don't know how the internet is. I don't
want to fuck up the zoom connection. Oh, I'll look it up. I thought you didn't want to look it up
because you didn't want people to know that you were looking up this actor. Well, I'm also nervous to
Google about a movie that started a bunch of 12 year old girls. And Jonathan Brandis, RIP. Brandis,
yeah, RIP. Tom Parks. Yeah. Do me a favor. Lower your mic just a bit because it looks like it's over
your mouth. Okay. I'm just worried that if you keep ducking down, we're going to have a bad,
no, no, just tilt it down. Oh, tilt it. Okay. All right. Not that far. Now it's below your mouth.
You want it on my mouth? Yeah, there you go. You know how bikes work, right?
I clearly know every week we start with me trying to figure out this this mic. And every week I remember
I have yet to turn it on. Today we're doing the incredible shrinking man, which is what my
ex -wife called me when she'd come in the room. Make it folks. I want to say original. There is no
remake. I can't believe there's the Lily Tomlin. It's a sort of a reasonable shrinking woman.
But anyway, we discussed this with Mr. Dana Gould last week or whenever that was our first guest.
Wonderful guest. Yeah, he really was. Who better to discuss horror and comedy and horror comedy?
I mean, he's a terrific commentary as we mentioned on the criterion interview. Does he also do
the commentary? Yeah, him and Dante. Oh, I thought they just did that bonus interview discussion
about it. I didn't know they did the commentary too. That's very cool. Yeah, they do.
Dana also, thank you for coming on and talk to the guy that just indulged you in everything.
You know what I mean? Like anything you want to talk about, I'll talk to you, but like
there are guys that aren't like that. Like that they're like, I don't know what it's
fucking talk about, you know, yeah, years ago. You know, like, but he jumped in on everything.
He's one of my favorite comics alive. I saw him open for a pepper tone recently. He's still got
the goods. Not that he's sure he's still have the goods. But yeah, you're right, Joe. It's a
conversation. Not a commentary. You win again. That's what I do. That's what Trump and
Jean taught me. We it's also got a the lost music of the incredible shrinking man. Something that
I would wager. No one has ever listened to ever. Who is putting on the blue ray at the thing? Do
I think would you throw on that criterion? Incredible shrinking man blue ray. I'm so
soon to the lost music. Well, I'd like I'd like to fuck you to the lost music of the incredible
shrinking man. Could you throw that on? Just hops on top of her. Oh my God. That is such a hot
crack. I was talking to Pinkstone about it last night. And I was like, you know, dude, you love
I brought him a birthday present. Yeah. And I got him some records. And but I said,
I go, dude, I almost got you the criterion head wig in the angry inch because I know you love
that movie, but I also know you already own a blue ray of it. And I got to tell you, I love criterion.
By the way, today this is it. Like last three days of the sale. These cocksuckers, they're just
emailing me. They can't let me keep my money in my pocket. I got to go fucking do this now.
But I said to him, I go, I love criterion. But you're not going to be able to tell the difference
with the 4k scan as we discussed last week. I think right here. And then also I go, the special features
are just not enough to make a jump to the criteria one. Like it's now, you know, it's it's you know,
it'll be like, the main guy goes to buy a toaster. You know, like, okay, I guess yeah, like,
you know, whatever his name is John Cameron Mitchell. The pink pink flamingos new
blue ray is awesome. I'll say that. It's got a great Jim Jarmouche interviewing John Waters.
I mean, part of it is John Waters in any special feature makes it truly special. He's just
endlessly funny and charming and fast. He's the best. He's the best. He is his audio books are great too.
It's a way better experience than just reading it because he reads them. But his his he's a great writer.
Great great prose writer too. In addition to his movies. I will say that as far as the pink flamingos
criterion goes, right? Yeah, you probably don't need 4k for a movie that looks like it was shot on
that. I was holding it. I was just going to say I just sort of commentary from a priest named Richard
Roer who talks about the how how almost like hilarious. The idea of a golden Christ is, you know,
I mean, the idea of like a gold statue of Jesus is like how absurd that is. And it's only the
absurdity of that idea is only matched by a 4k drink for pink flamingos. For sure, for sure.
It's so crazy. But it still looks horrible. I mean, he talks about how he filmed that he goes,
the sound we use to the same sound that they were using at the time for news bulletins like
woman on the street like, Hey, here we are at the fire at 14th and main. He's like, that's the
sound quality we were using. And I don't know. It looks as good as it's ever looked, but that's not
very good. I just got the 4 pack the trauma 4 pack of toxic Avenger movies, which bonus scary stuff.
I wasn't even going to talk about this. Do yourself a favor again. If you're a toxic Avenger fan and
you're a trauma fan, it's a great little set. I know Amazon has it for like 35 bucks, which is
an unbeatable price, but go to trauma and get it and pay the 50 or whatever it is. If you're going
to get it, I had a, I bought it from trauma. I was like, there's no world where I can justify buy,
and I buy stuff from Amazon, but I was like in a situation like this with a company like trauma,
I cannot justify buying it for cheaper on Amazon and not buying it directly from them.
You know what I mean? We're not talking about a Warner Brothers distributed movie here or whatever.
So anyway, I got the set. It's a good set. But the first one is really what it's all about, but
there's the thing in the first one with audio that's so funny, and I can't tell if they did it on purpose
or what, but like when he becomes the toxic Avenger, all of the toxic Avenger's lines are dubbed in.
And it go, it like the whole movie has a natural whatever sound to it. It's mixed in a certain way,
and it all sounds consistent. And then like when he talks, it's a completely different tone. It sounds
like he's in a booth. The voice doesn't match the character and they'll be like, I don't like
slaughter four people and then to save somebody's life. And then he'll be like, I'm terribly sorry. I
guess this weird shift, Mr. Herman, it's that ridiculous. It's that it's as ridiculous as that. And
it's so fucking funny. And, but you can't, I'm like, did they just not know what they were doing?
Or did they do that on purpose? Because they were, they were they like, who cares? Nobody's going to
give. I don't know. But it's part of the charm. It's great. And it's, it enhances the experience,
I think. All right. I saw the toxic Avenger when I was a kid and it gave me post -traumatic
stress disorder. Oh boy. Did it scare? I wouldn't be surprised if it scared you. I've actually never
seen a trauma movie. I tried to watch Tromeo and Juliet at some point and I was just appalled. But
I was a kid. Troma is exactly like John Waters. The phase where they're, where they're
doing it all themselves and whatever, not that they ever aren't. But there's a shift that happens.
Where it's suddenly the quality is too good for the content. And that's what happened with
John Waters. Yeah. But those early tromas, you know, Nukum High and, you know, where it looks
gritty and it's fucking nuts. And like, it's like, it all every element, that kind of cinema,
that sort of gonzo cinema, like the early water stuff, it's like, you have to every single
element relies on the other, on another element. Like, and once one of those things is out of place,
it doesn't work. So we didn't talk about it on the pod, but we were talking about it. You just
you and I, like the shift with Waters is serial mom. No, no, well, the shift is, is hairspray. But
hairspray works because it's not a typical John Waters movie. And neither is Crybaby. But then when he
goes back to being John Waters again with serial mom, but it looks like hairspray, yeah, it doesn't work
as well. Even if you like the movie, it doesn't work. It's just, it's just different. And that happens
with trauma at a certain point too. Yeah. I like serial mom a lot, but it's, it's, and I like it way
more than when you get into the other stuff, Pecker and all that, Cecil B. Demented and stuff.
Cecil B. Demented is terrible. I like Pecker though. Hairspray weirdly is PG. I saw when I was very
young, my aunt, my auntie, trust loved it. And we watched it all. My aunt introduced me to
everything cool I ever liked in terms of music movies, et cetera. But I loved hairspray so much.
My introduction to Jerry Stiller, of course. And that is really the perfect kind of bridge of a more
commercial movie and his sensibility even though it's got none of the gross out stuff. It's got divine
as the mom and everything out. But you're right. Then Crybaby. It's like even though that's a more
edgy adult movie, it doesn't seem as cool as hairspray because he's just, I don't know. He's lost
a little of his punk spirit at that point. Well, Crybaby, I remember when he made serial mom
seeing an interview with him on the press tour that he was doing for it, saying like I'm back
rad by lawn. I'm back in our rated territory. And it was, he was pitching it or selling it,
whatever you want to say, promoting it very much as a return to form, which it is in certain ways.
But it just doesn't feel right for some reason. And I'm not saying it's bad. It just doesn't feel
the same. Pecker's the same way. Like he said, a dirty shame is the last one he did. And that's like
you can tell he's really trying to get back into like the gross out stuff. But the problem is,
is all the gross out stuff is not, it's like Hollywood effect gross out stuff. Right. So it's not really
that gross. Like at that time, the fairly brothers would beat them at his own game as far as that stuff
goes. I mean, I'm perplexed as to why waters. I mean, look, he seems to be like pretty much set.
And he's living a great life. Like why not just go back and do a fucking eight millimeter or
whatever it's called a movie in Baltimore. Just for fun. I don't know. And he's really with a
billion famous people, you know, like his best friends are like Johnny Depp, Johnny Knoxville,
all these people, like call them up. You know, if not to be in it and keep it, keep it low budge,
then have them give you a little money. You know, do we Kevin Smith did get a bunch of college kids to
shoot it? That's what Smith did with that kill Roy was here thing that still isn't come out.
What is that? Kevin Smith made a hard movie called Kill Roy was here that he shot with students
from a college. And apparently it's coming out, but it hasn't come out yet. He's released a movie
since he shot it. The next being clerk three. But of course three trailer didn't have a laughing at
for me, but I'll see it. It looked like an improvement over whatever the hell that last one was.
James. Yeah. Yeah. It looks a little unterrified. It's going to get schmalcy because of it being
sort of based on him. He said it's very schmalcy and two got schmalcy, even though I really like to.
God damn it. So it's going to be he said it's going to be schmalcy. Oh yeah, he was like it's very
emotional. You know, we've all been through so much. And it's like come on man. People care so
much about these characters. Do they have? They just like you making dick jokes to do. That's all
they care about. Damn it. Just have some fun with it. What's up? You all right? I'm fine. I was just
thinking about Kevin Smith and got me mad. I actually was thinking about Tusk in particular. I love your
enjoyment. We all know you love Tusk. Did I tell you about what I met Justin long? Always. Yeah.
All right. I've told you this story. Yeah. You know, we have a nice we have a nice rapport.
It doesn't know who the hell I am. But if I saw him, we'd have we'd talk like that. Sure. He's in
a new horror movie that looks pretty good called Barbarian. I think it's called Barbarian and Samaritan.
I'm time. I think it's called Barbarian where the girl goes to the house with his name who played
Pennywise. Answered the door. Is Scar's guard or Curry? No. Yes. No. Scar's. I wish it was Curry.
That'd be awesome. Yeah. Why isn't Tim Curry in a modern horror movie? Is he sick? He had a stroke
and he's in a wheelchair. But he can he's in the documentary for it that's about to come out. Oh,
cool. All right. And they interview him and you know, he's got like slurred speech and stuff. But he can
talk and stuff. Like he does like, he does a lot of those like, like, like, it'll be like a pay
to meet him thing on zoom. Like he does those for comic cons and shit. And you know, he sits
and he talks to people and he's like, he quotes the movies and stuff. It's sad that his speeches
affected, but he seems like he still has like a fighting spirit and is doing his thing. But
that all said you could put him in a movie. You just haven't played a guy that's in a wheelchair,
you know, sure. You know, where he'd be perfect.
Perfect. If I was his agent, I would, I would have called Ryan Johnson immediately. He'd be
perfect in a knives out. Oh yeah. We know him from Clue. He's got that kind of personality. And
knives out is a movie where you, you want somebody in a wheelchair, you know? Yeah, coming
into the Patriarch. Yeah. That'd be great. That'd be great. I love it. I do hope. You know,
I like knives out quite a bit. And if it's going to become a franchise, great. They said that
Johnson and Daniel Craig each stand to make like $60 million from part two from Netflix.
Who's struggling? They're struggling and losing subscribers, but people are making $60 million
in a movie. Can somebody please just buy me a house? It's nothing. It's nothing. Yeah, to people.
Can somebody help me here? What the fuck is going on? Usually you're going to want to have something
to offer ideally a hot bod or something to somebody. And then maybe they would buy you a house.
50 cent is a millionaire. Have my baby. I'll make you a millionaire. And I'm like,
that's what an approach to life that is where you just, you have so much money. You're like,
look, if you sire me a child, I'll just make you a millionaire. Don't ask any questions. We'll
work out the papers. It's got to make sex horrifying as well, you know? As with, you know, NBA players
and with, you know, I know some actors who got into some trouble with this kind of stuff. Like,
there are people out there who see as a mark, you know, knock me up.
If I was the one getting pregnant, I'd thrilled. Oh, I'd be thinking about which the rest is like
the deposit into the account. I'd be so excited. Yeah. Why don't you take us to the movie corner?
Because in nine minutes, I have to stop and restart zoom because now it does this all the time.
Where it only lets us have 40 minutes. But let's at least start up the movie corner.
Yes, let's, Joe. I saw a movie that I have been wanting to see since I was a kid and I used to
like obsessively try to find movies and video stores, which honestly, sadly, I think
gave my life purpose. I used to love looking for shit. And that is all gone. We've talked about how sad
that is on this podcast before. But just like going from store to store, like I go, you go to a
blockbuster and like, oh, they got this one, but it's like 20 minutes away. Oh, I'll drive up there
and get it now. You just got everything you need. But I always wanted to find this movie out of the
blue directed by Mr. Dennis Hopper starring Mr. Dennis Hopper. And it's been out of print. I thought
that was because you know, Dennis Hopper's had a very crazy wild career and he's got some movies that
are notoriously bad, but this was close to this. Yeah. Right. Yeah. And I've been reading about it
in movie guides since I was little. So just recently Natasha Leon and Chloe Civigni put together
a little money to do a 4k restoration of this movie and get it re -released because it meant so much
to them as young women. I like those actresses fine, but whenever anybody in a position of power
does something like that, I just love the hell out of it. Scorsese devoted his whole career to, you know,
preserving film. And this is an amazing movie. And I see why they did it and I see why it would
have meant something to them when they were young women. The star is Linda Mans, who is dead,
but Linda Mans was an amazing child actress. There's really nobody else like her. She was in
Days of Heaven. She's got a very unusual look and voice, almost like a mix between the two kids from
Bad News Bears, Tatum O 'Neal, and then who's the guy who went on to play a pedophile and everything.
Jackie, her earl, her earl. She's like a weird kind of androgynous combination of those two kids.
You know, it's hard to tell at first if she's a boy or a girl, etc. But is there a dash of
math hell in there too? There's a little math. Yes, she's got jowls. The movie is, you know, I just
looked it up on Leonard Box and the first word is harrowing. And it is harrowing. It's 89 minutes.
I just bought the Blu -ray side unseen. There are two discs so stuffed with special features.
It make criteria and shit their pants. I started to watch an interview with Dennis Hopper and I
realized that it was two and a half hours. So I was like, yeah, maybe another time. But they went all
out. It's a very special movie to a lot of people. Basically, it's a young girl. We kind of follow
her as she goes about her day. She's very into punk music. The theme song of the movie is Neil Young's
My My, Hey, Hey. Better to burn out than to fade away. It starts with Dennis Hopper driving his
young daughter. She's like, you know, her head's on his shoulder. He's got his arm around her,
kind of the sweet moment they're driving and laughing. He's guzzling from a bottle of whiskey while
driving his daughter. And runs a stop sign and at full speed collides with a school bus full of
screaming young children. You see children's bodies like toppling out of the bus. I mean,
this is how the movie begins. From there, it's basically just a character study. He goes to prison,
of course, but we kind of pick it up as he is getting out. He returns home to find that his wife
and the young girl's mom has been shacking up with his best friend. This leads to all sorts of
complications. He is drinking as hard as ever when he gets that a prison. He gets confronted by
parents of kids that he killed on the bus. He treats like they're being assholes for bringing it up to
him. He's like a, he's an awful, awful character. Arguably worse than Frank Booth in Blue Velvet.
And Dennis Hopper just plays the shit out of him. Now it gets very, very disturbing in the home stretch.
Like the last half hour, very disturbing. I think that is the reason why it did not get a
release. And why was he started having sex with a daughter or something like that?
We're trying to. Near the end, he patches things up with the friend. And he's,
they're worried that she is, quote, a dyke, end quote, not my word. And the two parents of the girl
try to get this other 50 year old guy who's a friend of theirs to go upstairs and fuck the daughter
to make her straight. Okay. So they go up there and she kind of fights them off in a scene that
harrowing would be the word I would use for that scene. I was standing up while I was watching it.
Very uncomfortable to make suspense out of is this girl going to get assaulted or not?
Um,
picture and hopper trying to get funding for this and the person going, you know, Dennis,
it sounds more like a passion project. Do you have, do you have something with more of a hook?
Yes. Maybe an easy ride or sequel? I know. I know. Well, I will tell you, I will tell you off camera,
the final scene of the movie, Joe, in case people want to see it. But it's worse than everything I've
described thus far. But the movie is absolutely incredible. Hopper was an amazing director
he started with one of the most successful movies ever made easy writer. Then he made the last movie
while completely out of his mind on drugs. That movie, I saw it's not terrible, but it lost a lot of
money. And basically he was in director's jail for years. And the story of this, which is very brief,
but fascinating, I think, is they were doing this Canadian like family drama. And Dennis hopper took
an acting part in it for money. He was going to play the girl's dad. A weekend of production,
the financier saw the job the director was doing. And they were like, you know what,
we're not going to make this movie anymore. And at the time, it was just like a family story
about a young girl making her way in the world. Hopper goes, would you give me the weekend to rewrite
this script and make it a different kind of movie and direct it? And they were like, yeah, give it a
shot. So over the weekend, he made it into this sick twisted thing. And it's got one of the most
interesting stories of how it came to be I've ever heard. I just think that's so cool that like,
we're going to shut down production. And he was like, well, we got all these cameras. Let me write
something better. And then I'll do it. You know, I love that kind of spirit. I love hopper.
Strongly recommend this movie. If you're if you like, you know, your material, a little
fucked up. That's a great movie. I watched, I'll do two because I already, one of them was toxic
Avenger, but that led me into scary stuff. But I watched idiocracy. Yeah, I didn't talk about this
today. No, no. But have you ever heard anyone compare our current state of America to idiocracy?
I think I might write a like a Buzzfeed article about that because I don't think anybody's ever
brought it up before. It is even just even hearing that for 10 years now. Yeah.
It is shocking still how similar it is as I had never seen the movie. I'm a sucker for Luke Wilson,
as I said, many times on the show. Yeah. You know, it's a funny movie. It's the worst of the
Mike judge movies without question. In my opinion, extra, I love it's worse than extract. I love
extract. Wow. Okay. Extract. You got to give extract another chance. There's a lot. Bateman,
Bateman melting down an extract is enough. That's the price of admission right there.
All right. Then you got Affleck is the as things have burned out. Pimp when he's trying to be the
Pimp, the Jigalo Pimp. I remember him being funny, definitely. Keckner is perfect as like the annoying
neighbor like it's that's like complete office space vibes. Rewatch extract. All right. But anyway,
idiocracy as insightful as it is. It's it's it's it's it's funny. It's not not funny. But
my favorite part was when he when he's trying to explain to them that they need to water the plants
with water and not energy drink. And they don't understand. And then the narrator goes
finally, he became so frustrated. He just told everybody that he knew how to talk to plants.
Then it cuts to Luc Wilson, like, who punched over talking to a bush or whatever. Uh -huh. Yeah,
it was very funny. I remember loving some line and I'm sure I'll botched it where they were talking.
Is that movie the number one movie in the country is just an ass, right? Yeah, we just look at an
ass. Yeah. Yeah. And he goes, we used to we isn't isn't that a line in it where he's like, we used to
care about why the ass was farting. And you know, it's not in there. I might imagine. Yeah, it's
something like that. We used to care about the ass. We were looking. It wasn't enough to just look at
an ass. You cared about the ass. You were looking. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Um, uh, what's his name's very funny in
it. Um, I'm not usually a fan. Yeah, but that shepherd was very funny. He's doing some fucking
voice. That's like where he's like clearly was like, I'm going to sound as stupid as humanly possible.
Yeah. Very funny. I like that. It's a lot actually. And I started watching parenthood. The,
the network show based on the amazing movie. And he's the best part of that. That's a really good
show actually. Terry. I'm sorry. No, it's fine. Maya Rudolph is funny. She's just a bit underused
in the movie, but, um, but she's funny in it. Uh, Terry Cruz, I wanted more. They don't really give him
a ton to do. Um, but yeah, in the accuracy, it's, it's worth a watch. You know, I would buy it. But,
uh, but yeah, it's worth a watch. It's very odd to me that Mike Judge has gotten the swings
that he's gotten. Because office space, I saw opening night with my buddy, Ben and Mary and we were
the only two people in the theater. I knew I had seen something very special, but we were the only
people there. Uh, in theocracy, I saw with a different friend, and there was maybe four people in
the theater, and then extract. I saw at an advanced screening, and it was not even half full.
The man's always losing money for the studios, and yet he keeps going. I guess because of Beavis
and Budhead. And, you know, Silicon Valley was a big hit as well. But, um, yeah, not a lot of movie
success for the guy. I don't know. I love movies. He's fun. Uh, yeah, rewatch extract. It's, uh,
I will. I will. Yeah. TJ Miller's band. That's funny. Come see my band play. We're called God's
cock. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. That's funny. That's one of the funny parts. There's other funny parts.
Okay. Okay. Um, I rewatched killing them softly, which Joe discussed last week.
Ooh, baby. I recall being home for Christmas. I went out with friends. I had 10 to 14 drinks,
and then I saw a 12 45 AM show of killing them softly. And that's how I would have let that movie live
on in my memory if Joe did bring it up again, because I remember hating it. I was so drunk that I missed
that it's very clearly an allegory for American politics, which is it's almost too obviously an
allegory for it. Um, I just took it as a straight up crime drama, and I was like, this sucks. I just
didn't get into it. Second viewing. Absolutely love the thing. Uh, it's so short. It's so efficient,
effective, no fat on it. Uh, it's pretty good. The, you know, Leo does amazing in it,
and kind of a kind of a weak role for him. You know, you're rarely seen in a cock, but he plays it
great. He is, and I, you know, I guess it took his death for me to, I always loved him, but to
realize that he's a way more versatile actor than he gets credit for. Even in that soprano's movie,
Joe disagreed, but I thought his take on both characters was fantastic. You definitely could tell
who you were looking at in each scene, you know. Uh, the, uh, the, the, the killing him,
that scene in killing himself, where he's getting beat up is hard to watch. Yeah, feel sorry for him.
When he's like crying and you're like, this is really sad. And then what's interesting about
that movie is it's met. There are scenes like that that are very dire and upsetting. And then they're
met with scenes that are really fucking funny. Ben Mendelssohn should have got an Oscar for that
movie. I mean, he is off the fucking planet and that thing. He's so gross in it. Yeah, that's really
the first time he was on my radar, I think. And I was like, Oh, wow, this guy's a really good actor.
But the movie is, you can't even really use a word like stolen by you got to say just come like a
heist of the movie by James Gandalfini. Yeah. And they know it. They know that they've got like
a great character and they have one of the all -time great character actors playing. It starts with this
intro shot of him coming down an escalator, looking like he's been drinking for nine years,
which he has over at the airport. You, you in real life, he had been. Yeah, for sure. You immediately
love, love him and are like, what is this guy's story? Joe already talked about this. But the scene
where he sits down says his wife's leaving him. He has four drinks in the span of about two minutes
and is barking at the waiter to bring him more. Yeah. Is one of the best scenes he ever did. And that is
saying, that's really saying something. Uh, he's so. How was your bartini half half evaporated because
you're fucking long to bring it over here. Like he is wild in that thing, man. He's perfect. It's like
and he's not doing like the John can. And look, I love John can. He's not doing the John candy in
JFK where it's like kind of showy and he's showing off a little bit. It feels like a man who is
depressed in his pores down to his bones. And he he was. So maybe it wasn't that big a challenge for him,
but man, I watched that scene three times in a row. And then his second scene comes up where he's
with a prostitute the morning after he's gone on this huge bender. And that scene's amazing.
I think you also mentioned the line, Joe, stop treating your anus like it's a national treasure.
Uh, a shocking line in a movie full of shocking lines. But it's great. It's very, very timely. Uh,
it's set like during the, uh, the time where Obama's about to be elected. So there's talk radio and
politics. Basically in the background of every single scene, what's that that you're like, would
these criminals be listening to NPR this much? I don't know. I've seen people dig it for being a little
on the nose with the social commentary, but um, it's brilliant in that way. If you want to watch it
as an allegory or a satire and it's really effective, if you just want to watch it like a crime movie,
I underrated this movie tremendously when I first saw it. I think it resonates now more so
than it probably did when it first came out because I didn't care about politics. I didn't know
anything about it. Well, it's, I liked that it's a movie that has a take on. It's not a, it's not a
Republican movie. Yeah. But it is, it does take a stance of all this talk of hope and a new tomorrow
was bullshit. Nothing's going to change in this country. And seeing that now with reflection,
yeah, is much more poignant than at the time that it came out. And I find that very interesting,
where you're dealing with guys that are living in the lower part of society, the underbelly,
saying that speech that pit gives at the end, dude, where he's like, he's like, in all his foot,
when, when I got it right here, let me just, let me just read it. That's a hot fucking
thing. Because the guy that pits done all this stuff for is going the typical government
weasel route of like, yeah, he's a mob guy, but you know, he's like, I don't know if we're going to pay
you the full amount, whatever. It's Jenkins, isn't it? It is Dick Jenkins, who's clearly,
Pitt is clearly a fan of him because he was in every movie with him for a while there. But he goes,
don't make me laugh. One people, it's a myth created by Thomas Jefferson. My friend Thomas Jefferson
is an American saint because he wrote the words all men are created equal words. He clearly didn't believe
since he allowed his now children to live in slavery. He's a rich wine snob who got sick of
paying taxes to the brits. So yeah, you write some lovely words and rouse the rabble and they went and
died for those words while he sat back and drank his wine and fucked a slave girl. This guy wants to
tell me we're living in a community. Don't make me laugh. I'm living in America and in America,
you're on your own. America is not a country. It's a business. Now fucking pay me.
It cuts the black. It cuts the black. 89 minute movie. Just really, really good.
Really good. I got chills with you reading it. Now now picture Pitt delivering it with those blue
eyes. I have blue eyes too. You do. You do. But they're obscured by the microphone button. I have them.
It's a great flick. And I'll close this out with, I already, you know where this is going. I
got a movie. There's a movie. I saw that while I was working in an office in Austin, Texas. So here
I am watching a movie shot in Austin, Texas about the situation I was in when I first saw it.
I felt that that that God was whispering in my ear. I didn't understand how something could be
so spot on. Yep. To this day, I have never seen something that spot on to something I could relate
to every character in the movie. My friend Robert Davis and I were like, that's Mike. That's our
bought. That's like, like, and I don't mean like, oh, there's sort of a correlation. I mean,
it was like, did you sneak into my life and base a movie on it? I couldn't wrap my head around it.
It was the thought my senior year of high school. And I honestly don't think that there was a single
piece of entertainment that has ever had more of an impact on my life because I was I was trying
to decide what I wanted to do with my life. Did I want to even get out of Missouri? Did you know,
what did I want to, you know, career wise, et cetera. And that movie was just like, oh no, you can't,
you can't go this route. You'll die. You'll kill yourself if you go this route. It's the huge
impact on my life, honestly. It's the funniest John McGinley's ever been. It's the funniest Ron
Livingston's ever been. It's the funniest Jennifer Aniston's ever been, which is saying a lot.
She's done a lot of comedy. She is the ultimate dream girl in that movie. It kills you. That scene,
I laugh so fucking hard. The wind. She's like in the trance when he's asking her out for the first
time. She's going, okay, okay. Okay. Yeah. She's so funny that when she flips out about the flair,
you're going to lose it because it's stupid. Here's, here's what I think of this job where she,
the way she gives Mike, um, uh, Mike judge the finger. That whole scene is so fucking funny.
And then the guy that plays Michael Bolton, uh, it's just a, that guy's amazing who pretty much never
acted again. And, and, and how could he? I mean, he was that guy and that's it. That, you know,
he, I bet he works on an office now to be honest. No, I looked him up. I was watching it. He
actually acts steadily, but you just don't realize it. And he, he, but he lives in Texas. I believe
he does a lot of voice stuff. Okay. The Indian guy acts all the time. The Indian guy is so amazing.
Me and Pinkstone always go back up in your ass with the resurrection when he's rapping the ghetto
boys song. Um, when he started, I was high. The first nurse was movie. When he started break dancing
in the living room, I thought I was going to have a fucking stroke. It was like, I couldn't even deal
with it. But, um, the entire movie, what's his name who played? Okay. Uh, what's that actor's name?
That is, that man should have not been nominated. He should have won Best Supporting Actor. His name
is Gary Cole. Gary Cole. That's right. And he, that is one of the all -time great comedic performances.
That is it because it is, it could have gone into cartoon. And it comes close root. In my opinion,
the Milton character goes too far into cartoon. Started as a cartoon. My least favorite aspect of
the movie is the Milton character. I don't like it. But, uh, it's a disturbing character. But there's
a guy like that in every office. And it's testament to how good of an actor. What's his name is?
But I agree. Yeah. Uh, Stephen Roop. But, uh, no, Gary Cole in that movie is a killer,
just unbelievable. And then the fantasy when he's fucking Aniston while drinking out of the coffee.
The guy that's like the guy who also is in tons of stuff, it's a man where you jump to conclusions.
That, that, that, and the theater was one of the hardest I've ever laughed, honestly. The
jump to conclusions, Matt. And then later when they show you the mat is when I just lost it again.
Just an amazing joke. Amazing. The, the, the three of them reacting to that, where Bolt goes,
that's the stupidest idea I've ever heard in my life. And then when the Indian guy goes,
this is a terrible idea, this idea. Like, he was like offended and is sold by it. Like,
yep, it's so, and then the, the fate of that guy when he backs out of his driveway to one of the,
one of the only, one of the only times that's happened had been truly shocking because usually you're
like, oh, this guy's gonna hit by a car now. That, and then, oh my god, we're almost bearing the
lead here. Dietrich Bader, killing it. I worked with him on outsourced and he stole that show
as well. But man, he was the nicest, most genuine, funniest, coolest guy. He'd bring cookies to the
writers. He made cookies. I love that guy. And he's so funny in that movie. The, I mean, it's,
they go back to the well, like three times on this joke of him about to say something that you
think is gonna resonate. And it's an absurd thing. Like, so the first time they do it is when
he goes, if I had a million dollars, I'd wreck it. I know what I'll tell you when I do two chicks
at the same time. And then it cuts around living some laughing because he thinks he's joking.
And then it cuts back to Dietrich Bader with the most sincere face. He's so focused. That
at the end, hey, Peter, man. Yeah. Watch your corn hole in there. Like you. Yeah, that,
the, oh, which reminds me, the court scene, I, I sentenced you to 10 years and a pound me in the
aspirin. That the fucking, and then the Dietrich Bader line. And it's so, again, it's so perfect. And
it's so Texas and whatever. When he hands him, he goes to hand him the bottle opener. And he goes,
no, thanks, I got, I'm good. And he pulls the one out of his pocket and does every.
Yeah, you've never seen that little detail in a movie. And it's a movie full of a billion of them.
It's like, it's like what it does is what great stand up does, which is takes a little tiny moment
that you'd never think about in your everyday life. And shows it to you in a way that everyone can
recognize and understand. And it's funny. And that little, I used to be that guy. I used to have a bottle
opener on my, on my keys, you know, like, yeah, there's so many details like that, that the movie,
it's, it's, it's an, it's an incredible, incredible movie. It really is.
Because it's a philosophy movie on top of everything else.
Yeah, we should have just made the episode about off the space. Chris, I could talk about this for
you. I'm going to watch it today. I know that now. Yeah, I feel like I need, I feel like I need
to go in for another rewatch. Well, these great comedies, you know, like, you'd, like,
that just become part of the culture. You kind of feel like you'll never watch them again,
necessarily. Like I'm never dusting off Anchorman, even though it's made me laugh more than
most things in my life. But when you do something, I watch Napoleon Dynamite pretty recently,
which I remember, you know, enjoying like anybody else did, I was dying at this thing because
we forget comedy. It's not around anymore. So then when you watch something with like relentless
jokes, it can change your day. Yeah. Point of comedy. Yeah, it's, it's, yeah, that redip into Anchorman.
I was like, I was just watching the YouTube clips and I was like, Jesus Christ, man. Yeah. And
that was a, and at the time, that was a comedy that comedians and comedy fans, some of them
rode off like, I don't like that type of comedy. I actually like this other comedy that just came out.
Could you imagine having the luxury of that right now? You could go now. No, Anchorman to me is too
absurd in whatever. It's not for me. I'd rather watch this thing. Yeah. Like for, you know, wedding
crashes or whatever else was coming out at that time. Right. Like, which is also a strong comedy. Like
it's like, forget it, dude. You, it's anyway, Jack Black saying now this is happening and kicking
that dog off the bridge in Anchorman. I, there are 20 minutes in Anchorman where I was at the theater,
like not sure I was going to be able to make it to the end. I have a long said. Kingpin and Anchorman,
the two hardest I've laughed in the theater, no question. Unbelievable. Which brings us to a terribly
not funny movie that we're reviewing today. It's called the Incredible Shrinking Man. Yes, the
Incredible Shrinking Man, which I actually did find kind of funny in a certain way here and there.
But I also was very, very much not expecting how serious and depressing it was at times and how dark
this guy views his fate as a shrinking man. Well, Gould and Dante broke it down best on the
criterion special feature. They were like, this whole thing is an allegory for masculinity and
and it's very of the time. You know, this is a book that was written. I believe in the late 50s.
And at that time, it's, you know, it was America, Americana, you're a man you provide for your family.
This is not the other thing and you go, here's a movie where he's not only unable to
continue to provide for his wife because of this condition. He is now also unable to protect her,
which was another big part of the male female dynamic back then physically. And then also without
saying it in the movie and the book apparently goes a little further into this, he can't satisfy her.
Yeah. So it's literally a man shrinking in all ways, literally in metaphoric.
You know, and one thing I really like about it is it's not overly explained. It's like he goes
through a weird cloud. They're on vacation. In fact, God, this is brilliant. They're on vacation
and he goes through, they're on a boat and he goes through a cloud of some kind of
something that wafted off of a nuclear site somewhere or something like that. I forget exactly what
it is. But then he has glitter on his chest. There's not a lot of all the special effects money
went to the shrinking. Yeah. So, but what's so brilliant even about the setup is it opens with him a
line with his wife on a boat and he's saying he's being funny, but he's being misogynistic in a way
because he's saying, not misogynistic. So, what's the other term? Sexist?
Yeah, sexist. There's a different, yeah, sexist. But, you know what I mean?
He's saying to his wife like, well, God's man's wife, she get him a beer, you know? And she's like
arguing, like, it's playful, but they're debating it. And she says, she doesn't want to get him.
She's like, get yourself a beer, you know? And he's like, tell you what, I'll pay for dinner.
You get me something like that. And she goes, okay. And then because he makes his wife get him a beer,
she doesn't get hit with the cloud. He gets hit with it. Which is so fucking brilliant.
Like, here you go guys. This is what you get. And then that's what basically initiates the shrinking
process that gets more and more dire as the movie goes. The one bright spot of hope in the middle
is when he meets the circus woman who's supposed to be a little person. And that doesn't really come
across. But yes, it took me a minute to understand what was even going on. I was like, is this a little girl
that they have a grown woman playing or what's happening? No, they take a regular size woman
and they shrink her down to be a little person instead of just getting a little person.
But he, so he falls in love with her and realizes, oh, this might be my chance to live a regular life
again. Right. And then there's that incredible haunting scene where they're having like this,
this dreamish day and they're on up there, picnicking and whatever. And then they get off the park
bench and realizes he's shorter than she is. And that it's happening again. And he's shrinking
again because they think they've stunted it, but he's wrong. And then it would really maybe laugh
just runs off into the park. I'm like, where are you going? He's like, it's happening. I'm shrinking.
And then runs away. I thought that was really funny, actually. So the bulk of your movie takes place
with him being so minuscule that he, that then he lives in a dollhouse for a while and his wife is
kind of, his normal size still in helping him and feeding him and stuff. But eventually he
ends up, I forget what happens, but he ends up in, oh, oh, that's right. The cat,
the cat sequences, one of the great sequences, I think. It tries to kill him, right? The cat attacks
the dollhouse. Right. And they, you know, it's a movie where the scenes show a little bit and the
special effects because it's old and low budget. But like, it feels so much more real to me
than anything we've seen in special effects in a long time because it's handmade. You know, it's,
it feels like a like film students like trying to make something as cool and convincing as possible
on a tiny budget. They do an amazing job. You know, it's clearly just footage of a cat walking around.
But when you juxtapose it with him, they do all kinds of in -camera tricks that are so neat in this
movie. Yeah. Now, sometimes they mess up a little bit. Like, sometimes he'll get off a chair
and walk over to the phone. And it's a giant phone, but it's like, no, wait, the phone should not
be the same size as the chair. Sure. Sure. It's an older film. But, uh, I, but in terms of that,
like, you know, even honey, I shrunk the kids, which is, I love, when I was a kid, forget it, I
fucking obsessed over honey, I shrunk the kids. I didn't realize how influenced it was by this movie,
but that's it. You know, what they did was basically steward Gordon wrote,
honey, I shrunk the kids. You know that, yeah. Yeah. And well, he wrote the story. He didn't
write the script. Yeah. But they took a lot from it. You know, like, that's, that's the beauty of
the movie. Your average everyday thing becomes scary. The cat, to me, the spider, I know people are
more slow to spiders. Well, hold on. He ends up, that's, or I don't want to skip. He ends up in the
basement because of the cat encounter. Right. And now he's, he's the tiniest he's ever been,
and he's living in the basement inside of a match book. And now it becomes the entire movie now
becomes about his survival. Yeah. And he's dealing with two things. He's got to get to a piece of
cake that they really were very well done for shadowing in the beginning of the film where the
wife gets called upstairs and she leaves a piece of cake behind in the cellar. And that's his only
hope for food. His only nourishment is he has to get to this cake to eat stale cake crumbs,
which, which will feed him for years because he's so small. And there's a puddle of water that he can
drink from. And that's his life now that the problem is is there's a spider in the basement. And
the spider will try to kill him. And that's basically your whole third act of the movie, right?
Right. Yeah. Yeah. And this is another really short movie, 81 minutes. Again, no fat on it.
And it does become kind of this survival thing. The the effects in the in the home stretch with him,
the cat, the spider, the water, you know, you know, because there's a leak in the house that starts
to threaten him as well. Just beautifully done stuff, really amazing stuff. Sometimes I was
rewinding to check out what they did in terms of camera tricks. And it's also like it made me think
about how he like, I get right. Always shows on Twitter something called a Dutch Dutch switch,
I believe it's called, but it's, you know, when it's like the driven thing in naked gun where he
goes behind a couch and then you see some guy do back flips or whatever, you know, like it's ways of
tricking the viewer. And those are so much more fun. And I think even viewers prefer it to this
just CGI globs of shit punching each other. You know, there's an excitement to it, to the filmmaking
of it. And they're finding cheap and original ways to do things that look better, feel better,
are more exciting, more fun to watch. It's it blew my mind really. The whole movie. It's great.
And written by the great Richard Matheson, which is probably why it feels a lot like a long
twilight zone. It feels like a long, excellent twilight zone. It looks like it's shot on the same
stock as the twilight. Yeah, yeah, very much. And the book is the book is also apparently amazing.
I've never read it. I want to, but apparently the book gets even deeper. There's a part in the book
during the shrinking process where he's abducted by a pedophile. Yeah. I get, you know, so I'd like
to read the book, but he eventually does kill the spider, right? And he makes his way to the
outside world because he realizes that's the only way he can survive. And I was going to go out into
nature, basically. And when he gets out there, he realizes this beautiful existential ending that he
does have purpose. And it's not about what size he is, but he is part of the universe. And it pulls back
and it goes way, way, way up into the, into the stars. And you see how, and it's this existential
existential thing where it's like, we're all tiny. Doesn't matter. Look at this universe. Look how
grand it is. Right. It's a brilliant, brilliant ending and a completely shocking ending for that time
period. I mean, you talk about movies never ended like that. There was no such thing as indie film,
really, you know, this was like, everything was like kind of in the theater or not. And
that for this thing to end that way and be this big sci -fi thing and what it, it's just a great,
great movie. Again, a criterion release. It looks impeccable. The black and white's always look
great when they read, when they remaster them for, for Ken and Blu -ray. It looks amazing. My hog is way
up for the incredible shrinking. My hog is way up as well. It's not shrinking at all, Joe.
I would ask, can you name other than Twilight Zone the movie? Another movie that feels this much
like a Twilight Zone? I couldn't think of one. The block, I just know that Richard Kelly movie,
which felt like a Twilight Zone. Well, there, there are, that's math is into it. There's met, there are
other adaptations of the, of the box that are much better. They did.
They'd actually adapted that for the new Twilight Zone in the 80s, which was great. They did a
version of it in Tells From The Dark Side, which was great. But they don't feel like the Twilight
Zone is for the original Twilight Zone. You know, I think a lot of the, I just watched the blob,
the, the original, the original has a vibe. Yeah. But no. As far as a big picture, black and white,
full -length movie that feels like a Twilight Zone episode, or, or could almost pass as a Twilight
Zone presents the inquiry, whatever, to write. This is one of the only ones I can think of. And,
and a lot of it has to do with that existential ending. It's got a very, very deep ending,
which Rod Cirling famously wrote the endings of the Twilight Zone or the commentaries of
Twilight Zone to be over the heads of the suits. Sorry. They could get them into the show.
But no, this is one. If you're a fan of the Twilight Zone, check it out. If you're a fan of Richard
Mathis and check it out. If you're a fan of just good sci -fi, check it out. The incredible shrinking
man available now for only $20 through the Barnes and Noble Criterion sale. Get it while the
kittens good. Folks, we'll be back next month with something or other. We're not sure yet.
But this has been a really fun month. We've had a great time doing these different types of
episodes this month. And, and that's it. I'm not going to plug. It's the last episode of the month.
We don't need to be plug -ish pigs. Do you agree? All right. I do. And, see, nope. You know,
I think we're going to do nope. Definitely. I can't promise. I'm going to say it.
You're going to see nope. The people want us to talk about. No. I can't promise. I'm reading the
same review over and over. Despite the fact that it's all over the place. It's like, I can't with
this, man. I will try to see nope. All right. I will hopefully see. I will see it eventually.
I just don't know that I'm going to go into a movie theater and sit for three hours
to watch it. But I, I, I know I'm not going to let, let's, I'll probably say no.
I don't say you're not going to like it. I, I, all right. Well, I might, we might do no.
But in any case, we'll, we'll be back next month with a bunch of good stuff. We'll see you next time,
folks. And folks, we'll see you in hell.