We're Roland Paddy. Welcome back, folks. We'll see you in hell. Here we are.
Sayonia, I'm Chal. I'm Chal. Hearing you. You're hearing us. I'm Joe DeRosa.
And I'm Pat Walsh. And this is the podcast where we do horror movie commentaries. It's brought to you
by the Fangoria podcast network for more information about that network, including other programs,
how to follow our show or other shows and find episodes of all the shows. Go visit Fangoria .com.
But enough of that. Here we are. This is a special Halloween episode where we will be
doing Halloween six. No, no, I'm sorry. Eight. Eight? Well, I see why you might be confused, Joe,
because there's so many of them. We are, I think there's six. Then there's H2O.
Then there's Resurrection. And that's what we're watching tonight. Yes, we're watching Resurrection
tonight. Why? Resurrection. I'm sure you're wondering. Without question, one of the worst of the
Halloween films. It's because the only two Halloween films on Netflix are this one and six. And six,
which is the worst one. Now, I haven't seen six. I thought it would be too odd to be like, yeah,
we're just going to watch Halloween six. Resurrection, at least you're getting a fresh start.
But I just watched H2O and Michael Myers's head was cut off with an axe. Well, they explain what
happened here. I mean, is it like they attach them to electros? Now, I know I saw this in high school,
I don't remember anything about it. When I watched H2O, I did remember that. I remembered
LL Cool Jays masterful performance as a guy writing erotic fiction until he gets shot in the head.
And then he's like, Hey, I'm back. He does come back in the end.
Get shot repeatedly by Adam Arkin. And then he's like, ah, I'm all right.
Kind of crazy. Yeah. And then I think there's like a there's like a comedic beat on the way out
with him and the wife. Oh, yeah. He's like, I'm not going to write an erotic thriller.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. He's like, totally fine. Yeah. And then as he walks off, you hear a very ADR line.
He goes ADR and in the biz means you looped it in after the fact. Well, let's say what looping means.
Looping means you're you're they do it in comedies too. Like if everyone has their back to the camera,
you can add jokes for them. Like like awkwardly loop in dialogue to get extra laughs. And it's always
very obvious. It's like a completely different. Yeah, or you'll see their lips frantically moving and
then it'll say like three words. Yeah. But uh, LL Cool Jays he's walking off goes, yeah, I'm fine.
The bullet just grays me because clearly the audiences were like, yeah, could we get some
explanation as to why he gets shot nine times and he's fine. I'll tell you, I always had a problem
with those sort of explanations for things. Yeah. Uh, but I have spent the first portion of this
week. I'm spending this entire week for the first time writing a script. Yeah. I've written for TV
shows, but I've never received a script assignment. So I'm home. Well, thanks, Pat. Uh, but I'm home
about 20 produced apps to my name. And of course, all the residuals that that entails. But go ahead.
That's very exciting. I've uh, yeah, but I'm doing it for the first time and uh, that's very exciting.
Well, it's it's I'm not bringing up to be exciting. I'm bringing up to say,
I get those those half -assed tie -ups now like, yeah, oh, Christ, just put a fucking sentence,
one sentence explanation on page 28. Yeah, especially for a minor character like LL.
Yeah. And in resurrection, we have Buster Rhymes inheriting that role. Buster Rhymes. By the way,
if if you're home and you've heard the podcast before, this is the time, get get Halloween
resurrection. All cute up on your Apple TV or whatever your device is on your Netflix. It's always
Netflix movie here, and we'll see you in hell. So you can watch along with us if you choose.
That's why we're hard -panned. I'm in one of your pets and the other. Uh, if you don't want to listen or
if you don't want to watch along, you don't have to. But uh, find that now because we're about to start.
You got, look at this cast. We got, we got Daisy McCracken. Just sounds like a made -up joke name. It's, uh,
like if I were to pitch uh, in a comedy and her name her name's Daisy McCracken,
maybe like, what is this? Joe dirt three? That's not a real name, but it's her actual name.
I was so excited to see this film when it came out because I loved H2O. I thought H2O was amazing.
I saw it opening weekend in the theater. I think I did too. It's good and the last half of it is
very good, I would say. I loved it. I truly think it's a more or less flawless sequel. All right.
Uh, down, but it's pretty good. I really like it. I think it's the third best Halloween movie.
Well, I know, uh, Ken Hanley agrees. He just did a, uh, for Fangoria representative who put
this whole thing together. He did a Facebook post where he ranked them all and he went, uh, three,
one H2O as the top. Wait a minute. He put season of the witch as the best Halloween movie.
I thought it was kind of crazy too. I just watched season of the witch and really enjoyed it,
but I don't think it has any business being called a Halloween movie. But he ranked that as the
number one Halloween movie. Yeah. And to me, and I know you were saying two is up there,
which I think is really crazy. Two is my favorite. To me, one is so, so much better than the other
ones. And it's not just because it's the classic or whatever. It's just a million times better in
every regard, but okay. Well, I don't know if it's that to just pat just laying it down. It's a million
times better. Look, the first one, I'd say the first one is the most film like out of all of them.
What we're talking about films. Sure. But, you know, I, yeah, I would say, yeah, the second one can't
exist without the first one. The first one has a certain style to it. Right. That the other is
potentially don't have or at least in the amount that the first does. But I just, I love the second one,
because to me, the second one feels like the third act of a movie. It's, to me, it's when the story
really gets going. It starts right at the end of one. Yeah, I like that. It's where all the
mythologies reveal that their brother and sister and it's just very exciting. Good deaths, too. His
death at the end of two is amazing. Like he's on fire. There's also like, you know, like a woman
like, you know, sitting in a hot tub and like a scientist lab or whatever that makes it feel very
cheesy and not like any sort of classic movie. But I love that hot tub death. That's a good look.
She was a fantastic looking lady, but what do you say we start this? Yeah, let's start it up.
If you're watching along, get yourself booted up, hit pause as soon as the picture comes up there
on the movie and then we'll count it off. All right. Everybody's paused. Everybody set. Yeah.
Here we go. One, two, three, play. Now H2O, I did a little research, ignores all the events of
everything except one, two. So it's goes one, two, H2O essentially. Yes. And then does this pick
up after H2O? It must resurrect just picks up after H2O. This is why and how did they get it so bad?
It's why I was so excited to see it because I thought the all the promotion for the movie
showed Jamie Lee Curtis. Yeah. I said, they knocked it out of the park with with H2O. This was a fairly
recent follow -up to it. It wasn't like years and years went by and I was like, okay, they're riding
this heat. Right. The Buster Rhymes thing to me, I was just like, well, Eloculge is the other one,
so I guess they're just thinking like it's potentially good luck to have another rapper in the chest.
And I Katie Sackoff of Battle Star Galactic. Yeah. I was there opening week and you know,
as we'll soon find out spoiler alert, Jamie Lee Curtis dies within the first five minute
Tyra Banks. I didn't remember that. Thanks. Thanks, Joe. Oh, I wonder why they didn't list her in the
cast. So really, she's the last one. This film is Buster Rhymes. Yeah. Well, and I didn't know that
until watching a Buster Rhymes movie right now. Yeah. And in the minute you realize that in the
theater where Jamie Lee Curtis dies like six minutes in, you're like, oh, shit, this is like a Tyra Banks
Buster Rhymes movie now. Yeah. Um, which is not what I signed on for. But that's not, that's not
my bag. Uh, it also has Thomas E and Nicholas who was the rookie of the year. Who?
funky butloven. You never saw a rookie of the year. The movie about that kid that plays pro baseball.
Kid that plays pro baseball. That's a great movie actually. John Candy is the announcer.
Come out the same time as little big league where a kid inherits a major league team.
And that kid is the kid in, is it this? Yeah. He's in this. All right. And he's an American
pun. Now we can, we, I, we discuss this and then we forgot it again. Turn on the subtitles.
I don't think I can now that we're rolling. Oh, I think you have to do it before. No, you can't do
subtitles on Netflix. You definitely can. All right. Well, we're out. Who the hell cares? Yeah, I guess
not. We'll be able to follow the plot. You're right, though. We should be watching Pat
mentioned early. It's so ludicrous that we have them watching these with subtitles so we can see
what everyone's saying. We don't have to like listen and talk. It's just crazy that we didn't think
of this. Yeah. I'm in a very similar raggedy Andy situation. My sister had raggedy and never,
never liked it. Buttons for eyes. Like you'd be sleeping and you'd cut your cheek.
Pat's referring to the fact that Jamie Lee Curtis's character Lori Strode in this has a raggedy
and dollum top of her pillow. So wait, she's in an asylum. She's in an asylum. But she killed him.
Now this is, well, her nightmare is over. This is what bothers me. Okay. She's in an, this is,
let's start where the problem started for me. When I saw this originally, it opened. She's in an
asylum. Immediately you're like, she had a kid. She had a boyfriend. Yeah. Like she was going
all right. She had a drinking problem, but who doesn't? Yeah. She was, I imagine it's somewhat
traumatic to, or scarring to the soul to cut a man's head off. Sure. Especially if he's your homicidal
brother. Right. But it seemed like closure at the end of the last film. It seemed like the end of it
for her, you know, but apparently not. She's back and she's in worse shape than when she was in
the last one. Crazy. Now, did you like a season of the witch? I've never embarrassingly, I'm about to
admit, I've never seen season of the witch. You should have told me we could come over the other
night. I thought it was really fun. I heard it's great. I, here's the thing. The reason I never saw
it was because when I was a kid and I would watch the Halloween movies, which my mom
got me into, my mom was always like, part three was dumb. It didn't have anything to do with the
other ones. That's completely true. So I just never wanted to see it and then like all my friends
that weren't hard movies would say the same thing. And now recently, and by recently I mean within
the last maybe eight months, I've noticed horror fans often say it's a fantastic horror movie.
It's just not. Yeah, and I knew that going inside of give a ship. Yeah, it is truly crazy that out of
like this 12 part series, the third one is just its own thing. It's kind of insane. Did you catch
what happened there? Why Michael Myers is still alive? Switched his body, switched, put his mask on
the paramedic. So, so Laurie Strode accidentally decapitated the paramedic. But oh, and then he put
the paramedic in the body bag? Yeah. So when he stands up in the thing and all that, and walks exactly
like Michael Myers and reaches out and touches her hand and does everything exactly like Michael Myers
and she looks into her brother's eyes. That was actually some Randa. Yes. That's fucking stupid.
Same size. That's fucking stupid. It is stupid. It didn't need to be done. I'm realizing now I did see
this and I fell asleep in the theater, which tells you a lot about a horror movie. There's a reason I
poured a double black coffee before we started this podcast. 10 pm at night where we are. Yeah. And
late for our usual recordings, but the city we're in Los Felas just like I know you didn't fully come
outside to greet me, which I thought was rude. You should have come out in the lawn with your
arms spread wide, but it smells so skunky out there tonight. And I'm not talking about the usual
Los Felas weed smell. It smells like a truck hauling skunks overturned on the street outside of this
house. What do you think that is? It's skunks. It's Griffith Park skunks. Like when I go running at night,
I always see like a giant skunk. Oh, I didn't know that we had a skunk issue over here. Yeah. It's
a big problem. I also at my house, I'm going to sleep some nights and the light sensor on my deck will
turn on, which is horrifying. Like two in the morning and I'm like, oh, somebody is on my deck.
And I looked out the other night. There's a skunk that must have been 80 pounds,
waddling, like bigger than most dogs, waddling across my deck, just like it owned the
fucking place. So I'm like every night when this light comes on, I guess they just sit out here and
have a party. It's terrible. It's like it's like the great outdoors. Yeah, it's sub titles. Yeah,
right outdoors, man. It's got some really funny stuff in it. I'm a big fan of the movie. The problem
is the love story between the teens, which I was clearly kind of forced in, but sure, for the kids.
It's a really funny movie. I mean, John Candy's in Acroix. What do you want? It's a great movie.
I've told you this before, but I once on top of my trash can outside, not in the can, lid was closed.
Yeah, right on top of it. Perfectly like new spotless copy of the great outdoors on one side of the
disc and Uncle Buck on the other side. Oh, spotless disc just sitting there. That's amazing.
Didn't know, didn't know where I thought you were going to share your own raccoon or whatever story
when you said trash can. I got it kind of excited. I saw, well, I will say this. I did.
Uncle Buck's one of my favorite movies ever. It's fantastic. I saw, when I was walking the dog,
and I got home and there was a skunk sort of in front of my house. Okay, but then he scurried off.
And I just remember thinking, if he sprayed my dog right now, that would be a moment where I'd have
to really rise to being a dog owner. I'd have to deal with it. Or would I deal with it, drop the dog
in the trash and move on with your life? I'll tell you, when it's 11 .30 and you're tired, that's not
that crazy even idea. What do you got to do in that situation? You just violently scrub the dog forever.
No, you spend the rest of your day scrubbing a dog. I think I would have had to like leave them in the
yard for a minute, go inside, look at all up on the internet. It would have been a two -hour process.
I mean, it's not, it's not a one -and -done -er, petty. What the hell did he just get out of that vending
machine? All those choices and he gets some non -descript honey bun? He's, he's a chunky guy. I don't,
you know, he looks sort of like a key and peel character. He does. He, uh, yeah, he did get that weird
that was odd. Like, you couldn't read what it was. It's probably because he couldn't shoot.
They have all these rules with product placement. Like, if he chooses one, then you got to pay the
company or what they pay you. Yeah, they clearly shoved some kind of half -eaten donut into a saran rod.
That tells you the kind of penny pension operation we're running here with Halloween resurrection.
Now, for all intents and purposes, the beginning of the film here, it's not terrible. I don't like that
it starts with her and the asylum, as I said. But you got your security guards creeping around the
basement. It's a little eerie. It's a little spooky. Michael Myers is somewhere in there. You know
that he is. See, in that washing machine? No, but the washing machine just went into slow motion,
which means he's going to find something in there. I believe it's ahead. I remember correctly.
We just hit our dog cruelty quota for this podcast. There he is there. I love that. Now, by the way,
the mask in H2O was not great. And I looked it up and I was like, is this the mask I remember?
Because it's not the mask I'm seeing now either. And they said, people complained about the mask and did
reshoots. And they also did some CGI frame -by -frame replacing of the mask because people were like,
what is this? Wait, why? How do you mess something like that up? I never noticed anything out of step
with the mask. It's a different mask than the first one and two. And it's a different mask than
I'm looking at now. This is not this clown mask I'm talking about. What's the difference? Not a
major difference, but the one in H2O looked a little goofier, I think, and a little less scary.
I do remember looking a bit more crisp or something. This one makes very crisp. Almost like he bought
a Michael Myers mask. Yeah. And I guess maybe he doesn't always use the same mask. They probably took
it away if they put him away. I mean, this is basic movie trivia. I'm sure you know, but it's the
original mask was a William Shatner mask turned inside out. Bill Shatner, I did know that.
What's Billy up to? He's in a new horror movie, Tales of Halloween. So it's supposed to be great.
I didn't know that, but I'd love to say that. No, I'm sorry, he's not. He's in another horror movie.
The Christmas one. Christmas horror story. Oh, Christmas horror story. Which also has a
yeah, Krampus is there's a Krampus movie coming out. I believe by the guy that did Trick or
Treat. And then Trick or Treat is pretty good. I like Trick or Treat. I thought that'd be a
phone one tonight too, and that's not on Netflix. I know all these movies were at some point.
I almost suggested and then I forgot because I'm not prepared that we just go off the grid tonight
and not do a Netflix or but do a DVD. So we could actually pick
a Halloween movie we wanted to watch. Yeah, I do think it's smart though just to reach the masses.
Most people have Netflix since then. Of course, but I mean, we did. It's a brand too. Yeah, that's true.
Yeah, there wasn't people kind of rolled with that. People rolled with it. That was a fun event.
And as always, we love your guys feedback. Also, can I discuss the star ratings issue?
Oh, I don't care. All right, so tell them very briefly what happened with you and the
open Anthony showing why the racist of America hates you. Anthony and I had a bit of a public
falling out. It's been very quiet for quite some time now. I don't know what his stance on it is
currently. I have since everything went happen said publicly that my regret was that
grown men and I included myself in this resorted to Twitter and online fighting or something.
Right. And didn't handle things privately. And I again, I included myself in that blame.
There has been no noise about it. Everything has been quiet. As far as I know, it's more or less
behind us. But there's still some angry fans out there that are just crazy. I think it's one
little on my lives. Yeah, I think it's one guy. So it seemed like one guy wrote all these reviews.
They all said, roughly the same thing. And also had one sentence different to make it seem like it
was a different person. Yeah. And you know, she was our podcast had five stars or four or whatever.
It was doing really well. Yeah. And then somebody comes in and gives it eight one star reviews in one
day. And each review is like Joe DeRosa hates women. He's a racist. Anti -Semitic was another one too.
He's an anti -Semitic and they all said the same basic thing. And none of that's true, by the way.
It's obviously ludicrous. And so now this podcast hovers around like a three star. And it does
matter to get people to hear it. So like, congratulations. Your voice is being heard. And this fun
podcast about horror movies that we do now looks like it's not popular and you're shitting on it.
Thanks, man. Well, because why? Because Joe had a falling out with a guy that you don't know and will
never meet. What's wrong with you? So I'm asking you, if you like the podcast and you're listening,
it takes 10 seconds to click the five star rating and try to get us back up because now we're
going against all this shit. And now the guy's going to hear this. And now I'll be a target. And it'll
be like, oh, Pat's also a racist one star. You know, well, it happened. Get a life. It happened to.
I'm assuming it's the same person or small group of persons behind it. But I it also happened to my
album ratings and all this other stuff. So everything I have online basically has like one star.
I mean, like, why would you try to bring a man's career down for like, what's wrong with you?
It's wrong with America. It's look, this is social networking. Why did she just kiss him?
Oh, she said, I'll see you in hell. I don't like that Jamie Lee Curtis kisses him on the lips.
It's very weird. I definitely saw this movie because I remember that moment.
And this is where I checked out. Jamie Lee Curtis falls to her death. In the whole movie,
there was a tiny part in the back of my head where I was like, she's going to come back.
Like, he came back and then she never does. And I was furious. Well, that moment in age two,
oh, when she and him come face to face, not the indie pop group, but she meaning Jamie Lee Curtis
and him meaning Michael Myers. When they first lock eyes, she gets on the other side of that door
and slams it. That was a very exciting moment. It's one of my favorite scenes. Yeah. In horror movie
history, it's iconic. It's two iconic characters. It's the reckoning day. They're having the face -to -face
moment where she realizes, this isn't all my head anymore. This is really happening. I get chills at
that part. You got in the background. Josh Hardnet looking like he's missing a couple chromosomes.
As always, you got Michelle Williams with bizarrely drawn on eyebrows. Yeah, it was a different time.
It was a different time. Back when we just thought Michelle Williams was going to be a Dawson kid,
and that was going to be the end of it, went on to academy award nominations. Yeah.
And then I guess to not act for what seems like about six years now. Yeah.
I haven't seen her in anything. She seems like a sweet kid. I wish she'd come back to us.
I fucking love Blue Valentine is one of my favorite movies. Never saw it. It seems too sad.
Oh, it is, man. Anytime I have a pretty serious argument with a girl I'm dating or whatever,
I'll sit down 2am, fire up a glass of bourbon and watch Blue Valentine, which is very healthy.
But I'm just like, hey, I hear you folks. This is terrible.
Now, I do appreciate that they go 15 minutes before they show the title screen.
They do that in H2O as well. That's maybe scream kind of pioneered that.
But here's the thing. Here's the thing is the other part in H2O that I get chills from
is when Jamie Lee Curtis shuts the gates, she tells her kid and her friends to run.
She shuts the gates and she realizes that she's locking herself in with Michael Myers.
But now she's going to go and confront him. Yeah.
And it's literally the moment where the hunted becomes the hunter and she starts screaming
Michael and the music starts playing goose bumps. I remember I was dating a girl once and
on Halloween I showed her that movie. And I remember she didn't quite get why I thought that part
was so cool. And it wasn't long after that that ended. Let me tell you how this put out.
Now you don't understand. It's Laurie Strode 20 years late.
Yeah. That was her.
Her vagina getting so dry with each word that you say just dryer and dryer as you
rant on and on about what this iconic scene means to you.
Just a paling, drying slab of skin to look like crackling like the Michael Myers.
Yeah. Chafing.
Oh, we should tell the listeners about our real life. Well, my real life, Halloween moment
this week. A true terror come to life. I had a dream about our friendship. I texted you about this.
Yeah. A nightmare about our friendship that we were I haven't heard this yet. So I want to know
what it was. This was the nightmare. We knew a nightmare on friend's street. There was a third friend
that we had, but we didn't like him. Did you see him in the dream or it was a non -distribute?
He was like a guy in the dream. Okay. But like he wasn't like a guy in real life. Okay.
But he was this guy and we I knew in the dream that we hated him. Right. That was backstory,
though. That wasn't happening in the movie in the movie. You know what I mean? So I was with the
guy one night and I go, uh, what do you think? Pat's up to and he goes, I don't know. We should text him
and we both texted you separately and didn't say we were together, but just like, Hey, what are you
up to? And then you only texted him back and said like, Hey, man, I'm around. If you want to hang out
and I was sitting there like, he texted the guy that we hate. He didn't text me back. Yeah.
He must be furious at me. And I woke up, realized it was a nightmare was was shaken still went to
to the grove, bought some corduroy slacks and a Kindle fire. And then texted you and said, I said,
just that I had a nightmare. It showed me up so bad I had to buy something to take my mind off it.
And then and then I didn't hear back from you. And I was like, my God, it's happening in real life.
It was the nightmare come to life. And then and I have not been receiving several texts lately.
Yeah. And I get a lot of texts from unknown. It'll say unknown message not received. I'm having
some issues with my service. Yeah. AT &T. Can you help me out? Yeah. So when you texted me last night
and I said, did you get that text and you said, no, what are you talking about? I was the relief
that washed over me, Pat. Well, that's that's very touching that you care so much about the friendship,
of course I do. Of course I do. That's a sick thing that I've heard of people doing. And I've
often I've had a couple friends be like, hey, we should both text this person at the same time. I
don't remember who it was. I wouldn't say on air anyway. But somebody was like, this friend of ours
is such a starfucker. You text him because it was as a friend of mine who was kind of famous.
And then I'll text him and we'll see if he only responds to it. And I was like, I don't want to know
how this plays out. I wouldn't want to know either. I don't want to know that, you know, it's sick.
And we weren't doing a test in the dream. We were just like, let's both text Pat. We just failed
to say, hey, we're hanging out together. Right. And then that was it. And I was like, oh, God, it was
all kinds of, I remember once Pete was doing his podcast, Pete Holmes was doing his podcast. Yeah.
And he had Patton Oswald on. Right. And I don't know what they discussed before this happened. But
my phone rang. I saw it was Pete. I didn't answer. Then my phone rang a second time and it was some
weird 310 number. I answer. And he's like, his voice goes, Joe DeRose, it's Patton Oswald. And I go,
oh, hey, Patton, what's up? And he goes, can I ask you a question? I go, yeah, sure. And he goes,
why did you answer my calling? Not Pete's. I heard that, actually. Yeah. And I said,
I didn't, this must be a new number. I didn't have it. I thought it was work calling.
Right. I think I also did say, obviously, two Patton were at you. It still would have probably answered.
That's not a shot at Pete. I talk to Pete every day too much.
You know, anyway, Jen Kirkman in a supporting role. It does look like Jen Kirkman. Look at this guy.
That's they couldn't get the guy from that 70s show. They tried. That's a guy who when you cut to,
as we just proved, everyone at the same time says, look at this guy.
Who he's still going up in bars being like, hey, I don't know, you ever see this movie Halloween
resurrection? I was in that. It was like, my God, how hot was Tyra Banks? She was.
Banks is still incredible. I haven't seen her in years. So I don't know. I'm not saying like she lost
it. I'm just saying like right there. I'm like, my God, she still looks great. I mean, she has a
talk show and she seems to have a screw loose, but she was very hot. She still has a talk show. Yeah.
That fucking talk she was doing. I don't know if it's still on, but I remember when she had it.
She'd come out every couple weeks and be like, this is what fat looks like America. Yeah,
that was like a big thing, which was Oprah's bit first. Was it? Oprah would come out and be like,
I lost a hundred pounds and like two weeks later she'd be like, so I gained that hundred pounds back,
which I can relate to. I'll probably do the same thing a couple times a year, not a hundred. This kid,
by the way, in Hollywood Resurrection, is going for the Jason Patrick circa lost boys. Yeah. Yeah.
Look alike award. Yeah, lost boys would have been a good one too. I mean, really, we were like,
let's do a Halloween episode. We got to do a Halloween movie, but what? Well, this is feeling
very final destination here right now. Well, that girl just screamed so loud of glass broke,
which is absurd. Well, let me ask now. So obviously, H2O had a compelling reason to be made,
and it was released on the exact 20th anniversary of the original Halloween, which is very cool.
And they did a fantastic job. Yeah, you never Williamson did not get, he got credited as a co -EP on it,
and apparently he rewrote the script pretty heavily, and he just got that credit as like a thank you,
but he didn't get credit as a writer on the movie. He didn't? He didn't. It's two other guys.
He, you know, Jamie Lee Curtis got that movie made. I didn't. She knew it was the 20th anniversary coming up.
I saw it, saw it on an interview once, and she said, she said, I thought to myself, I can still get
something done in this town. I picked up the phone. I made a call and they say, yeah, yeah, I love
Jamie Lee Curtis. Always have. Who doesn't? I was watching trading places. Oh, God.
Really are today. How about the new scene and that? Holy shit. And I remember, I mean, I've always
been obsessed with Christopher Gaston, his movies, and when I found out he married her, I was like,
dude, you're the best. Yeah. And apparently he's just a complete like asshole, like so bitter and
angry, which I also love. Really? And he landed like the most positive happy woman there is, Jamie Lee
Curtis. Is he bitter? Any interview I've seen with him. He's just like, he's angry in a very
hilarious way. That's great. Very quiet. I can relate to that. I read Martin Short's bag,
biography. And he's got a lot of really funny Christopher Gaston. So he told, I think he made the first
like spoiler alert joke. I think before spoiler alert was a thing. But he was talking about, he was
like, even some of my friends were critical of my career choices during this period. It's like, I can
still remember sitting at a bar with my friend Chris Gaston. And I told him what I was working on.
This new movie called Captain Ron. And he said, what's it about? And I told him, well, you know,
Kurt Russell and his family, you know, me and my family are on a ship. And we bring on Kurt Russell
who plays Captain Ron and he is kind of a wild card and shakes our family up. And he's in the middle
of saying this Christopher guy goes, whoa, whoa, whoa. I didn't say ruin it for me. Just like,
you know, a funny asshole, which I like. We should also mention Jamie Lee Curtis and true lies.
A scene I masturbated to 8 million times, even though it features no nerdy. Which scene when she dances
with a Schwarzenegger? That was, I mean, that came out in 94. I was 13, 14. I was not able to see our
right of movies. I did not have the internet. That scene was huge for me. Mildly disturbing story
from Walsh. Not really. From the sidelines. I'll tell you what is disturbing is that Arnold sits there
and watches his wife do this elaborate strip tease and doesn't tell her like, hey, it's me, your husband.
I've always found that scene very sick and fucked up to me. There was a, there was a movie called Fall Time
with William Baldwin, I believe. It was a familiar with it, Evan Cena. You know, bank robber,
whatever movie took place in like the 50s or something. But they take a hostage and it's, he's got like
this younger like teenage cohort. Okay. And it's like the kind of good cop bad cop thing with the two
crux and the kids actually being kind of like nice to the hostage. Yeah. She's like this gorgeous blonde
and there's like this scene where she seduces him and they start making out and she gives him a
hand job. And she puts her hand, her hand down his pants and you see her kind of work it. So it
looks pretty real. But anyway, masturbated to that on the spot. So there's no nudity I'm assuming.
No, zero. Just essentially a hand down a pen. And you're telling me,
masturbating to Jamie Lee Curtis looking amazing in a, in a broad panties is disturbing.
Pat, I never said I wasn't a hypocrite. All right. The, no, it's not disturbing. I'm just giving you
shit. But I can tell you some disturbing tales, but I'm not going to. It was such a realistic depiction
of a hand job. Sure. It just, it got me. It probably get me if I saw it right now.
You know, it does kind of work that way when you, I stumbled one night upon hamburger the motion
picture, which was the first nudity I ever saw. And it's a movie about, it's came a lot,
you know, the same time as like ski patrol and that kind of shit. And yeah, I remember.
Hamburger is like, I think Jim Varney who played Ernest is in it maybe. Yeah, it always kind of
upset me that he was in a movie that was sort of brandy. Yeah. And then he wasn't playing Ernest.
But anyway, it was the first nudity I ever saw. And I stumbled upon it at age like 27,
one night on cable. And I was like, just rock hard. And it was scenes that, you know,
it shouldn't have had any effect on me. But I was like, it took me back to a time of innocence.
Yeah, I remember my roommate in New York was one of the roommates I had in New York. We were well
barreling towards 30. Yeah. At the time. And he still was like, he'd be like, oh, there's some good,
I think there's going to be good tit in this movie. I was like, who cares? We have
a porn machine sitting on a desk over there. But you do care. I care. I didn't care.
I just watched the full season of Red Oaks on Amazon Instant, which is a really great show. I think
my friend Rachel's in that show. Who does she play? If it's the show I'm thinking if she plays like
a sort of, I think maybe like a kind of flusy girlfriend to somebody.
Okay. Well, I mean, there's plenty of flusy girlfriends on the show.
I think I think it's that show. I got to watch. Anyway, whatever. It's a great show.
I liked it a lot. But I mean, what compelled me to keep watching aside from really enjoying it,
what made me be like, yeah, watch the fourth in a row was the nudity if I'm being honest. It could
just kind of, it's an extra thing that keeps you hanging on. You know, how much nudity is in it?
Ample. Ample. Is it like sort of like a take on like a caddy shack kind of thing?
It's a complete and I will say homage and not rip off. It is a full homage to those kind of
movies. They even do, which I found very bizarre, a body switching episode between the kid and his
dad. Like it's an 80s homage. Okay. I don't think this is the same show. It probably is though.
It's at a country club in the 80s and yeah, the show I'm thinking I really made a sloppy capuchino
there. She did. I think that's part of the charm of this scene though. She's dancing around being
cute. Is this, we're listening to a Leah? I couldn't tell you. By the way, the theme song of
Halloween H2O is Creed's What's This Life For? Which is a song I believe about giving your life to
Jesus Christ and an insane choice. It plays over the credits and everything. I heard that Creed
guys living in his car. You know what? Good. No, come on. Good. I made it good. Fucking Creed.
I remember like all this shit about Creed and him doing that fucking shirtless Jesus shit in
the video. I mean, the guy's a tool. I don't wish every song is about Jesus. And then what comes out
put a video of him and Kid Rock getting blown by 20 groupies in the back of a bus.
Okay. No, you can't do it both, my friend. Yeah. You can't do it both. Tiger Woods proved you can't.
You can't be on your knees on Sunday and then get them on your knees on Friday night.
Baple. I thought your knees was used for praying. See now I had this giant Halloween box set and
I've been going through it and loving it and watching like these feature length documentaries on
the movies. And I realized I can watch hours of documentary footage on any movie whether I like
it or not. And if it's a failure, all the better. You know, everybody's talking about season of the
which like, yeah, we messed up. Like it's a bad movie. The documentary comes around and it shows
you that people now love it. And it was, I was like, it's own little rocky, the documentary. Yeah,
it was very inspiring about how things can just take 20 years sometimes before they catch on.
So I loved it. And the documentary on H2O I haven't watched yet, but like that's awesome that Jamie
Lee Curtis got it going again. So now they're like, yeah, let's do H2O. Why would they kill off
Michael Myers where they just thinking they killed him in such a way that they cut his head off?
Like was Jamie Lee Curtis, like, I'll do it once and never again and we got to kill him. But then
the movie was a fit. And then they're like backing up the money truck because you know, she made at least
a million dollars to be in the first five minutes of this movie. I think it was probably,
yeah, I think it was, I think it was either that or it was just they said, if we want to keep going
here's how we'll justify it. But I don't think that I think it's probably the former. I don't think
that was the case. Nobody from H2O is involved in this one. Yeah, that's true. Except I mean,
every money's money and it was a big hit. Everything down to the titles. I mean, the titles in this film
look like the like video game titles. Like it's like it's everything. Everything none of this was done
with the value of that looks terrible predecessor. Well, that's supposed to that's supposed to be like
right. When H2O starts like the opening five minutes, it's kind of a stupid scene, nothing seem. But
when it starts with Joseph Gordon Levit and that woman, you know, the loomis's nurse gets out of the
car whenever it's shot so cool. It's great. It's playing Mr. Sandman. The titles look just like the
original titles. Everything's perfect. And then, you know, the very next one, they're like, yeah,
we'll just cash in with some dog shit. It upsets me that Jamie, I mean, look, who am I to judge?
If they said to me, here's a million dollars for a day's work or whatever. Yeah, okay.
But it upsets me that she's in this because I wish she wasn't. So I knew she was like
disapproving of it or something. Well, you know, the woman's doing yogurt that makes her shit
commercials now. But does any genre treat its fans shit here? Then the horror genre, it's
it's especially when you get into sequels and stuff like that. And and you and many other horror
fans reasonably so allow themselves to care. And it's got to be so devastating for people to be like,
you know, the other night, I almost watched tremors five. Oh, that's right. I was like, I tried.
I can't Jamie can't I can't do this. I shut it off because of Kennedy. Yeah, I was going to watch it.
I shut it off because of Kennedy. I can't stand Jamie Kennedy. He almost ruined screen for me. Yeah,
but I so I shut it off. But I tried. I was game. I was going to give it a shot. I like the opening
where the guys like lowering into that pit and falls and I haven't seen it yet. But, you know, the
they actually explain to how the different types of the tremor creatures.
Like how the cycle of life works with them. Okay. Which I thought was pretty cool. It made me
understand why there was a land one, an underground one, a land one, and then a flying one. Yeah.
So I thought that was cool. I mean, it's just there's only so many times you can you can we can watch
them like destroy the mythology of something before it's like, well, is the original still great or
has it been tarnish? And I can usually treat the original as great. But they just announced like
they're going to do a die hard prequel. Yeah. Well, like I can't I don't know what to do about that.
Die hard. I don't know what to do. The last die hard to me was the level was equivalent to this type
of sequel. Die hard. Live for your die hard was fucking awesome. It was it was solid. I loved it.
It was solid. But I felt like they were rebooting the thing. It was it was a true sequel. It felt
like die hard. That's fair. That's fair. That's fair. It was great. I thought it was great. I think
one, two and three are all A movies. They're just I mean, I love the first classic three. You corner
me at a weird time. I can be like, yeah, almost as good as the first. I love I love two is a blast.
I love the first four ran out to see the fifth one when it came out. Couldn't wait. So these guys
haven't steered me wrong yet. It's so clearly. I was so bad. It's like they took it's like they
I personally my theory is is because they did. Remember that movie with Bruce Willis on the boat
striking Dustin? That was supposed to be die hard for. Yeah. And I guess they were like this isn't
a die hard movie. And they just made it into striking distance. Yeah. Well, my theory is with die hard
five. Cool. What they just did there. Yeah, I was scary. No, I just mean like. Yeah, the mask.
It was a twist. Do you guys reservoir dogs? Yes. Nice little mirror. No, it's pulp fiction.
Pulp fiction. Okay, go ahead. Sorry. Die hard five. I was like, this is a script to another movie
and they just changed it to die hard five. This isn't dire. It had known none of the tropes or
elements of die hard. Yeah. And it had nothing. None of it was the same. It was special.
They used to do all the time. Like, you know, like this movie, like it's going to be a dirty
hairy movie. And I'm like, nah, nah, we'll throw it to somebody else. It's not good enough to be a
dirty hair. There were rumors forever that Grand Torino was going to be another dirty hairy movie.
Well, that honestly, that would have been amazing. If it was like the Rocky Balboa of dirty hair.
I would have loved it. And I think we can still get that in before he's would die. And I would
fucking love it. Yeah, I'd buy it. I mean, look, they're they're doing Indiana Jones five. They've
said, no, come on, man. Listen, I mean, I mean, you know, they said they're going to have
forward in it. And they're going to he's he said, he'll pass the torch. Yeah. But it will not be like a
James Bond thing where a new guy will play Indiana Jones. Right. I mean, quick, uh, a grand, quick
grand Torino story. I don't think I ever shared with you. Uh, I was in New York. Uh, and I was visiting
from LA, but I was trying to do a long distance thing. I had a girlfriend in New York. I went
and when she would work, I would go to all these screenings, Academy Awards screenings because I was in
the writer's guild. So you get you get to go to movies for free around Oscar time. Sure. One of them
was Grand Torino. And I was like excited to see it. I think Grand Torino is a pretty ludicrous movie,
but it's very entertaining. It's an absurd film. It is that it find it absurd. Yeah. No question.
It's, it's, it's confusing to when he's saying all the racist stuff, I'm like, it's supposed to be
funny. I can't plan it for laughs. They are right. And at the end, the funniest part of the whole movie
is Eastwood sings a song about a grand Torino over the end credits. And so it's like the movie ends and
I was like, wow, that was crazy. And then you hear this is a green Torino. He sings. It's insane.
Anywho. I'm sitting in New York and they have these tiny screening theaters that make you feel
like a king. And they're like 30 seats, big cushy seats. So I go in and watch the movie. And there's
a, I don't want to tell tales out of school, but I think you can only say he was extremely drunk.
Minimum. Philip Seymour Hoffman. Okay. And he's like, I feel like he probably smelled. He looked
homeless. He was drunk. And I was just like, whoa, this is a big sighting. Who doesn't fucking love
Philip Seymour Hoffman. And you know, when he died, I was like, I thought of that day. And I was like,
yes, guy had some demons, you know, whatever. But he comes in and he stumbling and whatever. And
he laughed so hysterically throughout grand Torino, like the Joker, like De Niro and Kate Fear with a
cigar. Like he was maniacally laughing at grand Torino. And it was so infectious that I had a, like the
whole theater was like dying laughing. And how funny he found this movie. And I wanted to ask him,
like, are you laughing at the racism? Like, do you think this movie is so bad that it's funny?
Are you just drunk? But it was such kind of like a joyous experience. And that's what I always
think of when I think of Philip Seymour. I had an experience with him in New York too, please tell.
So a taxi cab crash into scaffolding, scaffolding collapsed on a taxi cab. Bloody kid got out of the
back completely disoriented because he'd slammed his head. He was bleeding. I actually got his blood
on my coat because I tried to help him. Oh, wow. Sit down. You slept in that dry cleaning bill.
I had to see some sack. Crazy, crazy big crowd forms. It was the craziest accident I've ever seen.
There's smoke everywhere. It was insane. Okay. Crazy crowd forms. My friend and I are just standing there
in disbelief. We can't believe we saw this thing happen. And then through the crowd comes Philip Seymour
Hoffman again looking quite homeless on a 10 speed bike. Okay. Just kind of look it over his shoulder
like what the hell is going on here? Stop for a minute and then keeps going. And my friend Joanne
goes only in New York. Yeah. I thought you were going to say he rescued the kid or something.
He got there way after it happened. So he was just kind of like what the hell is everybody looking at
and then saw like the wreckage. But we saw the actual accident happen. We saw a cab drive
through scaffolding and the scaffolding collapse onto the cab. That's crazy. Now in a movie there before
like building painters up on that scaffolding. It was nuts, dude. Thank God it happened at night.
If people, I mean, I can't believe nobody died. Yeah. Now this is, I mean, is this pairing
could be more unbelievable that this is no way to me. He said big purve and they dubbed that dialogue.
Is this PG 13 or something? No. Sorry. His mouth just moved and somebody dubbed in big purve completely
off. Maybe it was, maybe they just didn't get it and it was just a bad dub job. Well, this movie is
pathetic. What are we looking at? This is, that's the first time this has been said on this podcast.
And we watched leprepon. And we're supposed to believe that chump was bringing that girl into a room
that's what that was what I was focused on was a lot to deal with this kid that looked like a
reject from like the Hogan family. Well, for a minute, I thought it was buzz from home alone. That's
that's what I was going for. I couldn't remember the reference. And then I realized he would have been
like in his early 30s. Buzz from home alone, by the way, well, he was in an episode of Louis
as the guy driving Louis to a gig. And it reminded me of the guy who drove us in in Denver.
Why would it, what was he doing? Well, the guy who drove us was great. Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah,
just me. I, you know, I don't do those. I don't like tour the globe or whatever like you do,
job. But the, the, the, the premise of the Louis episode, I know you were on a Louis episode as well.
Yeah. But the driver is just super chatty. And he has to tell him like, Hey, man, I don't want to talk.
And the guy like starts crying and has a breakdown. But he was awesome in that. And he's amazing in a
movie for you, Netflix, instant users. If you want a recommendation called blue ruin.
And I was watching blue room, which is kind of like a simple plan type joint. You got
buzz from home alone. And I was loving it. And this actor comes in and I was like, man, this guy is like
real. He was, he gives an amazing performance. And about 10 minutes in, I was like, where have I seen him,
where have I seen him? And when I looked him up and made the buzz connection, I about fell off the couch.
Good for buzz, man. Like, I love that. Nothing brings me greater joy than like, okay, your buzz and
home alone by all accounts. By now you should be working at an amaco state. And he's like, you know what?
I'm going to do some indies. I'm going to be on the Louis. And now he's probably, he's like a great
character actor. I love that ship. That's great. That's great. I'm happy for buzz. He's my favorite,
he's my favorite line in home alone. Look what you did. You little jerk. Buzz is awesome. Obviously.
That's the best line. And I loved what Callie Coker hosted SNL and Chris Farley did that
life. Yeah. It was one of the funniest things I've ever seen. Buzz your girlfriend. Wolf.
I'm going to see home alone. They're bringing it back to theaters for one night. One night only.
I mean, I couldn't love them anymore. Speaking of which, it's Halloween week. Very disappointed in
the options for what's screening in LA. There's nothing. Nothing. Nothing that interests me at all.
Nothing. I missed it. We missed the dawn of the dead one. That would have been good.
Downtown and I missed the thing, which I wanted to see at the arc line. I would have seen that.
Yeah, we just fuck the arc light have anything this weekend. That's good. I think they might be doing
like cycle Halloween night, but you never want to go to a movie at midnight on Halloween night.
You're at a party or something. What about tomorrow or Friday? It's conceivable. It's conceivable.
If you haven't figured out, folks, it's the Wednesday before Halloween.
It is. And we're hoping to hopefully this is dropping Saturday Halloween. It will give to the fans.
We talked to Ken. I think it's actually going to drop Friday. That's great. That's great.
So the fans will get it. Here's Buster Rhymes trying to bed Tyra Banks.
God, can you imagine even being in a position where you might have a 1 % chance of having sex with Tyra
Banks in these days. Are you kidding me? I would blow that immediately. I would just be a disaster.
It's a different. It's a different to much. Try to be charming. It's a different. It's a completely
different machine. It's not. I don't mean like the mentality of being able to flirt with somebody
like Tyra Banks. I mean the mentality of people in that position. They just think differently.
Male or female. Yeah. You're just in a status place where your ego, your confident, whatever it is,
it's all just designed very differently. Yeah. Well, it's like a girl walking to a bar,
and especially in LA, a girl walking into a bar or whatever. And like it's almost like a cartoon
where your jaw hits the floor and like your tongue rolls out, like a staircase or whatever.
Like you can't believe what you're seeing, but it would never occur to me to approach that girl.
Put to some guys. It's like, yeah, I'll roll the dice. I mean, I saw a girl tonight on the street
that was so hot and so cold to me as she walked by. She made me ashamed of myself. Now,
if you say something that she was cold, or you just got a cold vibe. I was walking with a dog.
Usually you'll get a smile from a girl when you're walking your dog. They think the dog is cute.
Right. Walking with the dog, walk past her, just gave a nice friendly smile. I mean,
ice. I felt like some sort of, but then again, the form troll that had crawled out from under
the bridge. She might be getting a lot of lecherous shit. You know, that's how she now treats the world.
We don't know. Who knows? You can't take it personal path. That's what they'll tell you in the
four agreements. You've never read it. I bought it and didn't read it. I bought it on your
recommendation. You could read it in the day. Like most things that would probably greatly help my
life. I ignore them. That's what I do. I'm working on a new bit about therapy. About how 90 % of the
reason I ever go to therapy is to work on my problems with intimate relationships. Yeah. Yet,
I've never left therapy where I didn't treat it like a weird breakup where I just slowly fade away.
It's no different than a relationship, exactly. It's every reason that brings me there. That's how I
end the therapy. I had so much tension with my thick, sweet, that I was like, okay, so now therapy is
really no different than like just a relationship that I'm trying to work on. Like I went in and she
starts every, she'll never listen. She starts every one by looking at me and being like, so
what's going on? That's how we start each week. It's like throwing a bucket of ice water
in my face. I can't, and I'm like, and I wind up talking around the issue for 50 minutes and we finally
latch on to something and she's like, that's time. Every single week, because it's that, and I told her,
I was like, you can't start with me anymore with, so what's going on? It's like it's this general
shit and it makes me freak out and I don't like it and she was like, oh, okay, and we got tense,
and we got weird. Then when we leave, usually she's like, have a great week, and this week she goes,
so I guess have whatever kind of week you want to have.
Does this drop this lady? It wasn't as, it wasn't quite as confrontational as I'm making it,
and I told her, I was like, I know why you say what's going on. It's a device, but I felt exactly
like Tony Soprano being like, I know what you're doing here. Quit trying to outsmart me. By the way,
the therapist you see on TV shows where you go in and they go, okay, so last week we were discussing
your father with it. That doesn't exist. I've had therapists my whole life. I've never had a
therapist where it felt like there was any, I've had great therapists, but I've never felt that
level of continuity. Maybe that's what you get when you pay 500 bucks an hour, I don't know, but
see my therapist too much tries to connect things to my father. I'm like, I just mean like the
continuation of the discussion. If you ever had a therapist that picks right up where you left off,
I never had that. I mean, my favorite, this is wildly politically incorrect, and I know you don't
even like the Sopranos. My favorite line in all the Sopranos is she talks to him for like a minute
and like kind of like nails what he's like, she nails him kind of. And he goes, this sounds very gay
to me. And I cackle laughing at that because it's like, it's such a defense mechanism and he's such
like a child. And that's how I am when I get in there. I'm like, I go into therapy, like please help
me. And then I'm like, quit trying to fucking help me. Yeah. Yeah. I know what I'm doing. It's
a terrible pattern of behavior as is most of what I do. My favorite therapy scene ever is in
curbure enthusiasm, even the thong. No, well, that's great too. It might be the same episode, but he's
in therapy and he walks out of therapy at the beginning and Richard Lewis is there and he's like,
how you doing? Urge Rob Reiner. And he's like, how you doing? He's like, I'm good. And he goes,
he goes, how was your session? And he goes, this, it's ridiculous. It's pointless, but you can't
bother your friends with this crap. Yeah. It's like, that's truly what it is. It's just,
it's the room where you go to be like, I hate the world, you know? Yeah. And then they go,
it's okay to hate the world. Yeah. Well, that's what I always say. I go to therapy because
it's somebody listening to me for a full hour without checking their phone. That's the reason I go,
I'll pay the money. I don't care. I'll tell you what I do. I got to work this into my, because I have
some bits on therapy, but I wrap it up half the time. You wrap it up pre -time. Oh, yeah. I'm
staring at the clock. I'm like, you might not be bail out. I'm done. I've said enough, I don't care
anymore. I wrap it up myself. That's, that's got to be something dysfunctional. This is a big kind of
frustrating thing for me. Like, you have an R -rated move. Oh, no, we're saying some boob aren't.
Halloween three, I noticed how carefully they were coming up this girl's nipples. And it was like,
a very tactical move that kind of annoyed me. And then I watched the documentary. And the girl was like,
I had a very strict, no nipple clause in my contract. Like, that stuff's really fascinating to me.
Yeah, I mean, you know, I'd call you a cinephile. I've called you that before. Sure. But I'd say
that's a mark of your cinephelia. Well, something a failure for sure. But now she, this girl's covering
up again. Like, for my money, you have an R -rated movie. Make an R -rated movie. I mean, she's covering
up because we just about to have sex. There's a killer on the loose and they just got what they think
are corpse parts dumped on them. I just can't help her flash back the 10 -year -old me waiting up
all night to see the nude scene in a movie. Oh, God. I would just say that showtime used to do a thing
called after hours on Saturday nights. Do you mean USA up all night? No, no, no, showtime. But showtime
already had nudity, right? Yeah, but they had a thing called pet, you know, there's more details
coming. The story doesn't end at after hours. They had a thing called after hours in Saturday nights
and it was right around the same time SNL was on. Right? And they would show like, you know, soft core
porn, basically. Okay. So they'd show like Lady Chatterley's lover. Whoa, you just blew my mind
there because I have seen Lady Chatterley's lover. Yeah. I watched that many times. Yeah, that was a
staple. Yeah. As were a manual in space. They showed all the manuals. Sure. There was always the
originals, like the ones that were committed to film. Yeah. Something with maybe a John Holmes at times
would pop up. Right. Anyway, it would show at the same time as SNL and I had a TV in my room
that you had that I had showtime on. And I would you were lucky. Put one channel to SNL and the other
to show time and have my finger on the fucking the flip to the last channel button. Sure.
And my dad would come in and I flip it real quick. And my dad would be like, what are you doing?
You better not be watching one of those movies. Yeah. On showtime. And I was like, I'm not. I'm not
Jesus dead. And as soon as you leave, I'd flip it back. But I never masturbated to it. I would just
watch it. I used to masturbate endlessly to scrambled porn, just like an American pie. Completely scrambled
to where you could barely see what was happening. Didn't care. Yeah. Your kids don't know how lucky you
have it. You really don't. I also I don't think I've discussed this on this podcast. But I used to sneak
out R -rated movies from the video store in the Tucker the Man in his dream box. Yeah. Because I was like
nobody's ever going to rent Tucker the Man in his dream. And they never did. So finally like 20 weeks
into doing this because I would switch the barcodes, peel the two barcodes off. And I also wasn't trying
to rent porn. I wanted to see like good fellows and shit. I couldn't see R -rated movies. So I would
switch the two barcodes. And I would put good fellows in the Tucker the Man in his dream case and put
Tucker in the good fellows case and hope nobody rented it and buy his first. Why would you switch the
barcodes? Because they scan it. Like it had to be completely legit. Right. But if they scanned,
the barcode was on the cassette itself. Okay. So I wanted to make sure I covered all my bases. Because
in my mind when you're that age, you're like they're going to call the police if they find out. Yeah.
And naturally, they'd be like, oh, we got the wrong tape in here. Yeah. And they'd put it on
themselves. Yeah. Or just rent you the R -rated movie in that care. Yeah. They probably would not have
cared if I wanted to do that. Right. But finally, one woman goes, boy, you really must love Tucker,
the Man in his dream. I was like a 12 year old kid. And I'm like, I love cars. I can't believe you
keep going back to the Tucker well. Yeah. Well, I said I love cars. It's about the Jeff Bridges and he
invented, of course. So one night, I remember I came home. My dad was sitting next to a bag of
videos from Schnucks, which is the grocery store, Missouri. Sure. And I would rent six at a time on my
bike and then ride home. And he had all six in his bag sitting there and he's waiting for me.
And I was like, God, damn it. And this was during one of the few times where I had tried to rent
some nudity. And I rented like basic instinct, I think. Right. So. And I'm probably 14 years old. And
I had already seen porno at a friend's house. But he's like, I walked in the door and as the door
shuts, he goes, what's next, Patrick? What's next? Am I going to go into your room and find the video
tapes where you actually see the penis going into the vagina? Well, he couldn't have made that
anymore awkward. It couldn't have been worse. I was, and I remember, by the way, that's a verbatim
quote. And I'm a thousand percent sure of that. And that's 20, 25 years old. Because I remember it
very well. When I was like, God, I'm sorry. Now, when he would rent our rated movies,
and I, and I knew that he wouldn't leave the house over the weekend, I would come creeping out
on my room. 4 a .m. Bring the tape downstairs. Once he went to bed at 3 .30 a .m. Bring the tape downstairs
and watch it with my ear to the speaker. I did that for Pulp Fix. That's the first time I saw Pulp
Fixion, one of the greatest movies ever made. I watched it with my ear to the speaker looking up
with my eyeball touching the screen. Because I was so terrified. And I was 14. I saw that in the
theater with my friend and we enjoyed it. I'm happy for him. Good God, Pat. This is like a prison
camp scenario. It was terrible. I remember when I was 19, I was home from college. I had a, I had a
had it in my room in like, you know, soctua or something. My mom goes, I come home one day. I'm
home for the summer and my mom goes, I, I hope I'm not embarrassing you. I was cleaning in your room
today. I found a tape, a red tape, and I obviously know what it is. And I go, mom, stay out of my room,
you know, because I'm mortified. Yeah. She goes, I just have one question to ask you. And I was
like, what? She goes, are you gay? You can tell me. And I was like, it was called anal honey pie.
And I go, no, I'm not gay. I'm just, it's a porn movie. And then I told my best friend that night,
the story, my friend Jim, have you met? Yeah, love Jim. Told him that night, that, that story,
that night. And he goes, and we were, I remember really high. And he goes, you realize what you were
saying to your mother was, I'm not gay, mom, I just love watching chicks take it in the share. Yeah,
which your mom was probably very relieved by the announcement.
My mother, my friend, I'll just say Ben, Ben A, because he might listen. And I want to,
I don't know, I don't want his name out there, but it's one of my best friends. He wrote down
word for word. This pen house forum, he had gotten his hands on a pen house forum. And he copied
word for word, the story for me and this yellow spiral notebook to jerk off to kids. Do you understand
how lucky you have it? I want you to step back. I'm masturbating to something my friend copied
down in a spiral notebook. So he wrote down this erotic story. And my mom did the same shit. I was
cleaning your room. By the way, my mom never cleaned my room. I had to clean my room. She said,
I was cleaning your room and I found this yellow spiral notebook. And Pat, what's going on here? And she
thought that I had written the story and it was an original story that I had written. It was insanely
graphic. She must have thought this kid's got talent. He's a little pervy, but he's got to get it.
It was beautifully written, but I said, mom, a friend of mine at school and I started to say
Ben and then changed the name. I go wrote this down and gave it to him and he was like, check out
the story I wrote. I read a couple of words and I was like, whoa, this is not for me. And you know,
the pages were probably stuck together. And I don't know if she believed me or not, but it was a pretty
good cover on the fly. And then what happened? She was very, very angry and crying and etc. Oh,
boy, you made her cry, huh? And then it's like now, you know, like, you know, I can go out to get
drinks with my mom and she gets wasted and I'll be like, oh, fuck this. Or, you know, like,
it's so sick. And I hope I'm not that way with the children I may or may not have, you know?
I remember, I'll tell you a double whammy. I was in high school, came home, had a tape in the
VCR. I had been renting spice. Remember spice? Did you have that? Well, I know what it is, but I
didn't have it. I didn't know. There was, you know, back when you had pay -per -view, where you had
to go to the league pay for the movie on the TV. Right. On your, through your cable network or what?
Well, I guess you still kind of do that. But it was, it was a different system. There was
its thing called the spice channel. And it was porno. They'd cut out the insertion shots. Yeah.
But it was porno. I think that's what I was watching scrambled. And, uh, yeah. And I would, I would lie
to my mom, because there was enough, there was enough in the price difference. Right. It was close
enough. The, like, the spice movies are like $5 .99 and the regular ones are like $3 .99. So I could
get away with, like, getting a couple of spice movies if I carefully pick the titles of the films, you
know? Yes. So I'd find ones that didn't sound too suspicious and I'd rent them. And then I would
tape it on a videotape. And then I'd masturbate to it later. Okay. And, uh,
this shit hit the fan one day because I was, you know, I did it one day and then I left the house,
came home, got caught. My mom was waiting for me. Had the cable bill fresh out of the mail
with like $35 and spice charges on it. Plus, she found the tape in the VCR.
And knew what I had been doing. That was a bad day. But, like, moms, there's no moms listening to this
probably, but moms, why would you do it? Why? Like, I still deal with these effects to this day
of the, like, shock and horror my parents have with anything to do with sexuality or me being
13 and having some interest in sexuality. It's like that fucks you up for life. Why was more in
trouble, I think, for the money aspect. I mean, my mom was mad about the porn too that I brought it
into her house, whatever. But, like, the money thing, you know, like the perfect way to handle it is,
like, Dean Weast and parenthood. I don't know why I talk exclusively about parenthood on this horror
movie pocket. And Dean Weast. And Weast. But yeah, she finds the bag of porno and she's like,
let's talk about it, you know, blah, blah, blah. Is it like Joaquin Phoenix or something?
Yeah, it is a young Joaquin Phoenix. Young Joaquin. And she's like, well, you know, I knew you must be
interested in sexuality or filmmaking, you know, one or the other. It's a good jump.
So Ken Hanley, because I feel like we need to at least talk about Halloween for one second.
Ken posted, it's a great post on Facebook. I'm liking it now. Fact, the three best Halloween
Ken is the thing is our Fangoria guy. And you should follow him on Twitter. And he knows his
shit, man. He's a he's a horror expert. Fact, the three best Halloween movies in order are Halloween
three, Halloween and Halloween H2O. Halloween four ain't bad. Halloween two is overrated. I agree.
Halloween six is underrated. Halloween five and Halloween resurrection are both mostly garbage,
as we're seeing right now. Rob zombies Halloween two is better than Rob zombies Halloween.
I can't believe he's putting six over five. I think that's ludicrous. Well, I got to watch both
of those. Those are the two I haven't seen. I mean, other than other than being introduced to a
young Paul Rudd in part six. I mean, I don't like I don't see the value in it. Six is also the one
where they it's called the curse of Michael Myers. And they make up this thing where like,
this is some ancient evil Indian spirit thing. It's stupid. Yeah, stupid. It's like it's not, I don't know.
They really go back to those ancient spirits and these things. I own now every Friday the 13th
moving. I've only seen the original and the the recent reboot. And I'm excited to go through them.
They're they're fun. The original in my opinion is one of the worst ones.
Part one is one of the is one of the least exciting is Kevin Bacon in one. Yeah, Kevin Bacon's in it.
He gets a good kill too. Have you seen sleep away camp? I've never seen sleep away camp. That's fantastic.
And even 30 years later, I will not reveal the twist of that movie because it is so incredible.
Is it a comedy beyond incredible for its time? It would be incredible now. I think it was a comedy.
Sleep away camp. You know, it's got a few comedic elements, but it's no different than Friday the 13th.
They just have an amazing twist in it. And they do it in like a crazy way. So if you haven't seen it,
see it. I just saw a speaking of slasher films with Jamie Lee Curtis. I just watched terror train
enjoyed it thoroughly. Never seen it. I did see prom night. Is terror train set on a train?
That would be why it's called terror train. I thought maybe they were running a train on Jamie Lee.
Great, great flick man. Leslie Nielsen. He's in prom night.
Leslie Nielsen? Leslie Nielsen is in prom night, yeah. He is? Yeah. I don't remember. Who's he playing
prom night? I don't know. I don't remember that. Her date. I don't know. Yeah, no,
terror train. I'd highly recommend to any fan of the slasher genre or the genie Curtis catalog.
I just bought because I had never seen it. And it fell off Netflix instant. The blob remake. Have you
seen that? I love the blob remake. I believe I own it on DVD. Yeah, shit. I should have borrowed it.
Yeah, I'm excited to see because I've always heard it's great. It's fun. Kevin Dylan introducing Kevin
Dylan in that film. Yeah, that's right. Yeah. I was Johnny drama. Yeah.
Actually, that's not his first movie. His first movie is Heaven Help Us. Oh, yeah. Which he is
tremendous in. Is Vince going to do the movie? Originally. I got this Johnny bananas caught too
coming out with dice. He's got the best one of the best lines and deliveries ever heard in the movie
is the kitty picks on and Heaven Help Us. This kid Caesar. They get in trouble for a prank. They pull
at school and this fat nerdy kid Caesar goes, I'll never get into Harvard now. I'll be forced to go
to Queens College. And Kevin Dylan goes, you want to fit right in at Queens College. Not bad,
cab. It's a nice zinger from the side. Sure. And he just lands it, man. All right.
He really is a master. Yeah, I like that Kevin Dylan. But the blob remake is very good.
I think it's one of the few remakes of a classic horror film that actually
the story in the original film or the original idea were serviced by the remake.
Like, they were able to do things technically that they just never could have done in the
50s. Right. And it could have been Russell did it, who's like a darebonsled running partner.
They did, I think dream warriors. Love dream warriors. One of my favorite horror movies for sure
is The Mist. Love it. We've talked about it. Yeah, I was so blown away by the ending of it. And
tonight, I think I'm going to go home and watch the black and white version because I have not watched
it yet. And I've heard it's the preferred director's cut. Yeah, the black and white's great.
Speaking of we've been sort of talking famous horror franchises on here, steal the other night at Best Buy.
Steal. Steal. I got a steel giant. Oh, I gotta wait, but what is steel? Not spawn. No, no, I'm saying I got a steel.
Is steel the shack superhero movie? Yes. Okay. All right. Let's move past.
Uh, but that's not what I, yeah, I didn't buy steel. Uh, by the way, this is in Halloween four.
This is like the cool part in Halloween four. She has to climb out onto the roof. And then they
just kind of ripped it off half -ass regurgitated in this one. Anyway, um, what do they do?
They're watching this on a video feed. The Omen all four original trilogy and remake on Blu -ray.
I own it. Seven ninety nine. Whoa. Brand new. I own it, but I think I bought it for like 15.
You can find shit like that. Tinker around Amazon. Like this thing I bought on Amazon is like six bucks.
And it's the blob. Christine. The seventh sign with Demi Moore, which I've never seen.
You see your boobs in that. It's pretty sweet. Pre, uh, job, though, right? I don't remember if it's
pretty job, but I think she got the job for strip days. She's pregnant in it. Okay. But you do
see a double baby. It's still kind of hot. I think so. Yeah. Something like that. I don't remember.
Um, I almost bought a Stephen King one the other night at best. Again, at Best Buy, it was ten bucks.
It was misery, needful things, carry, and the dark half. But I already owned carry and misery.
And I didn't really care to own the dark half. And dark half is terrible. Needful things is
barely okay. Misery is a masterpiece and carries a masterpiece. Yeah. I wanted to get it for
needful things. I thought, well, then I could sell the other DVDs, but I didn't pull the trigger on it.
It's okay. And a lot of times you buy those four packs, eight packs or whatever and the quality is
really terrible. Well, that's, I, I feel like these Ohm and Blu -rays are not going to be like true Blu -ray.
They know that they are great because I watched them. Oh, yeah. Yeah.
799. I mean, what's that's a steal? I got to go into Best Buy. I mean, Best Buy at this point
should just be like bartering with you like you're in India or something. I mean, they should just be
like, yeah, what do you want? Like, you know, like the deals are going under. DVDs are amazing.
All right. I'll head up there. Are they going under like in every department or just with media?
Yeah, I mean, I guess if you want a TV, although I got my TV on Amazon, you know, I think,
I think probably for electronics, they're still doing okay. A washer, dryer, that sort of thing.
Some say Amazon's the devil. I love it. I do support the, the physical stores. I go to Amoeba.
I do two records once every week, maybe every two weeks. I buy DVDs wherever I can. Yeah, but I do
love Amazon as well. I mean, it, it comes in very handy when you can't find the thing. It's great.
And then I, you know, I do feel really bad about it, but they're offering things.
They're almost immediately to your door and they're always so much cheaper. But we are supporting
the destruction of the small business. Well, I'll tell you, you know, for one thing, it's, you know,
I started like painting recently. Yeah. And I got this stuff on Amazon because I was able to get like
a 15 color acrylic paint set for eight bucks. And I was looking in art supply stores and a single
tube was $10. I was like, I can't, it's for some throwaway bullshit hobby I'm going to do,
like just to kind of relax. I'm like, I'm not going to spend $300 on it. Yeah, it's a really sad
thing, you know, like I, I eventually, well, now, I mean, here, it's not an issue, but in Missouri,
I was like, fuck Walmart, you know, like my dad was like, never go to Walmart. They're,
they're disgraceful. They're terrible people, et cetera. So I stopped going, but Walmart was kind
of the in store Amazon of its day. You know, like they just did everything, they get everything there
at the cheapest price. And it's hard not to go. Right. But you are destroying businesses when you
do it. I love a target. I'm not going to lie. Target's great. I love target. I'll do a target for
a lot of my and target if I'm not mistaken doesn't have, it's a little more expensive than Walmart,
but it doesn't have any of the bad rap that Walmart has, right? No target has a very clean rap.
Yeah, they're like the nice Walmart. By the way, this is always a sign of like
a really bad horror movie is when you're in like the final
you know, yeah, the final moments here and Buster Rhymes is doing like a stereotypical
shitty karate high -ah voice. Well, do you know why he did that? Because at the beginning of the movie,
this is all the foreshadowing they gave you that the beginning of the movie he was watching a Kung Fu
movie and in his hotel room and getting excited about it. And then in this final showdown with Michael
Myers, Buster Rhymes, karate kicks Michael Myers and literally goes, hey, hey, and I think it's
supposed to be like kind of funny. I've seen like a meme or some sort of video of Buster Rhymes
kicking off the door and going trick or treat motherfucker. Look, I'm a big Buster Rhymes fan. We haven't
gotten there yet. I'm a big big Buster Rhymes fan. Oh, his music is incredible. I don't approve of
the movie casting of him in this now. I like him in movies. I liked him in higher learning a lot.
I fucking love higher learning. Yeah. And I'll still put on Wuhan got you all in check.
Which, look, when a guy's got you in check, he's got you in check. Yeah, there's something you can do
about it. Higher learning is a very good, but you know what? It's singleton. Where's singleton?
Come back, baby. Yeah. I got today speaking of Academy screeners and that's probably what your
FedEx thing was on your door. I got the Academy Awards screener of Furious Seven. Oh, really?
And you flip it open and it tells what they want to be considered for. Best picture. Best actor,
Vin Diesel. Oh boy. Come on, guys. I like Furious Seven and I'm like, come on, guys. You're not taking
that home. I haven't seen it. I look forward to getting the screener. I was very excited to get the
straight out of Compton screener the other day. Straight out of Compton is amazing. And Furious Seven's
really good. Yeah, I'm looking forward to it. Furious Seven, it was kind of funny. I saw it with
Pete actually, Pete Holmes. We went up to the Vista here and we got up and we like, that was really fun
and he looked around and like, I bet half that crowd. And I'm talking about some bros in that crowd,
some dudes, head tears streaming down their face. They handled the pull walker shit really, really well.
Does he die in the movie? He does. And basically they have him like driving off to
heaven. And they handle it kind of beautifully. And I was like, they handled that really well. But
when I looked around and saw everybody crying, I thought, well, this franchise must mean more to
these people than it does to me, I guess. But look, people love that front. There's a reason there's
seven of them. And they are fun. And I think seven is about the best, really. That's what's so
crazy to me is that they got up to seven and seven is considered amongst fans. It seems to be like
the best one. Yeah. And five is great. You know, there's no real slip off. Like they,
they keep it pretty tight. Tokyo drift is probably the low point. No, that's the one I didn't see.
Nothing to do with. I was just going to let that marinate disliking Asians. I will see Tokyo
drift. Well, I didn't know it had anything to do with the others. And then I was reading
stuff about seven. And they were like, this is the first one to take place after the events of
Tokyo drift. Yeah. I was like, they were, they were, it was, I was like, I didn't know it was that
deep. All right. I went, uh, this year I was on a hiatus for my job. I got like three months off
a year, which is great. And I went up to the movie theater. And they were showing all seven.
It was the day the new one came out. And they were showing all seven in a row. And I was like,
I'm going to do this and write like a funny article about, I used to write articles all the time
for different movie websites and stuff. I'm going to do a funny article. Get it published.
You know, really do this. And as part one starts, I was like, no,
I can't do this. I can't watch seven fast and the furious movies. And I walked right out.
It's like 17 hour day. I'm like, I write a little funny snarky article. And I've given up 14 hours
of my life. That's not one. And that's not 14 hours. That's probably 16 hours. I was going to do
it with Star Wars. I already got my tickets for the Force Awakens. Are they doing all seven?
They're doing all seven. And it's dig this. It's the Force Awakens premieres at 7 p .m. on the
December, the Thursday, December 17th, whatever the hell it is. Right.
So the marathon is only that day and it leads up to that. So the marathon starts at 1 a .m.
with Phantom Menace. And then you're just there all day. And I couldn't get anybody to do it with
me. And I was like, you know what, this is ridiculous. I can't do this. But did you buy tickets for
the new one? I have tickets for just the Force Awakens. Did you get one for me for your boy?
I'm seeing it in Pennsylvania because I'm going to be home for work and then right into Christmas.
I made fun of everyone who bought them. And then I was like, well, wait a minute. I don't want to
wait a week to see it. I should probably buy some. I mean, if I were you, I'd hit that 10 a .m. Friday
screening when everybody else is at work. Is it available? Well, I'll be at work. You're not
you're not on break yet by then. December what? 19th or whatever. Oh, yeah. I'm a break. I'll buy it.
You're right. Yeah, nobody's going to be at that. Go to that. There's going to be screenings
around the clock. You can go in the morning on Friday. Yeah, that sounds. I mean, I am really excited.
I almost went up. They did it at the Sinoramid dome here in L .A. They had all three back to the
futures on that back the future day. And I wanted to go. But then I was like, you hit a certain age and
like, you just start to feel so stupid doing it. You know, well, I used to be like, you know,
I'd watched the whole back of the future trilogy on a Friday night and have the best time and drink
some sodas. And now it's just kind of like you feel like such a waste of life, if you do that.
Also, three is, you know, come on. That's it. That's a half trilogy right there as far as I'm concerned.
What are you saying? I'm saying one is a masterpiece and halfway through two, three quarters of
the way through two, you kind of stop caring because they. Oh, and I disagree because then you
because you know, there's my problem with the second, the second one is the whole time once you
get to the part where they go to the fifties again, you're like, well, they're now they're just going
to the fifties again. Even the makers of the film have said they didn't like that aspect of it because
it was just a retread. And I was like, so now we're just seeing the events of the fifties of the first
movie in a different perspective. And then I think here's Trick or Trick. Oh, bust around just a
trick or treat motherfucker. Look, I just watched two because eight million people were talking about
it this week for the whole, it was the day he went to thing. It is genius that they go back into the
first movie. You've never seen that really. No, but haven't, but it's too soon to do it in the future.
Yeah, I agree. I agree. Have I told you what my lay out for the third would for how it should have
been? I don't think so. This is what it should have been. The entire goddamn second fucking movie
should have been in the future because we waited five years to see that. Yeah, it was so exciting at
the end of the first one when he goes, when you're like, oh my god, they're going to go into the actual
future now. Yeah, the whole movie should have been that by the way, end of the, hold on. Okay, yeah, go
end of that movie should have been them going back to 1985. The camera pulls up as Marty steps
into the town square and realizes Biff has taken over 1985. And it's this dystopian reality or whatever.
Then part three is them trying to rectify 1985, come to terms with all that, then they go back to
the 50s. Yeah, the second half of part three. And then then you're tying it back to the original
and then it ends. And you don't want them to ever go to the old way. Oh, god almighty. No, it's
fucking terrible. That's fourth. I've sent it a million times. That third movie to me felt like when
they would do like the facts of life goes to Europe. Like, you know, I need to watch three again,
because that's the one I've seen by far the least. It's terrible. I watched two this week and I
fucking loved it. One is a masterpiece. No questions. Perfect. But three is kind of a question mark for me.
I need to rewatch it. Three. I love it as a kid. Loved it. Yeah, I just, I just, I hate three. I hate it.
I never set through it in its entirety. I tried a million. I can't wait a minute. You've never finished it?
I know it. I've seen it out of sequence. Like, you know, I know all the parts. I know everything that
happens, but I've never sat through it and viewing it and watched it straight through. I've tried.
Did you really wrap it? Do they really wrap victims of things in blankets like they do in movies?
I don't know. I've never been on a murder scene. Seems to only be when there's a murder that happens.
Well, they do it in die hard. I guess a lot of people do get murdered in die. Yeah, some sort of
traumatic. At any time, there's been an explosion. I just don't see cops having a lot of blankets on hand.
Well, the paramedics do that. That's not the cop. You know, and I think it's stupid. This is the
best part. Buster Rhymes description of Michael Myers here at the end. He actually, here we go. Here he's
Michael Myers on a sound bite. He's not a tie -in. He's not a scandal. He's a killer shark.
In baggy ass overalls. Do you hear that? That's fucking terrible. He's a killer shark
in baggy ass overalls. This was the end. This was the end of the Michael Myers legacy.
This was the wrap they never made a movie after except for Rob Zombie. Yeah. And I hate the
Rob Zombie ones. Holy shit. That was terrible. That's that's the end of it. They're doing part three now.
Rob Zombie? Or they're doing another Halloween. I don't know if it's going to be a, they keep,
they won't say if it's like part three or if it's another reboot, you know, they're fucking rebooting
the leather face again and the rebooting for the 13th again. It's like, why reboot it? Just make
a sequel. I don't know, you know what I mean? Yeah. I don't know. I just, you know, I was watching
because I'm sorry, Joe, but this is a back to the future podcast that we're doing. Not a not a
horror movie podcast. I was watching back in time, which is this new Netflix documentary. I was
that. I haven't watched it yet. It's very solid. There's a lot of great stuff in it. But they,
they seem pretty happy with the trilogy, I would say. Like they don't talk shit about two or
three really. No, they, they seemed happy with it. They seemed happy with it. You know, they
like that the third one is the old west. They were like, we thought it'd be a lot of fun. Yeah.
My problem with the third one is it, the, the focus shifts. It's not the whole point of that movie
about that series to me is, is the salvation of the McFly family. Right. That's the whole point of the
movie. And the third one suddenly is like a sweet, I got to go save Doc. That hell doesn't have to
do with anything. Yeah. Like it's like, it's, it's just a separate story. That should be a short
story in an anthology of fantasy. Yeah, exactly. Yeah, they were saying. Let me see. Back to what
we're just talking about. Back to the future base. You said they see you were watching the documentary
and they seem happy with it. No, I know. They do seem happy with it. I don't remember what I was going
to say. I had something important about the future. Now, see pop up here. There it is. His eyes open
at the very end. He's still alive, which is just stupid. Oh, I know what it was. Yeah. So, did you see
back in the future one in theaters in 1985? I mean, my parents took me and I was traumatized
because I only knew Michael J. Foxx from family ties and that's why they took me to see it. Right.
And I loved him so much and to see him being, to see him swearing was traumatic for me.
Oh, wow. Because I was in like second grade. Now, it upset me very much. But I love the movie.
I love the movie. Yeah, sure. They were basically saying, which kind of blew my mind is that when
it first aired in theaters, and I would have been four, I did not see it in theaters,
that they did not have the to be continued at the end of it.
Really? That was added for the VHS release. No, it said, I saw it in the theater. It said to be continued.
No, it's in the documentary. They they didn't have it in there. And well, if it didn't between
one and two, VHS came to came to light and they put that on because they knew they were going to
make the the sequel. I can tell you this, if that wasn't in there, it was glaringly obvious.
It was in plan that there was going to be a sequel. Well, my parents and I left going, I can't wait
to see the next one. Oh, okay. Well, now, because they didn't have a whole lot of faith in it,
the mechus in the movie. And he's like, oh, yeah, nobody knew. And he's like, we just
thought they were heading off to the next adventure, but we never thought there was going to be a sequel.
Yeah, well, it was five years later. And then they did parts two and three together. Yeah,
like Lord of the Rings. And which I had never heard of at that time. I think that was one of the first
movies to ever do that. There's also, and they go into this in the documentary because I remember
this vividly is that's a mechus talked in like a press kit type thing about how the hoverboards
were real. Yes. And there was like, I think it was on TV, like probably after, you know, probably
after the fucking facts of life or whatever. But as a mechus is saying, hoverboards are real and we just
haven't quite released into the market yet. He's like, fucking with kids, like having a little fun.
Yeah. But they talked about how there's this whole generation of kids who's like, let me see these
hoverboards. Yeah. And they were trying to make them and they had this guy go on in like a half pipe.
And it wasn't as far off the ground, but they were off the ground. They are trying to make them.
Yeah, no, I know. Did you see the sketch on Kimmel where they show up?
I waited the whole night to watch it and then forgot. It was great. Yeah. All right, I'll watch it on
online. Yeah, he's doing his monologue. He's talking about how he's like today's the day that they go
to and back to the future too. And then the time machine shows up in Doc and Marty get out and they do
just a little bit. It's a pretty long bit. And it's actually very funny. And he's great.
It was great. And the whole thing was them being like, you must have hoverboards here. And you know,
when you're people like, no, no, like just that was the gag. We don't have any of that stuff.
All right, that's good. And you know, at one point, Marty's like, Doc, the future sucks. This is terrible.
Yeah. It was funny. Anyway, folks, I'm happy we were able to bring you this special Halloween
edition. I think I think we even talked about leprechaun more than we just talked about Halloween
resurrection. I'm sorry. But some weeks you just don't give a shit about the movie. All right. And
I hope you just like us. Just a couple of men, even though Joe is anti -Semitic and racist and
hates women. I hope you come back for me and my quips. Why are they getting these things?
It's just terrible. And please, I'm not kidding. If you're listening, we heard what our fan total is,
what our listener total is, it's really good. And thank you all so much for listening. You can
told us we're doing really good numbers. Thank you. If you know, if a couple of you go and pop us
off of five stars, we'd be sitting pretty. Yeah, guys, we'd appreciate that. We would appreciate it.
Bringing you the goods. Here on We'll see you in hell. Presentation of the Fangoria podcast network
produced by Thomas DeFeo, executive produced by Ken Hanley of Fangoria Entertainment for press
opportunities, advertising inquiries and information about We'll see you in hell. Contact Ken via his
email Ken at Fangoria .com. Thank you, everybody. Thanks everyone. And what I want to say each week
and haven't I only answered somebody on Twitter about this is that the opening song is written
and performed by one Joe DeRosa. Because people love it. It's very nice, Pat. Thank you very much.
People should know. All right. Happy Halloween. Be safe. Don't eat any candy with razor blades in it.