Welcome to we'll see you in hell it's the podcast you turn to when you want to hear
that sweet sweet movie talk my name is Joe DeRosa my name is Patrick Walsh hello Joe and hello to all
of you I hope you're enjoying 2022 and I hope it's better than the last it won't be but who cares
at this point this is 2016 we've been saying this yeah yeah it's it's a new year doesn't
this is the new year and I don't feel any different who's that you're singing
death cab for cutie oh god it's a great song great album transatlanticism
fuck you it sounded like meal young you were doing yeah sure he sounds a little like
now she's married to one of the property brothers yeah who are they what do they do I guess they
have properties I mean they like an age I can't believe people watch two shows where they go to
from home to home I get right I've never been able to understand cooking shows you can't eat it
what are you watching is it teaches you had a cook certain things I don't think that's why people do it
no they're very comforting but I watch them to learn things a little dress here and there sometimes
you know but but they're enjoyable to what you know it's like you watch if you watch a baseball
game you can't play the game but you know you enjoy seeing the person in their craft I don't like
baseball either so I guess that's where we're at sure um what's new Joe what's happening you know
what I forgot to mention during our night my alley discussion is that a month ago I went to my buddy
Ian's birthday party and they had a fortune teller outside and I went in sat with her and she
flipped the cards over and did the whole thing and my center card was the hanged man and she put it
down and was like oh no which is never what you want to hear from the uh the card reader but then I saw
both versions of nightmare alley a few weeks later and of course the hanged man is the worst card
you can get it means death you know bad very least bad luck and I'm concerned about that frankly because
we sat down and she's like what do you want to know and I was like let's let's flip and see what
my 2022 will look like and uh am I going to die I guess is what I'm asking I don't know if you'll die
but I cancel that job interview with the local carnival you have scheduled yeah boy but by the way
I wish I had a job interview at a local carnival bring in a little coin what would you what would
be your dream carnival job guess some people guess some ladies wait I wouldn't want uh I would never
want to have to run them any of the machines because right god forbid something happened yeah deaths are
on your hands at that point I don't know the energy for barker right I think honestly I've said
some sort of freak that they wheel out people throw things at me and then they wheel me back in I
don't have to do anything mm -hmm I mean that seems like a decent gig you know you go eat some roll
afterwards and it does seem like everybody's fucking in in a carnival setting at least from my
viewings of the jerk with Steve Martin and uh I guess that's about it nightmare alley being the other
carnival there was fucking on that oh carnival was real uh a lot of sex um that dude I just read a
big article about that dude Nick Stahl star of carnival and apparently during that whole period of time
he was blackout drunk every day on set every movie he made and he lost his career and now he's
getting it back but he's like I don't blame people for not wanting to hire me I I was always drunk
he lived on skid row for a while he was falling like heroin addict or something yeah like he
had but he's apparently sober now and and putting I love Nick Stahl I think he's a great actor
he is he's amazing in uh bully which is what used to be my spec material and he's great as a kid in
man without a face starring how they would sweetheart mel Gibson
hmm um I used to really like you know there was originally called man without a race and it was
about a guy angry about the dissolving of the white man I didn't know that I used to um really
like that movie and I think I like the book when I was a kid but it's a movie about a man with a
burn face who everybody thinks is a pedophile but he's not it's basically the Boo Bradley story
beyond that I don't remember what what the plot could have been he'd be friends a young boy and they
go on adventures I know I saw it but I don't remember what happened he's like mean at first because
he's been hurt and then the kid brings the human out of him and okay kid teaches the town that he's
I don't think they think he's a pedophile they think he's like a scary man they definitely they're
definitely I think he's a pedophile maybe that's just in the book but okay um anyway what's what's
happening in uh in New York City is it as bad as it seems in terms of COVID what are you going
to do we had 85 ,000 new cases two days ago how many people live in New York it's the highest bike day ever
yeah I mean look man it's I don't know I mean it's going the way of like look this is this is a very
innovative from what I'm reading this is a very ineffective variant if if you're vexed yeah and
even if you're not vexed it's it's not as strong as the other ones and I think this is probably where
we needed to get right or or a step closer to where we needed to get which is this going from a deadly
flu to a flu that we're going to live with you know yeah in theory I don't I don't know I think
everybody's worn out a lot of places in New York are closed a lot of places are open we're one of
the places that are just choosing to stay open and um what can you do I mean I don't know yeah you know
it's every everybody everywhere is exhausted I will say this I will say this and this bothers me
and then I'll shut up for all the bullshit that the press has talked about Florida
and Florida's approach and this and that and the other me right my friend just came back from Florida
and told me it's the he lives in New York so it's the first place and only place he's ever seen
there's treatment facilities up like where you can get anybody treatments to make your resilient
stronger like why is that not in New York if they care so much you know what really bothers me
this this whole thing has been so politicized and split and I mean whatever you want to call it
I mean the CDC by the I mean you see all the jokes on Twitter but I mean like my god it's like
yeah the whole like cutting the quarantine time and half everybody get back to work this empty
promise of masks being sent to us which I sort of feel like won't happen learning that in October
there was a huge plan to get us all these tests and masks sent to our home that Biden vetoed
yeah it's a it's a dark time and we are we are all but it is a very dark time and I you can also
there is an option and I deal with this every day to just go out you know like when I went was home in
Missouri and Missouri the governor just declared that the COVID emergency is over as Missouri hit its
number one day of cases he's a hit and he you know he could have killed my grandmother basically he sent
every COVID vaccine to like the Ozarks and like the places where nobody wanted them so that anyone
who did want them in St. Louis meaning not his supporters had to drive my grandmother had to drive
like six hours to get her vaccine yeah that's it she's 86 anyway Missouri is a a nightmare in
that regard but I walked into a Walgreens to get to get some Christmas presents on Christmas Eve
morning as I usually do and there were you know for the cousins and shit you toss them a gift card or
whatever but I have 15 cousins they're not all getting a thought out hand made a gift card did
best by something that you would want to use and so I'm not giving them a gift card to Walgreens
Walgreens has a okay okay and I'm I'm getting them what they wanted you know maybe a dick sporting
goods for the sporty cousin you know but there's 15 people walking around Walgreens not one of them
had a mask and I'm including the people behind the counter sure and that was you know five minutes
from my mom's house and I was walking around and you know nobody made me feel stupid for wearing the
mask but it's also kind of like their eyes were saying dude it's okay you start to wonder is it okay
because I keep reading about these cases but again nobody I know has it but I do have you know I got
the gamut I got friends who haven't left their house in two years who when I talk to them on the
phone I'm terrified at like their voice sounds different they're haunted by life you know and then I
got friends like Joe who's the dude doing New Year's Eve parties and no one's getting sex I don't know
what to believe I know a zillion people that have had it and then do have it every one of them said
the same thing how do you feel I don't know you got a cold barely like anything man the worst I heard
was I can't really smell or taste anything yeah I've heard a lot of I have no symptoms whatsoever or
I just took the test because XYZ and it says I'm positive right so fucking shit show man it's a
shit show I've been exposed to it 800 times in the last two weeks you know you can't have a business
and not in some way some way some shape or form get exposed to it right I'm very safe after I get
exposed I do the you know stay home for three days wait you know take tests all that stuff because they're
saying now the incubation period I guess what this one is shorter but I mean if you look around
and you follow the money which I hate to say because I know it's cliche but it's true
so they're they're moving the gall posts here you know the CDC announced the shorter the CDC
announced the no need for PCR testing after the head of Delta in the hub of Atlanta where the CDC
Georgia where the CDC is located requested that they become more lenient on that guideline the NFL
changed its rules when too many players got sick yeah or not sick but tested positive it's
disgraceful if this is all disgraceful it's some people look I've said from the very beginning of this
thing there are two types of people that are going to come out of this people that could handle it and
people that couldn't yeah and unfortunately I don't blame either one by the way you know I don't
fault either one the people who use lives collapse around them it's a sad thing but I mean I get it
I get it I've had pockets of it myself it pulled out but it's hard for the faint hearted we've lost all
ability to have faith in any institution that was supposed to lead it I was talking about this
other I'm like you're stupid if you do you're stupid if you do just you know and I you don't want to
become some guy in a basement screaming into a microphone about who everyone's out to get us but
you I sort of get them too you know like you should be questioning thing you know that there was
that got doctored that just went on Rogan that said I think America is suffering from a mass psychosis
yeah that everybody started trashing him like this guy just but just got the all right on his side it's
like no I know a lot of liberal people that think that's happening now this is insane what's going on
everybody's never been so delusion disillusioned and it's because I miss my opinion
we went from the loudest blowhard masturbatory president of all time who we didn't think was
great at leading us to the most absentee feeble enabled president of all time who none of us think
adequate leading us no and then you look at the governors of each state how many governors and
how many states have gone batshit I mean I can I can speak for New York our guy went down a lot of
guys and a lot of states have gone down and it's like we have no leaders we have the CDC that's supposed
to be leading us medically and Fauci they're contradicting themselves and changing things you know and
not to beat a dead horse but Fauci admitted to lying to all of us he admitted to it so it's
you see Andy Cohen going off on build a blasio on the New Year's Eve thing I heard it was wild
it's the only New Year's Eve coverage I saw but I never had an opinion one way or the other
in Andy Cohen but this man is he's black browned out or blacked out screaming about build a blasio
and I was like do I love Andy Cohen like this is awesome and there needs to be more of it
I was trying to tell my dad about how I think Joe Biden sucks and he got so tense and is looking at me
like he wanted to hit me in the face and I'm like well what are you what are you happy about that
I'm just happy we don't have Donald Trump in the and great I'm glad my dad's not a trumpet and so
we have that divide between us on top everything else but it's like no better than Trump is not
going to cut it when when this is going on in the world my dad's whole thing is well you know it's
good to have a good Catholic man back I'm like this 1963 you know like Dave Smith had a joke about
the the fall of you know we're witnessing the fall of an empire and he was like you know Rome when
Rome felt it was terrifying but hey I got to see a guy fight a line and that was pretty cool and you
know it's true it's and I think the Andy Cohen thing funny enough speaks to that yeah because
I said to my friend the other night I go dude I have no allegiance to CNN right I have no
belief in in in corporate media I have no faith in any of it yeah but I also think it's shameful
that this is the best we can do now like look it look it this is newscasting now
a guy shit faced on New Year's Eve screaming about Bill de Blasio to the point that his
producers or whoever have to try to step in and be like hey dude you got to
reel it in a little bit man this is where we're at you know yeah and it's and it's what I always
said about Trump versus somebody like Obama so I don't give a shit if you love or hate Obama's politics
I don't give a shit if you love or hate Trump's politics I have no dog in either fight what I give a
shit about is is one guy has class and decorum and acts like a president and the other guy doesn't
and I say shame on you Mr. Obama when he wore that tan suit just smiling up there like he wasn't
wearing a tan suit made me so mad it's a wild time and you know we we avoid politics lately as
much as we can but sometimes it's like we got to talk about what's going on I know you don't turn
to us for this no no no in fact yeah in fact I'll close it out with this I'm gonna go to bed after
this again basically at 3 pm I'm not gonna go to sleep for the night yeah I'm gonna go to my bed
and sleep in it for a little while again even though I slept for 10 hours last I mean I don't know
if I'm coming or going anymore yeah and on the days where the bars not open and I don't
have shows or anything I'm just like I get how many drinks you have in at that bar each time you go in
some days none but some days you know I'll turn it up on some days you know but you know it's fun time
let me take you down to the movie corner you're let's talk about something more more fun more
positive we're talking by the way today about the fourth film in the matrix quadrilogy if you're not
counting the animatrix and all that other shit which I have not seen but we're talking about matrix
resurrections which I think we'll have a lot to talk about I'm gonna start with a screener sent to my
home the tender bar which as the credits roll I went oh bar tender oh I didn't get that neither
didn't get it but yeah basically it's about a kid a young boy and then he we follow him through
high late high school early college age played by Ty Sheridan he lives as a boy with his mom
played by Lily Raib who I thought was a little hammy and they basically have to move back in with
her father his grandfather played by Christopher Lloyd I love that Christopher Lloyd is having a
renaissance and I loved him and nobody with Odin Kirk I also found him hammy and weird and often
this I found his performance strange and I like the kid actor I like Ty Sheridan I like the people
at the bar the tender bar it's basically a story about how the bar becomes this kid's family they're
they're tender the bar flies there you got Max Casela who was on the sopranos and who played
you know doogie houses best friend the little Italian kid who's looked the same for 40 years
the movie is completely stolen by Ben Affleck who man when you get a part that's in his wheelhouse
which weirdly even the last duel was even though it seemed like it wouldn't be he's just good at
playing scummy guys you know he's really good at it and I think tender bar could get him a supporting
nomination he's really funny in it he's great in it the issue lies at Clooney's feet George Clooney
is a very bad director I just gotta say he's bad I've seen now so many of his I mean we're talking
midnight sky that movie I almost forget watching it it was so boring
uh i'd zv march monument suburban terrible film leatherheads terrible film I like confessions of a
dangerous mind I like good night and good luck but beyond that I got I don't know I just don't think
you can put together a movie there's scenes that this is such an easy movie it's like after all these
big action pictures and everything that he's done he's just doing a small character study and still
I feel like the cameras never in the right place and he's just it's not it's not a skill that he has
I don't know why he keeps going back to it but the tender bar does have a lot of charm it's uh
I watched it with my dad and maybe that's why it reminded me of green book because that's the movie
watched two years ago when I saw him but it's one of those good to watch with your family movies
that seems like it could have come out in 2003 you know there's uh the the diversity in it is
it's it's what you wouldn't have had in 2003 basically he falls in love with a black girl and then
goes home to her family and her mom's like an incredible bitch which is an odd choice so it's
it brings in the interracial romance at a time when that surely would have been addressed but they
don't really address it they make her parents really mean which I found strange um and that's where
it fell apart from me I don't know if that was in the original book or what happened it's another movie
about a kid who wants to be a writer he wants to write memoirs etc etc um there's big chunks of it
that just don't work but there's big chunks of it that do I think the the key is the relationship
between the little boy and Ben Affleck who's great and the other stuff is pretty hit and miss
but it's worth a watch and I think one you could watch with your parents and be pretty comfortable with
all right very good I watched
sorry scratching my nose I watched um in just like that finally yeah you all caught up
almost I think I have one more episode before I'm caught up they're they're doing a lot of episodes
it's like 12 or something and if they're only the only release like six um I avoided this for a long time
as a sex in the city fan of the original show you know I like most people thought the show got a
little cartoonish in the later seasons but still was good uh I thought the movies were terrible
the first one could be redeemable the second one is unforgivably bad uh and then when I
started to hear all the stories about what they did with this one and that Samantha wasn't gonna be
on it and all that stuff I um didn't really feel any urge to watch it but finally last night I was
like you know what let me just I gotta see it and as cringey as it is in places and as bad as it is
in places it did reel me in it did put a smile on my face seeing three of them together again
at the beginning when the little music from the original show played I do think they're doing
a good job I after I watched some episodes I saw the point of them killing Carrie's husband
I was and when she said I'm selling the apartment and she went back to her original apartment I was
like oh now I get it they're making like her Carrie again and they're gonna be it now it's
gonna be about like the the dating struggles of a woman in her 50s that okay that works for me I'm
into it uh I got excited when she went back to her apartment it was like solo going back to the
Falcon I was like oh cool man it's the old apartment um so Carrie's storyline I like they managed to
make the funeral death stuff funny and in the way that they make things funny on that show traditionally
I enjoyed a lot of it I and I do like some of the new uh characters I do think they bring some
interesting things to the table and I understand the push for you know there's been a lot of talk
about the diversity push in this in this new version I get it you can't make a show about modern women
and not address the the gender issue and and and the non -binary discussion and all these I get it you
have to include all that and for the most part they do it pretty organically what I didn't like
was the fact that as the show goes it seems to become more and more a show about diversity itself
yeah and nobody more than it is about sex I'll say that yeah nobody's there for that like we're not
really what you sort of exploring sexual issues with Miranda and her husband how they don't sleep
together anymore Miranda seems like she's going to become bisexual soon I haven't gotten far enough
to know if that's happening yet um Carrie is obviously adjusting to being a widow but then the whole
Charlotte storyline is like her and her husband trying to have more black friends yeah because
they only have white friends which is the cringiest most douchebag hollywood thing I can imagine is
affirmative actioning your friends um out of white guilt and I get that it's supposed to be a
commentary on that but they don't do a good job with the commentary they make it they play it for
laughs and I find that it comes off frankly offensive yes I still did a similar thing where they
realized they didn't know any black people when George had to you know go get that guy who you know
like the one that got time like an electrician was a Jerry's apartment but they they made it so
funny that it didn't feel so egregious and it was 25 years ago this this does feel weird and also
you know and I'll leave it as vague as I care to but one of the creative forces behind the show is
is a notorious racist so I know that going in I happen to work with the person for a long time
so it all feels a little uneasy and a little like just not in not in the comfort zone of
the creative team and not in the comfort zone of the show itself everything just winds up feeling
kind of uneasy and it's just like you're saying if you want to tackle this stuff great but I did
not expect that to be the show carry is now doing a podcast where they talk about woke issues
with Bobby Lee and then Che the stand up character Che does stand up later on that you will see
with no jokes in it well that bothered me too is that they I like the character of Che
but it bothers me that they have her saying things to carry that if a man said them would be
fireable offenses yeah like she's in an elevator with carry you need to step your pussy up it's like
what what is this I'm sorry what is this like you know he's ever told you that in the workplace Joe
and carry is literally saying I don't feel comfortable right and you're supposed to laugh
because you're like well this person's done binary so it's just funny yeah you know I had heard
thing when at her stand -up show when she goes I've had sex with men the crowd booze it's like yeah
what what what what are we doing here guys what do we do right so carry carry being uneasy talking about
sex doesn't make any sense you know like the I know time has passed but the characters don't quite seem
like themselves Charlotte I almost forgot that was her story her story is kind of doesn't even come
together until her son or her daughter says that she's once we referred to as a boy going forward
and I guess that's kind of her story but it it's hard to kind of latch into anything because they
bring that big juicy sub plot up and then it's kind of abandoned and then we're only halfway through
the season who knows but it's just hard for me to sink my teeth in anything really but then they do
then there's there's great moments like where they know these issues very well like the Mario
Cantons thing about the girl wanting to be a boy now when he's like who cares she's a kid
ignore it and she's like I don't want to ignore it it's my daughter I love her like I wanted to
and he's like you will wait and see like what happens if she wants to be a boy great if not you move on
like I was like this is some of the most sharp honest commentary I've seen on this yet where it's
like it's not condemning it it's not overly celebrating it's just saying dude it is what it is
can everybody just take a fucking breath kids are kids we'll see where this goes let's see
I thought that was actually very refreshing to see on the show yeah especially coming from that
character um you know but I'm curious to see where it goes it's very sad that Willie Garson is
in real life died it's very disappointing to hear the Chris note stuff that's come out
oh yeah would bother me about the show's response to it was guys if this is as well you can't say
it was would I mean you got you got people now saying they saw them doing stuff in the workplace
that that that he was drinking under the table on SUV and beer under the table whatever it's like guys
it's sounding to me like this was either very prevalent and you turned a blind eye to it or you it's not
prevalent and you just immediately threw under the bus the second something came out it bothers me
with with this in with when there's no in between or gray area it's like so okay so everybody that's
worked with him in his previous jobs we added the bar he owned in this place in that place and
the worry hung up and as you view all this stuff they're all saying they saw this behavior you tell me
on sex in the city nobody saw this for eight years nobody saw this nobody saw anything so I you
know I don't know that's a little odd to me that's a little odd to me that's not possible but I mean
even when I lived in New York I heard tales about North and watch out for him and you know I completely
believe everything being said here when you get people coming forward and saying I saw him drink a beer
once I think that kind of hurts the cause because if if that's people first expect what a Chris
note though okay Google he smelled her neck though he was drinking a beer under the day and then he
leaned in it was like smelling her neck or something there was like a thing that went along with it that
was bad but yeah but I just I just mean when you come forward with a story like that it's like
you maybe and I hate to even say this but like let the women who have had these horrific experiences speak
you don't you don't also have to come forward and join the discussion if a guy you saw a guy drink a
beer and he sniffed your neck again this is always a controversial issue that there are degrees
of bad behavior but there are degrees of bad behavior I've seen way worse way worse on sets
than a guy drinking a beer and sniffing a woman's neck doesn't mean it's right to do and I would
certainly say something to somebody who did it I always would I'm just saying it diminish there
there are there are rape allegations here that I firmly believe there were really graphic and unpleasant
stories so I don't know that we also need to come forward with I saw him drinking a beer but it's not
my place to say I'm just saying I think without that big note scandal and the peloton thing and him
dying in the first episode I don't know that we'd even be talking about and just like that I think it
would have kind of disappeared from the public conversation they're saying the note allegations are
what halted season two talks oh really I see it was presented as a limited series so but I mean I don't
you know and then on top of it it's like by the way the peloton thing when peloton made that statement
about like our bikes are safe I was like this is absurd why are they doing this then I watch the show
and I'm like they're saying every five minutes a peloton killed him right they keep saying it why would
they do that why would they not think that the product the sponsor would have a problem with that
I couldn't believe they didn't have to sign off on it you know at any time I've used a real product
on a show you have to get the people to say it's okay even if you're just saying like I took a
Tylenol so I don't know how that happened I hope good no I just and then you know Ryan Reynolds zooming in
to to save peloton probably making a million dollars in the process good to shoot an ad that will never
be seen again I mean that's hilarious they probably paid notes and Reynolds minimum 250 ,000
a piece to do that ad and then the next day these at least things come out it's like oh my god yeah
I mean it's just it's it's a shame that all that it is what it is but that's what it is um yeah
and and I I think the note allegations sound very valid which is why I say it's hard for me to believe
nobody ever noticed anything or you just didn't and then I don't know there's something strange
about that I doesn't add up to me but anyway I think I do believe what I'm hearing and and
you know it's sad I was he was one of my favorite characters on the show and you know it's sadder for
the women obviously but um the you know I don't know what the future of the show holds at this point
it's all obviously been very tainted I mean I can't imagine him him having the allegations what if
anything to do with season two talks because he's not in the show well they're saying that he was
spotted all over New York shooting uh and that clearly like they have not used all of his footage so
there's like some potential flashback plans or something interesting okay but I also wonder too did
you kill the character off because you knew this was coming mm -hmm this doesn't drop overnight and
nobody has an idea people know that these stories are gonna break about them yeah so that that makes
me wonder it it is it is very strange an eerie that you kill off this character in this thing and
then immediately in real life his career is killed it's a strange metaphoric circumstance um
well the woman said you know seeing him in the news again upset them and triggered them whatever
and I get that but Chris knows been a part of television now for 30 plus years so I don't know I don't
but um I believe the women and I've always heard talk about know for 25 years that's what I'm saying
I I feel like his death in the show was backwards engineered because they knew that this is coming
I really do um and then so then also to the uh what I hope happens is with all this unfortunate stuff
happening around the show and in the lives of the characters on the show they somehow convince
uh what's her name uh control Kim Kim control to come back in season two
is like a return of Samantha and we really get back to business here like I mean I get the feeling
she's out for good I think she really hates those women and and Michael patch king but I I do think
the fact that they're keeping her alive via texts and via her sending a gift to the funeral and
so forth they must at least be intending to bring her back but the show does miss a lot of I mean
it's the sex of sex in the city once she's gone it feels like three older women who don't have sex
I mean that's what it feels like to me now watching one of them doesn't Miranda doesn't have sex yeah
she says it um fuck you Chris knows uh I think the show is bad and a mess but I've watched five episodes
and keep watching it so um I'd like to recommend a much better show called yellow jackets which
my wife and I started last night I kept hearing good things which you know that's with every new show
it that's got its fan base and people talk about on Twitter and you're like all right maybe I'll
check that out but you know you won't something about this and the way people were talking about it
just sounded right up my alley a the two like most juicy scene stealing parks are julie at Lewis
and Christina Ricci two just two actresses I've loved since they were young kids practically
and to see them back like you know I looked up Ricci like oh whatever happened to her I wonder
she raised a family and that's why she dropped that now she's been acting you know like
her last kind of big movie was uh Bucky Larson with uh what's his face who's that guy
Nick Schwarzen and uh so she's been acting just in like small projects and like when you see her here
with a role she's playing a very annoying psychotic character in this and she's very very good
but the plot of the show is basically this Melanie Linsky who was a great actress who you have
definitely seen in things if even if you don't know her name uh Melanie Linsky julie at Lewis
Christina Ricci they are the adult versions of these girls called the yellow jackets they were a
girl soccer team about 15 16 years old maybe a little older than that they are traveling to a
soccer tournament via private plane and it crashes and you I'm three in me and my wife we we're
gonna watch one last night we watched three and we're up super late we're probably gonna watch the
rest of the season today it's that good but they're cutting back between what happened on this island
they were lost for 19 months trapped on this place and there's definitely strong hints that cannibalism
took place very Lord of the Flies type scenarios where some of the girls eventually emerged as leaders
there's definitely talk of horrific terrible things that happened that somebody in the present is
trying to expose and that the women as adults are trying to shut down but the show is really funny
it's uh it never goes into that Diablo Cody thing of every lines of joke and you get kind of exhausted
it's uh it's a Heather's kind of tone Heather's kind of vibe the girls are all dark and funny
but uh it stays away from like just big broad comedy and sticks with the horror and it's great
it to me it's a similar tone as like a castle rock especially that misery season there's
you know so many major characters and you have them as young girls and adults but it's always clear
what you're watching and I strongly recommend it I was very surprised to learn that it's a horror show
on top of everything else and as that it's a better horror show than almost anything I've seen in
recent years check her out yellow jackets on showtime you get a free 30 day trial you enter a code
check it out oh all right uh on the topic of relationships I watched a documentary called divorce
corp okay which solidified but I will never get married mm -hmm it's all about the big business of
divorce lawyers how they milk you how they get your money how simple personality sort of solidify
that you'll never get married it hinted at it certainly pointed me in that direction yeah this thing
man I was just like you got to be kidding me with the it's just about the business of divorce
and how it works and how they get extraordinarily a large amounts of money out of you
and how they turn amicable people against one another yeah in a divorce uh by planting and saying
things you have lawyers coming on camera going like oh I could I could make this guy look like a like
the worst father on earth in two minutes all I have to say is this this this this this none of that is
necessarily that true but it's factual enough that I could use it again it's it's very very frightening
yeah it was very very frightening and I was just like you know what if I fall in love great
uh I will love that person perhaps live with that person but there's no need to ever bring the
contract into it in my opinion fair enough I mean look at Kurt and Goldie you know that's true
look at Kurt but they go but then look at you and Heather and you say maybe I can't have it all
yeah six days a week and then the seventh you're like god damn it that I mean I don't think anybody who's
married would would argue with that all right fair enough things arise don't get me wrong um
but yeah you you can you can have a good marriage don't you know you know if you find the right person
great if not you know my dad said to me over Christmas he was staring at the window and he goes you know
Patrick there's nothing wrong with being alone and I was like cool well anyway my wife gets in
tonight at midnight you know like he just doesn't think that's his advice to a married man there's nothing
wrong he's talking about himself he means yeah you missed the beginning of the conversation but
all right all right well um look I'm gonna do we're not gonna do spider -man no way home are we Joe
I don't know yet hold off on it we'll hold off all right probably not but I was gonna
that that run time is really scaring the shit out of me everything's that long um all right I'll do
another Marvel then which you know seemed seemed like a sitcom at a brisk 132 minutes which for a
Marvel movie it might as well be a short film but I watched Shang Chi and the legend of the 10 rings
which is on Disney plus in I I max they're claiming on Disney plus they're showing the movie in
I max that I mean sure the Disney plus is lying to us what are you talking about the I max is the
big screen the big sound the bit oh I think I talked about something other thing too it makes
me so upset but Shang Chi is a good Marvel movie I'm realizing I like the standalone I like the ones
where they're not involving 50 characters and I'm like wait a minute what the fuck happened in black
widow that I'm supposed to remember now a movie that I slept through 90 minutes of you know like
that's a solar one though yeah all right good point there's too many to to really you know there's
always something you can say but what about this I like Doc Strange although I hated hated Dr. Strange
in in the new spider -man I thought he was not I don't know not my Doc Strange and I hate that they're
reshooting like 90 % of Sam Raimi's version of Dr. Strange but Shang Chi is really solid I like
you know Simu Liu fine I that I never really thought one thing or the other about Aquafina I liked
the movie the farewell but I think she's funny in this charming I like their chemistry I like
Tony Lueng of course from all of Wong Car Wise movies he's a great actor as the villain or as his
father slash villain and most of all I love the visuals I look you know they they keep it pretty
grounded they go to this kind of magical enchanted world and there's magical enchanted animals
in the background but they keep them in the background I just I like the vibe of it I like that it
was very colorful and not falling into this current trap of every movie looking like chrome or whatever
you know or like a penny and it's a look I don't like Marvel movies I didn't love this one but I'm
saying Shang Chi goes closer to the Dr. Strange end of things than it does to the let's say Wonder Woman
2 end of things I thought at least it was a story that I could follow and I liked the characters and
they devoted a little bit of time to you learning about these characters in their lives before you're
thrust into two hours of you know giant unkillable robots throwing clouds and lightning bolt at each
other I thought it was a little better than average in terms of Marvel Shang Chi
all right so my last one is a half movie corner half scary stuff I got finally I got my hands on the
copy of Dune 4K the arrow re -release of the Lynch movie yes I was intrigued I wanted to see
what this looked like in 4k I wanted to watch the Lynch one again I wanted to watch the special
features everything about this package excited me I re -watched it with devoured it almost I was
glued to the screen I swear I'm not saying this to be divisive or anything like that I think
it's awesome I just think it's an awesome it's so fun to look at it's so fun to watch the characters
are crazy it's just a fun movie made about a book I don't give a rat's ass about don't care about
the goddamn book no care about Dune legacy and I don't think David Lynch cares about the book yeah by
I don't care about any of that what I care about is this is a story that kept my attention because
it was so whacked out and the characters were so insane Harlan Ellison gives a great
interview in one of the special features where he says every character is so well rounded and
and distinct and interesting the aesthetic of the movie is awesome it does have some hints of the
Jordorowski's Dune seemingly in there or it's at least way closer to that than this new one is
it looks it's right from that sweet spot of the 80s where the effects in 4k look so cool and crazy
and the colors just pop and I just think it's I just had a blast watching it one of the producers says
in the in the special features I think it's time that Dune deserves a revisit from critics and the
audience like so it can you know I think it has a chance of becoming one of these it was panned but it's
got a cult following things I agree I can't believe that hasn't happened yet but I just I loved it man
I had a blast if you can get this thing for affordable price I I suggest you get it I think you can
get it on Amazon right now for like 30 bucks which isn't a great price but it usually sells it
like 40 or 50 or something so yeah I got the big special edition on Hamilton book of all places which
we have talked about before so my my my guess is they made way too many copies of it thinking that
this new Dune would bring more people to the old Lynch version maybe that didn't happen but
there's all these people who see this Dune first and go back to the other one you know it's like
the the current generation of film nerds makes me sick I hate them and you know them raving about
the the reason they like Dune and all these Marvel movies they think that's what movies are it's all
they've seen you know they grew up on this stuff that's their foundational movies so they go back and
see something weird or something with an actual kind of directorial vision like Lynch at Lynch has
and they think it's stupid and corny and whatever else I think either movie is perfect I think both
movies contain long sequences of boredom but I prefer the Lynch version just because he made more
interesting and dynamic visual and character choices he doesn't have everybody speaking a monotone he
doesn't have every scene look like it's covered in sand oh the colors and this thing pop the
barren is significantly better right the barren scene where he like sucks that kids blood is
about as disturbing as it gets for one of these kind of movies it was it's a fun movie it's got some
linchy elements and it's some of the dialogue is very linchy yeah the character design certainly feel
linchy and you can get the 4k you HD arrow release on target right now for 3349
then there's a two disc one also that I did not get mine only had one disc the jersey of two yeah
yeah I only get the one disc what's on that second disc I haven't really looked at it but it's a bunch
just I mean linchates the movie so it's not a lot of him but it's it's I watched a pretty good
documentary on it you know and they got all those many documentaries the sets of dune the colors
of dune the music of dune you know kind of the stuff that you think looks cool when you pay the extra
$10 for it but then you might have not watching it usually yeah the inner the the bonus disc has
nothing of interest to me on it except for an interview with Paul Smith who's the actor that played
Pluto in the pop -up movie okay who's also in this I would that would have been interesting but anyway
our movie today the matrix resurrections yeah in leading up to this I bought for $16 the matrix
4 movie collection on amazon blue rays of matrix matrix to be loaded matrix resurrection or
revolutions and animatrix I thought for 16 bucks it's worth it for the first one alone you can't
beat that maybe I'll enjoy the other two on reviewing and hey this new one looks amazing so I'm
gonna be real happy I bought this watch the new one on christmas day with my dad
within four minutes I didn't know what was happening I didn't understand what was going on
yeah I desperately tried throughout the movie to to keep my attention and the right from friends I've
talked to a an encyclopedic knowledge of the world of the matrix doesn't help much you know
did you understand it no no I watched it twice I oh god I um
you know we saw it here and I just found my mind just wandering and getting distracted and I was
like I'm not gonna be able to talk about this comfortably unless I at least have it on the background
for a second viewing and no I feel just as lost I can't I can't really talk about it from a plot
standpoint for that reason but um at least when it starts I thought it was kind of cool the meta
version the meta version of it was an interesting take it's not a fresh one per se but they're literally
talking about how Warner brothers wanted to do this with the new matrix and it's like that that
wink wink thing because you're gonna use plays a video game designer yeah yeah who's designing it based
on his remembrances of the matrix and his time in the matrix and well but that's not clear yeah
when you when you meet Keanu Reeves you know that the matrix exists because the cold open is the them
in them is some people in the matrix and you see Trinity yeah then it shows Keanu in real life and you
realize he's the creator of a video game trilogy that was called the matrix trilogy then his boss says
Warner the Warner Brothers thing our parent company wants us to do something you thought you'd never
do make a fourth major which there are so many of those awful winked to camera lines in this movie
like yeah it it it it it it it put that home alone thing to shame dude this this this this was yeah
it's not one joke it's a lot of it so they do that over and over but then and it's true they were
gonna make the movie without the wachowskies um they said look we're doing it one way or the other
and then finally Lana wachowskies said all right i'll do it uh and they the at least for an hour a half
hour of the movie they're making a lot of these kind of jokes like well they were gonna make it one
way or the other kind of thing and um at a certain point with a movie like this that with with
life or death stakes and things are supposed to be taken seriously you know that's very different from
home alone where you do that look to camera wink or whatever it it makes it impossible to give a
shit it's already a movie where you don't know if something's really happening or not and then
they're also making quips about it and you're like do you guys care you know that's what i thought it
was was do you guys who made this movie give a shit because i know i don't it's a terrible
so so then all of a sudden kiano starts to realize that his therapist is who's played by Neil
Patrick Harris who's one of the only redeeming parts of the movie um i never liked him he's good
in that eight bit christmas too right some he's kind of growing on me if he plays smaller parts i don't need
him in a lead but yeah he's giving kiano of course blue pills that's his medicine that keeps him from
being suicidal or something um kiano is stop taking the pills so he can free his mind so he can
develop this new game he starts having flashes of people from the matrix and then you don't know if
it's flashbacks from his game that he created or flashbacks of him being neo from before
which eventually is confirmed that it was because he was neo and he was resurrected for some reason
here's why this sucks and why it's so stupid and so fucking confusing and so dumb they establish in
the original trilogy that this is the fourth or seventh or sixth whatever rendition of the matrix
and that it reboots and then there'd be the new neo comes when they could have just done that
and it all would have made perfect fucking sense instead just like in rise of skywalker they could have
just said what they said in the comic books the emperor created Darth Vader and created lie and then
you would have been like oh okay that's how he's related to ray or whatever but they they ignored
completely and now you got this god damn thing where you're trying to make head or ass out of like wait what
they resurrected him so the so the computer program that hates him that he threatened to undo
resurrected him why would they do that and if they resurrected him and they resurrected trinity
why didn't they just resurrect Laurence fishburn why is there a new morpheus played by a younger guy
why is agent smith played by a new guy who's much younger i'll tell you why because as usual the wikowski's
or the wikowski in this case can't help but where their intention and their message on their sleeve
so transparently that it comes at the expense of the movie which is we are gonna take an older woman
make her the hero because traditionally in hollywood they toss aside the older woman which is
fucked up and i agree that they shouldn't do that and what are we gonna do with all the older men
in the movie except the one who's still gorgeous kiano we're gonna replace them with younger hotter men
because that's a statement and it's stupid it doesn't make sense with the story it's lazy
the new the new can't fly but now trinity can fly it was never just one it was always about the both
of you none of this adds up to anything it doesn't make any fucking sense no if you're if you're
looking at the entirety of this franchise that there's no connective tissue they the original as a
standalone movie even though it's tricky it does make sense and you feel like they thought about every
possible aspect of it the other two sequels have a couple great action sequences but they feel
like kind of like a mess like they didn't know what they're doing like maybe they were a little bit rushed
this new one has no good action sequences and the story doesn't make sense so like you know whatever
you think about let's say the second matrix it's got one of the sweetest car chases in movie history
this new one there's barely any fighting that goes on there the moments where they have them kind of
where you see them in kind of matrix time they're kind of freeze frame or whatever
it almost is like they clicked a button on the side of like the my first video camera that you get
when you're like 13 for Christmas like really cheap looking effects from a franchise that everyone
knows and cares about because of its action and effects they might have been they might have had
their minds open to a lot of cool stuff especially in that first matrix but they were there for the
awesome action and the fighting and the effects and to just abandon all that is nuts and to see
people raving about this movie again is like guys you have to go out and take a breath of air or
something I don't know if people are just excited to have a big budget movie into their home it's
almost like the early days of television where like everything that airs is cool but these movies that
people are giving a pass to I don't understand that this is a disaster the fact that they call
the effect that the wakowski's invented bullet time the effect that they call it bullet time in the
fucking movie yeah oh my god well the executives are like we need our new bullet time which I'm sure
they heard from Warner Bros you know I'm sure that she's taking personal pot shots at the Warner
Bros executives that that doesn't make for an entertaining movie for anyone you getting out your
personal petty grievances amongst them and also they were right if they come to you and say we'd like
a new matrix what's the new bullet time that means they're willing to pay a lot of money
for you to come up with some amazing new visuals and you didn't do it now the fight teams are boring
there are no stakes it's completely stupid that if every time you get in trouble you can just
dodge bullets and clap your hands and create a sonic boom why do you ever have a problem I don't
understand well that's my issue with the marvel shit too but yeah at the end of the movie they you find
out Neil Patrick Harris is a program in charge of the matrix and he's the bad guy they go and confront
him Trinity kills him three times in a row as like a joke and he just becomes alive again yeah and he's
like oh would you do that for it she's like that's because you gave me children and made me think
manipulated my motherly instincts or whatever the fucking is and you're like who cares yeah he you can't
kill him yeah and I don't understand you're just gonna now live in this place with it like it doesn't
make any fucking sense and then through the entire movie they're showing clips of the matrix
on every reflective circus these people walk into that it turns into it's like it's like it's like
so you want to show me Lawrence Dishburn while there's new Morpheus talks to me who they dress like
some kind of circus Barker by the way it's absurd looking and he can't come out of the matrix for some
reason but yeah the the new guy I'm gonna look him up but it's the guy I just I don't get it you know
I don't I don't get why he's here they do I mean they cut to a lot of footage of the original they
cut to fishburn and then he's like he basically says you know I'm just kind of doing my impression of
him or whatever and it's like what is the truth I heard Hugo weaving had a scheduling conflict but
they never even called fishburn correct fish person never even heard from them which I thought was
a red herring because he was gonna like show up at the end and it was like the the Andrew Garfield
and spider man thing like just keep saying you're not in it just keep saying you're not in it right it's
like no he's not in it yeah and it's not because and then I thought oh I get it they're gonna eventually
bring him back in it and it's like no there no this is the new Morpheus and Morpheus is dead they
show you a statue of orange fishburn and say Morpheus is dead and by the way
ruin the character of Morpheus by saying that he had hubris and was too arrogant to listen to
anybody and then he wallowed in being elected the leader of whatever and who delivers this dialogue
of course the female counterpart to Morpheus I mean and guys this is not me being sexy I swear to
you it's me just saying for Christ sakes guys don't ruin an awesome movie character just because
you want to have a strong female character make a point she can make a point and still be strong
without you destroying Morpheus's character and his legacy it's stupid and then by the way then
they undercut her and I'm like who the hell am I supposed to be listening to here right the whole god
man us etc to me made no no response and I think putting him immediately when sorry when you see him
putting him right up against Lawrence fishburn's iconic performance in the role it does him no
favors either you're like oh I just wish Morpheus was here I wish Lawrence fishburn was here yeah the
new Smith sucks that guy sucks that's the guy from mine hunters and you know on that show the second
the second we saw him had there was like oh it's your favorite person I used to hate that guy
on mine hunters I thought he really kind of it's it was such a great show and he just wasn't bringing the
necessary juice to it and that's what I felt here too like again they're showing you the guy going
so they have him go mr. Anderson and he has to scream it and it's like no the appeal of the other guy
was that he was unflapable and you're supposed to be playing the same character I know and then he
keeps saying like how Jonathan he is yeah and that's a whole thing it's just terrible it's just a
terrible terrible movie you know they undercut Keanu's character they're they undercut everybody
just to make it that Trinity was the real savior all along and that's not what the fucking matrix was
yeah and this concept of you know Neil Patrick Harris being like I realized if I resurrected you both
and kept you in a close enough proximity it's what the fuck are you talking about yeah you're worried
that these two characters will get too close and undo your doing and your universe so you wouldn't
resurrect them and then keep them in a it just doesn't make any sucks the movie sucks my hog is so
down on this movie I'm I mean and and and once again my point is proven the wakowski's made two good
movies found and the matrix not that's correct and now I'm mad that I bought that blu -ray set for 16
dollars and I'm looking here at letter box and I only follow people that I respect you know critics
friends whatever this thing I'm looking at four stars four and a half five stars five stars four
and a half I just don't get it I saw the interview with Reeves and he's like when Lana called me you know
she explained what she want her vision for this movie and I was up and I was dancing around my house
and I was so excited and I'm like what did she say I mean the only things she might have said was like
we're gonna make fun of Warner Brothers for wanting more matrix or something like that's a little joke
between you millionaires that doesn't translate to entertainment for us and I love Keanu I get
why he did it you know obviously they probably got paid him twenty -five million dollars but it winds up
they think they're playing this prank on the suits and making this like edgy like you know we
really pulled one over on the movie but you wound up just making a piece of shit that nobody likes
yeah and I hope I hope you had fun sticking it to the man but we actually had to watch this shit
I didn't realize how much I hated until I started talking about it I mean Jesus is there
going to be more are we doing two more I doubt it I mean just just dumping this on HBO Max they knew
they watched this and we're like and they're probably pissed I mean oh oh you're actually calling
us by name calling Warner Bros idiots okay well then we'll bury your fucking movie it didn't do
well at the theater I don't know and it didn't deserve to you know that that's the whole thing I
keep seeing that at Nightmare Ali and this and other movies too it's like art versus superheroes and
it's like these movies aren't art Nightmare Ali and the Matrix they each cost a hundred million plus
and they suck cock they're not art they're equally bad as the Superman movies they're Spider -Man
movies they cost the same amount I know we poke fun it it shudder and stuff but it's like forgot
six at least it's coming from the heart Jesus Christ that's true you know I hate creep show so much
but you can tell the people that did it love creep show and and they're trying their best they're just
not good at it the Wachowski seemed to set out to make a movie that pisses off their fan base and the
people who paid them a hundred million dollars to make it so good job guys two hogs down matrix we'll
see you next month folks with god I don't know maybe spider -man I don't know we'll figure it out
maybe maybe Boba Fett maybe uh maybe uh but I'll just coming out I'm not sure I mean January is
always a big dumping ground but it winds up being a pretty good dumping ground for horror they move the
black phone which I think looks pretty cool but they move that to summer that looks cool yeah I don't
know they're probably some new Annabelle movie or something coming out oh yeah yeah all right folks
we'll see you next time and we'll see and how