I'll see you in hell.
Welcome to We'll See You In Hell, the podcast covering all your favorite genre films and
films of all genres for that matter. My name is Joe DeRosa. My name is Patrick Walsh, and on
today's show we'll be discussing the Evil Dead, the Evil Dead 2, Dead by Dawn and the Evil Dead
remake. For those of you new to the show, which is probably not many of you, if you want to complete
our Evil Dead discussion, we did an episode on Army of Darkness two or three years ago,
which I forgot that we had done by the way. I've shown you how many of these we've done. Yeah,
I forgot that we did that. I will mention, I will give one or two brief thoughts on it today
because I also want to touch a little bit on the Ash vs Evil Dead series now that it's finished.
Sure. But yeah, so basically the Evil Dead franchise today, but if you want a more in -depth
discussion on the third installment, you're going to have to go to that other episode.
Correct. I'd like to just jump in with what I just read while peeing.
Two cancel, so I texted Joe the other day, Castle Rock, cancelled by Hulu.
It's like, okay, the first season was a bit of a mess. Let's be real. This second season improved
everything. Get a great lead performance by Lizzie Kaplan. I know who's pushing her for best actress
did not get the knob. So then they cancel it. It's like, even when a show is proving itself and getting
better and fixing problems, it's like, nah, fuck you. And then I just read the outsider. Yeah.
They wrote a whole show Bible mapped out exactly what season two would be. Put the focus on the
a revo character, the black woman who was kind of the standout of the first season.
And HBO goes, no. HBO just passed on a season two of the outside.
Reading that, because I read about the outside of this morning,
reading that I was just like, Jesus Christ, man, like you,
it doesn't matter who you are in this business. Like it says in Jason Bateman or not,
Stephen King or not. Man, if they're they're not feeling it, they're not feeling it, dude.
Well, I mean, I know, oh, I was just going to say sadly, this has kind of become routine
with these outlets. If you look at the sort of pattern that's forming at Netflix and HBO and a lot
of these other places that are doing this type of original content, it's kind of like, we give you
to there's critical acclaim, we pull the plug. I mean, like, I kind of don't get why the shows
themselves are not adapting to that. And I'm doing more finite storylines,
which I thought the outsider did. I don't really know where else it was going to go after that,
but whatever. Or why is HBO not or Hulu or whoever not approaching the shows more realistically?
And saying, guys, chances are we might have to pull the plug after two seasons. So make sure you
close things up. Right. Yeah, it makes no sense. And you wind up with everybody getting frustrated.
And nobody wants to start your new show until they're confident that it's going to be around for a while.
And the TV business is just bud fucking themselves left and right. They really are just so stupid.
But you know, I'm reading here, it's it's steadily built on HBO, grew from 1 .2 million
viewers for the premiere to 2 .2 for the finale. Networks most watched first year series in the past
three years did well in international territories. And then they pull it. I mean, what more do they
want? I don't understand. Like, now it's possible they pitched a season two that sucked. It veered from
the book, but the book was far from perfect. The book is excruciatingly dull for about half of its
running time. So get your season two that sucks. And then say your pitch sucks. We want to bring somebody
else in. Sure. Yeah, absolutely. I mean, I don't get why you I don't know. It doesn't make any sense to
me. Also too, if they handled this a little more strategically, the PR surrounding these shows
could be now we wanted to do too. And now we're done. Instead of it failed. Right. You know, well,
sometimes they'll get ahead of it and say like, Hey, this will be your last season. And everybody
knows going in, but it's it's very rare. I mean, Netflix has had three shows go the distance like
orange is a new black and the crown and stranger things. And I get that it's more expensive and you
got to pay actors more every year, but like it's not the best business model. Just keep yanking the
cord. And they think they're going to have this never ending supply of great quality shows. They're not,
you know, like if you have something nurture it. And by the way, going the distance isn't always the
move anyway. I think strangers things should have stopped already. Like absolutely. I don't want to see
these. We talked about it on the live show. I don't want to see these kids like at 20. Yeah,
riding their bikes around, fighting the same monster for the 80th time. Like I don't want to see
that. I've started seeing the kids in other things, then stranger things. And they look old. It's
going to be very strange. Yeah. Or stranger stranger. I feel a sneeze coming up. Go talk. I'd like to jump
right into our brand new segment that I pitched to Pat the other night and he seemed to be on board.
It's called mean old bitch or mob for short or mob folks. This segment is only going to be
comprised of us reading excerpts from Rex Reed's movie reviews on Rotten Tomatoes.
You can I didn't know you could do this the other night. You can click on the the critic themselves
and they just give you a list of all their blurbs that they've used on the website.
So I clicked on Rex Reed's the other night and I went down this thing and my god almighty man,
I was laughing my fucking ass off. What does he even write for anymore? The observer. Okay. He hates
almost everything he sees. My favorite was this back -to -back review.
Honey boy, 94 % approval rating on Rotten Tomatoes. Rex Reed, one out of four stars.
Rotten. I don't know about you but this is not what I go to the movies for. Color it despicable.
Followed by his review of Primal starring Nicholas Cage, 38 % approval rating on Rotten Tomatoes.
He gives it three out of four stars. I'm embarrassed to admit it but I screamed out loud five times.
Screamed out loud. He's lost his mind. If you're screaming at a direct to DVD,
Nicholas Cage horror vehicle, you've lost your mind. My favorite. Okay go ahead.
What I found fascinating is that he never gives anything four out of four. All the reviews are
bad pretty much except for Primal and then he gave a very good review to something called
fantastic fun guy. So clearly he's like Arm on white. Arm on white, I used to love reading in I
believe he was in the voice, the village voice when I was in New York but he was just a critic who
lives to piss people off and do the opposite of what everyone is saying is good and bad and that
seems like what Rex Reed has become. Although I don't even know what the observer is so he's maybe
he's kind of edged his way out of the business. His fantastic fun guy review was on the heels of his
Jojo Rabbit review which was two out of four stars which I didn't like Jojo Rabbit either but I do
think it's funny that he's smashing these acclaimed movies and then yeah. My favorite review of all of
them that I've seen so far and there will there will be more hustlers 87 % fresh on Rotten Tomatoes.
Rex Reed two out of four stars. JLo is the only reason to see it. I don't think that sentence has
ever been uttered by a human being. Yeah well it's like she's the best part of it like you have to
you are a critic but at some point you have to say something nice about things or not I'm reading through
this like man even I'm not this miserable about movies. He goes one that I really enjoyed here was
the goldfinch. His review is chaos reigns. The goldfinch. Once upon a time in Hollywood kind of a
universally agreed great movie two out of four stars. Frankly I find the entire experience baffling
and any attempt to laugh off the man's and murders as sitcom fodder embarrassing.
A film called Corporate Animals which I didn't see no which was not well reviewed overall 25 %
on Rotten Tomatoes. He gave it zero out of four stars. This one is just vicious. It's good to have
Demi Moore making a comeback after a prolonged absence from the screen but not in a load of
unmitigated crap called Corporate Animals. I mean I don't think Mean Old Bitch is going to be a weekly
segment but I didn't know actually we were going to be doing it but I'll try to find some good ones
from the archives and we'll probably do I think it could be a weekly segment. I think it could be a whole
show on its own. We found the first the first spinoff was the movie corner solos. I think the
second spinoff of this show is this. This was sort of auditioning the pilot sort of the family
dog in amazing stories. But Rex Reed he's a Mean Old Bitch. Now Joe I wanted to tell you
about my Amazon sales which have been thriving. Okay except now this week I received two
returns and you never get that but one guy's like I really want to return it. We talked
that was which is we're stuck together. I made no mention of that. There's a new Blu -ray and he comes
back and he's like sorry man I'm a collector and like I only need the Region A version and I don't
I don't really think it's cool that you were selling an item that was you know for foreign DVD players
and didn't mention that and I'm like no it is Region A. The Blu -ray you have is Region A. I'm
looking at it right now. I swear it is and then he's like yeah but could you just return it please
after we went back and forth like three four times he's like I just don't want it. Can you just return it
and so I'm like yeah fine which means he's got to mail it back to me and I got to give him the money
back and blah blah he's opened it it was new so now I can't get as much money for it. So I'm not
giving you some shit review that'll go unchecked and then that hurt you yeah I hear you. So I
agreed to the guy you know he leveled with me he was we were communicating well then the next day I
get one from this girl I had just put the thing in the mailbox like 24 hours after I get the order
and she was like I want to refund so she hasn't even received it I just put it in the mail so I'm
like hey what why do you need a refund for this it's exactly what you want it it's new and it's
wrapped and she writes back I because it was a vinyl record she goes I changed my mind and I want
a DVD now so what do you mean you you bought a vinyl record what do you mean and she's like yeah I bought
it and then I I decided I'd rather use my money to buy a DVD what are you handicapped it's like
what what are you talking like that's not how purchases work so I'm sitting and I'm getting kind of
pissed at her and then she stops writing me back so I go through I'm sorry I said handicapped but
I guess I said the right thing but I go I don't know well no you'll get shit either way that's yeah
it just felt like a person who was not not all there I guess is what I'm saying so I'm like okay
you want a DVD but you bought this and I'm like well you're gonna have to repackage it mail it back
to me pay for the packaging don't open it or you're gonna owe me money for that then I look online
and not only has Amazon made it so sellers cannot communicate with Amazon they're like you're a seller
you handle it you're like a store now that's their policy they don't get involved unless the buyer
wants to bitch about you in which case they immediately give them their money back and punish you the
seller so I'm like all right terrible policy Amazon and they go basically you are always required 100
percent of the time to give a full refund if the thing is open if the thing is you know no matter
what they do you're required to give a full refund and yet we still use this Amazon it's still a
better option than going up to fucking amoeba and getting one dollar for something this is why I don't
I won't buy from independent sellers on Amazon if I buy anything on Amazon it has to say distributed
by Amazon through prime because if I do have any problem yeah those corporate monsters will just be
like just keep it it's fine here's your money but you know whatever but like I don't like to get
involved in the whole you know but now I'm telling you if you buy from a normal seller you can
just return it at will but then I also don't want to do that to a normal so I'll do that on eBay
because that's the only option but on eBay there's a lot more it's it's based around that so there's
there's some sort of balance is you know balance and checks thing happening but checks and balances
thing happening but yeah no that's a bummer man that's a bummer that really sucks Amazon and eBay now
they both take about half the sale money and they you kind of make it up by getting the the money for
shipping it but they'll just they'll fucking honest man Joe they'll always fucking honest man
I love to fucking honest man I know that let's I mean I say let's just move into it because usually on
these yeah we're covering a lot of ground sort of franchise episodes we we need to go I so as you
said we're doing evil dead which the reason we're doing it is not just because these are classic
horror films for the most part but also Bruce Campbell and Sam Raimi have announced evil dead rise
what which is the latest installment it is not gone into production yet but it will take place in a
high rise building they they said they want to get it out of the cabin and into some place else
with the concept being that this you know this necronomic on book makes its way around it's not just
Bruce Campbell's problem you know Ash will not be in it Bruce Campbell is
publicly retired from the role he said but who knows you know Harrison Ford said that about Han Solo
well you know who knows and also the main character from the remake which I view more as way more
as a sequel but whatever she also Mia well she will not be in it either probably I'm assuming because
now she's like kind of famous and she's the main she's on that playlist show she's a star of it
so they're gonna have a playlist of always yeah yeah so they're gonna have a they're gonna have a new
character taking on the deadites but it seemed like a good time to revisit some classic stuff on
the show which we have done a little directing no no okay the guy that directed hold in the ground
is directing it so it's not even the director of the last one so I was excited and then with each
new thing you told me I got less excited I'm not crazy about the high rise concept because the
last time I can remember seeing a horror movie that took place in a high rise it was Poltergeist 3
and I did not like it a lot of matter action in Poltergeist 3 yeah and it's just I don't find a
high rise to be very scary no I hated the movie high rise that came out a couple years back yeah
I didn't see that but yeah so I don't know man like we'll see what happens I trust Rami I trust Campbell
but you know like they've made great stuff and terrible stuff like anybody else so so we'll see what
happens either way I'm happy to hear that the evil dead franchise is continuing on more is never less
to me I'm just like if I don't like it I just won't watch that part of it you know what I mean right
yeah it's out there hopefully it's cool but last night to get ready for this I re I've seen it a
million times and I own it but I rewatched evil dead one because I hadn't seen it in a long time the
original and every time I rewatch it I sort of forget and then remember that it's just a masterpiece
of low budget horror cinema it's just Rami just hitting a thousand out of the gate with this thing man
what yeah so well directed so well executed so well done I had seen I was not a big horror kid at all
but I was always renting movies out of this book entertainment weekly 100 greatest movies in each
genre and they were raving about evil dead too and it was at my video store evil dead too
I can vividly remember being one of the early swaps with Tucker the man in his dream that I snuck out
of the yearberg's video store and I remember my buddy and buddy and me were going to watch it
and we had to watch it with all our rated movies after my parents went to bed so for my dad that was
two three in the morning and then on the lowest volume with our ears like pressed to the speaker
but evil dead too I remember I was terrified to watch it because I I was like it's so extreme and it's
it was unrated and it was one of those if it wasn't a video nasty it was definitely always in the list
you know they had this list of video nasties which were like band it's a little late I think it's
a little late for that but um so I saw evil dead too first I saw that one first as well yeah it
really evil dead too is in many ways just a remake of one with a little more money to it
I think if I had seen evil dead one first I'd probably have a whole different viewpoint on the
series but basically evil dead too that night I wasn't really scared by it we just had an absolute
blast it reminded me of raising Arizona which I had recently discovered because the colon brothers
basically used the style of evil dead and evil dead too in raising Arizona with the camera flying up
ladders and sailing into people's mouths and shit like that but um I it maybe there were stuff done
like this before but not to my knowledge I mean it seemed like he was doing show with the camera
that you'd just never seen before it's a super influential movie both as horror and just as like how
to keep a movie relentlessly fun and exciting right when I went back and saw one I was like okay like
respect respect to the roots you know I respect to uh how this franchise came to be but I wish I had
seen them in the right order because to to me towers over one but one is I would say more scary
less fun definitely less funny and what I didn't like this time around about it is that Bruce Campbell
is just a guy he's not really ash in one he doesn't have the quips he doesn't have the swagger the
attitude he's just a guy but it works as you said as low budget horror you can't do much better it
works beautifully no it's the effects while on the lower end look amazing the practical effects some
of them have almost a peewee's playhouse kind of play do vibe that's really fun some of them I don't
even know how they pulled them off because they'll have shots and evil did one where like a body is
decomposing through like stop motion animation right and then another part of the body is bubbling out
fluid in real time and I'm just like how the fuck do you even do that like that's not a composite shot
they like they they figured out how to make that effect work yeah it's clearly a guy using his
resources it's clearly a guy that had access to a car and a cabin in the woods and new people that
could do this type of animation these types of effects these are my friends who are also actors who
could also double as producers some of them or whatever it is and he laid the groundwork really for
the genre of a cabin in the woods I mean cabin in the woods obviously is is a huge nod to this
and this you know what later became cliche of the like haunted cabin in the middle of nowhere
I really think if it if it wasn't born with evil dead one it's certainly you know it's it's
certainly what set it into motion in the way that Romero redefined zombies I love it and especially
when you compare it to low budget horror at that time which a lot of it was you know it was in these
are great films but it was Texas chainsaw massacre it was hills have eyes it was that sort of stuff it
was stuff that was based a little bit more into gravity a group of people being stuck somewhere while
a psychopath is going to do horrible horrible things to them right because that's a much cheaper route
to go than then monsters and demons and supernatural so for Raimi to pull this off his budget was
$750 ,000 which at that time is not a small chunk of change but to do this kind of movie it was
and still it still is it he really pulls it off in spades and I love that in the end nobody wins
the last shot of the movie is Campbell walking out into the sunset or the sunrise and
thinking he beat it and then the the you know the demonic force from the book flying through the door
at him and and hitting him you know and killing him basically is the insinuation yeah
and also it's a heavy flick man like like that like when she gets raped by the tree branches that's
intense man it's very intense I mean both of them particularly to the blu -ray has a two -hour
with Campbell with everybody two -hour documentary about the making of Evil Dead 2 and it's like
I wonder if people who love that movie so much know that that's out there like if you I think
if you knew that that was going to be a premiere like a two -hour Evil Dead 2 documentary people
would be so pumped and then they forget that these things are on DVDs all the time it's another reason
the physical media is so great is that you've got these interviews with people you get
your commentaries and so forth I hope that all doesn't go away but it probably will well
but yeah it's an amazing documentary on on two especially the the first one you know they didn't they
weren't on set as much filming behind the scenes because obviously they're trying to get the movie done
the second one was a little more advanced but I think Remy's Remy's approach to this famously has always
been he was a big three -stoogeist fan so it was like what if we made a horror movie that was like
the three -stoogeist basically and you do see some of that in Evil Dead 1 it's not comedic but there
are moments where you laugh because it's so crazy sure like it's so extreme like when he's beating his
girlfriend who's possessed repeatedly in the face with a two -by -four trying to get her to snap out of it
there are moments that were a managed driven to such lengths it is funny but
it is not purposefully fully comedic which which we'll get back to when we talk about the remake
and I'll wait till we get to the remake to address that but
Evil Dead 2 is actually a fun piece of trivia
I you know being everybody else and you and everybody that's seen it as always said you know it's
basically just a remake of one with a bigger budget but why why did they do that it's not like
Evil Dead 1 isn't a movie that existed Evil Dead 1 was brought to attention by Stephen King
and that's how they got the funding to do the second one which Sam Raimi didn't want to do he
didn't want to do a sequel he wanted to keep moving in new directions but after he made another
movie or two I'm I'm blanking on what those movies were he revisits right away with the
Colin Brothers which is not accurate yeah and crimeway I think was a critical and commercial failure
so yeah so Kings starts championing Evil Dead 1 the studio goes you can make a sequel to Evil Dead
he's hesitant but he doesn't anyway Mike just message us Raimi's so Ted Raimi's car is the car
they're using and that car has been in all of his movies apparently anyway I was at a festival I was
at Michael Moore's film festival in Michigan last year or a year and a half ago whatever it was
and there were two guys there that I befriended over drinks who had made a horror movie
and we were talking about horror movies and stuff and their dad was there and their dad had I guess
was a producer on their movie they were brothers their dad was a producer on their movie and the dad
was an effects guy on Evil Dead and I said you got to answer me this question man like I can't
find the answer to it anywhere on the internet why is Evil Dead 2 just a remake of Evil Dead 1
and he got he told me he said because Evil Dead 2 was supposed to be army of darkness
right they wanted to jump right into army of darkness and they couldn't because the studio was like
not enough people saw Evil Dead 1 you have to set up Evil you have to reset all that and then if
it works and it's successful enough will green light army of darkness is the third movie so that's
what they did yeah it looks like it was even called originally Evil Dead 2 Evil Dead and the army
of darkness yeah and Universal Past they went ahead and did crime wave which Universal preferred and
then obviously that was a huge mistake then they were able to go back and do it so so that's so
that's where that's where this this more elaborate version came from Evil Dead 2 clearly incorporates
far more of the comedic sensibility that you know Raimi was was a fan of and it really works
which it usually doesn't for me but it really works in this movie because it's not trying to be funny
it just somehow pulls off the comedy throughout radiusness and just saying well like you know what if
somebody's eyeball did splatter on you or flew across the how would you react you know what I mean
and capping like a real reaction of somebody you know what I mean or what if your hand did get possessed
and it was hitting you in the face and trying to kill you what would that look like and it's like it
would look absurd yeah and that's what's that's what's so great about this yeah I mean the in this
documentary they talk about watching Bruce Campbell film that scene in the kitchen where he's basically
being attacked and keeps kind of almost doing back flips and jumping around and like they said it was
some of the best physical act and they've ever seen Campbell gets no self into a summer salt in the air
it's crazy Campbell does not get anywhere near enough credit I have no idea how the man did not become
a big star it makes no sense especially like once he got jacked for army of darkness I guess if
that movie had been a hit he might have caught on but it's like I'm sure he kicks himself too but he
had a great career a fun career it's just kind of like he's good looking and super funny and can do
the physical and the action and just never was in that discussion for some reason and a great actor
great actor he's he is so good in it particularly to the hardest that I laughed and I didn't for
some reason didn't even remember this I remember he cut his hand off and put the chainsaw on but when
he is cutting his hand off and he's got blood splashing lovers face screaming who's laughing now at his
hand while he cuts it off he's going who's laughing now as it cuts his own hand off right I was
much like Rex Reed I was scream laughing in my in my living room it was so crazy and funny but yeah it's
like a guy saying groovy you know before he goes to fight a witch is not necessarily like grounded
believable character humor or something and it's not what we've seen from ash either so it's crazy
that it all works as well as it does but I feel like the groovy is almost like the birth of the ash
that we get carried over into the show an army of darkness right well it's a big moment in the
in the movie where he kind of like now I'm going to be an ass kicker there's there's there's true
character there's character development in the first one because he does go from a guy stuck in
a situation to being the the warrior that he needs to be but in the second movie you truly see
the transition you see a character be born like all this you know icon of hog it's born
right in front of you evil dead too to me is rainy at the top of his game he's made great stuff since
he's made okay stuff since he's made some bad stuff since but that movie to me it's it's just
un you can't in my opinion you can't criticize it he is at the top of his game because not only
are is the creative direction there not only is the comedy and wildness there the horror is there
the grandmother in the basement who when she's possessed is played by Ted Remy and Ted Remy reprise
the role on the TV show which was awesome um but that it's so fucking scary man that old lady which
like trying to like break out of the and she's going dead by dawn dead by dawn it's so god damn
scary man and one of the greatest moments I've ever seen in a horror movie I get chills just talking
is Campbell in the basement listening to the tape and the husband goes god help me I buried her in the
fruit cellar and you realize he's stuck down there and you're like oh shit yeah and she bursts out
of the earth and floor whatever it's just so awesome man it's just so so awesome it is it uh you know
it's I remember when I first rented raising Arizona I rewound it rewound it to date myself and just
watch it again and I rarely if ever do that and people that too was the same way it's even now
when I watched it for the 10th time as a grown man it ended and I was kind of like I just want to watch
it again it's like a ride you know it's like when you finish uh you know the ninja six flags or
something and you're just like let's go again there's no lion you know I want to keep having this
experience because it's that fun and that exciting and uh it just makes all other movies but especially
horror movies look lazy and feel tired because like it's just the camera is constantly flying around
and moving but it also doesn't seem show offy it's it's it's it's quite an accomplishment it feels like
you're almost like the camera is almost like another spirit in the room or something like it's always
whipping around and flying around the yeah and the makeup effects are incredible the makeup
effects of the deadites are up to me up there with Freddie Krueger yeah or or Michael Myers from a
from a horrific arc design standpoint I mean it's just so well done uh they don't need
nicotaro and all the makeup people and like the the people who did the the effects
is this you know big rag tag team of guys with long hair and ponytails look like they smell
really bad and they're so funny and have so many great stories but you can just tell like
all of them that they're interviewing now in this documentary have never had a better time than
unevaled dead too they all say it they've gone on to work on huge huge movies and they're like nothing
will ever be that experience it was so much fun and then seeing the movie they all the the uh
makeup guys talked about how they had to sneak into the premiere and they were like we've made
something amazing because they were all huge fans of the original um and it's just it's nice to see
a movie or any project where everybody is so proud and so in love with what they're doing believe me it's
very rare and it comes across when you watch evil dead too for sure and then at the end of this film
instead of Bruce Campbell getting killed uh like in the first one they do set up army of darkness
and he gets sucked into a void and lands in medieval times and the that's how the movie ends almost like
on this like time bandits thing Terry Gilliam note yeah with the camera craning up as he goes no no no no
yeah and I mean that that cliffhanger to me was up there with like empires tricks back where I was like
what the fuck is gonna happen now it's an unbelievable ending I wish that I was not so sheltered
as a kid and had been kind of able to follow this franchise weirdly I had an army of darkness
poster up in my room and I had never seen the movie the poster was up in my room for most of my
childhood and I used to jack off to it all the time because they gave the latest Campbell surely they
gave the lady giant yeah cartoon breasts on the poster and it was enough for me at that age but
yeah I do think army darkness is a lot of fun um but evil dead too is the masterpiece and I don't
think many argue you might get some true horror heads who were like no evil dead is more pure the
original but in watching them back to back there's just no competition it seems like it's
one's a trial run for the other uh I wouldn't say one's a trial run for the other I think they're both
impeccable on their own right uh but you know one is one wows me on look at what we did with no budget
and one wows me on look at what we did when we had a budget yeah you know now army of darkness the
third installment I have seen it many times over the years I own it I remember being in west
coast video and they had a wall up that said big summer sequels coming out this year
and uh one of them was army of darkness and under each movie they wrote what it was a sequel to
and I was like what is that a sequel to and then I looked down and realized oh my god it was evil dead
this is what he ends up in the other place holy shit this is crazy I'm gonna see what happens
and I liked it when I saw it as a kid the first time every successive rewatch I
have liked this movie less and less and less because now it's swung completely in the other direction
as there's almost no humor in the first one and you kind of want ash to be ash but it's still too soon
and it wasn't the idea wasn't fulfilled yet now it's too much winking to camera it's too much comedy it's
too much like hey baby and all that kind of shit uh is it a fun movie I guess is it an ambitious
movie absolutely I really appreciate the nods to Jason and the Argonauts and all the old um
with uh howery house and stuff that they doing it yeah that's where it shines to me that
that stuff's a lot of fun I hate though that the skeletons are making jokes and everybody's making
quips and you know as he has to face off with the witch it's jokes about like you are one ugly check
mama you know and like stuff like that yeah um I just think it goes way way too bad shit um in the
same way and meta in the same way that as we've discussed that gremlins two does where I can appreciate
the approach I can appreciate the vision do I want to sit down and watch it now I just don't I just
don't like it I don't enjoy it uh does that mean I'll never watch it again no I don't hate it
yeah but I mean you're coming off the ride of those first two movies it's all this animal yeah I mean
it it feels like a universal picture kind of thing you know like it's not it's it's feels like a
studio type thing but as with gremlins two I love that they got so much crazy shit into a big a big
budget movie you know a big budget studio sure sure it there there are aspects of it to be
appreciated I think if they would have allowed Bruce Campbell to be the only funny which for the most
part he is but if they just would have played some of it a little more seriously because you know
look we've talked about it with the Marvel films when there are that many quips and that many jokes
there's no sense of dread there's no sense of stakes sure it just becomes a sitcom at that point
to me or cartoonish so that's why when the remake came out which was the next installment
I was thrilled I was thrilled that they got back to making something scary because even the two has
very scary parts in it even though it has funny parts it's the perfect mix yeah it's a textbook mix
I got really angry when the remake came out at the critics let me ask you though good yeah do you
wish that when she's going out swallow your soul all swallow your soul don't you wish that he said
swallow this bitch instead of just simply swallow this no he says come get some you say swallow this
come get some's in there but in two he says swallow this oh oh and two yeah oh I thought you met
in three he says come get some at the end of three when she like attacks him in the S -Mart or whatever
right it screams it screams out for a bitch to me and maybe they just felt like swallow this bitch
felt a little too porno or rapier so who knows but well look it's one of the things I don't like about
where the character of Ash goes because he's not a swallow this bitch guy that's true you're both
but the first and second movie start out with him being like a very endearing lover of this woman
yeah that gets taken from him and he's doing everything you can right to try to get things back to
normal and then suddenly in this third movie he's like king cock it's like baby I fuck and that's
what I do and it's like where did this come from you were on a romantic getaway at the top of the
last movie yeah yeah so it's almost unlike any other franchise I can think of it the movies feel
very different from each other like the characters seem different the ash from from army of
darkness is not the ash of if evil dead one but it's a nightmare and I'm street thing it's like by the
third one he's like running around you know how do you think of these for fireworks you know
whatever right so you know whatever yeah um now Freddie would have said bitch Freddie always said
bitch yeah um but one thing I got angry about when the remake came out was what critics were saying
now a lot of critics hailed it but the critics that criticized it and I kept seeing this criticism over
and over was contains none of the fun and humor of the first film or of the original they would say
right and it's like you're a movie critic do your fucking homework this is not a remake of evil dead
two it's a remake of evil dead one right evil dead one is a straight up horror movie like god damn it
well I don't understand how you don't know that as a movie critic yeah um they probably just looked
up ebber's review of two and we're like okay now I've seen it um I saw a movie critic the other day
fucking she it was the name of the game it was some trivia thing and and it was like name uh so these
hitchcock movies and this film critic got out like three and she was stumped she's a she's a known
film critic I'm not gonna name her but it's like you can think of three hitchcock movies so anyway
uh it's embarrassing I had a I had a buddy of mine who whose favorite movie was evil dead two and he
demanded that we go we get high and go see this evil dead remake and I don't know if I was too
high or what but I was so horrified by it I was like boy this is really rough and I'll be honest I
wouldn't have minded a dash of humor in there as well it was it was pretty relentless and when I
rewatched it for this podcast uh I wasn't scared by it I think the theater does help a lot as just
being being very high but um it's sort of what I admired about it they definitely made a choice to
make this like a relentless and grim thing but it doesn't feel like the Texas chainsaw remake and
that stuff where you're like I would rather die than continue watching this movie like to me there's
something compelling about it and I think really in the second viewing it was just the Gore the
insane over the top Gore when when they they bring the knife down and it cuts between the two fingers
of the guy you know it goes down between the two fingers I was like whoa so some really really creative
and it's kind of spectacular Gore other than that the characters are a complete wash to me and I
didn't get a great deal out of it but I think it's a good modern horror movie for sure uh I when
I saw them in the theater I was beyond excited to see it uh I loved it I can't remember if I saw
with Jared Logan or not but I remember Jared Logan saying to me either during the film or or we
had seen it separately uh at the part where the woman is sawing her own face off that if the movie
had continued to be that intense he was gonna have to leave because it was he was too unnerving yeah uh
I thought the same no I saw it with pinkstone that's right and I remember when when he when I
remember when that guy walks in the bathroom and you see her doing something and you hear and you
realize before you see it she's sawing her own face off I remember pinkstone turned to me and he goes
Jesus and I was like yeah dude this is this is intense yeah so we had a blast uh seeing that he's a
big evil dead fan too um I loved it uh I then saw the second time with my mom my mom and I enjoyed
watching it on home you know DVD whatever the second time uh I watched it again last night
in preparation for this and I went right from one into the remake so I could have a better grasp on
the parallels of the two because I had never done that and there are tons of parallels between those
those two which again it's a remake of the first one it's not a remake of the sequel um for instance
the brother giving his sister the amulet that Bruce uh Campbell gives his girlfriend in the beginning
of one and um that playing a key role in the movie and all that stuff um her being her drawing and uh
that's basically what they did was they took the Cheryl character from the original film and made her
the made made her a combination of that character and Bruce Campbell's ash so she goes through all the
motions that Cheryl grow goes through getting locked to the basement getting possessed all that but
instead of succumbing to it she beats it and then becomes the heroin of the movie and then does all
the stuff Bruce Campbell does uh in the original so uh I thought it was an interesting reworking of the
story I love the effects I love the gore the scares were solid there were plenty of nods to the camera
work of the original movie that said on this latest rewatch I was bored um it just has that look for a
modern horror movie it's very solid but like you said about the characters the modern the characters
are just boring man like they they do this thing in modern horror movies where they think a character
trait because you mention it defines the character that's exactly right yeah that's the whole opening
five minutes as them being like well as you know I'm your brother and I'm and you're an artist like
these are the lines I mean yeah that bold yeah and you're like that scene where like you find out
their brother and sister by him saying come on I'm your big brother that's literally what he says
it's like guys you just had this guy yeah you just had this guy in another scene with two other people
that were telling you that your sister was out back that you should go see her you could have wrote
the line your sister's out back exactly and you would that's how somebody would say it it's like it's
like it's not a it's not a fun reveal to learn their brother and sister you're not you're not holding
it for something but that kind of stuff like but you're my but you're my older brother you know like
you'll see that movies and be like how did a writer miss that you can just find any other way to
get that information the correct yeah and then the big trait in this is the character trait is that the
main girl character Mia is a is a heroin addict yeah and you're like just because you're saying she's
a heroin addict which now I like this plot device I like that she's they're at the cabin to help her
kick and they're like we can't leave no matter what and when she gets desperate she's going to say
whatever she needs to get out of here and that's why they don't believe her about what's happening yeah
brilliant um but it's not enough to just go she's a heroin addict and then have her screaming and crying
and you go see she's a character it's not enough to have the brother go I don't believe you this time
we've been through this before and then suddenly he's a character it's not enough to have the other
lady go I am a nurse dammit and I'm giving her the care she needs it's the these care every line is just
interchangeable not one point now I will say this if you go back and watch the first evil dead
the only truly defined character is well that's not true no uh there's Scott who's the asshole and
then Cheryl you know and then you know the rest of the characters are kind of taken or leave them sure
but uh but yeah and this it just felt like modern horror movie characters it was the same thing
in that Texas chainsaw remake that the first I mean I've lost fucking track at this point but the
original one that Michael Bay produced where you're just like none of these characters are resonating
with me in any way right you know uh yeah it's it was the biggest problem of 90s horror I mean uh
he even screamed to some extent like I I love that movie and it's so much fun but uh they do a good
job making everybody funny but they're all kind of funny in the same way Nev Campbell is a great
character but you know at least they have some personality to them the these guys in this new evil
dead I and I get that that was that that was the style of the evil dead the original they didn't they
didn't develop them much but times have changed I mean you gotta know some you don't know one thing
about these people to care about them at all and the heroine thing was just not gonna do it for me
it's like oh so this is a junky on top of everything else and we're supposed to like really be rooting
so uh it was written by Fetty Alvarez roto sayag west hope hopefully right but Alvarez went on to
do don't breathe which we did on the show very very fun modern horror movie I trashed it I hated it
oh I liked it a lot um and he did the new girl with the dragon which was okay and he's doing don't
breathe too but um Bay from what I heard he wrote him in this guy wrote uh the evil dead remake and then
Diablo Cody was brought in just to translate it to English and I bet they gave her a million
fucking dollars for it because that's what the writing game was back then it does some of that has
it does have some of that Cody angst in it uh there is some of that when I heard that she had done it
I was like oh but I don't remember there being a lot of like stupid quips and shit in it and there
weren't so I think she really did just translate the movie um yeah um the uh I I would have liked to
have seen now all this said yes I was interested in now what was supposed to happen originally the
plan here was these guys are always making much grander plans and it seems they're able to execute
unfortunately but the original plan here was they were going to make a sequel to this movie
that centered on the Mia character once again and then they were going to make evil dead seven
which was going to combine Ash's storyline and Mia's storyline which is why I say I they
called this a remake I don't think it's a remake I think it's a sequel I think this is a sequel to
the uh uh ladies and gentlemen I just I need to point out Pat got up Pat just start plugging the
computer in from the top of the I can't I have to move it ever just start from that position why
don't you just do it through the whole show where you can plug it in it's not comfortable it's not
good all right fair enough every episode folks people that Pat gets up it wanders off like your
granddad at a fair comes back with his plug I'm always like why don't you just plug it in from the top
not yeah I wish I could I wish I could um so so these storylines we're going to cross over we're
so this is so so again this is this is to me as a sequel even though there's some differences one of
the things I didn't like about the remake is I don't like the way the deadites look they don't look
anywhere near as cool I also didn't like that like I always think it's a bit much when you're looking
at a sacred book there's contemporary English curse words in it like when they're looking through
the necronomicon it's like written in blood is like chop the motherfucker it's like right come on guys
let's be a little more elegant than that yeah uh but um hashtag death yeah yeah but this
clearly to me was a sequel uh the car is there when they show up in the post credit scene it cuts to
blues Campbell saying groovy uh as a hidden little scene uh and these were supposed to cross over they
didn't unfortunately um and what we got instead was the sequel series of ash versus evil dead uh which
I enjoyed for the first two seasons I was thrilled to see Bruce Campbell back I was a big fan of Dana
Dela Renzo in the show who Pat and I met at what was that bar we used to go to boardeners boardeners
she was very done now that bar set yeah she was very cool um I really like it's Cheryl came back in the
second season as I said Ted Raimi reprised the role of the mother and the seller they went back to
the cabin there were plenty of elements in the first two seasons that I really loved about this show
I loved the concept that the deadites were after ash and they were following him across the country
I just thought it was a really really cool show but then in the third season it just went way too heavy
into the comedy I mean the opening episode of season three is ash is opening a fishing store in
sex and poreum it's like come on guys like what the fuck man like take this a little seriously
um and that bums me out because I would have liked to have seen ash cross over with this mea storyline
where we would have gotten not just a bit of a brighter version of the mea storyline but a darker
version again of the ash storyline and I think that would have been really perfect tonally to see
and unfortunately we didn't get it uh from what I'm reading the from the quotes of the director and
everything for evil dead rise it sounds like they're on track to make it completely fucking relentless
again uh and super heavy so uh we'll see if that's the case I'm curious to see you know if that's
what happens but I'll be there I'll be there no matter what yeah I mean I will too I think that evil dead
the series to me asher is the evil dead I only watched seasons one and maybe half of two
unfortunately but I should probably finish it up um the scene where Bruce Campbell is stepping on all
the light bulbs at the then the very beginning of the very first episode of ash first evil dead
is some of the hardest I've ever laughed for a while I kept it on my phone to cheer me up I don't know
if you remember this but he he's trying to move a cardboard box he's like whistling to himself and then
5 ,000 light bulbs fall out the back of it right right and then he's trying to walk out without stepping
on anymore walk out of the center of the light bulbs he keeps stepping on them and going like
right for whatever reason it it made me how laughing but yeah it had some great moments I think it's
the you know I'm not saying Ramy's the only one that can do this this franchise but I think the reason
that the remake didn't stick with you or me and it wasn't as good as we might have remembered is
because of the characters and because it's just there's nothing memorable about it when you're sitting
in the theater and you're terrified you're like that was fucking awesome but with some time you're kind
of like I don't give a shit about anybody in this movie I don't remember any of their names I
don't really remember anything about them what it is is just a showcase for great Gore and it you know
on on the interviews on that Blu -ray he got Bruce Campbell going I mean basically I wouldn't
do it until we had somebody who was just as great a character as ash and we definitely got that
with it and it's like no you didn't she's just a girl who's allergic to her you know addicted to heroin
it's not yeah well and that's the funny thing is as much as I didn't like the the hard comedy
lean in the ass versus evil dead series the characters were very memorable they were all very carved
out characters you knew exactly who Kelly was you know exactly who Paco I think he kept
called him yeah was you knew who these characters were you know and which was really cool so
anyway folks this comedy horror brew is one of the hardest things to pull off you if you tip
the scales in either direction it's a mess and basically I think this franchise has has one shining
perfect example of how to blend them and that's evil dead too right great the the others either go
they if you wouldn't say they go too far in a horror direction but you would definitely say they go
too far in a comedy direction sometimes it's kind of a good franchise to study if you're like
if you're trying to make a horror comedy because you can see all the different ways it can go
and you know in terms of the remake it's it's like extreme almost x -rated violence you know rough
stuff in terms of army and darkness you've got like a kind of a ridiculous comedy in the show at
least the episodes I saw it was almost a road trip kind of vibe to it but yeah it's a it's a
franchise that to me is more successful than your Halloween franchise your Friday the 13th franchise
all your big boys and for some reason it's never really mentioned I know that we're going to do
Freddy vs. Jason vs. Ash but I don't think that in general horror fans consider the evil dead to be
a franchise that's up there with these others and I think they should it's it's I'd be curious to
find out if that's I don't know yeah it's weird I wonder I wonder myself everyone loves the evil dead
but you know like when it comes to Halloween season I always see way more stuff about Michael Myers
more stuff about Jason etc. Yeah but it's a franchise worth checking out if you haven't already I
can't imagine if you listen to this show you haven't but if you haven't go check it out that's our
show folks we'll be back with two episodes mid month not sure what they're going to be yet but
we'll be bringing you those on or no I'm sorry we'll be back early December for December first
this is mid month we'll be back December first with two new apps probably Christmas and Thanksgiving
themed in some way or shape or form we'll let you know please if you're in New York check out the
Joey Rose's sandwich shop pop up the menu is the heart eight eight sandwiches for eight bucks each
classic old school style big old sandwiches they're gonna fill you up they're delicious you're
gonna love them nothing gourmet here just good old sandwich eaten come by at the stand in union
square in New York City Wednesday to Friday 12 p .m. to 4 p .m. and my special you let me down available
now to watch for free on Comedy Central's YouTube channel follow me Instagram and Twitter at
Jota Rosa Comedy follow Joey Roses on Instagram and Twitter at Joey Roses Hard 8 you know what we
should do next month Joe is fat man the Mel Gibson yeah it'll probably be like one of those Amazon
releases so I'm very excited for that yeah so let's if if it's out let's do that 100 % I am the Patrick
Walsh on Twitter and Instagram I recommend especially if you love evil dead too as much as we do
that you get that Blu -ray there's 8 ,000 versions of the Blu -ray so just make sure you get one that has
the two -hour documentary about it because if you're a fan of the franchise you're gonna absolutely
love it I I loved it myself and also if you're a video game fan there are a few evil dead video
games I believe they're all PlayStation 2 era they're not fantastic but there are a lot of fun and
Bruce Campbell does do the voice so it's it's it's worth a dip okay we will see you next time
and we'll see you in hell