I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, and when the sound of your screams becomes
a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say, I'll see you in hell, you know I will, I'll see
you in hell, you know I will.
Folks, it's we'll see you in hell, the boys are back as we sang in the last episode, as
Pat sang in the last episode, and we're back this time to talk about our personal faves
of 2021, five TV shows, five movies, two guys.
That's right, and I would just like to say that TV -wise, I had, I picked my five and
then I had 10 honorable mentions that just missed the cut.
Movie -wise, I don't even love all five of my choices.
This was one of the worst years since I've been alive for movies, and what I realized
recently is that in the last couple of months, there's been a lot of great albums that I've
been enjoying, and they keep coming.
And last year, I don't think there was a single album that I loved.
It's just, it's a very bad time for the arts, I will say, except TV seems to be thriving.
There's a lot of cool shows coming out.
So, yeah, without further ado, Joe, let us start, let's start with TV, because we're
a movie podcast, what would be, and we're ranking them, yes?
I did, yeah, sure, we can rank, I didn't necessarily rank mine, but I can do that.
Do it on the fly.
What was your number five television show of 2021?
My number five was Hacks.
Loved Hacks.
Great show, very funny, love both the leads, love that there's a comedy out there doing
something edgy and conflicted and not just sort of puking out the virtues of the, of
whoever the writer is, or political opinions of whoever the writer is, love that the characters
are flawed, love that it's not PC all the time, love that they examine the PC versus
non -PC argument and discussion.
I just kind of did it for me, you know, and it's funny as a standup comic, the standup
was the least interesting, not that it wasn't interesting, I just mean like what drew me
to it or what brought me further into it was not because it was a show about standup, it
was the show about the types of people that it was about, and I thought it was very, very
good, I think Hacks is very good and well -deserved of all the awards and very happy for that
whole cast and crew.
It just missed my cut, I'm friendly with Jen Statsky, one of the writers, I love the show
and I think the two leads are incredible, particularly Miss Jean Smart, I'm a fan of
the show, the only reason I didn't make my list is I think they got bigger and better
places to go.
It's a Sin was my number five, completely took me off guard, it was a four part, four
hour mini -series made for British television, I want to say, but it's about a group of close
friends in the 80s who one by one are sort of picked off by the AIDS virus.
It starts with, you know, like hints that things may be going wrong, hey, have you heard
about this, what's going on in the gay community, etc.
And by the end, it's just a really devastating portrait, it's a global story told on a
personal scale about a group of gay best friends, it really, really blew me away, I was
surprised by it, incredibly well written and with an amazing soundtrack of some of my
favorite music, which is that 80s kind of new order gay disco type vibe, I love all
that stuff and it's a very well done show, it's on HBO Max, I don't think near enough
people saw it, but I loved it.
Kind of like, is it sort of like in the band played on that kind of thing?
Yeah, but it's not that, yeah, but you know, it's ballsy to say you're better than
Angels in America, but I'd say to me, it's better because it doesn't have those big
lofty goals, and there's not angels and you know, it's just a good, well told story
about a group of friends that, you know, says so much about many other things in the
process, I really liked it.
My number four, this is a made for TV movie, so I don't know, you know, maybe it's a bit
of a cheat, but I have the super Bob Einstein movie.
This came along right when I needed it, been a lifelong fan of Bob Einstein, lifelong,
I was terribly sad to hear it when he passed, have followed him throughout his career, I
was a huge Super Dave fan as a kid, and of course, you know, we're both huge Curb fans
on this show, and I've been a long time admirer and fan of Albert Brooks, and of Larry David,
and I don't know, this thing just came along right when I needed it, it was, you know,
it was a dark time in my life, and seeing this put such a smile on my face and brought
me such joy and such happiness, and I've gotten, I'm friends with Jeff Garland from
doing comedy from over the years, but it was like one of those things where I called
him up and I said, dude, I just want to say thanks, man, like everything kind of sucks
right now. And like this really brought laughter and like smiles to my face. And it was great
seeing you on it and whatever. And it was awesome. It was just it was just a really it
was nice to see a documentary that was uplifting, because most aren't. And that truly
celebrated the man that it was about and the people that it was about. And even when it
got into the sadder stuff about him passing away, it didn't go heavy handed. There wasn't
this big twist where all of a sudden tonally that shifted and it got dark. It stayed in
the zone emotionally that you would expect a Bob Einstein documentary to stay in. So
I loved it. I recommend it highly.
Yeah, we talked about it just last week. I like to I'm very excited about Larry, the
new Larry David documentary coming to HBO in less than a week. There's, you know, what
I assume is covering his whole career. My number four is what gave me really some of
the only belly laughs that I have experienced in the last couple of years. And that is,
I think you should leave season two, season two did not have the batting average of season
one. It almost couldn't because that show blew me away. But Tim Robinson is a comedic
genius. I hope they let him do another season. The I think my favorite in looking back was
either the I don't want to be around anymore sketch when he dresses up as the man in the
mall. And the amazing long running or long form sketch of the guy who looks like Santa
Claus, the guy who talks about how he you know, my quote is I get paid that even if
I don't show up, even if I do a bad job. Yeah, that guy was so incredible. I had a lot of
laughs that I think you should leave. I think it lost a little steam in the home stretch,
but there was at least 10 classic sketches. Love the show love the man hope it keeps going.
My number three is also I think you should leave. That was my number four. But that's
sorry. Yeah, I actually think I'm in hindsight might have preferred season two to season one.
Just in in in in. I don't know. It's hard to say. I can't say I liked it better or were
it. There were moments in both that I loved. And there were moments in season two that
I thought were superior to season one. And there were moments in season one that I thought
were superior to season two. However, it was a great season. Again, another thing that
came along when I needed it. And I just needed to laugh and not think about anything. It
was a great escape. And my highlights of the season were the first episode, the haunted
house sketch was amazing. And then I actually thought it did end on a strong note. I loved
the pants sketch. I remember you saying you thought it went on for too long with that
killed me. That was not not my thing. Yeah, I loved it. But but anyway, I think you should
leave. That is my number three. My number three is Mayor of Easttown with Kate Winslet
and numerous other great actors. Just a classic down the middle detective story. You know,
accents aside, I thought this was just a really, really well done mystery series that prioritized
character as much as it did the mystery. And the mystery was great. It kept you guessing.
It's one of those, unfortunately, and actually, this is, it's a thing with a lot of HBO. And
the Sopranos used to do this, too. Their best episode would always be the second to last.
And then that last one, you're kind of like, you're tying up loose ends. That's the same
with me for Mayor. But it had really exciting action moments. It had scary moments,
suspenseful moments, great character moments, dramatic moments, another amazing performance
from Gene Smart. And I just really, really liked it. I don't know what to tell you. It's
it's a very traditional thing. It's not like a lot of HBO stuff where it's trying to reinvent
the wheel. But it really, really works. Recommended if you haven't watched it. It's a Pennsylvania
town, a small Pennsylvania town, a lot of conflicting accents is my only grievance.
I didn't see it because I grew up in that area and I feel it's nothing to be celebrated.
Well, they don't celebrate it. There's nobody happy. There's nobody happy in the show. It's
getting as much a show about depression as it is about being a detective.
Um, the well, it does remind me of when I used to solve crimes back there. Sure. The my number
two or commit both. I'd commit the crime on knowing to myself. And then as I was solving
it, I would realize I was the I was chasing myself. It's something you did when you were
blacked out drunk. Yeah. My number two is pretend it's a city. The Annie Liebowitz docu
that Martin Scorsese directed. I loved it as a New Yorker. And I consider myself a New
Yorker at this point. I've lived here for long enough and I know that I'm going to probably
die here. So it's this is this is my home. I know that I am supposed to be here. And
I don't think that's ever going to change. So I just click with this place. I get it
and I have a love for it that a lot of people do not have. And a lot of people that live
that have lived here longer for me no longer have. But I continue to love this place. I
love to celebrate it. And I thought that this was just a wonderful time to spend to time
spent piece of time spent with a quintessential New Yorker. Somebody that had stories that
decades in the city, her attitude, her artistry, her humor, every aspect of her, I just have
great, great, great admiration for. And, you know, she's a rare breed. You know, and that
pains me to say it. But then again, if she wasn't a rare breed, this wouldn't be so cool
and unique. So I guess it's a good thing. But I urge you if you haven't spent some time
with Annie Liebowitz and watch this documentary also to for some reason, Martin Scorsese is
one of those people. It really charms me when I see him laughing really hard. He's one of
those guys. And I almost give the show a laugh track of Martin. He's laughing over every
single thing she says. Yeah. And this is one of those things where she Yeah, he's like,
he's just a step. I guess it part of it to me. It was this way in the Rickles documentary
to part of it to me is like somebody that you respect so much like Martin Scorsese. When
you see him like brought to stitches by somebody you're like you fantasize like, could you
imagine if you made Martin Scorsese laugh that hard? Right. And she does. And rightfully
so she's hilarious. But it's just a great, great documentary. And I just love the
perspective of it and the perspective of her and it's worth a watch. I loved it too. I
mean, my that one and pretty much everything on my list is either in the HBO or the HBO
Max camp. So you got to give them kudos they they really are bringing the heat lately. My
number two is succession, a show that I very much enjoyed a show with 10 a list
performances from from an amazing cast. The best of course being the great Brian Cox and
the great Jeremy Strong, whoever one made fun of because that stupid magazine article,
but you know, he who cares about his process if the results are as good as what he gives us,
but he's saying the magazine article, I don't remember. They painted him as a, you know,
it was all over Twitter for weeks. He just seemed like a method actor. And then they
interviewed the other actors and they were like, yeah, he can be a little annoying when he won't
come out of it. But, you know, it's worth it. He's an amazing actor. And it's like, he's a method
actor, give him a break. You know, he didn't do anything crazy. Jeremy Strong, he's the guy,
the most troubled guy in the family, the young almost looks like a vampire, sunken eyes, you know.
Oh, I know. He's like, he's like the not Culkin, but the guy above him. Right? Yeah. Okay.
Culkin, Culkin and the show itself was a little too quippy for me. And I think it is because it
is written by a comedy writer, the guy who did peep show, one of the all time great comedies.
In season three, they scaled that back a bit where every line was equipped because that was
starting to grate on my nerves a little, even though I admired the writing in a huge, huge way,
but succession season three becomes darker. It digs into more of the character's life,
as opposed to the drama, the high stakes drama of these big deals they're making and everything.
And I just thought it was a really good show becoming an excellent show. And if they continue
down this path, we're talking about one of the greats. I think it's a really, really amazingly
written and acted show. My number one is a two parter because these do go hand in hand, but
Mandalorian season two, Boba Fett season one, which ended in 2022, but started in 2021.
Boba Fett was an offshoot of Mandalorian. You know, we're far enough out from both of these
shows at this point that I can give the spoilers away, but Dave Filoni and Jon Favreau and Robert
Rodriguez are doing things with Lucasfilm and the intellectual property that we only wished we had
seen in the sequel trilogy. We got a bit of it in The Force Awakens, and then it kind of went away
after that. But the finale of the Mandalorian, where you've watched this journey with him in this
thing we called Baby Yoda for so long, and you know that he's got to get this back to a Jedi,
but the problem is the Jedi are extinct. And the season two ending with
fucking Luke Skywalker coming back, and it's de -aged Mark Hamill, and you're like,
holy shit. And then that setting up the Boba Fett offshoot and
mid -season Boba Fett, Mark Hamill, a full Luke Skywalker episode where the de -aging is so good,
you're like, I'm watching Mark Hamill from 1983 right now on a TV show. This is insane.
Yeah. And I'm not here to praise effects. I'm here to praise what they're giving to
Star Wars fans, which is all of the story and everything that we all wanted to see.
It misses the market times, but they're giving us the stuff we wanted to see for so long. What
happened after Return of the Jedi? Not this brooding, pissed off Luke and he hates everybody
and he's a curmudgeon. I'm fine with that, but how does he get to that point? Give me some of
the good stuff before you just give me the bad. And they're doing that in this. I love it. I love
the show. We finally got to see how Boba got out of the Sarlacc pit. Awesome. I just can't wait
to see what they do next. And the way they're crossing these shows over, where Ahsoka played
by the actor from kids clerks to what's her name? Rosario Dawson. Yeah. Rosario Dawson plays Ahsoka.
She's great. She's got her own show coming out. Boba Fett has now crossed over with Mandalorian.
They're swiping in and out of one another. Mando now has played a major role in Boba Fett and vice
versa. Ahsoka turned up in Boba Fett after she first turned up in Mando.
I love that they're creating this universe that's just going to cross over with like four shows
telling an interlocking story that's much too big to confine to a movie or whatever. So
I love what those guys are doing. You know, I had my qualms with the sequel trilogy. We've talked
about ad nauseam, but I think that they're plugging in the holes in the dam that will
make that trilogy make a hell of a lot more sense in the end, which I think is great.
I did not know Luke Skywalker returned. So thank you for that, Joe. No, but I watched the first
season of the Mandalorian and that was enough for me. It just felt like one of those stories where
he goes from A to B, then the next week is B to C. And I was just, I wasn't into it. Maybe at
some point I'll watch it. I hated the first season. I found it terribly boring. I didn't care.
Then that's, I should probably keep going. All right. Second season is where I started to be
like, oh shit. Okay. You know, okay. All right. And Timothy Oldefont showing up and he plays a
sheriff in, in most the Moss, BESPA or whatever space port. And he's great. He's basically,
he's basically justified except it's in Star Wars. Yeah. I've been slowly watching justified. He's
great on that show. My number one is the White Lotus. I really, really, really enjoyed this show
week to week. I love that it was not a binger that you had to, had it to look forward to every week.
A towering performance by the great Jennifer Coolidge. I did not see it as like her becoming
an amazing actress. It's just an extension of the incredible work she has done over her entire
career. But obviously she's the comedic high point of this show. But aside from Coolidge, who was
amazing and I hope wins all the awards that she deserves this year. Everybody else is great in
this thing too. Jake Lacey, who's an actor who I've always thought was pretty solid is playing
such a realistic portrayal of like an annoying 40 year old self -entitled dude. It's a show about
white privilege, show about entitlement at a time when these are the biggest issues going on at this
moment. It's a show about capitalism, colonialism. You know, I would, I would say it is a show that
devotes 99 % of its time to white characters and they're on a Hawaiian Island and no, no time spent
on anyone else. But that's kind of the point. These people don't have time or care about anyone
else. Mike White has been an incredible writer of dark, weird comedy forever. And this is yet
another great, great show from him. I highly recommend The White Lotus. And then real quick,
before we move on to movies, I also really enjoyed the other two hacks, which just missed my list,
Yellow Jackets on Showtime, which would have a thousand percent been on my list if they didn't
kind of blow the ending. And I think they blew it in a bid to just get more seasons out of the show,
who can fault them for that? But it seems like it's already going to have that kind of lost problem,
the show lost, where they just try to give you too much backstory and try to extend what could have
been an amazing story too far. I hope they proved me wrong, but the performances of Melanie Linsky,
Juliette Lewis, and especially Christina Ricci, I love that show, Yellow Jackets, made on Netflix
is excellent. Cue Into the Storm, one of my favorite documentaries and NYC epicenters by
Great Spike Lee, another one of them. Oh, and Squid Game, how could I forget Squid Game, which
we were obsessed with. Let us move on to the films of 2021. And as I said, not a good year for film,
but Joe, what is your numero cinco? Why don't you start us since I started us on TV?
I shall. I will go with Paul Thomas Anderson's Licorice Pizza.
I'm terrible things about this movie. I person after person comes in the bar and goes, have you
seen this Licorice Pizza? I love this guy's movies. God damn it. I hated this fucking movie.
I'm hearing this. Well, you're saying it's pretty good. And then I see trailers that are like the
best movie of his career or whatever. And I'm like, it's about why is it okay that a 25 year
old is fucking a 15 year old or showing her him her tits or whatever the hell it is that she does
in this movie? It shouldn't be. And I have two movies on my list about super inappropriate
relationships. Three, actually, now that I think about it, it was a weird theme this year. But they
don't fuck in the movie. It's not that they it's a it's a kind of will they or won't they or should
they or shouldn't they but there's very it's very chaste relationship outside of that flashing scene.
I really liked it on a first viewing and I liked it less on a second viewing. A lot of it I think
is just people's undying love for Paul Thomas Anderson. He is our Altman, meaning you're going
to get masterpieces and you're going to get stuff that leaves you scratching your head. But I think
they're all movies that stay with you and stand the test of time. Even inherent vice grew on me
on a second viewing. But as I think I might have said on here, Licorice Pizza is the first movie
his that went down on a second viewing for me. And that's not a great sign. But there's enough
here to enjoy. There's enough great set pieces. It's very influenced by 70s movies. It's a lot of
kind of it's it's episodic, as they say, there's not really telling a through line except that
these these two relations, these twos relationship, and especially in the end with the Sean Penn
scenes, Sean Penn playing William Holden, and then Bradley Cooper playing John Peters.
They're they're funny. They're interesting. Tom Waits in there as well. But you do sort of start
to wonder what does this have to do with anything? And at the end of the day, I don't really care
because this was such a bad year for movies. And it's a movie with a lot of memorable scenes,
great music, great performances, especially from Philip Seymour Hoffman's son, Cooper,
and Alana Heim, as well as all the Heim sisters who I love. Certainly an enjoyable movie made my
number five. How's Waits look these days? I haven't seen him. He looks great. I mean,
they have him like emerge from a cloud of smoke and he's like, baby, how are you? Like, you know,
he has a very small role in the film, but he's good. Look, these my picks were because I had a
hard time. And I just tried to basically I just said, what which five movies did I enjoy the most
year? You know, it's not not attacking it necessarily from not that I didn't do that
with the TV stuff, but with the TV stuff, there's a little more of an analytical approach
for what I was seeing versus what I wasn't hadn't been seeing on TV.
And appreciating the div that but but this is just a little more like I just went through like,
what movies did I really just enjoy seeing this year that really resonate and stick out in my
head. So my number five is spiral. I had a great time watching spiral never been a big saw fan
never been a big fan of the franchise and appreciated it enough. Went and saw spiral
basically out of obligation to review it on the show and ended up having a great time loved Chris
Rock. Say finally bought Chris Rock in a serious role like playing a detective. I never thought I
would buy it but I did love Sam Jackson as always loved every part of the movie just had a great
time with it. They got me with the twist. And I want to see what happens next. I mean, you know,
and and and every jigsaw style machine kill made my skin crawl. There you go. That's what you want
from a saw movie, especially 10 into the franchise. They had me squirming at most of those traps. I
agree with you. It didn't even cross my mind. But yeah, it was great. It was it was as much to me
anyway, as much a return to form as the new scream, even though I preferred spiral to the new scream.
My number four would be Ridley Scott's The Last Duel. House of Gucci got all the praise,
all the nominations, all the box office, The Last Duel lost a tremendous amount of money.
It got that they nominated Ben Affleck for a Razzie. That's that they should be ashamed
of themselves still doing the Razzie's at this point. Ben Affleck is awesome in this movie
playing basically a frat douche, but in medieval times. Matt Damon is he Matt Damon is the A list
actor who is most willing to make himself look like just a piece of shit, a complete loser.
You look at the informant, which is such an amazing movie to me.
He is so awful in this movie and such a like a dork and a loser. The the woman Jodie Jodie
Comer or Comer from Killing Eve is exceptional in this. It's told in a three part Rashomon story,
Affleck's point of view, Damon's point of view, the woman's point of view, talking about a rape
went on. Adam Driver is also excellent in this Ridley Scott in this sort of milieu,
you know, like a past either science fiction or or the past. I think he really comes to life.
And goddamn, I loved The Last Duel. I was so surprised by it. It's one where you're talking
the whole way home about, you know, all the different points of view, who you believe,
who you don't believe, what the truth is, et cetera. Really, really enjoyable movie. And kudos
to Affleck and Damon, who proved 25 years later that it wasn't a fluke Good Will Hunting, that
they're really excellent screenwriters, along with Nicole Hall of Centner, who wrote the great enough
said for, in my opinion, a perfect romantic comedy. My number four is Ghostbusters Afterlife.
It's a movie I waited a very long time to see. It was a movie that I thoroughly enjoyed seeing.
I saw it on a day where I had had a hard day in the process of trying to get the bar open, where
Con Ed shut our power off because they mistook us for the previous tenants who abandoned the space
and never shut their bill off. All right. It was a horrible day. It was a stressful day.
Our construction guys couldn't continue to work and we were on a timeline. The clock was ticking.
We were losing money by not having them work. My partner Paul and I got into a absolute screaming
match that was probably as close to a fistfight as I've come in 20 years because we were so
stressed out and sometimes it manifests in not a good way. We got the power turned back on. We
settled the issue. The guys were able to start working again. Paul and I had a heart to heart
and we made up and everything was good. I went right from that conversation, relieved
to the movie theater, had two or three drinks at the movie theater bar
at the Essex Street Regal Cinemas, and then went to see Ghostbusters Afterlife. It was just what
the doctor ordered at that moment in time. I'd been so excited to see it. Was it perfect? No,
but it was a really, really enjoyable film. We reviewed it on here and the nostalgia factor
obviously is always big with me and I just loved that experience. That's my number four.
Yeah. At a time when every reboot is just pathetic, the new Matrix, the new Space Jam,
I assume, the new any number of things that got dumped on HBO Max over the last year,
Ghostbusters, Spiral, Scream. We're getting into a place where they're at least
trying to keep the spirit of these movies alive and it just doesn't seem like a soulless
cash grab. I really like Ghostbusters 2. My number three, Ghostbusters also, although I did like
Ghostbusters 2 and RIP Ivan Reitman, by the way. Oh yeah, geez, I forgot. It came from out of nowhere,
man. Yeah, he, I mean, always just seemed to be in perfect health. I met him a few times. He was,
his company produced a movie that I got very close to getting made years ago, a 21st birthday movie
and he was great. He would come in after having read the script and give you like three things
very casually and you'd be like, yep, those three things would fix the movie. He's that kind of guy.
He's just a genius who's been around comedy his whole life. For me, number three is Benedetta,
Paul Verhoeven's Benedetta, a story about lesbian nuns. Again, a wildly inappropriate age difference
between the two of them. I had to Google it in the film to make sure I was, you never know with
Verhoeven. I was like, please tell me I'm watching a young woman who is of age because they did it in
France too. I was like, who knows, who knows what the rules are over there.
Right. Well, that's where, that's where Polanski went. Yeah. When he got in trouble. Yeah. So who
knows? Yeah. Paul Verhoeven is a hero of mine. He just is. He is every, he is the opposite of
everything I find wrong about Hollywood these days. He knows that a big part of the reason people go
to the movies is to see beautiful people naked, to see violence, to see crazy shit.
And he is determined to never let you be bored in his movies, just across the board. When they
stopped giving him the big budgets after Hollow Man, he just went right back to his roots and
started making better written movies that he often co -writes in his native country in France. I
absolutely love Benedetta. I was high and I probably owe it another rewatch, but at the time
I was just like, what a dream. It was, it was so good. I was honestly fully erect throughout.
And when's the last time, as I said online to much controversy, it just felt good to be hard in a
theater again. It's a, it's a crazy, funny, zany movie about lesbian nuns. And I can recommend it
highly enough. My number three, by the way, I said Verhoeven's French with that last name. He's got
to be German, right? Well, yeah, but you could be of German descent and still be born in France.
Cheerfully withdrawn. You're correct. My number three is a son of a bitch.
I just deleted it and it was like, I'll remember what I just had typed there.
Oh my God. Brain. Brain ain't what it used to be, kiddo. What the hell did I just have written down
there? Oh, number three, surprisingly, probably to people. How I house a Gucci. I had a great
time watching this movie. I enjoyed it. Really took Lady Gaga from being somebody who I said,
well, she's an amazing musician and wow, she's a great actor too. To being like, I can't wait to
see what Lady Gaga does next on the silver screen. She's tremendous. Um, Adam Driver delivers, uh,
Pacino delivers, uh, and you know what? Bite me. I liked Lido. The further I get from it,
the more I appreciate this insane, insane thing that he did in this movie. And look,
they said it about Pacino when he did Scarface. They were just like, what the fuck is this guy
doing? And then, you know, things heal over time. Uh, I think we'll look back one day on Lido's
performance ago. That was ballsy and wild and nuts. Um, but what really frustrates me about you,
Joe, is that you celebrate Jared Lido and house of Gucci's portrayal of an Italian and won't watch
the Sopranos because of their portrayal of Italian. It's so absurd. Your rules on things.
Here's why. Here's why. Uh huh. I know Italian Americans. I don't know any Italian like the
Lido. I have no point. I mean, my cousin, I'll say this, my cousin Marcello, who's one of the most
lovely people I've ever met. He lives in Rome and he's from there. He's, he's Italian, obviously.
He's, he's the closest barometer I would have on this. And I will say this.
He is always laughing. He hugs and kisses you like crazy. Uh huh. It's not dissimilar.
Okay. All right. Fine. Fine. Look, I enjoyed house of Gucci for what it was too. I mean,
this was a year where almost everything on my list was like campy pleasures. It wasn't like
excellent films and house of Gucci is definitely a campy movie. Now, did you see stars born or was
this your first Lady Gaga encounter? I saw some of it. I'm not really good. Yeah, no, I, I just
wasn't that interested in the movie itself, but like I saw enough of scenes. I was like, man,
she's a good actor. Like that's pretty, you know, so like when I saw she was casting this, I was
like, oh yeah, that makes sense. She's good. But then I saw this and I was like,
you have that moment where you kind of look up halfway through the movie and go,
oh yeah, that's Lady Gaga. That's usually to me the mark of pretty tremendous performance.
She's excellent. I think she deserves an Oscar nod for this, if not a win.
Um, I don't think she got one. Did they announce it already? Yeah, the nominations are out.
Jeez. All right. Well, the Oscar thing's coming up soon. Who's hosting Schumer and two other
women or something? Schumer, Regina, King or Hall. Didn't Regina King host it last year? No,
she just opened it. Yeah, there was no host last year. Okay. So Regina King and then I'm not Schumer
Rebecca Hall. Yeah, it's Rebecca Hall, the hilarious Rebecca Hall. No, seriously. Is it?
No. Oh, you said Hall. So I didn't know. Well, no, there's Regina Hall and Regina King and I,
um, it couldn't be King because her son just committed suicide. I don't think she's going
to be hosting it. So it's probably that would make sense. That would be Regina King. Who the
hell is Regina Hall? I'm getting, I'm getting them confused because their names are Regina,
not because they're black. Let me check up Academy Award hosts. I mean, very strange
choice. I think, Oh, Amy Schumer, Regina Hall and Wanda Sykes. Oh, okay. The great Wanda Sykes.
Who is Regina Hall? I don't know who that is. You definitely do. Regina Hall was in scary movie.
She's been in movies. Oh, I know who you're talking about. She was one of the girls trip ladies,
you know. Okay. Yeah, she's, she's great. As is, as is Regina King and RIP Regina King's son.
Yeah, that's very sad. Um, anyway, House of Gucci. Yes. And I also to love anytime I see a movie
that I can say to my mom, mom, watch this movie, you'll love it. And then she calls me and goes,
I loved it. Like that's, that's not, that's, that doesn't happen frequently. So yes, I enjoyed this
picture quite a bit. I should say I have not seen all the, all the movies released this year. I have
also, I've not seen drive my car, the three hour Japanese movie that ever review refers to as
meditative. I thought you were going to say it was a three hour Beatles documentary. No, although
that Jesus, I love get back that just missed my list actually. But um, I found it hard to, to award
that to a 12 hour film, but um, no, I haven't seen that. I haven't seen the worst person in the world,
which I hear is fantastic. And I'm sure my list will change. That's great. Uh, my number two,
and it was close is red rocket. One of two movies this year that I thought was excellent, uh, red
rocket stars, Simon Rex, written and directed by Sean Baker, who is fast becoming one of my
budget. He's another guy that does not shy away by any means from uncomfortable subject matter,
from sex and nudity in all its forms, even if it's completely inappropriate, there are sex scenes
in this movie between a 50 year old man and a 16 year old girl, uh, who definitely looks 16.
She is not, she is in her twenties, but it's, it's a true original why it's, it's very much
a piece with the seventies kind of anti -hero movies. It's a guy who's a completely irredeemable
scumbag who also does have a bit of charm to him. You can't deny it. Um, I hope Sean Baker makes a
movie a year for the rest of his life and he's never losing anybody, any money because he makes
them so cheap. So I hope he's getting rich off these little movies too. But, um, it's great.
Simon Rex is going to be one of those actors who is going to, you know, everyone's praising
his performance, but we probably won't see him again. You know, he's got his past involves
jerk off videos online, but, um, like, yeah, I was happy to see him that he did. I gotta still see
this movie. I feel like it's going to be a Napoleon dynamite situation where the movie gets praised.
Everybody goes, this is like a, almost like a phenomenon of sorts in cinema. And then he goes,
you know, John Hayter. Yeah. You barely ever see him. Yeah. Uh, and it's, it's actually not even
a bad comparison to Napoleon dynamite. It's obviously way more R rated of a movie and
some real explicit uncomfortable sex stuff in this film to be sure. But, uh, I loved it. I really do.
I think this movie is a great one. And if it had come out in 1972, we'd all be hailing it as a
classic. And maybe we will in 50 years. I don't know. Great, great anti -hero movie.
Uh, my number two, Pat. Yeah. Candyman. Really? Wow. Okay. Well, yeah. You know what?
Um, yeah, because the more distance I got from Candyman, I liked it when we saw it,
we gave it a nice review. We, we, we, we had some issues. We have issues with every movie we watch.
Um, there were some things I, you know, would have liked to have seen done differently that
didn't quite add up ultimately for me, but I will say that, um, the, the, the more I thought about
it and the more, first of all, I enjoyed it thoroughly in the theater when I saw it,
but for them to pull off a sequel, that solid in a franchise that had such disappointing
sequels already and was sort of left by the wayside to, you know, more or less to be forgotten
outside of like a scream factory, uh, rerelease or whatever. I, I thought it was, I thought it was
very, very impressive and it was important for horror for all the reasons that we said earlier
about Ghostbusters in this reboot and requal and sequel culture and all the stuff that we do
for them to make a Candyman movie as a true sequel that was that solid, that wasn't just,
and then the guy from the first one comes back and about, you know, like we were talking about
last episode with this new Texas chainsaw and the new Halloween or whatever. I thought it was a very,
very impressive feat. I thought it was probably arguably one of the most important horror movies
to come out in 2021, uh, for what it meant for the genre, uh, and for what it showed could
possibly be done with the genre. You know, I, I usually strike out against mainstream horror,
but the fact that this movie was released on the as large a platform as it was, uh, and
paying back, it's paying tribute to a legacy that should have been paid a long time ago,
or paid tribute to a long time ago, I think is a huge feat for horror. And I think it's will
hopefully serve as a blueprint to show how you can continue a horror franchise, which is always
something that horror creators do in a tasteful and good quality way instead of just rehashing
a bunch of stupid bullshit. Uh, okay. Yeah. I mean, nowhere near my list. I'm glad you liked
as much as you did. I did enjoy the film, uh, my number one, and really I never wavered on this.
I, when I saw it, I was like, well, that's clearly the best movie I've seen all year and nothing
really came close to it. Uh, titane, the new movie from Julia do Cornell, uh, who did raw,
which was one that the teenage cannibal movie that Joe and I really loved a couple of years
back on this podcast. This is her followup. She's clearly got a much bigger budget.
This thing, I mean, it throws all kinds of influences in a blender while being completely
original. There's a lot of Brian DePalma to it. There's a lot of Dave Cronenberg to it.
It is so good. Basically the first third of it is a horror movie, uh, with some amazing
kill scenes in it. And I was like, okay, this is a horror movie. I didn't realize
that it becomes something completely different and really kind of a beautiful allegory for
the trans movement, which is not said in any way explicitly, but that's definitely how I took it.
And I think how you're supposed to kind of take it. Um, it is a movie so crazy. It involves a woman
actually having sexual intercourse with a car. Um, and then, you know, kind of having a
mechanic half mechanical, uh, offspring type situation. I don't want to spoil too much of
the movie. Um, but I, and, and also talking about it might make you go, well, that sounds
stupid. I'm not going to watch that, but it's one you should sit down, maybe get a little stoned,
but turn the lights off, turn the sound up. It's got an incredible soundtrack, an incredible sound
mix, incredible visuals. Um, I just absolutely loved it. It's, it was this year's Mandy for me
kind of, um, except it's a better written movie. And this Julia du Cornell is definitely a filmmaker
that I'll be watching for a long time because this is a big step up. I think even from raw,
which I loved, uh, and it is on Hulu as of, I think yesterday. So there's no excuse. Check
out titane. I got to see it. Yeah. My number one wrath of man. Whoa. Whoa. God damn it. Did I love
wrath of band? I did too. I did too. Oh my God. I love this movie. I just, it's the first time I've
cheered in a movie theater in a very long time. I saw this movie on a date. Uh, we were both
cheering at the end of the movie when Statham picks up the gun and he realized he's going to
kill everybody. When he comes, when he pops up in a Eastwood juniors, uh, apartment at the end of
the film, uh, it was Guy Ritchie doing what he does best. He's, he's sort of been out of the loop
in my opinion for a little while. He, he had a strange comeback with, um, Sherlock Holmes,
but, uh, you know, I wasn't too into those movies, but yeah. Uh, he, uh, I just love this. I loved
seeing Richie and Statham working together again. I thought that it did, it gave you everything that
a John Wick gave you except with, in my opinion, a much more grounded story. And they, they, they
rationed it out beautifully. It wasn't fight after fight after fight after fight after fight.
It wasn't a one man killing machine who somehow is, is immortal. It was, no, this is a real guy.
He knows how to do this. Uh, and we're going to make you wait for him to do it, but when he does
it, Ooh, you're going to be excited. And that's how it was. I just thought it was an awesome movie.
Uh, I, it is a remake, I believe if I'm not mistaken, but it just reminded me of those
late 1970s, uh, sort of almost grind house, um, you know, revenge movies and, you know, the, like
we go back to the original sort of death wish or stuff like that, the style of the way this was
shot and the grittiness of it and the simplicity of the story. And it just was, it was the type
of movie I don't think we've seen in a long time. And I think it's the type of movie that started
to get a bad rap because, you know, the, the, the, the films like Cobra or, or some of the
Schwarzenegger pictures from the eighties started to make these types of movies seem a little
cheeky, a little stupid, a little corny, whatever you want to call it. But if you go back to the
influenced those movies, like the original walking tall, and in fact, the remake of walking tall
with the rock is awesome too. Um, but that's, it's that kind of movie. Um, it was just fucking
awesome. I loved it. I loved it. I loved it. I also loved wrath of man. Didn't make my list,
but, uh, I think the movie was stolen by its villain, Scott Eastwood. First time I saw him
I was like, holy shit, this guy's as good as his dad. But, um, yeah, I, I love wrath of man too.
I had a couple of, uh, you know, my honorable mentions are get back. I couldn't decide where
to put it. I know Joe has no interest in a 10 hour Beatles documentary, but for me to watch
that century's greatest musicians, I know Joe disagree, uh, sit and sit and hang out with
other and come up with songs on the fly and argue and bitch and all this. I just thought
it was an amazing experience that I almost don't qualify as a, as a movie or a TV show.
It was just an experience. And I thought it was an amazing one, almost like going to a museum or
something. Uh, Coda on Apple TV got nominated for best picture somehow. I mean, it feels like the
best Disney channel movie ever made. Uh, it's about a girl with an entirely deaf family who
wants to go to a music school. However, if you watch this thing and you aren't crying at the end,
I don't really want to know you. It's a, it's a really great tearjerker and one you can watch
with your family. Uh, pig, I gave a second watch because everyone loved it and I love Nicholas
Cage and I couldn't get in there with it until a second viewing where I still didn't love it.
But Nick Cage is excellent. I thought he wasn't, but that's really, I missed the first scene when
I saw it in theaters and the first scene wound up being very important. Um, Annette batshit movie
that if you told me you hated it, I would completely understand, but I really thought
was impressive with Adam Driver. Nobody with Odenkirk was my sort of wrath of man. I loved
it with Chris Lloyd stealing the show. And, uh, yeah, there's a bunch of other ones I thought
were fine, but all in all kind of a rough year for the films. My two honorables are, uh, the
produced nightbooks, uh, for Netflix. I love it. Uh, you know, look, it's a kid's horror movie
about a kid that gets, uh, kidnapped basically by a witch and stuck in her magical apartment.
And it does a play on sort of Hansel and Gretel and it's a lot of fun. If I had seen this when
I was 11, it would have made my life. Uh, so I have a great appreciation for dark children's,
uh, horror. I think it's a lot of fun and this movie was no exception. And then also I was a
Tammy Fay, which I know we've already praised on the show, but, uh, just a great, it was just great.
I just thought it was a great biopic and biopics are hard to do correctly as we all know. In fact,
the trailer for this Elvis movie looks ridiculous. It looks ridiculous. Why does it look like he's
wearing eyeliner through the whole thing? Because it's Baz Luhrmann, the guy who did
Moulin Rouge and all that. The, it has five writers credited for the screenplay and two of
the writers are Baz Luhrmann. Why is he credited twice? And everyone was trying to figure that out.
Apparently they shot two scripts at the same time because they were so not confident
in what they wanted to do. And he gets credit for both of them. I've never, it's never happened
before. And it's enough already with the Tom Hanks. I've had enough. It's just, you know,
it's enough. Now he's got to do these roles. I agree with you, but him and McDormand,
I've had enough of both of you. And it's somebody else's turn. And he's got to do these roles now
where he's putting on a fat suit and doing like, you know, it's, he's attracted to the roles at
this point by whatever accent he gets to do. Like, oh, here's one I've never tried. Right. Yeah. Oh,
who cares? Upcoming movies in 2022 that I'm looking forward to that I thought would be nice to just
make note of that will probably some of these end up reviewing on here. Curious about the Batman,
not excited, but I'm curious. I want to see what they do with this. I'm getting a little worried
that they keep focusing on how brooding and sad Bruce Wayne is. Yeah. When they were, when they
released Bruce Wayne's like driving playlist, I was like, all right guys, what are we doing here?
The movie I'm most excited about right now, which we already talked about reviewing
off air is The Cursed, which came out yesterday. Classic horror, period piece, gothic horror,
practical effects, werewolf movie. I can't wait to see this thing. I'm really,
really excited to see that. So we'll have a review of that coming up soon.
God, I'm looking at a list here. Godfather 50th anniversary. How many times are they going to
release these fucking movies? I've seen Godfather in theaters three times in my life at completely
different periods because it was a re -release. I mean, did you hear, by the way, speaking of
new psycho, Francis Ford Coppola is putting $120 million of his own money into making this big
metropolis style sci -fi epic he wants to do. He's 80 years old. God bless. I said, Matt McCarthy
sent me that, and I was like, you know who I bet doesn't love that announcement? His children.
I bet they're on the group text like, God damn it, because Coppola hasn't had a hit in 30 years.
Yeah, no, I know. It's just not, yeah, that's a bummer. But hey, I'm excited to hear it.
The Unbearable Weight of Massive Talent is another interesting movie.
Written by a big friend. Can't wait to see it. What else is coming out? This Firestarter remake.
I'm curious to see that. That's all I got right now. Jurassic World Dominion couldn't give two
shits. I probably won't see it. I'm done. I mean, talk about a trailer, too, where they give
everything away. I haven't seen the trailer yet, but, dude, the trailer, every big moment is in
the trailer. It's crazy. They show Goldblum. They show Sam, what's his face, and Laura Dern
reuniting for the first time. They show the reveal, the Tyrannosaurus Rex. They show the entire crew
together, which is clearly at the end of the movie. They show everything. There's like, you
know how every modern trailer now does the thing where it goes, where it ends, and then there's
two seconds of black, and then something crazy happens. They do that literally three times in
the trailer. They're pushing it so hard. Do they do the slowed down cover of Everybody Walk the
Dinosaur? Yeah, yeah. Nope, I'm excited about. I want to see what Nope does. I thought the trailer
was great for that. I guess that's it. That's pretty much it. Salem's Lot, September 9th,
2022. I'm very excited for that. Who's doing it? How did Mike Flanagan not do that? I think it's,
I'm afraid because I think it's the it guys, but you know, we'll see. I don't think they're
incompetent. I just don't think that movie worked, but yeah, and I forgot Dern, and then we're all
coming back. I'll see the new Jurassic Fine. I won't. Jurassic Fine? No, Jurassic Fine. I will
not be seeing it. Another sequel I will not be seeing is Creed 3. Oh, you got to see. You know,
you're going to see Creed. I hated Creed 2. It sucks. And Creed 3 doesn't even have Stallone.
Where are we at at this point? It's like, guys, you know, it's it's most I've heard it mostly
focuses on the ghost of Adrian. Then December, the movie I'm least excited about for the entire
year is the December 21st release of Super Mario Brothers. Animated? Yes. Yeah. With Chris Pine
voicing the Italian general instead of the guy that's made famous. Right. Yeah. For the last
30 years in the video games. Anyway, folks, that's our show. We'll see you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.