Welcome to we'll see you in hell folks we got a rare
rare occasion here I am sitting directly across from Patrick Walsh not a
computer or a zoom screen between us we are in person in the flash in my living
room and brother we are living Joe it's great to see you. Pat as I approached Pat's
Malaysian state today real who was the guy who was the aviator Howard you real
Howard Hughes thing I went to the front door I rang because I love the jars of
piss I have lying on the bars of piss yeah I rang the bell you didn't answer
then I texted to Pat I said I'm at the your gate thing here your door yeah he
said go to the garage like like we were meeting in secret walked around to
this he's got a very big garage door and ominously it just lifted like
Jabba's palace door in return to the Jedi and I lived it because I have a
switch here on the chair I sit in that that raises the door I don't actually go
to the garage door and you got the Matt Lauer lock on the back to nobody gets
out well as I've discussed in the show the previous owner had a stalker so there's
like a big privacy hedge that obviously grows with each passing year and now
it's you know even with trimming it's just it makes me look like I live in a
fortress sort of and the bell that you rang does not work if I were to get it
set up again I would have to have a landline for some reason it connects to the
landline and I would rather the one person a month who comes to my house just
text me I'm here okay I would and handle a light ribbing about the aviator my
my my thing is I have some OCD me to knowing that the thing didn't work would
bother me it would be like the one thing in the house that's not perfect and I
would I would get a landline just for that and then I'd never use it Joe I did
that I've been here 10 years so I've already done that I did it for a year
then they called them were like hey you're you're bundling packages up so now
your $99 bill will be $499 right and I was like no I'll just cut the the landline
and moved on with my life I didn't miss it the only time I miss is when I
haven't had a party in years but that is annoying or a poker night you know but
you leave a door open yeah it's not a big deal the it's not a big deal those
bundles man you know they get you and you go yeah it's a year and then you put
it in your phone I'll remember a year later phone pops up in your thing it just
says the word phone you're walking down the street you're like what the fuck does
that mean back in your pocket never cancel it like mom's birthday every year
morning of the text from dad comes through you know it's mom's brush shit shut up
of course I remember then that it clicks to midnight you've forgotten I called
one year wish my dad a happy birthday because it's not today and you're a
weak late I was like well all right it's what he deserves and yet I felt sort
of bad about it is my nephew's birthday on Friday and I texted him because I was
in the city he's in with the Navy and I said hey buddy you know I'm in town
today and it's your birthday can I'm I'm I seeing you at the show you coming
through yeah he said I wanted to see you but I'm on restriction and I'm not allowed
to leave the ship for 30 days hello well and I said is that like a punishment or
is that just how it works in the Navy yeah and he said it's a punishment and it's
what happens when you talk back to the slimy mother fuckers right wouldn't be
texting that sergeant clinging off grab your phone look through it I enjoyed the
response kids got spunk right out of high school I went into the Navy the old Navy
right there you go and I bought a couple of fleeces some of the used to have that
bit I just joined the Army the Salvation Army like a bass drum you know something
now pet let me ask you a question and shoot me straight yeah are you very high
right now just slightly okay because you got the eyes going well no I I feared I'm
still on this three -hour jet lag from Atlanta and I feared I wouldn't bring the heat
if I didn't do I didn't have any alcohol in the house we can go grab something
but I just felt kind of low energy I drank some coffee right before you got
here we can do whatever between shows I I I don't have any problem with you being
high I just wanted to ask to confirm my my assumptions I mean I'm surprised you
noticed honestly but it's you got a nice dreamy eye going on you look very calm
and they enjoy in joyous not joyous that's content that's the word I'm looking
for joyous is too far yes it's good to see I was watching before you guys
suppose we could have watched it together but I was watching the latest curb and I
don't want to beat it up and do a whole episode about it but I'm three deep this
is fucking awful so the third one second we don't turn no corner it's it's not
been good so far no it's like grandpa and the gang at the retirement home put
on a show and they brought it to Thanksgiving put I mean it's I didn't know I
didn't know how sad it could be right there's a sadness it's that I've never
reached it's there's something there's something I don't know what it it it
feels like to me it feels like Star Wars Disney it's like all the faces are there
but something's off like because it feels like the people behind the scenes yeah now
Larry Charles hasn't been with the show for a very long time right but you know
Garland used to direct and there were certain and I feel like all of those people
are are not don't have their hands in it or something it also feels very it feels
very scripted it feels very directed like they're lost the looseness of the of
that docu spontaneity in it like the lines all feel just like people reading lines
it feels or it feels like maybe they did improv for a while and said okay these are
the best lines but there's none of that like the heat of the moment that's the
reason you watch the show no there's also like there's a there's a tiredness yeah
they they seem tired yeah like like Susie just seems like how many more
times can I call him a bald fuck like I'm tired like I have how many strange
dialogless women can Leon fuck he's 60 it's it's the way and the predicaments I texted you
this the other night the predicaments okay I'll give you a perfect curve your enthusiasm scenario
this is and be keep in mind he's playing a fictionalized version of Larry David but he is playing
the Larry David that has almost a billion dollars yeah a perfect scenario for curve for him
is an ethical conundrum the Palestinian chicken is the perfect episode because it's like
it's perfect whether you're rich whether you're poor the people are going to have the same feelings
and opinions about Israel and Palestine they can argue he loves the chicken his Jewish friends
are mad at him he's fucking the Palestinian woman like that's perfect this season every predicament
is something you could something that I could easily financially fix yeah let alone Larry David
then how come after 48 seasons of this show is he suddenly too delicate to break up with Tracy Olman
for fear of her relapsing he suddenly gives a shit I don't yeah I don't know she's awful I don't
remember why he liked her to begin with because of that thing the pool thing also to like there's
you know he did that storyline better yes with Vivica Fox cancer yeah because she had cancer that's
funny it's like stakes are higher yeah can't do a lesser you can rip yourself off and do a
higher version can't do a lesser version and also too this is another thing I don't like that the
newer seasons of the show have been doing they're having people come in and do sit -comy style
characters yeah like Vivica Fox played a very believable woman right JB smooth plays a believable type
of guy Jeff Garland is very believable these are grounded characters Cheryl Ted Danson
Tracy Olman running around with like a fucking Halloween adventure mole pasted to her face doing a
crazy voice and I will say they have had that they had Sheri Oteri and stuff in the past and people
Catherine O 'Hare and people doing really outrageous characters but they would be one -offs one and done
this is now two seasons of this Olman character but I'll tell you why the Oteri and Catherine O 'Hare
characters worked they're playing nuts they're playing crazy people they're and it felt like a normal
person who had an issue going on yeah Tracy Olman it's it's it's too like I love Tracy Olman it's too
sketchy yeah it's too sketchy um then literally Vince Vaughan is like a pal he just like pops in to offer
another perspective on the situation it's like you've got no better use for this man they gave him
nothing funny to do he's the him he's such a master of this and he comes in and he's like I don't know
I kind of agree with you that's like all he said have they addressed that funcowser is dead yet
I don't understand I don't understand why why are they not a drug this is why say it's like Disney
Star Wars it's like there's obvious things that they're just not do it's it guys address this yeah my
friendship and I talked at length they even said he's in China and they'd why is funcowser not
patient zero of covid yeah they had a whole season where they did covid jokes and didn't do that
would have been great he would have loved it from beyond the grave um yeah it's odd I assume they'll
have to do something on israel palestyle maybe bring that chicken back the thing the thing was shot
in the can before that happened you know I don't think they're going to also the touchiest subject on
earth um you know I hate well I guess she was only back for the first day that it's all very
disjointed why was there a wrap up of season last season in the first episode like they brought back
the that shitty story of the Hispanic actress who isn't funny on the show but it also doesn't translate
to funny in real life and then they now have a moka joe look alike that was DOA the second that plot
started and I'll make it to the end it's the end of the road but like I don't see this going in
any sort of positive direction I'm bummed this is the last thing I'll say and this is the the harshest
of the criticisms there's a uh uh uh uh there's a self aggrandizing thing around this is what I was
trying to say to you before the season started why wasn't high I didn't have high hopes I was like
he's too in on at this point yeah like not that he was never not in on it but like it used to be
when when this show was first popular Larry David would go on like Jimmy Kimmel right and Jimmy Kimmel
would be like so Larry like which which your story man do you date and you'd be like yeah yeah I date
you know like yeah and he was revealing himself to us everybody now you see these clips of him on
talk shows they'd the one clip was sort of viral where the lady said so and so I wanted to be here
but she couldn't because it was her daughter's birthday right and he's going come on who do you think
you're dealing with here and it's like he's now just playing the character of Larry David yeah and I'm
like it's when the pretty pretty pretty started becoming like a catch phrase as opposed to something
that happened yes it's too it's it's all too pleased yeah there's a great now did you so I
I didn't mind him attacking Elmo on the today show but did you happen to see Will Wheaton's response
no I can't imagine with Will Wheaton's absurdly woke response must have been to this this was sort
of a universally agreed upon funny thing Larry David's on the today show yeah got Elmo in the back
kind of like co -hosting yeah Larry goes back and beat some up he's like it was a long time coming
you know classic Larry did yeah the hosts are laughing yeah to joke of course and it's also a puppet
and you can go read it I mean he goes on and on about how now children won't feel safe
and someone who represents safety to them has now been attacked violently and they will
they they now think that when they get hit by their parents it's a joke and on okay and on and
so let me tell you what's going on Will Wheaton this might ruffle a few feathers sure I speak for myself
not for pat and myself I don't know I haven't seen him doing anything since stand by me to be honest
with you he was he was the king of woke to Twitter okay and then he got in trouble somebody by
forget what it was some you know some he was going after everybody in passing judgment and all
that bullshit virtual was signaling and everything and then he got in trouble for like somebody pulled
up some old tweets or so you know whatever classic thing he protest too much whatever
my guess is he's got a wife at home that he's real tap dancing for like really like
uh because that's always the the it's always the there's always somebody on the other side pushing
somebody when they're tap dancing this hard I'm not saying it's always a woman doing it I'm saying in
his scenario I think it's the wife that's my guess you know anything about the wife or you just
making something don't even know if he's married I'm making up a thing in my head but it's like bro
you got pinched leave it alone yeah stop yeah stop and why call more attention to yourself with this
absurd shit yeah nobody on earth was upset about Elmo getting punched yeah uh we'll eat in sucks
the half of the episodes of the muppet show that muppet gets punched by the host
it's it's it's it's of all of all the cast members of stand by me can you think of the one you care
about less than will we I'd rather listen to key for Sutherland scream racial slurs than will we
well then I've got a movie for you we're discussing on today's episode the last voyage of Demeter
and on next episode freeway which is where you will hear key for Sutherland say things you might be
shocked by last voyage of the Demeter we'll get to it obviously but I left my phone over there with
my movie corner stuff on it but I will also tell you that since I've been in LA I went down to
our precious amoeba uh everybody is very nice very very nice uh well I like it and they're fine now
yeah camera it's not the old space no son of a bitch of people aren't buying those t -shirts because I
was in there and I was like guys what is with all the t -shirt real estate in here you got so much you
cut your movie section into like a third and there's like two full rows of t -shirts but I gotta tell you
we're packed the t -shirt rows were packed I guess people buy them cheap to make I got some box set that
was very very fairly priced some it's called like dance it's dance macabre but it's but it's
the Italian pronunciation of that uh the name of the Steve King book no yes but it's a box set I think
Severin put it out it's for like gothic horror movies on Blu -ray uh and for some reason they had it
very very well priced under what it was going for used on eBay uh which you know felt like a little
bit of a win because of me but sometimes we've complained about the trade in situation why they're
generally selling shit for $20 above Amazon you're like fellas I'd love to help you out here
if you were even tan over I we could talk but yeah sometimes it's it's kind of wild yeah it's kind
of wild um anyway I went to me but uh I went to a wrestling show yesterday with Vince we're at ballet
down in downtown okay uh at Don Quixote uh holdy okay enough money take a event space of some kind
okay uh I got there Vince was already a few pops in sure he was very excited to get me caught up
okay I then proceeded to get very drunk with Vince uh I think by the way folks and it's been a while
for me I don't know about Joe but I think that's gonna happen tonight as well as a long night at
planned ahead uh I think so too I I need to I need to do like a month off or something because I'm
gonna get right myself right back into like high cholesterol zone and stuff I have been comfortably
off for a while I would like to let loose tonight and then just get right back on the horse because I've
been enjoying the mental piece it is nice to have the mental piece uh in the mental piece where I keep my
teeth of women I've killed as trophies of my uh sorry I've been watching these freeway movies which are
deeply depraved um but we'll get to them we'll get to them yeah we'll talk uh because I want to
hear in the next episode when we talk freeway I'm hoping you're gonna fill us in on the watch of freeway
two abs I watched the yesterday and um yeah they've got these new vinegar syndrome releases that had
like hours of footage I watched everything on freeway not so much on two but we'll get to we'll get to
let's go let's go to that corner you go first I gotta get my phone for sure I went I'm gonna
do a little theme this week I went to Quentin Tarantino's newly remodeled Vista theater always one of
the nicest most spacious coolest theaters here in LA now that he has taken it over they are mostly showing
what you'd expect uh dune the big movies but also his friends movies like Thanksgiving
and all this month he is doing a double feature fest just like at the New Beverly
IB prints which are sometimes actually not the best looking but since they're from his own personal
collection these were all pretty great so yesterday me and my buddy went we saw a double feature
and I had to shout out the cartoon before the double feature first one froggy evening long known as
one of the best of the looney tunes but I think it is truly and I am amazed I'm saying this because
of how much I love and think the looney tune characters are hilarious way funnier than the fucking
Disney character uh never never never have laughed once not maybe Donald maybe never nobody else they
it's a it's a shitbag Mickey and Minnie are zeros Pluto I mean goofies I like goopies vibe he's not
fine I fucking hate goofy I fucking hate it I I find it I find it yeah I can't stand it I duck tails
was where it was at for me but not funny just an enjoyable and launch pad McQuack I always thought John
Candy should have voiced launch pad maybe we got in some laughs but I'm also thinking of the rest
it was down under where he played that big bird seagull um so yeah one froggy evening is where we first
are introduced to the wb frog hello my baby hello my honey yeah so it is so beautifully constructed they
put these before the new Beverly an old looney tunes cartoon lately about a quarter of the time
somebody gets upset about racism um I think I talked about the speedy guns all is that they showed a white
man stood up in the back yelled racist walked out got the person the clerk and we heard at the door
opened him yelling at the clerk outside to stop it stop the screening of it so strange that a white
person was the one doing that not strange at all yeah yeah did he did somebody pat him on the back
they actually didn't turn it off they just kind of let it play but I hope someone blew him in the back
it's also like there was there's look at some of the anti -Japanese propaganda that was put out in
cartoons during the war oh yeah it's wild um but anyway there's no one that could be upset about one
froggy evening it's a guy who finds a frog um and the frog is a singer and the bit is funny throughout
the frog has this hilarious like opera type voice or vaudeville type voice but he only does it when
this guy is around when other people are there he doesn't so immediately the guy starts seeing
money he's got the dollar signs flashing around him and he's all excited but he buys this theater
and whenever he puts on the show the frog won't do the act uh then in the end this thing takes this turn
where he bottles it up and throws it it goes into the future 50 years someone in the future opens it
he comes out he's like hello my baby and the future man rubs his hands together and money starts
coming out right so it's like this weird commentary on how even decades later we still only will exploit
something beautiful and wonderful for money right it was just amazing like everybody in the theater was
kind of like in all of it okay and it was funny as hell so again it made me just think about how
anyone could like Disney shit over lunitons it's absurd Disney blows I'll tell you where Disney
Disney's got it locked down the witches cartoon witches nobody did it better than Disney oh
Disney movies you'll get no I mean there's almost no duds for a hundred years they had to
really great stuff but god damn man Disney Disney was always better at dark they weren't good at
funny yeah now that's true uh Emperor's new groove is about as close as they got to like laugh out loud
but I mean a daffy duck I mean it's just the guys a master will you check him and Roger rabbit
when I was a kid and I was like hold the the boys are all here we got daffy we got Donald we got
Betty Boop uh you see it in every scene they go head to head you're like one of these people is funny
the other has nothing to bring to the table the voices aren't even funny good news kind of funny go
what movie did you see well that was my first one one froggy evening oh okay I see I see what you're
doing all right I think my favorite looney tune of all time masterpiece uh I'm well hell speaking of
Will Wheaton I watched the curse not the show where Nathan for you does a thing that we can't tell
is if it's funny or exploitative uh you know he rolls this is probably his least exploited yeah but
uh it's definitely I kid uh I know I know but uh I watched the curse it's uh uh it is a rendition of
color from outer space the hp lovecraft story uh from the late eighties starring a young Will Wheaton
Billy Wheat uh also starring the kid who played Caesar in heaven help us uh I forget
the actor's name but he often plays well it's funny I always knew him as Caesar and heaven help us
and Caesar he's a nerdy kid who winds a lot and he's oh he's a big part of the comic relief him and
Matt him and Kevin Dylan's friction and Kevin Dylan picking on him is like one of the funniest things in
the whole movie right and then when I saw him in uh he plays one of the assholes in uh Christine
and I was like oh wow that's weird seeing Caesar be a asshole Keith we're done my Keith Gordon probably
right not Keith Gordon uh no Keith Gordon's not in heaven help us I thought he was Keith Gordon the guy
from wait wait who's Keith Gordon I don't think I know Keith Gordon's in in uh Christine I don't know
that he's in heaven help because I haven't seen it I could tell you let me just get the kid maybe he's
in the chocolate war I'm gonna get this kid's name oh not heaven is for real just came up
uh that a Bible movie oh these movies were a camera kid dies for five minutes comes back and says
he met all his ancestors oh that's one of those what what a what a typical story uh -huh Malcolm
denares the actor's name never heard him anyway so Malcolm denares and Christina plays one of the
assholes and it was weird when I saw that because I was like oh the it's Caesar but he's playing a prick
that's weird then I watched the curse and he plays a prick again and I was like wow it's the departure
is him playing Caesar not him playing a prick he's but he's done that more um directed by David Keith
strangely I didn't know David Keith directed stuff starring Will Wheaton are you
maybe confusing it with Keith David no no no David Keith the officer in a gentleman guy yeah uh who
else is in this thing Claude Atkins Acons uh John Schneider of the dukes of hazard sure who recently uh
went on a rant comparing Beyonce to a dog John Schneider did yeah he's lost his mind why would he do
that he's uh she shouldn't be stepping into country music she's a dog and dogs need to stay in the dog
house a peeing dog over new country is he saying is he saying you know a dog songs it's like it's
like a dog is peeing on the songs I don't like this version of it's like you know how dogs do they
got like if there's no there's nothing subtle about all right if he's a hero of yours uh I'm sorry
no John Schneider branded racist for comparing Beyonce to a dog there you go headline pretty much says it
all I mean I've never seen one minute of the dukes of hazard I've seen the film but uh it always
seemed very racist to me the show what in the hell is this guy thinking John what are you thinking
he's trying to do the thing where you go right wing and then you're suddenly one of the most famous
people at those rallies buddy he's with Scott Bae on the front lines you don't got to do it by saying
something that's going to destroy your career no he chose wrong all you got to do is just go on
Ben Shapiro I just do it a couple of appearances and you know whatever he chose wrong uh anyway the curse
uh about a meteorite that hits uh farm from uh outer space wait is the cover of this like it looks
like the moon has a face that's angry kind of now the cover is it was a classic video store cover
it's Will Wheaton's face uh then there's the house and there's like a claw coming out of the ground
grabbing the house it was a really great poster okay uh but uh meteorite hits this farm the meteorites
for outer space obviously uh the farm is struggling all of a sudden all the fruit starts going growing
in large quantities but it's all rotten the animals all start going crazy and becoming deformed the
people get infected it's going to spread through the community it's color out of space it's it's
it's identical almost to the version we saw with was it Nick Cage Nick Cage um you know but but a lot
more uh you know bare bones in the effects department but some great practical effects a fun enough
movie some some some truly scary like creepy moments um and that's the curse I mean it's a little
hard to come by it's not streaming anywhere I don't think it's you I don't think you can pay
to rent it I got the double DVD because I you can't even find the blu -ray I got the double DVD for Christmas
of the curse and the curse two which is called oh I gotta the cursing
curse curse harder no where is it come on guys the worst curse related works how was there not
oh there it is curse to the bite which is actually like them it's which is completely unrelated
yeah doesn't make the bite goes with curse but I like it's a movie about snakes that have been altered
in government experiments attacking okay and wouldn't you know Pat it stars Jamie far I've worked
extensively with Jamie far I he's a lovely man he seems like a nice guy you're just not expecting
Jamie far to be the lead of the curse to no I was not there's your curse movie uh first up
I saw a glorious 50th anniversary whatever around that time print of Sam Peckin Paul's masterpiece
the wild bunch um I have to name drop walking in we ran into Steve little who portrays
uh Kenny Powers best friend on the down and I had to tell him what a fan I was and he seemed
embarrassed by the role and then I realized that character was sort of mentally challenged and maybe
he tries to downplay it but he just didn't want to talk about it but he was very nice um anyway
well what do you mean he didn't want to talk about it he just when I was like I'm such a huge fan
it was there was like nothing in his eyes okay although maybe he's the kind of guy who probably
goes into a bar and people are like doing impressions of him and like I probably gets old well he might
just not um he might just not uh uh maybe he just doesn't think a compliment well true he wasn't
rude about it he just wanted to talk about the movies but um we're losing we're not losing you but
keep your mic when when it drops down it's we're losing your volume over here okay sure we don't
lose anything all right sorry uh the wild bunch Sam peckin paw to me is a guy where I like what he does
I've liked most of what I've seen of his some of his later stuff gets kind of shitty but he's always
idolized and especially growing up he was always held in the top regard top top filmmakers and I just
don't think he's got that classic the wild bunch is considered his masterpiece I've probably seen
it once every three years since I was a kid I never saw it it's never a big westerns guy
I love a good western and it's good um there's I just love the days when Ernest Borgnein was had a role
every movie had a role for Ernest Borgnein right yeah you know yeah he's in every movie for like a
50 year stretch even in the 90s he was in like down periscope and uh you know all these movies
yeah he was like an Oliver plat where he's just yeah all over everything other plat's great on the
bear in that um but yeah it's the wild bunch is great to see on a big screen it is known for basically
inventing action filmmaking as we know it which means a lot of slow not the first but really put
together a lot of slo -mo a lot of like what was happening with like Bonnie and Clyde uh
montages of like real extreme violence and it's just kind I mean it's a blast I love the movie
on letterbox I gave it like an a four and a half out of five stars that's what an a minus an a
it's a good it's a good it's yeah it's a really good western and I love everybody in it you know
it's one of those like the dirty dozen that a dad's love where you put together a big team you
know we got oceans eleven now but that used to be a it's own genre put together a big team of dudes
to go on a mission and um what can I say the wild bunch is a great western it's the seven samurai
it's the magnificent seven it's one of those but they're older the movies got a little more to say
because pack and paul was kind of near in the end of his career so it feels like one of those
sort of flagship what do you call that swan song a my way sonatras my way if you will all right um
and he's still you know had at least 15 years more of movies to come but how long is it
it's 220 it's amazing there was a time my life I would have thought that was insane
now it's like that's a treat well and I learned that it was 220 and released with an intermission
yeah how dare these modern day filmmakers yeah one of the one of the most famous and I'm embarrassed
I've never seen the wild budge but one of the most famous movies in American history yeah runs at
220 and these people are cranking out like you know fucking road trip movies with Robert Downey Jr.
clock it in a 235 or whatever it's like fuck off man it is not the movie we're talking about today
is a five -page story stretched to two hours when I put on that running when I put on the thing
and the timeline popped up and I saw this was an hour 58 I was like what why I asked that when it
ended as well yeah no I know um I only have one more uh it's devil in a blue dress oh I love that
movie with Denzel right Denzel Washington I've been on a real Denzel kick ever since rewatching training
day uh so I watched devil in a blue dress I'd never seen it uh I always got to confuse with
mo better blues when I was growing up that's a tough watch actually it's that's not a great movie
is Denzel in that yes okay just because of the word blue I got it confused and then the Denzel part
and they're only three years apart uh but uh devil in a blue dress is a uh a noir picture takes place
in the forties yes southern California Compton specifically uh it deals with the racial issues
that were happening at the time uh that's one aspect of it but uh the main crux or thrust the movie
is a woman has disappeared Denzel is a guy down in his luck who is hired to search for this woman
things get more sinister and threatening from there uh and it's a caper Don Cheetle at his best
he's great in everything but man does he really fantastic in this I was one of his first big ones
and he got a bunch of nominations for it um and the movie is basically the big Lebowski except
not funny but it's the same it's the same kind of thing like this guy who is down in his luck
needs some money gets roped into a caper that spider webs in all kinds of directions it all is sort of
centering around this missing girl it is very much you know when they always said that the big Lebowski
was like I think I forget was it Phil Marlow or whatever they you know so um cutters way is
another move it's from the 70s Jeff British is in it and I feel like they ripped off a lot they
used a lot of cutters way for big Lebowski as well okay so anyway uh devil and blue dress very good
film yeah uh Jennifer Beals Jennifer Beals yeah so uh check it out it's worth a watch and it's in
the criteria in collection 4k oh really yeah I did not know that um the other feature and this was
a long night of the theater last night was one eye jacks which was another two hours and 20 minutes
and a western so this was all told about five hours of western entertainment yesterday
that me and my buddy watched uh and one eye jacks is notable for being the only movie directed by
Marlon Brando and it was co -written by Marlon Brando and when I read about it he was basically like
you're expected to do something every second of the day from the moment you wake up people ask
your question like you didn't know what directing was and boy does it show this movie is also a
criteria on release I had never even opened it but I was always curious about it but I really think
the only reason it's hanging in there is the Brando connection Marlon Brando is real bad in this movie
he's doing this like barely there mumble type Nicholas Cage type performance where he's like
hey I'm a I'm a cowboy how are you what's he's just like you know he he acts by it's I don't know if
he thinks he's doing method acting or whatever he was doing at the time but he's so boring in it
it's like watching a guy who's asleep right you would never know that Marlon Brando was considered
some great actor by watching and what year is this again this is 61 oh jeez it's a couple if I
want to I think I'm right a couple years after like on the waterfront and it's also Carl Maldon who
is also in on the waterfront so you basically it's it's just a standard western it's one of like a
billion westerns have this plot there's a heist you know a bank robbery gone a rye Marlon Brando
gets captured the Carl Maldon character who's his mentor flees and allows him to be captured
then years later five years later he gets out of prison and he goes to track down Carl Maldon and
kill him okay he stays at Carl Maldons he falls in love with his daughter who appears to be about
thirteen there's a full there's a movie length romance between the two of them that had the theater
in his sterics and let's feel his I'm gonna look this up as you the girl look to be very very young
and he basically you're like is this guy gonna get revenge on Carl Maldon by fucking his daughter
he does he does fuck Carl Maldon's daughter but the movie is so badly put together and edited and
acted by Brando Maldon is great as always Carl Maldon's awesome in this movie great villain
but Brando sucks he phones in everything else there are shots in this movie where you're like
who told this guy like where to put the camera even it's it's so amateurish it feels like
when Dennis Hopper was making his movies post easy writer where he was just completely cracked out of
his mind sure it feels like a guy who had lost control and compared to the wild bunch I mean boy did
it suffer because the wild bunch is you know by this point it's it's kind of every action movie it's
like let's get some revenge let's get our boys together to do some revenge but man it still works like
gangbusters one hijacks in my opinion does not work at all it's got a 61 % on rotten tomatoes so not
not well reviewed it's got a 72 % audience score but but I guess well reviewed enough that it would
make sense that Tarantino likes it and put it with this I guess yeah I mean also he doesn't always
program them you know it's not necessarily true that he picked this one but I've just it's one of
those that's gotten a reappraisal in recent years obviously criteria and put it out it just you
know unless you're interested in the novelty of of Brando's directorial directorial debut then you can
watch him all right well yeah one more no I only have two okay because then I gotta save the other
two for the next episode I thought I had well we might end up doing American fiction so I'm not
gonna do that uh in case we do I'll save that uh let's uh talk what's Demeter you the last
voyage of Demetri Martin it's a movie about a man the comedian trapped on a boat with a bunch of
sailors and he draws pictures to amuse them remember when he they tried to make him a movie star he
was in that ang Lee like finding Woodstock or taking Woodstock I've always liked Demetri's always been
nice to me I don't know if anything bad to say about him but he is there okay there are a few fall
downs funny or to me then that than that one because it was immediate it was ang Lee following yeah
crouching tiger hidden dragon was it maybe you follow and broke back I don't know or something big
he was doing Hulk he was yeah I mean the guy was like this was the guy and they go Demetri good he's
making a movie you're gonna star in it yeah about the biggest movie event a music event that's ever
happened in history Woodstock and it's just like we can't miss you know and I saw that in the theater
woo not a good film and not a good not a strong presence in the film I must say wasn't somebody else
wasn't it weirdly cast where like there was like a bunch of comedians in it or something that sounds
right let me look it up because what a movie what a time like Andy Kindler was in it playing
Jimmy Hendrix or something playing probably here we'll look remember oh David Cross played that's
what it was but that was in a different movie he played who's the guy who's like the Alan not
Alan Dershowitz but he was like part of Lenny Bruce's camp we're talking about the same person
I don't know that's Paul Dana and Meal Hirsch Lee F. Schreiber Dan Fogler
real who's who at the time those were all up in commerce at the time Paul Dana was still just the
other kid in the girl next door that's right I love the girl I love that right to buy a friend of mine
Josh Safty was in it there you go right I didn't always been at it that long anyway the last voyage of
Demeter this is a based on the captain's log from the book the novel Dracula as you said there's a
five page captain's log in the in the copula version this is when you see the ship show up and it rocks
on the waves and you see Dracula awakened in blood sitting the sails and basically this boat that
Dracula needed to take from Transylvania to England he rises at night and murders all of the crew and
feasts on them so he can live and then that's it so and that's the the spec script so that that means
somebody wrote it just like nobody asked them to they just wrote it for fun to hope to sell it but
was written by this guy I get his name here shut junior something sh braggie shut junior
he befriended a guy who worked on bram stoker's Dracula and he wrote a spec he was like what a great
spin off of this hit movie but it didn't happen languished in development hell for 20 years
Jesus Christ this fucking business amblin entertainment I would have been awesome if it was an
actual it was going to be like a spin off of bram stoker's with like practical effects and the whole
Gary oldman hopefully hopefully uh amblin entertainment Steven Spielberg's company obtained the rights
in October 2019 and they said the guy who did it Andre over a doll who did scary stories telling
the dark and other things uh was directing so that's what happened but shut junior found a
miniature of the demeter set used for bram stoker's Dracula and began writing an alien inspired film
set aboard the ship um so at some point I'm just going through the little bit of the history on it
uh the screenwriter of bram stoker's Dracula took it back on in 2006 and turned in his own draft
of the script they got the same guy who wrote it okay after that Marcus Nispell stepped in when he
got thrown off Nispell did the remake of Texas James on that uh which which won the uh let me see
by the way neither were we wait wait he did the remake or one of the two failed sequels he did the one
with Jessica Beal that's the remake that's not bad he also did the fright of the 13th remake okay
the that guy does some solid stuff he was gonna do it so he was the replacement of the guy who had written
written bram stokers then due to complications adapting the period setting and filming on the water
uh so I guess they didn't couldn't decide what period to do it in Nispell left
then new me repaced the girl in the dry girl with a dragon tattoo was doing it she was attached
Ben Kingsley was playing the captain this was like 10 20 10 10 15 years ago uh then everybody left
went on to do another movie called dead fall which I'm not familiar with david slayed came on board
who did like 30 days of night okay which I liked a lot actually 30 days of night is great
Jude law was announced as the star of the film in the 2010s uh david slayed he said the film still
gonna happen but I'm going off to do daredevil the bent aflight yes people just misfiring left and right on
this thing be joe mordanson was attached to play the captain ben Kingsley still attached
at this point girl with a dragon tattoo dropped out in december 2014 um when Andre overdol came
on board that's where some of the old drafts were dusted off they wound up using a lot of the
original drafts of the script um and then in reading this Wikipedia page it sounds very contentious
because the team that did the practical makeup effects said we interacted so little on set I showed
them what we had I gave them scans of our sculptures they took photos of the eyeballs they scanned
everybody on set but for the rest of it we weren't really involved with each other which is a real shame
and it's just like we're two departments working on the same film and they're just saying
not because of any conflict not because of any anger we weren't even in contact with each other
and they're like that's why the movie kind of feels just jointed and it does uh the movie overall
and we'll get into the details obviously it's not bad it's just fine uh clearly a lot of money
went into it they shot a true period piece here lost a lot of money it lost a lot of money
but somehow it still feels cheap it has that made in Canada vibe to it you know it's giving sci -fi
original it's giving like uh to be original yeah it's giving 90s direct to video but it's all very
authentic and it's all very practical and so I don't understand what it is that makes it feel cheap
there's just something not right uh the cast is very good uh I'm a big fan of the of the main guy the
kid that played Dr. Dre and straight out of Compton he's great uh you got the other guy that played
polka dot man in suicide squad demolition yeah he's very good uh everybody's very good everybody
delivers in their roles and I believe that this is a crew from from a victorian or whatever it is
England Corey Hawkins is the gentleman Corey Hawkins yeah you know I believe that all this is real
and the Dracula design is quite scary it is very much based on it's it's it's it's it's basically a direct
replica of the Selam's lot Toby Hooper Dracula um or vampire um it's got everything in place it just
doesn't come together in the way you need it to there my first gripe is it's got this cool ominous
text on screen at the beginning and it says the the the the the the the the Demeter
arrive in 18 whatever the Demeter arrived at port with it with with all of its crew missing it's written
almost derelict yeah yeah boat arrived derelict yeah it's written almost like it's this true historical
account right and then it says taken from the captain's log from the novel Dracula it's like don't
put the novel part Joe I thought the same thing I paused it because I was like what are you even
trying to say and I'm like if I'm this confused off the bat that really annoyed me I was like
based on the captain's log from the book like what what yeah I say at the end if you want if
you have to based on the proportion of the novel Dracula we know yeah yeah so that's the first misstep
the second misstep in my opinion yes and again I'm not I'm not doing a male gaze thing here I
swear to you I'm not but they were but where were the tits they were so desperate to get a woman
into this movie yeah they they shoehorn in this ridiculous fucking plot that there's a woman that
Dracula like for whatever reason was like gonna feed on her or what it was like I'll say you had
on some leftovers yeah yeah it literally was like Dracula packed sandwiches for the trip even though
they're like Drac they've got food on the boat he's like no no no I want to just in case he's
did blood oh Drac they patty the the ever he stows a woman away in one of these crates yeah who
they discover and clearly she's already been now here's the thing she's got to be bitten why
because she couldn't survive living in dirt otherwise right but we can't have her just be a vampire
like everybody else he bites who immediately turns yes so they do this half -ass thing where Corey
his character somehow knows how to do a blood transfusion there are a lot of blood transfusions
in the film way more than you'd think and he's like all you got to do is get all the we got to she's
they don't know what she's infected with yet they just think she's sick and he says I have to get all
the infected blood out and do transfusions until she has clean blood that's literally like taking
somebody that has cancer of the blood and saying if you just transfuse until the cancer blood's gone
they'll be fine it's like that's not how this works yeah so so it's just such a half -cocked
bullshit ass way for them to just have a female character yeah in a situation where they're never
in a million years would have been a woman and you know what I would have rather them just had a
woman as part of the crew right who was like a little brassy a little burly yeah and have some
character go I ain't work it with no woman or whatever right and they go yeah Susie's good people she's
strong in the arms or whatever and yeah okay they already do they have the guy go well if this
docky dockto wants to get involved yes like okay they do acknowledge the time period for that yes
they do yeah but they don't and and and they do that actually well because when the guy says that
uh the the character the Corey's playing he goes he goes say it again yeah and it's great
because it's this great moment where you're like thank you for recognizing the sweet he is a doctor
I miss that part I believe so well I kept thinking of the Nick the Nick is a one of my all -time
favorite television shows Steven Soderbergh directed it it stars Clive Owen as a direct uh sorry a
doctor in Victorian England who is addicted to opium and does all sorts of insane shit with patients
it's an amazing ship beautifully directed and this movie gave me similar vibes because it also has
a black doctor at a time where that seems unusual uh it wasn't happening there was a lot of racism
you know and that I liked the way they they look I a hundred percent don't need every period piece
that involves non -white actors in it yeah to have some sort of torturous pain storyline or whatever
about the the struggle of the racial I don't need that but I a quick beat just right it's very quick
I like that the the character sticks up for himself uh it almost accounts and here's my biggest
issue with the movie it counts as one of the only moments of character development in the film there
is nothing yes that's what I was gonna say it's it's it's it's there's there it is a great moment for
that in particular the the doctor character um but you're right now that you say it there is no
character development through these it's just people and you disagreeing with one another
and not even in an exciting manner really like that if you're gonna just look at a five -page book
that you're turning into a two -hour movie you would imagine that they would have to add a lot of
characterization but there's not I don't get this this okay so let's get into the link thing yes
wouldn't Dracula just sort of rise up and kill everybody all at once and then just go back to sleep
like they've kind of established yeah that Dracula does not need to feed like every single day
right why does Dracula just they have a lot of livestock on board for the so they could kill it
to cook it yeah which actually is a kind of cool little commentary that they're feeding on the blood
of live things you know to survive or whatever but why would Dracula kill all the animals wouldn't
he wouldn't why wouldn't he because he clearly wants the crew alive when he's feasting on them and
not dead also why would Dracula turn some of them into other vampires instead of just feeding on
them what does that gain for him then he runs the risk of them attacking other people and killing the
other people which they try to do which would ruin his meals yeah and his meal plan there's just a lot
of stuff they do to stretch out this story and they just don't go far enough in any direction with it
they just don't go far enough they do address the female thing where they say she's a stowaway yeah
but we're gonna well they they say she's a stowaway we're gonna throw into the waves and then the
captain says no even though they make clear that that's literally what they do every single time they
have a stowaway but he's making an exception just this once when there's a vampire on the loose so
you know they went for it with the kid at least at least they turned the little the kid gets
fucking whack yeah yeah the kid kids generally are safe in a horror movie for the most part and it was
kind of good to see a kid get chomped but it is the vibes are sort of fun the vibes even like the
font they use give it like this Disney horror movie vibe like I never saw either version of the
haunted mansion but it's kind of got that vibe but then some r -rated gore as well which is a weird mix
sort of how scary movie scary story still in the dark was where it's like violent but seems like it's
also sort of designed for families this is how it felt to me was this rated R who's rated R um I
just yeah ultimately I it becomes a slasher sort of it just becomes like a Friday the 13th or something
where it's just Dracula killing person after person and when you don't know anything about them or
care about them it's a pretty standard problem with horror it's hard to get that invested in the story
so then I'm as I'm watching this thing yes I'm saying to myself they're not going to kill
Corey's character yeah for two reasons they think they're not going to kill the one black dude
right because that's not going to look good on them yeah filmmakers and also they're not going to kill
the main character because god forbid they don't leave the door open for a fucking sequel that wouldn't
be that interesting anyway because the whole point is this ride and of course Corey ends up on a
plank in the ocean and drifts ashore and lives and then sees Dracula in a bar literally literally it's
like the end of the the dark night rises or whatever but it's like Dracula like in a in a hat
like just kind of chilling in the corner it's so ridiculous and then he vows he'll kill yeah to avenge
the the chip people yeah crew he'll kill who he did not seem particularly close to but now he's
gonna know one of them was racist to him not quite sure why he wants to imagine how like they're
never they'll never make that movie but imagine what they'd have to go back and tell you
here were the people on the ship that he kind of knew and now he's got a stand like fight for their
honor who cares uh yeah so so that's again a sequel nobody wants to see because the whole interesting
thing is the boat right nobody wants to see because by the way that's not what happens in the fucking
novel of Dracula guys they have to bring in van Helsing to kill Dracula why because he makes it to
shore on the fucking to meter and he kills everybody and nobody knows he's there and then he gets there
and they don't know what to do so they have to figure out how they're gonna kill this goddamn guy
there is no doctor from the boat that makes it into the book and then joins the team but I'm sure
they were thinking well we'll go comic book style and do a variation of this and yeah he'll now be
one of the he'll be maybe he is van Helsing or something I don't know because van Helsing's a doctor
so I don't fucking know but again a sequel nobody gives a shit about uh and and won't get made
now because this movie lost 25 million dollars at the box office yeah it just doesn't have enough
of its own flavor there's just something too generic about it to buy the numbers about it
um and at a certain point you're just watching Dracula but jump into people you know it's it's so close
to being great it's so close to the box and we're fun I was into the vibes yeah it feels like a classic
gothic heart this movie I kept saying if they made this movie in the late 70s uh with hammer studios it
would oh yeah yeah awesome it's amazing well maybe it's been made and I just don't know about it but I
don't think so it's kind of amazing it never was since they made eight million Dracula's um if it
would have been made when it was originally supposed to be made as a spinoff of the bram stoker it
would have been awesome if they would have just made this they could have made this still a spinoff
yeah it just did the makeup of the bat form of the Gary Oldman Dracula and you'd be like that's
the same Dracula we'd also all these kills there'd be something to them they'd have a heart and soul
in them you know these kills all feel like watching uh uh a screen saver you know why they switched it
from I promise you why they switched it from being a spinoff not because they said well this guy's
not in bram stoker's Dracula and we have to have him live so we can make more of these yeah so we
so it can no longer be connected to that it now has to be its own thing yeah uh so I mean there you are
scary stories to tell in the dark is a movie that you know some people think is okay it's I'm very
fond of it a lot of that has to do with my closest to the books growing up but I will say scary stories
has a tremendous amount of spirit in it the second that movie starts you feel like it's Halloween
it feels like Halloween yeah the girl the the backstory with the family and the dad and her mom being
gone and and there another movie that deals with the character in a in a time period where where his
ethnicity was not accepted because you got the Hispanic kid that comes in
and they deal with it just enough that you give a shit but they don't they don't make it his you
know his plight throughout the movie but they somehow address it and address his character as a whole
better uh address every character as a whole better every kid in that movie you care about you know
like the kid getting all mad about his spider costume being fucked up you know like they just give
you something to sink your teeth into with those characters and you care yeah and in this it's just
that you again you kind to get it with the main character you don't get it with anybody else
and you're you know you're on a boat for movies on a boat are tough
I love master and commander I love DOS boot you know there's definitely some I love what I would
really really recommend if you want an awesome horror thing on a boat similar vibes but done so much
better check out the first season of the terror on AMC my dad I love that show and they put it on
shutter and I watched that in like one day it is so good I did not watch too with George
to Kai in a Japanese internment camp I was like it seems like you're waiting a little heavier
direction for CZ2 boys but um I'd check out the terror if you if you want some boat horror in your life
this one is by the way I think we're both saying average average you know hog straight out
not down not up yeah perfectly passable Sunday afternoon yeah you know maybe you've maybe a dose
off maybe you wake back up you you go in the other room you're listening one of those kind of movies
yeah exactly and also if you want some boat horror check out ghost
shit I'm kidding everything go I have to go shit that was terrible it's terrible movie
if yeah and also if you want some here's a better version of the other also if you want some
boat horror check out out to see starring Jack Levin and Walter Mathau book a carnival cruise with my
ex wife no I can't do that anymore I actually have an ex wife I'm sure a carnival cruise but
there would have been a lot of fun folks can't do my old jokes we'll be back in the next episode with
freeway joderosa .com for all tickets to all upcoming shows uh march salsa windfall is doing shows
at the old south by southwest festival I'll be there also doing the sandwich summit it's under a new
name this year we're renaming it because it's covering more than just sandwiches but I'll be
there folks and I want to see if that's called sandwich and porn summit yes yeah and then off from
there I go to Seattle and I go to Portland in March come out to those shows please I'll see you out on
the road and if you're New York hit Joey roses Joey roses .com I'm on instagram at the Patrick Walsh
the show is on instagram at see you in hell pod posting funny clips and little bits and old past
glories and etc um we will be back with a discussion of freeway which was recently featured on joe
Bob sort of a cult HBO classic from back in the day uh we will see you next time and we'll see you in hell