I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell
And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say
I'll see you in hell, you know I will
Folks, we'll see you in hell back again with a very special episode
What Makes Us Cry
What Makes Us Tick
You make a grown man cry
What's that?
You know that song?
Brown Sugar?
That's Start Me Up
Oh yeah, that's right.
God, I really hate their music.
Really?
I mean, look, they've got some of the most overplayed songs of all time, but I think they have many a great album.
I've tried, I just don't care. I just don't enjoy it.
I'm not saying they suck, it's just not for me, and there's something about them that really annoys me.
I can't put my finger on it.
I mean, I feel like they've, aside from touring for 50 years, I don't think they do anything that could annoy anyone.
You mean him prancing around on stage making the goose motion?
Yeah, yeah, you know.
He's also, yeah, I just, I don't know.
I just, I don't know.
Fair enough.
They bug me, and it bugs me that they get this pass when they've done the same awful shit that all these other people that get in trouble have done.
They've done worse.
You mean cultural appropriation?
It's all kinds of stuff.
Anyway, that's not what we're here to talk about.
We're here to talk about the movies that make us weep.
Five movies each from each of us, from both of us.
Five movies each.
The films that make us cry.
Ideally, a movie that makes you cry every time you see it.
Maybe even a movie that if you think hard enough about the scene, you could drum up some emotion on a sad day.
And we haven't discussed each other's list.
I imagine there might be some overlap.
But let's see.
Joe, would you like to kick us off?
I'm going in no particular order.
Did you numeric arise yours?
No, no order.
But I will throw out two quick honorable mentions that I'm not going to discuss at length because we've already discussed at length.
Sure.
I was a blubbering mess during Elvis, but I haven't seen it enough times to say every time I see it.
I tried to decide when it was my life dependent caused the tears.
You know what I mean?
If it's just something that happened to hit me at a really stressful bad time and made me cry, I tried to not count those.
And I also am striking planes, trains, and automobiles because we've talked at length about the end and how it makes us cry every time.
So I wasn't going to bring that one up again.
I feel like we talk a lot about that movie.
Yeah, it's on my list, but I also have backups and I'm happy to knock it off.
I felt bad about doing it too because we've talked about it so much.
You know the parts that make you cry in that movie.
What I could add, if I never did talk about it, is that the first time I saw it, my dad let me watch it at age maybe 13 because I couldn't see our rate of movies, but he watched it and said it was OK.
And at the end of it, I said goodnight to my dad, very quickly walked into my room and cried for several hours.
All right.
I mean, it really affected me, as did, by the way, a movie I can't imagine ever making me cry nowadays, but The Breakfast Club.
My dad knew I loved John Hughes and watched The Breakfast Club with me, and that had the same effect.
I immediately went to my room and cried.
I don't know.
I was an emotional kid.
All right.
Fair enough.
I will kick us off with an obvious one for me.
Grumpy old man can't get can't get through it without crying.
Can't get through the part where Jack Lemmon has the heart attack is in the hospital.
He and he and Mathau are at odds throughout the entire movie in a funny way, but not in a cute way.
It's not like the odd couple like they truly hate each other in that movie.
And Mathau puts it all aside when he sees that Lemmon has fallen to the ground on Christmas Eve with a heart attack, comes to his aid, gets him to the hospital,
then goes to the hospital to be with him because he knows that he has, you know, his only family is his daughter and wants to make sure that he's not alone in the hospital because he's it's when it's when people put their differences aside to do the right thing.
So that gets me.
And then he's standing at the desk and the nurse says friend or family, sir.
And he doesn't know how to answer it.
And it kills me.
And then she goes friend or family and he says friend and is crying as he says friend.
I'm getting a little teary right now just thinking about it.
It's a wonderful movie.
I saw it probably three years ago, I want to say.
And then I saw it in the theater and I love the sequel too, actually, although it's much less emotional.
But can you refresh my memory why the two of them hate each other?
Is it that their son and daughter divorced or something?
No, their son and daughter have a crush on each other.
Darryl Hannah plays Jack Lemmon's daughter.
She's married to an asshole.
And Pollock. Yeah.
Oh, she's married to what's his face?
To Shooter McGavin.
Christopher McDonnell. I did not know that. OK.
Yeah. And he's like a dick.
He's like doing the thing he does.
He's always the dick. Always.
No, it's like him and Spader brushed his butt heads.
They must see each other.
He was on Biblically where he played my dad, essentially.
And I asked him about that after and he was like, you know, I don't know.
I don't really question it.
He's like, as long as I keep getting work, I'm fine with it.
He's like, but you know, I played Leave It to Beaver's dad once.
He's like, if that movie had made more than a nickel, maybe my career would have gone different.
He's like, but as of right now, I'm just the abusive piece of shit every time.
That's great. No.
So he plays Darryl's husband, Kevin Pollock plays Mathal's son, who's single and has a crush on it.
They hate each other because they had a they had a.
A feud over a woman.
And Lemon won and Lemon gets got her and married her.
But then they reveal that not just was the feud over a woman, but that the woman turned out to not be that great and wasn't really a great wife.
And and, you know, so Lemon is Lemon is very like, just get over it.
Like, I don't know what you think I won here.
Because in the movie, she's either dead or just long gone.
I can't remember. Right. And Mathal's like, fuck you.
Like, you know, he only sees it as who she was when they were young.
And and and then they're fighting over Anne Margaret.
Yeah. Then Anne Margaret comes in and they're already feuding.
But then that spark sparks the feud up again or heightens the feud, I should say.
Yeah. And then you get five minutes at the closing credits of Burgess Meredith making pussy jokes out the window.
Like the outtakes. It's so some of the greatest outtakes of all time.
Yeah, it's wild. It's a wild string of outtakes in that movie.
One of my hardest laughs ever.
And I don't I don't think it holds up current.
But for whatever reason, the first time I saw it, I laughed so hard at the very beginning when Walter Mathal was watching the news and the weatherman's talking about how cold it is.
Shut up, fat ass. Yeah. And it's clearly supposed to be Willard Scott.
Willard Scott. Yeah. The guy goes, fat ass. Yeah.
It's it's because the guy goes, it's going to be a cold one.
I bet they tried to get Willard Scott and he was like, he calls me a fat ass.
No, thanks. I'm good.
And everybody's had that moment when you live in a cold area and they're like new.
The weather guy is taking like an almost gleeful approach to telling you how awful it's going to be.
It's like the traffic guy going, hope you're not going anywhere today.
It is a parking lot. You want to strangle him. So I do that in Groundhog Day, too, with the wake up guys.
But it's it's I just rewatched and it's so funny how how much Bill Murray loathes hearing their voice every morning.
My favorite line, the line that makes me laugh the hardest is he talks about the guy that went over the bridge in his car.
As he's also talking about his son and Jack Lemmon goes, how is he?
He goes, he's dead. He died on impact.
And he goes, Jacob, moron, your son, Jacob.
How is he? Such a great like classic just miscommunication banter.
Funny bit. It's so fun. Such a funny movie, man. It's a great movie.
Are you a sequel fan of the sequel as well?
I don't like it as much because they I like it.
But they they they, you know, they really try the sequels missing a lot.
That's the the sequel just doesn't have the heart.
The first one has the second, the first one.
Dude, Ozzy Davis, the sequence where Ozzy Davis dies.
He's the he runs the bait shop like the first one just deals with the loss and in a very serious way.
Like Lemmon's going to lose his house because he's so in arrears with taxes.
Right. Like there's just so much stuff in the in the first one.
And Margaret representing both of them feeling like they have a second chance at life.
It's devastating that Mathau doesn't get her because like because of what it means.
You know, like right. The sequel is fun, but it just doesn't Burgess Meredith's character dies in the sequel.
But that's kind of the only part where you're like, oh, man.
Well, you know, and it's real. No woman would choose Walter Mathau over Jack Lemmon.
And what do you get Sophia Loren pulling out of that cup with your fingers right now?
I'm watching you. What are you doing?
I thought it was liquid that you were licking off your fingers.
I the explanation is it's too stupid.
I dropped a gummy vitamin into my coffee and now I'm scraping out the delicious vitamins.
All right. Got it. I didn't I didn't do it by by by purpose.
Is that the expression? No. On purpose.
I love grumpy old man.
And lately, I've been watching nothing but Jack Lemmon pictures after that saved the tiger.
I think that's I mean, not not not saying anything new here.
That's one of the greatest actors of all time.
For me. I'm going to shout out.
A movie I've shouted out on here before, too, but called about Schmidt.
About Schmidt is easily one of my favorite films.
It is often hilariously funny.
I think it is the best movie of Alexander Payne.
It was his follow up to sideways and actually a pretty decent little hit, which people forget.
This is a movie about Jack Nicholson being unable to connect with his daughter who is getting married.
And it made like a hundred million dollars.
Like, man, I yearn for these days again.
But it's Nicholson at his most restrained.
He plays a guy who has just been beaten down by life.
The opening scenes are very funny, just like him watching his wife, June Squibb, walk around.
And he's like, who is this woman?
Why is she in my house? Why does she smell bad?
You know, like it's really dark and really funny.
And he is he's as unlikable as he wasn't as good as it gets, except even more so because he's not charming in about Schmidt.
And as good as it gets, you you believe that he's that he could fuck Helen Hunt, even though he's 30 years older than her.
In this movie, he is just a sad, miserable old man.
He is very self -obsessed.
I. For me, like Joe said, two people putting aside their differences to come together.
That's a big tear jerking thing for me as well.
The biggest for me is a father and son shit, obviously, and be a previously stoic man getting hit with emotion.
A man who is completely closed off to the world, finally feeling some emotion and crying or making a connection to another person.
And this is to me is the ultimate example of that.
The movie goes along and is a at times even a kind of broad comedy like Dermot Mulroney's character is really funny.
But it's also a character you could find in like a Farrelly Brothers movie.
He's got a mullet and he's a complete hick and everything else.
But it's funny, funny, funny, funny for two hours.
And the entire time he is writing letters to a starving child in Ethiopia named Ndugu.
And these letters are also a source of high comedy throughout the entire movie.
So like when he wraps up a letter to Ndugu Ndugu, he's like, well, you probably want me to stop rambling on so you can head down to the bank and cash this check.
Get yourself something to eat like that.
They're really funny.
This thing, Dear Ndugu, and it's a recurring theme in the movie that makes you laugh every time you hear Dear Ndugu.
Now, at the end, Ndugu writes back.
He's never met this kid, has no ties to him, sends him a little picture like thank you so much for the money.
We love you.
You hear the translation of it by his teacher, who's this very sweet sounding African woman.
And it cuts over to Nicholson and he starts uncontrollably crying credits roll.
That to me is the best, the most impactful emotional ending in movie history to me.
That's just my own little personal quirk.
But it's so emotional to me.
This guy finally crying because someone appreciated him.
But it is someone who only likes him because they don't know him.
That's really the saddest part of about Schmidt.
This is a man who goes to his daughter's wedding, makes he doesn't he doesn't do what my dad did and make like a 45 minute embarrassing speech like you're expecting.
He makes a speech that suggests he doesn't know his daughter at all.
That's another really sad part of the movie is the speech isn't this big comedy point.
It's showing that he doesn't even know how to talk about his daughter because he doesn't know her.
But at the end, this stranger reaching out to him makes him cry.
I find that fascinating. I relate to that more than I wish I did.
And I think that that is a an incredible movie that more people should see.
All right.
Because it's sad on top of sad.
You're like, I love that this guy's feeling something, but I hate that he can't feel it with anyone except somebody he doesn't know.
It's a very complex ending.
Anyway, sure, I will.
Mine will go.
I guess I'll the order I'll go in is realistic to least realistic, meaning real life.
So so next on my list.
Well, I would have started with this.
But next on my list is is Malcolm X.
I find the movie it's in my top 10 movies of all time.
I still need to get this damn 4K, but, you know, God damn it.
I bought the fucking collector's edition blu ray that comes in like a storybook binder almost like.
And now I got a that's driving me nuts.
Anyway, the end of Malcolm X when he's assassinated and he knows he's going to be assassinated and played excellently by Denzel Washington throughout the film.
But particularly in the scene when the killer runs up to him, charges at him with the gun and he smiles because he's like, you know, I knew you were coming.
It's like almost like Christ moment, you know, where he knows the betrayal is coming.
And like, you know, it's just to beat the journey that Spike Lee takes you through in this movie.
It's it's a three hour film.
It's epic on the scale of The Godfather or, you know, or The Cotton Club, which is not considered a great movie, but it's certainly an epic one or Once Upon a Time in America, whatever.
It's just an epic, epic, epic film.
And it tells the story of this man's journey from being a street hustler to becoming reformed through religion in prison to becoming a tentpole of the five percent nation of Islam to having a racial awakening where he after has closed himself off from the idea of integrating with white people in America.
Well, I don't mean to say that to undercut his the reasons for his initial stance of not liking white people, given what he's been through in the history of his family and all that stuff, which is why it makes it so interesting when he redefines that and also redefines his role with the religion by leaving the nation of Islam.
All these things. It's just it's just it's just a piff.
It's it's evolution after evolution after evolution of this character or real life person, I should say, until you finally get to the to the end of the journey.
And he, I would argue, is the most fulfilled version of himself throughout this journey he's been on.
And it's it's cut short by an assassin, as so many luminous people's lives are, unfortunately.
And I'm just so invested.
And, you know, that's that's speaks leagues.
Denzel Washington is arguably my favorite actor.
I just love watching him so much, but it speaks leagues to his ability as an actor and Spike Lee's ability as a director that you can that that that this guy can carry this amount of movie.
It's incredible.
You know, I mentioned The Godfather.
Godfather is an ensemble cast and people do their job and do it very well.
This fucking movie is basically being carried by Denzel Washington.
It's just gargantuan.
And, you know, you fall in love.
And by the end of the movie, when he's assassinated, you realize what a loss it is, what a loss for humanity it is, how it reflects how stunted we are as people, what we always do in just callously shutting people down and shutting people off and and all this stuff.
It's just so tragic.
It kills me.
It destroys me every time I see it.
Yeah, I just rewatched it in 4K.
It's an amazing movie.
Obviously, I really recommend The Criterion 4K.
It looks beautiful.
But yeah, that the song, the Sam Cooke song.
Yeah, I was I was born by the river in a little tiny little world.
And yet I don't know the name.
Change gonna come.
Change is going to come.
Yeah.
Which is, by the way, the Easter egg, if you saw One Night in Miami, that's the song Sam Cooke writes because of the challenging the challenge he gets from Malcolm X saying you don't do anything with your platform to to to write.
You don't talk about the issues of our people and all that stuff.
And then that's the the song Sam Cooke wrote.
And then that's the song.
I didn't know that, you know, until I saw One Night in Miami, which was crazy.
Well, that that movie was made up, though.
That's one of many reasons I didn't care for that movie.
That's not a true story.
That movie.
But they but they did.
That gathering did take place.
And I mean, I don't know specifics, but I know that by and large that was invented.
But one of the first CDs I owned was 30 Greatest Hits of Sam Cooke.
And I used to listen to that song.
It's an impossible song really to listen to without feeling something.
But then combined with the journey you've been on and Denzel and the filmmaking and everything else.
Yeah, it's a it's a tearjerker for sure.
That's one of the great American songs.
No question.
For me, my next choice is going to be Manchester by the Sea.
Oh, boy.
It is hard for me to select a moment of Manchester by the Sea because I just sobbed uncontrollably pretty much start to finish.
I watch it around once a year, which is torture to myself.
I know.
But to me, there is no better.
Well, you know, yeah, maybe there is no better.
Expression on film of what it is like to live with depression.
The so obviously the turning point of the movie where Casey Affleck is drinking with his boys, his wife Michelle Williams tells them all to go home.
And then he walks up to the gas station, whatever he's doing fucked up while he is there.
A fire burns down his house and kills his children.
He has to live with that.
That is the cause of his depression and a cause for anyone to be depressed.
But watching him struggle and I love that they gave him that even though it's Kenneth Lonergan, one of the great writers ever.
I love that he gave him that that his kids died and that's why he's so depressed.
But the I think the reason the movie hits me and this is a very dark thing to say, but he feels this terrible and he's like starting fights and can't form relationships and he's lashing out and he's not connecting with his son and et cetera, et cetera.
Because of that, my depression and the depression of people, you know, largely people watching the movie does not come from an incident like your kids dying in a fire.
So it's it's it's almost it's not like it's worse, but it's also sort of more annoying.
Like you don't understand the reason for it.
I get why they gave him that because at the end of the film, he turns his back on his son.
This is why my dad hated the movie, actually, and we had a big argument about it.
For the entire time you're watching Casey Affleck connect with this kid and everything's going great.
And the kid finally says, hey, can I stay here and live with you?
And really the end of the movie is he's like, sorry, kid, I can't beat it.
Meaning depression. I can't beat it. I can't do this. I'm sorry.
And he's not going to kill himself, but he's also just admitting.
I have something so dark in me that I don't want to connect to another person ever again.
So what's the line? I can't beat it.
I can't beat it. That's what I just said. Yeah. Oh, you did.
I'm sorry. I didn't hear you say that. No, that's all right.
But yeah, that to me is the movie about depression.
And I know a lot of people who didn't like it just because of that ending.
You're watching it. You're waiting for them to patch things up.
You're waiting for him. Lucas Hedges, who is Casey's nephew.
But you're waiting for them for you waiting for what's supposed to happen in these movies.
Lucas Hedges character wakes up. Casey Affleck affects him.
He goes, oh, my God, I've wasted my life and discovers the joy of connecting with someone else.
And it fixes them. That's what this movie is leading to.
You're like, if you're putting me through all this misery, that's got to be where it ends.
But it ends realistically. Movies never end realistically.
It ends with Casey Affleck gone. Can't do it. Can't beat it.
The only hope you really have is that you get the feeling that Lucas Hedges has been positively affected by his time with Casey Affleck.
But it really does not give you any sort of relief.
This movie has so many moments that make me cry.
The Michelle Williams scene where she runs into him years later and they try their best to have a conversation is one of the most painful scenes of all time.
I think it's fucked up that Casey Affleck has his allegations and cut his career short because I think he's an incredible actor.
I do think he'll keep working, but it's on a lower scale. Maybe he'll be back at some point.
Admittedly, I don't know the extent of what he did, but I think he's brilliant in this movie, regardless.
And so is Michelle Williams. And it's a powerful piece of work. Check her out if you haven't.
All right. My next one is probably surprise.
The Untouchables. Oh, it is one of my favorite mob movies of all time.
One of my favorite David Mamet movies of all time. One of my favorite, probably my favorite Brian De Palma movie.
Definitely my favorite Kevin Costner movie. One of my favorite De Niro movies. My favorite Sean Connery movie.
I love The Untouchables. It's awesome.
And Sean Connery's character is the best character in the movie and his story as a cop who realized how dirty the system was.
And instead of becoming a Serpico of sorts said, I'm going to go walk the beat at night and be left alone because to try to fight this machine is pointless and it can only lead to a bad place.
And given the fact that all of that comes to him sacrificing himself for the cause that they are that they are all behind to bring down Capone, but it's literally a sacrifice for Connery.
It gets him killed and in his dying breath, he realizes that he has the final clue to put Capone in prison and is able to, as he's bleeding and dying on the floor with like, you know, bullet holes through his lungs and he can barely talk, convey the information to Kevin Costner as Kevin Costner is like crying and trying to save him.
It's just such an amazing, amazing climactic scene and a movie that's filled with climactic scenes.
I mean, this comes right after or right before. No, right before the bookkeeper staircase scene with Garcia and which is so awesome.
And then, you know, the greatest scene in the whole movie was is Elliot Ness throwing Frank Nitti off the roof.
You know, when Frank Nitti goes, your friend died like a stuck Irish pig and you're just like, and he's talking about Sean Connery and he's like, what'd you say?
I said your friend died screaming like a stuck Irish pig and then Costner throws him off the roof. Did he sound anything like that?
It's just awesome. But that scene where Connery dies, it kills me again.
It's just this thing of like a man going on a journey in his life and taking these stances and digging his heels in and then realizing I have to put that aside for what's right and to evolve and whatever.
And then that, you know, the act of doing that potentially being the thing that this is demise is just it just guts me, man.
So if you've not seen The Untouchables, dear God, do yourself a favor.
The greatest opening theme music next to, in my opinion, next to Star Wars ever in cinema.
Can you give it to me, refresh my memory?
Starts with the fan, the shadows of the fan spinning.
And the camera pans up, it says The Untouchables.
It's fucking, that movie is so awesome.
It is. I really wish De Palma, I love the weirdness of De Palma, but I wish that we they had given him the reins of more big shit like that.
I love his mission to Impossible.
I love his Untouchables and I love all his weird fucked up Hitchcock shit.
But like, I guess they did.
They gave him mission to Mars, which was absolutely terrible.
He had, he had some swings.
But man, when he's on, I really, I really love De Palma.
And that's a mammoth script, right?
Yeah, it's David Mamet.
And it's like, it's like a perfect mammoth script because there's just enough of the mammoth speak stuff that it's great.
But he's not like to up his own ass with it.
You know, it's very Glen Gary Glen Ross, like that kind of mammoth, like, you know, with.
Did you know that Bob Hoskins was in the De Niro part and got paid?
If you ever, if you ever get a free minute, look up on YouTube, Bob Hoskins, Bob Hoskins interviews on YouTube are amazing.
He's so funny.
But he is talking about how he gets paid every year, residuals on that movie, even though he didn't play the De Niro part.
Best role I ever took, best role I ever took.
Why didn't he, why didn't he end up doing it though?
I knew he was supposed to.
And then was De Niro came in.
It's like, oh, we have a much bigger star.
Fuck Bob Hoskins.
Oh, that was what they still had to pay him.
Yeah.
Another great clip is him talking about signing on to play Super Mario.
He was like, I just saw the cash offer and said, yes, because my kids playing the game.
And he points up and he goes, Dad, that's you see this little red man jumping up ladders and throwing fireballs.
I said, holy fuck.
I used to play King Lear.
I used to play fucking Macbeth.
Now I'm playing this little fuck.
It's really, really funny.
Anywho, my next one.
This is kind of an odd choice for me too.
But but I know that it was the right one because when I was thinking about the moment, I came very close to start to cry.
But it is the Royal Tenenbaums.
So I love the Royal Tenenbaums.
And I think another thing that really works for me in terms of crying is a movie that is funny throughout and then just drops that emotional bomb on you at the end about Schmidt and now Royal Tenenbaums.
So Royal Tenenbaums, I saw it in the theater.
Absolutely loved it.
I was very into Wes Anderson at that time, having loved Bottle Rocket and of course Rushmore.
And I love the movie.
I absolutely love the movie.
I've seen it many, many times.
But it's a comedy.
It's got serious moments.
But it's not only a comedy, but it's a Wes Anderson comedy.
Although he hadn't disappeared completely up his ass yet, referring to David Mamet as well.
He still knew how to make movies about people and not just movies about little doll houses that he's playing with.
At the end of the movie, Owen Wilson crashes his car.
He's the Tenenbaums friend and he kills the dog of Ben Stiller's kids.
And Ben Stiller is divorced and just having a really rough time and has to move back home, blah, blah, blah.
So really Stiller seems kind of annoying and wound too tight throughout the movie, but you know he's hurting.
You know, you just don't think in this comedy you're ever going to see beyond that.
You know, he's a guy who's wound up pretty tight.
A lot of times comedy characters, if you really looked at what's causing them to behave the way they are, it would be very dark and strange.
So when the dog dies, Stiller has been spending his whole movie hating his dad.
Again, fathers and sons, another trigger for me.
And trying to keep his sons, Gene Hackman's grandsons, away from him and to keep him from falling in love with him because he's like, this guy's no good.
So at the end, when their dog dies, he doesn't know what to do, Stiller.
And Royal Tenenbaum, the Gene Hackman character, buys a Dalmatian from the fire crew, fire truck, and gives it to his kids, his grandkids.
And that's moving enough.
But then Ben Stiller whispers, thanks to him, thanks him, but then he doesn't know what to say and you're just hanging there.
And this is a movie with a billion great one liners, but it's the only time it just kind of stops.
And there's like this silence.
And then he looks up and says, I've had a rough year, Dad, to his dad.
And then Hackman says, I know you have chess.
Yes, I'm getting close now.
I'm getting close now.
It's a it's a rough seed.
Amazing.
And yeah, here we are.
We're getting a little tears in the pot, a little tears in the pot.
It'd be great if I just started mocking you.
You wuss.
Well, I've had a rough year too, Joe.
But that's what happens, you know, like you.
I cried so much watching it that I had to run away from my friends, which has happened before.
Like you were saying, you ran away from your parents.
I ran away from my friends.
I would not look at them.
And I like hit out in the bathroom because I was crying at the end of it and couldn't stop it,
which means obviously that it hit something pretty serious.
I'm really crying.
I'm not laughing at you.
I'm laughing at the at the moment we've captured here on the pod.
This is a first, folks.
We've got real tears.
I'm not mocking it.
Oh, you've seen me cry, Joe, but the first time on the pod.
No, the last time I was walking into your home and asked you, Pat, are you crying?
I wasn't that time.
Wiped his face just now with a COVID mask, which I love it.
I love that the emotion came out.
It's a beautiful thing.
That's what this is all about, man.
And I can't even explain my reason for loving the moment.
You can probably gather it, but I just cry more, so I'm not going to do it.
Well, you'll you'll listen.
You're going to this.
This almost seems disrespectful.
Now the next one I'm going to name because it's so not it's but it gets me.
It truly gets me.
Is it flubber?
You can say flubber.
It's flubber.
It's it's it's honest.
It's Jumanji.
The next level.
See, we're joking about these.
But that reminds me that what really should be on my list is that scene with Williams
and Damon and Goodwill Hunting.
It's not your fault.
No, no, no one alive can make it through that scene without sobbing.
You know, I've I've I've never.
I don't know that I've ever seen that movie in sequence.
I've seen it.
I just don't know if I've ever seen it front to back.
I'm just, you know, so that movie always Williams accent in that movie bugs me.
It feels it feels the Boston accent.
I hear you.
I'll be right back, sir.
I'm grabbing a Kleenex camera off from Walsh.
Folks, you heard it here.
We had we had we had actual tears on the on the podcast today.
We've and you know what?
I'm glad we did, dammit.
Because you've heard a lot of well, you've heard select emotions on this part, haven't you?
You've heard you've heard laughter.
You've certainly heard rage, probably more rage than anything else.
You've heard depression.
You've heard dejection.
But we've never had, you know, true emotional tears.
We've said we've said at times I'm getting a little wispy here.
You know, I said it earlier today.
We've had those moments where you go, oh, geez, I'm getting a little honestly getting a little teary.
But we've never had full on, you know, actual the actual waterworks.
And up on snuck up on.
I'm glad that it happened.
I think it I think it and I get by the way, the only reason I'm not also crying is because I can just hear those cash registers going on.
This will bring in the bucks.
Yeah, it's like the Barbara Walters special.
No, it's it's a thing with me lately is that I used to I didn't cry for 35 years.
My parents said I didn't even cry when I was a baby.
But then something something changed in me here around 40.
I mean, my life changed, obviously.
But yeah, it's like it used to be if you're getting that little missy thing, you just cut it off.
It was easy for me.
But now I can't.
If there's if there's a waterworks situation happening, it leads to tears.
So there you go.
I'm not apologizing.
That's that's toxic masculinity.
That's toxic masculinity.
The yeah, no, I think I hear you.
I hear you.
I can I can I can I can relate in my own ways.
And I mean that, which is why I feel bad about my next selection.
I'm not making a mockery of the theme of the show.
This is real.
Superman, the movie every fucking time makes me cry when when when Lois Lane falls out of the helicopter.
He becomes Superman for the first time, like in public.
I mean, you see him in the outfit in the portrait of solitude.
He catches her.
The music is playing.
He what's the line?
He goes, don't worry, miss, I've got you.
And she goes, but who's got you?
The the whole city cheers everybody watching it.
It's playing the muse.
I mean, it fucking levels me.
And this kind of scene and then and then the most, you know, the famous I hope this doesn't put you off a flying man.
Statistically speaking, it's still the safest way to travel.
It encompasses.
So there's two things happening here for me.
It encompasses Superman so well.
It's just perfectly written.
Of course, it's perfectly written.
It's written by Godfather Guy, the Mario Puzo.
Mario Puzo wrote Superman?
Yeah, yeah, he wrote Superman.
Yeah, he wrote Superman.
And it's directed by Richard Donner.
So, of course, it's just a perfect sequence.
Right. It's acted by Margot Kidder and Christopher Reeve.
May they both rest in peace.
So the whole the pieces are there.
I will quickly say story by Puzo written by written by Puzo and three other notable writers.
But yeah, I had no idea.
Interesting. Yeah.
So they they now it just encompasses Superman so perfectly.
And it was the first time ever on screen.
I think that they I mean, I know that show in the fifties was big.
But this was to me was the first, you know, this is really it where where superhero movies become a thing.
And that's awesome. But also, too, I'm just a sucker again for seeing people come together, seeing like a bunch of dejected New Yorkers cheering at somebody getting saved.
And, you know, like in that moment and I know this is maudlin, but, you know, in that moment, all of their differences are put aside.
It's not about anything except we hope this person is OK.
And then here comes Superman, which is the beacon of that concept.
And he saves her. And then, you know, you got the John Williams score going.
I mean, Jesus God, it's what an awesome, awesome movie moment.
I mean, iconic doesn't begin to sum it up.
And yeah, it'll get me. It gets me every time, man.
It's awesome. Superman, too, also get me when Zod care to step outside.
I love hero shit like that.
It's just a perfect hero moment for me will make me cry, which will be explained in my final movie.
But which is my ultimate example of that. But I will wait until it's my turn.
Tom Sharpling, who I love and I know, you know, which makes me jealous because we're friends now.
Everyone I know is seemingly friends with him. And I just can't get on his radar for some reason.
But he was texting me last night.
Yeah, he cites on his show all the time.
Two things that make him cry, one being in Superman to win.
Everybody is like, hey, keep your hands off Superman, like when the town comes together.
I've seen that clip where he talks about that.
So that makes him cry. And then also in the Spider -Man and it's Joey Diaz actually who does it.
But like, hey, you don't fuck with Spider -Man. It's not fuck, but you know what I mean.
So those two moments.
Then he also cites when Pee Wee is saving all the animals in Pee Wee's Big Adventure.
And even though he's terrified of snakes, he runs in and saves the snakes from the fire.
And I was like, yep, I could see that getting you. People are weird. You never know what's going to hit you.
That's very funny. That's interesting. That one. I get the other two.
I don't get crying at the Pee Wee thing because it's so funny to me that he's like, it's so funny that he keeps passing them and he won't get the snakes.
He's getting everything else. But I think he's just saying like literally the worst thing to him that he could do.
But he's like, I got to save these animals lives. I get how that could touch you.
But I love too that he chooses not to pick up the tank and carry it out.
Does it the worst way possible? Because Tim Burton was clearly like, it's funnier if you're holding handfuls of snakes.
That's funnier, you know?
And then he faints holding the handfuls of snakes to top it all off.
Well, look, I have It's a Wonderful Life on my list. We just did it.
I'm not going to talk about that. And everybody knows why that movie is a classic tearjerker.
I feel like bumping that. I don't got anything new to say about that movie.
What I would like to focus on, man, mine are all dad -son shit. That's so embarrassing.
It's not embarrassing. Beautiful thing.
Well, After Sun is definitely the newest movie on this list.
But I saw that alone, thank God, at the theater and not on a date or something.
Thank God. I didn't even know that was supposed to be a moving movie or an emotional movie.
But it's out now. You can rent it for whatever, five bucks on Amazon.
It's Paul Mescal.
Wait, what is the movie called? I missed the title.
After Sun.
After Sun. Oh, I thought you said father's. I thought you were saying.
I thought you said father son saying like it's a father son movie. It's called After Sun.
It's called After Sun. S -U -N. Yeah, not even. I don't know why it's called that.
It's not S -O -N.
It is Paul Mescal from normal people who is a great actor who is playing Gladiator in Gladiator 2
or the Gladiator prequel or whatever that is now.
So, you know, hopefully he'll go the Russell Crowe route and keep acting and things and not just be that.
But who knows?
After Sun is a movie about a young dad.
Paul Mescal is like 27 years old and he's got like a eight year old daughter.
And much like Tar, After Sun is my favorite movie of the year, just above Tar.
Much like Tar, you don't you have to pay really close attention in this movie.
But on its surface, it's a dad and his daughter on vacation in Greece and they're having a nice time.
But clearly there's some issues between them and in the family.
Mescal is dealing with something very serious, whether it's depression or anxiety or drug use or being an alcoholic or what.
Like there's a scene of him with his daughter watching a little fun show at the resort they're at.
And he's got like eight empty beer glasses in front of him.
So it's definitely hinted that he's got some some demons.
He's also always doing things like his daughter's asleep and he has fun with her.
But once she goes to bed, he like steps out on the deck and is like doing Tai Chi.
He's clearly just a guy who's constantly in pain and trying anything to be normal.
His daughter is trying to connect with him, but can't know him.
She can know him as like a fun guy, but he doesn't come off as like a dad to her.
And the ex who you learn over time he is divorced from, the mother, they're clearly still in love with each other.
But this guy is just a fuck up. He can't get his shit together.
Similar, you know, to Manchester by the Sea, similar to definitely things I've dealt with in my own life.
But it's hard to explain and make it sound even interesting.
It's a really hard movie to put into words, really.
But it is about a man who completely fucked up his life, knows he can't fix it,
and is trying to have a fun vacation with his daughter where he doesn't reveal to her how fucked up he is,
how fucked up his life is, how sad he is, etc.
Devastating movie, unbelievable.
I think it only got nominated for Paul Mescal for best actor.
He won't win, but he's incredible in the movie.
And there are some shots in this movie that I can't discuss without spoiling.
And I think, you know, even though we do spoil stuff in the show, it's not like plot shit.
It's like the stuff that hits you emotionally.
I don't want to spoil it for you and take that experience away from you.
But yeah, it's a great movie. It's a 90 minute indie, super low budget.
It's set in the early 90s, so you get some great early 90s music if that interests you.
I think what really affected me is that the song that I used as kind of a mantra
to help me through this past year was Tender by Blur.
Come on, come on, come on, get through it is the chorus of that song.
I listen to that song all the time.
And they play it in this movie on top of everything else.
It's a song I was listening to 20 times a day.
Also, it's a blur obscurity.
And when they play it in this movie, it's one of those moments where you're just like,
wow, this is really like hitting me.
I, to end on a funny note, as I was leaving the theater,
a young black gentleman pointed at me and said, damn, this N -word been crying, crying.
Which was humiliating and yet very, very, very funny.
I had like puffy eyes and shit.
It's amazing.
And I'm happy to be able to recommend a new movie to you
that will hopefully affect you the same way it did me.
All right.
My final, and you probably saw this coming,
and it's the most fantastic of all my suggestions from today or candidates from today,
whatever your picks for today.
The Empire Strikes Back.
This movie took me apart at the seams as a child.
It's the first movie I'd ever seen where tragedy bestruck the heroes of something.
I'd never seen that.
I'd never seen a movie end with a cliffhanger.
I'd never seen any of it.
But the most traumatizing aspect of this movie was Han Solo getting frozen in carbonite.
Han Solo, the coolest and toughest guy in the galaxy, even by today's standards.
There's a reason why that character still hasn't been topped.
I don't think it's toppable.
I don't think Indiana Jones is toppable.
That's it.
Like it's kind of, we've done it and it's not going to get done again.
But the scene where he does get frozen,
and finally after this cat and mouse he's played with Princess Leia for all this time,
you see finally that he actually loves her.
God damn it.
We got them both.
The loyalty.
When Chewbacca starts freaking out and throwing the stormtroopers into the thing,
and then he grabs Chewbacca and he's calming him down.
Oh my God, dude.
It's like the ultimate Golden Retriever video.
You watch those videos on Instagram where it's like our baby was sick,
and it's just like the time lapse of the Golden Retriever sitting by the baby.
Those blow my mind so much because they'll be under a minute and cause me to cry.
I'm like, other than yanking a nose hair out,
there's nothing that could make anyone cry this quickly.
So you see that, and up until that point Chewbacca had just been in the two movies
with this force to be reckoned with, like this beast.
He was a good guy, but he was a beast.
And then you see like, oh my God, he loves him.
And then the capper, of course, the thing that every guy ever on planet Earth wants to do,
she goes, I love you, and he goes, I know.
And confirmed that that is, Harrison Ford said, no, no, no, he should say this.
He should not say I love you too.
Which is why Harrison Ford rules, which is why that character rules.
That scene, I have tears in my literal eyes.
You heard me get chokey.
I didn't get quite as deep as Walsh did, but damn it, it got me.
That scene destroys me.
And again, it's this thing, we're both talking about these childhood things
that end up triggering us in these movies we see as adults,
or that we saw even as children and watch again as adults.
My thing is always humanity.
It's like seeing the humanity come out, like seeing that happen,
it destroys me because I was a kid that got bullied, I got picked on.
I love my parents dearly, but there was a lot of fighting in my family.
The world view from the time I was a child that my family and I had up
through now has never been sparkling or very positive.
It's always been very like, it's a bad world out there, watch out.
And when I see things that exemplify humanity, but underneath it all,
there was always the concept of those of love and honor and your family
and all that stuff.
So when I see that in a movie, when I see people act with true humanity,
it just gets me.
It just really fucking gets me.
So that's my number one pick, people.
And I will say, just real quick, sorry, I will also say as a sort of
honorable mention, but it's connected to this, the trailer for the new
Indiana Jones, the Super Bowl one where it's playing the fucking music,
it's only 30 seconds long.
That made me cry.
And then the Flash trailer, Keaton coming back as Batman.
I might as well have been a fucking puddle.
I haven't seen either of those trailers.
I didn't know they were out.
There's a 30 -second Super Bowl spot for the new Indiana Jones, and it starts
with Mads Mikkelsen, and Harrison Ford goes, I know you, and Mads Mikkelsen
goes, have we met before?
And Harrison Ford goes, I don't know.
Are you still a Nazi?
And then the fucking music kicks in, and it's just like awesome action scene
after action scene for 30 seconds, Raiders march fully on, and you're just
like, yes!
It's everything you want it to be.
And then the Flash trailer, it's the Keaton voiceover and showing the Flash
stuff.
And then finally, mid -trailer, Keaton walks out in the fucking Tim Burton
Batman suit, and Ezra Miller is like, oh my God, oh my God, and Keaton goes,
yeah, I'm Batman.
And I saw that in a bar when the Super Bowl was playing, and the entire fucking
bar cheered.
It was so awesome and nostalgic and fun and whatever.
So anyway.
I am hearing, and they got to be real terrified about old Ezra, but I am
hearing that the Flash is supposed to be incredible.
And they're actually, they're showing it to people three months in advance,
like to critics and stuff, whereas most of these movies try to avoid being
shown to critics.
That's a level of confidence you don't get anymore.
They're like, no, come watch this.
And I think, too, it's why they, I heard rumors that they got rid of the
And I think that they did that because they're like, we can't continue on with
Ezra Miller.
We have to pass the torch in this movie to a new DC universe, which they're
doing the Flashpoint thing, which is their multiverse and whatever, and I
think that's going to be it.
I think they've got a great movie on their hands.
It's going to probably end with Flash going back to the Snyderverse, and then
we're, as an audience, going to stay over here now, and that's going to be the
end of it.
But I think that's also why it's been so delayed.
I feel like they were like, we have to figure this out because it's good.
If you're willing to throw a $100 million movie away because you've got a
better movie that it would mess up, that movie's probably pretty fucking good,
I would say.
Yeah.
So anyway.
All right.
I will do my last one, but I wanted to quickly read off my honorable
mentions that I did not shout out.
Obviously, it's a wonderful life.
Various Rockies.
There's moments in one, two, and Balboa that get me, and Balboa, it's the
ending when they're going through all the people running up the stairs and
stuff.
There's a lot of great moments in those.
The Balboa one destroyed me.
I saw that in the theater with my parents in Florida, and when he says,
let's start the training, and it plays the music for the first time, it does
the training sequence.
My mom turned to me and goes, could you imagine if we were watching this back
home?
Yeah.
And I was like, holy shit, people must be going fucking crazy in Philly.
Balboa, it's a very underrated movie, Rocky Balboa.
It's really good.
Yeah, it's awesome.
Schindler's List, I cried multiple times, of course, throughout Schindler's
List, but then there's the ending in color where all the Jews who survived
returned to the homeland.
Spielberg, weirdly, for making so many emotional movies, he doesn't really
land on my list because I don't like sentiment.
None of the things on this list are on my list are moments where the music
swells, and I liked very understated emotion in my life and in my movies.
But to me, the hardest Spielberg has ever been, and because of the subject
matter, obviously, is Schindler's List, and that's why it moves me a lot more
than his movies that fall all over themselves to make you cry.
Home for the Holidays with Holly Hunter.
Charles Durning plays the dad in that.
Charles Durning is every old Irish guy in my family.
He looks exactly like them, maybe a little fatter, but he looks like them.
And him at the end of that movie, his family's all been screaming at each
other and fighting, and he's sitting watching old home movies and getting
emotional, and it's playing The Very Thought of You by Nat King Cole.
That is an emotionally devastating sequence in one of the more underrated
movies of all time, Home for the Holidays.
I think that movie is amazing with Holly Hunter and Bobby Downey Jr.
And I want to shout out the three saddest documentaries ever made.
Dear Zachary.
Dear Zachary is the most brutal film maybe of all time.
It's beyond Hellraiser in terms of like, I mean, it's putting you through an
emotional wringer.
I won't even tell you what it's about.
But Dear Zachary is a movie that I very foolishly watched on a plane, ladies and
gentlemen, where you're already on the verge of tears at the time.
Dear Zachary, The Work, which is a documentary about a bunch of guys
learning to convey their emotions in a prison setting.
That movie I wept start to finish.
It's difficult to find maybe at this point, but an excellent documentary.
The Work.
And then Dick Johnson is Dead, which came out two years ago, which is the
documentary about the guy dying of Alzheimer's.
But those three are all incredible.
Now I will give you my final choice, which has got to be, I think, 127 hours.
Which I have not seen since I saw it in the theater.
I don't really give a shit about James Franco.
That is a movie I saw with a couple of friends, like an Oscar screening or
something.
We all had breakfast.
We were like, you know, maybe a couple mimosas.
We're joking, laughing.
I was like a kid.
And I had just moved to L .A.
And we went and saw that movie.
It's going along.
It's a good adventure.
There's disgusting stuff in it where he has to cut his arm off.
Obviously, it's a story of a young man who gets caught between a rock and a
hard place, if you will, and has to saw his arm off.
But there is a series of like flashbacks at the end of this thing where he's
stuck.
He's thinking about the people in his life.
And you realize that if he had just connected with his girlfriend more, his
parents more, if he had told them where he was going, anything, he'd have been
fine.
And that's what he's realizing.
And that's what you're realizing.
And that's, of course, the theme of the movie is, if you're not going to
connect with the people in your life, you might as well be dead.
That's what I took out of it.
It was hitting me really hard because it is hard for me to connect.
It is hard for me to connect with friends, family, girlfriends, et cetera.
I get there, but it's a challenge.
So in that movie, this guy who's like Mr. Independent, and I don't got to tell
anybody what I'm doing.
And to go off and do that really dangerous, reckless thing and not let
anybody know what you're doing.
For some reason, it just hit me.
I was like, now this guy's going to die alone because he can't connect with
people.
And I cried so uncontrollably in that.
That was another moment like Royal Tenenbaums where I walked 20 feet ahead of
my friends to the car.
They kindly did not make fun of me.
But these are guys who they have told me since, like they assumed that I didn't
cry, that I did not have access to these human emotions.
So when it came out, I couldn't stop.
And we're driving in the car, like talking about girls and shit.
And I was still just tear streaming down my face.
I don't know that the movie would still have the same impact.
But I had to shout it out because that movie devastated me for like a day.
I didn't mention Mighty Wind because we've discussed it and Joe doesn't like
it.
But the scene at the end where Eugene Levy has to sing with this woman that
he's clearly been pining for for 30 years and the song sounds so beautiful and
that song's building up to them kissing.
And they kiss and it finally means, you know, you know what it means now to
Eugene Levy.
That kiss means everything.
It's another big moment that hits me.
And then the end of the wrestler really got me, if I'm being honest.
I love the wrestler, but it doesn't get me emotionally.
But I get it.
I get it.
It's him dying and then into that Springsteen song.
Have you ever seen a one legged pony?
Whatever it is.
It gets me.
Well, there you go, folks.
You got some real tears.
You got some tear picks, tear jerkers, tear jerkers from two jerks.
Hey, listen, that's our episode, everybody.
We'll be back.
What the hell is it?
This is these are the last two of February.
We'll be back in March with we don't know yet.
I am not saying we're going to do this, but a possibility I would think might be
this Children of the Corn remake that's come out.
I don't know if you've seen the trailer.
What's that?
Peacock or something?
Shutter, baby.
It's it was finished two years ago and it is just now seeing the light of day.
It looks like it looks like it was made with a budget put together by the
allowances of the children that are starring in the film.
I'm curious.
Children of the Corn has never been a banger franchise, but I'm just like,
why not, man?
Let's see where this where they take this one this time.
Yeah, no, I was very surprised when I watched it with you, which was the
first time I saw it to realize that it sucks.
You know, it's got kind of a reputation, but even the first one is not good.
Wasn't that our first ever episode?
First or second, by the way, we're if we're if this isn't our 300th episode,
it's probably the next batch.
We need to find out.
Maybe do something special.
All right.
And then we'll probably do an Oscar or something or other next month.
But until then, people, thanks for listening.
We'll see you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.