I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, and when the sound of your screams becomes
a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say, I'll see you in hell, you know I will.
I'll see you in hell, you know I will.
Folks, it's we'll see you in hell, that's wheel, not w -h -e, but wheel, w -e, apostrophe.
An important clarification 10 years in, I think, for anybody who was confused.
I think that's why the pod hasn't become as big as I think it should be. People are spelling it
see you in hell. Then there's also wheel enthusiasts coming to our podcast and being let down,
leaving bad reviews. I haven't checked because they used to give me high anxiety, Mel Brooks style,
but we always used to have four and a half, five stars. I'm sure your fans have taken us down a
notch or two throughout the years. Well, those aren't my fans. Those were my true anti -fans.
No, I think we're still in the fours. Okay, good. Nothing is worse than a review
online. Even when it's good, it's not good for you, as they say. Your ego doesn't
need that shit, somebody telling you how great you are. Absolutely not. Well, I could use it
in a while for Christ's sake. Jesus. I had a, had a gal back to the place last night
and then, of course, it's,
Hey, you think I can stay over?
I'm gonna do the Andrew Dice Clay's girlfriend voice.
You think I can stay over?
It's like, you can't, I can't say no. I'm sure you throw them out on their ass, but I'm always
like, yeah, you can stay, but Christ, you're, I'm just like, yeah, when I say yes, I'm saying yes.
I agree that I will get 12 minutes of sleep tonight, you know, and that's about what I got.
Just trash. It's hard to sleep with somebody, you know, really well and a stranger. It's like,
of course she's, she's out in five seconds after positioning herself in the most uncomfortable
position for me. I'm pinned to the edge of the bed like a goddamn wrestler.
I get offended if they don't stay. I'm like, what am I, what are we doing here? I've had girls do
that. They come right in right after the deed with putting their, like walking into the room,
putting their pants back on like fucking Al Bundy or something. I'm like, what are you doing?
See, well, you, I mean, you're also dating a lot of runaways and vagabonds and people of that nature.
Right. She's, she's putting everything back in her kerchief, tying up this on the end of the stick.
Yeah. As she creeps the lobby, your lobby manager is reading a newspaper with a wanted picture of
her on it, but it's up over his face. So she tiptoes out past it, that kind of thing.
Um, anyway, I didn't even know what I was talking about. It was the worst night of sleep possible.
End of story. That sucks, man. Is it, I'll tell you what I have a hard time with with the sleeping.
It's not usually the position of the body. It's usually that the other person's body runs hot.
I'm, I'm very hot when I sleep. I'm like air conditioner in the winter, hot when I sleep.
Uh, and that, that is a tough one for me. I can't do it, you know?
Yeah. I turned the thermostat low, didn't do any good, you know, just a sultry evening
thinking about what I've done, what I've become.
Look at what you did. She wakes up and you're saying that in their bathroom mirror in the
middle of the night. Look who, a picture of Jesus that I've taped the bathroom mirror.
Who watches me always.
I'm in, for those of you at home, if you're hearing a little weird reverb,
uh, I apologize. I'm in my new home that I have finally finished the transaction of.
I've been down here for about a week and a half trying to get things in order. Um, and I'm in my,
what will be my office and I have a desk in here, but I don't have any other furniture in this room
yet. And it's lovely hardwood floors in this home, very lucky and blessed, but,
but it's, it's echoey. It's echoey. I got to get like some books I'll never read on these walls.
And this is a, this is a home in Philadelphia. Yes.
Let's call it the Philadelphia area, but no, not in Philadelphia proper.
And isn't it true you bought the shack that Paulie fishes in, in the Rocky movies?
I bought that. I bought that. Uh, and I walk around town in the outfit that Tom Hanks wears,
uh, in Philadelphia, the movie, uh, the beanie with the scarf.
Can you fit in that? I mean, he got pretty thin.
Yeah. Uh, I called a friend of mine the other day. I won't say who it is because I don't want
to blow up her spot, but she's pretty, you know, notable. She's famous in her own way.
I don't mean that in a shitty way, like in her own way. I just mean like,
she's not like globally famous, but she's, she's famous. People know who she is. Um,
she had fucking Tom Hanks on her outgoing message.
Oh, she just like met him and asked him. I don't, I didn't get the story. I just,
somebody hadn't talked to her in a long time. And I said, I left this voicemail. I go,
what, what is going on with your out? I thought like she knew a guy that did a Tom Hanks impression.
Yeah. She texted me and she's like, I got Tom Hanks to do my outgoing message. It's insane,
but I got him to do it. And it was wild. That's very cool. Now I, um, so I'll stop making sense
talking heads concert movie. One of my favorites in IMAX, uh, at the Americana,
not, not the greatest IMAX in LA, but it was one of the last showings of it.
And who was sitting about three rows ahead of me, but Mr. Tom Hanks. Right. And I don't know,
I didn't know until the end, when the lights came up, I, my assumption is he was sitting with
Gary Getzman who produced stop making sense. And I believe now is Tom Hanks is producing partner,
although I don't know what he looks like. So I might've just made that up. Um, and then as we
were leaving me and my friend, a fire alarm went off and we both said that must've been Tom Hanks
sneaking out because people started to recognize him. And I think celebrities
are so famous that they're like, eh, I'll just set off the fire alarm. Cause that happens all the
time, especially at the Grove and the Americana here in LA. It's crazy. Well, that's how they
leave a theater. They're like, I'll just do this. I don't think I've told this story on the podcast
yet. I don't believe I have. All right. Uh, wait, I gotta get this. Hold on. I gotta get this right.
Hold on a second. By the way, I'm drinking a, a black cherry bubbly, which is, uh,
Michael Buble's entry into the seltzer game. Um, it's not very good. And the slogan is,
that's not true. I just made it the Buble thing. Uh, these sips don't lie.
And you know, Shakira is not seeing any of that. The sips don't lie. These sips don't lie.
Jesus. Good. Now if I'm Shakira, I go, where's my cut Buble who does not own the company bubbly.
Seltzer game just got out of control. I mean, I'll admit like the big one in writers rooms out here
is La Croix. I think there's no grosser seltzer soda water than La Croix. It's awful. And always
winds up tasting like the can. Um, but there are some good ones. I like a spin drift with fruit
juice. You know, uh, there's some interesting flavors out there, but what I learned recently
is when it says natural flavors, that doesn't mean like juice. It just means like chemicals,
but they call it natural flavors. Yeah. Like there's nickel in there. That's natural,
right? Yeah. Yeah. Um, we'll be in lied to the story. I was going to tell. It's not that
interesting. I, when I went to see back to the future, the musical, who was two rows in front
of us, but one Alan Silvestri composer. Did you recognize him or they announced him? Uh,
I wouldn't recognize. I think I, people were taking pictures with them and I was with
my friend, uh, rapper Esoteric from czar face and my friend Brian Quinn from impractical jokers,
just to name drop a little bit. A lot of that going on this week. Yeah. But, uh, and, um,
I said, uh, I was like, guys, who the fuck is this up here in front of us? Like people are taking
pictures with them. Is this like the director? And then I looked in the, the, the, um, play bill.
I was like, holy shit, that's fucking Alan Silvestri. Like that's the guy that wrote the
music to back to the future. And what I didn't know at the time, he also scored.
Predator, my favorite sci -fi movie ever. And, and, uh, and, uh, cat's eye, one of my favorite horror
films. And I assume picture with him. He was very nice. I assume Max Silvestri, his son.
I don't know. Is that his son? Oh, well, no, it doesn't, it doesn't appear. So
I work out of the same place as Max Silvestri. I will ask him. How's Max doing? I haven't seen
him in a while. Um, you know, I see him once in a while and I always have a nice time. He's a nice
guy and he's very funny. He's very funny and he's very sweet. He's got a very kind soul. I like him
a lot. Funny comedian. Um, we're talking about him like he died for some reason. I went to see,
a friend today. No, no, no, go ahead. Tell me, uh, what, how was back to the future musical,
by the way, bearing the lead. It was, it's okay. It's start when it first, the first act, I was
like, I'm not into this man. This is like a paint by numbers. Like just, they're just, they're just
rushing through the beats of the movie and it's without the nostalgia of any of it. Who cares?
And then in the second act, the like depth of the characters kicked in. I started to kind of care
and by the end of it, I was crying. And so, so overall, I really liked it. Um,
the part where George stands up to Biff is awesome. And like seeing that live within a theater was
really fun. And the car effects are incredible. The car effects are like the way they make the
look like it's disappearing as it goes back in time and shit. And then at the very end of the
show, major spoiler alert, when doc picks up Marty and he goes, we don't need roads,
the music kicks in and the car flies up over the audience. And it's pretty awesome. You know,
you can't help but get swept away in that. So it was fun. We, um, it's in, it's in Times Square,
right near where Caroline's used to be on, uh, it's between 50th and 51st on Broadway.
And, uh, the closest bar was the bar inside the TGI Fridays. And that is a rough TGI Fridays,
but we made the most of that bar, man. We got in there. I've had some fun in that bar. I'll tell
you that they used, they used to do a 24 ounces of beer for a dollar from like four to seven every
night after work. And my office would just go straight there. There was like an arcade in
Times Square that it's no longer there. Um, yeah. Up like four escalators. It was right by that AMC
20, those two big AMC theaters are the, you know, giant multiplexes up there.
Yeah. There's the AMC 42, which is on 42nd street. Yes. And then right across the street from it is
the Lowe's Ewok. It's called correct. I never knew why it was called the E walk, not Ewok,
like E W a L K. I never, I never understood what that meant.
I do not know. Um, my last memory, really my last memory of being in New York, even though I've been
there since, but my last one of like, where I think I was like, I don't know that I'm coming
back here anymore was one of my very best friends out there. Elon and his lovely wife,
who were both NBC pages with me and I watched them beat the early days of musk. You mean Elon,
yeah, exactly. But, um, I watched him and his wife, you know, meet and fall in love and they've been
married and have kids. It's a beautiful thing to watch. I liked them a lot, but, um,
Elon, the fuck was I talking about the early days of NBC paging, going to the regal Ewok.
Yeah, sorry. Jesus Christ. I was like, well, I'm remembering my old friends. Then I'm like,
so anyway, we, uh, him and I go to see the sitter, the Jonah Hill vehicle, which was hated. And I
thought, you know, had its moments. I didn't think it was that terrible as like an R rated adventures
and babysitting. You can do worse. It's another one that if you watched it today, you'd probably
be like, this is a goddamn masterpiece compared to what's out. But, um, we go see it and my friend
Elon's a bit of, you know, he's, he's kind of in his own world, which is his charm, you know,
he's got like a Lebowski kind of vibe about him, but we get home and his wife's like, what'd you
guys do today? And we're like, we went to this blah, blah, blah theater. She just immediately
starts screaming at Elon. She's like, that's the theater with the bed bugs. I told you never to
go to that theater. We have children. We have children. I was like, whoa, just immediately
like slipped out the back. Um, we, we laugh about it now. It's very funny, but she was very stressed
that we were going to give her kids bed bugs. And I was like, I didn't know that was when New York,
everything had bed bugs, every hotel, every theater, everything was like gross. Not that it's not gross
now, but it was really gross. Who'd have thought you'd long for the time when all you had to worry
about was bed bugs. That's true. Jeez, man. What a, what a happier day that was. Um, I was going to
sit her in every multiplex. We had it all and we threw it away. Uh,
we're reviewing today is the exorcist believer, but the story I'm going to tell is got to do with
the movie theater. I saw this in the, uh, play the area where I bought this home and I went to the
movies and I went for a matinee on a like a Wednesday or something, uh, by myself. In fact,
no, it was Monday. It was this past Monday and I just went, I was out running errands and I was
like, shit, you know what? I got time. I got to see this. I'm going to go see it. I pop in for 2 30
PM. Uh, I get a popcorn medium. I get a Coke zero medium and I get a ticket for the movie
and you buy it all at the one counter. Concession stand also sold the tickets
and the kid goes, that'll be $21 please. And I was like, what fucking time portal have I walked
through? This is incredible. And I was literally the only person in the theater.
I don't think they're going to make it. I think you're confusing your life with the majestic,
the Tom, uh, Jim Carrey vehicle that I remember absolutely nothing about.
Remember that he like inherited a theater or something. What a boring fucking movie.
It was his first foray into drama and yeah, the majestic was the first leap he made. It's pre
Truman show. I believe I'll look at it. I don't know about that, Joe. Hold on. And what about
eternal Sunch? No, that's, that's definitely after, because I remember going to see the majestic and
thinking like, I bet this guy would be a good dramatic actor. And then the movie sucked so bad
that I was like, I don't know if he's doing, uh, he might want to rethink this.
Well, Darabont did so much great horror. Then he does Shawshank redemption, green mile. You're
like, Oh boy, here we go. Then majestic, but then he bounces back with the mist.
And then has it, has there been anything since? Yeah, I think so. I'll tell you that in a second.
Okay. The majestic is later than I thought, but I am correct. It's before eternal sunshine.
And it's after the Truman show. Oh, it's after man on the moon. Wait, what? Okay. I was really
wrong here. I'm sorry. Um, yeah. Remember Simon Birch? I loved Simon Birch. I wonder if that
holds up. I never saw it. What a weird fucking movie. Um, the majestic, Jesus Christ. Okay.
Then you know what it was. And I went into this thing going, Oh, this guy's a great dramatic
actor. I can't wait to see this. And I was very wrong. Yeah. No, Frank Darabont has not directed
anything since the mist. Um, pre the mist was the majestic pre that was green mile pre that I just,
I just got, uh, the 4k, the mist, which is four discs. And it has a black and white version,
which I've never seen of the mist, but in reading about it, I learned that the studio said you can
either keep the ending, which is probably the bleakest ending in the history of horror movies.
And one of the bleakest endings in the history of movies, or you can do it in black and white,
you can't do both. And he decided it was more important to keep the ending, but apparently
the black and white version is awesome. And I'm going to watch it tonight actually. So I'll report
I don't get the, I mean, maybe I'm an idiot. I don't get the fascination with
a modern movie having a black and white version. I get why old black and white movies have
wonderful texture and, and, and all that's an aesthetic and all that. Like I tried to watch that
black and chrome or whatever the fuck, um, uh, mad max. I, I, I'm just like, I don't know.
It just looks like the movie, except their color's not there anymore. Like I, there was no like
elevated experience to it, but what am I not getting here? What am I missing?
Well, I was just reading about this last night, like, like something like the mist,
it was important to him. He wanted to have both versions. He that's his preferred version of the
movie. But like Logan I've heard is cool. I heard that the mad max one is actually probably a step
down from color, as you're saying, which makes sense. Um, sin city started as black and white,
but what used to suck is when they would colorize black and white, like the colorized version of
it's, it's a wonderful life looks like dog shit. And they used to do that because they were like,
kids won't watch it if it's black and white. I don't know. I think these, these like,
like they just released it, uh, on the criterion channel, no less, a black and white version of
Johnny mnemonic, a movie that is one of the worst reviewed movies of all time with Keanu Reeves.
I'm like, guys, just because they, they put a filter on it does not mean it's suddenly a
masterpiece. What is the, well, yeah, first of all, you're, you're very right. The black and white
of, and I've talked about it on here when we did mad max, um, the black and white of mad max, um,
what the hell is it called? Thunder road or whatever? Fury road. It's, uh, it's
Springsteen's thunder. You can't, you can't tell what the hell is going on. Yeah. Like you're like,
it's cause it's all in the desert. You're like, what the fuck is happening, man? I can't tell
what's what in this fucking thing. I recently saw Lawrence of Arabia and 70 millimeter and it looked
incredible, but like a black and white version of that movie would suck because it's all sand.
That's not a movie that looks good in black and white. Um, you want to, you want to go to that
movie corner? I'm excited to talk about the movie today. Well, I went, I saw a triple feature this
week of exorcist, the musical, not exorcist, the musical exorcist believer, by the way,
I bet my friend and lost $10 that something really scary would happen in the final scene
of the exorcist believer. And then as the end credits kicked in, it would play Neil diamonds.
And then I saw her face, the monkeys, I'm a believer and that didn't happen. I lost $10,
but I was certain that that was going to happen. Why would you, why would you think that? Because
every horror movie now plays some ironic oldie over the end credits every time. Fair enough.
Okay. Including, uh, what was, what was the boogeyman one? They were playing
like something about the heart at the end or I don't know. Yeah. Well, you know, that all,
that all, as far as I know, oh, burn and love remember because there was a fire in the movie.
Oh, that's right. That as far as I know, all of that, all of it stems from
the great Sam Raimi, the original, um, uh, evil dead, the, the very first one. Yeah. That ends
with like, it plays like a golden oldie at the very end. Yeah. And then a couple of years after
American werewolf ends with a bad moon rising at the very end, if I recall. Yeah. Yeah. And they
the, uh, like hooks in, um, American werewolf is that it, it, like they play those, those ironic
old, they play like blue moon. That's it. That's the one at the end of the movie.
Yes. So what's the triple feature? Triple feature was, uh, exorcist, which we're going to discuss.
It was also Dick's the musical, the new, uh, eight 24 produced joint, um, directed by Larry
Charles, the guy who did Borat and, uh, you know, other great comedy things. He's a very well -known
comedy director. This movie was done on the cheap. Um, I was sort of excited just that it was a
released comedy, which is rare. And there have been a few good ones, little ones coming out lately,
but, uh, my God, I thought this was absolutely terrible. Um, it felt to me like
a comedy central pilot that didn't go to series from like 2010. Uh, it felt out of date somehow.
It stars these two guys who have no credits between them. They were putting on a show,
uh, in like a Gristides grocery store in New York and they got offered this film deal.
There's puppets in it. Nathan Lane and Megan Mullally play in a strange couple in it. Um,
they're doing weird voices and accents. They're leaving takes in the film where people laugh
because I guess they shot it very quick. And at first I started seeing it get compared to like
John Waters and shit. They have like a Megan, the stallion cameo or whatever,
and they're trying to present it like it's this big campy cool event. And I'm like, if you're
before the release of the movie, if you're trying to compare it to like a John Waters
midnight movie, that usually means you've missed the mark and you're trying to pretend that it's
something it's not. Cause this movie just seems like it misses every comedic target it's aiming
for. I did not hear any laughing in the screening I was in. Um, it just doesn't work. This
is a couple of funny jokes, but, um, it's just, it's a musical where none of the songs are catchy
or particularly funny. Um, I hate to be harsh on it, but it's just not, it's not very good.
It's not very good. What's his name? Larry Charles, who I guess directed it, you know, but he,
he's a nut now, right? He's nuts, but he's, yeah, he's like, I don't know, said publicly,
and I don't disagree with him, but he was like big budget movies. I find them offensive. And it's
like, all right, well, that's fine. I don't disagree, but Christ make a cool low budget
movie. I mean, I don't know. I haven't seen it, so I can't look at what it, what is cool about it
is it's low budget, handmade quality. And when, when I speculate like how, how the fuck did this
thing happen, it's probably because it costs under a million dollars. And I think they made it in like
seven days or eight days or something. And to that end kudos, but it just really,
it's so I'm surprised it was released. I will say it was, it was just not successful in any way.
Uh, a quick, uh, news psycho speaking of Larry Charles, uh, who was very involved with Seinfeld,
you know, this Seinfeld clip is all over the internet. I mean, he, he's at a live show,
somebody, he does a Q and a, somebody says, are you happy with the finale? He says, it's funny.
You asked me that I can't really tell you what we have cooking, but we are working on something.
And that question has been on me and Larry David's mind too. And we have something coming.
Something is happening. What do you think it's going to be? Do you think it's going to be like
a Seinfeld? You think it's a bullshit thing where it's going to be like a Superbowl commercial?
Cause that's what he did last time, but this seems real. This seems like, no, they're like
working on like a movie maybe, or like some special or I can't imagine it's a movie,
but he's making this, um, Netflix he's already made. I just heard him being interviewed about
it on smart lists. The, uh, one week, the podcast we discussed on here and he's directed and co -written
this movie about the maker of the pop tart and created this like satirical look at this race to
my guess is he made that movie for Netflix. They were happy with it and they were like, Hey,
would you be interested in doing like an hour long, like a new continuation of the Seinfeld
story is my hope, but it could also be another thing on curb. However, I almost wouldn't want
that. I'd almost rather they try to correct, even though I liked the finale of Seinfeld,
I'd almost rather they try to correct it by writing an episode of the show,
then try to beat what they already did on curb regarding Seinfeld, which is the funniest
season of the show. Probably that was an amazing season for fans of the show. I hate to see them
not, not hit those heights again. I always said, I wish they just would have produced the damn
episode. It was written. Like, you know, you watch curb, you're like, the episode is pretty much
written. Just do it. You've rebuilt the sets, everything. Just shoot the episode with an
audience. Like, why wouldn't you just do it? And also too, the Frasier reviews are in,
it premieres I believe tomorrow. I've seen, I've seen mixed. I've seen nothing terrible,
but I've seen mixed. Yeah. It seems like the one consistent thing everybody is saying is,
when Kelsey Grammer is on screen, it's awesome. Even the people that aren't too hot on it. And
the worst I've seen anybody say is, is look, the supporting cast just can't deliver in the way the
original supporting cast could, but boy, they sure look like duds from the trailer. I hate to say,
it looks like he's just surrounded himself with zeros. Well, I got to say though, if you watch
the first season of the original show, it takes a minute, like for those characters to become,
like John Mahoney is playing it very cliche. Like he's doing this voice where he's like,
oh geez, Frasier. Niles is just like, David Hyde Pierce has said, he's like, when I read the part,
I was like, what are they doing? They wrote just the exact same character. Niles doesn't become
like, it takes a minute for Niles to really become Niles. Like Daphne is a very cliche,
run of the mill sitcom character in the first season where they lean way too heavy into her
like mysticism. And by the way, this is, this is every, uh, sitcom, but they never learn,
you know, it's, it's the classics. It's the first season of Seinfeld is hard to watch. The first
season of friends, the first season of, you know, Will and Grace and all these shows, they got,
they got to find their way because it's just unnatural and awkward. It's like how a play has
to rehearse for 180 days before they start. But, um, it just don't take the time anymore,
unfortunately. I'm excited for that. Like, I think the English professor, his friend looks funny,
who like looks like the guy that seems to be like the drunken Englishman. Right. That guy looks
funny. Uh, and I'm excited for the Nile. I read the pilot script. I'm excited for the Niles and
Daphne son, like who's like a combination of the two of them. I feel like he'll be funny.
The main son, Frederick, is the one character I'm not too keen on. But look, the first season,
the first two seasons of Picard with Patrick Stewart were very poorly received and, and
certainly a much more expensive show to create and to produce. They were very poorly received.
Then the third season, what'd they do? They brought back the next generation cast and all
the YouTubers were rolling their eyes like, Oh Christ, here we go with the fan service.
And then everybody was like, Holy shit. It was fucking incredible. It was the next generation
movie we never got. So I feel like even if this first season is a little wonky, they'll figure out,
look, if Kim Cattrall went back to, to, and just like that, they'll get David Hyde Pierce back to
Frasier. Like, you know, like they'll, and Bibi Neuwirth and Perry Gilpin are in this season.
And I think in the second half, so I think it'll find its footing. I'm sure we'll get some cheers
cameos. I'm sure there'll be a thing where Sam shows up or whatever. They put up the John
Ratzenberger signal, the rat signal to lure him. He's like, I just gave gallops on all fours to the
studio. Um, I watched, speaking of Tom Hanks, I watched two, uh, frightening films, both about
not, not frightening because they were about homosexuality, but frightening for different
reasons. The first was Philadelphia, which is a, a very upsetting film. Yeah. Uh, but a very good
film. Aside from, aside from two moments that are painfully cliche and obvious,
which is when the woman testifies who is HIV positive from the blood transfusion and Mary
Steenburgen goes, but you didn't get this from your own fault. You got this by accident. And the lady
goes, I see myself as no different than this man's. It's just bad dialogue. And then there's,
there's one or two moments with Jason Robards that are so obvious where he's like,
he brought age into her off. That's kind of stupid. That's a good Jason Robards, but yeah,
it's, it's a movie that at the time seemed like crazily ahead of its time and progressive,
but it can't help, but seem a little dated now for sure. But Jonathan Demme, the man,
the man knows a closeup for that's for sure. He's a great director.
Jonathan Demme, Tommy Hanks, Denzy Wash, uh, JC Robes, Mary Steen's, uh, it's a great cast. Um,
I think that Hanks Washington pairing needs to happen again. That was a really great pairing.
They're so good at it. You're so good. And like there was stuff I was picking up on in, in this,
I haven't seen the movie a ton of times. I've seen it like three times. Maybe this is my fourth
watch, third watch, but there was just stuff I was picking up on story -wise that I never really
realized when I saw it when I was younger, where I was like, Oh, that's cool that Tom Hanks is the
actually like altruistic, like tried and true lawyer who believes in the craft and is the one
that is dying. Uh, Denzel is the ambulance chaser, but is the one that has the flourishing life.
Denzel's child is being born as Tom Hanks is dying. There were all these interesting
juxtapositions I was noticing. It's a really wonderful movie. Antonio Bandera's early role.
Uh, yeah, I wonder why Bruce Vallanche didn't get cast a different, a different film,
a different film. I can't see. I think I need to go to the hospital. Um, the, uh, but you know,
the acting is, is, is beyond, I mean, Tom Hanks is, I mean, it's, it is a grand slam performance
on his part. I mean, Jesus Christ. Um, and that was great. I mean, and they go, they really go
for it with Denzel's like home of his character's homophobia of install of it. Like it's, it's,
it's, it's a really, it's a good movie. It's a very good, challenging movie in many ways. And, uh,
I enjoyed it. And then a Roger Corman cameo. Yeah. Well, he gave Jonathan Demme his break.
Oh, okay. That's right. And has a cameo in silence of the lambs too. Who's he playing?
FBI guy, I think. Okay. He's the head of the FBI actually.
That's cool. But it's a, it's a great movie. It's a great way. My favorite part. And again,
this is something I didn't notice before, cause Mary Steenburgen is so, she's so unlikable in
this movie. She's such, she's so vicious as the prosecutor or no, the defense attorney, excuse me.
And then there's that scene, you just think that she has no humanity. And there's that scene where
he has to open his shirt and show the lesions. And she sits down and just under her breath to her
partner, whoever she just goes, and you're like, oh, that's such a great moment where you see like,
and, and, and, and then that, that amplifies Denzel's role. Cause Denzel says like,
there's the part where he's like, I hate gays or whatever, but a law has been broken and that's
my job or whatever. Like, and Tom Hanks's thing with the trial where he's like, I can't prove
that they fired me because I have AIDS, but what I can prove is that I was not a bad lawyer.
So there's really all these interesting positionings of all the characters where
they're all doing their job in regard to the law. And that job is being dictated by what their role
in the judicial system is. It's just a really well -done film, very well. Who wrote it?
That I don't know, Joe. I'm going to look that up. Why should I have to know?
You usually know that stuff. You usually, you know, you know,
it's got that Bruce Springsteen song. I've been driving around my neighborhood,
just cranking that Bruce Springsteen song. It's a great song. I also love his song for
wrestler. Great ending to that movie. Well, let me know when you know, but the third movie
of my triple feature was the Royal Hotel, a title that I have not been able to remember once. I've
tried to say it 10 times now. I called it the blue room at the ticket counter. And I realized that I,
I guess I've just fully become an old man. I'm like, I have a ticket here for the blue room.
Like what? Oh, I'm sorry. The Royal Hotel. The girl's like, you know, those two sound nothing
alike. Yeah, I do. I'm sorry. But couldn't you get a blue room at a Royal Hotel, Ben? Okay.
This movie, Joe, did you ever see The Assistant?
No. So it stars Julia Garner, who is the incredible young actress from Ozark,
the blonde Falmouth girl. And The Assistant is basically the story of a girl who was an
assistant to a Harvey Weinstein type. You never see him. You just see what her miserable day to
day life is like. And I remember liking it, but also kind of hating it because it reminded me so
much of me kind of coming up in this business and having to work for so many monsters and
stuff. But it's a movie that's really stayed with me over the last five years since I've seen it.
It was very, very well directed, a very interesting movie. I recommend, and this is their follow -up,
same director, same actress. The lady who did its name is Kitty Green. And it felt very influenced
by like a straw dogs or a movie I watched recently, Picnic at Hanging Rock. Because it's
Australian. It's these two girls who are like going on a cross -country college trip, partying,
drinking, having fun. They run out of money. They wind up in this Australian outback village
bartending to make extra money. And the men of the town, because it's a very male dominated town,
and I know what it sounds like, but this movie isn't really heavy handed at all.
The men of the town, as they drink more and more and more, like society really breaks down.
So it doesn't go to like dark horror places. It's just a very tense, slow burn.
These two women sort of realizing they're in over their heads and they're surrounded by
these animals who are like drunk and horny. And it's not funny anymore. Like it's that
moment when things turn for them. And Barry, again, it's a movie that was sort of unlike
anything I've ever seen and unclassifiable sort of, and that's what I liked the most about it.
It kept me on edge the whole time. I recommend it. The Royal Hotel. Joe?
I watched another terrifying film, In and Out. I went, I tried to go -
With Kevin Kline?
Yeah. I love that movie.
Watch it again. No, you don't.
Joe, I do.
I used to love it too. I watched it again.
A hilarious film.
Oh, it's terrible. It's terrible. I thought so too. I watched it back to back with Philadelphia.
I was like, all right, that was a heavy movie about gay issues.
Yeah.
We watched like a light movie about gay stuff, like just, you know, light in the mood.
And Jesus Christ, it's just, okay, it's from that period. Grumpy Old Man is another one of
these movies. It's from that period in, it's like late 90s, I guess.
97. Saw it on a double feature with The Game, the Fincher movie.
They were doing a thing aesthetically and tonally in the late 90s with comedies where
every big studio comedy had like a whimsical orchestral score.
Yeah. And they look like Hallmark movies, like House Sitter.
Yes.
You know, where it's like, it's almost something funny can't happen in this space. It looks too
perfect. I hate movies like that. I agree. I know this is one, but yes.
And, you know, man, you know, the plot of the movie, if you haven't seen it, is
there's, okay, Kevin Kline plays a teacher at a high school. He is engaged to
Joan Cusack, who also is a teacher at the high school.
The high school -
Supporting actress nominated for the film.
That's insane.
She's hilarious in that movie. She's hilarious in that movie.
So the claim to fame of the high school is that this guy that went there played by Matt
Dillon has become a famous actor and he is now nominated for an Oscar and everybody's all excited.
And the amount that they're talking about this guy.
This was the first red flag to me where I was like, what is going on? Like,
like this just isn't, it's just not believable.
Like everybody's talking about the guy all the time at the play. It's just stupid.
Anyway, and so the guy wins the Oscar. The whole town is watching on a Sunday evening.
Um, he, in his speech, in the movie, he plays a gay guy. This is okay.
This is one of the things I really hate about the movie.
He's nominated for a movie where he plays a gay soldier.
Okay.
The whole reason in and out came to be is it was inspired by Tom Hanks accepting the
Oscar for Philadelphia and outing his drama teacher from high school.
I didn't know that.
That's why I thought you watched them back to back.
No, um -
That's why the movie happened. Go ahead.
He plays a gay soldier in the movie that he's nominated for.
They break, in my opinion, the cardinal rule of comedy, which is a thing you never do,
which is they show scenes from the movie.
Too many scenes.
And the scenes from the movie are funny, written comedically in a way that the people
who you're supposed to believe made a movie would be in on the joke as if they were making
a comedy. And that's not what it's supposed to be.
What it's supposed to be is a send -up of melodrama where you're supposed to laugh at
how melodramatic it is, but they joke every single joke.
And it's a terrible, cringy fucking sequence that's supposed to be a send -up of melodrama
and just fails on all fronts.
Anyway, he then outs his teacher, Kevin Klein's like, but I'm not gay.
And then we're subjected to a farcical romp where everybody is saying he can't be gay
because gay is weird, doesn't age well.
Bob Newhart comes off as particularly unlikable and homophobic, his character,
who also wants to fire Kevin Klein because -
I thought Bob Newhart was pretty damn funny in this movie.
He's funny until he starts becoming -
Listen, you know me, I ain't no wokey -woke.
I'm telling you, the movie didn't age well.
Anyway, it's just not that funny of a movie.
And then the big thing was Tom Selleck kisses Kevin Klein in it.
Yeah, I mean, it was PG -13.
It went for a very broad take on it because again, these were two movies,
one a drama, one a comedy that came at a time where outside of the birdcage,
there wasn't much discussion about this kind of stuff.
And Birdcage was like an R -rated movie.
But when me and my friends saw In -N -Out on opening night,
the audience was very uncomfortable.
And when Tom Selleck kissed Kevin Klein,
three -fourths of the audience left, stood up and left the theater.
So it was a different time.
I mean, it's Missouri, mind you.
But that's kind of the best way to explain what it was like,
because it's not like it was Mississippi burning or something.
But a gay movie was not well received.
The fact that that even got wide release was kind of crazy.
I don't know, I might just have affection for it because of the age I saw it.
But I always thought that movie was pretty damn fine.
I'm telling you, I felt the same way.
I was excited to watch it on the plane.
I was like, this is going to be great.
And I was watching and I was just like,
this just isn't funny.
And I don't mean like funny because I'm so offended
or like funny because like, you know, oh, this didn't age well.
I just mean like, it just wasn't funny.
It was just corny.
Every joke hinged on, you know, gay being the punchline.
And you're like, okay, like, it's just not that funny.
I don't know.
Right.
It's like a way better version of what they tried to do in that movie to me.
And something that does age well, in my opinion, is the birdcage.
Nathan Lane trying to learn how to act straight is still really funny.
It's funnier than Kevin Klein going, why is my hand doing this?
Why is my rib doing this?
Okay, anyway.
Fair enough.
Maybe I should rewatch it.
I watched, I was up for some Netflix show and in classic Hollywood style,
I was up for it.
I was told I was the favorite.
I was told I would be receiving a call that I had it.
And then I was told the position no longer exists.
But I watched an entire season of a Netflix show last week before this
meeting with about three hours notice.
I crammed it in for no reason, wasted my day.
And in starting up my Netflix subscription again, I also checked out this weekend,
Arnold, the three part, three hour plus documentary about the great Arnold Schwarzenegger.
And here's my grievance.
The first hour of the film is Arnold's rise through being a weightlifter.
And this stuff I really already knew about.
And I've seen Pumping Iron.
I know about his past and that world and everything.
Then a one hour section about his movies, by which I mean,
Conan through, you know, end of days, like his entire movie career.
And then the third segment is about him as a politician.
And to me, a movie fan and Arnold fan, that balance just felt way, way, way off.
It's very interesting to me how he became a politician,
but that's a chapter of his life.
We know we saw it.
We watched it happen in real time.
His rise is semi interesting.
You know, he's one of those guys like the rock where the story's like,
if you work hard and keep your head down, you know,
you'll eventually get to where you need to be.
That's his whole thing.
And it's not particularly compelling.
We all know it.
So for me, the frustrating thing was I wanted Arnold's stories
behind the scenes of twins.
They don't even mention kindergarten cop, for example, not a great film,
but I wanted a step by step movie by movie look through his work.
That's what I always want when I watch a documentary about a filmmaker,
an actor, whatever.
I'm glad I watched it, but I will say I was fairly bored in the first and third parts.
So it was just an average overall movie for me.
Some great stuff about the Terminator.
They interviewed Jamie Lee Curtis and Linda Hamilton and James Cameron
and a bunch of people that have worked with Danny DeVito
and Ivan Reitman and all these people.
They have great interviews, but that stuff's not enough to me.
All right.
I only had two.
So let's get to the movie.
Well, then here we go.
Here we go.
Exorcist.
Believer.
This was the third movie of my trilogy.
I saw it in IMAX, which added nothing to the experience.
I was kind of bummed out by it, especially after how cool
style making sense was in IMAX, I thought.
But yeah, so this is David Gordon Green and Danny McBride's reboot,
the exact same team that brought us those Halloween movies.
And as annoyed as I was, I've had this conversation a lot this past week
of like, why after how fucking shitty those Halloween movies are,
would they have this guy take over this $400 million franchise?
I don't get it.
They paid $400 million for the rights to The Exorcist.
And they were like, yeah, we'll just let you do it.
The reason is whether we like them or not, those Halloween movies were made for cheap
and they made a lot of money.
That's what horror is supposed to do.
And they did it very well.
It was a success.
But now they're pulling him off because the movie got bad reviews, the new Halloween,
and it made like 28 mil, which, you know, that's going to be a bomb.
That movie's not doing well.
They're going to have to go in a completely different direction for a sequel.
And we'll get to its failures as a movie, but as the launch of a franchise, what a failure.
Who are we compelled to follow in the future here?
I mean, was it supposed to be, you know, spoiler alert?
Obviously, we're going to be talking about this movie.
There's a very brief cameo at the end from Linda Blair.
Is she supposed to take over the franchise?
This we'll get to that.
All right.
I, first of all, want to say if you think Paola is not real,
the fact that I am seeing articles on certain movie websites saying,
Exorcist scares up 27 million as if that's a big success for a movie that cost them 400 million
dollars.
That is, those are people in cahoots marching for the studio.
There's not a doubt in my mind about it.
This movie, as Pat already said, cost them quite a pretty penny.
And it becomes disastrous.
This is one of the few movies we've reviewed where I have notes.
I often can just kind of remember what I think and talk about the movie and whatever,
but some special things come along where I have notes.
David Gordon Green and Danny McBride, God bless them and their great work in comedy,
should not be allowed to do anything like this ever again.
They are not good at it.
They are not capable.
They don't get it.
The first half of this movie, and I will define the halves as this.
Ellen Burstyn is the second half when she comes into the picture.
The first half is everything leading up to her.
The first half of this movie works.
It makes sense.
Why?
It didn't work for me, but it's certainly more successful than the second half.
I'll grant you.
Well, the first half worked for me because it's what David Gordon Green is capable of doing,
which is defining a indie style dramatic relationship between two characters,
mainly the father and the daughter.
Any other character that has to play a certain
adversarial role or contrary role or whatever role you want to call it,
is not really very well written.
The joke that I keep hearing is the white family is punished for being Trump supporters.
They never say they're Trump supporters, but it's basically insinuated that they are.
But the first half works in the sense that I gave a fuck about Odin, who played the father.
Leslie Odom Jr., yep.
Yeah, and the daughter.
I gave a fuck.
I believed in the relationship.
I cared that something bad might happen.
And you know what?
The one really great exorcist style William Peter Blatty -ish scene takes place in the first half
when the girl is possessed and the first sign of the real possession that you see
where she's laying in the bed in the hospital and Ann Dowd who plays a nurse is taking care of her
and she starts talking and the voice is dubbed with a really creepy man's voice and it sounds
awesome and she goes, Sister Mary Margaret scraped her.
Her insides got scraped out like a rotten pumpkin.
And you realize she's talking about an abortion, but you don't know who.
You just know she's talking about a nun having an abortion, which is a bit jarring to hear.
And then her vagina starts bleeding through the sheets as she cackles laughing.
And I'm like, when that scene happened, I was like, here we go.
This is the exorcist.
Holy shit.
Are they going to pull this off?
Yeah.
And in the next scene, Ann Dowd goes to Leslie Oden Jr.
And is it Oden or Odom?
Odom.
Okay.
Goes to him and says, hey, your daughter is possessed basically.
And he's like, no, she's not.
You're crazy.
And she's like, well, let me tell you why I think she's possessed.
I was a nun and I got pregnant and I aborted the baby and I never told a soul.
And she just, she just, and I also never told a soul what my chosen nun name was.
And she just knew that name and brought up the abortion.
So she's possessed.
Here's a book written by this mother that went through this in the 70s.
Of course, the book is written by Chris McNeil, Alan Bernstein's character.
He goes inside.
He doesn't believe it.
He starts reading the book.
He becomes a believer quite quickly.
Oh yeah.
And then goes to see Alan Bernstein.
And at this point in the movie, I'm excited.
You're putting an end in there.
Just a burst.
Burst, excuse me.
I'm excited at this point in the movie.
I'm like, okay, I care about the two main characters.
They just did a creepy scene that I thought worked.
And now we're bringing in the legacy characters.
This is awesome.
I'm in.
Why are people saying this movie is laughably bad?
And then enter Alan Bernstein with the line of the century
because pussy ass fucking Jason Blum can't fucking help himself.
I can't fucking wait till this guy fucks up
and the chickens come home to roost on this.
This jag off stroke himself fucking virtue signaling douchebag.
Alan Bernstein is telling Leslie about her exorcism,
her daughter's exorcism.
And he says, did you witness it?
And she says, no, I wasn't allowed to.
And he says, why?
And she goes, if you ask me, it's because I wasn't a member
of their damn patriarchy.
Ellen, you saw the first movie.
You were in the first movie.
You know, as well as any of us who love that movie,
that is not what happened.
How dare you even let them put that fucking line into the movie.
Nothing to do.
I watched two nights ago the new 4k version of The Exorcist
and that it sat me up in my chair how wrongheaded the line was.
Unlike Joe, I wasn't really loving it till that point.
I was bored out of my school till that point.
But yeah, that is a turning point when she enters the film.
And it just starts this endless flow of speeches and monologues
where the characters say exactly in the most thuddingly obvious way
what the alleged subtext of the movie is.
And what a slap in the face.
What a crucifix in the vagina to one of the great horror movies of all time.
I mean, a movie that pushes the envelope in every way,
a movie that makes you feel evil.
It makes you feel like you're watching something genuinely evil
in a way that every horror movie has been chasing.
And after all this time and all these failed sequels,
by the way, I would say this might be the new worst.
This might be the new worst Exorcist sequel.
They make it suddenly into some weird message movie.
And messages that are confusing.
There was a point in this movie, I was watching the guys from Dead Pit.
I follow them on YouTube.
I really like the Dead Pit guys and I really love the Red Letter Media guys.
And I watch a lot of their movie reviews.
The Dead Pit guys were like, I think it was an anti -abortion movie.
They were like, they were like, I couldn't tell what the fuck the message was.
Well, look, to me, I've said it before.
Eastbound Down is one of the most perfect TV shows ever made.
And I like everything else they've done on the comedy side.
This is not their forte.
I hope that they stop this.
Can I tell you something, Pat?
Yes.
Two things.
First of all, the speeches are written as if Kenny Powers wrote them.
The speeches are so dumb.
It's like what Kenny Powers would write into a script.
And number two -
You mentioned the great Ann Dowd, her speech at the end,
where she basically said that this got laughs in the theater.
When she's like, people just want to follow their dreams.
And the devil, he makes you not follow your dreams.
But you gotta learn to fight the devil.
I'm like, is this a reading rainbow episode?
Follow your dreams is the message of the new Exorcist franchise?
So -
What the fuck?
The big turning point -
I don't want to make it sound like the turning point for me is the patriarchy line.
I actually was willing to swallow that line and go, all right, maybe there's a sense to it.
And then as the movie went on from there, I was like, no, it doesn't make sense.
The movie tonally shifts when Burston comes into it.
And it's not her fault.
They give her dogshit dialogue.
It's terrible.
But the movie tonally shifts -
They blinded her early on.
She's wearing a bandana for half the running time.
It's very clear that the editor saved and salvaged the first half of the movie
because he knew how to edit a movie to make it look like The Freedkin Exorcist
and to make it look like Blatty's Exorcist 3.
Then there's tonal shift happens,
and somebody's fucking fingerprints are all over the second half of this.
I'm going to say it's David Gordon Green because of how bad those Halloween movies were.
And it feels like those Halloween movies in the second half.
But what I was going to say before is this is why this needs to stop.
The rating of the original movie has now dropped like 7 %
because people have now left worse reviews for that,
saying that this movie is making us realize the original is not good.
Guys, stop fucking this up.
This is not what William Peter Blatty would have wanted.
You've made a sequel that is ignoring the sequel written by the guy
that wrote the goddamn original book and movie.
Yeah.
Look, it goes against the spirit, the tone, the vibe.
It goes against everything we want from The Exorcist,
everything we expect from The Exorcist, everything we'd like.
I think we all were kind of hoping that even if it wasn't perfect,
the ship would be righted a little bit.
But it's such a miss on every level.
But the biggest, to me, the biggest issue,
especially having just watched the original Exorcist,
is that the effects are worse in the new one.
It is 1000 % less scary.
And the original Exorcist now is 50 years old, 50 years old.
It is so much more horrifying, so much more everything.
This movie has all the tools in the world at its disposal,
all these tools that did not exist in 1973,
and it does nothing with them.
I can't point to one other than what Joe mentioned,
which I just thought was kind of repeating the shock value
of the crucifix masturbation scene from the original.
I can't think of one moment in this
where the hair stood up in the back of my neck.
I felt uncomfortable even, let alone scared.
I mean, I just thought this was a pathetic relaunch.
And I'm surprised with what they spent,
that they didn't scrap it or else keep the first half
and bring in a horror person to fix the back half.
If you're going to launch a franchise this expensive,
they've made huge mistakes.
They do nothing with it.
In the original movie, she shoves her mother's face
into her bloody crotch.
I'm watching the climactic exorcism sequence in this thing,
and I'm waiting for the daughter
to start saying sexual things to her father.
And I'm like, that's upsetting.
Do that.
Take this to a place where it's upsetting.
And they just do nothing.
There's a lot of stupid vomit effects that are terrible.
This also, and this is Red Letter Media
went in pretty hard on this point,
and I agree with them 100%.
The inclusion factor of bringing in like this
Avengers of all religions in the end
is not only just convoluted and pointless.
It also means you can't pinpoint who the demon is.
A demon can't belong to every religion.
That's not how it works.
And then it undercuts Burston's thing
where she's going, we've met before.
By the way, how about,
this is when I knew we were in real trouble.
Burston confronts, first of all, she goes,
when she sees the young black girl in the hospital,
she goes, where is the other girl who's possessed?
Because there's a black girl and a white girl.
They go, it's literally like,
what if two girls were possessed?
That's probably how the sequel came to be.
They're tending to her at home.
She goes, that's not good.
Yeah.
Then what do they do in the climax?
They bring the girls home.
It's fucking idiotic.
But anyway, she goes to the girl's home
and it's laid to waste.
And you're like, holy shit,
did this little girl kill her whole family?
No, she didn't.
They're just all freaked out, I guess.
The little girl and Ellen Burston face off for a second.
And she stabs out Ellen Burston's eye.
It's the most absurd, fucking ridiculous.
I'm talking ridiculous, violent,
in the way that that Kevin James movie
where he plays the Nazi is absurd.
Becky, yeah.
It's just so fucking stupid.
And it is, it really is.
It was just such a letdown.
And what you're saying about this,
all the religions thing,
the original Exorcist,
that I think the reason it's so powerful,
the reason that this was the first horror movie I saw
and it deeply traumatized me
is because my dad wanted me to see it
because of its strong roots in Catholicism,
which I know is very fucked up.
But he's like, I want you to learn about your history basically.
So they say at the beginning of the Exorcist
that like this is something that the Catholics bury under the rug.
You know, they're the only people who still do it.
And again, this is a 50 year old movie.
And they'd often rather they sweep it under the rug.
A lot of them think it's a joke.
So why do we now have five religions joining in?
What are you talking about?
They also do.
Of course.
Also, where was Russell Crowe?
Where was the Pope's Exorcist?
If we're going to get the truly best Exorcist.
I mean, I'll tell you this.
This movie goes from one star to four and a half.
With like five minutes to spare,
they cut to him on that Dumb and Dumber scooter
coming up and the music kicks in.
I mean, I would love it.
Did you know William Friedkin made a documentary
about the guy that the Pope's Exorcist, the real guy?
I knew he made a documentary.
I didn't know that was the guy.
It's about that guy.
So there is connective tissue.
But instead, what they do is, of course,
they make the Catholic priest the weakling
that won't come into the fight.
Because there's too much bureaucratic bullshit.
And by the way, my hat's off to David Gordon Green
for now bringing in the latest racist cliche in horror movies.
This is my new favorite racist cliche in horror movies.
Now, David Gordon Green in the past
and all three Halloween movies had offensively,
in my opinion, stereotypical black characters in those.
Oh, yeah.
I remember, you know, really being jarred by a few of them.
Well, the worst being that DJ in the third movie.
It was just crazy.
The foul mouthed Webster kid in the first one was genuinely funny,
but also like, OK.
And then I remember really being uncomfortable
when Michael Myers slowly kills an elderly black couple.
It just felt really weird and gratuitous.
Yeah, it always had a weird vibe with race for some reason.
Yeah.
And the only way he could make it worse or more offensive
is if one of those black characters was also into voodoo
and explained what was going on.
Now, he does that basically in this movie
with like this high priestess lady, basically.
She saves the day with everything.
So he's getting that cliche in there.
But he matches that and he ups the ante
with my new favorite horror movie cliche racist character,
the Mexican priest.
I love the Mexican priest that's in everything now.
Never just a guy.
It's never just a Hispanic guy who happens to be priest.
It's always a guy who literally just got here from Mexico.
You know, the Pablo talks as if he was praying over
the dying soldiers at the Alamo.
Like, it's just it is me.
So that guy is the guy that works for the church
and won't partake in the exorcism and then comes in like a hero,
which they also do this with Burston,
comes in like a hero.
And you're like, OK, here we go and immediately is cast aside.
These girls have the power and the strength to murder people
with their minds.
They do to this priest by mentally twisting his neck till it breaks.
Yet they're not killing everybody in the room trying to exorcise them.
There are, you know, I'm a big stickler for rules with this stuff.
There are no rules to any of this.
It makes no sense when they go one girl must die.
You're like, but why?
I don't understand the whole.
Their hearts are beating in unison.
What? What is what is going on?
Like, like none of this makes any sense.
Yeah, I'll tell you, you know, what really did the movie
no fucking favors was watching this new 4K of The Exorcist two nights before.
And in recent years, recent Halloween's,
I've only watched the director's cut with the spider walk.
So I was going back to the OG version and it's just.
You know, it's imperfect.
I won't say it's perfect.
It's imperfect, which leads to something perfect.
You know, like the scenes that don't immediately fall into the story of the movie
are these great little character beats.
Just it's just one of those 70s things where it like almost seems like by accident,
you've got like this perfect, like amazing thing.
I cranked they had this Dolby Atmos sound mix on it and the, you know,
the new picture and everything.
It was incredible.
And how's the picture on it, by the way?
It's it's great, but it isn't it is an old movie.
You know, it's not like it's not like like the best looking.
The biggest upgrade is the Iraq section at the beginning.
Okay.
So like the Georgetown stuff and in the streets probably wind up looking the best,
but it's a good transfer for sure.
The sound is incredible.
And they let you use the original 70s sound mix, which I guess has never been available.
I didn't do that, but you could.
It's just perfect.
And the new one, you know, it's just the hubris, you know,
the hubris to step up to the plate at this point.
With this movie and, you know, they must have gone back and watched the original
for inspiration and like, we got to capture the raw feeling of this.
You know, there's 70s film guys, every, every interview I've ever seen with McBride
and Gordon Green, they talk about how much they love 70s film.
Observe and report with Seth Rogen is a better example of the 70s film.
That's like the taxi driver of comedy.
It's a very, very incredible on the edge R rated comedy.
And somehow their exorcist has less bite to it.
Less edge.
I don't know if that's a reflection of the times we live in or what, but,
yeah, my, I would say my pulse did not raise watching this movie.
And I don't know if I would see future entries in this franchise,
but the same team behind it.
I just don't know if I,
I just, I think that I've said it before on this pod.
I'll say it again.
And I will also say the only good thing that came from this is that my claim
of Jason Blum being the biggest hack to Evergrace Horror is only
reassured with every fucking movie he produces.
He is terrible.
He makes bad shit.
And he's got to smear his fucking agenda feces all over everything he does.
And it's finally biting him in the ass.
Finally.
And he has said, this is the riskiest movie I've ever made
because of the amount of money we spent on it.
He wanted to go wave his big fucking dick around
and it's blowing up in his face and it makes me happy.
And that's, and I stand by that.
He's got no balls.
And if you want to know how little balls this fucking guy actually has,
go watch some interviews with William Friedkin.
That's a guy with fucking balls.
The interviews with William Friedkin are, have you watched these things?
Yeah, for sure.
I mean, there were two documentaries made about him, Friedkin Uncut,
and then another one about The Exorcist where they interview him at length.
And he's just one of the great cranks of all time.
But you can also see compilations of him saying insane things.
And I don't give a fuck what Al Pacino fucking said.
You know, like he is great.
But he goes, Al Pacino said in Cruising that he thought,
and he just cuts the guy off and he goes,
I don't give a flying fuck into a rolling doughnut with Al Pacino things.
Is that clear enough for you?
Is that an answer?
You know, what you would love is,
have you ever seen him dressing down Nicholas Winding Refn?
No.
So who I know you hate, but -
Wait, Nicholas Winding, who's Nicholas Winding?
He did Drive and Only God Forgives and all those, you know, kind of,
we reviewed a few of them on the show and you hated them.
Neon Demon and all that.
But he's interviewing Friedkin.
You can tell Friedkin just is not a fan of his.
And it was supposed to be one of these like director on director,
like mutual respect things.
And Refn's teasing him a little bit, but he's like, you know,
only time will tell if, you know, his Only God Forgives a masterpiece.
And he goes, time will tell.
He goes, Grace, would you please call the sanitarium?
Would you have them sent?
We've got a man who's lost his fucking mind here.
Would you please send?
You think the movie is a fucking masterpiece?
Are you fucking kidding?
Right to his face.
Are you kidding me?
He's like, you know, Drive is another one.
He's like, Drive?
Time will tell?
That movie was made five seconds ago.
Shut your fucking mouth.
It's fantastic.
And I love Nicholas Winding Refn.
Well, the funniest thing is about, in my opinion, about Friedkin is
he, he sounds and once I tell you this, Walsh,
you're not going to be able to unhear it.
All right.
He sounds exactly like Donald Trump.
The other similarities, for sure.
But you like him.
He sounds like Trump, but you like him.
So he says like, he'll be like,
When I'm on the set of The Friends Connection.
A little bit of that.
There's an interview where he's like, they're like, what do you think of all these like,
you know, CGI and AI and whatever.
And he's like, I think it's marvelous.
I think that's all up to the people who use it.
And he goes, you can't say it's bad.
That's like saying, you know, people, would you drive a buggy down the street now?
No, you drive a car.
Cars are fantastic.
Jesus, he's Trump.
But anyway, yeah, the that it's there's a thing where I'm watching.
There's an interview with him where a guy says, like some famous critic.
And he goes, this critic said that making a film is a tennis match.
And it's the director's job to lob the ball to the critic.
And it's the critic's job to lob the ball.
And he gets that part.
Freaking goes, that's stupid.
That's stupid.
I don't give a shit how respected this guy is.
That's a stupid thing to say.
Yeah, yeah, he's great.
I also highly recommend his autobiography, either on audible or in book form.
We will return folks with talk to me, which has been much requested for such a recent movie,
but the new horror film, which is also Australian.
Yes.
Our New Zealand ish.
I believe it was Australian.
Joe, are you there?
Joe, Joe.
I'm listening.
Yeah, I'm listening.
I thought you were going to say, sorry.
It was one of those moments where I thought you were going to keep talking.
And then you didn't.
I was just asking if talk to me was Australian.
Oh, oh, I didn't know you were.
I'm sorry.
I didn't realize you were asking me.
I thought that was like a, I thought that was like to the,
I thought that was a, what is that called?
A rhetorical question?
Rhetorical, yes.
Hey, just so long as the question still doesn't get answered.
That'd be great.
Yeah, it's either Australian or New Zealand, as you said.
I can't tell the goddamn accents apart.
Can you?
No, but we'll look it up before the show.
But that's what we're doing next.
Joe and I are going to be doing, we'll see you in Hell live on October 28th in New York City
at Arlene's Grocery, where Joe's band will also perform, Salsa Windfall, very exciting,
and many other special guests as well.
Some announced, some not.
Joseph?
Yes, I'm excited for our live thing.
Emily will be in the house.
She's bringing some merch.
That'll be for sale.
And we've got, we've got a trick or two up our sleeves for live.
We'll see you in Hell.
And you know we're bringing the treats, baby, but we also got tricks.
Okay.
We're very, we're very, very excited.
And I'm excited, of course, for Salsa Windfall to be playing
and to the other acts that are going to be there and everything.
Also, I want to just plug my shows coming up.
I got to pull these up here, Pat.
I apologize.
I can't remember.
It's just so many shows, Pat, you know?
Radio City musical.
To furnish here.
Yeah, I'll be selling juji fruits in the lobby.
New York, New York.
After the Arlene's Grocery show on the 28th, I'm doing a reading at KGB Bar
for my audiobook that came out earlier this summer, The Penthouse Papers.
That's November 9th, part of the New York Comedy Festival.
November 11th, I'll be in Philly, PA, hometown.
Theater of the Living Arts, big show.
Saturday, November 11th.
November 17th, Pittsburgh.
That's sold out, actually.
Pittsburgh is sold out.
Philly is almost sold out.
Get your ticket now.
November 18th, Buffalo, New York.
November 30th, Denver, Colorado.
December 1st, Phoenix.
December 3rd, Salt Lake City.
And I've got fall, excuse me, winter dates coming soon for the new year.
Anyway, go to joderosa .com and get your business.
And also, if you're in New York, you can go to Joey Roses.
Seven days a week, joeyrosesnyc .com.
I think that's it.
All right.
Thank you, everybody.
We'll see you next time and we will see you in hell.