It's your bonus app, it's your bonus app, it's your goddamn dirty bonus app.
It is.
How are you, Joe?
I'm doing all right, Pat.
I'm doing all right.
I'm in the Christmas spirit.
We're about, we're a little ways out yet.
We're still about two weeks out, but I'm always happy as it approaches.
I'm also in the Star Wars spirit because per this recording last Jedi is four days away
from premiering, and the spoiler free reviews came out last night.
How are they favorable?
Extremely favorable.
Now, how does it hit like, I understand that Justice League was better than people expected,
but I remember you saying and also reading on Ainut cool and other things like that it was
an all time action masterpiece, so how do these things happen?
Did I say that about Justice League?
You said you had heard that it was like, well, there were mixed, they did early screenings.
The first screening said, oh, it's brilliant.
The second one said, it's a mess, okay, then all that just, we didn't stuff happen, so I
don't know.
I guess that's what happened.
I don't know.
But this was, they had the premiere last night here in LA, and these are the reviews from
Hollywood Reporter and stuff, they had to do all their spoiler free reaction tweets, but
every tweet was like, it's one of the best Star Wars movies ever, it's crazy, do not read
any of the internet spoilers, do not, the new TV spot, it says in it, do not let anyone
spoil this for you.
They said it's definitely not a rehashing of empire, and they're just like, it's crazy.
Apparently, it's got like the best Star Wars action sequences, and I don't know, they're
really great reviews.
Do we have 3D tickets or old fashioned?
Old fashioned.
Good, good.
I like to go in old Pat and I are going Thursday to see it, early show, 7 pm Thursday, East Coast
is beaten us by three hours, but that's the first one we could get into, so we're in good
shape.
We're in good shape.
You know, I got four tickets, five maybe, maybe I don't give any of them away, we spread
out like Kings, I heard of a guy who was on the best show podcast, I'm sharp one, and
I thought it was a story that you would, that would just anger you just on site, not even
knowing this man.
Sure.
He goes to see King Crimson, the guy's big prog rock fan, he goes, he gets third row seats
because he's there by himself, and he sits down, guy sits down on the seat right next
to him, and there's two seats to his right.
So he's like, I don't want to sit need and need with this other guy who's like here
by himself.
It's very awkward.
So he starts to move over into one of these open seats.
The guy behind him goes, excuse me, I have these two seats, the guy behind him, and he goes,
well, what do you mean?
Are you planning on sitting here?
And he goes, no, no, no, no, I bought those seats, but these seats behind were open, so
I'm sitting here so that I can have a clearer view of the stage, but I paid for those seats
so you can't sit in them.
Well tough shit, pal.
I know.
Well, he said he just kind of, you know, moved head down like, I don't, I can't even get
involved in this.
But did he sit in the seats?
No, because they were technically the guy's seats, but he wasn't sitting in them.
This is, this is how sick people are, how self -obsessed people are.
I tell you, I had to do, yesterday and today, a trip from my home, or in the Los
Villas area, to deep Marina Del Rey, in one case, Venice, in the other case, we're talking
an hour long drive to go, in both cases, 12 miles, and I'm shaking a little bit.
I'm so rattled by this drive.
I won't do it when my parents visit, I'm sorry.
I say, take the car you guys go, I know, I'm not going.
I did both of those, and then in the middle, a trip to LAX, which is the same distance,
to, with more irritants, because everyone's honking and driving around like crazy.
My mom was in town this weekend, I drove her out there, I mean, I tell you, I know people
like LA for a variety of reasons.
The driving, which I, more often than not get to avoid, you know who loves it, it's time
to get out of here.
You know who loves it away, Randy Newman.
Yeah, you can beat me to it.
You like that song?
I love that song, it makes me very happy, and it's very, the song is kind of anti -LA, which
I like about him.
Oh, it is?
I mean, he's always got like the gentlest of satire to his song.
Sure.
You know, the one of the verses is like, look at that bum man, he's down on his knees, you
know, like, but he sings it all up.
Right.
Well, at first, it's like, look at the beaches and everything, and then by the end, it's
like, look at this bum, look at this.
I got one for you, I do hate Randy Newman, but that's a good song.
I got one for you.
Go on.
Well, wait, here's a good transition.
Speaking of Randy Newman, my friend, you always tell me about when Phantom Manus came out,
Mad TV did a sketch, where it was Randy Newman was going to do the soundtrack to the Phantom
Manus.
I never saw it, but he would always tell me he would do the one little sasso as Randy Newman.
I don't know who played it, but he said, he said, one of the jokes was, he sang this song
and he goes, spaceships fly, oh, me, oh, my, which is really funny.
You got a friend, didn't me.
I hate him and I hate Dr. John, who have a very similar vibe, like an old swamp loser.
I can deal with Randy Newman.
Dr. John is like, that reminds me of all, like, the fake hippies I went to college with.
Yes.
Like, that's like, oh, Dr. John, so cool, man.
He's like, oh, shut up.
He's really not.
Yeah.
He'd be cool if he was a black man.
What I don't find cool is a white man doing essentially black voice, which is, which is
a lot of music.
Gavin DeGraw comes to mind.
I hate Gavin DeGraw.
I hate that affected style of singing where a young, squeaky, clean looking white man sings
in a, sings, emulating old, like, R &B singers, and then goes on to greater success than
those people.
Yeah.
It drives me insane.
It's irritating.
It's insulting.
Iggy Azalea comes to mind.
I mean, it's just disgraceful.
Wow.
But she's got that ass.
I mean, I get why she's.
I also get tired of, I'm just going to throw this out there.
Please.
Maybe I'll finish.
I'll finish.
I'm tired of white lady singer songwriters that have like a rich voice.
So I'm getting tired of that.
Like every time I hear about a new white young, female musician, and then somebody goes, she's
so good.
And I cut to it.
And every time she's doing that, like knock off Fiona Apple voice, like, oh, I should get
in there.
And I'm like, it's like, it's like anybody can learn how to just imitate.
Fiona Apple actually has that voice.
And Nora Jones, everyone was doing that for 10 years.
Tell you what, Nora Jones sucks too, guys.
I never mind it, Nora Jones.
I think I'm starting to like Fiona Apple.
I heard that.
I heard that Fiona Apple song on the radio the other day.
And I really liked it.
The one where she's like, I'm a dirty old.
No, no, no.
No, no, not her songs go.
I'm a dirty old.
Anything.
Yeah.
She's like, I'm a bad, bad girl.
Oh, I mean, her first big song, Criminal.
Yes.
I've been a bad.
Yeah.
Great.
Great song.
It's got a bit of a who's coming up and see me sometime.
May west.
Yeah, it's got a little me west to it.
I like it.
Anyway, Apple, I went to a concert of hers at the Greek ones by myself.
I was out in a walk.
And I walk past the Greek.
and some guy was like $10 tickets.
I was like, sure, I like Fiona app.
I mean, I might as well have been hissed
on the way to my seat.
Like a guy walking down this sea of women
and they all were just looking at me like,
look at this fucking asshole.
To be fair, Pat, you were wearing
your free pussy inspections t -shirt.
Which, sure.
I don't think you should,
I think you should have changed that.
In my defense, it was a tank top, not a t -shirt.
That was wearing his, no ma 'am shirt
that he bought from the married with children.
The set of the web store.
But before you go on, I feel like we should probably
just take this time to get on with the show.
And in doing so on, we the jaw.
I don't want to fall in love.
There you go, right?
Good. Now we're back on the 90s hits thing.
Yeah, that was 91.
That's very good.
That was very good.
Thank you.
I gotta know.
Now you sound like there's white girls I'm talking about.
Yeah.
I gotta tell you what I saw today.
All right.
Brought me to my knees.
Okay.
Driving into your dad came by?
Fuck.
I thought you said you hadn't seen that uncle in years.
I drove to the climate we shouldn't be joking.
Supermarket today.
Okay.
Ooh, it's rough.
Sitting on the curb.
Tell you what, wasn't so super gang.
Okay.
Sitting on the curb on the outskirts of the parking lot, right?
A man I can only assume by the state of his face
he was homeless.
Sure.
There was dirt on his face.
Okay.
Wearing a Santa Claus suit.
Clearly drunk.
Just staring down at the ground.
It was a rough combo man.
I was there all day.
I wish you'd said hello.
And the Santa Claus suit looked new.
That's what I understand.
His face was dirty but the suit was sparkly clean.
Was the gentleman trying to solicit people sitting on his lap
or no, he was staring down like what has it all come to?
How has it come to this?
So maybe look, maybe he was a mall,
a jersey that twilight zone,
a night of the meek with the drunk Santa was like that.
Or maybe he was like bad Santa.
Right.
You know, like, but it was, it was, it was crazy.
Sounds terrible.
I mean, he wasn't even asking anybody for anything.
It was just sitting there like, fuck this shit.
Well, then maybe he found it.
Well, they do a Santa con here just like New York.
Somebody probably threw it in a dumpster
and he was like, here's a nice warm outfit.
Very some poor bastard came out from Kansas
on his last dollar to go to Santa con.
Got turned out by the first pimp that saw him
when he stepped off the bus.
Ho, ho, ho.
Pimp's pointing at three Santas.
That was good.
That was really good.
Now let me ask you, have you ever gone to Santa con?
No.
Now it is, it is a very justly hated event.
People always talk a lot of shit about it.
I used to, was it hated?
Well, the people, the two cool for school crowds
always like, fuck in Santa con.
Just we need more alcoholics running around the town
and the people always tweet about how much it sucks
and whatever.
It's a lot of loud drunks.
There's a fratty element to it.
Is it mall, Santa's getting together?
Anyone can go.
You got to dress as Santa.
I went, oh, okay.
Well, maybe one of my first years in LA,
I was trying to make friends and I went with a couple friends
down, dressed up, not, you know, not heavily,
but you know, I had in a jacket or whatever.
And for me, it was a very cool way
to see like a ton of different bars.
We went downtown.
We went to like a union station and had a drink and that.
So it was kind of like a bar crawl
with people dressed as Santa,
but we didn't team up with the huge mob.
We started our own kind of side group and it was fun.
I must say, I made out with a Mrs. Clause by a dumpster.
How old are we talking here?
Gone a little beyond making out at one point.
Folks, it's not your business.
Did you, did you, why did you bring this up, folks?
Yeah, did you reach into her cookie jar?
All right, Joe.
All right.
Wow.
No, I was probably, you know, 25.
I had a good time.
I saw a lot of Santa's puking, okay,
which is always fun.
But it gets a bad rap.
It just seems out of control.
Like by the time I got to like the 10 p .m. slot,
when you started drinking at noon, it's rough.
It's like when we do our pub crawl and like as I've discussed,
our friend Kurt was angrily talking to a wall
when I left that last thing.
Things get out of hand,
but a lot of the people who would go to a Santa con
are more kind of testosteroney
and things get a little weird.
Right.
But I liked it.
If you're looking for friends in a new town,
it's not bad.
I thought you were saying that it's literally a con
for like where malls Santa's get together
and trade trade trade secrets and things like that.
I'm sure that exists too.
Here's how you get a kid to sit in your lap longer
where stuff like that.
Here's how you move the higher end merchandise.
Right, right.
That was a joke on cheers the other day.
Moving the big like Santa was trying to move.
Norm becomes a mall Santa and then they're all drinking
in the barn, Christmas Eve and they're one of the jokes
is like they moved a lot of the high end big box products.
Right.
Like they're planting it in the Santa's
to move products for them.
Now are you going through the cheers now?
No, but I watched.
Well, I'm gonna save it for the non bonus episode,
but what I did this week for Pat's movie corner
which will be part of our Christmas episode.
Yeah, that we're recording in a bit.
I watched Christmas episodes of several sitcoms.
Sure, sure.
And I really went through the game.
Always, some of the best ones really.
Yeah, I went through the game and I hit a lot of them
and they were all really fun to watch.
Okay, but anyway, that's why I watched the cheers one.
Yeah, favorite TV Christmas episode of all time, Jen?
I'll talk about it.
You know what?
I'll do it here.
I'll do this one here for the fans
because this is my favorite thing.
The two -parter, it's a Bundiful Life episode
of Married With Children is, in my opinion,
nothing short of a masterpiece.
It is so fucking funny.
I remember it well.
It is so depraved.
It is so tasteless.
It's awesome.
I mean, they hit all the marks.
It opens with, you hear Al's car pull into the driveway.
And from inside the house, you hear him walk towards the door
and then go, oh God, that's how the episode starts.
And Peggy goes, daddy's home.
He's so sad to be coming back to these people.
And then the premise is, he started a Christmas fund
like at the bank or whatever.
So they were actually going to get presents this year.
And so the whole first episode is them trying to con him
and to buy each one of them trying to buy him
the most presents or whatever.
You know, like in Bud telling him, Kelly doesn't love him
and Kelly telling him he's dying, whatever.
And then of course, he doesn't get to the bank on time
and he doesn't get the money.
So he can't buy the presents for Christmas.
This is the first start.
Some key jokes, though.
He's bitching about the mall opening line, opening line.
I hate Christmas.
The mall is a, it's a, it's a madhouse.
Women and children everywhere.
I want this.
Give me that.
I need this.
And then there's the children.
We're up to a good start.
Yeah, that's fine.
Yeah.
I can't argue with them.
He starts bitching about the Santa Claus in front of his thing
that's collecting for the needy.
And he goes, I've got the Salvation Army Santa Claus
in front of my store ring in a bell all day.
As if you need a bell to recognize an alcoholic
and a costume, which is another funny joke.
When he can't get to the bank, he starts a thing in the store
to raise money at the last minute
where he says, oh, watch people's kids while they shop
and he ties the kids up with Garland in the store.
It just makes it.
I do remember this.
So anyway, that's part one.
He doesn't get the money, everybody's pissed at
or gonna be pissed at him.
He goes home the next night in the second part.
Everybody obviously is very mad at him
that he didn't bring this money home
and they're not getting presents
and they go to Denny's for dinner without him
and they can't afford for all four of them to eat there.
It's only the three of them go.
And he's outside trying to get the Christmas lights to work
and they don't work and he's frustrated and he says,
sometimes I think it'd be better if I'd never been born.
Sticks a screwdriver into one of the lights
like into the socket and electrocutes him.
Sure.
And then it turns into what's a wonderful life.
Sam Kinnison is his guardian angel.
Was he, so he was trying to kill himself?
No, he's just, he's an idiot.
That the joke is he's an idiot
and he's putting a screwdriver into an electric thing
but as he's doing it, he goes,
yeah, sometimes I wish I'd never been born.
Right.
And then he falls down and Sam Kinnison comes
and he's guarding the angel and that I do remember that.
And then the gag is, which is brilliant
because this had never been done at this point.
Everybody's life is infinitely better
that he's not there.
Right, right, right.
And that's what makes him want to live at the end.
Kinnison's exit from the show is a network sitcom.
Yeah.
He talks about how much he hates his ex -wife.
Great line, he goes, he talks about his ex -wife
how she like fucked everybody behind his back.
And he goes, but I showed her, buddy.
I canceled my insurance and hung myself in the garage
and he starts cackling and Ed O 'Neil goes,
and you're here to help me.
Right, but what's it called?
They go in, whole family's happy.
But he's like, I want to live.
Kinnison's like, why, I don't understand.
He goes, these people are happy, I can't have this.
I have to go back and make the miserable again, which is great.
And then Kinnison's exit is him saying,
I'm gonna get my wings now, I'm an angel.
And he goes, but before I go, I'm gonna go back
to my wife's trailer where she lives.
And put a box of ding -dongs just out of arms
reach of her 1 ,000 pound body.
And as she heaves her gut over the table, right?
This is exit.
This is the very wife who was fucking all over town.
Yeah, okay.
As he heaves her gut over the table
and grabs one of the ding -dongs and lifts her four chins
to fit it into her mouth, right?
He goes, I'm gonna turn the ding -dong into my rotting corpse.
Holy cow.
Then as he disappears into thin air,
because he's an angel, he spins in a circle.
As he screams to the side, daddy's home,
you hear me, honey, you pig, you slut.
This is exit.
That's insane.
Yeah.
And then Al comes back and everybody hates him, right?
But I absolutely love it as a Christmas special.
It is so, I'm watching it when I get home tonight
because I saw it probably when I was a kid.
Yeah, it's just bad taste.
And it's funny and you know, it's fun.
Well, when you go low, Joe, much like Michelle Obama,
I will go high, I'm often compared to Miss Michelle Obama.
I would have to go with, and actually while you were talking,
I was kind of thinking, I don't even really have a runner up.
I go with the office Christmas special.
It's beautiful.
It's just one of the best hours of television of all time.
Now, I like the extras Christmas special
more than the office one.
It's great, but they're both really wonderful.
Yeah.
And I will say, I don't know that we've ever discussed
the Steve Carell office on here, or if you even watched it.
I didn't watch it.
It was, it got so bad in the end that I forgot how much I absolutely
loved it for a really long time.
And I started watching a couple of old favorites the other night
and I was laughing hard.
It was a very funny show, but they did a white elephant exchange
episode.
That's a real masterclass as well.
So if you're watching sitcom Christmas episodes,
I would look that one right.
It's really, really funny.
And Carell on that show, that's the best vehicle he ever had.
I mean, he's hilarious.
Anytime I've watched clips from the show,
yeah, he's very funny, obviously.
It's crazy.
I wanted to hate it.
I was working, I was an NBC marketing
when that show came out.
So I was doing like PowerPoints for it, not to brag.
And I was just kind of like, what are they doing?
Like they're going to ruin one of the greatest things of all time.
And the first one is a line for line remake of the British pilot.
Okay.
And it's trash.
It's terrible.
I think I saw that and I think I was like, I'm not doing this.
Yeah, they, yeah, especially if you were a fan of the British one,
it's like, what are you guys doing?
It's down to like the stapler in the jello bit is exactly.
Yeah, exactly.
But they, they lock into it perfectly in episode two,
two is diversity day, where they all are supposed to put a minority's name
on a sticker on their head and guess who the other one is.
And it's got Michael Scott doing the Chris Rock bit,
complete with F words and N words.
And I mean, this is you going high now.
Oh, no, the office one was you going high.
Sorry, the British office, yeah.
But I will say not that anyone needs my recommendation
for the the American office.
But I think it's oddly become a very underrated show
because it just, it was on the air too long.
But in its first five years, I mean,
it was a really very, very funny show.
I will revisit it.
All right, all right, because I've had some distance now.
Now I feel like I could watch it.
But I do, if you to do, I can tell you if you to do.
The British office is great.
The British office Christmas special is great.
It's just a beautiful moment at the end.
The microphone bit.
The thing with, well, there's the picture.
When he's like, can we do just the people
that were here then?
It's just a really nice moment.
I love the David Brent movie.
I thought it was hilarious.
You know, it definitely had some laughs.
I'll give you that.
I didn't love it, but it definitely had some laughs.
Yeah, when he goes, when he goes coming spelled C U M M I N.
And he goes, got it.
And she goes, why would you say cumin?
He's coming, think.
Yeah, he's really good at being a prick.
Yeah, oh, well, obviously.
Yeah, no, he's, he's fucking, I'm still a fan of your base.
I wish you would do what the fuck's the worst thing even did?
Well, Derek probably, which I never watched.
Derek was not great.
It was pretty heavy handed, but Derek had some really
really funny shit in it.
Yeah, when it got sappy, it got too sappy.
Yeah.
But the funny parts, there's a character in Derek.
I can't remember the guy's name.
He's the most disgusting character
that's ever been in a TV show.
Yeah.
He walks around in sweatpants drinking all day,
hanging at the home for elderly people.
Right.
Because his friend is the gender there.
And he just tries to fuck anything he can.
Wait, someone does this in Derek?
Yes.
But not your race.
No, Jervais plays Derek.
Right.
Oh, there's a character who's trying to fuck handicapped people?
No, no, no, Derek doesn't, we're going to handicapped him.
We were sort of senior citizens.
Oh, okay.
And this guy doesn't try to fuck the people at the home,
but he's like, he's just, he's just disgusting.
Like, he's got no moral.
There's a scene where he farts at the table.
And then he's like, uh, shit myself.
And he's got to go, you know, it's one of those characters.
Uh -huh, sure.
Sure.
But he's, it's really funny
because he's so gross.
I, uh, in looking back most of the times I made love, uh, in my single days,
we're always wildly unexpected.
Like, I would be, I would be like, even the next day, like, how did that happen?
Whereas, right, anytime I went out like, what was his name?
Anytime I went out like, oh, let me really, you know, uh, use the clone and shave
and get myself all ready and make my bed and vacuum.
Never, never even close.
Right.
But I always stumbled into it.
And one particular time, a friend of mine from back home, lovely girl,
why it had a decade -long flirtation with.
So I'm thinking about coming out to Los Angeles.
Would you like to go see Ricky Jervais with me and I could stay at your place?
Said beautiful.
We saw him do stand -up.
It was hilarious.
Right.
We had some drinks.
Come back to my place.
I'm like, well, uh, I'm good out here on the couch.
You know, we hadn't discussed if it was romantic or not.
Right, right.
She goes, please, if it's okay with you, I'd like to sleep with you.
Right.
Of course.
Getting to bed, lying there, talking, laughing under the cubs.
And then finally, I'm like, so, uh, I guess, uh, she was, I should tell you, come on,
dude, I have a boyfriend.
Come on, dude, come on, man, she was like, you're going to hate me.
I have a boyfriend.
Why'd she want to sleep in the goddamn bed?
Now, Joe, you can't say any of this stuff.
And I didn't.
I sat and stared at the ceiling until daybreak, stewing.
But I was like, oh, no, it's totally okay.
Like my voice cracking.
I was like, yeah, totally okay.
Of course, of course.
Trying to be a gentleman and, uh, she was like, are you sure?
Are you sure?
As if I was saying, like, no, it's not okay.
It was like slowly turning into ice balls.
Yeah, Jesus Christ.
But I was like, okay, I was so baffled by the, by the whole exchange.
So she literally just wanted to sleep in a bed.
No, but you offered to sleep on the couch.
I, I, I was like, you know, by the way, when I offered the couch,
I, I did kind of expect her to say, come on.
We know what's going on.
My point is it's not like you said you sleep in the couch and then she goes,
why'd rather sleep in the bed and you go, you said, I will sleep on the couch.
And she didn't say, let me take the couch or any of that.
It was just like, come on, we know we're sleeping in the same.
It seemed like it was just on, very on, but it was off.
I was all, I always miss, I miss red, everything, always when I was single,
I was just bad at it.
Just that's not your fault.
That's, that sounds like that one was probably her hustle.
That was probably her.
That's, that's conveniently leaving out the, the, the one detail until the very last minute.
Yeah, because she knew she had told you initially that maybe you would have said,
no, you can't sleep over.
Maybe you would have said you had the couch.
Maybe you would have said, no, I don't want to go on a weird date with you to see Ricky
Drew base.
Well, the truth is I would have been thrilled if she had said, hey,
I'm going to come out.
I haven't seen you in a while.
You want to see Ricky Drew base and, you know, go get dinner or whatever.
By the way, I have a boyfriend.
So it just be his friends.
But I'm just, and I'd be like, yeah, great.
Exactly.
That's all you got to do, exactly.
You just, you know, wait till like our lips are touching.
Well, we're sharing a really gross way to save money on a hotel room.
I'd like to think that wasn't the reason, but I don't know.
I don't know.
It sounds like that was exactly the reason she didn't want to get a hotel room.
Should this guy, can I say, can I stay at your place?
But I have a boyfriend's probably going to say no, you may be right.
You may be right.
You may be crazy.
You made.
Now, Joe, did you see the news about our boy, Josh Homme today?
Yes, I did.
It was upsetting.
It was very upsetting because it's going on with him, man.
As far as modern bands go, I have a real deep love for Queens of the Stone Age.
And I had heard through a friend that Homme, Homme, Josh Homme, Homme, I've heard it pronounced
every different way gets into like real hard drugs.
I mean, listen to their albums, that's no surprise, but apparently had like a real dark period
where he was like bedridden and people thought he was going to die and et cetera.
Watching that video, it seemed like he's back on something pretty serious, but he walks over
and just kicks a woman's camera into her face.
Right.
Because when I saw the head, the article heading, Josh Homme kicks photographer in the face.
I was like, awesome.
Can't wait to see this.
Thinking it was a male paparazzi that he kicked in the face.
And I was like, you know what?
People are going to love him.
People are going to love him for this.
And it's a woman and he clearly looks right at her and kicks the camera into her face.
Then his apology was, sorry, I was caught up in the power of the performance or whatever.
Oh, Jesus.
And he's like, I was walking around kicking amps and kicking lights, carried away by the music
and just assumed that she was another light.
Then you watch the video and he doesn't kick any amps or any lights.
He walks directly up to a woman and kicks her in the face.
Now this is the first one to really affect me because I really love that band.
This before he cuts his far head open, he starts bleeding down his face.
Now I also love that he was saying, fuck, muse, because I hate the band muse.
Muse sucks.
And I did like they were saying, fuck, muse.
I honestly didn't mind that he was trying to get the crowd to boom.
No, I'm not sure I'm cutting his head open.
I'm not sure why he called them retards.
I said that, but you know, he was fucked up, but he was fucked up.
I think, I think, look, I think any one of those other acts you could, you could let it slide in some way or whatever.
Yes, the kicking the woman in a face, though, is you're, you know, it's suck.
And his apology, when I saw it, I was just kind of like, dude, at least say, let me buy you the nicest camera on the market.
Let me pay your medical bills, something like he had a real chance to get on people's good side again.
Just kind of fucked it off.
The, but what easily to one of the top five rock shows I've ever seen was Coachella desert, Queens of the Stone Age, where they're from, playing with like a sand storm blowing palm trees around, playing that like a Cochella about five years ago.
They were incredible.
And the second muse started on the, on the stage next door, 99 .9 % of the audience ran in moss over to see muse.
And I walked right into the front row, but looking at this bill, I'm like, I under I don't, I still don't understand why he kicks somebody in the face, but I was like, why are Queens of Stone Age opening for both muse and 30 seconds to Mars?
Lido's fucking band.
Yeah, I know that's.
I'll take muse over 30 seconds to Mars.
Of course.
I mean, come on.
But, you know, don't kick people in the fucking face.
Yeah, that sucks, man.
Even if it was a guy, it's, no, I guess it is better if it was a guy, not that it's ideal, but it's just kind of like.
When I, when I really saw it, I'm like, this is a rock photographer with credentials in the front row, taking badass rock star photos of you.
Yeah, that really sucks.
Is that really sick?
She was hospitalized.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's terrible.
It's a bummer, man.
I can't take this anymore.
How many more people that I think are like cool are going to do something where I'm like, God damn it, man.
I don't know.
I mean, Joe's favorite director is Brett Ratner.
So you can imagine how that's been.
You get it wrong.
Brett Ratner is Harvey Weinstein is my favorite producer.
Right.
Brett Ratner is my favorite character actor because he does act sometimes.
For years, though, you were in the rat pack where you, Brett Ratner and Jerry Ferrarra, a turtle from entourage, would go up to canners.
You'd eat a couple big pastrami sandwiches and try to fuck.
I would try to fuck the two of them and it never worked out.
They had the pussy posse and you were kind of the pastrami posse as you called yourself.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
I would try to fuck them and they were always not interested.
Sure.
But I did grab Ratner's dick and, you know, this clears ownership.
Oh, Spacey.
And thankfully he didn't, he didn't sue me.
Yeah.
Ken Hanley made a joke about the pilot.
He was like on Facebook.
He was like, Pat, is it true that you were digitally replacing all shots of Joe DeRose in the pilot with Christopher Plummer?
That was like, yes, that's 100%.
Very funny.
That's very funny.
I love that.
I'll see the movie now because of that, that they rushed in Plummer.
I was like, what a cool thing.
And then what seemed interesting was it seemed to me when I read an interview about it, Ridley Scott was kind of like.
It seemed like he was bothered by the spacey thing, but he really did it because he's 80 and he likes a challenge.
Yeah.
Well, I'd also, too.
Now we get an actual older man and not Spacey and old man makeup, also.
That's an added bonus.
It's going to tell you something.
Oh, I got, and then we should do our, what we're here to do.
Yeah.
But I've got Fumans chew news.
Fumans news.
Oh.
Does he ever turn it on?
He did that last week.
Oh, I did.
Yeah.
Sorry.
I don't remember.
I'm half in the fucking bag.
We'll do these things.
The Fumans chew has announced the track listing for the new record.
Okay.
And the title of the album.
The title of the album.
It folks.
If you're a Fumans chew fan, you don't get more food than this.
The album is called Clone of the Universe with an awesome Fumans chew title.
The album is only nine songs, I believe, because the last song is a like 16 -minute art slash
stoner rock song with Alex Lifeson from Rush playing guest guitar.
That sounds fantastic.
Yes.
So I love Rush.
I love Fumans chew.
I'm so excited.
These two, this album is super heavy, and it's, and it's got a bit of an art rock twist to it.
Or something drop.
I believe February.
Actually the day they play L .A. is the day the album comes out, I think.
So I believe our dear friend Vince copped some tickets for us.
And we're going to be at that Fumans chew show at the troubadour in L .A.
So if you live in L .A., come out and say hi.
You know, we're going to go to see Fumans chew it or come just to say hi to us.
But say hi.
But if you see us, you say hi.
If you see us, say hello.
Folks, we're here to do one thing today.
One thing only.
That's deliver you a god damn mother fucking bonus episode.
It's Jonas.
And boy, do we got, do we got a treat for you today?
Well, Joe hit me with this.
I'll admit I got hard.
You know how much we love our new segment.
PSI love you.
Perfect strangers.
I love you.
I've been going through my daily routine of watching two to six perfect strangers a day.
Six.
No, I'm, I'm exaggerating.
What is the max that you've watched?
Oh, I've easily done six in a day, but I mean not,
I love how you, you scoff at it that immediately admit that you have it back.
Not, not regularly.
Like on a Sunday when I had like three hours to do nothing.
I just sat there kept watching.
But I was, I'm, I'm, I'm need even season seven at this point.
They have moved into the house.
All right.
Finally, I get my answer.
Yeah.
And as the quality dropped off substantially.
Pat, in ways you can't even imagine or, or re -imagined because I know you've seen all these.
I've already watched this episode in preparation for this.
This thing is a fucking shit show.
I'm scrolling through this season seven episodes.
Yeah.
And I text pat immediately.
I say, because pat of the idea off, I think it was off air.
I don't think he said it on air.
He was like, we should do the perfect strangers finale on, on the show.
We've talked about it so much.
We should do a commentary on it.
Where in a Mexican standoff style situation, Larry,
Balkey and the girls point guns at each other and squeeze the trigger all at the same time.
All four of them go down at the same time.
That's how perfect strangers ends.
Stop it.
I'm not kidding.
You're kidding, right?
Yes, I'm kidding.
Okay.
But it should be the ending.
Listen, after this episode, I think anything's possible.
Well, I equipped before Joe gives you the backstory.
So you can bring it up on Hulu.
We're going to do a commentary on the perfect strangers episode entitled,
Fright Night and it's season seven, seven episode.
It's just called Fright Night.
They're titled on Hulu.
Perfect strangers, Fright Night, season seven.
Go do that now and pause it.
Bring it up.
Go on, Joe.
Anyway, so Pat said, let's do the finale.
And I said, yeah, that's a great idea.
And then a day later, I texted him.
I said, dude, I'm scrolling through season seven here.
There's an episode called Fright Night.
Good sign already.
Yeah.
We got perfect strangers.
And now the episode is named after one of the best horror movies of all time.
And I say, here's the plot.
Larry and Balkey have to battle a ghost.
Right.
And they're new haunted in their new house, which happens to be haunted.
I said, that's the one we should do on the show.
Pat agreed.
Quickly agreed.
Here we are.
So here's what you got to do.
If you're watching on Hulu, there's a little man, like when you hit play,
it's going to do this ABC logo thing that you can't pause or skip or anything.
Get past that then hit pause.
And that's where we're going to start from.
Now, can you and I pause so I can get myself a cocktail for this?
Yeah.
All right, let's do it.
Guys, we'll come back and we're going to watch Perfect Strangers Fright Night.
Great time to do an ad.
Back into your listening.
Well, this is the bonus one that Hulu doesn't do.
God damn it.
Oh, boy.
Then I better do a quick ad to cover it up.
Fruit of the loom.
If you like your dad's underpants, it's Fruit of the loom.
Back into it too.
And we're back.
Hello, everybody.
Okay, folks, we're getting ready here.
We got our drinks.
Perfect Strangers Fright Night.
I hope you have your drinks.
If you're going to be watching season seven, Perfect Strangers.
On the count of three, then play.
One, two, three, play.
And remember it.
Now, here's the credits.
Pat, you haven't seen the show in a long time.
Oh, they don't have the lyrics?
Oh no.
What's coming?
Sometimes the world looks perfect.
Nothing can be arranged.
This credit sequence runs a cool minute 10, a minute 10 in the seventh season.
They still haven't shortened this thing.
No matter what the odds are this time, nothing's going to stand in my way.
Pincho.
Now, over Baker and the credits.
Coming up is my favorite part of the opening credits.
They show a bunch of clips that are not in the show.
But look funny.
Here's Larry about you.
No, they're battling the wind.
Here's them running into a baseball game.
I can almost guarantee that battling the wind clip was at some point in the show.
No, they did an odd couple style opening where they just made up little scenarios.
This isn't in the revolving door gag.
Well, no.
That battling the wind thing looks really funny though.
It did look funny.
Yeah.
And then here they come up in the tuxedos from the subway going to see the odds.
Oh, see.
All right.
We're in, folks.
ABC.
Perfect strangers.
There's the exterior of the house.
Which looks like a haunted house, quite frankly.
Larry and Jennifer.
Jennifer on the couch.
By the way, Jennifer is roughly a thousand times more attractive than the other one.
I know you went with Mary Ann.
Well, as I said, I find Jennifer to be a more interesting person.
But Mary Ann's body just don't quit.
I feel Jennifer's body is not quite quitting on.
I like Jennifer.
She's prudish though.
You like the film Jennifer's body?
No.
I never saw it.
I mean, I don't know.
Maybe I would.
I mean, it's, you know, you got, you're not off in a good direction with what was it?
Isn't what's her face in it?
Megan Fox.
Yeah.
You think Pinchot got laid a lot?
I bet you Pinchot was killing it.
I think so too.
I think people loved Pinchot.
And I think they loved, I imagine that when fans met Pinchot.
Yeah.
A lot of pictures.
And we're expecting him to be like, they're like, I love you because you're cute Balky.
And then he's like this deep voiced sort of swive guy.
Yeah.
Hey, well, thank you very much.
Like that probably, I think he probably did very well.
So Balky just came in and told you guys can't hear the audio as usual.
But Balky just came in and he told Larry and the whole gang, they all live together.
Larry and his wife, Jennifer and Mary Ann, Balky's girlfriend and Balky all live in the house.
Balky and Mary Ann do have separate rooms because it is a decent show.
They don't have sex.
They have separate rooms.
They make jokes about them having sex?
No, they've never made a sex joke about Larry and Jennifer until they were married.
Okay.
Ever.
Wow.
Oh, well, I guess it wasn't always TGIF though.
It was on Tuesday and Wednesday.
Well, it was just a different time.
You know, they were like, we got to sell this.
When you, like, they were like, they were like three years into their relationship.
And like, Jennifer would say things like, oh, in fact, in the engagement ring one that I told you about.
Yeah.
Where he gets the cheap ring and has to swap it out.
Right.
He has to break into Jennifer's room while she's asleep to try to take the fake ring off her finger.
And his line is, I've always dreamed of being in Jennifer's bedroom.
I didn't think it would be like this.
This is on the eve of their marriage.
And they've been together six years.
Yeah.
And he's a 42 year old man.
Yes.
Now, you think Lynn Baker got the ladies or was he a married man back in the day?
I mean, my guess is that if you're on a show like this and you have any sort of game whatsoever.
I guess.
Yes.
You're probably doing okay for yourself.
But he seems like he was probably already married and stuff.
I think, yeah, he seems like I think he's been married.
You go out tonight, Bronson.
I need to go check in on the kids and Jean.
Yeah.
And then Bronson would leave.
And as Bronson was exiting Mark, which shake his head and go, that Bronson.
Yeah.
Norm MacDonald told a really funny story on his podcast recently about three weeks.
Are we this deep in the show without introducing the story?
Because that's a big sitcom mistake.
No, they introduced it.
We talked straight through it.
All right.
Good.
The balcony came into the neighbor said we have a ghost here.
Oh, okay.
And the ghost shows himself once a year.
All right.
Go ahead.
Sorry.
And what do you think Larry's reaction to that was?
Oh, poppycock.
Exactly.
Yeah.
So now, Balkey has a book about ghosts.
And he's trying to convince Larry that ghosts are real.
And there's a ghost in the house.
Yeah.
But Norm MacDonald is on a funny story on his podcast about Warner Bros. Studios.
They shot three companies there.
Yeah.
And they would go to the smokehouse after.
That's where I go every week.
Yeah.
As many shows do.
And Don Nuts, when he was on the show.
Yes.
But he said he would.
I heard the story from another person.
Yeah.
He said he would like hit on women because he didn't.
And he said no game whatsoever.
Yeah.
But his line was.
I am married.
But it's not going well.
Honestly, I can't imagine a better line.
It's not going too good.
Now, would you say this vest shirt combo is.
Normal for Balkey.
Oh, yeah.
Crazier than normal or less crazy than normal.
This is, this is par for the course.
Okay.
But he has gone crazier, you're saying.
No.
I mean, I'm sure this looks insane.
I'm sure it's desperate to me.
I'm sure he's been a little wilder.
But this is pretty much the way it's been from the beginning.
Yeah.
He is not assimilated to American life in any way.
Right.
Aside from seven years in.
Aside from the fact that he gets like.
He got like valedictorian at his graduation.
Yes.
And he somehow is.
Uh, he becomes like the student body president is college
and night school.
But aside from those things like he doesn't seem to understand
anything else.
Like he doesn't, you know, he doesn't dress differently.
He doesn't.
He still uses every word incorrectly.
Sure.
Yes.
You said, you said wilder.
And it made me realize that Lin Baker is.
The poor man's gene wilder.
That's a good way.
He's doing something very similar.
He's got the curly hair.
He gets loud and crazy.
And I think that's what I liked when I was a kid.
He's like gene wilder for kids.
Yeah.
I agree.
I have to say I respect everybody on this show quite a bit.
Sure.
I know we make fun.
But it's, you know, it doesn't mean I don't respect the performers.
But I do think that Lin Baker is.
The, the guy I'd most want to.
You know, if I was, I don't know, directing something cast him in it.
Right.
Now, did you know that perfect.
I watched the first season of the leftovers on HBO and found it so relentlessly miserable
that I was like, I don't need this in my life.
Right.
I'm miserable enough.
I've heard that two is better than one and that three is a masterpiece.
And I've heard that three in this somber show about the apocalypse basically,
a large part of season three is about perfect strangers.
And Marklin Baker plays himself.
I do know this.
And I can't wait to see it for that reason.
I've never been so intrigued by anything in my life.
I do know this.
I don't know if it's a large part, but there is a storyline with Marklin Baker,
where he's the only member of the cast that's still there.
Okay.
And he has, he has a theory.
There's something, he has a theory as to why that has happened.
Okay.
So it is sort of serious, but it's a ridiculous thing.
But I've heard it's awesome.
I've heard the storyline is really fun.
Is the boss still in the mix?
Arnie Sabella?
Now in season seven, the voice of Pumba.
In season seven, they're not going into the office much.
They're just always home.
They're doing a lot of time in this house.
In fact, they started picking up second jobs in the house.
I just watched an episode called Door to Door,
where they become salesman of soap, rug soap.
And the only reason they do it is because they live next to a,
they live in like the same neighborhood as like a barrenness or something like that.
Okay.
And Larry buys all this soap.
And he's like, we're going to sell it to that barrenness because she runs a hotel chain.
That's his whole scheme.
I mean, it's getting real sad.
Okay.
So here, let me bring you up to speed where we are because we're re -appin' away.
Balkey loves Wayne Newton.
I remember that.
Yes.
They're going into Balkey's room.
There's a giant poster of Wayne Newton on the wall.
Here's why they're going into his room.
Balkey said, the ghost appears once a year at sundown in my bedroom.
That's the story of this haunted house.
All right.
So now they're in Balkey's bedroom.
I also add out that window there was very visible light.
No, they said though.
They go, the sun's about to go down.
Oh, okay.
They're going down.
So they're in the room.
They're waiting for the sun to go down.
And...
The man's body isn't quitting.
And Barianza, he is not quitting.
Jennifer, coming through.
Yeah.
Larry, wild and out.
Wild and out?
Yeah.
Wilder and out.
Oh, wilder and out.
You get what I'm trying to do here.
The poster of Wayne Newton, by the way, Wayne Newton is wearing a fingerless leather glove.
Yeah.
Isn't that odd?
I rolled with it.
Did he do that?
I don't know.
Lifting weights.
Look at this.
He's got a...
He's got like a two finger ring on.
And a leather fingerless glove.
Well, if you look closely at the hands underneath that finger, they appear fake.
Unless he's just self -tanned.
Underneath what finger?
Underneath that ring.
The doorbell ring that he's wearing.
I don't think they look...
What do you mean they look fake?
They look like fake fingers to me.
In what sense?
All right.
I'm willing to get off.
No, no, I'm not challenging.
I'm just curious.
They look like fake fingers, like a fake hand to me.
They're big, they're big brown sausagey fingers.
Like a, like a, like a kingpin kind of thing.
Yeah, exactly.
Like a rubber hand.
What I mean, yeah.
All right, all right.
What am I going to do with the rubber hand?
So...
Larry.
Larry goes...
Oh, no.
Your do's are in a wrist.
Yeah.
25 years times.
Oh.
You owe 17 fingers.
You're like, well, that's it.
We got to go home.
That's the beauty of kingpin.
Okay.
That jokes like...
You can see that joke on Golden Girls.
The bowling...
Yeah.
All you can see that joke.
But then they go one further every time.
Yeah.
Well, 17 -50.
We can't pay that.
We got to go home.
And they can't pay it.
They have no money.
Yeah.
What's it called?
Larry just said...
What I was laughing at was...
So the story of the ghost is this guy was killed by the mob
because he bet on a world series game where the cubs lost
or something like that.
And the mob killed him in this room.
Wait, how do they know the ghosts back?
Because they found a book that had the story in it.
Again, we talked through a lot of this exposition.
So Larry goes...
Larry goes...
There's no ghost.
This guy is just somebody who was dumb enough to hide in his own bedroom
when he owed the ball of money.
And then the ghost threw him into the wall.
And now they're floating.
I will say it's...
Oh, my lord.
There's the thing.
I will say it's very visible that they're being held up by harnesses.
His shirt is actually...
Yeah.
Put lifted up by the harness.
Visible.
It's just floated off the ground.
Because Larry keeps doubting the ghost and bulky keeps trying to tell him like...
You can't doubt the ghost.
You're going to make it angry.
That was a cool effect.
I'll give you that.
It was not a cool effect.
Look, absurd.
You expect a goddamn sitcom based in reality?
You don't expect a multi -cam sitcom.
You're four leads to float.
That's all.
It was unexpected.
All right.
But yeah, I mean...
This is like...
By the way, this is out...
This is out desperate.
They've gotten these characters at this point.
They're floating in the air.
And Larry's still going...
There's a logical explanation for this.
There is no ghost.
This is what they're still...
Yeah.
They refuse to let this man evolve.
Now, they all floated into the air.
Three of them said nothing.
And Larry went...
Oh, my lord.
Yeah.
But now the ghost is mad at Larry,
because he keeps doubting him.
Oh.
So, the ghost is now thrown Larry into the wall.
Now, what do you think happens?
Lin Baker gets this script.
Sunday morning at the house.
He's got coffee.
He's like, let me see what I'm up to this week on the set of PS.
Does he talk to the writers about this?
Or is he like, love the script, guys?
I think he closes.
He reads the last page, closes it, puts it down.
Looks up in the air, says PS.
I love you.
I think he's pleased.
I think...
I think they were having fun.
And I think...
You know, they do an episode where they do the...
They do like a Honeymooners episode.
Yeah, I remember that.
Like, I think they were just trying...
And then they...
Like, the one after this is an habit and...
Or not a large, hardy episode.
I remember that.
Like, I think they just were like...
Let's just do like, crazy, goofy shit.
Yeah.
It's not good, though, at the time.
No.
Yeah.
But I think...
Now, has anything in this six, seven season been like...
Oh, that's a really great episode.
Or is it all pretty much shit?
I've...
I've yet to see...
It's been a dark ride through this seven season.
Is this the final season?
No, there's one more.
Oh.
There's an eighth.
And I assume you're going till the better end.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm gonna see it through.
But they're getting tough to watch.
Yeah.
They're getting tough to watch.
If I didn't have to finish this one for the show,
I probably would have shut it off.
They have not left this room in ten minutes.
No.
And now they're trapped.
The ghost just shut the door.
And it's a hideous set, by the way.
Hideous.
Well, it's Balky's...
It looks like Peewee's playhouse.
Yeah.
It's on steroids.
By the way, I think two episodes after this
is the one where Balky's mom comes to visit.
Who portrays her?
Balky.
Bronson Pinchot dresses up as an old woman.
And the language she speaks is this.
This is Mopozion.
She just goes,
And Larry is translating it the whole time.
Now let me ask you this.
It is terrible.
Lynn Baker said,
Now the script's on that morning.
Is he jealous?
That Pinchot gets to play both roles?
I think so.
They gave Pinchot all the juicy stuff.
They gave Pinchot to the Robin Lee's impression.
Yeah.
They let Pinchot do the voices.
The ghost just appeared, folks.
And he is being played...
It's Meatloaf.
By Meatloaf.
What the fuck?
I definitely didn't see that coming.
To take this to a...
What the hell?
To take this to another relevant level of this podcast.
The ghost is being played by Sudohar musician Meatloaf.
By the way, the audience didn't even applaud Meatloaf's arrival.
I don't think the audience is there, Pat.
I think this is a canned thing happening.
There's a lot of special effects going on.
Meatloaf is wearing a plaid suit.
But you'd imagine they'd be watching it on a monitor.
Maybe they didn't.
Sometimes they don't do these in front of an audience.
I don't know.
Now here's the thing.
Here's the thing.
Any writer worth his salt would have put the joke in.
Ghost appears being played by Meatloaf.
Larry still skeptical, pulls Belki aside and says,
That's not a ghost.
That's Meatloaf.
Right.
Why not put that joke in?
Well, maybe they weren't ready to break the fourth wall joke.
What?
Because they've got these people to grittily realistic.
Loading up into the sky.
Yeah.
You don't put in the joke?
That's not a ghost.
That's Meatloaf.
All right, fair enough.
You don't like that joke?
You didn't laugh at all.
I like it.
I mean, for this kind of thing, I mean, I know it's a good joke.
I...
Well, I was about to say I'd have a blast writing
for like one of these late seasons of a dog shit show.
I did it on two broke girls.
I mean, you do still care sort of.
I mean, but I can't imagine the people creating
perfect stranger season seven were really...
There had to be a sense of humor about what was happening.
They didn't all think they were making art.
Well, I mean, I don't know.
I would rip in my goddamn hair out in this writer's room.
Yeah.
They said they want a ghost episode.
What?
The fuck are you talking about?
Yeah.
This gag is coming up soon where the ghost starts
taking control of their bodies.
And they can't...
Again, this is a blown bit here.
The ghost takes control of Balky's arm.
It's not happening just yet.
It's coming up soon.
And then...
Oh, I'm sorry.
This is first.
This is Balky explaining how to get rid of the ghost.
Balky's now saying...
The whole episode has been him saying,
Larry, stop making the ghost angry.
That's not good.
Now Larry's saying,
what do we do to get rid of the angry ghost?
Balky goes,
if you make him angry enough, he'll disappear.
I mean, this is no goddamn logic to any of this shit.
Where are the girls, by the way?
They went to a hotel.
And Larry goes,
even after they floated,
I'm not being scared of my own house
by something that doesn't exist.
Why wouldn't these two go to a hotel and fuck those beautiful women?
Uh, and then come back the night the ghost isn't there.
I told you this before.
I think something goes on off camera
that we don't see between these two.
Some sort of an abusive lust arc.
It gets dark, yeah.
You know?
So this is the gap.
You know what would be a funny sketch
would be like a date line
behind the perfect strand.
And you know what?
If you and I wrote this tonight,
we could get these two to be in it.
They'd come by.
If we promise them a hot meal.
Like a behind the music kind of thing?
Why?
Now do you think they realized how much this looks like Bronson
is trying to force Lynn Baker to filate him?
He was just forcing his head toward his dick again and again.
He's got no control of his arms.
The ghost is controlling his arm.
But again, here's the gag.
Balky's like, I can't control my arm.
The ghost is controlling it.
And then just keeps whacking Larry in the chest.
Yeah.
Do the slap in the face thing.
Like Larry's talking to him.
And then he slaps him in the face.
Stop that.
You're like, what?
That's the funniest way to do that.
Why not do it that way?
Uh,
so they're trying to make the ghost angry and they can't do it.
but of course they think they've done it.
They think they've,
what do you think they're pulling at this point?
75KH,
1015 grand an episode tops.
Yeah, I mean,
we were talking about what, 1993 dollars?
This was, this was sitcom money was better than, though.
I mean, who know?
Yeah, I mean,
it was crazy.
They could have been making three million in episode.
They could have.
Yeah.
I think Seinfeld was the first one to go to a million episode.
That's correct.
And the friends eventually followed suit.
So,
and then, and then,
and then Raymond.
So I think they're probably,
I don't know,
they're probably making a few hundred grand in episode.
All right.
What did you think?
My thinking is these,
these two
capped out around 100K on that.
But I don't know.
I don't know.
I mean,
this was TGIF, right?
Yeah.
I guess TGF was big business.
It was huge.
I mean,
Erkel,
he's still living.
That's true.
You know, he's not exactly
popping up everywhere.
I don't think he's got an office job.
He's doing all right.
I'm sure he played beer pong with a man once.
He was a complete asshole.
Erkel,
Joliel White,
complete asshole.
More Stefan or Kelle than Erkel.
I'll tell you that much.
In what way was he an asshole?
He was cocky.
He was,
just kind of like,
there was,
it was a Halloween party,
and he grabbed a girl,
a girl at a squirrel tail,
and I grabbed the squirrel tail
in a very unsettling way,
and she like yelled at him.
You know, he,
he's just...
That's me coughing,
not laughing.
He was,
he was gross,
and he was just an asshole.
He was too competitive
for like a Halloween party game
of beer pong.
I can't believe somebody that
talented.
I know.
It could be that,
that shit.
Hey, I idolized him,
growing up,
I loved Erkel.
The ghost now made Larry
and Becky run themselves
into the wall face first.
And they got knocked out,
but you can still see
they're breathing on the ground.
These TG,
I'd love to see,
I would watch like a four -hour
documentary about
behind the scenes on TGIF,
because it seems like the kind of,
like,
studio system type deal,
where they would,
they would have no qualms
telling an actor,
you need to lose 15 pounds
by two weeks
from now you're off the shut.
They're doing it now.
Yeah, talking about me, Zach Taylor, Annie Pots, Jean Smart, Dixie Carter.
Yes.
No Delta.
No, she...
That was a huge...
I can't believe you don't remember that.
That was like a huge thing in the news, like...
Remember she was married to major dad?
Sure, I remember seeing interviews with him where he was like,
I just...
We find it disgraceful and...
It is disgraceful.
Yeah, she got fired for being too heavy.
Holy shit.
And she wasn't even...
It wasn't even like...
I'm not saying this would have made it okay.
But it wasn't like she was playing like a goddamn like sex symbol on the thing.
She's playing a lady that designed clothing.
Like who cares?
You know what I mean?
I'm not even saying like if she was playing a sex symbol,
she has to be thin.
I'm just saying like...
It like doubled in make any sense to me.
No.
By the way, the episode just ended as we have through.
There is no explanation.
The house was haunted.
There was...
It wasn't a dream.
It wasn't somebody spiked their punch.
There was no twist to it at all.
No, the house is just haunted.
That's it.
The house is haunted.
Perfect strangers has crossed over into...
The haunted house...
Yes.
I don't know if I love you, to be honest.
It's a rough episode, man.
Gang...
We appreciate you.
We appreciate having you as fans.
We wish you a happy, healthy, and a safe holiday season.
I'm on Twitter, Instagram, at the Patrick Walsh.
Pat no plugs on this special episode.
That's all I know.
All right.
We've...
We've established this.
I didn't know.
But like every other aspect of the show,
you seem to just kind of not remember it for a week to week.
But it's all right.
Fox, we love you.
We hope you enjoyed the bonus app.
Merry Christmas.
Happy Hanukkah.
Happy Kwanza.
Happy New Year.
Happy...
What else?