Sometimes you might get drunk, but you normally get drunk.
That hot talk about the hot movies coming out these days.
I'm Joe DeRosa.
And I'm Patrick Walsh,
and we're talking about the hottest new release of 2022,
Night of the Living Dead,
directed by George A. Romero.
If this film were reviewed this year,
the review would say the most lifeline film of the year,
you know, they would have some terrible
like that automotomy, a puppet movie, whatever the fuck it was called,
that we talked about last time,
the most human film of the year.
It's achingly human, they like to say.
Achingly human, you know, the zombies are the ones teaching us
that we're the dead, some stupid bullshit like that.
You know, I was watching a bold allegory
for our Fox News saturated times, something like that.
I was watching Stephen King's graveyard shift today,
just before we started recording.
I put it on while I ate a late lunch of plain tuna and an apple.
Yeah, because I refused to exercise.
Anyway, it's, it's, you know,
it's a passable shitty horror film from the 90s.
It's not very good.
But you know, one thing I'll say, you know,
the credits roll, the sinister synth music plays,
there's ominous sweeping shots of a graveyard with mist.
And I'm watching it and I'm going, you know, it might not be good.
But it feels like a horror movie.
Yeah.
And so many horror movies now, you can't even say that much.
You're just like, it doesn't even feel like a horror movie.
At least this feels like a horror movie, you know,
like it's, it's got a fun, you're intrigued by the credits
when it does have to that it's his own business.
I watched that one not too long ago.
No, I watched Monkey Shines.
I've never even seen graveyard shift.
Monkey Shines.
I remember that.
I even remember as a kid thinking it was stupid.
But yeah, it had the monkey with the symbols on the cover.
I remember, which is so much scarier.
Then an actual monkey that that hurts people.
Yeah, it's like nobody is scared of monkeys.
So it's a very strange thing to write a horror movie around.
And it's the least scary monkey.
It's the like, it's the tiny monkey, you know what I mean?
At least it was a orangutan, like in any which way, but lose monkey,
but with a machine gun or so that you'd have reason for pause.
Should the planet of the apes?
Yeah, you know, or Congo even.
Yeah, because a grown guerrilla or monkey could kill you.
A small monkey cannot unless they're rabbit or something.
Who's in that one?
Dorif?
Steven Dorif?
No, no, Brad Dorif.
Brad Dorif's in graveyard shift.
Is he also in monkey shines?
I'm getting a mixed up.
No, nobody is in monkey shines.
The star is Jason Beggie.
B -E -G -H -E.
Yikes.
I will say this, Dorif, grand slam performance in graveyard shift.
He plays it anyways.
Derminator that it hates rats because of an experience he had in Vietnam.
And he chews tobacco the whole time and he's dredged and sweat.
He's awesome in it.
Yeah, he's awesome in it.
Yeah.
I always love Dorif.
He never phones it in.
No.
I mean, you know, we're going to be talking about cursed films on the next show.
And I was actually watching some of a similar sort of doc you show,
which is Eli Roth's history of horror.
You ever watched that?
Yeah, I like that show.
I like it, but there something has gone wrong over there.
They're talking about bad movies.
They're citing movies that no one cares about as like great.
They did one about like great sequels and they're talking about the purge
anarchy and stuff, you know, like a 10 minute segment on the fourth purge.
And you're like, guys, come on.
Well, yeah, that's the problem with those kinds of see.
You know, we'll get into it in the next episode.
But that curse film season two had a bit of that.
We were like, yeah, where it's like they said the munchkins were alcoholics
in the Wizard of Oz.
Like that's not a curse, guys.
The rumor.
Yeah, yeah.
And then they talk about stalker, which is not a horror movie on cursed film.
There's a lot of weirdness.
I couldn't get through the stalker episode.
I watched the other ones.
The stalker, I was bored to piss.
And the whole thing was subtitled.
I was like, Jesus Christ, I tried to get through the movie stalker
and couldn't do it when I was a kid.
I don't know if it'd be any better now.
But that one too, they were like, there was a lot of like
and the curse was that his film was not his vision.
He wanted you like, guys, this isn't like they lost two reels of film
at the Luxembourg airport.
I'm like, yeah, that isn't a curse.
That is a human error.
Anyway, curse films coming up next.
Today's Latin night of the living dead.
I'm also going to, if I can find it,
well, you know what, actually, I have a scary stuff.
Okay.
I bought the, and I urge all of you to go get this,
if you don't already have it.
I was shocked that I did not have these in my position.
I did at one point.
I had the Superman films on DVD at one point.
Yeah.
And recently I thought I should, I should get them on blue, where I should upgrade.
And I went to look for my DVDs to very excitedly get to pull them off the shelf
because it's always fun when you start to consult, you know, when you can consolidate down,
when you're like, sure, I've got these things on like seven discs.
And now I'm going to get a compact little box and I get to make space.
And the DVDs were gone.
Apparently I got rid of them a long time ago.
I guess with the idea that I eventually would upgrade.
So I went on Amazon and I bought the Superman motion picture anthology.
1978 to 2006.
There's a lot of blu -ray collections of the Superman films on Amazon.
But this one is very, very fairly priced.
I think it was $30.
Maybe $30.
Maybe $35.
And it's Superman 1.
Then the extended cut of Superman 1.
Then Superman 2.
Then the Donner cut of Superman 2.
Superman 3.
Superman 4.
And Superman returns.
And Superman returns as a bonus feature.
Contains a sequence where he goes back to find Krypton that was cut out of the movie that
apparently was a crucial cut from the movie.
It was a mistake that they cut it.
Because that was one of the big complaints about Superman returns.
The whole premise was that he went to look for remnants of Krypton.
And that's why he was gone.
And then they don't show any of that in the movie.
He just comes back at the beginning.
Cool deleted scene there.
And it's great, man.
It's loaded with special features and
interviews and it's just awesome.
And the films look beautiful.
They're in high -death.
That I recommended greatly as a strong addition to the collection.
I think Superman 1 and 2 are masterpieces.
I think Superman 3 is not great.
But it's worth the ride just for the junkyard scene where he fights them.
Superman 4 is terrible, but it's canon and it's very fun camp.
And Superman Returns is a passable return to form.
I think they're very much a set worth only.
I don't know, I might not.
Actually, I really like one.
I really like two.
I've never seen three or four.
And I thought Superman Returns was horrible.
You never saw three or four?
Really?
No, I've never seen them.
It would make you appreciate Returns a little bit more
because that was one of the first times I ever saw a director go.
We're just going to make a sequel that comes right after
we're going to ignore these other two they made.
But three, three's pretty wild.
Three's the one richer prior.
And three's the one where he turns evil for half the movie.
And I saw that in the theater as a kid.
And it was so upsetting.
But when he turns good again, it will make you cry.
Like it's awesome.
Okay.
Sort of like the Indian temple of doom.
When he goes.
Very, very similar.
Except the movie surrounding it is terrible.
Whereas in Temple Doom, it's a fun movie.
Favorite Indian?
I love Temple Doom.
Mads Michelson said that who's directing this new one?
James, what's his name?
Mangold.
He said that he very much took inspiration from Raiders and Temple of Doom.
For this new one.
He said it feels like an old Spielberg movie.
That's those words, so I don't know.
We'll see.
Love it.
What is it coming out?
I feel like they've been shooting it for a decade.
Dude, it's done shooting.
2023.
It's like maybe there's problems.
I remember they just don't want to release it in the theater.
This top gun, I have not read
a single review that wasn't over the top glowing.
They're all like, this is, this is an amazing movie.
Really?
Yeah.
Any speak of the Kilmer sequence and how they do it?
No.
I didn't know he was in it, but people.
Including people I really trust.
I mean, I follow a bunch of critics and I've worked with some of these critics
in the past and stuff and they really, everyone was just like,
this movie is fucking awesome.
So I'm excited to see it.
The trailer looked great.
I mean, I'm pumped.
Wow.
I'm out here in Atlanta.
I never saw the original.
I believe it or not.
Really?
It's pretty good.
I never saw it as a kid and then, you know,
once I passed 12, I didn't give a shit anymore.
And I wasn't going to go back.
You know, I know I'm no interest in seeing it now.
But, yeah, I might watch it just in the sequel.
It's very 80s and it's, and the supporting cast is great.
You got all kinds of big actors in there.
Meg Ryan's like the 12th lead in the fun.
Tom Garrett.
Do anything for you?
I love Tom Garrett.
Mike Ironside.
Do anything for you?
Love Mike Ironside.
I, uh, I'll tell you who doesn't do anything for me.
And it makes me not want to see it.
Is this fucking Mr. Fantastic in this new one?
The key to one is the Oh, Teller.
Flash, I point to whiplash.
Whiplash is a wonderful movie.
Teller something about him bugs me.
I can't put my finger on it.
Seems like a guy I would hate to be around.
That's what I mean.
He's got it for sure.
I think why you might hate him as he's got the vibe of a guy
who would walk into a party and immediately leave
with the girl you're talking to.
I, after putting in about 10 seconds.
Yeah, something like that.
Oh, wow, I, I found it by the way, what I was looking for.
And it is, it is important to the point.
Boy, Rex reads review of the lost city.
Okay, now on Paramount Plus.
The lost city is witless, boring, and stupid.
That's, that's the, that's the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the movie.
Got pretty good reviews, too.
Yeah, I liked it.
Uh, it's two paragraphs, the review.
Now, they're longer paragraphs, but it's two paragraphs.
Here we go, ready?
Yeah.
Watching the lost city and the, is the cinematic equivalent
of slogging your way through monkey poop.
Come on, Rex.
Wait, didn't you read this on the show?
No, I sent you a blurb of it from, uh, from Rotten Tomatoes.
Okay.
Yeah.
I squirm and moaned my way through stinkers all the time.
But I can't actually remember the last time I saw a sub mental
farce, this witless, boring, and stupid.
Because the stars are Sandra Bullock, Channing Tatum, and Daniel Radcliffe,
with an inside joke cameo by Brad Pitt, and a long, blonde wig,
the appeal for audiences with low standards and no knowledge of or interest
in genuine comedy timing is guaranteed.
But nobody in this comic book twaddle displays any talent for farce,
and it is doubtful that either of the two directors, Adam and Aaron Nee,
could successfully stage the baking of a batch of cookies.
Jesus Christ, come on, Rex.
They also wrote the screenplay, which sounds like it was dictated by bad
blooms on tranquilizer.
See, at this point, you're not even reviewing the move.
You're just trying to entertain people with your quips.
Wild.
Who are there so -called writers?
Orrin, Yuzile, and Dana Fox are also credited.
I'm curious which one forced Sandra Bullock to deliver a two -page monologue
to Channing Tatum's penis?
Yes.
Holy shit.
You guys get a cameo.
Does he do cameos?
That's a great idea.
Matt McCartney, get on, probably, not try.
Like he would probably just be like, hey,
and I'll give you the bare minimum.
Matt would be worth it.
Matt is listening.
Matt, please, bring us direct.
Matt has sent me everything from Rex Reid.
Matt, find us this cameo if it exists.
All right, it goes on.
No point in dragging in the detail.
Sandra Bullock is also one of the producers.
So the film doesn't make one lick of sense as hardly worth analyzing.
She plays the author of Violent Trashy Adventure novels
that appeal to giggling girls with IQs of less than 50.
Mr. Tatum plays a bone -headed muscles McGurk named Alan.
The hunky model on all of her book jackets,
who actually thinks he's the heroic character she's created
in her schlocky novels called Dash.
Daniel Radcliffe, the fated glory of his Harry Potter
date's a distant memory.
He's called Daniel Radcliffe, a washer.
Whoa, he plays a billionaire nutcase
who kidnaps them on a book promotion to her
convinced that Loretta can lead his gang
of murderous criminals to the wellness
to the well of endless tears, blah, blah, blah.
All right, I'm going to skip to the end.
The, okay, okay, well, I love that he uses his sense.
Stripped naked, he bears his buttocks for her to ogle
while she rips the leeches off his most intimate hot spot saying
it's like pickling anchovies out.
It's like picking anchovies out of my favorite salad.
These are the jokes and you don't know whether to laugh
or continue the nap from which you've been rudely interrupted.
In quotes all that time and money spent on a cheat metaphor
groans Daniel Radcliffe at the end of the law city.
He must be describing the movie itself.
Oh my god, this guy is gold.
Well, now wait a minute.
It's like picking anchovies out of my favorite salad.
It doesn't make any sense.
What is his ass is her favorite salad?
Why do you need favorite in that joke?
I'm always all I guess because he's I guess because he's hot
and she's pulling gross leeches off of him and she's saying like
you're not sure at this point of the game.
They're not in love with each other.
They got to keep that bump until the end.
She wouldn't be calling it her favorite salad,
looking at his bare ass.
I mean, you got me.
It's the clip they show like
it's the clip I sent you when I got mad that you wouldn't
trash the movie with me and I sent you the clip
from YouTube of her point leeches off his dick.
I haven't seen it.
There is a leech scene in the African queen that's very famous
that I recall, but I haven't seen the movie.
I know a lot of people liked it,
but I think what has happened is that movies have gotten so so bad
that people are like,
if something passes the time,
it tends to get really good reviews.
The only leech scene I can remember
stand by me.
It's stand by me.
There's got to be other ones, right?
But yeah, but I'm sure.
Yeah, I'm sure like a western.
They did it like, you know,
I think admit evil times they use leeches to get like
disease out of people.
I can't wait for you to take us to the movie corner
because I want to keep talking bad comedy here
because we both got one.
Well, then I know what both of our number one will be.
Jesus Christ.
And I want to say to the man who put this podcast together
so many years ago,
can't handle it.
I saw you on Twitter talking about how much you love this.
And now your taste is in question
for eternity.
Talking about Mike Myers return to to form
the pentaforid.
I also saw Ken's tweet.
He said, I can't believe it.
It's actually very good.
And I wrote, Ken, are you insane?
He did right back.
Joe, I don't know anymore.
There was one joke in each episode that made me laugh.
Maybe that's all I'm looking for these days.
Look, I get that.
But I didn't have that one joke in each episode.
I mean, I don't think I laughed.
I would consider myself a huge Mike Myers fan.
You can see the light has gone out of his eyes.
It went out years ago.
Anybody who is that universally loved,
where you're creating characters and they become
what everybody in the world is doing an impression of
for years to come,
then suddenly you just start striking out.
Like he's got to just have his, he must be a mental disaster
because he rode so high and then came love guru and cat in the hat.
And what was the last movie?
Has it been since love guru?
Love guru was his last starring vehicle.
He was in, no, he did like little dramatic cameos.
He did, you know, I know that.
I know, I know that.
I know that.
I'm talking like a big Mike Myers comedy project.
Love love guru was the last movie.
Love guru was horrible.
My thinking is
it was better than this, but I'd have to do him back -to -back.
I remember Cole Bear actually being funny and love guru at least.
This is before he was overexposed.
But this pen tablet, so going back to so I married an axmer,
my best friends and I growing up used to re -watch the
Mike Myers as his Scottish dad scenes over and over and over.
Oh yeah.
Look at those eyes of that boy's head.
It's like an orange on a toothpick.
Yeah, yeah.
And then the funniest was him talking about the pen tablet.
Yes, he was a conspiracy theorist and then he gets into Kentucky fried chicken.
Yeah, the wee kernel with his beady eyes.
And he got lapaglia sitting on the couch with him drinking beers,
trying to keep his laughs in, but just blowing it, just laughing throughout
every scene that he has with him.
But it works for the part because he kind of's making fun of his dad.
Hilarious hilarious scenes.
In a very underrated movie with an amazing Charles Grodon cameo
and also an amazing Phil Harbman cameo.
But it's Hartman.
It's the funniest Hartman thing I've ever seen in my life.
Is that amazing?
Isn't that saying a lot?
I mean Hartman is a gym.
Amazing.
So I will say as much as I loved it,
I certainly never thought to myself I would love to see this brief comedic monologue
expanded to a six part three hour mini series.
But I said he's doing all these characters.
Let's do it.
All right.
We got all new Myers characters.
Who are they going to be?
He has assembled characters that are certainly not funny,
but they're also not really convincing or good or interesting
or entertaining in any way.
And he's playing a lot of characters.
They suck.
They all suck.
He piles a lot of makeup on half -baked characters,
unfortunately.
And I think we all learned in Goldmember
that Mike Myers had, you know, he's got characters that he does exceptionally well.
But Goldmember was the crack in the dam where you were like the character of Goldmember.
You were like this is sort of half -baked and it seemed like you kind of just needed a character
and he didn't know what else to do.
So he's like, I guess I'll do a Dutch guy.
Like we haven't gone there yet.
The only thing anyone remembers about Goldmember.
I can't remember a line.
I can't remember what his voice sounds like.
All I remember is I love Gold.
I mean, that's it.
And the only funny parts about the character are when he does
Mike Myers like stick when he's like when he's talking about how she has the box.
He puts his skin in so he doesn't eat it or whatever.
He goes, it's really gross and he goes, it saves me from myself.
Like the way, you know, you're like that's a very Mike Myers.
Like he understands why that sentence is funny and he makes it.
But whatever.
You know, in my opinion, you know, Scott Fat Bastard is a grand slam character.
You know what I mean?
And it's like, but after that, and even with that I was like,
oh, he's doing the dad from the Max Axmer.
But that's funny though, because I like that character.
Yeah, um, you know, Austin Powers and Dr. Evil and Wayne and a lot of SNL characters.
But the well has dried up.
So, yeah, so so that was the first crack in the dam was Goldman.
And then also, let's be fair, the whole reason he had a falling out with Dana Carbius
because Dana Carbius was like, you stole Dr. Evil for me.
Like that was my Lord Mike.
Did you ever listen to that podcast?
Did you ever find out if he admitted it?
It's weird for Carbius to say that because so many people have Dr. Evil impressions,
but including in brain candy.
But yeah, I could definitely believe that Carbius was doing that around the office of Myra just stolen.
I don't think it was necessary.
I heard that it was this.
It was the little things.
It was the pinky and that's what I heard.
It was the little things that he took.
Yeah.
Um, because Carbius said publicly, he's like, everybody does a Lauren impression.
Like when Stern's like, but come on.
Didn't he do your, you know, anyway,
this thing and then Love Guru was like, oh boy.
But I'll tell you this thing, this thing makes Love Guru look like the goddamn glory days.
This is, again, there were like five times in six episodes where he did a Mike Myers
sticky thing that made me laugh.
Yeah.
Like when he's doing the bad jokes on the newscast,
like when he's next to the bear and he's like, I just can't bear it.
And he's doing the like, like that's a good for me.
But, but it only right.
That's what I'm saying.
Like it only made me laugh because I'm like, oh, that's like classic Mike Myers.
That's funny.
You know, like, but like, that was it.
Every character was so just like whatever.
It was just like, oh, I'll do this accent because I've never done that accent before.
And I'll do the, there's the old British guy,
which I would say is a very accurate impression of like an old British character actor.
But it doesn't make it funny in any way.
He gives him nothing funny to do.
The funny, it's, you're supposed to think it's funny that he's like in that like wheelchair.
Like that's the whole joke.
And you're like, and then he does the backing up beep noises.
Gagged, like, which they did in horsepower.
The, there's the Russian guy who is very minimized in it.
He's barely in it.
But he's, I guess, kind of a borat clone that isn't very funny.
There's the Canadian newscaster who I hated looking at.
I mean, the makeup they picked, I was like, God, this guy's awful looking.
And I don't even remember the other people to be out there.
There's all the Australian Rupert Murdoch guy.
It's just dead weight.
He doesn't even have anything funny to say.
Yeah.
And that was confusing because it was like he had the Shepp Gordon and Shepp Gordon.
Who's that for?
His old manager who they did a documentary about that I actually saw,
but I would bet very few people have seen.
Why are you doing an impression of your manager, Shepp Gordon, who nobody knows?
It wasn't doing, but it also because I had seen the documentary,
it confused me because like when Keegan Michael Key's character comes in, for instance,
he's referring to the Australian as a person as if we should know who he is.
He immediately goes, well, we know this guy's evil.
And you're like, I looked it up.
I was like, wait, is this a real guy that I don't know about?
And then it wasn't.
It was just very confusing to me.
I also didn't need, I'm sorry.
I didn't need to see a Mike Myers six part comedy about basically about QAnon,
like like a commentary on QAnon believers.
Like it's just not funny subject matter.
It's boring.
Like I don't, I couldn't tell you what the plot was from moment to moment.
Plotting has never been his strong point.
I mean, Austin Powers is hung together by Gags, but he's got to get his mojo back,
you know, not really a strong plot.
It doesn't matter.
It's so funny.
But here, you really feel like there's nothing compelling you from seeing the scene.
He hasn't learned anything about how to structure a script or how.
They say at the beginning that it's about they're there to save the environment.
And you're like, okay, then why is none of them?
Why are none of the people were supposed to not trust or not,
like railing against the environment?
Like I don't understand why is that the focus?
When nobody's speaking out against it, you know what I mean?
Like think for five minutes and make it a group of people.
And also the whole thing of like they're the good guys,
but in the end they realize they are sort of the bad guys.
It was just, it was way too complicated in all the wrong ways.
It was way too simple and misguided in all the wrong ways.
It just sucked.
It just fucking sucked.
And yeah, you know when Netflix has a mic mire show, like,
look, he has his star fallen, of course, but is he still a widely recognized figure?
Yes, he's not even on the homepage day one.
Like I actually, I was going to watch it the night at premiere.
I got to be honest, I was excited.
I've been looking for a little pick me up and needed to laugh.
They didn't have this thing up at midnight.
Like it was one of those like we'll get it up when we get to it.
You could tell they were ashamed of it and they should be because it's really bad.
But it was for me the Netflix cord pull.
I finished it and I immediately pulled the plug on Netflix.
I was like, they're not making quality programs anymore.
And they don't have good movies anymore.
So what am I doing?
One of the reviews I read said this is everything.
This is a perfect example of everything wrong with Netflix bloat.
And I thought, I'm glad finally, it's being called out by critics now finally.
Like, yes, finally everybody's against Netflix, yeah.
So, but yeah, it's a bad show.
It's not funny.
Joe sent me also, and you owe it to yourself to look it up.
There's a clip.
The one of the Mike Myers characters is that an ogre festival.
I don't even really recall how he got there.
There's Sasquatch plays a major role in the episodes.
He's always actually shitting on the floor.
There's billions of shit jokes in the thing.
But the ogre comes out and as he's about to kill Mike Myers,
Shrek, a life -size bigger than Mike Myers, Shrek comes out and goes,
I'm the real winner of the ogre festival and like beats up the Sasquatch.
His mouth, they don't even animate Shrek's mouth.
Dude, it's like a Disney World costume.
That's why I texted you and I said, I don't understand if it's supposed to be a guy in a costume
or if you're supposed to be Shrek.
Supposed to be Shrek guaranteed.
And they didn't, I guess they ran out of money to animate it,
but then don't include the bit.
And I told Joe when he sent it to me because he even had it cut off perfectly.
Like sometimes there's like extra on the beginning of the end of a clip.
He had it cut off perfectly.
I go, if you tweet this, you will go extremely viral.
He didn't.
And the next day I saw somebody tweet it and get 70 ,000 likes.
And I told you, I told you, I'll tell the people what I told Pat, I didn't tweet it.
I feel bad for, I have a sauce spot for Michael Myers.
I felt bad publicly shitting on him.
Like this, this doesn't count to me because it's behind a paywall.
But I wanted this show to be funny so badly when I heard he was doing it.
I was so excited and oh my god, it's terrible.
And look, he's apparently making another Austin Powers like I'm there.
When I saw the Super Bowl ad, I was like, he's still funny, man.
Like it made me fucking laugh.
So I'm like, all right, maybe if he goes back to the old character,
so whenever they do, when he's world cameos and stuff, it's funny.
Like he, so maybe he just has to go back to the old shit and it'll be funny.
Like, you know, maybe it's just, you know, the other trigger warning.
And I don't use that word often.
But the other trigger warning I need to mention is that there is a five -minute sequence
with extended views of Mike Myers' penis.
Oh, yeah.
You think it's just real dick?
I do. I think he's clearly got some weird exhibition history.
He's been naked in all his movies, but they covered up last second, you know?
He clearly must like being naked in a room because he always is riding it in.
He looks terrible, of course, by the way.
So does a lot of people naked it.
But he's volunteering this up.
He's completely nude and he surrounds himself by men with big,
sexy dicks.
And the gag is horrible.
It's like a new Netflix censorship thing.
Like, where they're going to.
When they cut to the Netflix guy, have you seen a cheaper set on television in your life,
including like Tyler Perry shows?
Like, it was the saddest.
I don't know.
He's like, here I am at Netflix HQ.
Like, they do all these cutaways that are like embarrassing.
I don't know, man.
It was a, it was a drag.
It was a drag.
I watched all six parts.
Yeah.
Keegan Michael Key turns up.
It's terrible.
Terrible.
He's doing like his thing.
He plays like a nuclear physicist,
but he's still doing like a sketchy key and peel type character.
Doesn't really make any sense.
Who else is in this?
Jeremy Irons narrates it into just painfully unfunny narration.
They also steal that bit from Ken,
Ken Jong, yeah.
They steal that bit from Talladega Nights,
where you do one serious quote and then like a funny quote.
There was a very famous bit in Talladega Nights that they did,
which they probably didn't events at either,
but it just feels tired.
By the way, Pat, last thing I'll say,
and then we can move on is
there's also a weird amount of bush chainy jokes in this.
Yeah.
You're not wrong.
Guys, is it because you wrote it then and didn't update it,
or you still think bush chainy jokes have some steam in the tank?
Like, what the fuck, man?
Real wild.
He's wearing a bush chainy t -shirt at one point.
Yeah.
You know, like, I don't know what's going on in the damn thing.
I really don't.
Anyway, a mess.
I will go next with something about working for Miss Pat
and how sanitized everything has become,
has made me really crave edgy, raunchy, button -pushing comedy,
because it's in not even short supply.
It doesn't exist.
So I dusted off an old favorite, Eddie Murphy Raw.
Oh, yeah.
Just a classic, just a classic.
I love the opening sketch where it's Eddie as a kid
telling the shit jokes in his family,
Samuel Jackson cracking up in the corner.
And then he comes out, man, and it's like it's a 90 -minute special.
You see all these, you know, I'll reference yet again,
Aziz's 27 -minute, heavily padded hour on Netflix that came out this year.
It's a 90 -minute top -to -bottom, no bad bits, no bad jokes,
funny, funny, funny.
Is some of it dated?
Sure.
Is some of it offensive?
But it's just a thrill.
He's had his just peak confidence.
He was dressing down, Bill Cosby way before it was cool,
way before it was cool.
I mean, he went out there and while Bill was thriving,
nobody talked shit about Bill back then.
And if you talked, not only talk shit,
but said Richard Pryor talk shit, too.
That sequence took me a part of the seams when I was a kid.
It bothers you that.
No, I'm saying it made me like, I was like forbidden to watch
Eddie Murphy Raw, and I would sneak watch it.
And that Cosby thing into the prior impression,
it would destroy me.
Eddie Murphy, it really cannot be overstated,
the talent that man has.
And I think his real gift above all else is that no,
I don't think anyone has ever made comedy looks so effortless.
Yeah.
You've never seen a beat of sweat on the man.
You've never seen him appear anything less
than completely confident and in control of the situation.
He doesn't miss a word in any of the jokes.
He doesn't stumble.
He delivers everything as funny as it could be.
His impressions are insanely accurate,
but also he puts enough of the spin on it that they're really funny.
He's a gifted storyteller.
I mean, I can't say enough.
He's a legend, and he did it to himself
by making 400 shitty movies in a row,
but he has not been given the flowers that he deserves, I will say.
He's a legend, a true legend.
And if he does this stand up to where he's been promising,
I'll pay any price.
Yeah, it's, that's, you know,
delirious and raw.
I mean, Jesus Christ.
Talk about two bangers.
You know, I'm sure that's a lot of his hesitation to come back.
It's like, what am I going to, you know,
where do you go from here?
You know, right.
But yeah,
you get up there in the red leather suit for your next special.
But I mean, it's been a joke that people have done.
Like Tony.
Oh, really?
Yeah, Tony Roberts did it.
He came out, he did a special where he came out in the raw suit,
and talked about like how it was like,
it was, it was his idol, and like, you know,
and then in the gag was like 30 seconds and he's like,
this shit hot, then a motherfucker.
And then he like went and took it off.
And then Amy Schumer did it on her special leather.
Oh, you're right.
You're right.
Yeah.
But he's Tony Roberts from Annie Hall.
No, Tony.
I'm sure that's kind of red leather.
So stand up comedian named Tony Roberts,
who's fucking hilarious.
Okay, not familiar.
Who has a joke?
My favorite Tony Roberts joke is he goes, he goes,
he goes, Wendy Williams and Danny Glover is the same
motherfucking person, y 'all.
All right, never seen them two in the same place in same time.
Danny Glover and who?
Wendy Williams.
So what do you want?
Okay.
Anyway, I watched, you know, I'll give you a quick two shot here.
And I'll, and that'll be the end for me.
But I, for some reason, turned on a show that I always thought was bad.
Rules of engagement.
And I jumped in like the fifth season.
Probably was a palette cleanse from the pentaver.
I was like, I just need to quickly go to another show.
I can try to binge that might have some jokes.
Yeah.
I jumped into it season five.
And found myself laughing quite a bit.
You, I can't believe this show is still streaming by the way.
I mean, it is, it was a beloved show and syndication.
It ran long time by today's standards.
It would be banned.
I mean, it is inappropriate joke after inappropriate joke one after the net.
I told you the one where the, the wife says something to spades assistant
and she leaves the room.
And he's like, yeah, and the Indian guy goes,
oh, somebody had a extra helping of bitch this morning.
You know what I like, it's like jokes like that.
And by the way, far worse jokes than that.
There are, there's a scene where
spades hiring a new assistant and the male lead,
not, not Patrick Warbird or whatever his name is.
But the other guy goes, he spades at something like had to fire the last girl.
She asked too many questions.
And the guy goes, where am I and how long have I been out are valid questions.
And you think like he's just saying it to be like, you're a scumbag.
Ha, ha, right.
And you realize he's not saying that because then spades says
that was, that was two years and a lot of hush money ago.
And you're like, oh no, he really, the character actually did something awful.
Like this is joke on the sitcom.
You're like, yeah, he's just Christ.
But anyway, I found the show in places enjoyable and funny.
Warburton is very funny.
There was a really,
part of me was just the nostalgia of when you could make a terrible joke.
And you know, if you didn't like it, you just turned it off.
And part of me also did understand like, wow, some of the shit is out of control.
Like I can see why standards are changing and evolving.
So I'm not a monster, but, um, but for the most part, it just made me laugh.
There was a really funny sequence where, oh, by the way,
but then I went back to the first season.
I was like, I'm going to start from the beginning and it's fucking unwatchably bad
for like three seasons.
And then all of a sudden it just gets funny because they get like a lot of sitcoms,
especially take a while to find their footage.
But there's a great Warburge.
It's a, it's perfect where he's talking to the Indian guy and he goes, and he goes,
need to buy a rug.
You know anybody?
Help me find one.
And the Indian guy goes, oh, I see, because I'm of Indian descent,
I must know or be related to someone who markets in corporate trade.
And, uh, Warburge just goes, well, do you?
Yeah, and the king, uh, the very defeated just goes, yes.
I would add him just hand him a card whip a card out like he's got it on him.
Uh, just a perfect,
inappropriate hilarious sitcom joke, uh, and, uh, you know, it's a good show.
You know, it's not a good show.
It's a funny show.
And Kelly, uh, I want to say, not price, Kelly.
The woman who plays Warburton's wife is very, very funny.
And charming.
And it's, uh, it's an enjoyable little program at times.
But that led me into a surprise, which was, I didn't know,
Spade's new special dropped, nothing personal,
Netflix hour special.
And I'm always very happy to see a new David Spade stand up thing come out.
I really love his two audio books.
I loved his last special.
I love his first special.
Uh, I go to sleep to David Spade more than I go to sleep to anything.
I find the man, for some reason, extremely comforting,
extremely funny.
And I don't know, he, he, he brings me a warmth.
He's somebody I desperately want to be friends with.
I feel the same.
And I think that that quality, whatever it is,
is probably what makes him so successful with super models.
There's just something about him that puts you at ease.
And yet, he's also incredibly funny.
It's, it's strange.
He seems to have his shit together.
But yeah, I like the special too, even though for about a half hour,
I didn't really laugh.
And then I thought he kind of found his footing.
But he's just a guy I love listening to.
I like his voice.
I like his take on things.
And when he's on, there's just a few funnier.
Yeah, I agree.
I will close with a brief one.
I watched Death by Temptation, which we've always wanted to see.
Joe Bob did it on his show.
As he did Nightmare on Elm Street the other night.
It will be doing shortly.
And Death by Temptation.
No, Nightmare on the Living Dead.
What did I say?
Nightmare on the Street.
Oh, sorry.
Death by Temptation is
not great.
It was clearly made with not a lot of money and a lot of love.
And that's what that's what I appreciate about it.
It's a vampire thing.
It's evil succubus who is praying on black men in New York City.
The movie is very strange.
It doesn't really hold together.
Not sure it makes sense.
That set up an evil female succubus, I hate to say it,
should have led to a lot more sex and nudity that is in the film.
It should have been an erotic thriller kind of thing.
In my opinion, it just kind of doesn't quite work.
Kadeem Harterson is in it.
The cast is the selling point.
They're all very likable.
And the guy never made a movie again.
James Bond III or whatever is a child actor who made it.
I recommend that the Joe Bob, a lot of fun facts, a lot of interesting stuff.
But the movie itself averaged.
I don't know how it's Kadeem Harterson bit.
He pops up occasionally in things.
I mean, he's got to be, what, 60?
I always saw him as like an alternate or Cineo.
Him and our Cineo have a very similar quality about.
Sure.
Kadeem, let's see what his last work was.
Either way, we have Jalil White on the mispatch of this week.
Yeah, you were saying.
Is he playing like a creep?
Are you kind of like playing him against type?
He's playing, yeah, kind of a creepy boss, not a nerd,
but he's playing a boss at work.
He's funny.
He's very good and very nice, very likable.
I'm sure.
I mean, you don't love or hate oracle.
You don't do that without having the goods.
Well, we booked him also the same day that the new story dropped
that the mom on Family Matters said that Jalil White
wanted to fight her on the set.
Fist fight her?
Fist fight her.
He was a child.
He was 13.
You can read the article about it.
He was trying to, she's coming out with this story now
that he tried to fight her on the set of Family Matters.
Anyway, let's get to the film at hand.
We're talking about a movie it's crazy.
We haven't talked about it in the show.
An all -time classic.
Arguably, the textbook zombie movie or whatever you would call it.
The example, though.
What do you call that, Jalil?
Like the quintessential zombie movie.
It's George A. Romero.
It was made in a shoe string.
It still looks great.
They did a criteria on release that looks fantastic.
The one on Shutter now with Joe Bob's,
you know, our plus commentary is fantastic.
The Prince Great.
It's a movie I have always enjoyed and admired more than I've loved.
I gotta be honest.
I give it all the respect in the world.
I think it pioneered a lot of things that became, you know,
second hand in horror movies, zombie movies especially.
But my preference is with Dawn of the Dead.
My preference is with even the remake of Dawn of the Dead.
I gotta be honest.
I saw the remake and I had a living dead recently.
And I didn't really like it.
And I think -
Well, which remake?
Because there's a few.
They're the one directed by the makeup guy.
Tom Sivini?
I don't have any.
I really love that movie.
I, it's the Gore is good and kind of updated.
I just for something, for some reason to me,
I need more story in it.
I think it's all it is.
It's basically people in a house
warding off zombies and fighting.
But for me, I just needed a little more personal touch,
a little more personal dynamic.
I want to know more about the people.
I love that like Joe Bob talks about how cool it is.
And he's right that the lead of it is a black man at a time when they weren't.
They hear with him and they never comment on it.
Isn't that cool?
And yes, I agree.
However, wouldn't it be kind of interesting
and couldn't you tie it in thematically to your movie?
I guess they just cast him because he was the best actors, what they say.
But I guess I was missing something like that.
Some sort of thematic thing through it.
Even though you can sort of make any thematic connection to the movie you want.
And Joe Bob makes tons of connections on his show.
It's a great allegory for filling the blank,
any number of things.
And we also, Joe Bob talks about how depressing it is
and how nihilistic it is, which I really noticed this time around.
I think it's a four out of five.
I love the original and I get why it's so praised.
That said, I like other horror movies more.
That's all.
I agree with the nihilism saying.
I mean, the black lead thing has been talked to death, right?
It's the main commentary that everybody makes
that the idea that the hero is black at a time of racial unrest
that he gets killed unjustly at the end.
Because the assumption is that he's a zombie
by the guys cleaning up the neighborhood or whatever.
All that stuff has been talked about at length.
And it's one of those things with Romero where
half the time Romero will kind of say that it was done on purpose to make a commentary.
And the other half of the time he'll just be like,
he was just the best actor.
So we hired him.
So it makes you kind of go, he does that with dawn of the dead too.
Or the big commentary is the public trudging through the mall,
the brainless consumerism of the 80s.
And Romero will be sometimes,
I think I've heard him say, a mall was available, so we used a mall.
And you're like, do you know what you're doing?
Yeah.
Well, and that's what I'll say.
We started this talking a little bit about monkey shines.
I have a George, I don't think George Romero was a great director.
Well, no, like I've never seen what's the one?
What's the zombie one from 79?
Martin never saw Martin because it's so hard to find.
I want to watch it.
Martin's the vampire one.
All of his early movies that aren't
neither living dead suck.
Sorry, season of the witch or whatever is bad.
Yeah, the crazies isn't great.
Crazies isn't great.
That one we watched that was like the amusement park.
And then up through, he did monkey shines.
He did a lot of movies throughout the 80s and 90s
that I don't consider very good.
So that is a masterpiece.
Neither living dead is a great movie.
But I don't know how great a director is.
I think George Romero is a case of the Anthony Ketus's.
He, it's all about who he's collaborating with at the time.
The chili peppers.
Where you're going with that?
Well, the chili peppers are a great example.
When they collaborate, when they have Fushante in the band,
they're head and shoulders a better band,
like above what anything else they do.
There's new album, see if you still think that.
Well, they're also all, yeah, they're getting old now.
I kind of liked what I heard.
It doesn't matter what's that thing.
But you get my point, right?
You know, like it's like the, you know, it's,
it's very obvious that like certain people are,
when they collaborate with the right people,
the best comes out of them.
And Romero is one of them.
Look, Romero's collaboration on the first movie
is half with Dan O 'Bannon's a part of it.
And then he went on to do return to the living dead.
You know, they parted ways.
The second movie, it's Savini, you know,
like in Savini is a huge input into things.
Creepshow is him, Savini, and Stephen King.
You know, like Creepshow and Tells From The Dark Side,
which he didn't direct are both good anthology horror.
Don't get it wrong.
The Night of the Living Dead remake is Savini directing.
And you know, it's like, it's, but Romero is involved.
He's better when he's with people.
The Dark Half is a good Romero movie.
But you know, he's like Carpenter,
when like, I think part of it is like,
when he gets taken out of the like, we're recording
on a four track in a garage circumstance
and gets given like the high end state of the art studio,
it does not work to his favor.
His product having the gloss on it does not work very well.
So that's why Night of the Living Dead does work so well,
or one of the reasons, you know,
it's extremely gory for the time.
It's got some great jumpscares in it for the time.
It's very dark for the time.
And my biggest takeaway this time was the nihilism.
I, for some reason, I never quite noticed that as much either
on previous watches.
I, I didn't watch it with Jobab.
I finally cracked open my criterion collection version of it.
And it is, if you don't own it and you want to own the movie,
that's the version to own.
It is fucking gorgeous.
I mean, it's sparkling, pristine picture, beautiful,
and some really cool special features and great packaging too.
But yeah, the nihilism of just the guys just, you know,
at the end, so matter of factly, just being like,
yeah, you put them in a pile and you burn them.
All right, got another one, boys.
Let's move on through like where it's just like,
hey, this is just life now, whatever, it's awful.
That really resonated with me this time,
given our current cultural climate and how down and
dejected everybody seems to feel the idea of like,
sometimes you just gotta press on and say,
fuck it, it is what it is, I guess.
And that makes you a bit of a shell of a human being.
So, so that was interesting to me.
It's also interesting to me that
and this is much more prevalent and dawned to the dead.
But a lot of the people's deaths are done
by mistake by human error versus the zombies being out of control.
I love at the climax, her brother coming through the door
and actually being the one that comes to get her.
I think that's such a great plot twist
after the way it's set up at the beginning.
And I also love that as when she and the main character first meet
in the beginning, she's almost emulating a zombie
because she's so in shock.
I think all of those things are very, very cool.
And the opening scene is great too.
I mean, oh yeah, you've seen this so many times
because much like it's a wonderful life
it was in the public domain.
So like anytime you're watching a Christmas movie,
somebody's watching it's a wonderful life
because it's free to show him going like,
my very Christmas movie house.
Right.
But then you've also seen in a million horror movies
somebody watching the coming to get you,
well, bro, because that's just what they always show.
So I don't know if it was the fact
that it was on TV for years for free
because they didn't copyright it.
And Joe Bob tells that story which is fascinating
which is that they just added a credit
and it covered up the copyright
and that's why they didn't have the copyright to their own movie.
They added a little something to the title screen.
That might be why it's hung around so long
but also, and correct me if I'm wrong, Joe,
is this the first time we saw zombies like this?
It's arguable.
I mean, apparently, yeah, look,
George Romero is renowned as Godfather
of the modern zombie film.
There certainly was shown in movies
before the concept of a zombie.
I don't know that we ever saw them literally crawl out of the grave
before, but I do think the idea of dead people
being brought back to life, you know, zombies weren't,
sometimes zombies are just hypnotized people.
I think the idea of the dead walking again
because of a voodoo curse or whatever was done somewhere.
But I think what Romero was the one that did was like
that it was always connected to some sort of ritual or something.
Romero is the one that was like corpses are crawling out of the grave,
you know, like before this it was,
you're enslaved to be a zombie after death because of X, Y or Z.
So look, for that alone, you owe the guy,
we owe George Romero a lot, obviously.
But, you know, I don't think, I would say this is his second place.
I would say, look, this is kind of like when you try to compare
the beetles and the beach boys, right?
You got to go, well, Christ, how much of any of it would have existed without the beetles?
That's neither the living dead, the beach boys that were drawn to the dead,
where you go, yeah, but they did this first and it was so fucking amazing.
You know, so...
Yeah, and another kind of comparison is the evil dead,
to the evil dead too.
It's like you get kind of the raw, great version in the original,
but everything is just perfected and amped up to its best possible place in the sequel, in my opinion.
Yes.
I mean, hogs up and hogs up for the night of the living dead.
Hogs for sure up to a legend, a real one night of the living dead.
Folks, we'll be back discussing season two of cursed films,
which is on shutter as well.
And I guess that's it.
I'm on Twitter and Instagram kind of at Patrick Walsh.
That's all I got.
Go to Rosa Comedy on Instagram and Twitter.
Bad news, hour special taping is not happening.
The festival I was supposed to shoot it at got rescheduled for November.
So I'm trying to fund a new time, a new place, new space to do that.
I'll keep you all posted.
But in the meantime, if you are in Texas, I'll be in Austin at the Creek and Cave May night,
sorry, May 20th and 21st four shows running that hour.
Just not taping it and come to Joey Roses in New York City.
Joey Roses NYC dot com for all of our info.
That's it folks.
We'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.