Howdy folks, welcome to we'll see you in hell it's the podcast you turn to in this
fine new year when you need some conversation about your favorite movies I'm Joe
Derosa and I'm Patrick Walsh happy new year everybody we're still about 48
hours away from the new year as we record but as you're listening to this
you're fully entrenched in 2021 which I was just saying to Joe it's got to be
better than 2020 it has to be and I said it's not that's that's horribly false
and inaccurate claim it could be absolutely worse yeah 2020 was but who knows who
knows I you know I mean yeah this thing could take a turn I think that's why
you know everyone is about spent in terms of their mental energy there it's like
even people who like don't accept if you're a denier of it I guess but it's just
this lingering thing in your head of like could this eliminate the world you
know that's where that's about where I meant now what did you think of spacey's
Christmas Eve message this year well that's the movie we're discussing right
for the full hour it's just yeah I miss creep show it's we don't mean the TV show
creep show I know that I for one like to be like when I'm feeling down when I'm
feeling depressed I like to be reassured that everything's gonna be okay by a
pedophile on a park bench I like to know that things are gonna get better and
that I myself could find myself without a career and friends and just simply
re -emerging once a year like the groundhog to scare people as an old man I
certainly don't approve of spacey's tackling the 14 -year -old to the floor in the 80s
and I also don't approve of grabbing men's balls and bars although one is much funnier than the other
but I will say I appreciated his message and it didn't give me I was like maybe one day
we'll forgive Kevin and he could maybe he's a human being after all but then I also remember
he's one of our greatest actors that's ever lived so it could just be completely false oh yeah well
I mean who knows for me you always figure what actually went on is probably much worse right now I think
in his situation like the fact that so many of his victims or people who accused accusers
have killed have died that to me is the most interesting wrinkle I forgot about that part yeah I
forgot about that part all right and to tie that into this video he's telling you not to commit suicide
and all these guys are alleged to have killed them say there's a whole another weird element to it I
forgot about that while you're right all right I'm back to anti -completely anti -spacy not that it was
team -spacy but I thought there was a glimmer of hope the redemption for a second but it is weird I
mean I like I feel like if he was an action star they would just be still making action movies with him
that seems like a genre where whatever you your crimes whatever you've done will welcome you with
open arms and you can still make direct to DVD shit well that's what I was going to say you can
it doesn't matter action movies no no bounds as far as distribution is concerned sure you know the
type of movies Kevin Spacey makes it's like you know they're like sorry Kevin this biopic about a banker
from the 1920s isn't isn't really direct to video the Bobby Darren story isn't really what we're
looking for in the genre market yeah he did you ever see that Bobby Darren picture by the way I watched
about it's bad it was real bad I think it ruined I feel bad for what's her face in it it was like
that was like the end of her Bosworth yeah it was she was on her way that she did that they were like
we'll see you later I mean she was 40 years younger than him yeah he's he's he's got a problem but I
think his way to come back is to be the villain in these Travolta Willis soon to be deaf cage
direct to DVD projects he's got to be the over -the -top villain he'd fit right in he'd be perfect in them
right I think that's his way back but right now he's probably like it'll blow over and then I'll
be right back to the American beauties again and he's wrong yeah it's a wrap I think it's a wrap
yeah Jesus man that's that's a heavy shit that's heavy shit I don't know if you saw it we talked about
LaBuff on the last episodes but there's this movie coming out called what is it called so many of
the titles this year are so generic and they just they dumped every Oscar movie on the streamers
in like a one -week period yeah 30 movies you're supposed to see that just came out yeah none of them
seem interesting to me at all but it's this movie with Vanessa Kirby who is an actress I like and
Ellen Burston who is one of the best actresses of all time yes and Shia LaBuff and as far as I know
it's like a relationship drama between LaBuff and Kirby and it's a supporting role from Burston now
this thing's being advertised as a just a Burston Kirby project no mention of LaBuff and Netflix put
a two -minute trailer online that LaBuff isn't in oh wow they're just pretending he's not in and then I
saw a great comment where somebody is like so is it true that you're reshooting LaBuff scenes with
Christopher Plummer I thought that was very funny that is funny I was gonna make the Tignitaro joke but
this is face Chris DeLia in that new zombie movie coming out of the guitar right right it's
frightening what they can do these days with technology there's an app now the movie's called
pieces of a woman I'm sorry go ahead there's an app now there's an app now that's like it's like a
deep fake app yeah it's something it's literally just the easiest thing ever like in the in the ad
for it they replace McCauley Culkin's face and home alone with Leslie Nielsen and it's literally like
just like with the tap of the screen it does it and you're like this is dangerous this isn't a good
thing like this is this is getting way way way too easy like why would I saw a picture the other day
where I was like oh my god Trump's put on 50 pounds and then you look at the comments and it's like
not some great doctoring job yeah and I love to like my favorite thing of these fucking nerds and of
course like the movie sites I'll pick this up and and run the story as if there's any like real
validity to it they'll be like they'll be like super fan makes the Irishman look better than Scorsese
could it's like yeah Scorsese he couldn't sit around for two months working on one scene right you
know what I mean it's like yeah that's yeah of course if you had that much time what you know what I
mean they just did it with the with the are you gonna watch the Mandalorian I don't want to spoil
anything yeah I am yeah I am all right well it's a shame because I wanted to review the last episode
today and damn it I've had so many people rave about both season one and season two to man I know
you like season two more but like people just thinking I'm absolutely crazy for not loving the Mandalorian
so I'm gonna give it another go see if that's fine painfully boring um season two I loved and but season
two especially if you're a star wars fan they're really doing a lot of redemption work to the franchise
with season two like it's great it's really great all right all right but the surprise in the finale
is over the top okay um so all right I'm gonna take that off my list for today everything's gotta have
a twist I mean I when everything has a twist nothing has a twist in my opinion right that was sprites
slogan for a little while did you know that I didn't know that I um I watched uh well I'll talk
about it in the movie corner but I watched one of the big Oscar pictures last night and when the twist
hit I was just like give me a fucking break everything has to have to have that and there's no surprise
when everything has that is my point yeah no I agree that was David mammoth's philosophy on writing
a story script was uh I'm paraphrasing but it was like if you can surprise them in the last act
you've got a good story if you can surprise them in the last five minutes you've got a hit or
it was something like that yeah yeah anyways I said fucking cocksucker a lot in it but it was the same
basic idea I have a new psycho I'd like to do please spacey was one of them I never
ever recovered that uh but I am excited about something by the way what what do you think was the
discussion that made him step away from doing the house of cards videos which were genuinely chilling
well he he I don't think there was a discussion I think he thought I'll really wow them if I start
this video as if I'm gonna do another one of those and then no but seriously folks like that's a
that's how you you you get their attention like there's he's still putting showmanship into his don't
kill yourself videos sure sure which I guess is admirable on its own way but uh it's odd yeah I mean he's
on that bench and like if that's like he's in like echo park or something yeah looks close yeah yeah
also he was he was caught you know and by the way you know it was a consensual encounter it's not
not a big deal to me but he was caught doing gay stuff in a park in London maybe that's the park he
was in no because there was palm trees I think right that was an LA park I didn't know where the park
I don't know why you're you're putting people mentally with an image of you in a park bench when when
your history has this in there you know yeah well yeah you want to you want to just try to to show
you're on the straight narrative no matter what so yeah it's like even though there's nothing wrong with
uh doing sexual things of any nature well sub -nature in a park yeah there it but publicly yeah it's
not good it'd be like if you know George Michael was doing a press conference from a right but he
did do that joke on extras which I my hats off to him I thought that was great like that he came out of
the bushes driving fucking man uh uh i so disney plus announced since we last recorded uh the slew
of or the slate rather of um marvel tv shows and star wars tv shows it is a tremendous amount of tv
shows are doing with both uh brands i don't care at all about the marvel ones but i am very excited
about the star wars ones most of the titles i are are exciting to me and i'm looking forward to some of
them i don't care about but whatever um the reason i think this is interesting and the reason i
think it's a good thing and i the reason i think it's quite frankly very smart is talk about
uh uh a media conglomerate and major studio that saw the writing on the wall with theaters and was like
fuck it we're doing it all as tv shows on straight and we'll have all the fucking slack in the world to do
whatever we want we can write any wrongs very quickly when we have seven simultaneous stories and tv
shows going on and this is the future and we're gonna embrace it instead of fighting it and being
pissed off about it you know mark uh that for star wars they announced like seven tv shows and
one and a half movies or something like that right so i thought it was really really smart uh on uh
disney's part to do that uh uh you know and it got them completely around all the bullshit that
Warner brothers just went through with the hb o max announcement you know yeah let's definitely discuss
uh all that when we get to the wonder woman episode which we're doing next because now we are in
kind of a post experiment world of of dropping a huge movie like that and everything that happened
so we'll get into it but i do think the uh the movie business is on is on its last legs
i certainly as we know it and yeah same but i you know i i feel like the theatrical experience may be
gone soon i will stand by my opinion that i think it's just it's just gonna be it it's gonna go
back to the eighties there aren't gonna be these you know these big multi -screen movie plexes that's
very recent i mean that's the last 25 years basically yeah it's just gonna go back to the eight and i
was watching gremlins uh over christmas and that's seen where he runs through the town square and it's
so uh you know sort of heartwarming to see this quaint little town covered in snow and he and
and in every one of those scenes whether it's back to the future or whatever they always run by a movie
theater that has two movies laying in it and it's an endearing sight and i was like that's just what
it's gonna go back to it's gonna be that again it's gonna be two screen theaters and and and smaller
movies which i think is a good thing i think that this i to me the marvel in particular the marvel
cinematic experience was the was the movie equivalent to trump it was like we hit this
peak of of indulgence and and audacity that was just so crazy and so out of control and so extravagant
that it had to burst it had to it came to a head finally and it popped and i and i so i think it's a
good thing personally but uh we'll see what happens um yeah i mean it's hard for me to to view anything
as a good thing these days but it it it certainly doesn't seem great to me but i also don't like
anywhere that the movie direct the movie businesses headed so um i i don't even understand movies anymore
i find myself looking at the screen just confused and i'm like am i an old man is it is it you know
but i i don't even know what's going on minute to minute in actually in both movies that we're discussing
this week i found myself just baffled uh the creep show special and wonder woman
just baffled i uh i i'm gonna and i texted you in apology let me say it publicly on the air
way before we even get to the review i apologize for making you watch the creep show christmas special
i thought it would be fun i thought it was a good idea you pushed back a bit
uh i pushed back on that you said okay let's do it but in my defense that was the exact same
exchange that happened with wonder woman and here we are with both true i mean i i i knew that the
the fans you folks would want to hear about wonder woman um and i think joe's love of creep show just
keeps him optimistic that this show's gonna turn around but i mean we're on i we've seen 15 episodes
of this thing now it's it's it's bad it's a bad show so my promise to you is we're not going to
discuss uh the creep shows and the main and the main body of the of the reviews anymore and my promise
to you will be that uh i will not push us to do the justice league's action writer cut when it comes
out because you know what i'll do it it's four hours man it's four hours you know what that that i'm
i'm going to sit down with a notebook and a pen we're gonna do a special we should do a special
like three -hour edition for that when that finally comes out when is that coming out
like twenty twenty three and a half or so yeah it's so far away it's like it's fucking ridiculous
anywhere they know there's a trailer comes out now three years before the fun yeah movie gets released
i love re -editing a movie that has already come out and lost money is going to like
bankrupt HBO max it's the worst decision that they spend an extra seventy million on
they spend an additional seventy million which means a hundred and thirty million yeah so um
let's take take us to the movie corner pet absolutely and uh on the on the wonder woman episode
remind me even though i hate to remind me but let's talk hilarious bold one
oh yeah we talked about her at length last night on without a country
and um which also comes out today uh on youtube but uh uh we uh and wherever you get your
podcast but uh we um we talked at length about that that's my favorite thing i've read since Rachel
dola's all whatever name was the n double acp infiltrator yeah it's just great though because
dola's all was her own thing i mean the the tie of hilaria to allic baldwin is what make just the
most blow hard blustering guy i still love baldwin with all his massive faults i mean he's a guy that
i have always enjoyed as an actor as a human i certainly don't get mad at him for punching
uh paparazzi's i mean i don't know how you don't but like this he's in over his head and his
his his follow up instagram was hilarious we'll talk about it on the next one um
all right movie corner so speaking of before we get too far off the subject of redoes
uh re edits re releases uh my first movie is i watched the godfather kota the death of michael corleon
yeah uh storied uh re cut of the godfather three that fans frances for copula has been working on
uh and is much closer to the original vision that he and mario putzo had for the film uh in the
disclaimer at the beginning of the film copula explains that the godfather three
was never supposed to be called the godfather three the original title of the film
was the godfather kota the death of michael corleon and he goes on to explain that you know in music
terms of kota is a summation of the piece and he said this was always supposed to just be a summation
of this character's life it was never supposed to be the godfather part three because they knew
that then it would get tied into the other two and these comparisons and it's not as epic and this
that the other thing so anyway he also explains in the intro there's a new added a new beginning on it
there's a new ending on it uh and all that's true to an extent you know usually when these directors
say there's a new beginning there's a new ending it's like well it's kind of a new beginning there's
you know these there's like two extra frames of something you know something like that but uh but it
is a new edit of the of the beginning of the of the film uh and the edit of the ending is
slightly different but makes a huge difference emotionally with the story um did you know the movie
well enough to recognize what was different or did you have to look up the changes it's not that
there i recognize the differences in the beginning and the end in the main body of it there were
things where i wasn't sure if it was in the original or not right and my mom knows the movie really
well it's her favorite of the godfather films oh yeah so is it because of the catholic thing or what
no idea but she loves it uh and i was like so i would ask her she's like no this is all in there but it
was like more like this scene was put into a different place in the movie it's different in the timeline
where this scene is a little edited a little differently or a little longer or contain some more
information or whatever and i will say this matt McCarthy texted me after he saw it and he said
it's a perfect example of how editing can make or break a movie and i agree with him
it the story of the movie is so much more clear it is so much more concise it makes so much more sense
um and that's it like it's and it works under this new title it just shows you how the
the last years of this man's life are are what what transpires during them right and it works
it works and i think had this come out under that title at the time of its release uh it would have
fared a lot better with critics and and and and that sort of thing there's more
there's just more focus on smaller details that help just make it all more palatable
there's more reference from what i could see there's more reference to tom hegan and tom hegan not being
there which makes the george hamilton uh character less jarring then you know makes it way less like
what the fuck is he doing there right to get more into the details of of Kate and michael's relationship and
where they're at there's just stuff like that in there that help the the depiction of the way
the the depiction of Vincent and he or she is character through the film it's just it's just
introduced much more informatively and it just makes so much more sense like when you watch that
original cut it's kind of like who the fuck is this guy coming in from out of nowhere and when it
went right so um i thought it was a good job look it's still a long movie man it's two hours and 35
minutes so it's not it's not a it's not a brisk watch but but i thought i thought it worked and i
think he reached i don't know if he rescored it but i think he changed the music and you know you
rearranged the scoring of it or whatever so i think it works i think it's worth watching do you need to
own it i wouldn't say so should you own it instead of the original godfather three yes if you're
gonna own one of them i would opt for this one yeah we talked i mean johan i were originally talking
about maybe doing this for the the podcast my issue was i had watched the other version of godfather
three within the year so it just would have been too much i mean it's it's i don't think the movie
sucks and it's original version i just don't think it it really works it i i think the reason it
doesn't work is because it's part of the a franchise that includes two of the greatest films ever made
it can't help but pale in comparison if you look at it as a mob movie with al Pacino that came out in 1990
you know i think it falls in line with uh the other movies he was making around then but as part of that
franchise yeah it's it's it's a little rough so i'm curious to see the recut but for me it was just
hearing everybody say it's these tiny little tweaks that make the difference and i was like well
i don't know if it'd make that much difference since i just watched the damn thing but yeah yeah okay um
i soar see it watched all kinds of things johan you think we might do the wolf of snow hollow
what the fuck is that i'll take that as a no that's a lot more forced to movie yeah yeah yeah uh i
i would do it i'm not against it is it streaming um it's not free but it'll probably be free shortly
i would do it i would i would i love a werewolf movie i love robert forster i would do it
we'll hang on to it maybe we'll do it um all right so i'll start with uh sole the new Pixar
lot of twitter b for him this movie yeah you know it's like
it it is really reached a point where just you know like shits creek uh became very controversial
yesterday and i'm why did shits creek become called shits creek is just the most innocuous sweet
pleasant show you know i don't have quite the passionate love that everyone has for it but i watched
every episode i enjoyed it the cast is just incredibly delightful and kathano hara is a queen
is damp quiz for that that voice she does on it is outrageous and the fact that she makes it
passable and believable is insane well she quadruples down on it each season so like by the end she's
just talking like as if it's in a different language almost but um i'm a i'm a i like the show i
think it's fantastic but uh this guy rizwan was on the show outsourced that i did um it was one
season wonder for nbc uh it was in an indian call center and was moderately controversial at the time
because we did jokes about the indian accent you know um so now 10 years later
rizwan is in i would say one out of five episodes of shits creek he comes in he does essentially
the same character same voice he played on outsourced a little less evil but he's really funny he's
got a funny little supporting role and god it was it was just a a mass thing on twitter yesterday
of people talking about how his character like and using accents is wrong if he didn't have an accent
and i'm like even when you do the right thing you're doing the wrong thing technically this is a
show that's entirely about inclusion and about gay couples and and and etc etc um and even then it's
like well wait a minute we we were too nice on this show we talked we talked about how inclusive
and great it was that they it showed a full like seven season gay relationship that was very sweet
um let's let's instead find something that we can declare ugly about it and i i i just hate it
you know of course as it goes off the air too which is what i yeah which is what happened with
Seinfeld Seinfeld breathed through nine seasons with all types of outlandish jokes yeah and in the last
two episodes it got all this heat for the the Puerto Rican Puerto Rican Day parade episode which is
by far the worst episode of Seinfeld it's a yeah outside of season one yeah but after all the jokes
they made it was like all of a sudden it was time to kind of crack the whip and go no this isn't funny
anymore and then in the last episode with the fact with john pennett yeah um so yeah so that seems to
be the trend with with beloved shows is let's let's get mad at it right at the end because now we because
we secretly enjoyed this whole time and snickered at things maybe we shouldn't have and now that it's
going off now we can shit on it because they won't take it away from us well by the way to my recollection
they don't make a single joke about him having an accent or about Indian people in general there's
nothing like that he's just an Indian character so imagine being Rizwan a guy who's like
struggling to get to get you know he I think he had a couple lines in wolf a wall street I'm always
happy to see him he's a family man he's very funny actor and now you're a part of something that
everyone loves it's done you feel like okay now my career is going and then it's like oh no wait
you open twitter one day and you're the source of controversy so of course they ask him for comment
and he says look I guess the one thing I could say is it would have been cool if my character had
like a family and a home life and you can talk about the creators with that if you want that could be
the issue but as far as me being an Indian actor using an Indian accent I don't know what your issue is
so now it becomes this thing of like the creators of the show or like oh yeah this show that was about
very much about this family now a guy who comes in every five episode like less of a character than
Newman now we're supposed to suddenly go home with him and like do episodes where we see his family like
so yeah soul soul the issue with soul is basically that they're for at least half the movie there's
a white woman inside a white woman soul is inside the body of a black man and people took umbridge
I think the reason they took umbridge was that Tina Fey voiced the white woman and Tina Fey has
had numerous skirmishes with racial material um I think the reason Tina Fey has these skirmishes is
because she is one of the true comedic voices working who who understands that discussions of race
is very much a part of comedy and should be even though it can't be anymore um regardless
it's a terrible thing to bring into soul I think if you want to write those articles or read those
articles do it but soul is uh you know I'm going to need to watch it again I was so thrown by like the
the way the worlds were created in it it just it's very trippy the afterlife is designed in this way
that like it's just not what you'd expect from animation it's really really interesting stuff
and I kept getting kind of lost in the visuals and missing important things so I would like to watch
it again but I liked it a lot Jamie Foxx plays a guy a jazz pianist who on the eve of his big break
dies and the movie is really sort of this look at like what your dreams mean what it means to give up
your dreams why giving up your dreams is not bad necessarily um it discusses how even when you do
get your dreams you can still be unhappy he doesn't understand how like um wait what I got this
and I still don't feel good you know what is that that's who can't relate to that I can certainly
relate to that yep I got my dreams and I still hate everything um obviously Pixar is operating
at a very very different level than than most animation they talk they bring in themes that are
just like I kept thinking about a kid watching this I don't know that a kid would even enjoy this
it's it's dark it's like I imagine parents would be like well don't teach my kid that message I want
my kid to think he can be the president of the United States or whatever else but there's something
really interesting about it I feel like I I'm going to watch it again I admired it certainly from
an animation standpoint I thought Jimmy Fox did a great job you know the problem with these things
is that it is animation so you got a bunch of like a cat a fat cat like you know having antics while
this man's exploration of his soul is going on those tones sometimes don't quite gel but uh you
know Pixar does really interesting shit and even the ones that there's I don't like I feel like I
should go back and rewatch because they're just they're good they're good shit all right I'll never
watch it but yeah and that a Pixar guy but uh but I talked it to add nausea we talked add nausea
about this without a country so I won't go into it again here but um anyway um I watched a movie
that I've always been told was terrible yes uh I watched it with my dad because he's a big fan of
the franchise and I found it delightful I watched Star Trek Generations with my dad whoo on Christmas
day uh first one I saw first Star Trek movie I saw that's not one to start with I'd say no but look
is it a great movie no not at all but uh is it a fun Star Trek crossover thing where you get to see
Kirk and Picard together yeah that's a lot of fun and I'm a sucker for Kirk in any way shape
reform I'm a fan of Picard in that crew you know it was a great movie to watch with my dad uh it was
a lot of fun you know a lot of silly humor and uh and I can't help but get a tear you know it brings
a tear to the eye when it plays the little Star Trek music and Kirk's something inspirational and and
they save the day you know what can I say uh I I really liked it uh first contact out of the next
generation movies is the one that's supposed to be great we watched that right after I fell asleep
not because it was boring because I was just really tired um so I can't speak to it but uh but uh
first contact first contact is supposed to be the best of the next generation film um but anyway I'm
a huge fan of the of the Kirk crew Star Trek movies and I enjoyed generations as much in the same
way as the godfather koda it was just a little period on the end of Kirk's story and I was happy to see it
so yeah my buddy Ryan and I used to always do the bit from the trailer where uh Kirk wrote up on a
horse if memory serves yeah yeah and then Picard asked him to do it and he goes sounds like fun
we see that all the time so like I'd call uh call him up and go hey man you want to go see
forest gump today and he goes sounds like problem even though we had never seen the film but uh
that's a great that's a great scene where he goes where he finally agrees to do the mission and he
they and as far as I know it's the first time Kirk calls attention to it yeah and he goes he goes
he goes uh what's the line he goes uh uh Captain the Starship Enterprise you say huh
and Picard goes yes and he goes dangerous mission and he goes yeah I assume the odds are stacked
terribly yeah yeah yeah yeah he goes yeah yeah sounds like fun yeah like yeah seven movies thank you for
finally saying what it always is I heard him and Takai on stern yesterday it was from like 2010
and they were at each other's throats that uh I mean he was such an asshole like anytime
Takai would be getting upset he would hit him with like the most hacky gay joke again and again
and again it was it was kind of incredible you know it was just like um the their their their
issues are like 40 years old and yet they still just bicker like children it was amazing
yeah I listened to the Leonard Nimoy I am I am Spock book audio book yeah it was a sequel to his book
from the 70s called I am not Spock which he talks about it in the new in the newer book how he got
tons of bad press for saying I am not Spock fans were so if so this fan overactive fan should have
been like it's been going on forever yeah but uh but he talks in that book about about uh he talks
with admiration for Shatner but he also you know he hints greatly at Shatner's ego
he'll be like you know we were supposed to have a lunch to discuss the possibility of doing a third film
I show up all of Williams lawyers are there for some reason you know he comes off like a monster just
and everything out of the red about him but uh all right I saw a movie called bloody nose empty
pockets and I had seen it on a couple top ten list this year I was curious to check it out basically
what it is is in theory it's a documentary about a dive bar off the Vegas strip and the people inside
it like on the last night before it's shut down basically or you know it's it's just I guess it
might just be another average night of this joint but uh when you really look into it they actually
filmed it in New Orleans so I'm sort of confused by the whole setup of the thing because it's one of
these things where it is a documentary they took actual people actual barflies put them in a dive bar
um and just kind of saw what would happen like an experiment and they shot it and people were
actually getting drunk and fucked up and talking about whatever they wanted to talk about however
as much as I enjoyed it and I really did I think the reason I enjoyed it is that I am not
able to go to dive bars and have not been for a year and just hanging out in a dive bar was fun
to me and seeing all the drunks it seemed like a night at the roost you know particularly
uh crazy night at the roost maybe but I can't for the life of me figure out why these guys wouldn't
just actually go to a off the strip Vegas dive bar and do it there or do it about a bar in New Orleans
like why this why the the fakery it makes no sense to me I guess if you're already gonna make it fake
and and and have this like team of chosen barflies then it sort of makes sense but
um that's what I would say about it I very much enjoyed it but knowing that it was knowing that some
of this could have been faked knowing that a few of the people were actors and some of them weren't
some people really like that stuff uh to me it just sort of bothers me and takes me out of it uh but
overall uh you know getting to experience a night out with some drunks was really fun and like seeing
people actually behave crazy and get drunk and stuff it's good to see when you've been sitting inside
your house for a year so you know I think I got it for 99 cents on on prime certainly an interesting
movie I just couldn't for the life of me figure out why you wouldn't just do a documentary about a dive bar
you know I think they would have wound up with roughly the same level of interesting footage you know
if if all these drunks know a camera cruise and they're gonna be performing and and having fun with it
right so the the mix of fake and real always bothers me a little bit but it's worth watching
all right my third and final something a little bit different uh my friend Jared McGlennigan who's
a tremendous actor and one of my oldest friends uh we went to college together uh and he's a theater
actor and he's he's ever since college was well he's been theater acting I think since high school but
I saw him for the first time in college and I was like wow this guy really is talented uh and you
know it's one it was one of those moments where you watch your friend do something you know artistic
for the first time and you go oh this isn't like watching my friend do a thing this is like watching
a real artist do a thing that I don't know uh and um he he he's just a fantastic actor uh he
and he is part of the Wilma theater group uh in Philadelphia they did a quarantine production
where they took all these measures and testing and all these quarantined things whatever
the play called heroes of the fourth turning where they went up to a house
somewhere in the country I think it was in the poconos um and shot this play uh but you know
because they were shooting and not live on stage they were able to shoot it like a film but on video
so it still feels like you're watching a play uh and in fact the way they shoot the actual house
because the whole story takes place in the backyard of a home
they did it in a way where it you know it i i wasn't sure if i was watching a set or a real house
throughout it so it feels very much like theater uh even though it's shot like film um
anyway it is it was something that they that they did uh then they streamed it you you could buy
tickets online it's unfortunately no longer streaming uh i think he was telling me they
might it might come back for a second run online uh it received tremendous reviews including
from the New York Times uh and and the play is just it was just masterful it was just an amazing
amazing piece of theater uh it's about a group of friends reuniting for the inauguration of their
college revisiting their their very Christian college for the inauguration of one of their
friends mothers who's becoming the president of the college uh they're all every character in this is
is a conservative Christian and it attacks the discussion and the debate uh of everything going on
in America right now but through the perspective of four or five different conservative Christians
and those different perspectives uh keeping in mind this is produced by a very liberal group of people
uh i just found it riveting i found that it did the impossible which was humanizing you know the
people that we always tag as just being these sort of archetypal villains or whatever uh you know
these midwestern uh uh very very devout Christians who are you know uh you know who we all claim are
just blind trump supporters and this that and the other thing this got into how some of them like
trump how some of them thought trump was disgraceful it got into how some of them think that there's a
race war coming and how others thought that that was absurd and what it just got into every bit of this
very very hard very challenging discussion that we're all having but that we're all usually
having amongst people that think exactly like us and to watch something like this
that was not only challenging but in some way humanize these people that i have never encountered in
real life and only have this media idea of um it was brilliant and it was it i find it brilliant
every time anytime you can watch something where you could 100 percent more or less disagree with the
characters yet still find them human and relatable in their own ways i think that's an almost i just
think that's the the mark of brilliant brilliant writing that is a very very hard thing to do all of
her stone kind of did it with w um and it was one of the things i liked about that movie i didn't think
this guy that i didn't agree with and made me in some ways feel sorry for him and like understand
what his plight was in his own way and that to me is again brilliant writing and that is also why so often
on the show i rail against things that write these paper thin black and white villains and i say it's
so boring and it's so stupid because that's not the person you disagree with isn't that they're not
the embodiment of evil they're a human being like you that on some level you are able to relate to
and that's what can be so frightening about it sometimes so uh it was just an amazing amazing amazing
piece of work that you New York Times raved about it uh if you have the chance to see it whether it's
this production or otherwise or even just read it i would strongly recommend to do so uh it's just a
really really amazing piece of work all right that sounds great what's it called again heroes of the
fourth turning okay and it's also by the way it's not theory in its writing and by that i mean
anything that at the beginning of the show you start to take is just like sort of theater
quirkiness because you know theater dialogue can sometimes have that quirky aspect where it gets a little
too like almost like kevin smithy or something yeah where it's too gets too cute any aspect or element
of that that you kind of sense at the very beginning is immediately justified as you learn who these
people are and you start realizing like oh my god no this is how people and this is how this person
would speak and this is why they're speaking that way and it's just it's just an incredible piece of
work check it out all right uh speaking of w which i also didn't really care for but i think i
love her stone did an amazing job on nixon doing something very similar kind of making you sympathize
with somebody i recently rewatched nixon it was kind of blown away by it compared with what with trump
it's like there it's the same thing basically yeah yeah but um yeah i'm just letting you know that the
Oliver stone uh episode which will be long and involved i've been recording it in chunks because i
promised it before the end of the year which now gives me two days to to drop it but the Oliver stone
retrospective episode will be posted likely tomorrow on new year's eve where i discuss each movie
that stone wrote and directed um the midnight sky is my third choice this is this is really what i'm talking
about when i say that the movie business is an extreme jeopardy uh a George Clooney movie starring
a space epic George Clooney movie directed by him and starring him is dumped on netflix two days before
christmas nobody knows it exists it cost over a hundred million dollars uh you know that you
can only do that so many times before things start to to become a problem in in your uh banking
situation but um the midnight sky is bad you know it's it's it's it's George Clooney it's his take at like
an arrival type movie it's from the guy who wrote the revenant mark l smith
not a fan of that film i'd like the revenant quite a bit um this is sort i mean right off the bat
it's like okay we're we're all stuck here between christmas and new years uh you know give me some some fun
and i understand why nobody's watching this thing i mean George Clooney is dying of cancer
he's in the movie in the movie yeah okay he looks very very old in this in this gray beard and at the
beginning um you're watching as everyone is being rushed the the remaining survivors of an incident
on earth which they don't discuss but which clearly is supposed to call to mind the pandemic um has
killed basically everyone on earth and they are taking people from this like snowy the thing
really reminding me the thing at the beginning i was like awesome it's Clooney with a giant beard
in the snow i can't wait to see the action in this thing he's dying of cancer they're gonna take everybody
to another location uh i guess to die there to die let in a less solitary place which is already a
very depressing opening scene and Clooney says i'm just gonna stay i'm gonna stay here and die alone
because that's what i want to do this is also uh they they also keep flashing back to a young
Clooney um giving a speech at like a a nasa type place and they also keep cutting to people on a
spaceship including felicity jones uh david oh yellow oh Kyle Chandler i should i shouldn't i wasn't
trying to be funny mispronouncing his name i i don't know how to pronounce his name um and that's
a problem i i should know i'm sorry but i don't uh Kyle Chandler Damian Bashir all these actors who
are like names but all kind of boring actors to me if i may say they're all on this ship it's very
much like the alien crew and you don't know what the connection is really between these people but
Clooney is basically trying to warn this ship that's been out there in the in the ether to not come back
to earth because earth no longer exists this incident is caused everyone to die uh add to this
there's a girl that got left behind a young girl is there with George Clooney as well
if if you seem sort of like confused but also bored that's what the movie does as well
it is so dull and there's something about George Clooney i like everyone else really really like
George Clooney the actor i really like George Clooney the public figure i think everything he does
is pretty good to have a career that's going on this long and like have no scandal and no nothing like
i think by all accounts he's a great guy as a director he's not good he doesn't know how to like make
you care about it's it's the strangest thing how he could be on all these movie sets and just miss it time
and time again suburban con with Matt Damon the the colon brother script that he kind of took over
is so bad you're just like wow i see what happens when other people try to do a coin script like it
just they don't know what they're doing um good night and good luck but you know good night and good
luck which i think was his first was a very well done one but you got a wonder did he have like a
team really kind of helping him out there yeah i'm looking through these leather heads with krisinski
is one of the worst movies of all time um monuments men has this amazing cast and just it's just like
every senior like why isn't this working why doesn't it click and i i can't explain it but i just
i think it boils down to him just not being good at directing you know this movie has it it looked
and felt kind of like ad astra which i did enjoy uh the Brad Pitt timely Jones space movie also very
depressing and slow i don't mind depressing and slow that's my life but um it's just it just doesn't
work i can't imagine anyone loving the midnight sky and i also pet can't imagine anyone loving
today's feature yeah creep shows christmas holiday special not to be confused with the creep show
thanksgiving holiday special uh which was barely animation uh was halloween wasn't it for halloween
no no it was thanksgiving because it was all food related wasn't it both things were about eating
yeah maybe i don't fucking know anyway yeah maybe it was halloween uh yeah it was you're right okay
it makes sense that it'd be halloween yeah it was a creep show animated special is all it was called so
well anyway he's holding the pumpkin it was it was it was halloween this time around uh they are gonna
they were did a live action one -off episode uh i had high hopes because it was live action uh good cast
adam pali leading the whole thing um the lady for madman uh and camp yeah is she was she on madman
i know she was on yeah she's like his wife i think on it i think she's no she was on madman have you
seen madman drew uh no but i i looked her up and she's in pictures with don draper okay okay she might
have been in there but she's not as wife now that's anyway different actors decent cast is the point uh
January Jones that was his wife all right so um you know it was it's a story about uh it's called
shape shape shifters anonymous which even the title i was like okay this sounds like creep showy
tells in the crypt like it's a support group for people that are shape shifters this is interesting i'm
listening uh and and that's where it starts at the beginning of the film or the story starts at this
meeting that adam pali is coming into because he believes he is a werewolf and that's just about where
it ends too uh basically he believes he's a werewolf because he's finding stuff in his shit i mean that
this thing it's it's got a two minute proctologist scene of a doctor dig and stuff out of his
asshole well also how about like where they started to lose me when he's sitting in the when he's
like i had to bring a sample in and he's sitting with a shifter where full of his own shit yeah and
you're like come on guys like just it's also why did those things make him think he was a werewolf
i guess because he was eating people yeah he was eating yeah yeah uh and and you know man it's
anyway so it's it's trying desperately to do this horror comedy thing it does you know my pet my
biggest pet peeve which is like i'm fine with horror comedy but make it make it believable in some way
and and again they they completely go off the rails with this gag with the shit in the Tupperware
then they get into this biblical backstory about shapeshift shapeshifters that Santa Claus was created
to hunt them down and kill them and they talk about this uh testament uh from the bible that was uh
that that you know a secret testament which is kind of a cool idea i love the da Vinci code for that
reason and it's called the book of Bob and you're like can you make it sort of believable
can you use a name they would have used back then like yeah this is what i mean when i you know
it's jokes at the expense of anything of the quality of the story it's jokes for the sake of jokes
and not even good jokes for the sake of jokes right dumb stupid jokes i respect the hell out of
the career he's had this guy should not be writing and directing these things uh it makes no sense he
he's a one of the most gifted makeup artists in the history of film doesn't mean he's the only
got to do that for the rest of his life but why why would you think a makeup artist should be the person
to write direct run a show it makes no sense i don't understand Joe Hill should be running the show
okay running the show not writing and directing everything just running somebody like that should
be running the show yeah they're doing they're doing nothing that that made the original creep show
brilliant the original creep show was brilliant because you had a great hard director George A. Romero
paired with an amazing horror writer Stephen King paired with an incredible affects person
Tom Savini Greg Nicotaro should be in the Tom Savini role here they should have Joe Hill or
somebody like that in the Stephen King role and then they should have an amazing horror director
in the director's chair for these things and they're not doing any of that at all
i know Nicotaro is not writing and directing all of them but he
these things are under acted this one you were under acted this one and i got to say for a guy who
respects so much when it comes to creature effects and that sort of thing my god almighty man
there are like creature effects and this thing that literally look like they pulled
an animatronic like not even out of disney world like out of like fucking dornie park in Pennsylvania
and threw it on set and you're supposed to believe this is a monster come to light and it's like
this is terrible the the creep that they wheel out at the beginning of this thing every time
they do an episode it look i think i said this last time it looks like they bought it at fucking
Walmart or like Hollywood city like something for your lawn on how it's like
and then on top of all of it you don't even write it an intriguing story i mean i don't know if the
source material itself was intriguing or or interesting or scary or whatever but this story in the way
it is portrayed at least for television it's not interesting it's not intriguing it's ridiculously silly
it's convoluted it's so complicated when it starts to get into and santa was invented to hunt down
the shapeshifters but then santa turned on jesus and now santa's a bad guy but we're also sort of
bad guys because we're wolves and we eat people and then santa's army aren't elves they're
drunken mall santa clauses and it just goes on and it's like guys why are you going so big for something
you've got a two thousand dollar budget to do pair it the fuck down that's a bit that's entirely the
issue is budget and on shutter you know like it it's starting to annoy me because i know that shutter
does extremely well i don't know what their subscriber rate is but i mean maybe it's just that i'm
i'm a horror fan or whatever but everyone i know has shutter and and is excited about what's coming
out each month and whatever and they keep they have a title like creep show you know one of the biggest
horror titles of all time and for them to keep giving so little money you know that's what i have
feeling what happened is he's like i want to do something big for christmas and they're like okay
then we can't give you any money for halloween and that's what we got this fucking thing where they're
literally panning over coloring books you know and presenting it off as entertainment but also too
why are you doing a halloween special and a christmas special when you've got season two on the horizon
do one special and do something do something well yeah exactly and the thing is you're not going to
do something well with nicotaro writing and directing and i hate to say it but like i'm looking back
like okay so he must have written some horror movies at some point that i'm just missing he didn't
well so why they would he's never written anything so i don't understand the the budget on this
it largely takes place like in a a dear john type support group for people who turn into
shapes you know shapeshifters turn to other creatures the cast you know it's the kind of cast you get
when you have no money the the guy who's playing the annoying asshole is like really annoying you know
there's like see from is he from the sitcom dear john is that the same no no no no you're thinking
of jerry burns who was that that guy i'm watching this thing i'm watching that actor in that role
and i'm sitting there like almost punching my tv like i can't get fucking booked i know i audition for
thing after think this guy gets booked not only is he a no name he's completely hammy yeah it's it's
it's a it's terrible it's fucking terrible then they put in i mean i found this just down right
offensive they got the one black character in there and she's literally written like ooh child
i gotta tell y 'all something and i'm like guys what are you doing and she's she's overweight so
everything is about her weight her the thing she shapeshifts into is a hippo it's like oh boy
like when the woman got this part it's like she doesn't even shapeshift she just dresses up
in a hippo costume she's there because this is what i mean with convoluted why are you adding this
layer to it now when now there's a character who isn't even one of the shapeshifters she's just
allowed into the secret shapeshifter meeting that's supposed to be like top fucking secret because she
puts on a hippo suit what and then in the end they make her the hero instead of the guy Bob
who ends up showing up right from the bible they don't never explain how that works they
got through played Bob did a good job i sort of bought him even though he was just kind of a big
muscle dude but the the ending of this project so after she kills Santa or whatever evil Santa
here's where my jaw hit the floor oh here's where my jaw just hit the floor and the amount of
money in the budget that went to this cameo probably could have been spent a little better but they're
like wait what did you wish for they're thinking she wished to become like a full -on shapeshifter but
instead she wished for a sexual visit from Lil Yachty who she was granted a wish for killing Santa
Claus which again where does this come in now where's that rule come in so of course the only thing
a black woman could wish for would be to have sex with a rapper my guess is that the script said
in walks ice cube and then they scratched that out and there's 18 scratch outs until you got to
Lil Yachty I disagree I think they went for Lil Yachty and that Lil Yachty like he's pretty big
like I think like they were thrilled to get like a very Instagram popular rapper like yeah I mean when
he walks in there at the end I mean then it's just like okay this has already been too crazy too
over the top too comedic in a not funny way because funny excuses everything you know if it's low
budget and it doesn't look good and the acting's not good funny excuses all that but this wasn't funny
so he comes in and then you're like okay so now I'm watching an episode of the love boat you know
or fantasy island or something where it's like Lil Yachty what are you doing here yeah you know it's
just I know creep show was never the most serious project but they treated it with a lot of love
and respect and that that is what is gone from these and I told you I'm not watching any more of them
for the show but I'm also just don't want to watch anymore for my life I've now seen hours of this
and there's nothing even above average to me I think when you look back at all the creep shows
there was that one sort of Nazi werewolf thing that was cool and beyond that I don't know what else
to even recommend about this creep show it's a failure they got off to a good start I enjoyed
the gray matter story I enjoyed the house of the head story enough that was the first episode second
episode was the werewolf thing which I thought was cool yeah remember with the second story in that
episode with I was like okay all right here we go and and they just never got off the ground like
it's just terrible and they they do this trick in every episode because they have no money we're like
anything you know any big set piece that transpires they cut to panels in the comic book yeah because
they can't afford to show like a gun fight with between the monsters and the sandals or whatever it is
right you know and it's just it's just fucking terrible it's just terrible
pally when he finally turns into the werewolf is the only shapeshifter who doesn't speak in costume
right every other shapeshifter becomes the whole thing at the end is that they get this wish to fight
these sandals and they and basically what they wish for is is to be able to change into their animal
form but still have their human brain so they can utilize so they can basically be superheroes
which is kind of a cool idea and everybody does that and so everybody turns into their respective
animal and they all talk and and you know they're themselves under the makeup pally transforms and never
says a word but only acts like a feral werewolf which not only makes no sense to the premise that they
set up of them transforming into the animals but still having their brains it also points to the
fact that I believe pally's not in the fucking suit that he was like guys I'll do this I'm not getting
in a fucking wherewolf suit I'm not doing it I just read that about about Malcolm McDowel in a in
Star Trek generations he plays the villain and he said he said he he specified in his contract he
couldn't be an alien because he didn't want to show up for earlier I get it so so the whole
thing man it just feels like corners are so cut I think they've done their second season a tremendous
disservice yeah by putting these specials out any anticipation I had is now gone I can't imagine
many other fans don't feel the same way and they also spent money they shouldn't have spent they
should have saved it for season two or saved it to make something great one time I mean they could
have made a 30 minute special one episode these stories are supposed to be short creep show is never
supposed to be 45 minutes long as a story it's supposed to be 12 or 15 so they could have made a 22
minute episode of something and that they padded with fucking wraparounds with the dumb Halloween
adventure creep doll and made something cool and simple and direct and fun it's like that Joe Hill
story the tweeting from the circus of the dead thing they did that could have been like a really cool
fucking fun hard thing that you saw yeah and instead of just doing that a great story in the right
way they half -ass that they half -ass this they half -ass survivor type which is one of the greatest Stephen
King short stories ever and none of it's good in the end it's all just you know you got key for
Sutherland doing a fucking voiceover and then meanwhile on screen you got this jackass that turns into
a fucking pig you know like like it's like what are you guys doing yeah you with thing with key for
Sutherland in it there to give you an idea of the budget on this thing I know Pally very slightly
you know I like him but you know he didn't mention this on his Twitter I think he's probably
deeply embarrassed about this I haven't asked him but that's just my guess when he goes and first we do
like I guess it was a flashback to see the the first Santa ringing the bell when he realizes that
the any Santa ring in the bell is part of Santa's army the first shot is like him on a street but then
when they cut to the other angle and where you see like it's a town I don't know if you notice this
but that is green screen meaning they didn't have the budget to go like on location just to shoot a city
street I I paused it to make sure and I was like holy shit like that they they've green screened in
a city street that's crazy the easel outside to do no lights needed you know but I mean and you want
to talk about bad writing one of the things with the evil Santa Claus clauses they go the the weapon he
used to kill shapeshifters was named Satan's Clause right because they're big metal claws
so you get it you get what the plan words is and then Pally goes okay Satan's Clause which I assume
over the years has slowly transitioned into being Santa Claus and it's like did you just write that
sentence into the script who do you think who's head do you think this is going over like what
this this shit is written like this is this is this is writing directing acting 101 shit to me
it's like it's like student film quality it's it's I'm really disappointed I've said many times
on the show my favorite horror movie franchise ever is creep show creep show one creep show two
tells the dark side of the movie in my opinion a perfect horror trilogy with the book end movies being
the best of the three in this I was so excited for this show and it's at a point now where I'm
just like I don't even I don't even care about the second season and I'm not one of these purists
that feels like you ruined it it's just additional content that I'll never watch but it's a real
fucking bummer man it's a real real bummer two hogs down two hogs down and and to discuss shutter
the bigger picture for a second I've been I've been keeping up with these joe bob specials and
I basically thought I will keep paying shutter until joe bob dies they it is such an exciting Friday
night for me when there's a new joe bob especially now they have decreased the budget to that show
like that show was a man sitting in a lawn chair drinking lone star beers and I know there's a
pandemic but the budget for this show now looks like I mean I can't believe it and he calls him out he
calls him out on air on this Christmas episode where he was like I'd love to sing this song for you
right now you know we were going to perform this song for you but the people at shutter couldn't
put up you know five thousand dollars for me to do it five thousand dollars people shutter couldn't
put it up to do it and that's the thing too with joe bob it's like the whole point of the it was
called the last drive and for a reason he said in the first season this is the last time I'm doing
this I'm not doing then it was this big smash hit that they guess they weren't expecting and they're
like you know what let's keep doing it so it's like okay great every year we're going to get one crazy
marathon out of joe bob and it's going to be nuts and then like just like with creep show it's like
now it's like we're going to do a Thanksgiving special now we're also going to do a Halloween special
now we're going to Christmas it's like stop doing the fucking specials you're taking away from the
luster of this thing yeah I that that 13 movie first first marathon that he put up I was still
watching that months later because I was trying to like save it and make it last um and man I mean
they they they they've made Darcy as big a role as joe bob Darcy the Darcy seems like super cool I
mean she's a horror expert I get why people like her vibe but the the fake fighting between the two of
them is depressing and not working um I don't know they ruined it so quickly it's just like you have
this great thing I think a big part of the reason that shutter has connected with people is joe bob and
it's like they're punishing him they they he basically put them on the map and he shut down their servers
and he got people talking about shutter and anytime he appears on air now it somehow looks worse
than it did when he when he came back it makes no sense it's like you know you got to take care of
people when they're bringing eyes to your struggling streaming service you know they're they're punishing
him and he when he's calling them out on on camera you know hopefully they should be embarrassed by that
and fix it but everybody's too greedy you know like at some point you're going to have to put the money
on the screen you can't just keep plopping it in the bank or people are not going to keep doing it
oh boy all right folks next episode wonder woman 1984 whoo that's going to be a hot one uh
joderote's a comedy on instagram and twitter check out the taste buds podcast with salvo kano and myself
on the no -press network channel on youtube and check out without a country with korean fisherman
myself every Tuesday live 7 p .m. on the gas digital network that's east coast time uh and everywhere
you get your podcast the Saturday every Saturday every month of every week excuse me uh thank you so much
and happy new year to you i'm the Patrick Walsh on twitter and instagram
i have nothing else going on we will be back uh well we'll be back in in two seconds with
uh wonder woman 1984 i have already posted my uh December solo movie corner but you're getting a
second bonus Oliver Stone episode tomorrow well thank you all yesterday yesterday you're getting it
yesterday uh thank you everybody we will see you next time and we will see you in hell