Welcome, folks, to We'll See You in Hell.
It's a movie podcast hosted by me, Joe DeRosa, and me, Patrick Walsh, and me, Patrick Walsh,
well, Jiminy Glick. We're talking today about the night house, working on the night house.
And folks, if you saw, if you thought the day house was scary,
wait until you see what we have in store this week.
The yeah, we'll talk about it in this movie. All right.
I think it's a theatrical only release, but is scheduled to be streaming very shortly.
So if you're still not venturing out, just be patient. Everything's got like a one month
window now. So fair enough. Fair enough. What's going on, Joseph? What's happening?
What's happening in New York City? Well, I am sitting here the feast. There's a big feast
happening tonight in Bedford, Bedford, Stiverson, Bed -Stuy. No, no, no, no, not Bed -Stuy. Yeah,
Bed -Stuy. No, wait, not Bed -Stuy. Oh, boy. Bensonhurst, Bensonhurst, Bensonhurst.
Um, big Italian feast happening out there. The feast of San Gennaro. That's in Italy. No,
that's here. That's in Manhattan, that one. No, this is another one. Big street fair thing,
you know, food booth. Looks like a hell of a lot of fun. I was going to go meet Chris DiStefano
out there tonight because he lives kind of close to it or much closer than I do. I was going to
meet him out there at 6 p .m. That was my plan for this evening. But I just looked at Ubers and they
are in the $80 range. Yeah, I think Uber and Lyft are essentially bankrupt and are just not telling
anybody or they have no drivers or something, but it's impossible now to get one of those things.
So now you're faced with the decision, you know, is it worth spending a lot of money to go experience
this traditional New York thing? You know, am I, am I being short sighted if I go, I don't need
to do it? Or do you do it and you get out there and you go, son of a bitch, you know, like,
this is cool, but God damn it. You know, so I don't know, there's like carnival rides and stuff and
I'm just so, you can have fun. Yeah. But then the other part of me is like, I can walk up to the
stand and drink with some buddies and right. You had just have myself a little Friday, you know,
so I don't know. What do you think? Well, I think you go to the fest and go to the stand anytime.
But you think it's worth $160 round trip to go to this festival. That's what I'm saying.
No, I don't. No, I don't. That's my point. You are not talking a $20 Uber. We're talking. And then
also too, I get out there. I got to get home. Now what if the Ubers are scarce out there,
you know, no subway. I ain't getting a fucking subway with all this shit going on right now.
What are you nuts? I didn't get on it when there wasn't a fucking pandemic. Well, I mean,
you're going to a festival with carnival rides. I don't see that much difference.
You're out. I'm not going to get, yeah, we're going out there. I'm going to go into the house
of mirrors. I'm not going to go on the rides. I'm just saying like, love a house of mirrors.
What do you think? If I can get out there affordably go, if I can't, it's not worth it,
right? For sure. I mean, do you still have your car have 10, 12 drinks and drive out? Yeah.
That's the other thing I was thinking about driving my Jeep out. But like, do you think
parking near the biggest Italian festival of history is going to be easy? I think it's going
to be like, it won't be easy, but I bet you could find 10, $15 parking a half mile away,
you know? Yeah. And we'll see. And then maybe you stay out there. I don't know.
Then he can't drink, you know? Yeah. It's seven miles from me, which seven miles in New York is
like, you know, it might as well fucking be, you know, might as well be in another state.
Yeah. Yeah. Anyway.
There you go. That's the whole story. That's what's going on in my life and my world.
I mean, I sort of meant what's the, what's the city of New York going through currently? Is it
are things back to normal pretty much or no? Yeah. We're heavily vaxxed at this point. Yeah.
They're imposing the mandatory vaccination thing to go into bars and eateries here.
Everyone. As far as I know, I don't know. I've only had it once out here.
I mean, our mayor was like, this is it. Like we're imposing this. So, you know, look,
I say all the time, I have no problem with that. I also fully understand why somebody
might have a major problem with that, but we're living in a time where, and I think we talked
about this recently, you know, America is the United States of America. It's becoming a much
more European landscape where state to state is, is the thing. And just like in Europe,
they're all on top of each other, but it's one country is its own country. So I feel like that's
sort of happening here. And it's just a matter of you got to live where you can put up with it.
And I realize everybody doesn't have the means to relocate. I know I don't at the moment. I'm very
lucky to be in a, in a, in a world where, or an environment rather, where I am okay with it. So,
you know, I've said from the beginning, amen. If showing a vax card means I can go drink
and laugh and smoke and hook up, I don't give a shit. I just don't care. Like I'm not worried
about it. So, and New York is doing that now and New York is, I think it was the only way to keep
New York, New York. Yeah. Yeah. I did a little three bar crawl the other night. Nothing,
nothing too intense. Just kind of walked from bar to bar and had a drink, but only one of them was
doing it. And I felt great about it. I felt extremely safe. I don't hook up, but I think
that would be a big appeal as you're in a place where you know, everyone is not going to get you
sick. So LA, we're, we're fine. We're kind of, I feel like we were circling another lockdown and
now maybe we're not, but our issue is they're trying to take our mayor or our governor Newsom
trying to recall him. And he's done such a fine job out there. He's done a terrible job. And
everyone on Twitter and beyond has said, this guy sucks. He's the worst. Everything he does is
terrible. Then they switched on a fucking dime. When this recall came up and started saying,
we must keep governor Newsom. I know he sucks, but you have to vote no on the recall. And they
just shot themselves in the fucking foot. You can only talk so much shit until people go,
Hey, maybe you're right. Let's, let's take them down. Our issue is if they take down governor
Newsom, the front runner is this guy, Larry Eldard, who is super Republican. He's pulled a gun on his
wife. He has, he doesn't believe in anything climate change. He doesn't believe in the pandemic.
He's taking away the mask mandate. He's taken away the vaccine mandate. And if LA goes and is not a
democratic city anymore, California is not a democratic state anymore. The country falls
pretty quickly. And I'm not, I'm not one of these guys who thinks that California is the center of
the universe or something like that, but it's always been this democratic stronghold in the
country. And if we lose that it's bad news for a variety of reasons, because if they
recall him, they're going to learn, they can do that everywhere. They can get little grassroots
efforts to recall every democratic governor in America and replace them with these extreme
Republicans. I mean, this guy, but it's a two, it's a two way street. The Democrats could do
that to Republican governors. And they absolutely will not because they're fucking pussies and they
don't organize and they, they don't, they, they, well, we don't play dirty, even though they fucking
do, of course, but it's like, we don't do these things. Well, then you're going to lose every time
because I wouldn't worry about it. These are, everybody here is extremely worried about it.
We're at 50 50 right now. You got, that's all you guys do out there is worry. That's California's
pastime. Your, your, your state mascot should be a wart. I'm not losing sleep. Don't get me wrong.
I know you're not. I'm just, I'm going to say you people, I don't mean that in a derogatory or
aggressive way. Yeah. No, I I'm just saying the people in that environment. Look, you're in the
eye of the storm, dude. Like you're living and working in Hollywood. It's like, it's going to
seem like, you know, the, you know, the world's about to collapse, but I, I, you know, it's, it's
like the COVID worries where they're like, well, we don't know what these new variants it's like,
okay, we didn't know what the initial one either. Yeah. So let's not start saying all the children
are dead. Right. When we don't know, let's take a breath. Keep seeing this is the worst time for
cases and it's not like it's not going great. Don't get me wrong, but like if it's the worst time for
cases, why were we locked down for a year and now we're not? None of it makes any sense. None of it
makes any sense. We just watched Donald Trump tell a room full of Alabamians to get vaccinated
and then he believes in it and they booed him. Yeah. And then he said, I, your, your personal
liberties are very important. We need to protect them, but I do believe in the vaccine and I'm
sitting there going, did Donald Trump just nail it? Yeah. Did he just say the thing I've been
thinking the whole time? What is happening in the world? What is happening? I don't know what's
going on anymore. Yeah. It's, I mean, you can't make a hero out of the guy because if he had just
fucking said, get the vaccine when he got it a year ago, this whole situation, I don't know that
it would be alleviated, but it would certainly be, well, I, I don't, I don't even know that that's
the case. I think that I don't know. I don't think that's the case. I knew his, his supporters at the
time that he got it were telling me that I'm friends that supported him. Yeah. That's that
we're saying, I'm not getting that fucking thing. Yeah. It's like everybody's just everybody. This
is what happens when you make an equal playing field for everybody. When you tell everybody
that they have a platform, social media, and that they're allowed to be a critic. Yeah. Amazon,
rotten tomatoes and everything else. We've always bitched about on this show. When you give this
power to everybody, everybody suddenly is a epidemiologist and everybody is an expert and
everybody's it. So then you go, here's a president that I love. Not me. I'm just saying a person.
Here's a president I loved and supported tooth and nail to the point of certain people, not everybody,
but certain people that liked him supporting a storming of the Capitol. And now I'm not going
to follow his lead. Yeah. It's nuts. It's wild stuff. It's wild stuff. And you got Democrats
doing that with, with Biden and yeah. I mean, I think the only way out, the only way out is,
is going to be this vaccine mandate. And I think they are going to do it, but I think they're going
to do it nine months from now when it's just too fucking late. They, they don't, they're, they're,
scared of riots in the streets. They're scared of violence and they should be. These people will
not go quietly. They're already comparing it to the fucking Nazi party every chance they get,
but it's like, they're going to have to do it. So why not just do it? It's this pussy footing around
that's not helping anybody, I think, but they're not going to do it though, because the group of
people not getting vaccinated far exceeds crazy right -wing people. Well, it is a very, it is an
extremely, extremely diverse group of people. Yeah. The dams will only continue to paint it
to their advantage of saying by demonizing just the Republicans. I know plenty of people on the
left that haven't gotten it. And the whole anti -vaxxing started with like far left -wing
hippie types. That's where it all came from initially. So, and then it was adopted and,
and, and, and, and amplified by the right. Sure. And sure the typical right -wing pundits take on
this is, is what is advantageous to them is to talk it down. Why? Cause the, cause the dams are
only talking it up. So doesn't matter. It's not going away. Nobody, and we have now made a,
we've made it protocol in this country that whoever you are, whatever your causes, whatever you
represent, if you don't like something, you can storm it. Yeah. Well, destroy it. You know, those
graphs that are like the two circles and then it's where they meet in the middle and there's a
little diamond or whatever, where they meet. There is no diamond anymore. It, there always used to
be, it would be Republicans have their beliefs, Democrats have their beliefs. And here are the
we see eye to eye, but now, which unquestionably was fueled by Trump, they, there is no overlap.
They, they will not say, I agree with you on anything because they're so both sides are so
disgusted with each other. It's beyond polite disagreement. It's disgust and hate. And they,
we are saying, I don't agree with a single word you say, and I never will. And in that case,
at some point, I think we're going to have to divide the country. You know, I think,
yeah, well, I don't know what else, what the other option, absolutely good. You live in a blue state.
If you want to live in a blue seat, I live in a red state. If you want to live in a red state,
I respect everybody's personal freedoms and beliefs. Yeah. I think, I think Trump certainly
put the icing on this cake. I do not blame him for starting it by any stretch. I think you can go
way back before him. I think the, the left calling anybody that could have thought to vote for him,
uh, a racist and a moron was a horrible, horrible fucking misstep on their part. Uh, and then,
but before that, I don't think anybody who voted for him was a racist and a moron. I think people
who were supporting him three years in were racist and morons. Yes. Um, I think, and you can disagree
with that. That's fine. I think that's my, but I'm saying the left started saying that during the,
his campaign. Yeah, no, they did for sure. But, but then you could flip it and go, yeah, but that's
just a response to the way the right responded to Obama. And you could go, well, yeah, but that was
a response to the way it goes on and on and on and on. The bottom line is this, this snowball's
been a roll in a long, long time. And old Trumpy is the cherry on top to the point now where
who knows what the hell is going to happen. My point is this, you got it. It's, I said it in
my hour special years ago, Walsh, and I hate to pat myself on the back, but I have been prophetic
in my day, the hour special that you didn't come to because you had to go see Tom Petty.
No, it's actually worse. It was, it was anti -vaxxer Van Morrison, but it was,
it was a, if it was me and Heather going to the show, I would have sold my tickets in five
minutes. I was taking her father and mother to a show. I'm breaking your balls. Plan years in
advance. I know years, years. I know I'm busting your balls. But I had a thing about Arizona in
that hour where I was like, stop wasting my time with how we need to make Arizona evolve. Don't
go to Arizona anymore. If you don't like what they're doing, which a lot of us don't, don't
go there. If you can put up with what they're doing, go there. But this idea that we have to
make them think and act in a certain way, it's pointless. It has never worked in the history of
humanity ever. It doesn't fucking work. So let it go. Just let it go. Go live your life. That's it.
All right. Enough controversy. Let's talk. Do we talk about this too much?
Not at all. Let's move on to Afghanistan.
No, I mean, it's a, it's a time, man. We are living. I don't want to be living through history
anymore. I would be fine living through boredom again. It was fine by me and sorry. I do apologize
to anybody getting a little irritated with this because I know it's, you don't tune in for this
kind of talk. You tune in for the movie talk, but I will say this. I do think that anymore,
this subject matter is almost synonymous with the entertainment talk because the, every problem
we're discussing right now is reflected in entertainment. And that's kind of where it all
starts. It all starts with, we're going to cut this here. We're going to cut that there. We're
going to make this here. We're going to make this do that over there. And people go, Oh, stop being
ridiculous. And it's not going to get out of control. And that's crazy. And this and that.
And here the fuck we are. It's gotten that crazy. Yeah. In my opinion, on all sides, I know people,
other people think it's worse on one side versus the other, whatever. That's fine too. My opinion,
it has exploded down to a point where it's just nuts. It's just, everything is nuts.
I've been pitching a show for the last couple of weeks and generally just, it's something you
learn from your parents. Don't talk politics. Don't talk religion. And now I go into pitch
and the questions that follow this pitch of a show that is not super political
revolve around politics, diversity, the world, red states, blue states, et cetera. To say that
it's separate from entertainment is kind of silly, but I do get that if you come here for movie talk,
you might get annoyed and we'll move on to movies now. And you're going to get that movie talk,
bitch. Here it comes. I have three, instead of movie corner for me today, I have three news
that I want to discuss. Let's do it. And I want to, I don't want to just glaze over them. Number one,
the venom trailer for the old one. Is there a new one? Yeah. Venom let there be carnage.
The new trailer. Did you know? Okay. Uh, trailer starts.
You're pretty excited. You got Woody Harrelson in there as carnage, whereas he says carnage
uh, the effects look cool. The venom character looks really cool. Carnage is a cool character.
This is going to be cool to watch these two face off. I'm like, all right, they're jumping in with
both feet. Uh, the, the, the criticism of the first one was it took too long for him to turn
into venom. You didn't get enough of that, blah, blah, blah, blah. This one clearly, you know,
we're in the mix already. So I'm excited. I'm watching the trailer and then comes
the inevitable fucking Marvel humor. They just can't fucking help themselves to a point now
where they've got this alien symbiote or whatever it's called, who's supposed to be the most vicious,
scariest, carnivorous, human eating demon that has ever walked the earth, cracking jokes, cracking
jokes, hitting Eddie Brock, who's the host played by what's his face Capone, uh, Tom Hardy, Tom
Hardy, like jokes were like the venom demon arm comes out of his chest and like hits him in the
nose. And he's like, ow. And he's like, and then the demon's like, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I didn't
mean to do that. And then he does it again. And he's like, I'm sorry. I just like hitting you too
much. And then like being like, you're a loser. I thought it was definitely too much when he did the
got your nose bit to Tom Hardy. I was taken out of the film by that. I mean, it's just like,
it's just, it's like, you're doing like three stooges humor. Yeah. Get a hold of yourselves,
Marvel. Get a hold of yourselves. Stop with the goddamn jokes. The, for me, and you know,
my opinion is not a good one of these movies, but for me, the sweet spot is somewhere between that
Marvel three stooges shit and the solemn, we're all at a military funeral vibe of DC movies. And
very rarely do they hit that. But you can have humor without like gags. Yeah, for sure. Like one
of the, one of the gags in this is like, he meets his ex -girlfriend's new fiance. Yeah. And he's
like, he's like, nice to meet you. You seem like a nice guy. And then you hear the demon in his head
go, it is not nice to meet him. We do not like him. And then, and then Eddie Brock slaps the guy
in the face and he's like, sorry about that. And then the, and then as he walks away, the new
boyfriend goes, he needs some serious couples counseling. That's the, that's the last line
of the venom. Let there be carnage trailer. Yeah. I, uh, you know, really when I'm describing that
sweet spot, I think I'm describing suicide squad. The only one of these movies I've liked are the
suicide squad. Excuse me. Uh, how did these, the spider -man trailer look? Cause I know everybody
was shitting their jeans over that one. Uh, that looked pretty cool. Okay. I love bringing Molina
back. Always happy to see him. Yeah, that was very cool when he comes back. But again, it, this is
another classic case of Marvel just completely fucking ripping off DC. As soon as I mean, it's
unfucking believable, man. As soon as they announced Batman versus Superman, all of a sudden,
it was going to be captain America, civil war. Right. And it was going to be the Avengers fighting
the Avengers. Oh really? Where'd you get that idea? Marvel. Then they announced two years ago that
flash is going to be flash point where they were it's crisis on infinite earths. And they start on
the television show, the flash time together, all the different universes of DC and saying like,
we're bringing this in from the Christopher Reeve universe. We're bringing Keaton in from the,
from the, uh, Burton universe. We're bringing, uh, Affleck in from that universe. And we're
going to start crossing everything over in this weird time, you know, this time warp thing that's
happening. And then what happens with spider -man? Oh, you're doing the multi, you're doing the
spider verse for the next spider -man. Oh, and you're bringing all the spider -mans back. And
you're just such fucking hacks. I really, really, really do not like Marvel at all.
You suck. You suck and established and the eternals, my God. I mean, it's just like,
it just looks so boring.
It just looks so boring. And I love that in that trailer, they go, they go, well, why did you guys
fight all the other fights we've been fighting? It's like, well, we didn't have them in the
franchise plan at that point. That's why they go, we were forbidden to be called shut the fuck up.
Well, uh, the picture I'm taking out involves a member of the eternal. So I won't be speaking
on it, but I think it looks, uh, who's really cool. I mean, I don't, the trailers I see are
kind of wordless. I don't even know what it is. I got nothing against any of the actors of the
I just think the movie looks painfully fucking boring. And then, uh, they, uh, they, uh,
what's it called? Uh, and Marvel, uh, and I mean, just hitting the peak of gluttony,
the peak of gluttony is now them casting the same actor in different character roles.
When is it enough? Well, when is it enough?
When Doc Ock Malinak is, is talking to Peter Parker, I did in that world. Is it Toby
McGuire or does he know it's a different Spider -Man crossing over from the Toby McGuire
universe into this Spider -Man's universe? There are multiple realities, which is exactly what
the flash is doing, which is how Keaton and Affleck are going to be together in this one,
because they're crossing realities. Did Sam Raimi do the new one? Sam Raimi is doing the
Doctor Strange movie, the sequel. Oh, okay. Okay. So I'm excited about that. I mean,
I like those McGuire Spider -Mans, even the third one. I enjoyed it. I do too. I actually,
like I said, the Spider -Man trailer was good. I was excited to see Malina. There are heavy rumors
that Defoe is coming back as Goblin. Yeah. That they're going to bring Andrew Garfield in. Jamie,
Jamie Foxx has already confirmed as Electro. So, you know, they're crossing over with the Andrew
Garfield universe. That was far and away the worst of any of these movies was the Spider -Man
with Jamie Foxx. And I can't believe they would bring that horrible character back.
Well, I think it's, I think the idea here is, and it's a smart idea. It's let's right all the
wrongs. We can right all the wrongs here. So, you know, my point is, is I have nothing against any
of the actors in any of these. Well, some of the actors, but not for the most part, not anything
against any of the actors in any of these movies. These movies just, it's so goddamn paint by
numbers. And it, what was I saying? Oh, who from the eternals are you going out with?
Well, I don't want to say, I mean, you'll, you'll, you'll know. I make fun of any, I'm not making
fun of an actor. No, it's not a pitch that I can discuss. I probably shouldn't have even said that.
Oh, oh, well, sorry. Somebody's got meetings with Joe Lee. It sounds like,
you know, who I'm going out with Joe, but I can't say it on the air at the moment. It'll be
announced. No, I don't know who you're going out with. We haven't discussed it. You don't tell me
anything. I'm disgusted by you. You keep, no, we haven't discussed it. I said, I know I, I flipped
it. I, I did a little fun word play. Look, save something for the pitch, man. It's done. I've
it has sold. Oh, that thing you were telling me about. Yeah, Joe. Oh, okay. That's great.
Yeah. That's great. Yeah. That's pretty cool. Well, I wish you best of luck with that. And I
liked that actor quite a bit. Thank you very much. And so do I. I thought maybe you were going out
with another member. No, no, no, no, no, no. Of the eternals. I'm dating Salma Hayek. That
might be the confusion. I've been seeing Kamel Nanjiani quietly in a CD motels around the country.
I don't know if I've told this Conan story. It's a two second story, but Salma Hayek came to Conan
when I was there and she was wearing like, it might as well have been in a bikini. She comes up
and she had to sign the paper that which get everyone who appears in a talk show gets $600,
which I'm sure is laughable to these people. But I I'm handing her the clipboard to sign it. And
she like rested it on her chest. And I was like, I was literally talking to her like,
Hey, yeah. I mean, I could not pull myself together. She is extraordinary looking
and has been for 30 years. She's unbelievable looking. Yeah. You're doing the old
Yeah. Old car horn goes off.
Oh, yeah. All right. Second, second news psycho. Trailer I saw that I was very excited for and I
didn't think I cared until I saw the trailer and I was like, this movie looks fantastic. The eyes
of Tammy Faye caught that. Right. God, it's really good, man. It does. I was always fascinated with
those guys. Tammy and and, and I are just forgot the man's name you just said, which is troubling
to me. Andrew Garfield. Yeah, but also Garfield eyes. Jim Baker. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. They both look
great in it, especially Chastain. And I guess it's D 'Onofrio is Jim Falwell, right? Is that who that
was? Jesus, I didn't even catch that if that's who it was. Jerry Falwell. Yeah, Jerry Falwell. It
looks great. It really does. It's like, to me, any movie that comes out now that isn't one of these
giant robots throwing each other around is exciting to me. I like movies about people.
And I love that it's like, it looks like it's gonna show this wonderful, amazing side to Tammy
Faye that a lot of us didn't know, you know, for years, she was just the punchline to the joke of
makeup, you know, right. And this is like, they show you in the trailer, like that she has sympathy
this guy that has AIDS. And like, it's, it's very controversial in their community, because that's,
you know, that was back when they were all saying it was a sin and all that shit. So it looks like
she was fucking around. I mean, there might have been news stories at the time, but I didn't know
that. I don't think any of us knew because all the focus was on Jim Baker getting caught with
fucking Jessica Hahn, right, right in the hotel and then blubbering like a baby. Yeah. Remember
that? What a fucking idiot. Yeah, there's been a long rich history of idiots falling for idiots,
you know, just, just going like, yeah, these people are right. And it I'll never understand it. But
that's, that's the beauty of life, you know, like they were, they were huge and seen as religious
even after that. Is Paragon a word? I think it is. I'm going to look up Paragon. Paragon, I think,
I hope I used it correctly. I typed in Paragon and it brought up Yahoo Finance. That's really weird
to me. A person or thing regarded as a perfect example of a particular quality. Yes, I'm right.
A person viewed as a model of excellence. Trust yourself, Pat. Trust your vocabulary.
Uh, yeah, the movie looks great. I agree with you to go back to Spider -Man for one second. They
showed the Doc Ock Spider -Man fight and they were like, isn't it tragic that this fight from 2002
has not been bettered by superhero cinema? And I completely agree because Sam Raimi knows how to
direct the fucking action sequence. And you're watching this thing that should feel dated and
old and it seems completely fresh. You know what each party's point of view is. You know, why is
they're fighting and you know where they are in relation to each other, which is just the bare
minimum. But sometimes you don't get that in today's action movies. Right. Well, wait, I don't
understand though. What, who's saying what about what about the Doc Ock fight? What hasn't been
bettered that the fight in Spider -Man two, the, the, the Raimi one, they're just like, isn't it
sad that with all the advancements in technology, this fight hasn't been bettered by superhero
cinema? Did it look that bad or something? No, it looked great. That's what they're saying.
I think I'm being quite clear. Oh, you're saying like it's never been beat, even though they can
do so much more. Oh, okay. Okay. We never made it better. And they showed, you know, Spider -Man
flying through New York and it was like, why does this look better than current Spider -Mans? You
know, and it's, it's true. It's like, it's the same way Jurassic Park looks better than Jurassic
World. You know, it's like they've, they've, they've gone too far and fuck things up.
And let me be house. We're discussing tonight. Somebody pointed this out to me in the theater
by talking, but they, there are no, there's no wild, they did it digitally. So like the
lake behind them is still the entire time. It's, it's a CGI lake. Like that's how bad things are
getting. Everything has to be CGI. I mean, guys, it's a one location shoot. You can't just rent a
house and shoot in it. Agree more like, and then also when everybody goes home for the day,
Rebecca Hall just gets to live in a beautiful lake house instead of some fucking hotel.
Like rent an Airbnb, you know, on the lake. I just, I do not get why everything's so I just
read some big thread from Edward Zwick, who's a director. He did glory and courage under fire
in all these. He also did the sequel glory hole. He did do glory hole, which I liked by the way.
I liked it. It was a departure, but it was good. It was certainly a departure. And I think we were
all shocked that Denzel returned for it, but the, the, he did a thread on Twitter that was all about
uh, directing tips and it was circulated a lot. Cause these are really good tips. His number one
is call ahead and ask about actors and find out if they're monsters. And I was like, yep, that's
number one. But then he also had some great points. Like the one kind of disturbing thing
was he's like, I did a movie once where you see the actor on film day one and you're like, this
guy doesn't look too good. And he's a big movie star. This is a problem. And then you're like,
okay, maybe he's hung over. And then day two, it's like, Oh God, this guy doesn't look good on camera.
What are we going to do? And then somebody came in cause he's an old kind of old school director
and was like, Ed, they do it with CGI. There's stuff we don't even know about. They'll go through
and I'm not just talking about the X -Men where they're de -aging Patrick Stewart or whatever.
If an actor's got wrinkles or an actor's hung over red faced or splotchy, they CGI that that's how
these budgets get completely out of control. And it's also how we watching movies feel terrible
about ourselves because we don't look like these actors, but they don't look like themselves.
It's insane. I always wished I could see the genitals of all the biggest actors in the world,
not for perverted reasons, but that would be the great equalizer. You know, very few people
have attractive looking genitals. I just listened to Sam Jackson on Stern, a wonderful interview
of Sam Jackson on Stern and they were talking to him. Stern was like, would you ever show,
he always asks actors, do you get hard in sex scenes? It's like his number one question.
And Samuel Jackson was like, I tell them, you know, I took this from Denzel because I tell
them I'm sorry if I do and I'm sorry if I don't, which I thought was very funny. But he also said,
like, you know, Stern was like, wouldn't you show your penis? Have you ever shown your penis? Would
you show your penis on camera? And he goes, no. And he's like, honestly, the reason is it's fine.
It's not super impressive. He goes, my whole thing is I'm the guy who walks into a room and goes,
listen up motherfuckers. And if they see that I got a normal sized dick, those motherfuckers
are not going to listen to me anymore. And I was like, that's exactly it. The only big stars I've
seen do it are like Willis in color of night. And he had a good size hog. I mean, the only actors
who want to show it are the ones who got big old dicks. That is true, baby. That is true. Unless
it's a comedy dick, like in sideways, where the comedy is that it's a little dick flopping around,
you know. So my last news psycho, and then you can do your, then you can do your little movie corner.
Thanks, Joe. It's about the reviews of the new Candyman. Yeah,
excited to see it. I'm hearing a weird thumping on your end, by the way. Consistently.
I'm touching my computer. It's probably that to stop doing that, I guess I got it. Yeah, I need to
go to the website. It's like a heart. It's like I'm hearing your heartbeat. And it's
done now. Yeah. Okay. So I'm going to go to top critics reviews as of now Candyman,
just open to I'm half excited. Look, you know, I think it's a duty of ours
on this show to speak honestly about the movies we like, whether or not,
or just like whether or not people or colleagues are involved with them.
And you know, look, I'm a guy that roots for Jordan Peele. I am in the class of people thinking
Get Out was one of the greatest horror movies ever made. You know, my thoughts on a lot of
what he's done since. I don't mean for them to be spiteful, but I don't like a lot of what he's done
since. And my continued, my continued criticism has been the message is too heavy handed at the
at the expense of the enjoyment of the film. And the reviews of Candyman, for the most part,
are pretty good. Like I said, it's got an 87%. My concern is the few bad ones I've read
is that are exactly this. Sarah towel black says the kernels of complex ideas regarding race,
class and gender are too often thrown out or too often thrown out at us without consideration for
full breath and form. Adam Graham says Candyman lacks a center as well as grounding. Chris Hewitt
says, Nia da Costa, the director has lots of ideas and she seems determined to cram every single one
of them into Candyman. That was my problem with us. Yeah. A black critic. And I think that's
relevant to point out with a movie like this and with Jordan Peele's company, because it is very
race based stuff, right? He said, yeah, I was about to say the most negative reviews I've read
have been black critics. Yeah. Robert Daniels of Polygon says Candyman is so message driven that
it flattens into a generic fable. It's like, so look, am I going to see it? Absolutely. Are we
going to review it on the show? Absolutely. But my hopes are a bit dashed because this is a lot of
this is exactly what happened with us. Everybody said it was this coming and birth of this
brilliant new art artist. And if you remember, the one guy said, we have our Hitchcock about
Jordan Peele, whatever. But those few bad reviews kind of got lost in the shuffle. And the few bad
reviews were the ones I agreed with, not even having read them. So I'm seeing the word slow burn
a lot in the reviews. You know, that scares me a little bit. That said, I look forward to seeing it.
I hope it's good. But the message driven, you know, I saw another review that was like, we are
more than our tragedy. It was like one of those reviews. And I was like, oh, boy, like, right,
you know, so we'll see. Well, the hope is it wouldn't be along the lines of like an antebellum.
But yeah, it's, I think it looks really cool. Of course, I enjoy the original. I still got high
hopes, but I have been seeing the reviews get kind of more and more mixed. But fingers crossed,
I've actually never seen the Candyman sequels or any of them good.
Farewell to the flesh is passable. I never saw Day of the Dead. Yeah, I think that one was straight
to DVD, if I'm not mistaken, I might have tried to start it once. And I was like, yeah, this is like,
yeah, I actually want to purchase all of them. I think I have the I think I have the Scream Factory
version of the ridge. I do. Yeah, I believe that was one of the ones you could get recently for
it was like a hell of a deal. It was like $14 or something. But I don't own the other ones,
but I'm not against actually eventually purchasing the other ones. And I hope Tony Todd shows up in
this. I mean, there's heavy speculation that he will would be awesome. I don't know. But yeah,
I'm gonna see it as soon as possible. So doesn't get ruined for me. But for me, my movie corn is
I finished watching the White Lotus on HBO. It's also on HBO Max. I really liked this show.
Speaking of reviews, this is a show that like everyone seemed obsessed with. And now that it
has ended, the backlash has really begun. And a lot of people are criticizing it for being a show.
It's a it's entirely about white privilege. It's about these very privileged white people who go
Hawaiian Island, treat the staff like shit, don't care about the culture of the island and
are so swept up in their own problems that they don't really notice what's going on around them.
But that's the commentary, right? Like it's to me, that's called satire. And that's what it all
that's the whole point of the show. Is it a comedy? Yeah, a dark comedy. Okay, it's Mike
White, who wrote School of Rock, he did the enlightened with Laura Dern, which was a brilliant
show on HBO that ran for a couple years. He's done a lot of really good work. He worked on
freaks and geeks, all kinds of things. But it's very good. I love the show. It's stolen by my
friend, Jennifer Coolidge, who I am extremely proud of. I it's a little annoying to see her
getting all this praise for the one role that she is more serious in, because it's just another way
that critics are so biased against comedy. She's one of the most brilliant comedic performers of
time, in my opinion. And it's like she can't get praise for it until she's in a more serious role.
But she's very funny in it, too. Steve Zahn is awesome in it. Natasha Rothwell is awesome in it.
The guy who plays the hotel manager is awesome. I've never seen him before. Is this the one with
Kidman? No, that's nine perfect strangers. Oh, that's why I asked if it was okay. And basically,
all the reviews of that were Oh, boy, I bet they wish they didn't come along after the white
lotus because this ain't good. She's doing a Russian accent and that thing Nicole Kidman that
is absolutely absurd. But the white lotus I read all these reviews, the most interesting ones are
by black critics, minority critics who who think that it missed the boat and that it was almost
celebrating white privilege. And it was all written by Mike White. So that means it's all just one
middle aged white guy's opinion. The interviews with Mike White have been fascinating where he's
supposed to stop writing. Am I supposed to hate what I do just because of where society is headed?
There's a lot of really interesting stuff to dig into for a six episode comedy series. And that's
what I loved about it. I had great conversations with my wife. I've really enjoyed reading the
discourse online about it. And I've agreed with both sides and the points they make. I do think
Mike White is smarter than a lot of these people take him for and that he's criticizing these
people. I hated these people and I think you're supposed to. But his gift is portraying characters
that feel very, very real, slightly heightened. I mean, you hate them, but it all just felt very
real to me. That's why it's exactly why we're losing Bret Easton Ellis. Bret Easton Ellis's
content now is a podcast that is fully behind a paywall. And I'm sure it's a great podcast.
I might even subscribe to it. What I've heard of it, I've enjoyed. But it's why we're losing
him because he's a guy where it's like, you couldn't get a guy that's probably more
centered and open minded and was at the forefront of progressive culture when it was still quite
taboo and these things. And you can hear it, man. He's had it with the shit. It's like, oh,
because I write characters. He's never said this, but I'm assuming he would agree. Because I write
characters that don't redeem themselves in the end. It's like, fuck you.
It's like they take it as though the writer is supporting it. It's like what I said in the last
episode about Scorsese and racism. It's like, just because you don't have somebody come in and say
this is wrong does not mean the writer agrees with it. But the points are good ones. I mean,
in the premiere, there's a Hawaiian woman whose water breaks and she gives birth. She's a worker
at the hotel. And then it's like, what happened to her character? We never see her again.
There's one other Hawaiian character who's kind of central, but then he gets in trouble for stealing
and one of the other characters puts him up to it. And it's like, so they just come in and just use
him and toss him to the side. And it's like, yeah, guys, that's the point of the show.
And unfortunately, that means you're not going to have as well rounded characters for the diverse
characters because it's presenting them as not being important to these white people at all.
And that's true to life. And that was, to me, the whole point of the show.
Well, this is like, this is like when they were like, that dipshit reporter goes to Tarantino.
Why would you have, what's your face?
Harley Quinn.
Harley Quinn. Margot Robbie.
Margot Robbie. Why would you have Margot Robbie in this movie and give her so little to do?
It's like dipshit. Do you think he picks the cast and then writes the movie for them?
Yeah.
He's that fucking established that Margot Robbie was willing to do a two -line part in a Tarantino
movie. It's not the other way around, you dumb fuck. God damn it.
At its core, that movie is about late in life male friendship. That's what that movie's about.
So of course the focus is going to be on these two guys.
We're both reading the book, by the way. It's a great book.
I love the book. Yeah. It's very specifically geared towards people who like film, I think.
There's 30 page chunks where they're talking about actor's careers and it's like, well,
I love this with the average reader. I don't know.
I'm earmarking every Sith page. There's five movies on this page.
Yeah. To me, that's a kick, but it's like, that's, you know, it's not going to be for everybody.
I really recommend The White Lotus. It's six hours of your time. It's definitely a conversation
piece. There's lots of stuff in it. That's like, whoa, you know, like big water cooler type moments.
And the cast kills it, you know, and I get, I get the criticism. I get the love. I recommend it.
It's a good show. We got, what's her name in it? From D 'Addario. Yeah. The hottest
in this. She is really good in it in a way that she has never been allowed to be. She's very
good in this and her boyfriend in the show, Jake Lacey, who's an actor you've seen in a bunch of
stuff plays the greatest entitled fratty asshole I've seen in a long, long time. So they float in
the first episode. It's like a murder. She wrote, you know, that one of the people on the Island
dies, but you don't know how I, my, my recommendation is don't worry about that too much because
you just sit and enjoy the characters and their interaction. It doesn't really work as an effective
murder mystery. It's just kind of, they needed a hook to get them on the Island.
I saw a double feature at the new Beverly. I'm so glad it's open speaking of Mr. Tarantino,
but I saw a double feature of two old Steve Martin's one dead men don't wear plaid,
which when I was a kid, my favorites were Steve Martin and John Candy. No one came close except
maybe Short and Chase for a while, but dead men don't wear plaid left me cold. Then it left me
lukewarm. Now it's a cool gimmick that he's, it's a film noir parody of sorts. He did it with Carl
Reiner after the jerk and it's all in black and white and it's Steve Martin interacting with
film noir movies. So he's like, when he makes a call, an old clip of Humphrey Bogart in a,
Maltese Falcon type movie answers the phone on the other end. So that's kind of its hook.
It's gimmick is that it's Steve Martin talking to all these old greats from old Hollywood.
That works really well. It's seamless. It's shot beautifully by Michael Chapman who did raging bull,
great black and white photography. As far as like hard laughs, it doesn't quite
do it for me, especially for a Steve Martin classic, but I liked the movie.
And then the follow -up to that was Carl Reiner and Steve Martin. Again, they made three movies
together. The jerk, which is of course the best dead men don't wear plaid, which is fine. And then
the man with two brains, which I think is super funny. Kathleen Turner kind of steals the movie.
Steve Martin has some hilarious bits in it. But by the end, when they're all running around the mad
scientist lab, it's kind of like, wrap this up. It has the problem. A lot of comedies have where
you start getting bored and you've only been watching it for like an hour. Because I used to
say, why do comedies need a story? And the reason they need a story is because they got to get you
to the end. Gags can always take you there. It works with like Wet Hot. It works occasionally.
It works with MacGruber, but you do need a plot if the jokes aren't A plus level throughout.
And men with two brains doesn't really have that. I liked it. It's Sissy Spacek is the voice of a
and he wants to put her in the amazing body of Kathleen Turner,
who plays just the biggest bitch in the world. He's obsessed with her physically, but he wants
her to be nicer and be better. So he tries to do a brain transplant. It's kind of the
bride of Frankenstein story. Some big laughs, especially early on. If you've never seen them,
check them out. But they're not Steve Martin classics, in my opinion. Have you seen either
Neither. Really? Neither. Never. My mom tried to show me man with two brains when I was a kid and
I hated it. Okay. Okay. And then dead men don't wear plaid. I just never had any interest whatsoever.
Well, that title doesn't lure you in. That's for sure.
I'm not a fan of the jerk either, which I know was sacrilege to a lot of people,
but I don't find it funny. I love the jerk, but I would put it, you know,
pretty far down the list of Steve Martin's. I think he's made better movies, but I think it's
got a huge laughs in it for sure. Steve Martin to me is funniest with like,
I thought he was, I thought he, I like his standup, but to me he's funnier when he ditched the whole
I'm an idiot thing. Yeah. I like that. I like that version of Steve Martin way better. Sure.
Well, he exudes such intelligence that you don't really buy it in a weird way. Like his whole
standup was, I'm a wild, crazy idiot kind of thing. And that's not my favorite stuff of his
either. I think he is truly a comedic persona like no other. There's never been anyone quite like him
and he's, he's been great and stuff and weird and stuff. You know, sometimes he doesn't work at all,
but just a huge favorite of mine. I love the guy. All right. Well, let's get, you know, watch that
short Martin, uh, it Selena Gomez. I'm fairly interested in it. It's interesting that Selena
Gomez is in it because she was one of the more, she made her, I think her last movie was a Woody
Allen movie. And this movie to me is Manhattan murder mystery. I mean, it looks, it's almost
similar, identical. If podcasts had been around and if Woody Allen had ever heard of a podcast,
then yes, it would have been for sure. Yeah. So I was, uh, I want to check it out. I mean,
I don't know. It looks, it looks similar, but, uh, you know, it's Martin Short and Steve and Steve
Martin. Yeah. They haven't acted in anything together since three amigos. I'm down. It almost
makes me sad that Chevy's not in there with them, you know? Yeah, no, I'm excited about it. When I
saw the, I saw their standup special on Netflix, of course, but then I saw them live here at the
Greek and it's great. You know, they're, they're, they're older, they're in their seventies and you
feel that, but it's, they're still super, super funny and great together. So I'm excited to watch
and I still sort of, because it was like a side of New York that I saw before I ever lived here.
Yeah. And a side of New York that will never accept me or I will be a part of, but I still
have, uh, I romanticize that upper west side pseudo intellectual, right? My going to my analyst.
Yeah. Yeah. I mean, I just, I couldn't pay my way into one of those cocktail parties, but
it always looked like fun to me. Um, anyway, uh, our movie today
is the night house, not to be confused with any of the other house films,
house one, house two, horror movie titles. I mean, they have a real problem. There are so many of
them that are so generic that like, if you go up and even like, even when I went up to buy my
ticket for the night house, I had to check what I was seeing. It's just too generic a title. And I
texted Joe before I was like, I'm going to see spooky house. I knew it wasn't called spooky house,
but I also had no idea what it was called. I think this was originally called the lake house.
I think when I first saw the trailer, it was called the lake house and it was retitled. I think
there's a Sandy Bullock Keanu Reeves movie where they communicate and that's my mailbox.
That's what I'm thinking of. Nevermind. Then this was always called the night house. Um,
I saw the trailer. All I remembered was this. I didn't remember the trailer. I just remembered
seeing it. And then I wasn't interested because Rebecca Hall has done some indie horror flicks
that I've found very boring, uh, you know, and they've flown mostly under the radar,
but she's been in a few where I'm like, Oh cool. Rebecca Hall is a good actor. This is a horror
movie. It must be good. And then I'm just kind of bored senseless. Yeah. However, uh, you know,
we've been locked in fewer things are hitting theaters. And when a new horror movie does hit
the theater, I get excited about it. Uh, this resurfaced, I didn't quite remember seeing the
trailer. I just saw that it was getting good reviews. I was excited. I said to Pat,
we should review this. He said, what the fuck are you talking about? I've never even heard of it.
Said it's some new Rebecca Hall. Heart's supposed to be pretty good.
Uh, and then I, and I went to see it and I ended up texting Pat an apology that I made both of us
see this film. Uh, I think he liked it better than I did. It's a, I mean, you want to talk slow burns.
This is a movie about a woman whose husband, again, spoilers as always, but a woman whose
husband has died. You learn that very early in the film. You then learn that he had shot himself.
That becomes a confusing aspect because they seem to have had a very good marriage. They do the old
afterlife Ricky Gervais thing where she's watching old videos of them. And by the way, you gotta find
another way to tell that, you know, the, the videotaping that much. No. And it goes both ways.
I mean, every cop movie, it's a guy up late drinking bourbon, watching his wife on a beach
with like the wind blowing her blonde hair around. It's like, guys, you gotta find another way to
tell this story. And by the way, by the way, there they portray it in movies coming out in 2020 and
2021. Like it's a guy with a Sony shoulder cam in the eighties. This footage is like, it looks like
snuff film footage. It's great. It's like, everybody has a high definition camera in their
pocket now. Yeah. Rebecca Hall is 40. Her husband, you know, these videos would have been taken five
years ago. Give me a fuck a break. So anyway, yeah. And slowly the mystery unravels of why he
killed himself. Was he having an affair? It seems that he was, it seems that he was having affairs
with numerous women. It seems that she never really knew her husband. And then the big reveal is
she finds plans for a house. He had built their house that they live in. And she finds plans for
the exact, for an exact opposite replica of the house. So it's a complete reverse version.
And lo and behold, at nighttime, this house illuminates somehow across the lake, even though
nobody has ever seen it. Nobody knows it's there. She goes looking for the house. She does find it.
There is a structure in the woods. It's completely dilapidated and unfinished. Yet somehow it's
lighting up at night. They don't really quite explain that. There's a, there's the old mysterious
black neighbor trope played by Vondie Curtis Hall, who I always fucking love. He's a great actor and
great in this. But it's like, you know, is he involved? She goes out looking for the house and
she runs into him in the woods and he's acting very strange and mysterious and you don't know why.
Yeah, go on, Joe. Sorry. No, it's fine. She, you know, and then I guess the reveal is, is that
eventually you realize he's been, he's probably murdered some women in this house, but you don't
know why. And it's more, you get the feeling that it's more so than he's just a bad guy.
Yeah. And Vondie's like, he told me he had urges, strange urges. And I'm like, I gotta tell you,
if I'm murdering multiple women in an abandoned night house, I'm probably not telling my neighbor
that I have dark urges. You know, there's so many things like that in this movie where I'm like,
it feels like a screenwriting exercise as opposed to a living breathing thing.
And that's the thing. There's too many cryptic clues throughout this thing that when it's finally
revealed what the husband was up to, none of them make sense. For instance, his suicide note.
That's what I was about to say. Yeah, I got it right here. There is nothing,
nothing is after you. You're safe now. Right. That's a, that's a completely bizarre suicide
note. That is clearly just a clue for the person watching the movie. It's not a suicide note.
Anyone would write. And if he's going to write something to his wife before killing himself,
why wouldn't he make it clearer to her? So she knows what's going on.
Well, that's the point. And so she interprets it as she told her husband that she had, she had,
she had, she was in a car crash where she died for five minutes and was rejuvenated.
And she tells her husband, she said, my husband is the only person I ever told when I died,
I saw him absolutely nothing. There was nothing. And so she goes, this is what his note means.
There is nothing. Nothing is after you, whatever. He's telling me there's nothing after we die.
Then you find out that what it is, is, is there is a ghost who's a shadow called the nothing,
which I read online, like in the never ending story. Yeah. Yeah. Like you,
would not say, especially to your fucking wife, nothing is after you. And, and what you actually
mean is that there's a being called the nothing that is trying to get you. That's absurd. Yeah.
It's absurd. Yeah. So you, so, and this thing's after her for, for what reason? Because she didn't
die all the way. And it's like, what, who cares? And then also how many people almost die and don't,
he's just fixated on this one woman. Like he wants her soul. And, and does he do this with
everyone who almost dies or he's just fixated on her and why would he be? She seems like a perfectly
nice, normal woman. It makes, you know what? She does seem like a nice, normal woman until about
halfway through the movie. And you're like, you know, you know, Bex, whatever, I forget her
character's name, but it's like, you get about a two week pass on that pissy mood grief thing. Like
she really is just being an asshole to everybody. Well, my favorite aspect of it is they don't make
her the sad morning victim. She's kind of a bitch. And I've talked about with Joe, my favorite scene
of the movie is right after her husband kills herself. She's back at school. She's a school
teacher and this mom comes in wanting a different grade for her child. And she's like, what do you
want to be? What do you want to fucking a, my husband just blew his head off. She's great in
like a tough cook. Yeah. So to the point where you're starting to go, I get why the guy blew
his brains out. Yeah. I certainly get why he cheated. Definitely. Yeah. So, so that,
but I think that's a red herring. That's that's that they did that for the reason. So I'm being
funny, but that's actually one of the elements, one good storytelling elements in it. But,
but my biggest gripe with this thing is, you know, it's like you had to, why is the ghost?
So you find out the husband went out, got all these occult books. He learned in the occult books
that if you build the reverse of your home, a ghost can't find you because it gets confused.
Already you're like, for Christ sakes, what are we talking about here? This thing can travel
through dimensions and time. It's about it. It's able to find you on planet earth,
but you're going to confuse it with a copycat house. I mean, it's so crazy. So why don't you
do the Looney Tunes thing of, of, of put up a house and then when he runs towards it, it's
actually a screen picture of a house. So then he knocks himself out and you can kill him. It's
that stupid. Which by the way, I've seen that new Jack Gastrella eight times that thing of the guy
bike into the fake. It's like, it's, I can't wait. It's just unbelievable. Anyway.
So then you find out he's not having an affair. He's like seducing these women and luring them
to this house and murdering them because women who kind of look like his wife so that he can
fool, fool the ghost, the nothing. Of course. Here's what I was imagining is pitching this movie.
Yeah. How does the person hearing this pitch not go, all right, wait a fucking minute.
You know, it, there's too much like that in this movie. And, uh, of course he doesn't fool the
ghost. Yeah. And then by the way, after he kills himself, the ghost just starts haunting her. And
you're like, why didn't you just do that to begin with? Yeah. Yeah. This is nuts. This,
this makes sense. No. Uh, I not only hated this film from a logical standpoint,
it was one of the most boring movies I have seen in years. There is not a happy moment.
There is not a speck of joy. I'm not asking for jokes or anything. I'm just saying for Christ's
sake. It's, it's, it's Ricky Gervais's TV show without any of the comedy parts.
It's a woman walking around in her house, depressed with no dialogue, watching videos
of her dead husband and then turning the same dirge like song keeps coming on the radio. Like
the good, the husband turns it on or the ghost turns it on. And you keep hearing the same song
over and over and then, and then just, I guess the husband, I guess the ghost is after the husband
to lure the husband into killing himself because that'll lure her in more easily. Cause at the end,
she almost kills herself when the ghost is trying to convince her to, but it's just a long way around
the bend. It's pointless. It's just fucking pointless, especially when she says halfway
through the film that she had mental problems or she's had mental issues through her life.
And it's like, again, then why wouldn't the ghost just prey on you and exploit those issues to try
to lure you in? I just don't, I don't know. Maybe he needed the husband out of the way first.
I, you know, I guess that makes sense because he was her rock or whatever, but
well, I'm going to, I'm going to surprise you here, but I liked the movie for an hour and 15
minutes. I was enjoying it because I trusted the filmmakers. I was just like, they're building to
a great reveal and these moments that might not be clicking for me right now will make sense later.
And there's really nothing more frustrating than when you put that kind of trust in a filmmaker
and then they get to the end and you're like, what the fuck? But I'm not a guy who, when the
sucks, I write off the whole movie. I think it was pretty damn effective as a thriller.
I loved how they did the jump scares, which is generally it's like, Oh, it was just a cat. Oh,
and then everybody calms down. And then the thing jumps out behind them. That's the jump scare. I
hate that's how they train audiences to like, and when Heather jumps and stuff like that in movies,
I'm like, you didn't know that was coming, but she doesn't, she doesn't like horror movies.
Uh, for me, this one had a much more effective way of the jump scares are just like,
bam, the, the sound design was great. You know, they hit you out of nowhere. That moment were all
the women in the bathing suits, which I still don't really know what that was when they were
all jumping and running past her. Do you remember that? That was, yeah, that was like, she was seeing
the ghosts of all the women he killed, I guess. And it was supposed to be like, this is how they
ran when he tried to kill them. Cause he did, I mean, I guess down to their panties were going to
and then he would kill them. But it's like, how is this ghost making you see all this?
You know what I mean? I don't know, but that 32nd, it was a 32nd nonstop jump scare essentially.
And to me that was extremely effective. I was like, this is fucked up. I don't know where this is
going, but you can only sit in that feeling of, Ooh, where is this going for so long until you
got to start paying it off. And that is where the movie falls completely to shit. I walked out,
that women running thing was way earlier on than you're remembering, man. Cause a long
while after that, I looked at my watch and I was like, Holy shit, there's another 45 minutes of
this. Oh no, I'm not saying it's at the end. I'm saying it was a super effective moment. And I
thought that there were several of them that scared me. Like when you first hear his voice
in the house as the ghost, I mean, look, that's not exactly fresh to hear a ghost like you don't.
They do it in the funniest scene of Talladega nights with a John C. Reilly, but it's to me
was super effective as a horror movie. These guys have talent, but as the thriller and the plot
elements of it, it doesn't work at all. And when you really look back at it, I immediately walked
out, everybody that was in this movie walked out and got on their phones and was looking at
Wikipedia. There were people in the lobby discussing what happened to with strangers like, well then why
did she do this? And that's just not good. It got a really bad, sorry. Wow. Really wobbling. It got
a really bad cinema score review, which is when they pull audiences after. And it's, it's because
the ending is the most important part to your average audience. Like in the 89 % on rotten tomatoes
and then like a, like a C minus on cinema score. And it's just because it doesn't play by the rules.
When it ends, you're left with more questions than answers, but not really in a good way.
What I will say is great about it is Rebecca Hall, who is excellent. I think in the movie,
Sarah Goldberg from Barry plays her friend. She's great in the movie. Bondi Curtis Hall, as I said,
the mistress I thought was really good in it. Well acted. It's, it's the guys who did super dark
times, which we reviewed on this show and which I love that. Did they, did they just, I loved super
dark times. Did they just write? They only wrote this. They did not direct this. Did they direct
super dark times? No, they wrote it in this guy, David Bruckner. Let me make sure because I'm
often wrong. Oh, he didn't direct super dark times. So let me check. Oftentimes we just go,
yeah, yeah, yeah, this happens. We don't really know, but that David Bruckner is directing the
new hellraiser and it's being written by these guys who did the night house, which is a little
troubling, but super dark times was directed by this guy, Kevin Phillips. I don't know who that is,
but they wrote super dark. They are writing the new hellraiser and the director is also directing
the new hellraiser. Well, what's funny is this played tonally and pace wise and twist wise,
exactly like hellraiser hellseeker and hellraiser infernal, which were the two direct to video
follow ups to the first four that were direct theatrical group released. And yeah, it's just
a slow burn who gives a shit of a mystery. Like you just don't fucking care. I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm
over the, my husband, I never knew my husband thriller. You know, I've trashed what lies beneath
on the show before. I'll trash it again. Like I just don't find it. I love that movie. I know.
I don't find it to be interesting. This is up there with the cop with a dirty secret
thriller. Like I just don't fucking care, man. It's right. So anyway, my hog is way down on the
night house. The more I think about it, the limper it gets. And, uh, you know, my hog, I would,
I would honestly put it in exactly the same position as with don't breathe to it. It's out
front of me. I would recommend it to somebody who liked horror, but I would also say, you know,
just don't be expecting it all to fall together into a nice bow at the end. And I, I understand
people who, if the ending doesn't work, the movie doesn't work. I get that. But for me,
I try to look at the big picture and for at least an hour of this thing, I was pretty riveted to it.
I thought it was well done and certainly well acted. Um, it's got, I'm pumped about the new
because I feel like these guys are circling something great and not quite hitting it,
but I don't know, man. I felt like every scare in this was,
aside from that one with the women, every scare in this was a jump scare that was based entirely on
volume. It was just blaring volume at you after a long stretch of silence. And it's like, of course
that's going to startle me, man. Like it's not scary. I'm not at all scared by the music
turning on, but it wasn't going by the jump scare formula of, Oh, it was a fake out, whatever. And
that's what, that's why they were more effective to me. I agree with that. But here's the thing,
have jump scares. Fine. Yeah. But you gotta have some real scares too. You gotta have some movie,
you gotta have some spooky, whatever. And they, this had none of that in my opinion.
And I, and I thought it did. Although at the end, especially when they're in, when, when the,
nothing is dragging her around the house and then she's watching her husband kill these women in a
parallel universe or something. I mean, I, I truly had no idea what was happening at the end.
When she went to the house that was like half built in the woods, why, why did she,
why was she able to see, why did it look finished? My point is if this demon can do all these things,
why is this such an elaborate scheme? You could do whatever you want. You could make her walk out
into traffic. It's stupid. Yeah. No, it's, it's for sure. It's like it, it's when these guys were
mapping this movie out, they were strictly focused on the screenwriting element of it, the twists and
turns and not being concerned about how it would play to an audience. That's, that's just what it
is. And that's why I think audiences aren't responding to it at all. They're that suicide
note is anytime something like that, like a clue in a movie is written or designed in such a way
that it only makes sense to make your story make sense. You haven't done your job.
You know, it's very much like when the, the guys got one final piece,
honestly, the best example of it is, is Rollo Tomasi and LA confidential. You buy it because
it plays out so beautifully. But if you think about it for a minute, you're like, would Kevin
Spacey have known to say Rollo Tomasi there? And, and so he, I don't know if you remember that
specific, but sometimes that works. If everything else around it is great, you can get away with
one thing. Everything around this is not great for sure. Yeah. All right. We'll be back next month
with Candyman for sure. And wait, no, no, no, no, mid month. These are for the first of September,
right? Oh yeah. We'll be back mid month with Candyman, the new one. And well, there'll also,
of course, be some discussion about the old Candyman. If you want to refresh yourself
and Jacob's wife, right? Yes. We will be doing Jacob's wife, which is new to shutter starring
Barbara Crampton and the great Larry Fezenden. Yes. How the hell you say power couple. I just
saw today, although Emily had told me about it a few weeks back, that there is a zoom
horror movie group offshoot of our Facebook page where see you and how fans are getting together
to talk, to sort of feel better about the world, to have friends, to, you know, to bounce things
off each other and have a good time. And I, I love that. I think we have, you know, everyone says
we've got the best fans, but I love that you guys are all connecting and getting along with
each other and finding some outlet for these kind of very isolating times. Love that. Love you guys.
That is awesome. Thank you for supporting us via Patreon. Thank you, Emily, for keeping the
online world alive for us as we increasingly want to be detached from it. And I'm Instagram,
Twitter, the Patrick Walsh Jotaro's a comedy on Instagram, Twitter,
Joey Rose is coming very soon. Brick and mortar September, hopefully
on Rivington street, New York city. I will keep you posted. We'll see you next time.
And we'll see you and how