I share it.
Welcome, too.
We'll see you in house.
My name is Joe to Rosa.
My name is Patrick Walsh, and we are here, folks, to talk about the remake of Stephen King's
Firestarter. Now, twisted Firestarter. We've discussed this before. Is this a remake or is it a
new adaptation of the book that nobody knew Stephen King wrote? I've never seen a copy of Firestarter's
tour. I've never seen it on anybody's bookshelf. I have a copy of Firestarter. I bought a paper,
I bought a lot. I used to have these on eBay. A lot of books, but it was a term. And I bought the
whole lot every Stephen King book up to that time in completely abused paperback form. And I got
it for like ten bucks. So I have Firestarter. They still do that. I still buy lots all the time.
And I just got scammed out of a lot. I bought a lot of used NES games. Okay. And the guy
scammed me. He was like, he's one of these guys that post the thing repeatedly and steals your
money. I think it was on Craigslist. I reported it to Craigslist. Of course, he heard nothing back.
You never will. Expecting an email that says as far as we can tell, he did not violate any Craigslist
guidelines by stealing from you. For sure. But the way I went to this ice cube concert ice cube
snow e 42 short. Warren G opening. Great night. But I've seen short and cube separately. And they both
put on a good show. I can't speak to e 40 or who's the other guy? Two short. No, no, two short.
So I've seen ice cube. I've seen e 40. Oh, it's new. Of course. Yeah. Okay. Well, they're called mount
Eastmore or Westmore. And they have one song. It's nuts. They're touring as Mount Westmore. They've
released one song. They play it twice in their set. But they have no other material. But it was a
great show. Anyway, I bought, I'm talking about getting ripped off here. I bought tickets.
It's six people at work said they wanted to go. I said, okay, but they're very expensive tickets.
Is everybody for sure going to go by the end of the day? Three of the six had fallen out.
I was I was in $1 ,300 for the tickets. So I couldn't go to the pre hang. I had to immediately rush
down to the venue and try to sell the tickets. Wait, they didn't give you the money. That's
bullshit. Correct. StubHub and ticket master did not allow resells of this of these tickets
because they don't for rap concerts a lot of the times. I don't know why that is, but it seems
kind of fucked up. Couldn't resell them online. I went down after fighting off the scalpers as I
have done every time I tried to sell tickets. Like, finally, I went get the fuck away from me.
These tickets were $2 .25 a piece. I am not selling them to you for $20. Get the fuck away from
me. I yelled in this guy's face because he had approached me 15 times and he was aggressive.
This is always the case with these scalpers. So and if they want them that bad, you know you're
sitting on a good pair. I had floor seats. So I'm waiting around with a little sign trying to
sell them. Police asked me three times to leave while the scalpers run around ripping people off
all around me. I don't know if they have a pay -old deal or what, but they had a big problem with me
selling them. Finally, one of the scalpers comes up and he's like, hey man, you're right. We were
countering the rip -off. Would you take him for this amount? It was a fair amount. I had to get in to
see the show. I sold the tickets. I then went into a gas station. I was going to buy something and
was informed that the 50s and 100s that I was given were all fake.
He goes, they're really good. He holds them up to the light and shows me that the sun shines through
them and you see the reflection and everything. They're really good fakes, but these are fakes.
I lost about $600. It sucks. I talked to one person at work and he's like, oh, that's all over the
news here. I'll go, what's all over the news? Oh, they're passing fake bills everywhere. Be on
the lookout. All right, great. The one I'm going to carry around a jeweler's loop and start inspecting
each dollar bill I use. It's, by the way, it's yet another telling sign of how fucked we all are.
It's how hustling has evolved. Very similar to that. That's a bit of a long con.
Yeah. They reel you in with a confidence game. The guy that got me on the games, he didn't do any,
because I've been buying games and collecting now long enough. It's not very long, but long enough
that I understand now a lot more than I ever did how to spot fakes and scams and all this stuff.
This guy didn't do any of that shit. He had original pictures of the games. He was in correspondence.
He was answering questions. He was not pressuring me. It was incredible to the point that a
week after he had scam me and I realized he's got me, I still was holding out a little hope of like,
maybe he didn't, maybe these games are going to show up. You sent him money and then we're waiting
for that for the games to show. I paid him on PayPal. Okay. Again, yet another like it's fine. It's
PayPal. Cash app is the one that you always had to look out for. And then I found out that because
I paid him on friends and through friends and family that feature on PayPal. It wasn't protected.
I didn't know that. But my point is is like, this guy, I mean, dude, he emailed me at one point.
He goes, so sorry, it took me two days to respond. I had a family emergency, but everything's okay now.
Like, I'm here. What do you need to know? Yeah. I'm shipping you this tomorrow. Thank you for your
patience. Like, dude, it was crazy. How real he made this feel? You've been writing him since
like him and where the fuck are the games? He just doesn't answer. I sent him once and said,
where and I said him one email that finally said, dude, I think you're scamming me. I hope it's not
the case. He didn't respond to that. I then wrote to him, hey, dude, just seeing if there's an update
on the games haven't received him yet, didn't respond to that emailed him from a different address
when the post went back up and said I'm very interested in this. He didn't respond to that. I think
somehow he knew it was me. And then I just reported him to Craig's list and they haven't responded.
So at this point, think that Craig's list is the one that put the post up themselves.
Let's try to keep the lights on a little bit at Craig's list HQ. I can't imagine they didn't take
a huge hit when they banned all sex activity, which is why everyone got on Craig's list in the first
place. And I got news for you people. It's more than just Craig over there. I know you think it's
a little mom and pop, but it's not. It's not. I hate to burst your bubble. And what's the other one?
Angie's list. Angie's list. I don't know what she thought she was doing, calling it the exact same
thing. Apparently, Angie's list is more for like house help. Like I need a plumber. Okay. I had the
the goal of people. So when I'm out here in Atlanta, I book Airbnb's and I go home for a week
in a couple weeks. And then I'm back out for the last five weeks. So I booked this house.
And it's two seconds from work should be perfect. Lady emails me. It's not that there's anything wrong
with us to quote side felt, but like it's these two middle aged women who are like holding each other
in the picture. And they keep describing themselves as friends. And it's like, are you friends?
Are you lesbians and you don't want to put that in this day and age? It's just a very odd thing.
But they write me, hey, we just want to make sure you've read all the rules of the house before we'll
approve your request. Like approve my request. I'm giving you money for your house. That's
what Airbnb is. It's just it's helped destroy the housing market. That's what it is. I go, yeah,
sure. I read it. I understand it. And she's like, then there's not going to be any and then goes
through each of the rules. I'm like, yeah, yeah, lady, that's right. Well, we just find it unusual that
you're a single man wanting to buy a house or wanting to rent a house.
I eventually deleted this part from the email, but it started with what the fuck is the
matter with you kind of vibe? Like I can book whatever Airbnb I want. And I just explain, look,
they give me a stipend for work. I can get a one bedroom in the city or I can get a nice three bedroom
house, five minutes from work. They both have pros and cons, but I'm kind of bored with Atlanta.
So I'm fine. Just staying in a nice house. I write this to her, send it back.
This morning, I get an email from them. By the way, I've never had contact with anybody before
moving into an Airbnb other than, hey, here's the gate code or something. She writes this morning,
we'd love to hop on a welcome call this week. Good. And look, I'm moving into this place in three
weeks. It's irritating. It's irritating. But this is what we're forced to do at this point. We're forced
to prove at every turn that it's legitimate. Yeah, it's wild. It's a hard,
God, hop on a welcome call three weeks out of going over there. I got to talk to these people.
It's over people. I want to be like, look, I'll be very honest with you about what I want out of your
house. If you two will be honest with me that you're in love with each other. And will you also tell
your family because you can't keep living alive. We're both trying to live lives here. And it's not
right. It's just, we live in just a terrible, terrible world. It's just horrible. I can't disagree.
All right. Well, I got a, I got a new psycho. Yeah.
Trailer for Mission Impossible 7. No, it looks awesome. I think it's eight. Yeah. And they're doing
a two -part finale, which is the sort of, you know, trend these days. Right. These last two movies
are art, you know, two -parter. What's it called? Like death?
Continual or something. I don't know. I don't know either. I watched some bootleg trailer.
Everybody looked awesome. Anyway, I just watched Reckoning Part 1. Death Reckoning?
Dead Reckoning. Dead Reckoning. Yeah. So I just watched it in between episodes here.
They officially released the teaser today. Oh, I'm 100 % in. It's, you know, all I needed to see was
Tom Cruise driving around in a car that had, was missing all the doors for some reason. Yeah.
And running happens earlier. Yeah. He's running. I mean, see him running. It's always good.
They curiously seemed to have buried bald women in this trailer. Not as prominent as he was in the
life. Well, he's the first voice you hear. They didn't bury in that voice. I'll say that. No, no, no. I
thought it was him. It's not. It's another guy. Oh, you're right. It's that Henry Sernigai from the
first one. Yeah. So, um, but at least you see Simon Peg running.
Vin Rames standing completely still. Not surprisingly.
Vin Rames is always just like typing into a computer. He's, you don't see him running around.
Um, but hey, it's, you know, it's got all the elements you want in a mission and possible movie.
It's, of course, it's got clips of some big dance party with a bunch of colored lights. Like,
you know, that's always a sequence in these things. Yeah. The end stunt with the motorcycle,
which I think is real. I think they really did that. Well, Cruise does all the stunts pretty much.
I don't think he drove a motorcycle off a cliff, but I'm sure he did something. It looks awesome.
And I think they'll be, they'll be pieces about it when it, when it comes to an end, but we got a
tip or hat to that franchise. Really? They, they beat James Bond at their own game. They made James Bond
look old -fashioned came along. The diploma won the original. I remember having a blast when I saw it.
It's got at least one iconic scene of him with him dropping from the ceiling. It's parody to
million times. And I love the Palmer. So I love that one. But then the switching up the director
thing worked great for a while. I love the John Wu one, even though it's the worst by far.
I love the one with Philip Seymour Hoffman. He's the best villain they ever had.
And that's Abrams, no? Abrams, right? Yeah. But then they just settled on Christopher McCory,
known for being the writer of the usual suspects, but not known for being an exceptional director,
really. And he has made all -time action classic after all -time action classic. Some of the best stunts
I've ever seen in action movies. The other, the only other thing competing at that level is the fast
and the furious movies. And there's so much worse. There's so much dumber and worse written and the
stunts aren't as cool. They do better, I think, probably the mission impossible. That's probably because
they're more diverse to be honest with you. There's just a huge diverse cast that appeals to every
nationality of people, whereas mission impossible remains pretty white because it started in 1996,
or the 50s, if you want to go back to the TV show. So whenever that show was on 70.
Six months. Man, the quality control of this franchise is just off the charts.
It's a formula and yet they feel different enough each time.
And just they always hit you with five set pieces that are the coolest stunts you've seen.
You know, they're really awesome. What the hell is it just going to say?
Oh, they keep getting juice from the lemon, man. You know, with, unfortunately, with John Wick.
You know, I want to see the next one, but a third of the way to that third movie, I was like,
I think they're out of Wick. There's much left to do here.
Yeah, it's that thing where you're trying to light the candle, but you're actually just
putting the flame directly to the wax trying to get it to light because the wig is gone.
Yeah, so, but I'm excited to see, but again, man, next year it says, why is like, I don't understand why
this Indiana Jones, the flat, I guess they're trying to just really weight out COVID,
where they're like, we're making sure we get blockbusters back to being blockbusters.
And that's yeah, like, well, I think they're waiting for the ones that they know are great.
And I think the ones that got dumped on us during COVID, your Wonder Woman 84s, you know,
shit like that, they knew they had just a piece of shit on their hands.
I think is what happened and they were like, let's just dump them and pretend it's because of COVID,
because like this top gun that is getting just non -stop amazing reviews that comes out this week,
everybody's like, there was never even a discussion about taking a streaming.
We knew we had like an action classic and these are IMAX level flight scenes. We wanted to showcase them.
So I get it. I think now they feel like people are pretty much open at least to going back to
the theaters. And I know I am. I mean, I don't care anymore. I welcome it. Welcome to COVID.
Yeah, I'm excited for that sort of to take place. And it's a big week. Top Gun 2 comes up this week.
Friday, the premiere of Obi -Wan, I mean, I just am beside myself with excitement.
Okay, okay. Who's doing it for us?
I guess he and Philoni are producers on it. I don't know who wrote them, but
Philoni and Joe. Philoni and Rico.
I don't know who you meant. Philon. He's the guy that is basically like way up the ladder at Star Wars.
Dave. Anyway, you and McGregor has said that it basically plays like one long movie, which is awesome.
That's what I wanted. You know, Hayden, Christensen, back as Vader. They said there's a lot of fun,
surprise Easter eggs. And I think it's just going to be something that we've been all wanting
as Star Wars fans. So I'm very excited. So that comes out Friday. Yeah, big week, big week.
Yeah, I mean, hopefully we're getting back to a place where there's something good to see
every week. It has not been that way for a very long time. And then, you know, I think they're shooting
themselves in the foot by, for example, Northman being available to rent for 20 bucks right now. It's
like you're killing your own business. This movie came out a month ago. And they're talking about this
40 -day window or whatever. A 40 -day window is nothing. So if everybody knows that they can watch
movies at their house, they're not going to go to theaters. So as that window gets shorter, I mean,
this used to be Supreme Court level shit. Remember, like they would say there had to be a window
before something hit video where everybody had to make sure they got enough profits. And you know,
now it's just like Johnson sued Disney. Yeah, it's I'm talking, you know, back when we were kids even.
It was like, if, you know, Jurassic Park came out on VHS, I remember probably a year and a half,
two years after the move. I don't know. It's a strange thing they're doing because it seems like
every move they make to save the theatrical experience is actually hindering it even further,
in my opinion. But what a line up. Did you read this week that Tom Cruise claims that he wears a
disguise and he goes to see every single movie that is theatrically released every year?
I know that he does go to see a lot of, I don't doubt it. I mean, he, you know,
it can't be everyone released, but I believe he goes a lot. That's pretty cool. I'd love to see what
the disguise looks like. I'll tell you that much. I mean, yeah, he's pretty, you know,
especially first. Well, that's the thing too, especially for a guy that's so recognizable in
sunglasses. Like every Tom Cruise impression is sunglasses. Is that strange? Yeah. So I don't know
what the fuck he wears, but, you know, who knows? But I'll be looking for him now. I have a friend who
saw him once at that century city mall theater. So I'll be on a look out from here on out. The Vista,
the best theater in my neighborhood and your old neighborhood, Joe, after promises that Tarantino
had bought it, and it would be reopening by Christmas as a mix of Repertory House and new theater,
new theater place. Someone sent me a picture of it the other day. It looks like a shelter. It's just
going to re - something it. I mean, if it was supposed to open at this point, almost six months ago,
and it looks like this, I don't have a great feeling about it, but who knows?
I went, I saw three movies at the theater yesterday, which is something I used to do, and then my
attention span has been so shot that I have not been able to, but I forced myself. I was just like,
get out of the house, watch some movies, have some fun, and I didn't really. I love the Northman,
and then Joe, do you think we will do men on the show? I wouldn't rule it out. So let's say I would
love to hear what you have to say about men, and boy, do I have a lot to say? I mean, look, I live
anymore to shit on the products of 824 and Blumhouse, which is why I'm so excited about today's episode.
But I wouldn't rule it out. This one operates on a different level because it will also upset you
on a personal and political level, and it is so stupid, but thinks it's so smart, which is always a
good target. But I'll leave it. We can talk about it on the show. You know it's bad when you go and
run tomatoes, and you see rotten reviews from top female critics at like, you know, places like
huff -pulled stuff, when they're like, it's brainless, it thinks it's saying something, it's not.
When something like this is like trying to fight for the cause and many of them, even the female
critics that are particularly down for the cause are like, this movie sucks. You're like, oh boy,
this must be real bad. Well, Alex Garland did X -Mahina, which was just like a little classic,
like a modern day twilight zone, a perfect little jewel of a movie, with a lot to say, but also
really entertaining and fun, and everything you want out of a movie. An annihilation, that's when
the man started disappearing up his own ass. I know a lot of people think that's a masterpiece.
I need to watch it again. I think it is a interesting movie with some terrifying and great stuff in
it, but on the whole, kind of a mess. This thing's an absolute disaster. You won't believe your
eyes, I think, with this one. So we'll hang on to that, and I'll get on to the third movie I saw
at a sneak preview. I believe this movie comes out in two weeks. So is this movie corner? Are we in
this? The movie is called Bob's Burgers the Movie. And I'll briefly give you my experience with
Bob's Burgers. When I got Hulu, when I first got Hulu, I was like, I've never seen this show. I hear
it's the next sentence. It's hilarious. I have friends who really love it, and I have friends who do
voices on it. And I thought, great, I watched maybe 10 over the course of a couple weeks. I definitely
understood why people like it. There was one episode in particular. I thought it was absolutely
hilarious, but it was something that eventually I trailed off on. I've had this experience with shows
we all have. You're just like, I don't need to watch six seasons of this. I kind of get it.
But I was excited to see the movie because honestly, I'll take any excuse to see a theatrically
released comedy, which does not really happen anymore. I was excited to be laughing in a theater again.
And it was a sneak preview. And I know the show has such obsessed, culty fans that I knew it was
going to be a real responsive crowd. And folks, for an hour and 40 minutes, me and everyone else in
the theater sat completely silent. Sold out show of people wearing Bob's Burgers shirts.
It reminded me of when I was a kid and I saw the Beach Boys open for Chicago. And Chicago said,
here's something off our new album. And this thing started with an eight minute flute solo. Eight minutes
of just the flute while everybody was backstage, you know, icing their their arthritic joints probably.
And I sat there in the lawn at Riverport Amphitheater in St. Louis as a mob, a swarm of
people in Chicago t -shirts left in droves because of how bad this was. And I'm not saying Bob's Burgers
is bad is that flute solo. What I am saying is the Simpsons. I mean, Joe, I don't know, Joe always has
weird opinions about the Simpsons. It's clearly not an important show to Joe. I recognize it's legacy.
I'm just not a big cart. I've never been a big adult comedy cartoons guy. I just just
doesn't do it for me. Meaning, however, the first I'm going to go, I'm excited to 12 seasons of
the Simpsons are some of the greatest comedy. There is easily one of the most important comedic things
ever in my life, change my whole world, change my perception of things, etc. As it did for a lot of
comedy, people, comedy writers, etc. And by the time the movie came along, I was like, all right,
I hadn't watched the show in a decade at that point. But when I went to the movie, I was like,
look, they brought back a lot of the great writers. There's a lot of great stuff in here. A lot of great
jokes. I was happy I saw it, even though it wasn't the greatest Simpsons movie it could have been,
maybe. The Bob's Burgers fans, you know, I'd be really shocked. No, I wouldn't be shocked because
that's what's going to happen. They're going to see it and they're going to say it's amazing and it's
hilarious and it isn't. It's not funny. There are no real good jokes in it. The story doesn't
really exist and they try to make it a musical like the South Park movie, but the songs are not even
remotely catchy. I couldn't remember them the second they ended. It's really bizarre in that way.
It's like they didn't put the time and energy into making a good story. The story is not
existent. The jokes that I saw were worse than the jokes I saw on the television show that you
can get for free and they don't do anything special with it outside of the musical numbers, which the
show already does, and these musical numbers, there's about five of them are complete fucking
duds. So I'm very curious to see how this movie is received, especially by the fans of the show,
but I think if you're being honest with yourself, this is not a good boofy. I think I'm probably
bumming out a lot of people saying that because people do get obsessive about this, but
there wasn't even anything interesting on a character level. You know what I mean? The dad
on Bob's burgers, whoever his name is, never gets a hero moment and the mom never gets a hero moment.
They don't do anything well. Remind of me of the Mitchell's versus the machines, which is the last
adult cartoon I watched. And I thought that an amazing job of giving everybody a special moment.
It did a lot of things really, really well. And boy, I just thought it sucked. I don't know. I don't
know what to say. It was depressing to me. I think you said it. I do know what to say. I just
talked for five minutes about it. It just, I don't know. You know, I try to get so excited about things
now. And I'm always let down. And I think you do know because you hated it. You think it was
shit, but you got friends in the cast and you got to watch how you say it. I get it. I've been there,
baby. I got friends in the movie. I don't want to see it. Yeah, I don't care. I watched,
well, definitely, I'm sorry, interrupt. Doesn't it seem that we're just, you know, whether,
I don't know what you want to call it, simulation, whatever, but doesn't it seem that everyone is just
blindly loving things? Yeah. But, but you talk to everyone in your life and everyone hates it.
But they live in a world where we're entire world seems to love it or they don't love it. We live
in a world that's ruled, we're ruled by algorithms now. And everybody says what they need to say to stay
consistent in the algorithm. So you either say you hate things to stay in it or you say you love
things to stay in it. And it's all about key words. Yeah. In the description and things that will
get you traction on social media, it's why I didn't post the stupid trick thing when you were like,
that'll go viral. I'm like, yeah, maybe I don't care though. Like I don't give a shit. What's it
going to do? Make me money. I don't give a fuck of 8 ,000 people or 10 ,000 people think my
trick thing is funny. You know, so I got I got to tweet it like 10 ,000 likes in 24 hours. And it
has gotten me two followers. Yeah, it's not it means nothing. Nothing means nothing.
All right, go ahead. Speaking of movies that are funny. Oh, I rewatched
I broke out the old WC field set and watched almost all of them. But I'll highlight too. The
bank dick classic. I believe is the masterpiece of WC fields. You know, who was obsessed with the
bank dick Tony soprano. Oh, really? Didn't I know that? No, you wouldn't. It's a great movie. The
highlight is when he almost throws a vase in a child's head. Yeah. You can guess the plot of this
thing. He for some reason has to become a bank dick. He's an absolute drunk. Alarity and so
what more do you need? That's the plot. The guy is so weirdly funny and the instincts for
the time are so odd. Yeah. Or so sharp, I should say, and unique because he does things where at
that time, nobody else was doing them. And there are things you would do now that are funny.
But like, so in the movie Poppy, which is a movie where he plays a drunk, except he's somebody's
dad. Something like that is the plot. The plot's pretty fast and loose. I haven't seen Poppy.
I've seen a couple of them. Not that one. In Poppy, I believe it's in Poppy, he owns a store.
And there's a gag where a blind man comes in. Oh, I have seen that bit. Yeah. And like, for some
reason, there's loose light bulbs for sale. Obviously just for the gag that the blind guy will knock him
over whatever. And like, that's as far as it would have went like in comedy in those days. That would
have been the whole joke. Right. WC Fields is this thing where he draws that scene out, man, for like
three minutes of the guy hovering around the light bulbs unknowingly. And he keeps saying he
keeps going sit down, honey, honey, honey, he's called a 90 year old man, honey repeatedly.
And it is so weird and funny. It's odd. Yeah, that's like Tim Robinson kind of stuff falling
in that year old man. Yeah. So like, I say, give these things a watch if you can. Your arc that you
want to stick to is is Poppy. You're telling me is a great one. The bank dick. I think in Poppy,
he also actually you're telling me might be the one with the store. Your tell Poppy is the one I think
where he he tries to marry an old woman aristocrat so he can like provide for his daughter finally.
And there's a great scene where he's walking with the old woman through her estate. And she's like,
do you croquet? And he's like, of course, it's not enough for him to just lie and say, yes, I croquet.
He says that. And then he goes, I'm a top croquet instructor in most parts of this world or whatever.
That's his big. Yeah. And they walk onto the croquet lawn and he trips on one of the croquet wires
and falls down and has no idea what any of it is. And then he goes, what lousy,
lout put wires all up for this lawn. The lady's like, this is the croquet lawn. And he's like,
of course it is. I guess. So then it's like, it's like the love, it's liar characters in there
a little bit. You know, like it's, they're just the good ones are just such joys to watch. Like
they're really gift is the other classic in my opinion. The bank dick and it's a gift are his,
the, well, they're the two favorites of mine. That's one. It's a gift for you. I think it's the old house.
Yeah. Yeah. And then my little chickadee with Mae West is a lot of fun too. Yes. But you know,
it's like we always see it when in like old like that movie, the majestic. I don't remember this
scene being in it, but I imagine it was in it. You always see in movies big audiences of people howling
and slapping their knees at Charlie Chaplin movies like back in the day. The truth is, and I have a lot
of course admiration for the silent film stars. You're watching Buster Keaton. You're like,
holy shit, he did some amazing stunts. Charlie Chaplin, you're like, oh, okay, this is kind of where
modern comedy and drama was birth was born, you know, but I define anyone who's howling laughing,
watching a Buster Keaton movie or Charlie Chaplin movie. WC Fields hits you in that same three
studious spot of like just shocking you into laughter. Yeah. And he's still laugh out a lot
funny a hundred years later, which is obviously very, very hard to do. Yes.
But brace yourself, by the way, if you do go watch these minutes, they're of the time. There's some
problematic stuff in there, but you know, but yeah, anyway, I rewatched a movie that I always loved
and my opinion went down a bit on this viewing, but I watched a revolutionary road. A sort of a
portrait of a marriage and in complete despair, starring Leonardo Caprio and Kate Winslet.
Wait, I thought you meant the bomb movie with Jeff Bridges. That's called Blondaway.
No, Blondaway, but then Arlington Road. Okay, yeah, sorry.
Two bomb movies. That's right. I like Blondaway and I love Arlington Road. Yeah, I liked Arlington
Road too. I was like, yeah, that's a bummer. It's not as good as I remember. Okay. Anyway,
no, I saw Revolutionary Road in theater. I think I saw it a second time. And it's the same
director, Sam Mendes, who's Kate Winslet's husband, same director as American Beauty. And it's,
it's the same way. When I saw American Beauty, my senior year of high school, I was like,
and I think a lot of people who were 17, 18 when American Beauty came out, I know all my friends
were like, this is the most deep, most impactful move. Like one best picture for God's sake. We
used to just be like, oh my God, this movie understands the truth. And then you watch it now,
and it seems sort of ridiculous as you get older. Like, it's like when you're younger, you think
I'll never be like that. But at some point, everyone goes through these things, you know? So
Revolutionary Road actually was making me laugh out loud in a few spots because it's a lot of
people like screaming at each other like, I can't die in these suburbs. I can't do it. It's carrying
me apart, you know, at that level of drama. And at some point, you're just like, guys, you're
living in a beautiful house. And movies never had the, now it's all movies are. It's like this sort of
like, well, how, you know, judging at this point at the movie would be about white privilege or
whatever else, to watch people this obsessed in this beautiful house with family and kids and
everything. And think they'll be happy if they just leave the suburbs. I almost found it like a dark
comedy, even though that's not how it's intended. So it's super melodramatic. It's a lot of decaprio and
yelling at each other. You got David Harbour, who's the stranger thing Sheriff and Catherine
Han, both in early performances as their couple friends. You got Michael Shannon in a great performance
even though he's just hamming it up. His whole role is to come in and be, he's a mental patient
and he's supposed to come in and be like, you're gonna die here in the suburbs. He just continues
delivering the theme of the movie, which is like, you should have moved to Paris when you had the chance.
Now you're going to die on this beautiful cherry tree street, whatever. And then you've got
Kathy Bates, who has the one scene that I really remember to this thing that I think hints at the movie
this could have been if they had leaned more into the dark comedy like if Danny DeVito had directed it
at the end of the movie. It's an amazing scene where Kathy Bates is just talking to her husband.
And the whole movie you've seen these two is like the picture of content married happiness as a
nice counter to the misery that DeCaprio and Winslet are in in their marriage. And the very last scene
of the movie is Kathy Bates is yammering on to her husband and you see him crank up his hearing aid
so that he cannot hear a word that she's saying. And little by little her voice gets drowned out.
And it's the last scene of the movie. It's like, oh, this couple that you thought was happy.
They're also in misery. Super depressing, but I think that's a brilliant ending to a movie that
doesn't really earn it. I mean, it's it's a very entertaining piece of Oscar bait just like marriage
story was. But I think marriage story is a lot kind of smarter about divorce about all kinds of
different things about marriage. This felt like a second tier episode of Mad Men really is how
revolutionary road felt. I think the reason it didn't seem as good this time around is because
Mad Men tried to do the exact same thing exact same time period and they did it better. There you go.
I watched on the WC Fields theme WC Fields and me which is a biopic about him from the late 70s
that starred Rod Steiger as WC Fields. He's tremendous in it. He's so good in it. The movie's not great.
That's a biopic. He plays a little bit like a TV movie, but it's interesting enough.
He's really, really good. He really captures the guy in an honest way and a very grounded way too.
I've actually watched interviews with him about it where he's like, everybody did a WC Fields impression
back then and everybody said you do it like this or like that. And I found I had to find how to do it
for real and he's great in it. Billy Barty is in it and a supporting role playing one of his
partners from the Vodville days and it's just about his journey from Vodville out west to Hollywood to
make movies and his relationship with his pseudo wife played by Miss Tess Mocker from Superman
who's also the actress that was in Lenny. She plays Lenny Bruce's wife and Lenny.
And unlike WC Fields on screen off screen, he is a bastard and a drunk.
Next sense. He suffered a lot of abuse as a kid. He did not come from a good background. Nobody
even knows his true background because he's always like sort of lied, like changes the story and
stuff. He's very mysterious. But you know, not a great guy. And honestly, which I was surprised to
learn a true drunk life. I always thought he kind of hammed it up a bit, you know, like Ron White or
something like that for camera. Ron White likes to drink, but like, you know, he's a normal guy,
you know, Dean Martin like to drink, but he was a normal guy. WC Fields, it's like no, dude, he was
like literally like a liability because it was drinking like they wouldn't ensure him at one point.
You know, so, you know, the gin blossom knows and all that stuff is very real. And it does kill him in
the end of his life, but his nose killed him. His nose kills him. If you, I don't know, if you're a fan
of the guy and you want to see a little bit more of a glimpse into the real man, which is very,
very hard to find because there are no WC Fields interviews out there. And you know, I don't know,
maybe there's a book or two, but anything short of that, you're not, you're not really going to learn
much. So I enjoyed the watch for that reason. Okay. I know my dad had that. I never saw it. But yeah,
he's a guy that I think is ripe for rediscovery. He's, he's always been hilarious to me.
And I will close my movie corner with a movie called either
Err, like an animal growling or RRR. I believe it is called RRR. And I also believe it stands for
something in the movie, although I can't find where it is on Wikipedia. But basically,
Oh, here it is. Rise RRR revolt. Okay. And also there are a lot of tigers and animals in this movie that
make the noise for this is new to Netflix. But it is in theaters now. I would, I saw it at home. I would
absolutely recommend seeing this thing at the theater. I have, for all the movies I have seen, I had
never in my life seen an actual Bollywood film. I have seen, you know, Slumdog Millionaire and things
of that nature. I've seen movies made in India, for sure. But I had never seen an actual Bollywood
film and chalked them up as kind of, you know, just not for me. They're always four hours long and,
you know, musical numbers and etc. But this one I just kept hearing from people, it is awesome.
It is awesome. You won't believe it. You've got to see it, etc., etc. I was concerned because the
running time is three full hours. This is just a true old fashioned Hollywood epic like they don't
do anymore. It is incredible. The highlights of it are the musical numbers and like the Indian dance
that goes on between the two leads of the movie. There's a dance off about an hour in that is one
of the greatest scenes I've seen in a very long time. It goes on for a very long time. And then there's
just amazing epic battles. And they don't all look real. They're definitely done with some CGI.
But that's what led a lot of people to compare this to the Marvel movies because they're like,
look, just like in Marvel, this is a lot of CGI, a lot of special effects. But it is directed so
cleanly and clearly that it's really kind of showing us what we're missing at our big action movies.
And I could not agree with that more. It's not real animals fighting. It's not real sword fights
and stuff. And a lot of times you can tell and that's kind of a drag. But it's done so precisely
and the action is so exciting. And even the dancing I think is a little helped out probably by effects.
I mean, really, not bored for three hours. There's a million twists and turns in the thing.
It is a little heightened, a little zany at times, but it's really just payoff after payoff after
payoff. And I recommend you check it out. Everybody should see a Bollywood movie at some point in their
life. And I think most people are in agreement that this is one of the all -time greats. And it just
dumped on Netflix. So check it out. It is awesome. Made in a budget of, oh, only 72 million dollars.
It's pretty impressive. It's pretty impressive. That's it. Second highest grossing film in India.
History. Excuse me. It's awesome. It's just a great action movie. Check it out.
I'll close out with the trauma piece. Class of Newcomhuy. I wouldn't have to see Class of Newcomhuy
forever. I'd never seen it. I finally found a copy on DVD. Finally, I mean, it's available. I just
finally found one that was decently priced. And I tried to be a little more meticulous or careful
about purchasing things I've never seen, what I paid for them now. Anyway, I found it a little
while back, kept it on the shelf for a while, and finally popped it and watched it. Really enjoyed it,
man. That early era, I mean, yes, it's not that early, but that's sort of the heyday of
trauma. It's the early 80s, mid 80s. This is when they're doing toxic avenger and all that stuff.
And it's fun. It's low budget. It's grainy film. It's crazy, disgusting, practical effects.
It's absurd in your face comedy. And, you know, it's just a fun time, man. It's great driving
fodder. As I said in the last episode, I wish I smoked pot. This would be a great thing to sit
around with a bunch of people, get stoned and watch. But I enjoyed it quite a bit. They've made sequels.
The sequels look higher budget and not anywhere near as interesting. But the Class of Newcomhuy is one
of the trauma classics. And trauma usually, from what I can tell, because I also just bought the
toxic avenger collection, really packs in a lot of fun bonus features on their stuff. So like,
that's also cool to see interviews with people that were part of these crazy productions and hearing
the stories of what went on behind the scenes. And, you know, again, this is simpler time stuff.
This just reminds you of when, you know, things like this just existed because people cared and
put it out there and it got traction somehow. And there wasn't any trick to any of it. So
I recommend it as a fun watch, ridiculous trashy romp. It's a good time.
All right. I've seen, I don't think any trauma really outside of Jobah.
You know, the trauma has got some great stuff, you know, mother's day and I think rabbit grannies
is trauma. You know, some of those classic trauma films are really fun. You know, when it gets,
you know, it's like John Waters, though, unfortunately, when it gets into the later years and it starts
to get shiny, and film just doesn't look like film anymore. It loses a lot of the charm, I think.
I agree on Waters, for sure, for sure. Anyway, let us move on to
the second adaptation of Stephen King's Firestarter. It is in theaters, but also streaming exclusively
on the peacock. To me, I don't know why, but to me, the peacock is still the funniest one.
They're all sort of equally, you know, like doomed to fail at this point, but the peacock still
makes me laugh. Just like Wibi still makes me laugh. It's NBC. That's why it's funny. It's like, yeah,
this major emotion picture is streaming on NBC. Yeah, exactly. Today, I'm going to watch you won't
be alone. This new horror movie with Noomi Repace that's getting great reviews. That's on peacock
for some reason. Well, I should watch that at some point. Do we do that next time or something?
They're fertile. Well, there's, I guess, their second foray into horror. First was when Halloween,
whatever that was, dropped on peacock. And in addition to being terrible, I just kind of was like
like watching it on peacock made it much more depressing. I'll say that.
This movie, The Firestarter Remake is written by the same guy who wrote Halloween kills with
McBride. And he did not know, but he doesn't have them on board this time. And I mean, I don't know.
I don't know what you can really say about this thing. It felt like it should have started Mark
Paul Gosler and been on the sci -fi channel for starters. Yes. In terms of production value, budget,
script, direction, everything. Who's Mark Paul? Is that Zach? Zach Morris. Yeah. Zach Efron is
no better an actor than Mark Paul Gosler. I want to be very clear about that. I'm not trying to
to slight Mark Paul. Zach Efron is a zero, an absolute zero. And the fact that he, somebody was like,
Zach Efron, he's a fire his agent. No, he's getting the roles that are on a par with his talent,
which is non -existent. Yeah. Somebody wrote, somebody wrote that, I saw that, I saw that review,
and I also saw a review that said, Zach Efron is just not capable of emoting in a way that a guy
that loves his daughter should be able to emot and it's true. It's just, it's so true. The daughter
is acting circles around him in this movie. Yeah. It's embarrassing. The wife is acting, everybody's
acting circles around him. Let's start with the fact, and this is something I read in another review,
which is, this is the Stephen King book nobody wanted an adaptation of to begin with.
Fire started original with Drew Barrymore is better than this. And it's still a terrible movie.
We reviewed it on here and it's bad. I don't understand. I don't understand what possessed anybody to
think we wanted another fire starter outside of Jason Blum's weird obsession with telling female
stories. It's getting weird at this point that he is, I feel like this is a guy, something's going to
melt or something. It's odd to me. He's got an obsession with, with female empowerment, which,
hey, supported, I think it's a good thing. He's got a weird obsession with it at this point. I don't
understand why he is telling the stories he's telling with his company. They're not good. They're
not interesting. Nobody wants them. They're, they're, they're things that have failed in the past.
We saw that with black Christmas, the remake of black Christmas, the first remake didn't do very
well and wasn't that well received. He did a second remake. It's odd. That old side, my personal
shit with that, you know, my opinions about his company aside. Let's just start though with the fact
that nobody wanted this adaptation or retelling. Did Blumhouse do new pets, I'm a territory too?
No. No. Okay. That was, I mean, to me, as, as, as miserable a slog as the pet cemetery remake was,
it's five times the movie. This is, oh, it got 100%. I hated it. I hated the new pet cemetery.
So that tells you where we're coming up, coming from here. Is a terrible movie. It starts as being
bad where you just don't care. It starts as normal bad where you go. This just sucks. And like
you said, it's like made for sci -fi. And you're like, this is like just bad. Who gives a shit, though?
But then it becomes ridiculous. But you don't believe, you don't even believe that Efron and this girl
have met. You know what I mean? It's like, it's like, okay, even in a horror movie that doesn't do
its job at all, at least you know what like the relationship between the two people is. You understand
that a dad's going to care about his daughter or whatever. You never buy that he's a dad in general.
Let alone this girl's dad. He seems lost. He seems like he cannot convey the most generically written
role of like dad who cares. He can't do it. He can't pull off anything. You're, yeah, I agree with
that. There's a scene where she lights a cat on fire because she gets mad at it. And then it's,
you're watching it burn and suffer, which is just awful. And then he comes in and he goes,
it's suffering. Put it out of its misery. This cat. He literally used to say about Keanu,
but Keanu was always a better actor than this. He literally, Zach Efron literally sounds like
that voice David Spade does when he's doing like a dumb person where he's going, but I thought Ken
that's that. The writing in this thing, the directing will just chalk up completely to the guy
does whoever it is doesn't know what they're doing. And it's also again, Pat Erie said, it looks like
I made for sci -fi movie a past the writing. Let's get into the writing in like scene three. He's
exclaiming things like, but she needs to understand her powers. Like it's like shit that you wouldn't
scream out in a Spider -Man movie. And then like she need, but the antidote, the serum. Oh, that's
that's about when they go and meet the doctor that like that like you learn that she was born because
they did some sort of government testing on people that had telekinetic abilities. Zach Efron and
the woman who plays his wife are two of those people. And this daughter was born out of that.
They then flee and hide her because they don't want her being tested for the rest of her life.
They go and find the doctor at one point because their cover gets blown and the government wants to
find her now. So they go and track down the doctor that ran those experiments played by Kurt Wood Smith.
Kurt Wood Smith from Robocop. And yeah, 70 show soon to star in the
parents focused sequels series. Friend of mine, right? Not
good friend. You know, anyway. So anyway, so well, then you got also the Kurt Wood Smith
from ER as the captain. And she was the leader of the company that did this. She's terrible in this
when she realized they're doing what they can with just a spirit that is just pathetic.
When she meets Kurt Wood Smith for the first time and she goes, I need to talk to you about what
you did. And he goes, ah, the serum. You're like, oh my god. This is like what I would like how I
would have written a comic book when I was 11. Like it's so stupid. Yeah. It's so stupid.
There's no lesson to be learned in the end. The ending makes no sense, especially when you compare it
to the way the book ends, when you compare it to the way the original movie ends. The whole time,
I'm like, okay, this is literally killing my soul watching this movie, which is only 90 minutes.
But I thought at least at the end, we're going to get the big awesome showdown. The original movie
sucks, but for the last 20 minutes, it's drew Barry more blown up shit with minefire. And we don't
really even get that. There's no exciting moment at the end of this. Actually, Barry does any fire
into the last. And even then you see like her point of view, you see like what she's looking at,
and then like, it's literally like they draw orange flames on the four corners of the screen
around it. Like that's the level of effects we're talking about. The effects are bad. And then like,
yeah, it'll be like, you see her, then you see her point of view, then it cuts away for no reason to
a clock, and then it cuts back and everything's on fire. Yeah. Now the blow knows he can keep making
these five million and below movies and dumping them on peacock and making his money back.
He's going to try even less. I mean, it'll just be a dumping round now. This is what I mean about when
I say weird obsession. Okay. The ending of this thing, I'll say you have a weird obsession with
Jason Blum. Let's say he does horrible work and he keeps going and we're going to keep reviewing his
movies because we do mostly horror. We have no choice. But I had the guy is not good. I mean,
look, you coasted on your fumes from from whiplash and get out. It's over. You do bad work. So like
so so the end of this thing, for no justifiable reason, she sets her father on fire because he tells her
to and this movie ends with the guy that's been trying to actively kill her throughout the movie,
bowing to her and saying, teach me. I want to now learn from you because I'm also just a puppet of
this facility that you've just burnt to the ground that you escaped from as a child or whatever.
And then it's her leading him down a beach. This is what I mean. Every bit of logic has been
no pun intended. Burn to the ground. Why? So we can show it. Yes. So we can show an eight -year -old girl
having power now over a grown man. It's stupid. It makes no sense. It's at the expense of her character
or through the detriment of her character. It's to the detriment of any relationship in the entire movie.
You're supposed to somehow now have sympathy for this fucking contract killer. It's idiotic.
Yeah. What we're seeing, idiotic. Lately, especially in horror, we see it a lot lately,
is that the themes that used to be in the background or maybe something that didn't even reveal
itself until much later or on a rewatch of a movie, the themes become the whole movie. The themes take
precedent over character, story, scares, anything. So you're just watching like some writer.
In this case, this is what I would truly consider a writer jerking themselves off is when you go
into this, a man is an even better example of the theme taking over the movie to the point where you're
not left with a movie anymore. And for something as dumb and empty as fire starter to try to give it
some significance is just pathetic. At least men is attempting to do something and failing
miserably. Fire starter doesn't attempt anything but then at the end tries to pretend it's got some
feminist slant to it. And it's as embarrassing as you say. It's a really terrible film.
I think Blumhouse has become a company that exploits and takes advantage of a cause at the
expense of its customer with no regard for delivering the quality product to its target audience.
And just like I said in the last episode with the Sandler movies, I guess these things just made
money so people kept spending them. But just like they never delivered quality to the stoner crowd,
it was like they'll buy it. Who cares? That's what Blumhouse is doing now with the feminist or at least
feminist leaning audience that want to see his movies. He's just selling them crap.
You know, it's just crap. It's terrible, terrible product.
I'm trying to think of this as a bad. No, this is a bad, bad, bad, bad, bad movie. Really,
really bad. Like I can't imagine anyone saying that they...
Can't imagine anyone saying more than they liked it. That's the most I could imagine.
Someone in the world saying is, I don't know, I liked it. And even then I wouldn't believe them.
But nobody would love this movie. And you should make something that at least your goal is that
somebody out there will love it. Nobody is going to love this movie. It's not even trying to be good
in my pen. It sucked. Limp. Not even down. Dad limp hog on this one. Limp is correct. We didn't even
showcase the John Carpenter score, which I was excited at least to see his name in the credits. But
as I saw someone on Twitter point out Carpenter was originally supposed to direct the 1984
fire starter. Something tells me he had the score lying around. You know, there's no way Carpenter
watched this movie. Unless he just needed a little extra cash to play video games in his
basement smoke weed like he does now. But the score is, it's not prime Carpenter. It just fell. You know,
I got to say this, man, and I'm sorry. You know, I like John Carpenter's themes as much as the next guy,
but it's a one trick pony for Christ's sakes. It's just every fucking... So one trick pony, but
that pony has proven very fruitful. Like, it influences the stranger thing soundtrack. It's
simple what he did, but it also can't really be overestimated because it had such a huge impact
on horror scores, and he still does. I don't know if he started that or not though. I'd have to look
into that. Yeah, maybe he's just credited at it. But like, certainly, people constantly, just not to
cut you off, but people constantly credit him as the creator of the holiday slasher movie.
And it's like, no, black Christmas came years before Halloween. Yeah. But that that's
Cynthia kind of Cassioe thing, you know, maybe he just popularized it, but it definitely is still
felt in horror what he did. It's just sure this is not a score that people are going to be buying
of John Carpenter's I assure you. I think really like you said, his lost themes, his two collections
of themes are where to go with him. You know, when you get into like one of his albums, it's like,
all right, I get it. But the themes collect the best of his work. Well, I do find it interesting that
his solo records now, I believe he's collaborating with his kids. Yes, for sure. And there's a noticeable
yeah, tick. You know, like when you go see John Carpenter live, like for instance, you can look up
the YouTube video when they do Halloween. Yeah, he doesn't play the dude, dude, dude, he doesn't
play that part. He does the part that goes bound, bound, bound. So, you know, I think John Carpenter
is capable. I think he had a few cool tricks up his sleeve. But I'm getting over it at this point
where it's like, okay, dude, I get it. You're going to hit low E on an analog synth with some delay
over and over. And then do some some sustaining high notes. Like it, I get it, dude, like, you know,
but anyway, Firestarter sucks. Oh, it's down really. So Andrew dreamed of the soundtrack to the original,
by the way. And they've got endless classic scores. Also, RIP to then jealous who've had a lot of
great scores, many of which I still write through to this day. Don't watch Firestarter even on peacock
even if you have a free trial. It's really awful. We will be back with reviews of the new kids
in the hall season of Amazon Prime. Yep. And something else, some other big horror movie that comes out,
maybe Top Gun, I don't know, but we'll talk again. We'll see you next time. We'll see you.
Oh, Joe live show, are we talking about it yet? No, not yet. All right, but there is one coming.
All right, probably. See you next time. See you probably in hell