I'm here for Bet River's online casino and sportsbook with poker icon Phil Helmuth.
And now thanks to the excitement of Bet Rivers, I'm also a slots icon.
That's great! And a same game, Parley icon. Cool, cool. A Blackjack icon, a moneyline icon,
a roulette. Take it from Phil Helmuth. If you love games, Bet Rivers is the place to play in Bet.
Bet Rivers. Games on.
Must be 21 plus in present at West Virginia. Void were prohibited. Terms in conditions apply,
gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gambling.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning, or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 -plus gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberler offer not available in all states
terms apply, see Phenatic Sports Book App.
Hi everybody.
Buddy, it's time for you, we'll see you in hell.
You know it's a podcast.
You know it's part of the Fangoria podcast network.
You want some info about that network
or this program or other programs
or how to find and follow shows in past episodes
of all of them, including this one,
you go visit Fangoria .com.
But for right now, it's time for this episode,
the business at hand, I'm here with Pat Walsh.
Hey, bringing you the first of the September
Yeah, episodes of we'll see you in hell today. We discussed Stranger Things, Stranger Things, a Phenomenon.
It was a Phenomenon, wasn't it Pat?
Yeah, I just I think I was reading an interview with the creators of it who said they their hunch was that it became such a big deal
because the summer movie season was so shitty
And it truly was that might have helped that people were just like
Wanted something fun. Well, I don't agree with that statement as you know
you thought there were good movies this summer yes yes I don't know if I can
think of one but I I thought there were some nice movies that came out this
summer well we know bad members I sent Joe right before this started Mel Gibson
referred to bad members to Superman as quote a piece of shit right and I thought
that was very funny and that I was showing Joe that I was on the side of good
Mel Gibson. Right. Everybody's favorite. Right. Celebrity. Yeah. Well, that's the you know what,
I'm not gonna bad mouth. I could be easy to make a Mel Gibson joke right now. Yeah. Where I go,
ah, you know, great, great source. I'm happy to guys like back on his feet and cleaned his act up.
And if that took him, call him Batman versus a superman, a piece of shit. I'll take it. People are
loving the what's it called? Hobo with a shotgun or whatever he did on. Well, Hobo with a shotgun was
Rutger Howard. I saw that who never fell from grace. No, I don't know if he was in grace to begin with. What was the movie that he did? I think you were telling me about. He's got a new milk Gibson has a new movie with a bomb.
It's called a mean daddy or something like that. I think I was closer on my angry father. Yeah, bad father. It's not that bad.
Yeah, it's new to Netflix, our new to iTunes and people seem to enjoy it.
It's like a taken style movie with Mel, which is exactly what he should be doing.
But he just directed that new movie, something rich or whatever, and that's supposed to
be amazing.
It's got a 10 minute standing ovation.
Yeah.
I mean, I think he did the right thing.
It's like, okay, I would say those racist things.
No, obviously that's the wrong thing.
But he handled it in an appropriate way, and I think people are seeing
How horrifically bad people can behave in this day and age and as long as you do your little time after you do your little crime
They're gonna be fine as long as you're not feel cost beer something the man got wasted and messed up and
His friends including like Jody Foster like the guy doesn't have hatred in his heart and I believe them
I think I you know, you know, you can't you can't be mad at somebody for the rest of his life
It's in a bad place and he said some things he shouldn't have and he God only knows too if the stuff with his
Girlfriend was rough to me and yeah, and Pete you so listen to those constantly those tapes. There's so
they're so
Outlandishly awful and funny. Well that those are always maybe wonder if he had some kind of mental thing happening
He said like a man that was off his medicine or something. Yeah, so the point is he's back. He's looking healthy again
And he, you know, he seems to be redeeming himself.
I'm, you know, he should have time as he said.
Oh, the jacuzzi.
Yeah, he apologized.
So it's, you know, here he is.
So I, so all that out of the fact that I wasn't gonna slam
Mel, I was gonna make a cheap Mel joke.
Right.
Just to defend Batman versus Superman.
Yeah.
But he's wrong as you are.
I just got the, well, not just a month ago.
I've been out of town for a month. I've been in Scotland at the Edinburgh Film Fringe Festival
performing for a month straight. So we actually recorded our August episodes before I left and
I was gone all of August. I just got back now. We're the beginning of September here. But before I left
for the plane ride, the long plane ride over, I picked up a sweet blue ray copy of Batman
V -soups, how much extra footage is in there?
30 minutes of extra footage, it's three hours exactly,
it is an R -rated director's cut,
and it is a masterpiece.
It has officially become my favorite superhero movie
of all time.
I honestly, I don't know why anybody would keep listening
to this, but...
Because there are people out there.
The minority is usually right, you know?
So you look at the great voices that were vocal in the minority throughout history, Bay Blinken, Martin Luther King, Zack Snyder, all the greats.
uh... we don't need to get back into that
no but we can before we do today in the r -rated footage
no but the it that's the only extra footage i found helped the story
quite a bit okay and help shape the arc of why Superman
was entrusted why batman had reservations about him
uh... i loved it i loved every minute of it i've seen the movie now four times
i guess and i and it hasn't
I just, you know, I like it. I just like the film. But let's not
say I liked it more than suicide squad. I loved suicide squad.
And I obviously hated that. But I walked out of suicide squad.
First of all, I've walked out of a movie in 10 years. Walked right out.
That's not true. You told me another movie you walked out of about a year.
I can't remember. I mean, I can't, I can't think of one. I walked out of
the the Cinderella reboot with like the Kenneth Branagh did got rave reviews. I don't
know what I was doing there, Frank. I think it was one of those whatever's starting
else. The one with with Helen, Helen a bottom card or is she was in the mix? Fairy Godmother.
Yeah. No, I, especially when I'm on hiatus, you got a lot of time to kill. I go up to the
grove. I'll see whatever's starting. And it can be fun like a grab bag, like an Easter egg
type, but Cinderella was a mistake. It was a very capably made kids movie. It wasn't
for me. I'm not supposed to be the guy watching Cinderella at a matinee. I
quite frankly put me on a watch list. Quite frankly. I don't think you're the
guy who's supposed to be watching Suicide Squad either. I don't think these
movies are for you. I don't think you get them. I don't think you get them. They're
clearly not for me. I don't make that face like I'm insulting. I'm not insulting. I'm
saying I don't I think they're speaking to a part of you that doesn't exist. That
could be because there was nothing for me and either of those movies. But you
know by and large and I know this argument never does anything for you people
who are really obsessed with superheroes and comic books didn't like these
movies either Kevin Smith loved Batman versus Superman and Smith has obviously
lost his fucking mind reshaped his opinion of Batman and a pot haze and we're not
getting them back oh come on you've seen the reviews on yoga closers no but I
want to see it very bad I know you do you know they're bringing back the Johnny
Depp Tusk care I know I've seen the trailer and I'm excited about it I love Tusk
What are the reviews on yoga way better reviews yoga. What are you what are they saying about yoga don't sidetrack me with yoga
Hoesers suicide squad. It was a fun movie. Yeah, there wasn't at all. Leto was a fantastic joker
Ridiculous. Why ridiculous why why I mean if we're just gonna compare him to the other two
He was about a thousand percent shittier. Oh stop it
But if we're just gonna compare him to like a normal crazy person performance, I
Guess he was fine. Why was he shitty? I?
Think he was barely in it
I think and and and since most of the early press releases were about him
You feel like the director must just bit must have been like there's nothing here
Little claims that they shot like an additional hour and a half of Joker footage. Yeah, it's not in the movie. They did apparently so clearly it didn't work
Well, no, I thought it worked to to the Joker's the name and this, I mean, Will Smith's obviously the name is
Suicide Squad is what the movie's about and the Joker's not a member of the suicide squad. Yeah, they're doing a Harley Quinn solo movie
They brought in the Joker to set that up her. I liked but you know, you know, you know, it's a beautiful woman. I thought Will Smith was great
I mean, I I can't even I don't really have anything to say about it
I my I left I texted my buddy
Because I couldn't sit with him. It was so crowded and I was like, I think I got to get out of here, man
And he was like, I'm already gone
Really? Yeah, like I just don't know any anyone who's enjoyed it. That's a shame
It's a shame and I'll never I'll never watch the other half when they're there's the thorny hateful place that you people all live in that
Which they kept cutting back to the which control them and viola Davis and they're going up in this building
That's about when I walked out. I'm like, I don't know what this building is where they're going. I don't care about anyone here.
They're playing a
Classic rock song for every
Character that enters the movie. Yeah, it was fun. Like let's just put a song in and everywhere so people don't notice that this is just
Nonsense. It felt like a comic book. It moved and felt exactly like if you went to meltdown comics right now pull the graphic
a volume of a suicide squad off the shelf and read it it would it would feel
just like that which I have done and I that's why I enjoyed it all right I
mean you are coming in from a place somebody who's read these books I I couldn't
give two shifts but that's why I say I feel like it's not for you it's it'd be
like for me if they made a movie about the the the the gritty underside of
football and I'd be sitting there going but wait how does the game work and they'd
Like we don't have time to explain the rules of the game right now. This is not about that
But see I can like anything. I mean, I don't care at all about any sports, but I've loved sports movies in the past
Sure, I know the basic rules of them
But so everyone knows basically what a superhero movie is also the fact that I think cost two hundred million dollars
Means that they need to be accessible to a wide audience there
They should not be making these for comic book nerds who also did not like either of these movies
That's not true, though.
That's not your suicide squad as a very high audience rating on Rotten Tomatoes.
Or does it?
I don't trust their credit compilation.
I certainly don't trust their audience.
Well, but the audience that you're not trusting is the audience you're saying they can't make this movie for, which they can.
I just mean by and large, people don't like it.
But I am just going off people I talk to.
But it's a hated movie.
It's a hated movie by the top critics.
By the top critics and everyone I know saw who's everyone you know
They're people. How many people how many people are you talking to people who love suicides?
I don't I don't really talk to anybody about it to be honest with you
I cuz I for my own opinions and I don't let I saw this movie before it came out
I don't let the hollywood. I yeah, I said before it came out. I didn't know anything about you know
I was gonna I've actually thought it was gonna be cool the trailer was cool
But you know if you want to play game ball with the brass that's that's your business man
I don't I can't I can't tell you the ball with the brass. I'm it's a
Yeah, I don't know that it is an expression
I was gonna say it's it. I was making a joke about Hollywood
But once you say I was making a joke it kind of gets ruined hold on a second. I'm trying to find this
I
I believe you, I bet it's got a 67 or something from audiences according to their obviously messed up aggregator
because then when a, as we've always said a movie, a movie that will be horrifically reviewed
will have a tomato on it. Like they don't, whoever's scanning them is like, it's got a 67.
I got it exactly. Yeah, it's audience review.
Which is higher than the Batman audience, Superman audience review if I'm not mistaken.
Now, let me see here, hold on a second. Batman, I mean, it wouldn't kill you to talk just a little bit as I look this stuff up.
Well, I don't know what you're, you're, you're proving here with us, but we're also supposed to be talking about stranger things.
65 percent. Yeah.
So it's higher.
But what is that?
Where are they getting those numbers? Those are the review, those are user consensus reviews.
So whoever actually wrote a review on Rotten Tomatoes.
Yeah, Rotten Tomatoes works as an aggregator,
thumbs up or thumbs down.
There's no in between.
But you're talking about the people who will get on Rotten Tomatoes log in.
Well, there's top critics and then there's the audience reviews.
Yeah, I guess so.
Yeah, I don't know.
I mean, I don't think...
I think as an audience member you can go on there and click a thumbs up or thumbs down.
So it's a it's a compilation of people who are willing to write a review for Rotten Tomatoes
I don't even know if you're probably not the smartest
Well, why?
Those people now because anyone who's willing it's like somebody who's willing to leave a comment on a porno video
You're an idiot
I'm surprised you can write if you feel you need to comment on a porn video
Do you think people that leave Amazon reviews are all idiot?
I think one of my favorite Twitter accounts is a compilation of hilariously stupid Amazon reviews.
I'm not saying they're not stupid. I'm just saying I can't be stupid, but I'm saying do you think every one of those things is always stupid?
I think zero people who I want to hear their opinion are leaving reviews in the depths of Rotten Tomatoes on Suicide Squad in the hopes that somebody will see it.
You know you do have a point because I don't know why I'm defending this because I actually say I actually trash all these rating sites in my act about how it makes me
Furious that everybody's a food critic now that Yelp has come out of it. It's all the only people writing a Yelp review or somebody who had
The best meal of their life or a problem or somebody who likes it or the air conditioner was blowing on me
Speaking of people who like to wine. I got a Joe and I just watched this video this woman anilis
I don't remember her last name either do I refuse to learn it. Apparently she works in the in the pornographic
Industry kind of a suicide girls type site. No, no, no
She was that girls attacked her. That's how I found out good because I follow the suicide girls
She's sitting in a lift and as you watch the video you realize it's a lift shared so there's other people in the in the car and
the driver is
an Asian male
Who's like completely nice and pleasant and reasonable and he has a hula girl on his dashboard
So not a literal woman, you know, a doll of the corpse of a woman a little doll like you would see it like
There's tiki -t the tiki bar right by us has a thousand of these things and if you go to Hawaii
There's a billion of these things living hula girls as well as dolls and they give you the lays when you get off the flight
and et cetera, et cetera.
It's a big part of their culture.
I saw a very beautiful hula show when I was in Hawaii.
It was like two hours long.
It was amazing.
This girl is sitting in the back seat.
I guess she was Asian.
I don't think she's Asian.
I don't know what she was.
You couldn't see her.
But she is starting to get blackness.
Yeah, exactly.
You can even see the damn hula girl.
She records this entire 10 minute thing
and you gotta look this video up.
She is telling him that he has to take down
this hula girl which is super glued to his dashboard because it is exploitative of Hawaiian culture.
Well she says, she says the raping and pillaging of the continent of Hawaii.
The right. The pillaging of the continent of Hawaii. So this person's working at an intelligence
level that one might have who's leaving reviews on Rotten Tomatoes film. Yeah, she, she's
saying to take it down on the guy's very respectfully like, I'm not going to, it's a doll. I'm sorry.
She eventually she then also explains to her eventually it's glued to the dashboard I am Asian
She's like what kind of Asian are you what percentage of Asian this is after she calls him a white male a white male
The passengers like you're being very rude like the other people are all turning against her
She's like you're gonna have to throw me out of your car take me to my destination because I'm not taking your destination
I'll drop you off wherever you want, but I'm not taking you. She's like yes, you are call the police and the passengers like
please call the police I love to see how this play out the cops show up and you
say he won't take down this hula doll the cop will arrest you on site hopefully
right so this woman is like you're going to be on gocker tomorrow and that the
whole time is using that tone of voice that's like oh I'm going to love it when
everyone is laughing in your face tomorrow this is great the whole obnoxious voice
going and going going then now it's hit the internet Joe showed me this and the
America has turned against the woman right which makes me very happy all of a sudden
America's opinion counts when it comes to this monster comes to a great movie like
Suicide Squad doesn't mean shit but hey that's Pat Walsh and that's how Hollywood works folks
you just got a crash course 101 lesson in Hollywood why why couldn't we just bash this woman
together are you on her side now no to bash me over this woman now I'm not I this video got
me so upset and I want you to watch it. I almost didn't want to do the podcast. I was so mad.
You need to know people where this is going. The fact that everyone turned on her is reassuring,
but we are headed into a dark time of oversensitivity in America that I think is going to ruin us.
But here's the thing, it's not... And honestly, that's what's thrown people into the arms of Trump,
because he's the polar opposite of that to the other extreme, to a problematic extreme.
But people are like I'm so sick of people screaming at this guy because he has a hula girl on his dashboard
At least trumps the man who will slap a woman in the face. They know that they're going over there
I like I like an old an old son old guy. I can't support any of these comments you're making at this point at least
Trump's a man who will slap a woman. That's what people are saying. Oh, you're doing a character
People are voting for him are like if that's where the world is going where you can't have a hula doll on your dashboard
than I'm going to vote for Trump because he will reinstate racism and
horribleness because you're saying you're saying you're saying what what the
supposed fight against evil does is it creates a worse evil exactly it's gone
so far I mean obviously these are both extremes Trump in this one didn't you say
she's a port of Trump? I went to her Twitter thing and it had a bunch of
Trump things that couldn't tell they were sarcastic but I don't think they're
proud of our cast I feel like they're not I feel like I read something that
said she supported Trump. But here's the thing. What you're saying is is by trying to stamp
out this evil in the wrong way in two proud away as, for instance, the Jedi were at fault
for doing. Yeah. Many moons ago. Sure. They've now created an Anakin who's going to become
a Darth Vader. And that's, that's worse. If I think everyone has gone so far into political
correctness, that eventually comedy is not going to be funny. And that we've sort of created
this monster of Trump, yes, to go so far in the opposite direction of this political
correctness that everybody is hating, that he's going to go way too far, and then the society
will be racist and horrific to live in.
Well, it's, here's what my take on it is, I don't think the problem is oversensitivity.
I think the problem is, certain people have realized they can exploit
oversensitivity to make themselves more famous or to gain notoriety somehow.
That's what scary thing is I'm going to be on Gawker, you're going to be on Gawker.
What is your full name? I can't wait for everyone to see this.
You're going to be a meme tomorrow. She actually says the words meme.
Well, that's the frightening thing to me is that she's not truly offended.
Did she just seize an opportunity to bring her own notoriety up a notch or whatever?
She saw that headline being hero, Annalise, whatever the fuck calls out this scumbag for
exploiting Hawaiian cultures, what she sees, and thankfully the other thing happened.
I thought when I heard the story that this one was gonna be upset that it was a lady wearing
a coconut bra and that it was exploitative of women, but the race thing makes it even
weirder to me.
Well, I think she that was what she was saying initially
To me, I only heard her talking about Hawaii and the beautiful people of Hawaii, right
Who I guarantee would not care about this
So wait, so it wasn't a gender thing. It was a almost I mean, I watched maybe I miss I just had it in my head
Yeah, I tuned out after about four I couldn't she was saying it's offensive to her and all but it was all focused on
Hope being Hawaiian. I'm I'm sure the woman might have triggered it
I cut it off about four minutes in and you know Pat first internet video. I
Didn't finish in 10 years really
I was a call back to the suicide squad story. Have you walking out you see I see but I don't really know when I'm supposed to feel about it
We should get on to stranger things we will but real quick. Oh, oh, okay. I'm sorry boss man
I went and ate at Salazar the other night with Heather. It's a beautiful new restaurant in town
And I'm talking to her and I was talking about how much money comes out of my paycheck
And how it upsets me. Hey, you know the conversation that everyone in the world has every time they get their taxes done
Are you gonna support Trump again? Is that where you're heading with this?
I never have and never will and I don't think that Trump's gonna fix my tax rate or anything else in America
But I'm walking in and again doing like a character. I'm complaining to Heather about it and I'm like, and
In conclusion, that's why I'm voting for Trump, you know, Dylan voice and everything and
We sit down at the table and Heather's menu blows away with the wind and lands in this woman's lap next to us and
I said, oh, I'm sorry about that and I stand up to grab the menu from her and she holds it up over her head
Lifts it up away from me like somebody keeping a ball from a little sister or something and she says I'm actually not giving this to you
And she was serious what and I said, what are you talking about she says I'm not giving this to you
If you're voting for Donald Trump and then turns to resume speaking to her friend and ignore me
And I had to say then to this woman
Now I was doing a character. I was doing a bit obviously. I don't support Trump
I don't we don't can I please have it back and she gives it back and I
Bit into my tongue so hard that I tasted blood to not start fighting with this woman
Because I'm sitting there with Heather and we're both so annoyed by her because we do agree with you when we do hate Trump
but
What if it is it is still a free country you can't keep someone I'm not giving this back to you. How old was she 45?
45, you know, I had to find myself having to explain my political beliefs to a woman
to get my menu back.
Well, you didn't have to.
No, I didn't have to.
What am I going to do?
Grab it out of her hands and get arrested.
What I would have done was I would have told on her.
I would have said, she's got my menu.
I'm going to treat you like the fucking baby you are and I'm going to tell on you.
And I went and said, this lady took my menu and she won't give it back because for some
Reason she thinks I'm voting for Trump and whether I am or not what the fuck kind of restaurant
You run here the customers or call on the shots like that on other customers
That's what you should have done and gotten her fucking kicked out or reprimanded. It's not a bad idea
Now let me flip it for you. I'm let's say I'm back home. I'm Missouri for Christmas because Lord knows no one here is voting for
I don't think. I don't know. I hope. But, uh, let's say some woman's menu blows over to me.
And she's talking about how much she loves Hillary Clinton. Right. And I'm a big Trump supporter
or whatever. Right. And I go, oh, hell no. You know, I'm not giving you this. Right. Because I'm
voting for Donald Trump. Hillary sucks. I can't give you your menu. But that's the kind of thing
that could make national news. Right. I agree. I agree. This is why I don't vote. I
am not voting. I'm not getting a vote at this. I have to. I think now I have to vote.
I see I see all sides in this because your vote doesn't matter, frankly. Doesn't matter
at all. But things are too dire now to. Well, they're not dire at all. These fucking idiots
all want something to fight about. None of it means anything. I don't think I ever
means everything. I don't think the world changes that much with Trump in the
helm. He's not going to get in the helm. He could get in that helm. He's not
getting that hell. I think so many people are quietly privately going to vote
for him. I disagree. I think that it's just the other way around. All right. I
think people hate Hillary, but but quietly and reserveedly know that she's a
option than Trump and are going to shamefully go and vote for her. I don't mean I'm shaming them. I'm
saying they'll feel ashamed because they talk so much shit about her. Maybe those people won't
vote but I don't know that they're going out to vote for Hillary. There's a lot of women hitting
involved. Very proud to say I've never voted in my life. Never will. I refuse to play this fucking
charade of a bar game. I'm just not doing it. Yeah. I mean this world can have itself. I don't give a
Shit, I get it and that's not apathy folks. It's called a little bit of realism. Okay. Okay. In a world where where Trump is a is one of two candidates
I guess people will say will there are still no, they're not there's two candidates
In a world where Trump is one of them it is hard to want to get out of bed and fucking vote because what what what sort of
Country allows this to happen, you know, look they're conspiracy theorists out there that would say
he was planted in as a means to secure Hillary's election.
I mean, it's insane, it's all these things work.
The whole thing is insane.
It's nuts.
You can't see your smile, you can't see your smile.
But anyway, hey Pat, I'll tell you something.
Few stranger things have I heard of.
than a guy named Trump.
I was just about to say you say Trump's not going to win,
but stranger things have happened.
I had a very similar, I would have been much smoother about it.
It was much smoother.
Well, you're the writer, you know?
The 32nd pause in the middle helped the time
in quite a bit on your then.
I couldn't think of how to, I got in a couple of words
and I realized I started it wrong
and I couldn't get out of it.
And that was the end of it.
Now, but stranger things, and again,
it's going to be a sort of contentious podcast
Yes, because everyone that I knew,
everyone that I saw was raving about it.
I wound up having to wait an additional two weeks to watch it,
because my girlfriend was out of town.
We were gonna watch it together, of course,
with all couples, you wind up not watching it together anyway.
But by the time I finally watched this thing
because people were throwing around words,
yourself included like masterpiece.
Here we go.
Did say it was a masterpiece.
Here we go. Guess who just proved suicide squad's a good movie.
I absolutely did not prove it.
I found myself, of course, enjoying Stranger Things.
It's designed for enjoyment, you know,
that it's an arguably a pretty entertaining thing.
But with the expectations I was given, I was like,
come on, guys, come on.
My issues with it are as follows, really.
It is such a piece of its references to a fault, I would say, Spielberg, Stephen King, etc.
It's all things I love, but it just sort of unenthusiastically checked off the boxes.
It did a nice job of recreating that time period in the 80s, and obviously that's what people
love about it is the nostalgia because if it's a modern day set thing, people would be like,
Yeah, there's nothing really interesting about the story. It is essentially polter guys. Joe Beth Williams did it better
When a writer is going hysterically over the top and ever seen when a writer was fantastic
I won't have you say anything a lesser. I've always loved when a writer and I liked her in this
But found her to be a little wanting. I like the sheriff guy fine. I like the kid with no teeth
I thought 11 was good and the other kids were kind of very generic and didn't I like the sheriff
guy find. That's yeah. That's that's that's what your take is on that. I'm gonna go on through the
characters. I like the sheriff guy find. You know he was great. That's correct. Yes. And you
thought we're not a writer overdid it. Yeah. Thought she overdid it but was also fine. The kids none of
them had enough flavor or comedy to me to really stand out except the kid with a teeth issue.
The alien was extremely boring and generic when it came.
The story every single aspect of the story had been done before and better.
Then when they finally went into the other world, it looked identical to the film under
the skin, which no one has seen with Scarlett Johansson, which I loved.
But they clearly took a screenshot of under the skin and said, now when we go into this
other world, we really have an opportunity to show off and do something original and fresh.
Let's still rip something off and make it something that people haven't seen, which
is a little dodger than ripping off each.
I didn't see under the skin, so what, I was afraid to watch it because of the man with the
face.
No, it's rough.
With the weird face.
It's scary.
It's one of, it was more of my favorite movies of that year.
It's being mean.
It's just that.
Yeah, it's the best.
It upsets me.
But these guys literally took screenshots from under the skin.
But what part when you go into the other world, the black dimension,
so you see the other world cheese from in under this game.
You go into this other dimension.
It is our directed identically.
It is lit identically.
And I was like, guys,
now you have an opportunity to create your own other world.
Do whatever you want.
And you're ripping off the movie from two years ago that nobody saw.
And what I was saying is you want to rip off VT that everyone has seen.
And we're all like, yeah, we know you're ripping off VT.
That's kind of one thing.
That felt a little more
Sleazy to me then ripping that off. I didn't think it had an original thought or idea in it and even I'm saying all this
I didn't think it was very fun
I didn't have the addictive quality to me where I blasted through it all in a night
I was like I can give her take this but I watched it very quickly in the span of a week or two. I
enjoyed it and
Yet I think having it built up that much hurt for me. Well that hurts anything
It does and it's a shame in this internet world
I try to see things as quickly as possible or before they come out because everything you hear taints it
But yeah, it just I
Found it both good and a let down and I would give no episode above like a B -plus
Because I didn't think any any of it
gave me goosebumps or made me like sit up or made me go whoa I got to watch
the next one it all felt like a pleasant time passer and I enjoyed it quite a
bit but didn't think anything about it was exceptional all right well I don't
agree with most of what you said most don't from when I gather I thought I thought
it did an excellent job of being a self -conscious piece. It was almost like a
self -conscious piece within a self -conscious piece. Not only did it take place,
not only did they clearly set out and say we're going to do a horror, thriller,
mystery thing that takes place in the 80s with that 80s vibe, they also managed to
incorporate all of the elements of that time period so brilliantly and so
organically. For instance, she needs lights. Okay, so she needs more lights now. So, okay,
so she gets the Christmas lights. Okay, so what do they look like? Oh, exactly the Christmas
lights from 1983 or whatever year was the orange bulb, the purple bulb, the red bulb, the whatever
multicolored Christmas lights. There's bullies chasing him through the woods. The bullies need to be
menacing. So what's he do? He pulls out a switchblade. Of course he does. What every fucking mean kid
had in his pocket in that time period.
Everything like that in those movies.
Well, in real life, too.
I mean, every kid I knew was obsessed with
getting a switchblade and some of them had them
and some of them didn't.
We used to buy the switchblade combs
and then take the comb out and sharpen the metal part.
But my point is these things were woven so seamlessly
into the fabric of the show.
It didn't, to me, feel like a throwback
back to a 1980s, an early 1980s horror thriller mystery, to me it felt like something that
actually came out of that time period. Even the reference to the movie that they're
going to go see before he goes missing, which is Poltergeist, and the elements that are
related to Poltergeist throughout the show, it was just very, very, very well done in
that. And that was actually pointed out to me in my good dear friend James Pinkstone.
I mean, that made it fun to me, yes, but I think just saying we're going to go see Poltergeist and then ripping off Poltergeist for seven hours.
I don't think they rip off Poltergeist for seven hours.
No, but I mean, there's a lot of it that felt really, really familiar to me.
To me, it did not feel like it was of that time, unless it felt like a lesser movie of that time.
It felt like maybe like a monster squad or one of those that like people have a lot of affection for
But that really at the end of the day is not a classical on the line. No, I just a guy store a disagree
I mean to me it felt like well it is I'm talking more about the book of course sure
I love the movie. I love the movie till the end. I love the movie too
They said that the new it movie will feel like stranger things
By the way, I don't I don't doubt them, but you know why they threw true detective often?
through what the true detective guy off it Gary Fukonawa off of what it the it
remain it's not I didn't even know he was on it he was on it he wanted it to
be two two -hour movies and he wanted to include the teen orgy the child orgy
they he he wanted the movie to be NC 17 and include that graphic long yeah
there's a thing where she like takes all their virginity right right and he was
You know the pact or whatever he was like we're doing that we're making an NC 17
I want it to be two hour and they were like you can't get any of this we're throwing you off the movie
Then they bring in the guy who did mama
And mama to which was okay. I didn't enjoy mama
It was okay. Yeah, exactly. I mean, I didn't love it, but it was fun and
It's I looked at the cast everybody in it is like a Nordic actor. I've never heard of so I was like is this a
Made being made in Sweden or what's going on? Well, I don't think it'll be good frankly
But I hope it's one of my favorite books of all time excited for it
I want to see it the kid from Stranger Things isn't it. Yep. I think Pennywise is far too young
Oh, yeah, the guy they cast is far too young. Yes
But hey, who knows maybe he'll be great, you know when they said yeah
If Ledger was gonna be a Joker. I was like what exactly so we'll see Michael Keaton being Batman people were surprised
But back to Stranger Things. I thought Winona Ryder deserves three Emmys for her work in this
And I don't think it was too much. I think in in
Poltergeist you're dealing with a stable family who's daughter
Disappears they know and have clues as to where their daughter all of them have an idea of where the daughter has gone
And there is some communication with the daughter
Stranger things. Nobody believes the mother. They all think she's crazy. She's fresh off the heels of an abusive alcoholic marriage.
Right. Deadbeat dead. It's a little different. She can't, she can't afford to buy fucking cigarettes. It's like she's.
Yeah, but I liked her in the smaller moment. I liked her performance overall really. I just thought
If you're putting up her scenes against Joe Beth Williams who did almost the exact same material in Poltergeist
I preferred Joe Beth Williams, but it's a different character. It is a different character essentially, but like I liked when she is
Going and she needs an advance on her check and she needs some supplies from the store. Right. I thought that was a great scene. I thought she had
good moments kind of scattered throughout. But you know, I wasn't feeling for her in the way that I felt for the family.
I felt terrible for her. I hugged my TV a few times. I would kiss it. I'd say, okay. I'd say, no need, baby. It's going to be okay.
Yeah. All right.
And she didn't respond, of course, because she didn't, you know, she was a picture moving image, but, you know.
And I thought that I thought the I can't remember the guy's name, but he was in black or a black mass and he was in suicide squad as well
I'm a big fan of that guy though, and I thought he was great. I really enjoyed and I thought he was a great part of the show
I liked
You know who's the guy who looks like oh Matthew Modine look they had him looking like David Kronenberg in that moment
I'm also a big I thought 11 was fantastic. Yeah, but that girl acted in an emotional range that was
beyond my comprehension for which 11 the girl oh yeah okay I saw her in an interview on
Fallon and I was like when I was watching and I looked her up on ID because I was like this girl
has to be older than like 12 hmm she's got too much depth no she is 12 and then I watched her in
interview on Fallon and it's like she's like she's like one of those kids like a grown person she's
sitting there with like her legs crossed and she's like yes that was quite an interesting day on set
you know with this proper English accent yeah but I thought she was great I enjoyed all the kids I
I especially liked whatever the toothless kid's name is.
I liked that for once they made the sort of chunk
in Gooney's character, the guy that becomes
the aggressive leader, the take no shit guy,
instead of him just being the butt of jokes.
Yeah, I guess for me, I think Gooney's is a lot of fun,
but has also kind of gotten overrated with time.
But all those kids had a real flavor and personality to them.
The kids in E .T., same deal, and these kids didn't really jump out to me, and I wish that
I had been more emotionally engaged in stranger things.
I think that would have kept me coming back for more.
I kind of felt throughout like everything's going to be fine.
You know what's going to happen right from the jump, right?
And I didn't feel a lot of suspense or emotional connection to the show while I freely admit
that I enjoyed the show.
I just, you know, in my mind, this is not some crowning achievement of television.
I'll be excited for season two when it comes around.
Now, see, that's where we differ.
Yeah.
That's where we differ.
Uh, I am not, I am not excited, I mean, I'm not not excited about it.
I'm not dreading it, but, you know, I'm not thrilled about the way it ended.
That was my one question.
Oh no.
No, of course not.
I didn't think there should have been a cliffhanger ending and if it was going to be cliffhanger
ending, I would have liked to have seen it executed a little bit differently.
This is one thing that's really bothering me.
When the sheriff gets into the car at the end with the two government officials, immediately
after he says to Winona Ryder, I made a deal.
You get in the car and you realize, oh, God, they're going to kill him now because they have to keep wraps on all this.
And then they don't.
Yeah.
I was like, so wait, no, his deal literally was just, I'm going to turn the girl over to you to get the kids back.
Right.
Which, okay, you got the kids back, but that's still kind of shitty for the girl.
You know what I mean?
because she had decimated it and disintegrated into oblivion or whatever.
And then I thought that was great that she died in this sacrificial way.
And then I was angry, not angry, but I was disappointed to see him putting the
waffles out like, oh, maybe she's still alive, wink, wink. And I guess I thought
it was kind of cool that the kid coughs up that slug or whatever. But what I was
really hoping for was there to be a tight up bow on it, not necessarily happy, but a
tight up ending to the season. And I thought it'd be really cool if they did an American
horror story thing here where Stranger Things season two was new story, new characters,
maybe the same actors playing different characters, different time period. I would have liked that
people love those kids so much that they would not have been into that at all. And it would
It would be a classic case of people watch the first one and they're like, eh, and then
they drop out.
All the one Netflix doesn't release their fucking shit.
You can love those kids all you want.
They're hitting puberty in three weeks.
Yeah.
I mean, they're not going to be those cute kids anymore.
That is also true.
No, they're not going to be bad looking people, I guess, who the hell knows, but my point is
is those voices are going to drop and, you know, that's going to be the end of that.
For sure.
And I'm sure that's why they're rushing this season two in a production.
My other, I think that was, that was a grievance I have with it as well, is that I never really felt the edge and the danger that you feel in an it or, you know, in a lot of these different things.
There was no real edge to it that made me scared.
Like I didn't think it was scary.
I disagree. You know, the scene where he jumps off the cliff, I was the part of me was like,
holy shit, he's going to kill himself like to see, I also, I never felt that danger.
Here's another thing that kind of bugged me about that scene was awesome when she saves him.
I was like, I got chills. That was a good scene for sure. But again, maybe I'm nitpicking,
maybe I'm being a dildo. The thing I thought that was a little disappointing there was,
They set up at the beginning of the show where if somebody I forget what character is claims to have jumped off of that thing the
Cop does and he's like you'd you'd die the other cop is like you would die that'd be like hitting cement
And I thought when he jumped it was gonna be like holy shit. No, you can't do it. Yeah, so I thought it was
So but I guess the setup was like no
He's gonna die here because the cop just said it would be like hitting some man or whatever right but
But I was looking at you my seat when they were hiding the bus and the
Modine people showed up and everything. I liked all that stuff. I thought it was a lot of fun.
When that, what I would say, what are your feelings on Donnie Darko?
You know, I like it. I don't love it. I enjoy it. It's a well -made film.
I really, really, really, really loved it in college and I've seen it probably 10, 15 times.
And still, I think it's a pretty great movie, but there's a scene in this where they go
to their teacher and they're asking him about time travel, and that scene is, again, almost
verbatim from Donnie Darko.
They go to Noel Wiley who's a professor and the flea in the Acrobat thing.
Yeah, Darko keeps asking him those questions and he's telling me, he's like, I don't think
I can talk about this with you anymore, and it's kind of a really cool scene in Donnie Darko, and
Again, I just am watching it like well, this isn't really fair. There were so many moments like that where it was too much
And I think the reason that one bothered me more than the others is that Donnie Darko is to me a movie that approximates the 80s in a much better way
Well, that's a great job of it
I wouldn't do that but I also think it approximates a different time in the 80s and a different perspective. Yeah, it's a me that and again
Stranger things tapped into my child like literally my childhood. I was like maybe there are a couple of years older
But it's like nope. I remember hanging out in that basement. I remember playing that game. I remember that TV set
I remember being excited about this movie coming out like yeah those aspect of it of it I liked
But yes, for sure, but I just kind of felt like every single bit of it I had seen before
and that's a me kept me from ever being fully surprised or fully engaged by it.
Well look, you know, man, it's, it would be disheartening and it would be upsetting, but
it would not be unthinkable or unimaginable that what happened with true detective might
happen with this.
Oh sure you know true detective that we all thought oh my god it's the greatest thing ever and then
Slowly but surely you stood to realize wait a minute that was from this and this was from that and that and then the
Second season came out and people were disappointed and oh we'll see now true now true to detective
I didn't feel any sort of familiar that all felt very fresh to me so what do you tell I thought you met just the season two drop off
Which I'm saying season one felt very fresh to me too. Yeah, but then slowly but surely people went oh you know
That's a reference to those and that's a reference to this so like for instance
Which is maybe smarter was referencing shit that people don't you know the donny the donny dark
Oh, and under the skin references. I wasn't recalling so
Let's go to the questions Pat oh to the phones as they say before before we have to wrap up this episode
We we I finally remember to tweet out and ask for questions today
First question here comes from my friend Danielle
Now, she says, I was interested to hear how you felt about the show taking place in the
80s.
I feel like it was a cool choice for a thriller series.
We kind of discussed that already, and I really like that.
I think there's an element to, there's an element to mystery and suspense and horror that
is certainly affected if not damaged by modern day technology.
You know, yeah, I tweeted about the new ring movie and I was like
You know the movie rings where
Where the ghosts use YouTube and the people are still using corded phones. It's like
It's like it's ridiculous to me. I'm supposed to now think that the girl ghost from the ring was keeping up on like how to upload to YouTube
And they say it's right. It's silly. So I'm gonna take a class at the genius bar or something like that
I mean, yeah, just even the idea of it is like a bad sketch, you know what I mean like so well it could be a great sketch, but I
Actually, I haven't seen the trail yet, but when I heard I was like do we need another ring and then when I heard that they were coming through through viral videos
I was kind of like yeah, all right
I mean of course somebody's gonna pitch that and hopefully they do it well, but maybe they won't yeah
How does it get from the video tape online maybe somebody up?
I guess somebody uploaded it. I guess that's probably the yeah the the simplest idea is somebody uploaded it
And then they died and now they can't find the user to take it down or whatever and it's there
I already feel like they made and they made it for about 50 grand pretty much the perfect viral video horror movie
Which is unfriended. Did you see that?
No, it looked like an MTV sort of teen it is to me, but it is I think it's I think it's on HBO on demand or HBO go it's
They did it so cheap like I would be surprised if it did cost $50 ,000 and
It's really suspenseful and the entire movie is on your computer screen basically
Which is a gimmick that somehow doesn't get old and it's actually really scary. I would recommend watching it. All right
I'll check it out a couple quick questions here at TOSIS most hated
TOSAS most hated he asks what's your favorite Stephen King book or movie?
my fast answer to that movie wise is wait we've talked about this yeah it's two
different questions I mean the mist is the mist or misery are my two favorite
Stephen King movies misery is my number one for sure but I thought the mist was
fucking fantastic of course I love Shawshank I love Green Mile I mean I think a lot
of great stand by me stand by me to me as well it's wonderful obviously a major
influence on. Wonderful. Yeah, major influence. But as far as book goes, I would probably go with one of his giant ones like it or the stand.
Just because he keeps you reading for that long. And those those are in his culture of days.
But I just think those are terrific stories that have like millions of good ideas in them. It and the stand.
My favorite Stephen King book is Skelton Crew because I like anthology are best.
It's a collection of really amazing short stories.
I think the mist is in that book.
I get it mixed up sometimes with the other one.
Graveyard shift?
Graveyard shift, different seasons.
But anyway, Skelton Crew is great.
It's got the jaunt in it.
It's got survivor type.
Really, it's got the monkey.
It's a great fucking book. So check that out. Great bedtime reading.
Okay, at Lucifer Brews asks us to discuss a remake. Oh wait, no, that's for that's for the don't breathe episode. Excuse me.
I'm sorry. At ham underscore dinner. That's a great handle. When
known as never been better, this should be a good app. Well,
thank you. I hope it was. We're all disagrees though. I do
disagree that she's never been better, but I do like her. I've
always liked her. I actually sat next to her once at the new
Beverly for a screening of the goonies. Really? Shortly after
she was arrested for shoplifting. We did not hook up. But I've
I've always been extremely attracted to her.
Well, she's just there, like literally you sat next to her.
So I sat down and my buddy who I was with was like,
are you sitting next to her?
We're known a rider and I'm like,
I'm gonna go ahead and say no.
And I turned and it was going to run.
Jesus.
Who was she with?
Like a boyfriend, yeah.
Honky dude.
At Clive Gulch, which is G -U -L -C -H.
So Stranger Things equal Star Wars and Raiders
in synthesizing its influences, discuss.
I don't think I understand what that means.
I think what he is saying is that Indiana Jones
took from all those cereals and gunged in
and all this shit and made it into a seamless blend
and Star Wars was using Kurosawa and all that shit
and blended them all together.
I think though, I mean, I maybe Joe agrees with you.
I do not, although I definitely see your point,
but I think that those movies were both synthesizing all kinds of different things and even different styles and genres and making them into something fresh and new, like the invented, obviously Star Wars gives you Darth Vader and the Stormtroopers and the other other shit that is not in the Seven Samurai.
I think what Stranger Things does is essentially just say you like this, here's the same thing.
It did blend them in in a fairly smooth way and people like what they saw
But I think a lot of those people who are really loving it never saw the things that influenced it
I hate to say this you're you're you're slightly turning me on stranger things
I don't want to do that and I hate that that's what's happening. I don't want to do that, but I hope that people
Especially people watching it with their kids are checking out
The shit that inspired it because I think it's a lot of really really great stuff
A guy I work with watched it with his sons and he said that they must have asked 50 times
why they're not using their cell phone to call home.
Like it's just stuff you forget about.
I think a lot of people's love for Stranger Things is for an nostalgia both for those great
movies and books and for the time period of the 80s.
Which I get.
That's why I liked it too.
Last but not least at tone underscore Berg T .O .N .E. underscore B .E .R .G. says still loving we'll see you in hell. Thank you
Thank you close your eyes Joe DeRose a comedy equals Lewis Black
Patrick Wallace equals Neil Brennan slash Jerry Seinfeld
Right, I've been a two of my favorite comedians ever I know I don't think of Neil Brennan and Jerry Seinfeld as sounding alike
I wouldn't shake a stick at any of those people. I'm taking off. That's this episode stay tuned for episode two
which is going to be don't breathe. We're covering that and that'll be out in the next week or so or two weeks whenever the hell it is
plugs time to plug things. I am going on the road. If you live in Minnesota, I'll be in
some casino
comedy club up there. Lake something. Twin cities.
something with the lakes, something lake casino comedy club.
Okay, well, I'm sure they appreciate your glowing endorsements.
They're happy they're paying you for this great publicity.
It's, you know what?
I'll do my plug second.
Why don't you do yours and let me figure out what the hell this,
where the hell this thing is.
I mean, unfortunately, I got nothing to plug.
I got no shows coming up.
I did the high and mighty podcasts.
I like giving shout outs to other podcasts.
my buddy John Gabriel is one of the funniest people on earth. He does a podcast called High
and Mighty where you know it's implied that you get stoned but it's not like getting
high with Doug where you have to and you talk about a subject that you love and him
and I talked about Vegas and gambling. We had a blast that should be out within the next
week. Alright I got it here. Friday September 9th, Saturday September 10th I will be in Minneapolis
at the Mystic Lake Casino, they got a comedy club inside that place and that's
where I'll be. Falling week, I'll be in Arizona, Scottsdale, stand up Scottsdale
starting Thursday and going through Saturday and then October 13th here in
beautiful sunny Los Angeles. I will be shooting my special, my debut comedy
central one -hour special. So if you're in L .A. keep your eye out links should be
hitting the web pretty damn soon for that. I will be there. Pat, you'll be there.
Come here, there's your bigger goal. And yeah, that's it. I guess, right?
Joe DeRosa County on Twitter. Deep Patrick Walls, buying Twitter
Instagram and you know, maybe we'll talk with Kim. We'd love to be at
you know, check out some sort of horror thing coming up heads we head into the Halloween season.
So if you got a horror festival, a film festival, anything, let us know. We had it such a blast
last year and we'd love to do it again. And thanks for your comments. Thanks for your ratings and
iTunes. Thanks for your questions today. Keep at it folks. Thank you very much. Thanks for your
downloads and stop by and check out my fiction column on fangoria .com. Some severe situations.
questions, and know that we'll see you in hell as a presentation of the Fangoria podcast
network produced by Thomas DeFail, executive produced by Ken Hanley, a Fangoria entertainment
for press opportunities, advertising inquiries, all information about we'll see you in hell.
Contact Ken at his email, Kennetfangoria .com.
You