Folks, it's We'll See You in Hell. Here we are, back to talk to you about a movie called
Possession. I'm Joe DeRosa. And my name is Patrick Walsh. Hello, everybody, and welcome
to We'll See You in Hell. We are discussing the film Possession, the 1981 -2 film? By a
guy whose name I can't really pronounce. A movie about male -female relations gone wrong.
Gone quite wrong, folks. Andres Zulowski. I don't want to blow up your spot, but you
texted me that you had a weird date. Oh, yeah. I was hoping to hear the story. I was hoping
you'd share it with us. I will tell you before you even tell your story. I met someone very
recently for a drink that I had to say, I am putting you in a car to go home. She was
that drunk? I don't even know if she was drunk. She was obnoxious. She told me that I would
be paying for her car home earlier in the conversation. I'm sorry? Wait, how did that
come up? She just brought that up? By the way, you're going to pay for my car? Not in that moment.
I still gave it a shot. But once I watched her do a shot of tequila that she ordered and then
sternly tell the bartender she never received her shot, she literally walked back to me from
doing that. It was like a sitcom moment. I had my phone open and I go, so what's your address?
Like I had the app open. It put in the coordinates. Yeah, and still had the audacity to be like,
what? What are you talking about? We're having such a good time. I was like, I'm going to call
tonight. I'm going to go home. I wish you well. Take care. Yeah. Haven't spoken to her. No text
after that from her? I know not to her. Why would you thank a man for getting you a hundred dollar
Uber? I'm in shock that she said, you're buying me this. I don't even mind at the end of the night
or something like, hey, do you mind splitting this? And I would pay for it kind of regardless,
I'm sure. But it's like the demand is insane. Yeah, I've many times paid for an Uber or whatever.
It was the demand. That was the least audacious thing she said to me that night. So you can only
imagine. I won't get into the details just in case God forbid this person listens to the show.
I don't think they do, but yeah, I'm in the same boat where I'm going to have to leave a lot unsaid.
But this day last night was off that one of the apps and I met her at Bordeners where you and I
have hung our crowns many a night, kind of a nicer dive bar. Yeah, we're having pranks code for the
glory hole in the bathroom. Yeah, we're doing drinks. She has three martinis to my two drinks,
you know, she, you know, she's, she's drinking and not crazy, but drinking. And I noticed her
getting, I was like, that's like six regular drinks, three gin martinis, kind of fast gin. Yeah.
Ankh baby. Jesus Christ. Not calling her a tank. I'm saying tank, right? Yeah.
Pat was out with earth a kit.
She was, she was very attractive, very funny, cool, nice, smart, et cetera. But as the night
went on, it's not like she was slurring, but she was getting very argumentative about things that
we had no business arguing about. Really weird shit. Yep. And everything was bothering her and
everything I said, she would tell me the opposite. We had an argument at one point where she insisted
that diet Coke is just as good for you as water. And it's got this bad marketing around it. And
everyone should just be drinking diet Coke all the time. She's like, it's got no calories. I go be,
you know, she went to, you know, you went to an Ivy league school. You don't know that.
You don't know that honestly, you don't know that this is bad. Like you've never seen it
disintegrate, uh, something in a glass, like they do the science experiments.
Yeah. That's like, that sounds like a Felicity Huffman scenario. The kid was shuffled in with
a payoff to it. Yeah, for sure. For sure. Anyway, um, for sure. But the time I'm having a kind of
worst time as it goes because of all the arguing and I sort of missed the person I met at the
beginning of the night who I really liked, but I was like, okay, she's getting kind of drunk.
It's getting kind of weird. Then I started talking about, um, well, she mentioned, uh,
an actor that she had met at one time. I said, oh, you know, that guy's got a little bit of a
me too situation on his hands coming up. She goes, did you not just hear me say that I met him once
and that he was nice to me? But hand on my hand, like that level of condescension, like, did you
just not hear me say that? And I go, yeah, I don't care. I go, I've met him before and he was nice
to me too, but I'm telling you something that happened. That's not nice. And she's scolding me
about it. She goes, aren't you trying to be a writer in Hollywood and you're going to sit here
trying to be a writer? I was like, she was winding me up. And, uh, the actor in question,
eventually I got kind of so heated in this and she was sort of raising her voice at me.
And I said, you're now a woman yelling at me to believe men that, you know, like,
I don't understand why you're defending a guy because you met him once and he was nice to you.
It doesn't make any sense. And no backing down, complete stubbornness. And I said, you know what?
I didn't, wasn't going to put her in a car, but I said, I'll take you home. We go outside. I was
going to walk her the two blocks to her place. I got to tell you, and you can only learn from
experience. Yeah. I've been down this road and many times I didn't get the car and many times I said,
I should have got the car. Oh yeah. You can only learn by not getting the car and going,
God damn it. She was, she was two blocks away. No, I mean like get the metaphor of like
getting out of there. I've got you the car. Take care of yourself. See you later. Yeah, exactly.
Down the road. Yeah. I had, you know, I have a thing. It was on Hollywood Boulevard. So you're
like, I don't want to be a piece of shit and make this girl walk home three blocks at midnight or
whatever. So I say, yes, but she goes, let's get your car. You got to get it off the street.
I drive us over parking her parking garage. She's got this key fob thing. Go upstairs.
We have a couple more drinks. I notice as I'm looking about the place that she is doing shots
in the kitchen, like private shots, not hiding it exactly, but not offering me shots. She sees me
looking. I go, no, I go, it's 1230. I have to drive home. I'm not looking for a shot. And she's
like, you're not driving home. So I'm like, okay, all right. So the vibe starts getting flirty,
making out. We're on the couch, you know, and I'm like, I'm kind of coming around on this person
because we weren't talking anymore. We weren't arguing, having a nice time and a really great
conversation. And she had a adorable dog who like didn't bark at all, which was great. Just having
a really nice time. And I'm like, okay, this is working again. I can sort of see how this is
happening here. I go, do you mind if I stay here? She goes, yeah, you're staying here.
I go, okay, my car is good in the garage. Yes. So she goes in to the bathroom, gets cleaned up.
I lay down. I'm in, you know, skivvies, comes out of the bathroom, naked, gets on me, straddles me.
She goes, okay, this is happening. Meaning sex. Now imagine if I were to get atop a woman and say,
this is happening on a first date. Imagine if you were to get atop a man and say it, it's a problem.
Um, this is happening. And I laughed like out of disbelief. And I realized that there was no
humor coming out of her. She was like, this is happening. And I, I'm just going to be graphic
with you here. She goes, now you're going to fuck me real good right now, but I want you to know
that after tonight, that's probably it. I said, okay, actually brought up the text that I sent my
friend this morning because I wanted to make sure I got the wording exactly right. It was ringing
in my ears. Uh, okay. Now you're going to fuck me real good, but I want you to know after tonight,
it's probably it. So I laugh and I go, okay. Uh, any reason why, any reason why she goes,
well, Patrick, you get it, right? I mean, I hate this woman so much.
I go, what? Tell me. I go, I go, I go, that's fine. But why, why could we only hook up one time?
She goes, I mean, you're going to make me say it. I go, yeah, now I'd really like you to say it.
She goes, well, I mean, you're in nobody.
Wow. She is naked sitting on my dick. Look fabric dick. That's not out, but I'm just like,
what in God's name? I couldn't believe it. You are nobody. I respect it. That's wild.
I respect that wild. That is she. And by the way, no judgment at all, but this person was living
in a cluttery one bedroom apartment off Hollywood Boulevard. No judgment. What do you mean? No,
yeah, it's judgment. You're, you're, yeah, she's awful. Judge, judge. No, no, no, no. I'm saying
I'm not judging that she lives in a one bedroom apartment. I'm saying, how dare you, like, how
dare you look literally looking down on me while saying it? I'm just like, and I wanted to get
defensive and be like, don't you, I've done all kinds of things. And I'm like, just go home, Pat.
I get up, I start getting dressed. I felt like a, a gooma the morning after.
And she's, and I'll have to tell you these off, off camera, Joe, but let me just say that
things got more insulting from there. As I was packing up to leave, he was hitting me with some
stuff. I'm like, holy shit. I don't know if her thing was like, let me get daddy mad, or I don't
know what the deal was, but I also knew I did not want to be a part of it. So I left. She's yelling
to neighbors. He can't even get it up anymore. It was up. That was the most frustrating part.
I was like, all right, we'll see you later. So I leave as I'm leaving. She's like, you're leaving.
Like, yeah, shut the door. And then I hear her go, like, are you fucking kidding me behind the
door? What an awful, awful person that expected to be like, Oh, thank you, mommy. I get to have sex
with you. Exactly. Yeah. As, as, uh, Queens, the Stone Age once saying counter proposal, I go home
and jerk off. One of my favorite lyrics of all time. But I mean, I, so I'm not, I'm not quite
done. I shut the door. I hear go, are you fucking kidding me? I go down and I'm like, okay, where
am I? Cause remember I'm kind of stumbling home with her and now it's four in the morning.
So I'm like, all right, not where, where was my car, whatever. I'll just go down all the
way to the park. I go down and I realized Joe that I have left my phone in the apartment.
I go up, I'm knocking. I get nothing. I go down. I'm like, I'm going to have to call on the,
on the intercom thing. I go down to the parking garage. I dial her a thing because I had her code
at least no answer. Like this thing in her apartment. She's passed out drunk probably.
So I'm sitting there and I was getting to my car and I'm like, all right, well I'll head out
and get the phone tomorrow. It'll be awkward, but oh, well I pull up $45 to get out. Cause she used
her key fob thing, but I don't have that key fob. It's an apartment building. $45 to get out. It's
one of those, it's Hollywood Boulevard. It's like, you know, what? Yeah. They, they do the, uh, if
you have no ticket, you owe for the whole day thing. So of course I had no ticket.
But you were knowing a public parking garage.
Well, no, but it's one of those giant Hollywood Boulevard apartment complexes.
I've never heard. That's interesting. I've never heard of that.
No, that happens here. So I pay the 45, put it on the credit card, head out.
Just driving home, just like, holy shit. And I had stayed in there too because I was waiting
for her to hopefully come down or something. So I get home, I got a meeting at eight. So I'm like,
I'm just going to stay up, try to power through it. I had two meetings in a row, then my job.
Now this with Joe, but I text her and I go, I text her, um, with my laptop. Cause I knew she had my
phone and I go, Hey, um, this is a little awkward, but I got to come by and get my phone today.
Sorry about that. She's like, Oh, okay. Um, do you have any idea where it is? I don't see it.
I said, well, you threw my pants across the room. So my guess is it flew out the pocket.
So she found it in some weird corner or something. And then, um, she's like,
uh, LOL, that's embarrassing. Let me know when you want to come pick it up. Okay. Great.
Then I go, Hey, do you have any recollection of saying really fucked up shit to me last night,
right before I left. And she goes, Oh, text comes back. Uh -oh. She's like, Oh no. Oh no. What did,
actually she never asked. What did I say? Very interesting in her head. It was probably a good
date. Like she doesn't even know this is a, this is a, this is a heavy level of a, of an alky here.
Exactly. And she goes, Uh -oh, uh, what did I say? What did I do? Whatever. And actually,
I just did it again. I said that because that's what I would say in the situation. She never
asked me what she said. I said, you said a lot of fucked up shit to me. She never asked what,
what it was, which is crazy unless she was just, she knew she'd be ashamed of it.
But, um, she's like, I'm sorry. I had an adderall and I just cannot mix alcohol and adderall.
I'm like, if you cannot mix them, then why would you have eight drinks and shots?
Yeah, just insane. So no recollect. I just went over now right before I met you. I had to speed
over there to Hollywood Boulevard, get my sweet phone back. She apologized. I did. It's not like
I feel bad for her, but it's like, good Lord, you know, like just give me a few boring dates
for Christ's sake. You'll learn next time. Probably not next time. Probably about seven
more of those. Then eventually you'll go, I'm just going to go home.
Yeah. I mean, listen, I went home the second somebody called. At least I knew that it's time
to go home when a naked woman calls you a nobody while straddling you. That's, that's at least that
registered as this is a moment where you need to go home. That's truly incredible. That's truly
incredible. What a terrible, terrible, uh, I think I can use the word bitch in this scenario. This is,
she's a bitch. Sure. That's terrible. Um, you know, actually she has, let's say she has a problem.
She's an alcoholic. We don't have to call her names. All right. All right. We'll call her
something nice, like an alcoholic. Pat's better than me. Everybody stop. Well, again, I'm like,
if she's listening now, like that's the part she'd be bothered by that someone she doesn't know
called her a bit. I, I, I own that. I am the one that said, bitch. Yes. Chris rock just got a note.
He's getting like slack because he referred to Jada Pinkett as a bitch, uh, on the special.
And it's like, guys, you know, maybe he's a little angry, you know, maybe we,
well, like what, what they, what, why, why are curse words a problem now? We're,
it's beyond the fifties. We're losing bitch now. He said that, uh, he said that people said it was
a misogynistic term. He says, yeah, he says in the special, he goes, people said I was punching
down on her. I'm paraphrasing. People said I was punching down on her. He goes, she started it with
me. She criticized me publicly for hosting the Oscars the year that she expected me to boycott
because his shitty movie concussion didn't get nominated. And he goes, he goes, I didn't,
something like, I didn't start nothing with this bitch. She started it with me.
Like the most benign way to say bitch even, you know what I mean? Outside of like, yes, bitch.
But I'll, I'll save it. That's my first movie corner, but I can wait to talk about it.
People are out of control, dude. People are out of control. It's a bad scene. I sent you a post
today. I can't see who. I don't know if you saw it. Oh no. Cause it's on your phone. Damn. Well,
now I have my phone. I got it back right before this, but just people calling themselves hot
all the time now at Instagram and yeah, body positivity, a lot of body pause. I say this all
the time. That's not body positivity. Taking the toxic version of a thing, like the toxic thing we
did and bending it to mean more people. Right. Or to include more people is not body positivity.
Yeah. Like, like you, if you're falling out of your clothes and out of shape and whatever,
and you go, I'm hot. And you want the same results of saying you're hot that a traditionally like hot
model would get first. That's not body positivity. You just want the reward. The other person got
you criticism. How about we don't need adulation from other people. How about that? You know,
maybe that's a thing, but find your strength within, you know, it's just wild stuff, man.
It is Joe. It is what's going on in the world of movies. What we talk about.
Yeah. Let's get off of this before it turns into two guys, two single men in my day.
Uh, a woman knew her for me.
Movie. Well, let's go to the movie corner. I'll start with, uh, I'll start with,
with, uh, Chris Rock, you know, this big event special. Yeah. Finally happened. Uh, only an hour,
right? It felt like a tight hour. It felt like more than an hour to me. I also have no attention
span anymore. So sure. Same here. Uh, selective outrage. I actually did get to see the full thing
with like the pre show and the post show and all. I didn't see the post show. I saw the pre show
thing. I heard the post show is one of the great train wrecks of recent time. Like it's a night
just off the rails. Well, if it was worse than the pre show. Yeah. That's astounding.
Who was on that? I think post was like Dana Carvey and Snoop Dogg or something.
It was Spade and Carvey. Okay. I'm saying this like I know them, but, uh, and then Kareem Abdul -Jabbar
because you want to bring him into a comedy. Yeah. Always funny. Uh, you know, he might be,
I don't know. It's just a weird choice. Yeah. Uh, um, I don't know who else, but the pre show
was hosted by my buddy, Ronnie Chang, who I felt very bad for because it just seemed like,
it just seemed like, like when you got to do like a thing at your friend's wedding.
Yeah. And they're like, we're going to have a roast at the reception, like that kind of thing.
You're like, yeah, I guess. Okay. I'll host it. And like, it's just awkward and whatever,
but he did a good job. Um, that said the show, the pre show was, I gotta be careful here. Uh,
cause this is really close to the vest and the business I work in. And I know some people that
were on the pre show. Uh, but it was one of the worst things I've ever seen in my life. I mean,
Ronnie hosts it. Then it goes to, he throws to Dion Cole, who is pretending to DJ for some reason.
Yeah. Not a strong bit. Yeah. It wasn't a bit. It wasn't even a bit. It was just,
he was just pretending to DJ like there was no Jones. Very funny. He is. Yeah. And I thought,
Oh cool. Dion's going to say funny things now. And instead he just sincerely talked as if he
been surprised with the question of what Chris Rock has taught him in the business. Yeah. Then
it went back to Ronnie, right? He did a couple more joke, joke, joke, you know, Netflix is,
and all the jokes are kind of like Netflix is evil. Ha ha ha. You know, and you're like,
enough of that fucking shit. You're doing it. Don't also like, I love when people call that
brave too. Like they're not getting paid. Well, there was a good joke where it was like
Netflix, like this is the biggest streaming event in history. We'll never know if that's true or
not. Ha ha ha. Like about how they don't show you their numbers. Right. And I was watching this
with a friend of mine and I turned to him and I go, that's like so depressing to me that like,
that's like, that's the point of corporate servitude we're at where it's like,
we know that the, this big corporation is doing this fucked up thing
by not giving us information and we're just recognizing it and moving on. Like it's just
sad to me. Anyway. Yeah. Um, then he brings out Arsenio Hall, uh, who I'm a fan of, but
Arsenio actually told sort of a funny story that had no ending and then went on to talk
about how Chris Rock is going to kill tonight. I hope you're all ready. Okay. Then they brought
out Leslie Jones, who told the story about Chris Rock helping her get SNL, which again felt like
she was asked while running an obstacle course to tell a story about Chris Rock. Like it was so
off. Like there was no rehearsal, like just not, I was like,
wait a minute. She's not setting up the big punchline. Like, and then like,
why didn't she not explain what that part, man? It's like, did anybody rehearse this?
Then JB smooth comes in and does like a bit, which did kill, but it wasn't very funny, but
does a bit about like, I'm here to see Chris. And the bit is like, Chris isn't here. Like Chris is
Baltimore. You're at the laugh factory in LA, but at least JB's thing and Ronnie's things were
like rehearsed and written, you know? Then they played a video of celebrities on their iPhones
talking about how much of a genius Chris Rock is. Oh my God. Walsh, you want to talk about the
moment you see something jump the shark. Now this had already jumped the shark, but if you want a
real jump the shark moment, it's the moment in the Chris Rock pre -show during the celebrity
dick washing montage that Anthony Kiedis pops up and then brings his teenage son onto his iPhone
video to do bits about Chris Rock. This thing was so bad, right? Yeah. They come back, they
throw to Spade and Carvey to tease the thing. They were, Spade was funny and then Carvey started
doing Joe Biden and it was bombing and it was awkward. I'm not saying that to shit on Dana
Carvey, but it was, that's just what happened. Then it came back. Then they announced the special.
I hope you're all ready. This man is going to do X, Y, and Z and you're not ready and blah,
blah, blah, blah, blah. Oh, and then at another point they cut to the stars of tomorrow of the
Comedy Store who are all here. Because of Chris Rock. To stand up or to wave? No, to all scream
and cheer like cheerleaders in a room. A couple people in that room that you've told me you thought
were funny. I won't get into it. Look, I try to find some people funny to get through the day.
Anyway, then it cuts to the special. Special starts with a black and white thing of now
I have met Chris Rock. I am not friends with him. He's always been sort of nice to me when I meet
him. He's never been rude to me or anything, but also why the fuck does he even need to talk to
me? I haven't had any great interactions with him, but he's nice. I respect Chris greatly as a comic
and quite frankly as a pillar of the standup community. Tony, his brother, is a friend of
mine. I'm not trying to talk out of school here in any way, but there was this big thing where
he's walking down this hallway in slow motion in black and white and it's playing clips of his
old bits and it's so serious and whatever. This is a commentary on the culture, not on him.
I'm just over. I'm over this the cool kids know all the cool kids thing that we do.
I'm over this like we're all over here, successful, money, this and that. Look at us all telling each
other we're great. I'm a genius. Look at me. It's just too much. There's no humility in any of it.
There's just no fucking humility in any of it. Now, this is also a guy who just got slapped on
international television a year ago. Maybe his thing was like, I'm going to come out here like
a boss and whatever. I tried to keep in mind throughout this whole thing, this guy probably
has some form of PTSD from that incident. It's traumatic. Anyway, the special in and of itself,
not his best. He had some great bits in it. There were five bits or so in it that I was like, wow,
classic Chris Rock. That's really funny. He did a thing about Elon Musk. You know who's never
worried? Elon Musk. You know what he does when he makes a million dollars? He gets his dick sucked
and did a whole thing about the shortage of Elon Musk cum because of all the women sucking his
dick. He was like, there's a six month wait list for Elon Musk cum. There were some really funny.
Oh boy, I bet Elon was sitting at home loving that shit.
Yeah, probably. There were some really, really funny like classic Chris Rock style bits.
There was a thing about Lululemon saying they're not racist. We don't hate anybody. He's like,
$100 yoga pants. You hate somebody. He's like, I'd rather have $20 yoga pants than got some racism.
Yeah.
And then the moment, but a lot of it was just stuff that was less
riveting to me. But he had some really killer bits in it. But also too, he's doing it live.
And again, there's a lot of moving parts to this. And then at the end, he goes in real hard
on Will Smith, like real hard. He had some funny lines in there. People keep asking me,
did he hit me hard? Did it hurt? He's like, I still hear summertime ringing in my ears.
And then it got a little more serious, less punchlining about Will Smith and a little more
tacky, which I thought was cool. I'm like, yeah, fuck it. Go in on this guy. I liked that he did it.
So overall, it was an experience watching it. Again, I thought there was some really
killer material in it. But it's hard anymore not to see the moving parts of all this.
It's like, I sat there wondering if it wasn't for, there had to be a time frame on this.
It was very obviously a result impartial to the Will Smith slap. Chris Rock is going to
do the first ever live stream, live special on Netflix. And he's going to actually finally
publicly address this for the first time. There's a time limit on it. You got to do it,
you can't do it less than a year out or more than a year out.
And I just wondered, I was like, some of this material, maybe it wouldn't have been in here
if we didn't turn it into this event. And as impressive and as interesting as the event
ended up of itself is, I felt like the event becomes the focus instead of the product. And
that's why I didn't like everybody coming out and being like, he's a genius. It's like, guys,
we all know this. That's why we're here. He's proven himself. I don't need a bunch of other
famous rich people telling me that. It makes me feel bad and really left out. So anyway,
Chris, the USA Today critic gave it what I thought was a very, very unfair and scathing review
as if she had sort of half listened to it. Some of the stuff she was referencing,
I'm like, that's not what he said. Like, what are you talking about?
That happens more and more with criticism now. I think because they pay so little and so many
people had to leave the industry altogether, and newspapers are going under and magazines are going
under that we just have shitty people writing now. Well, it's that and then it's also people
like this just happened with it went viral. This female critic or I don't know if she's female,
she might be non -binary, but she presents as a woman at at Wired did this like one out of 10
gave a one out of 10 to the new Harry Potter game. Yeah. And the whole review was focused on
JK Rowling. And it was to a point that other outlets were like, this is not how you were.
You're not here to talk about that. You're here to talk about this fucking game that like
1000 people worked on. Right. And it went viral and whatever. But I think what that critic did
is an example of what a lot of critics are doing nowadays where they're going,
he doesn't deserve a good review. Why should he get a good review? He said he called Jada
Pinkett Smith a bitch. He made a joke about trans people. He said this, he said, whatever the hell
the issue is. Right. And they go, I'm not going to give because they don't deserve a good review.
And it's like, but that's not what a critic is there to decide. Right. You know, what's her name?
What was the Scorsese? Pretend it's a city. What's her name?
Fran Lebowitz. Yeah. She put it best in that thing when she talked about like, you know,
when she was like, this guy's a great writer. He's also a complete pervert and a horrible man,
you know, but that's not what I'm talking about. I'm talking about his writing, you know?
Yeah. So I don't know. And this is coming from somebody that had a major that closed,
I closed my special with a bit about the the awfulness of people not separating the art from
the artist. And I've really kind of turned on that because it swung so far in the other direction
at this point. Yeah. So anyway, you ever tried to separate the fart from the fartist?
That's the title of my new special. Brian Poseyne did it or he did it when the artist came out. He
it anyway. So anyway, Chris Rock's new special, I think it's worth a watch.
You know, I can't say you'll like it or not like it. But I'd say there's some there's some
good stuff in there. I rewatched anger management. Oh, terrible. Wait, the movie, not the Charlie
Sheen, the entire Charlie Sheen series. Never seen the series 100 episodes shot in like three
weeks. No, I never saw that show. It's better than the movie. Really? That's how bad I think
that movie is. But it's unquestionably a bad film. I had only seen in the theater and remember
liking it, I guess more than Little Nicky, but less than pretty much everything else that he did.
And Jack Nicholson is actually I think awesome in this kind of broad stupid comedy. He's very
like perfect for it in a way that when they tried to do like that Seth Rogen, Barbara Streisand movie,
she's not good at it. Like some of these older generation people don't handle the new humor.
Nicholson I thought was funnier than Adam Sandler in this movie. Sandler is playing it way too
straight for me. You got John C. Reilly as a monk because literally half the plot of the movie is
Adam Sandler trying to keep his girlfriend, Marisa Tomei, from fucking Alan Covert
because he has a legendarily huge dick. She has no interest in this man.
It's just her friend, but it's a big driving thing in the plot is like I've got to keep
my girlfriend from experiencing the glory of this guy's giant penis. Now there is a shot in the movie
where an obese cat, because Adam Sandler's job is designing clothes for obese cats,
does a double take upon seeing Alan Covert's penis in his khakis and that made me laugh out loud.
A fat cat doing a double take at a bulge in a man's pants is unquestionably funny, but
the movie does not make sense. So the people in the anger management group are you got John
Turturro, Louise Guzman. He always stacks these casts and then gives all these amazing people
very little to do. So you have Woody Harrelson playing in a scene. You revisit a comedy from
six months ago. There's stuff in it that would never fly now. Woody Harrelson is in full drag
playing a sex worker who Nicholson buys to fuck Adam Sandler. Then Harrelson gets into the car.
He's dressed as a woman. He looks horrible and he goes, he's talking in a German accent.
Woody thought the character needed a little goose thing. Wasn't quite big enough.
He does a horrible German accent. Harrelson can't do it. That's it. He's Iowa or whatever.
That's it. A hundred percent. Yeah. I have never seen him as out of his element as in this movie.
I've never seen him where I thought he was bad until now. He's really bad in this.
You got Rudy Giuliani giving a supporting performance, which nobody could have expected.
It's like when I went back and watched Jack and Jill, because I had never seen it,
Jared Fogel makes a cameo appearance. I'm sure around that time Sandler's crew was like,
stop with the cameos of the moment. But the premise is so stupid and so convoluted.
Adam Sandler is not an angry man. He has an incident on a plane where he accidentally hits
a flight attendant. So he gets sent sentenced by a judge like in a 1950 sitcom to anger management.
Then Nick, he goes to get the anger management and Nicholson is the teacher,
the same guy who was next to him on the plane. I know that and you're waiting for him to reveal
that it was a setup. Yeah. And it never happens. It never happens to the extent that you think
maybe it came out of the script at some point. But I'm like, if that's just a coincidence,
that's the stupidest thing. Honestly, that seems like a note, like we got to get Nicholson in this
sooner or something like that. If we're paying him 20 million, get him in there sooner. But
it makes the whole movie confusing. It doesn't make sense. Then Nicholson suddenly fucking
Marissa Tomei by the end of the movie. You're like, what's going on? What are you doing?
The one funny line in it that my friend John Kensel pointed out was funny is when Nicholson
talks about tormenting the girl when he was a child and he goes, I told her she had ghosts
under her dress. That's a funny line. I thought the movie, honestly, I thought it had several
laughs. It was funnier than I remembered, I think, because of how bad comedy's gone. But
it's just really bad and really stupid. Like Nicholson making him sing, I feel pretty in the
car. It's like, what is this scene? Why is this happening? I get that two men singing a song is
funny. What got us here? Do a little bit of work. So yeah, it was a let down. Sandler sometimes
goes way too lazy for me. But I'd put this actually closer to his middle range. I used to put it near
the bottom, but it's better than click. It's better than a lot of shit that he's done.
What do you got, Joe? And this is a movie, by the way. It's called Anger Management. It's about two
men that have anger issues. And it stars Adam Sandler and Jack Nicholson. And they get zero
laughs out of that element of the movie. Nobody is better at getting angry and funnier at getting
angry than Adam Sandler. And nobody's better at it than Jack Nicholson. And you get zero laugh.
You're waiting for it. You're like, oh, we're going to get all these scenes where Sandler's like,
oh, shit. And doing all the funny outburst stuff. And it never happens.
It never happens because he's not that angry. The entire premise of the movie is flawed.
He's not an angry guy. I guess the pitch was he's a guy sentenced to anger management who's not that
angry. And Nicholson is an anger management teacher who is. But that is not a movie. That's
ridiculous. I don't know. It's clearly one where they just went for the jokes and didn't pay
attention to anything else. But so be it. Sometimes just seeing the cameos are kind of fun. They had
fucking Heather Graham in here playing. She's revealed to be a sex worker. There's so many
prostitutes and porn stars in this movie. Nicholson pays her to go home with Sandler. And then that
bit where she's like, you think I'm fat, don't you? While she looks amazing in a bikini.
Do you remember that bit? No, you wouldn't because it has no business being in the movie,
but it ends with Heather Graham, like throwing a plate of brownies at Adam Sandler. And you're
like, why did this supermodel have a plate of brownies out at her house? Like there's so many
questions I had that were just were not answered. But carry on. Hopefully that criterion anger
management 4K director's cut will answer it. Which has all 100 episodes of the show as a
special feature. That would be a good criterion bonus feature for once. My theme will be streaming
thanks to HBO Max and Pat's login. I have finally started watching Friends. I never watched it when
it was on. Oh, yes. I'm enjoying the show. It's very funny. It's a killer cast of six people on
taste buds. We just battled Seinfeld versus Friends and I took friends. I took team friends
and I enjoyed battling for it. I find the show very, but you don't feel friends is better than
Seinfeld. No, Seinfeld I prefer, but I was like, I could, I could argue the quality of Friends
against Seinfeld. Like I, there's enough, there are enough differences and, and, and attributes.
For instance, the emotional depth of Friends. Yeah, they give you that. They give you that.
And also Friends reminds me of like a little bit of my life in New York. Like I'm like, yeah,
this, this is kind of what it's like living in New York. And this is nice, you know, and my friend
Chrissy popped over today to, to, to, to pick something up that I was lending to her.
And it was, you know, it was like last minute text, like, hey, I'm coming over. Can I, you know,
and you're like, I was, when she came in, I was like, oh, this is like Friends. You know,
it's just kind of nice. Anyway. They get that on Seinfeld too, Joe. They went to each other's
I know, I know, I know, but let me just do my thing. Yeah. Anyway, I like the show. I want,
it made me want, in watching it, it made me want to go back and watch more of everybody.
And I've seen all of them in many things over the years,
but it just heightened my appreciation of everybody. They may, if you really
um, listen to what is being said on that show,
like Seinfeld's dialogue on paper is very funny. And then the gifted actors make it very, very
funny. Often the dialogue on Friends sucks, but those six make it work every time. Like the actual
jokes are like sometimes just pure duds, but they sell everything so hard. Well, they create actual
characters, you know, they'll do a thing. Like there's an episode where Rachel,
Jennifer Anderson is supposed to waitress for Monica Courtney Cogs for a cooking gig. I'll
just do it for the listeners. No, I don't. And she has to bail at the last minute and she's like,
so she gets Phoebe to do it. And I'm watching it and I'm like,
you, they, why, why wouldn't they just have Phoebe do it to begin with? Right. That would save some
time. And I was like, Oh no, that's how well structured these characters are. You're going,
you would never ask Phoebe to do this. Right. You would ask Rachel to do it, but now she has
to ask Phoebe to do it. You know what I mean? Like little stuff like that is the kind of shit
they 100 % overlook in current sitcoms. I think, you know, for sure. You're, you know, and out of
everybody, uh, I've gained the most post appreciation for, for Perry. I mean, he's,
that guy is a fucking beast, man. He is so funny. And I'm like, he kept me watching the show back
in the day. He was, I loved him. I'm like, it makes me sad that we, I guess the whole nine yards,
but I'm like, where, how did we never get like a couple home run, like Matthew Perry comedy movies.
I tried to watch fool's Russia and it's not good. It's not, no, he didn't him and LeBlanc never did
anything good. Schwimmer was, Swimmer wisely stayed to like little supporting parts, like at pupil,
but they all pretty much failed. Anniston had way better luck than anybody else. And then
Cox, cause she went with scream. Well, I wouldn't say any of them failed. They all had like fruitful
likes. Don't forget. Perry had like two other fucking sitcoms after this and LeBlanc had
episodes. So they all worked for sure. But I got episodes, then man of the house or whatever.
Oh yeah. He's had two, uh, like guys quietly working. Yeah. Yeah. That's a, that's one with
real fun, a deep bench of supporting people too. Just like science, but all the parents are great.
Elliot Gould and Kathleen Turner and all these great people come in. Oh, it's, it's great. It's
a great show. Giovanni Robisi. Yep. And then in the later seasons, the guest stars are literally
like Paul Rudd, Ben Affleck, uh, you know, Brad Pitt, all these, not Affleck. Uh, Bruce Willis,
et cetera, et cetera. Yeah, that's right. Yeah. Van Damme in a really funny scene where like
Monica's all happy. She finally lands the date with him. Yeah. And Rachel sabotages it because
she steals him away from Rachel. Right. And then the reveal is as Van Damme goes,
his, him saying that Rachel, he's, or she's like, I'm surprised you went out with me after you went
out with Rachel. And he's like, well, once she said you wanted to have a threesome with Drew
Barrymore, I said, okay. And then he goes, that said, Drew has some ground rules. And I was like,
Van Damme getting a sitcom laugh. That's funny. Like he delivered it really well.
It was probably take 90, but yeah, he got there. He got it.
Anyway, friends watch it if you haven't. Friends heard of it. Check it out. Uh, I
saw a movie called bad luck banging or loony porn. This is a movie that is about censorship
and, uh, hypocrisy. It is Romanian and some of the, you know, some of the stuff in it
I wasn't always sure what was going on, but, um, obviously this country is dealing with tons
of censorship right now. So it felt very timely of the moment. And it was pretty funny. It opens
with, if you're going to watch the movie, you have to rent it on iTunes and don't watch it on Hulu,
even though it's free on Hulu because, um, it's a movie about porn and there's actual hardcore
graphic porno in it. And if you're going to watch that, why would you watch it edited also on Hulu?
This is why I started watching the movie on Hulu. They have giant, uh, cartoons over it saying like
censored, censored, censored, like, how are you supposed to get into the movie when that's the
first five minutes? So if you're going to watch it, watch it on iTunes, unedited, it opens with a
very graphic, full penetration, uh, deep throat, et cetera, porn scene between a man and his wife.
Then we see the, what the woman go about her day and we learn that her husband has uploaded
the video of them fucking two porn hub. Uh, she is a school teacher and the movie becomes,
especially in the third act, a very funny satire about how hypocritical people are
with issues of sex and the entire school board wants her fired and she's saying,
I just had sex with my husband. I didn't put it online, you know, and they're all pissed at her
really for just having sex with her husband. It's about how puritanical society can be.
There's a lot going on in this movie. The middle section is a bunch of little short sketches
about these topics about, um, you know, mostly that theme censorship hypocrisy, but, um,
I was really entertained by it. There is graphic X -rated stuff, so don't watch it on a plane,
but, uh, it's worth checking out bad luck banging or loony porn. Do not know why
they didn't just pick a title, why they called it two titles, but that's the name.
Uh, my last thing is a movie I streamed on a plane.
I'm on a plane. It's a good song. Uh, it's, it's a movie I'd never heard of, but it's new.
It's a recent, it's called see how they run Rockwell. Yeah. Sam Rockwell, uh, comedy
mystery caper, Sam Rockwell and socio or not. So I was what's her name from, um, lady bird.
Greta Gurley. No, no, no. The main lady bird, lady bird herself, her name, Joe. Oh, short,
short Ronan. Yeah. Yes. She's, she's, it's, it's she and Sam Rockwell are the stars and there's a
very big supporting cast. One of which is Adrian Brody, who's really, uh, funny in the movie.
Everybody's very funny in the movie. She's the, she's the standout. I mean, she's really great
in it. Um, but everybody does a great job and, uh, it's funny. It's a deconstruction of a murder
mystery while being a murder mystery. So like the, it's narrated in the beginning by Adrian Brody
and he is sort of taking apart an Agatha Christie style caper at the seams and like,
here are all the tropes. Here's why it's stupid. Here's why, you know, here's why it's predictable.
Here's what, you know, and as he's saying it, you realize, Oh my God, I'm watching all of
what he's saying happen actually. Yeah. And as it goes, everything he sets up in that intro
happens in the movie, but it still keeps you guessing. And it's very funny. And you realize,
Oh, they weren't taking the piss out of murder mysteries. They were just misdirecting you
unreliable, uh, narrator, as they say. Uh, and it's, it's just, it's just a fun little 90 minutes
in and out. And, uh, it's like if knives out was a straight up comedy, um, which it sort of is,
but this is even more so of a, you know, okay. Did you see the second knives out?
That was one we were going to do on here. Uh, that was much more of a comedy. I thought I
liked both of those movies. The knives out. I heard that the second knives out sucked because
of the use of flashbacks, which they talk about in this, about how that's a major cheat.
I mean, I don't, I didn't care. I was there for the ride, the fun, the laughs, not so much the
mystery. All right. Um, to be swept away with this. Look, Joe, we'd all want to be swept away,
but I'll take being swept and nicely into a dust pan, you know? Um, I saw I am going to discuss
stolen youth colon inside the cult at Sarah Lawrence. This is on Hulu.
It's madness. It's complete madness. It is this girl and her friends at Sarah Lawrence College.
They are like, they just seem like really cool college age kids seemed a lot like the people I
used to hang out with in college. For the most part, very nice. You cut loose and have fun,
but for the most part you're doing, you're doing your, you're doing your thing. You're not,
one of the girl's dads who she talked about all the time, she idolized her dad, but he was in
prison and she was like, he's in prison for a crime. He didn't commit, but my dad is the best
man that ever lived. He's amazing. Blah, blah, blah. The dad gets out of prison and the girl asks
her friends, Hey, is it okay if my dad crashes with us? This is a documentary by the way. Ask, can
my dad live here with us? And the friends are like a little weird that a 50 year old guy is
going to be staying in our dorm room and stuff, but yeah, we'll allow it. So they buy this little
house and he's living in there sleeping on the couch and little by little this like bald kind of
thick, dumb seeming guy weaves his way into all of their lives. He's, he's fucked them all.
He's pitting them against each other. And it's deeply disturbing. He's fucking like 18 year olds
he's, you know, in his fifties and then he starts, uh, hitting them, hitting them with hammers and
things, telling them to do tasks for him, but then also convincing them that they have done him wrong
in some way. So there's all these disturbing scenes of him saying like, why would you hurt me like
that? And they'll be sobbing saying, I didn't mean to do it, but they know they didn't do anything.
He's just, his whole thing is just fucking with their brains and he does this over a period of
years and years, eventually setting up the sex cult and having some of these people under his
spell, like his zombies go out and start fucking people. Um, this one girl in the, in the doc has
thousands upon thousands of sexual partners. Um, and she's, you know, like a sophomore in college
and she's doing it because this guy, this dad has told her you ruin something of mine. He's made it
completely and you owe me a million dollars to make up for it. So she just started fucking these
men to make money, to pay him back for a thing she never did. And then you, they, they have
interviews with some of these kids. Now it's not, it didn't happen that long ago. And of course
they're deeply embarrassed by it, but they're just back to normal. They've got their trauma of course,
but it really more than almost any other cult thing. Cause always I'm like, these guys are
fucking idiots. I never would be like that. But when I saw this and how casual it was and how it
worked on everyone in a house, that means you're not getting one stupid person to fall for your
bullshit. You're getting everyone in a house of different races, different backgrounds. They all
fall for you and start treating you like a prophet and you're some fat dad sleeping on a couch.
So, I mean, the power of suggestion is insane. Maybe it's cause they were college kids and you're
a little dumber in college. I don't know. But, um, if you like that kind of shit, a good cult doc
now and then it's a really entertaining one and fucked up. All right. That brings us to the task
at hand possession. Possession Elvis custom, uh, possession is a, I'd call it an art house film.
Oh yeah. Made by an Austrian or German. Is he German Austrian set in Berlin? Yeah. I believe
he's German. This is his only English language film he ever made stars a French actress whose
name escapes me. And Sam Neil, Isabella Johnny, say her name. Isabella Johnny. Uh, it is, uh,
about a crumbling marriage where the wife suddenly decides she does not want to be married to her
husband anymore. He is at a loss and doesn't understand why, uh, it drives him to be very,
uh, confrontational with her about it. In fact, physically abusive at one point. Uh,
and eventually we learned that she is living in a abandoned flat with a tentacled thing
that she is having sex with, which spoiler alert will every time she fucks it become closer to
being a doppelganger of her husband, Sam Neil, in theory, the version of him she actually wants.
While this is happening, Sam Neil meets, uh, his son's teacher also played by what's her name again?
Isabella Johnny. Isabella Johnny, uh, who serves as a doppelganger to his wife.
Um, he gets closer with her. The wife keeps fucking the tentacle thing.
People die. Uh, and eventually Sam Neil and Isabella Johnny die and the doppelgangers
at the very end of the movie get together as the son that Isabella Johnny and Sam Neil have
in their marriage kills himself because of the horror that the two evil entities that he's aware
are evil will now get together and cause him even more pain than his original two parents did.
Uh, it's a fun one. This is what I would call the very definition of a nihilistic film.
It's heavy. There are no smiles. There's no hope, let alone smiles or anything.
Yeah. Um, and I don't really know where to begin with my opinion on it. All I can say is
I'm a fan of nihilism in art. I'm a fan of darkness. I'm a fan of dejection. I'm a fan of,
of a bleak view, but I hated watching this movie. Every second of it, I hated. I just
this worked as a, this was clearly a major influence for Hellraiser, like clearly.
About the same thing. I thought the same thing. It, it feels like it in a, in a weird way. It's
almost like they use the same sets in some scenes kind of. And Hellraiser is a bleak film,
but this made Hellraiser look like fucking Billy Madison. I mean, I was like, Jesus Christ. So,
um, you know, uh, this is to Hellraiser, what like the new Hellraiser was to like the Hellraiser
remake or whatever it was. It was just, it's, it's, it's dark. It's very dark. I just didn't
enjoy it, man. I just didn't, I didn't, I, I, I texted you this last night. I'm like, Sam Neil,
a bad actor. Like he's so hammy in this. I really hate, she was magnificent. I thought of him hammy
and goofy. His choices didn't make any fucking sense to me. Like I didn't like it. I'm never
a huge fan of Neil, even in Jurassic Park. I like him, but I always think somebody better could have
done it. However, um, I did like him in this movie quite a bit. I saw it for the first time
over the pandemic as I was having marital issues and I found it to be almost, uh, like you're saying
too much for me. It was just a lot at that time. Um, but I was kind of blown away by it. Every,
every scene is kind of like handheld and it's like, it seems like they're dropping the camera
into just like the cameras flying around. And there's that one scene early on where they're
just like, uh, three guys interviewing him. He's a spy, which is very loosely alluded to that. He's
a spy. I missed that. I didn't catch that. So I was reading as I was watching it, I was reading
the Wikipedia a little bit because there was a couple of things I was unsure about. And the
first line was like a spy returns from, I was like, what a spy. Yeah. You don't even realize
it until a second. But, uh, it's why those guys are chasing him with guns and stuff at the end,
but it's, it's the movie is, you know, uh, an art piece. Like there, it's not reality. Obviously
they're fucking squid creature in a bed, but, um, also the dialogue they're using is not
how you would speak to one another. It feels almost like we're talking about with Pinter or
Mammoth or something like that sort of, but it's also almost like at times they're doing like a fake
play about marriage. And then sometimes it gets very real and very hostile. And, um,
this is written like Andy Warhol and Salvador Dali wrote the dialogue, you know, you know,
there is nothing, the lines that's, that stood out to me was there's nothing left to fear except
God. And then Samuel says to me, God is a disease. You know, like, yeah, we're all feeling a lot right
now. Well, when I, um, watched it the second time and maybe it's cause I'm, um, you know,
coming out on the other side of my situation, but I, I absolutely loved it. I thought that it,
I mean, I, I, I threw it a five star. I think it's an amazing movie and one I'll probably
start watching more because I got a whole lot more out of it on a second viewing. Um,
it's very hard for me to like when I'm trying to follow a plot to go to get the symbolism.
And with this movie, I was trying to figure out what was going on and that's not really what you
be doing because it's not that kind of a movie. Um, so much like Mulholland drive, the first time
I watched it, I'm, I'm loving it, but I'm also kind of taking notes and trying to figure out
what's going on. Um, until you realize that that's a movie, you just need to kind of let wash over
you. And then eventually it starts to make a lot of sense. So this movie, what it has to say about
love marriage, about how painful it is when it goes away about separating, they have a kid too,
which makes this all the more painful, some really disturbing scenes with the fucking kid who
drowns himself in a bathtub at the end of the movie. Um, it's tough. I thought, I think Isabella,
Johnny, um, is absolutely incredible in this movie. She has a very famous, justly famous
scene where she goes down into a subway and has this extended freak out and then gives birth to
and gore. Yeah, she's, she has a nervous breakdown because she's having a miscarriage
from the tentacle thing that's been fucking her night. Right. It is, it's an incredible scene.
I watched a little documentary about it. They said it was two takes and she was like, I, I,
if I do that again, I will die. And she tried to kill herself after production wrapped. I saw an
interview with Sam Neal where he said that was about the it for me. He goes, I barely escaped
that movie with my sanity. Um, the director was suicidal throughout production, having just gone
through a bad breakup himself and was actively suicidal while making the movie. And, um, you
feel it, you feel it, but I also think it has a, a beyond dark. I'm not, you're not laughing at it,
but I don't think it's as unfun maybe as we're making it sound on the second viewing. I actually
did have some fun with it, but I also like really depressing and dark shit. Certainly something
everybody should check out. I think at two hours plus, it's a little too long for what it's trying
to do, but that's really my only, my only, right. I fucking loved it. It's a slog. It's a commitment.
Uh, it's, um, I was going to say something. It's, you know what? It's along the lines. I was like,
anti -Christ. Oh, that's what I was going to say. I was going to say earlier, I was trying to think
of the third movie. I was like, this is to, you know, this is like, yeah, this is the step. It's
hell raiser is the ice creamy version of this. Right. Then there's this, then there's anti -Christ,
which is takes this and goes, let's go down a few more levels. You know? Yeah. And you're just like,
Jesus Christ. That's seen with her in the subway. I just was like, I can't do this, man. Like this
is too much. Like it's just, she's screaming and like gagging and I'm just like, and then I know
that she, I read about her having the breakdown or whatever, you know, or saying it was killed
herself or tried to. And I just was like, I'm not enjoying this. Like it's just too much for me.
Sam Neal said this movie, the director had him go to places he wouldn't go to again.
I wonder if some of those were literal, like physical, because there's a part where he is
cutting himself with an electric knife and saying it's painless. And I'm watching this and I'm like,
that fucking thing just cut through his shirt. Yeah. And then as he's bleeding, like I'm like,
is he actually cutting himself with this? Because this crazy director would be like,
but you do not feel the pain. So just cut yourself. You know what I mean? Like,
it seems like that kind of thing. It did. And there's these, there's scenes in it where like,
he's always doing weird stuff. Like there's a scene where he, for 10 seconds, graphically adjusts his
dick. That to me is like, he's doing it, like calling your attention to it. There's a scene
where he's walking with like a half hunchback with no explanation. So there is a Lynchian kind of
quality too. There's a lot of just bizarre shit in it. Joe texted me, she better start fucking
this monster at some point. And I was like, you're not going to like that scene when it comes.
Because that squid monster is like holding her down. And then Sam Neal's watching him get
cucked by a squid. It's tough. It's tough. It was, it was tough. And I kept thinking,
because the creature is very Lovecraftian. I think they did themselves a huge disservice by
putting in the opening credits, the creature designed by so and so. It's a massive surprise
an hour into your movie. I agree. It's very Lovecraftian and Sam Neal stars in one of my
favorites in the mouth of madness, which is terribly Lovecraftian. And I just wondered if
Sam Neal must've been on the set of that movie, like you fucking pussy. You think you're making
a horror movie. You don't know what the fuck horror is. Well shit that he did event horizon too. Like
he must like extreme shit or else he just gets typecast in it. I don't know. Event horizon is
very Hell Razory. It is. Yeah. Little Lovecrafty. Yeah. Anyway, I would say,
although my hog is not up for the movie, I recognize that it is a very well -made piece of
art. I can't possibly give it a bad review. I just didn't enjoy it. And I did say, I did think like,
well, maybe if I watched it at another time, in another place in my life, I might go, oh wow,
this is great. Um, I didn't think it was bad. I understood what I think I understood what they
were going for. It just wasn't for me. And I did not enjoy the experience of it, you know, which
again, this director seems like a director that would be like, yes, good. Then my work is done.
So like, you know, I told you at the time I met Abel Ferrara, cause I went to that private
screening of when he made Welcome to New York, which had like straight up porn scenes with
Gerard de Perdue, fucking multiple women. Yeah, I saw that. And after in the lobby, he was like,
he was like, what'd you think, man? I go, I found it very disturbing. And he goes, all right.
He looked down at his jacket off. So these guys, like, they like that. Like they, you know,
I don't know. Like, no, uh, look, that's, that's what I like. If I had to pick like my favorite
kind of small genre of movies, it would be extreme. You know, I like to be challenged
by something. Um, I'll, I'll never watch that Serbian film, which has like a baby getting
fucked in it or something. And I'm not, I'm not a human centipede guy either, but I like, um,
and I think this was super successful on the second time around. It took me two viewings,
but, um, I, yeah, I was kind of blown away by it. I had a lot to think about and it's another one
like tar where you can go read a bunch of online shit and have a field day reading all sorts of
interpretations of the movie as well, which I liked. Um, yes, I did do some of that. Um,
all right, folks, we'll be back next time with knock at the cabin. Uh, M. Night Shyamalan's latest,
uh, Jonah Rosa comedy on Instagram and Twitter. Uh, I, this comes out, yeah, this weekend,
I'm in Louisiana starting Thursday in Baton Rouge, then on the Lafayette Friday, then onto New
Orleans Saturday, uh, Sunday, Monday, Tuesday. I will be at South by Southwest and Austin, uh,
Monday at 5 PM. We're doing the sandwich summit where I discuss sandwiches with other sandwich
makers from Austin restaurants. Uh, that's at the Creek in the cave at five. And then on Monday,
Tuesday, I'm doing my hour. I never promised you a Rose garden 7 PM at the Creek in the cave. Uh,
I also will be doing the kill Tony podcast live from the Vulcan on Monday night. I think, um,
anyway, uh, come out to some of these shows. I'm back out again at the end of the month in
the Midwest, Chicago and surrounding areas. Joe to Rosa info .com for tickets, uh, and, uh,
show information. Also crane theater, March 22nd for the residency, doing the hour there again.
And of course, as always, Joey roses in New York. If you're around, if you're in town,
come through. We're open seven days a week, sandwiches, drinks, great times.
You open on Wednesdays too? Every day. Friday nights.
Seven days. Oh, okay. Great. Uh, I'm the page picture.
A great picture. Uh, the Patrick Walsh on, uh, Twitter and Instagram occasionally.
Also, I am on my good friend Ben Rogers, new podcast. I am his very first guest. It is called
Raj tapes. Um, and I love doing it so much that the premise of the podcast is that he
has a bunch of old VHS tapes of very obscure movies. And he was trying to explain to me
what the podcast even was. And I didn't even really get it. So we kind of did it on the fly,
but we are riffing, basically doing just like this podcast, an hour long discussion about a movie
that does not exist. And he gave me the genre, which was like erotic thriller.
He had a few details about the movie and then we went from there.
Um, I'm look, I'm not an improv guy, but I like doing it. I like doing podcasts and that kind
of shit. And it was one of the most fun kind of challenges like that I've ever had, especially
cool to see a lot of people being like, where is this movie Pat and Ben are talking about? And they
actually think it's real. Um, but it's cool. I'm going to check it out. He's got a lot of big
guests coming up on it. And I think that's just a great idea for a podcast. So check that out.
All right, folks, we'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.