🎵 I'll see you in hell. I'll see you in hell. And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say. I'll see you in hell. You know I will. I'll see you in hell. You know I will. 🎵
Folks, it's We'll See You in Hell. We're back to talk about a fine new horror film in a violent nature. My name is Joe DeRosa.
And my name is Patrick Walsh. Hello, everybody. It's June. Experiencing June gloom here in Los Angeles, the phenomenon where it's hot but gloomy for a month.
Um, really sort of miserable, except I like the gloom. But you go outside expecting a nice, crisp, cool day and it's 100 degrees.
I, uh, I remember, uh, June gloom. I didn't remember it being hot. It is hot. I always, for some reason, thought it was, you know, not hot, but temperate.
Uh, so that's the worst, man. Overcast and hot. Really sucks.
Um, Joe, let's get, let's get right to the big story this week. Practical Magic 2. You, you put it in your sort of wish cauldron and stirred it up.
I put it in my dream cauldron and stirred it up and we, somehow we got what we wanted. A 25 year late sequel to one of the more underwhelming movies ever made. Practical Magic. A movie I remember as being notably awful.
I find it saying a lot when you can say one of the more forgettable films of Nicole Kidman or Sandra Bullock because they have both, they're both fine actors, but they have both cranked out a series of films that, that I couldn't even tell you the name, the negligible movies.
Kidman's in five a year that just come and go. And she probably makes 20 million on each. And she does like three TV series a year, 10 episodes each.
Nicole. Yeah. And stopping off at the AMC to tell you to get your ass out of the house.
I always wonder in a situation like that, in a, in a Cannavale, in a Kidman, what's going on at home?
You know, when you hit, which Nicole Kidman would have hit in about 1995, when you hit a hundred million dollars, your life's not going up or down much. You don't need to do five $20 million projects a year.
She must hate the huzz.
I don't, who's she married to again? Blake? That's some country guy?
Keith Urban, I want to say. He looks like a beautiful lady.
Or is that Stephanie's married to Keith Urban?
She's married to Blake Shelton. That's right. Okay.
Nicole Kidman is married to, because there's also Carl Urban, who's an actor. Yeah, she's married to Keith Urban. We're trying to talk me out of what I know.
And he's a singer?
He's a singer. He's the kind of man that when a woman goes for him, I'm like, really? Like what's going on here? Like if you look him up and see a picture of him, it's like, he just looks like a middle -aged woman, like a cool LA middle -aged mom.
Oh yeah. They both, they both next week. Oh Jesus. Look at this picture.
Like it looks like they'd be asking you to join their little, you know, like weird exercise cult in a park somewhere or something like that.
Look at this one though. If this came up for you, I'll put it in the old chat here.
Yeah. I love just taking digs at Nicole Kidman. If you could see what Joe and I look like right now, taking digs at Nicole Kidman.
I'll tell you this. We look like two normal human beings. These two people look like space people. They look insane. Look at that picture. They look insane.
No, you're not wrong. You're not wrong. He's got full cleavage, like a V -neck down to his navel. She's covered up. It's a real weird vibe.
By the way, standing in front, these two like plastic, and I mean that literally. I don't mean like they're plastic fake people. I mean like literally plastic faced people.
Standing in front of the Amazon Prime insignia, forcing these smiles. It looks like this would be on the brochure for hell. Like it's like this is what selling your soul does look like.
Come on in.
Very dark. There's nothing very dark about that.
No, I agree. But we're all real pumped about the Practical Magic sequel.
What is that movie even about? And by the way, don't you love a light witchcraft movie? Where you're not even sure if there's witchcraft involved. It looks like a Crate and Barrel take on witchcraft, the original.
It is. Like from what I remember, here's what I remember about the movie. They're witches, I want to say they're sisters, and they do a long extended dance to Harry Nilsson's Putty Lime and De -Coconut from Reservoir Dogs.
That's all I remember. Two witch sisters raised by their eccentric aunts in a small town face closed minded prejudice. Witch prejudice, Joe. And a curse which threatens to prevent them from ever finding love.
Okay. Outrageous.
Is it a comedy? Oh yeah, it is a comedy.
It was.
Griffin Dunn directed. I don't know if they'll bring him back or not.
Something tells me Dunn's not going to get to direct the sequel.
Dunn's Dunn, baby.
No offense to Dunn, but I don't think they're giving him a Hollywood studio project at this point.
No. It's a really bad movie. I remember more about her other movies of the time. Sandy Bullock Hope Floats, which was a rom -com starring Harry Connick Jr. and her.
28 Days, which was her in a rehab facility with Steve Buscemi, falling in love there as well, of course.
Well.
I saw all these movies. I don't know why or how, but I did.
Here's, let's add a little more confusion to this story.
The movie had a budget of $75 million. Somehow Practical Magic cost $75 million. It cost $25 million less than the Irishman that had breakthrough technology that had never been achieved.
Four -hour film, yeah.
Practical Magic cost $75 million. It made $68 million.
So lost money.
Lost money. And it has a 22 % on Rotten Tomatoes. It was also a critical bomb.
Gang, what are we doing here? What are we doing? Like, just make another witch movie with those two or something. Like, you don't need to dust this off.
Yeah, Rotten Tomatoes, it's got one out of five stars.
Then here's a people story. Practical Magic 2, everything we know so far.
Oh yeah. They love those.
Love that, like it's a, you know, a government breach.
Yeah. Yeah, they love those. This is, I mean, it's, my assumption is that whatever studio, who did this, Abbey Road, no, that's a soundtrack. Somehow I'm onto the soundtracks.
Warner Bros.
Warner Bros. So my assumption is, Warner Bros. still has the intellectual property, and they're gonna, they thought, you know what, it didn't work the first time, but we already have this, let's do it again, let's put a bunch of young women in it.
Empowerment, young witches, very now, all that stuff, and we'll have Kidman and Bullock as, you know, they'll waltz in every 22 minutes and say a line and then leave, and none of the witches will question why a woman with magical powers had to get so much plastic surgery.
That'll be left off the table. There'll never be question that a woman that belongs to a religion that literally worships nature.
Yeah.
It's a valid cue, Joe. It was a valid cue in the Northmen as well.
I got a, I got so much new psycho here.
Okay.
I don't know what to do with it.
Say it.
Well, let's start with, while we're on the subject of witches, you know, this comes from MovieWeb, as most of my stories do, Blair Witch Project Stars, Slam Studio, this is, again, we talked about this before, this is happening again now, five days ago, over reprehensible behavior and lack of compensation.
So I read this whole article.
Here's what it pulls down to.
It was a non -union project.
They signed non -union deals.
Yeah.
Those deals said, this is what you get.
Right.
This probably won't amount to much, but that's what you get.
The movie smashed everybody's expectation into pieces, and it went on to become huge.
And now the actors are complaining that they should be getting the kind of compensation they would have gotten had they been in a union at the time and had union representation.
Well, you didn't.
Right.
And it sucks that the deal sucks, and it sucks that you're not getting a bigger piece of the pie.
By the way, they went to court with this in, I think it was the early 2000s, and they were awarded $300 ,000 each.
A drop in the bucket compared to what the entire franchise has made.
Pretty good money.
Yeah, 300 grand each.
Now, there was some controversy over the use of their likenesses and that sort of thing.
Yeah.
And as far as I could tell from reading the article, when they were used without permission, they pushed back, and that was not allowed to happen again.
And I'm not even saying that the studio is not doing anything kind of shady.
Maybe they are. I don't know.
But at the end of the day, you signed what you signed.
This is the deal.
They're demanding compensation and like consult, I think, consultation rights on new movies.
I mean, I guess it's a little odd because they were sort of the creative team for that movie, too, due to the improv.
But yeah, I mean, I'm sure this was all laid out contractually.
You know, you go on to read this, look, at the risk of sounding like an asshole, but I don't think I'm wrong.
Risk it, Joe.
I'm going to risk it, as I usually do.
At one point in this article, they're talking about how one of the actors is like, yeah, you know, it's been tough.
I was living at home with my mom in my 40s or something.
It's like, that's a you problem, dude.
Like, I'm sorry, man.
It's not the Blair Witch Lionsgate Studios fault.
Yeah, it's like you can't make a living in life.
In the years following Blair Witch and you're not getting acting work, that's on you to come up with a new career path.
There is, and you know, we're going to get to it with next week's movie, which is Bratz, this Hulu documentary about the Brat Pack.
People, and I've been guilty of this and everyone I know has been guilty of this, but hopefully you have therapy or something that can snap you out of it.
The entertainment industry is one where you can really get stuck blaming other people.
And a lot of times it is other people's fault, but it's the kind of business where you just got to say that project is over, set it on fire, walk away, waiting to exhale style.
I've struggled with this myself, but these people get so hung up because you spend your whole life wanting a taste of the gold, but not everybody is guaranteed a lifelong taste of that gold.
Some people get their five minutes and then they sweep you out the door and it's very cold and it's very harsh, but that's what it is.
The business doesn't owe you at all.
Well, there is something here that said, they said if the contract stated if the movie made a million dollars, they would be granted one percent of profits.
Okay.
They said it was very clear they weren't going to get that.
That's not fair.
I agree.
But it says then, all three performers then sued Artisan, which is a very sad thing that happens in this business where you have to sue for the money owed to you.
I'm not saying that's okay.
I'm saying it's very pathetically standard, but they sued and they got three hundred thousand dollars in a settlement each.
So I don't understand.
Like a hundred million, one percent of a hundred million is hold on.
My math is not great.
One percent of a hundred million is a million.
Oh, that's a good point.
There really aren't many easier math problems than that.
Okay.
So one million divided by three is about three hundred thousand.
Yeah.
Now, let me see if it says each.
It says if the in their contracts, it stated if the movie gross more than one million dollars, the performers would be entitled to one percent of the profits.
It's not clear if it meant the three of them together.
Yeah.
Or each of them solo.
So look, if the if the it later says in the same article that they're seeking, had they here goes, something that might be tough.
These goals that, you know, they're seeking might be tough because there were no union contracts covering the film for Leonard.
This comes down to knowing your worth with the actor saying, I don't need Lionsgate to like me.
I don't care that they know that.
I think their behavior has been reprehensible.
I don't want my daughter to ever feel like anything is more valuable than her self -worth.
It's very convoluted.
It sounds to me like they signed a bad contract.
It sounds like they had a very I mean, here's the thing.
If it was as cut and dry as your contract says, this is what you are owed.
Lionsgate is in breach of that.
Therefore, you have a case or you don't when there's all this other sort of fogginess around it.
And by the way, around an article that's not being unsupportive of them, it's not a scathing article about them.
It's it's it's arguably supportive.
When there's all this this this blur, it says to me all the information is in here or they're giving a certain amount of information.
And that information is the stuff that leans in their favor and they're leaving out the stuff that works against them.
Because what is there to argue? Yeah, what is there to argue?
Yeah, I think sometimes these cases very often these cases are unfair.
The giant corporation is at fault and the people are owed money.
But sometimes it really is just people who are like, I was in this big hit.
I want more money.
And if the contract doesn't reflect that, you're not going to get it.
You might get sympathy. You might get publicity.
You might get someone reaching out and offering you a role.
And maybe that's part of this, but they don't owe you any money out of good.
They're good nature. This is Hollywood.
It says the actors have requested meaningful consultation on all future Blair Witch projects that would use their likeness.
I don't know what meaningful consultation, I guess, maybe just like how are you going to use my eyes?
A lot of eye contact.
As well as retroactive and future residual pay for the movie that would be similar to what would have come to them through SAG after.
Well, that to me, that kind of says it all.
We didn't have a union and we didn't get it.
We didn't get what we should have got.
Not disagreeing with that.
But I don't know, man. You know, I said this before.
I'll say it again.
I'm in Grand Theft Auto five and I have a pretty significant part and my likeness and I didn't mocap.
I'm in the game, not my voice is in the game.
I'm in the fucking game.
The game made a billion dollars.
I got three grand.
Right.
OK, that's what I signed.
You know, that's it.
Like, that's what the fuck it was.
Yeah, it sucks.
Yeah.
And also, let's be real here.
None of that game's success is attributable to you.
Oh, I agree.
A very small sliver of the success of Blair Witch is those actors.
Now, were they great and convincing and we bought it?
Yes.
But they took that role at a time when everyone trying to break into Hollywood says,
I would do any role for any money.
You know, like, you know, and now the money's dried up.
It wasn't much money to begin with.
But like, you've had, since 1999, you've had time to track down another career path
if acting wasn't going to keep working out for you.
End of story. Sorry.
I think they all have gone on to other things,
and I don't even think they all want it to be actors.
I think they just want it.
I think that's part of why, I don't know, man, it's just this whole,
it's a shame that we've gotten to a point where every single thing you read,
no matter how the victim at the center of the story is portrayed,
you have to sit here and scrutinize and question it
because victimization has been so weaponized
and people are doing anything, not all people, but some people,
are doing anything to get their five minutes or 15 minutes and get their money.
You know, everybody thinks they deserve, not everybody, I'm sorry,
a lot of people think they deserve something for nothing.
It's a change in the mentality of the culture.
I have a friend who has a business.
He told me he fired, he had to fire an employee for stealing.
They caught the employee stealing.
Okay.
And he goes, two weeks later, who do I see sitting in my business?
Is this employee, like having a night?
He goes, I had her escorted out.
Like, it's like the entitlement.
Like, it's so insane.
Like the lack of accountability that anybody has.
Was he able to then go over and be like, hey, you stole here, get out of here.
I didn't just let it go.
He said he had management go over and say, you need to leave.
We will be escorting you out.
Your food is being wrapped to go.
Take care.
Okay.
You're not allowed to be here.
And he said, of course, they were like, wait, what, what?
You know, so anyway.
Not quite the same situation as, as the Blair Witch, but still people are,
people are struggling and it's going to lead to more and more desperate actions,
I think in all walks of life, in all careers.
Now here's a lawsuit against the studio that I agree with.
Despite some of the parties being involved.
I'm not a big fan of because Elon Musk is backing this.
Gina Carano from the Mandalorian who was fired for comparing very vaguely,
barely comparing the persecution of conservatives in Hollywood to the similar treatment
of Jewish people in Germany pre what led to the Holocaust, excuse me.
Keep in mind, guys, she was fired for this and it was called.
This was called reprehensible and abhorrent.
These are the same people telling you right now that if you don't chastise Israel,
that you're a horrible person.
So this is the way this game gets played.
They're defending the group one minute and firing you for not defending
and stepping in line with the group one minute.
And then the next minute they're telling you to damn that same group.
And if you don't do that, then you're complicit in silences, violence and all this shit.
That is not my opinion on Israel Palestine, by the way.
I'm just saying it's funny to me how that lane shift happens.
We watched it happen with women in Hollywood.
Women were celebrated and lifted up and told that your abuse needs to be talked about
and whatever.
And two years later they were being called Karen and told shut the fuck up.
So this is how this works.
Again, not giving my opinion on any of those situations.
I'm just saying it shifts.
But anyway, Gina Carano is suing Lucasfilm and Disney for her firing,
not because she thinks she deserves money from the project,
but because she said you guys basically did a plotted and orchestrated strategic pursuit to destroy me,
which they did.
She talks about how her male co -stars have posted controversial things that were never reprimanded.
Absolutely true.
She talks about how behind the scenes, everybody from the show has entirely been supportive of her.
But they can't publicly say it because these people will ruin their lives.
It's ridiculous.
You can't find the original tweet she said.
What is she suing them for?
Missed wages or a full career loss?
Well, what Disney came out and said was Gina Carano is not currently employed by Lucasfilm
and there are no plans for her to be in the future.
Nevertheless, her social media posts denigrating people based on their culture and religious identities are abhorrent and unacceptable.
She didn't do that.
What she said was the fact that if you're a conservative...
I'm paraphrasing.
She said something along the lines of the fact that you're a conservative in Hollywood and you cannot express your opinions
and you're being literally silenced by your co -workers, it has echoes of pre -Holocaust Germany,
which by the way, if you know anything about history, there's truth in that.
Jewish people were not like a lowly class in Germany.
They were very rich.
They were prosperous.
They were doing well.
So I thought it was a pretty fair analogy.
I didn't think it was that crazy of an analogy.
But it was at a time where it was like you can't say anything.
She went on to say nothing could be further from the truth.
The truth is I was being hunted down from everything I posted to every post I liked
because I was not in line with the acceptable narrative of the time.
I agree with that.
My words were consistently twisted and demonized and dehumanized me as an alt -right -wing extremist,
which she was not.
It was bullying, smear campaign aimed at silencing, destroying, and making an example out of me.
That's 100 % right.
So she's suing for, I guess, damages.
But good, good.
Fuck this shit, man.
And I'm not one of these rah -rah, go fight, we're losing the country fucking people.
I'm not for either side of it.
But I mean, my God, man, it's fucking wild, you know?
It's like I know she's annoying.
I know she's annoying.
And by the way, I'm a fan of Jimmy Kimmel.
Again, it's not me taking sides.
I saw a thing where Megyn Kelly was like, oh, so Jimmy Kimmel gets to host the Oscars again?
Remember when he was in Blackface and that's like just forgiven?
And I asked a question about the context of Blackface and my career was destroyed.
Wait, who asked the question?
Megyn Kelly.
Because remember she said on that morning show, she was like, she was like, yeah, but there's Blackface,
but then there's people dressing up as a person they admire.
And she's like, isn't that different?
And they were like, you're fired.
Oh, is that what ended her career?
Yeah. And then she went on to talk about the recent Oscars and she's like, so Jimmy Kimmel,
and she started playing all the clips of him as Karl Malone.
Yeah.
And Sarah Silverman and you know, there was all those 30 Rocks, all those scrubs, all the, you know,
there was a lot of Blackface going on.
Kind of a lot.
So I'm of two minds.
I don't think you can hold people to the fire for something they did 20, 25 years ago
when comedic tastes were drastically different in every single way.
For example, comedy existed 20, 25 years ago.
You can't hold people responsible.
But when one of those people comes forward like a Sarah Silverman or a Jimmy Kimmel
and becomes a finger pointer, that's when I start to get a little annoyed sometimes.
I agree with that.
That's what makes me so mad about Disney.
Nobody has contributed more inappropriate and racist content to the public entertainment sphere
than Walt Disney.
They have done some of the most egregious racial takes that have ever been committed to film.
Period.
Song of the South, can't even find that movie.
They banned it themselves.
Yeah.
They did the Morgan Spurlock RIP, stepped out in front of it and go,
we're just going to go ahead and take this off the shelf before you guys can really get to it.
But my point is, and now Disney, this is a fact.
Disney removed, I think it was Star Wars, the new ones, and I think it was John Boyega.
Disney removed black characters from the movie posters in China
because they found statistically that the audience in China would not go see a movie
if there were black people featured in it prominently.
They removed the black characters from the posters.
This is the company that's coming out and telling all of you right now,
this is appropriate, you're not woke enough, you're not this, you're not that.
And that's what you're saying.
It's like when the offender becomes the finger pointer, what the fuck is going on?
This is so crazy.
It's like you never apologize for the other shit.
You can't just transition into yelling at me for doing something that I didn't do.
I hate it.
I hate being lectured to by people with huge egregious crimes against humanity on their record
who have made no effort to stop that.
I do think, and I do not subscribe to any political party, I fucking refuse to,
but I do think there is some truth to if you're not in lockstep with the right party,
they're going to make it a lot harder for you.
When I'm on a podcast railing against Disney, and not that I was really railing just then,
and I've worked for Disney, we all know they suck.
It hits a point where I start to feel like, oh boy, I don't want to be a guy railing against Disney
and how woke they are or something.
That's not really my bag.
And not for my own career.
I'm just saying when you align with that sort of narrative,
you're aligning with a bad group of people generally.
You're DeSantis' who are battling Disney and all this, et cetera.
But Disney is, what I've noticed in their current output, namely that Beach Boys documentary,
is they're afraid of anything now.
They told the story of the Beach Boys in an hour and 45 minutes
and made it seem like they had never had a fight between them.
That is a group of men who have nearly destroyed each other at a soul level on multiple occasions.
It goes so far beyond any other band's issues, even Fleetwood Mac's issues.
Sick shit that those men did to each other and their parents and everything else.
And it's just not in there.
And it's presented as this official document about the Beach Boys and their legend
and one of our great bands, a warts and all look, whatever.
This thing is so generic and cheesy.
And I think that Disney has gone beyond woke into just a fear of offending anyone for any reason.
And that's going to make for some really boring watered down product going forward.
Now I'm hearing that this Deadpool is R -rated and has all kinds of crazy R -rated content in it.
And that's some big step forward for Disney.
But there's still a company that goes through with a little check mark and tells you what you can and can't do on each project.
And now they own Fox, they own FX, which used to be one of our most boundary pushing networks.
It's all bad. It's all bad.
Everyone I know looking around being like, wow, television's getting bad again and movies are getting bad again.
Yeah, like, you know, we're in this really strictly regulated time and it's bad.
You can't. You can't run art.
Now, the problem is, you said it earlier, this is Hollywood.
Nobody owes you anything. I mean, it's a cutthroat fucking business.
The problem to me is that that sinister, callous, you know, cut your heart out, whatever.
It is now trickled down into non -monetized art.
And it's not everywhere, but it's prevalent.
And you're seeing a lot of no money and low money artistic ventures being treated with this same level of scrutiny.
And my take is you can't treat art like it's fucking romper room.
You can't have safety bumpers around everything. So nobody hits their head.
Nobody gets hurt. It's it's I'm not going art is dangerous, man.
You know, I don't mean it like that. I just mean like you have to be able to create.
And you have to be able to create freely.
You know, I had I had an instance and I've I've spoken to the woman since and we've made amends.
I had an instance the other night where I went on stage.
You know what? I'm going to leave names out of it because I don't want to blow up anybody else's spot.
I'll just speak for me. I went on stage with a friend of mine at a show that was not at a major club.
It was a little tiny open mic, literally an open mic.
We went on stage together. It was going to be a big fun thing.
He told a joke that the producer of the open mic deemed as transphobic and they cut our mics off and turn the music on and took us off stage.
And I was like, what is going on?
And I won't get into all of it, but it got to I got pissed.
I got really pissed and I didn't even tell the joke and I got pissed.
But it ended with me being called transphobic.
Me, me, transphobic, a lover of the trans women because I didn't think a joke was offensive.
Yeah. And that's my point.
And I said to this person, I said, if you want to wait, even if you did think a joke is offensive, think it.
You're at a comedy show.
Well, the point was made to me.
That's that person's open mic.
They can run it however they want.
That is true.
But I made my opinion clear of you can't get anywhere like this.
You can't get anywhere if your finger is on the trigger, ready to react to whatever you're hearing at all time.
You can't do it.
You can't develop that way.
People are like, why aren't why are comedies not funny anymore?
Why are sitcoms not funny?
Because the goddamn writers room, they're afraid to pitch jokes.
Everybody's afraid to pitch a fucking joke that you're going to get you're going to get sent down to HR.
That is very true.
And you pitch a joke and you're scared while saying it.
I have this every day with a writing staff that I love very much.
You pitch a joke.
You're scared while saying it.
You're scared for the three seconds after you've pitched it while the silence hangs in the air until you either get that laugh or you don't.
And you can't you can't operate that way.
You can't write comedy that way.
It's really bad.
You know, like the room should be there to go.
Oh, that's too much.
Yes, that's fine, too.
But the room's job, they used to always be the room's job.
I don't think we're going to make a joke about Roger Ebert while his jaws off.
You know, like on Broke Girls, we had those discussions.
I think we need to take a shot at Roger Ebert after he just had a stroke.
Sure.
And those are healthy.
You know, those are like when you decide, OK, who's the joke writer?
Who's the human being?
You know, and these are important discussions in terms of comedy.
Now you would be fired for pitching the Roger Ebert joke.
It's and that's that's the fear is that one person in the room doesn't like it.
It's hey, he told this joke.
Then there's no investigation, no discussion.
You're out.
So and here's the thing.
This is neither of us saying I've always said my biggest fear is to become one of those comics
that sits at the back table at a club going, it sucks now.
It used to be good because back in my day, you could be you.
I never want to be that guy.
And this is neither of us being that guy.
I think what we're both saying is, is it's OK to times change.
We accept the times change.
We're willing to listen as times change.
But times changing means give me the chance to be told that's not appropriate or we don't think
that works here.
And then we go, OK, and I won't yell at you and you don't turn the music on on me.
How about that?
How about we gauge it by it falling flat and then go and you go, OK, not gauge it by you
fucked up two seconds ago.
Let's take everything we can possibly take away from you in this moment right now.
Right.
Whatever the most power play, the biggest power play, we're going to do it right now.
It's nuts.
We were doing on a show once one of the black characters wanted a Cadillac.
And an older black writer on the show said to me, I don't even think I pitched it, but said to me,
hey, just so you know, that's a bit of a stereotypical kind of racist want for a black man.
Black men coveting Cadillacs has been going on in television for 50 years or something.
I had never seen an example of this.
I've never heard that.
I just was kind of like, wow, OK, immediately changed it.
That's a black person telling me this is a stereotypical thing.
End of end of discussion.
I got it.
We'll change it.
But if in that moment she had gone to H .R.
and said, can you believe that this guy's doing some horrifically racist story about a black character who wants a Cadillac?
And she's upset.
There's a 75 % chance I'm just immediately fired for that.
So what the fear is, I think the vast majority of people getting more tolerant and understanding of each other is good.
Obviously, it's just a it's a net good.
But what we're losing is people.
And then there's another I realize all these issues are so complicated.
But like, there's another issue that that people of a different race should not have to tell you how to talk to them.
That's on you to figure that out.
OK, but there are going to be blind spots.
For example, I didn't know a black man wanting a Cadillac was a racist thing.
If if if that person is not comfortable telling me and I'm not comfortable hearing it, then where do we go from there?
I just always want to create the kind of environment where everybody's like, like in my room on Miss Pat, somebody says a fucked up joke.
The whole room goes, oh, you can't fucking do that.
And everybody laughs. OK, sorry, I didn't mean it like that.
I didn't mean like that. That's healthy to me.
It's funny driving home in fear, which I have done numerous times, driving home in fear of what I have said in the 16 hours of stressful work that day is no real way to live, you know, because at my core, I'm a good human being and I shouldn't have to feel that way.
It's funny, by the way.
It's funny, by the way, how you mentioned the experience.
We're talking about the experience on predominantly white shows.
And then you talk about the black show and you're like, oh, the black show was where everybody was open minded and cool and whatever.
I can't fucking white people have such a point to fucking prove.
And they're so afraid of not proving it that, you know, they'll gut their mother in front of you to make it look like they're a decent fucking human being, you know, literally, literally.
And I think, you know, this is not anything new, but generally somebody going that far out of their way to point out your fuck ups has a giant pile of bodies buried in the basement.
But yeah, I can't speak for all black rooms, you know, this is the first, this is the first predominantly black room I've been in.
But like, and Miss Pat being at the head of that room changes the dynamic drastically.
That's a woman who doesn't get offended.
But like, man, oh man, is it a different environment where like, you should be, you should feel like within reason, you can fuck up at your job, especially a writing job and be fine within 30 seconds.
Within reason, don't pull a Michael Richards in the room, you know, by the way, how weird is it to see him suddenly everywhere after 20 years of being off the air?
Which, by the way, this is, I messaged you about this.
Yeah.
He's on the view, pushing that new book.
First of all, the fucking view, I mean, the five of them sitting around going, we feel that you did take your time and it's like, what is this?
Like, who the fuck are you the moderators?
They make themselves the tribunal, you know, it's like, we decide if the women of America are going to like you again, it's really weird.
But he's on there and he goes, I canceled myself.
You didn't, Mike.
No, you didn't.
By the way, he doesn't mean I can't.
I knew it was time to step away from the spotlight.
It's like you were on Letterman three nights later.
Yeah.
Three nights later.
Because he meant it like that.
He meant it like I decided I needed to go away.
Yeah.
It's like, no, you didn't.
No, you didn't.
And then he doesn't realize that it's an ego thing, too, because he's saying he's saying I would have been doing lots of great movies and TV over the last 20 years.
Believe me, I've had offers.
No, you haven't.
Well, by the way, he's on there talking about how he hasn't worked in 10 years.
He's worked fairly frequently over the last 10 years.
He was on Kirstie Alley's sitcom as a regular.
That I don't recall.
What was that show?
It's called Kirstie.
It was one of the it was when TV land started making their own sitcoms.
They did Hot in Cleveland was the big hit.
And then they started.
He's been in stuff.
He hasn't not worked.
Yeah.
He's worked as much as he ever worked outside of Seinfeld.
Period.
I think our and I haven't thought this through.
I hate trying to talk about something like this without having to having thought it through.
It's always too risky.
But that's what we're talking about.
Michael Richards is kind of the great example of everyone loves him.
You can you can sense even when you see bloopers from Seinfeld, something's off about that guy, though.
Like, yeah, yeah.
Elaine or Julie Louis Dreyfus will cut him off or she'll start laughing during one of his takes when he's doing something hilarious.
Three inches from her face, she'll start laughing.
And he'll like pull his fist back to punch her like he's not going to punch her.
But like he's got a level of anger in him.
That's that's inappropriate.
And there's a lot of bloopers where they're all laughing and he's like, come on, guys.
Come on, guys.
Come on now.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Seems like he's and you saw that Jerry Seinfeld comedians in cars where Kramer winds up sitting on the floor of a diner like he's not well.
And I think that incident can only make somebody worse.
But Kramer is a guy.
Who is kind of our first national test of cancel culture, like the first one where we're all like, it's it's happened before.
But everybody knows and loves Kramer.
Everybody saw that clip.
The clip when you watch it now, 20 years later is way worse than you remember.
It's it's not rough.
Like he says it once and moves on.
There's other stuff in there.
And we all have agreed as a nation, we're not going to stop watching Seinfeld, one of the funniest shows of all time.
But Kramer, you're not going to get the big roles anymore.
If you come on TV, you're going to have to talk about the incident.
We're not sending you to jail.
There's no trial, but you can't really do what you did and continue being a big part of the entertainment scene.
To me, the way Kramer has been handled is about the right way to do it.
To me, that feels like punishment sort of fits the crime.
He's clearly a guy who maybe you don't want on a film set.
He seems like he's way too reactive and hot headed.
Um, it seems fair.
We haven't taken Seinfeld away.
What do you think?
Do you think we were too harsh on Kramer?
No, no, but I will.
Everything seems right to me about Kramer and how we handled it as a nation.
I will equate it to, uh, now you look at everything you just said.
Now look at what Roseanne did compared to what Kramer did.
And they were like, there's the door, lady.
Take care of yourself.
You're never coming back.
It's like she did one one thousandth and as offensive of a thing as he did,
whether you construe it as racial or not, it was nowhere near what he did.
And again, Roseanne was a very open Trump supporter and she has repeatedly said,
if I didn't support Donald fucking Trump, I would still be working.
And that was the real problem.
And it's true. It's fucking true.
Whether you love or hate Trump, I don't care.
That that is a truth period.
Yeah. So I think somebody there saw an opportunity to get her out quick
and not have to pay, uh, you know, fifty percent of their check to Roseanne each week.
That was probably what motivated that drop.
And she's she's seems she seems happily not going back at this point,
but she's gone in on everybody, even Goodman at this point.
And I was that that made me sad when she when she when Goodman came out
and was like, I miss Roseanne.
And, you know, she was on her podcast and she's like,
he kind of fucking said it when they were fucking crucified.
I was like, all right, I guess I guess this is truly done forever.
Yeah. But who knows?
Slash and Axel got back together.
Anything's possible.
I get how angry people can get in those situations and your friends turn their back on you
and everything else.
But like if Goodman is coming out in this moment in our nation's history
and saying he still supports you and misses you, that's your win, Roseanne.
He can't do anything more than that.
And he's doing a lot. He's sticking his neck way out there.
I agree. I agree with that opinion.
I agree with that. And your friends will not get your back.
When I got canceled by the alt -right people, I won't get into it.
But my God, it was two years of hell and it was before they had a word for it.
But I mean, it was torture, it was harassment, it was whatever.
And this was the alt -right doing it to me.
Not one, not, well, two. Two.
Keith Robinson and Marina Franklin were my only two friends that came.
So even when you're getting it from the team they think is bad,
they don't get your fucking back.
Right.
So anyway, let's get to the, let's go to the movie corner
because I actually have two things that relate to everything we're talking about.
Let's do it.
I talked about a bunch yesterday on the solo corn.
So let me find one I haven't done here.
I have not done how to have sex, which I always pronounce like flex.
Time to have sex. One of the funniest songs ever.
Who sings that song?
I can't remember. Is it shaggy?
No, it's pre -shaggy.
I don't know.
How to have sex is on Mubi.
A couple times a year I get the Mubi free trial.
Mubi is an interesting streamer because they're kind of expensive.
They're 10, 11 bucks, but you can always get the free week trial.
And very often they have an indie movie that gets released nowhere else.
They're one of the few places that gets it exclusively,
so you can't buy it on Apple or Amazon or any of these places.
And to me it's worth it. They usually have really great titles.
They had Decision to Leave.
They had Fallen Leaves, which I'm excited to check out.
And this one, which I had heard a lot of raves about.
It is very good. How to have sex.
Three British teenage girls go on a holiday, drinking, clubbing,
and hooking up in what should be the best summer of their lives.
It's sort of an anti -Euro trip, an anti -American pie,
a much sadder version in that this is girls,
and girls have to put up obviously with a lot more shit
when they are going on these sexual exploration vacations.
It's a short, very, very well acted,
just like slice of life look at one of these trips
where there's guys kind of circling their group.
Some of these guys might have ulterior motives.
It's very stressful at times.
Sort of a less comedic Spring Breakers in that
it just puts you in the mindset of a young hot girl on vacation
who once she starts drinking and having fun at night
is in a great deal of danger.
So the movie becomes pretty dark and somber,
but an important movie.
I dug it. I liked it. Check it out.
I watched, speaking of Keith Robinson,
Keith Robinson's new Netflix special, Different Strokes.
Keith is one of my closest friends in comedy
and has been a bit of a mentor for me over the years.
He had two strokes.
The second one rendered the right side of his body.
He can't use his right arm and he walks with a cane now.
But he's still out there doing comedy
and he's still out there doing what I would say is the best comedy
he's arguably ever done.
His special, Different Strokes covers exactly that, his two strokes.
It is hilarious.
It's never at any point heartbreaking.
It's never at any point sad.
It's truly funny all the way through
because he leans into the fact that he's kind of an asshole.
My favorite joke in the whole thing
is he's talking about getting mad at God
and going, what did I do to deserve this?
Oh, yeah.
So it's a great special.
Amy Schumer produced it.
It's awesome. It's just a great special.
It's really funny.
And the one part I got a little teary
was when I watched him walk out on stage
and get a standing ovation.
And then at the end, there's a shot of his face
and you can see how much this means to him.
You can see he's like, I did this.
And the guy's spirit as a person is incredible.
You know, he has mobility issues, obviously.
And to watch him show up at the clubs every night in New York,
walk, drive his own car,
park, walk 30 minutes in what should take seven or 10
because he moves so slowly by himself with a cane,
pushing through all of that,
getting up on stage every night, doing this.
It's truly, truly incredible.
And it was really nice to see the final product.
And I'm very proud of Keith.
And it's a really funny special.
So check it out.
In my queue.
I can't wait to see it.
I rewatched, though I hadn't seen it
since I was a little tiny kid.
Like I remember watching it pre -10, I think, on television.
The Sugarland Express.
That is Steven Spielberg's second movie,
his follow -up to Duel.
And it's good.
It's not great.
Spielberg immediately, I love Duel.
I think Duel's fucking awesome.
But immediately after these early movies,
he'd snapped into like making nothing
but masterpieces for a while.
So he's kind of finding his way.
The Sugarland Express, you don't watch it
in the way you watch Duel,
where you're like, this guy is a master
who's going to go the distance.
This is much more, it has kind of a TV movie feel to it.
It's Goldie Hawn, a very, very young Goldie Hawn,
and her husband are having their child taken away
by the state of Texas.
And they decide they're going to do whatever
it takes to get him back.
They kidnap a highway patrolman,
and there's a big pursuit, basically.
The Blues Brothers famously shouts out Steven Spielberg.
He's working in the office at the end of the movie
when they finally get to the office
where they're supposed to pay the orphanage's bill.
And it's Steven Spielberg.
And you realize in that moment that I think
John Landis was probably heavily influenced
by early Spielberg because this movie
feels a lot like the less comedic Blues Brothers.
The back half of the movie is 70s style cars
just piling up on each other,
crashing, flying over embankments.
It's cool.
It's a small character study
that turns into a giant car chase movie.
Not classic Spielberg, but if you've never seen it,
it's a fun movie, and Goldie Hawn is great in it.
Joe?
I have one more, again, on topic.
The Acolyte, the new Star Wars show on Disney+.
I'm curious about it.
Well, look, I'm not...
You know, you were saying earlier,
if you express certain things,
you kind of inadvertently get in league
with people you don't want to be in league with.
Yeah.
I certainly don't want to be in league with...
Not that I disagree with all of their points,
but I don't want to be in league with these YouTubers
that are constantly... that have made their lives
about complaining about Kathleen Kennedy
and Star Wars being too woke.
The Acolyte is not a good show.
It's just not. It looks beautiful.
It's the most high -quality Star Wars product
that I've seen hit the television,
and it had, I think, double the budget of Obi -Wan,
which is a weird thing to do.
It's weird to go, we're going to do a limited series
that features Ewan McGregor,
and it's going to be about one of the biggest characters
in the history of this franchise,
and it's going to fill in the gaps between the prequels
and the original trilogy,
and Darth Vader's going to come back.
It's weird to give that half the budget of the Acolyte,
which has none of that stuff in it,
but you can see it on the screen.
It looks great.
And I think the story is cool.
I'm not... Everybody's mad about it's...
It's betraying canon and all this stuff.
I don't know. I thought the story was cool.
I thought it was interesting.
I just think the execution of everything is bad.
The acting is bad.
The writing is okay.
I was going to maybe watch this one
because I love the writer, Leslie Hedlund.
So I'm bummed to hear it's not great,
because she did Russian Doll,
which I think is kind of a brilliant show,
first season anyway,
Sleeping with Other People with Sudeikis,
which I thought was a great rom -com,
one of the really good modern rom -coms.
Bachelorette with Kirsten Dunst, which I loved.
But I also was confused as to why she was taking this,
because her MO is usually writing very smart,
very R -rated dialogue, usually for women.
So I was...
She's not necessarily the name I would think of,
but she's a great writer.
Well, it's this thing that...
You know, usually what happens
with these big franchises,
and we've talked about it,
is they go find some up -and -coming,
amazing indie film director,
and they go,
this guy is somebody we can handcuff,
versus a Joe Dante or somebody
who's going to come in and tell us
what we need to do to make the movie good.
And we'll puppeteer him, and he'll do what we say,
or she'll do what we say, and that'll be it.
Lucasfilm is doing the opposite.
They're going to get in these young...
Not young people, but these lesser -known mainstream people,
and they're going, do your thing.
And it's not working.
They did it with Rian Johnson.
It's not working. It's just not working.
Like, you have to guide these people,
and she's...
The writing's not terrible.
It's not terrible.
The dialogue is not great.
It's passable. It's good enough.
Star Wars has never had amazing dialogue.
It's the acting, and the vibe of the show,
it feels very, like, Matrix -y or something.
It's just off.
And it's a shame, because it could be cool.
People are bitching that it's too woke and all that stuff.
I got to be honest with you.
I thought it was going to be way more heavy -handed
with some kind of agenda or whatever.
It's not. It's just not great.
But everybody's targeting it,
and they're going to try to make an example out of it.
And I think that's stupid.
But, you know, it's...
I feel like it could have been good. I really do.
Whereas Obi -Wan, by the end of it,
I was fucking furious at the decisions they were making.
I don't feel like that with this.
I just feel like it's just not...
It's just not hitting the mark.
There's some really cool concepts, though.
And actually, I think she does have a great respect,
despite some of the things she has said.
I think a lot of what she's said publicly
about Star Wars has been a little misconstrued and whatever.
But I do think she has quite a respect for the mythology of it,
and I think she has quite a respect for what it is.
I just wish this was being carried out better.
And I think it's not being carried out better
because they don't have somebody in that company
that's saying, here's how you do this.
Because I don't think that person exists there.
I used to think it was Dave Filoni.
I love Dave Filoni.
I'm starting to lose a bit of faith in him,
but we'll see what happens.
Let's get to that movie at hand.
This is a title that I have not been able to remember
any time I've tried to say it.
It's too many words or too much something,
but it is called In a Violent Nature.
Yes.
I think that's why I don't remember it.
It's not even proper grammar.
All the violent nature.
I just realized, in a violent nature,
because they're in the woods, nature.
I never put that together until right now,
the play on words, because it doesn't work, really.
I think it's a good title.
Yeah.
I don't know.
Of a violent nature.
Having a violent nature.
In a violent nature, it doesn't work for me.
Yeah, the movie, look,
there's a real bare bones of a plot to this thing.
The basic gist of the movie, let's face it,
is that you're in a Friday the 13th movie
that's not a Friday the 13th movie.
You're following around behind Jason,
who's not quite Jason,
as he walks through the woods,
and every 10 minutes or so, brutally kills somebody.
A couple of the kills go beyond brutal
into like, terrifying, disgusting territory,
or terrifying, if you will.
I also just learned that Jason Patrick
was just cast in Terrifier 3.
I was like, what?
Well, dude, the second movie was huge.
It was huge.
Yeah, the third one's going to be pretty big.
Anyway.
Yeah, they give you tiny touches of plot,
or you can read more into what's going on aside from that,
but for the most part, it feels like a video game
where you're following Jason around
in the world of Friday the 13th on his kills.
What's kind of notable about the movie
is that between each of the kills,
you're basically watching a 10 -minute art piece.
It's shot well and shot interestingly.
It's just extremely slow.
There's also a slow cinema kill.
Slow cinema is the term for these movies
that are like Jerry,
the Gus Van Sant movie with Matt Damon or whatever,
where you're just real -time walking around with people.
Slow cinema is a nice way to say boring, basically.
This movie even has a slow cinema kill
where we're watching very slowly
a guy's body be cut up by a woodchipper, Fargo -style.
That scene in particular looked fake to me,
and I thought to myself,
this is neither scary or disgusting or funny or anything,
so what am I watching, really?
The whole movie left me with that kind of an experience.
By the end, I said, well done.
I enjoyed getting another look at the slasher genre
from a different POV.
I enjoyed that they didn't go crazy with the running time
because, look, 45 minutes of this, nothing happens at all.
But overall, I was left kind of with a question mark on it.
I admired, especially the kill
where he pulls the girl's head through her body.
I was like, that's a very impressive kill.
That was great.
But to do those crazy, violent, intense kills
offset with 10 minutes of nothing in silence,
interesting experiment
in the way a lot of these shutter movies are.
I thought Late Night with the Devil was an interesting experiment,
but did I love it? No.
Would I watch it again? No.
I will say,
and boy, am I going to piss some people off
with what I'm about to say.
I thought it was a solid movie.
I did enjoy watching it.
I did enjoy the killer perspective.
I did like the approach of you're just going to kind of
overhear characters saying certain things
that are going to clue you into the mythology
of what's happening here and who this killer is
and how he rises from the grave and all that shit.
Right.
I felt like that the way in which it was executed at times
was not good,
meaning why is the sheriff telling the story of this guy
as he's walking toward him
to these people he just met?
And it's like, well, because efficiency -wise,
that's how you have to do it in a movie like this.
It's like, yeah, but you could have thought of a better way of doing that.
It's also, we're in his POV throughout,
and then there are scenes where you're just not,
and it's like, well, wait a minute.
Is this a formal exercise or isn't it?
I'd want to...
Well, you're in his POV. You're with him.
Yeah.
But it's not really...
You're with those two women in the car on the side of the road.
He's not there.
Well, that's an interesting shift, though, at that point,
because at that point, spoiler alert,
it's revealed at the very end because he's gone now,
and it's like, oh, that's interesting.
It's shifted to...
Yeah.
This is where I'm going to piss people off.
So despite my criticisms, I do think it's a solid movie,
even though it's not a great movie.
And that's what I will say about most young horror directors
in early ventures.
Here we go.
Halloween is not a great movie.
It's got some interesting stuff.
It's well done in certain places.
There are other places where you're like, that's corny.
The guy wouldn't talk like that.
Or this part's kind of boring.
We all love Halloween.
The Hills Have Eyes is another great example.
It's not a great movie.
No.
It's enjoyable.
You wouldn't go, my God.
I wouldn't even say it's enjoyable.
What a film.
My point is there are always...
Black Christmas, in my opinion,
is a much better piece of cinema than Halloween is.
Whether you like Halloween better or you disagree, fine.
My point, though, is that this movie, to me,
speaks to the importance of a movie like Halloween,
regardless of whether I think it's a masterpiece or not.
It's important.
And I think this movie, to me,
because the same guy did The Void, which was a cool movie.
Again, not great, but very cool.
I felt like this guy did...
I didn't know that.
And I didn't see The Void, actually.
Very HP, Lovecrafty.
Okay.
But this, to me, felt like something that mattered in the horror space.
Somebody doing something, run and gun, low budget,
that gave you just enough to enjoy yourself
and be curious as to whether or not there was going to be more of it.
I thought there were some bad choices made.
You shouldn't see...
The killer, they go through such this...
Excuse me.
They go through such a long and intriguing setup
to the killer finally putting the mask on.
Yeah.
Where you see the back of his head,
and you see...
Because he starts with him rising from the grave.
You know he's kind of like a zombie or something.
And...
By the way, Jason wasn't that.
Right?
Eventually he is.
Eventually he's...
Eventually he gets summoned from the earth?
I don't remember that.
Well, that's what happens.
Jason's a normal human up until part six.
And part six was called Jason and the Hymns,
because they literally resurrect him from the dead.
Right.
Yeah, okay, gotcha.
This was very Jason in that sense.
You know, he put...
So after he comes out of the grave,
you see that he's got back of the head, side of the head.
You never see his face.
And then he finds this really cool old firefighter mask.
It's really creepy looking.
And he puts that on.
I'm like, wow.
Bravo, guys.
You've managed to find the last thing a killer can use as a mask
that's still scary that we haven't seen already.
Like, that was very impressive to me.
But then, like 10 minutes later,
he takes the mask off and you just see his face.
And you're like, don't show me his face.
That's part of why this is scary,
is because I don't know what he looks like.
And it bothered me.
I found that quite weird that we're looking at his face
like up close at that point in the movie.
Yeah.
I was like, huh?
Yes.
Yeah.
So I didn't like that.
The part you're talking about with the,
it wasn't a wood chipper.
It was a log.
It was like a log splitter.
Log cutter.
Yeah.
Gas -powered log cutter, whatever.
That part I didn't get because it's like,
why is he dragging a dead body to cut the body up on the log?
Like, he's not depraved.
He drags a dead body,
sets it in front of the line of this like slow -moving wood cutter.
And then you see like, in my opinion,
a pretty damn fake looking dummy get cut up by a wood chipper
very slowly for several minutes.
And it's like, I just didn't get it.
In a world where we also have clearly a very expensive,
gratuitous, disgusting kill,
one of the all -time kills in one of these type of movies
where he like turns the woman inside out,
then why are we now watching this logs thing?
It's like half the kills are creatively staged and exciting.
The other half are boring.
And then all of the walking through the valley stuff is pretty dull.
Also, why is he cutting the body?
My point is, the whole point of him rising from the grave is,
he was wrongly murdered.
His mother's amulet, who he loved more than anybody on Earth,
guards his grave.
And if the amulet is taken, he will rise from the grave.
And kill until he finds it.
He's not a depraved, you know, he's not Charles Manson,
where he's like, let's go play with a dead body now that we killed it.
Like, put a live guy on the fucking log cutter.
Show the guys alive. Show them screaming.
And like, oh my God, this is horrifying.
The other part that really bothered me,
and stuff like this will send me spinning,
the sheriff shoots him as he's explaining to these campers
who this guy is and what his legend is and why they need to stop him.
He shoots him.
The monster goes down, unconscious.
Yeah.
They go, is he dead?
And he goes, no, that'll just put him down for a minute.
And then they spend the entire time that they have disabled this man,
when he's unconscious,
discussing what they should possibly do next,
instead of walking over to his unconscious body and blowing his head off.
Yeah.
And they literally talk, talk, talk, then walk over just in time for him to wake up.
I'm like, guys, come on, man, that's fucking lazy.
Say he's out of bullets.
Something. Come on.
Like, this is come on.
It really suffers at a screenplay level,
to an extent where it's like, I almost don't know if it had one, you know?
It's like, well, we're just going to follow this guy around,
and we're going to shoot some kills, and we're not real worried about the story,
whatever.
But it's like, man, do I wish they had put a little more effort into it,
because I just kind of was left with a shrug at the end of the thing.
I get people liking it because it's a different take on the genre.
I think I would have rather watched this than yet another generic teen slasher.
But just because it's different doesn't mean it's great.
You know, I think doing this kind of formal experiment
and making it great is what would have made it great.
You know, sometimes, like, there's a lot of movies that use one take,
or I watched this movie called The Tribe, which was all deaf kids,
and they didn't give it subtitles,
so you never knew what people were talking about.
Those kind of gimmicks are just interesting, but they're just gimmicks,
if you don't take the time to write a great script around them.
That script, The Tribe, is a really cool and interesting movie.
It's disturbing, you get it, you're on board with it,
because they took the time to tell an engaging and creative story
to support the gimmick.
This to me didn't, and I was just left with too many questions.
I'm like, what are you trying to say thematically?
Are you trying to say anything about, not that you have to,
but are you trying to say something about how we watch these movies?
Are you trying to say something about violence and how it affects us?
And if not, fine, but since everything about this movie is so artistic,
it leaves you looking for something that is maybe not there, in my opinion.
It's not that deep and it's not that well written.
It's well shot, but I think the story needed a lot of work.
Even if you don't make it much more of a story than what's here,
which is bare bones, that's fine.
It just doesn't hit moment to moment.
You don't care what's happening, and that's a problem, obviously.
I think it's a nice effort.
Yes.
It's not as good as Halloween.
No.
I'd put it above a Hills Have Eyes.
And again, it feels like one of those earlier stripped down works
of some of our fine horror directors.
And I think those movies are flawed, and I think this one's flawed too,
but overall I think it is worth a watch.
Yeah, I agree.
It's interesting.
And that's what I would say.
My hog is up.
It's not soaring, but it's fine.
Yeah.
Yeah, it left too much up to me,
and I didn't care enough to fill in all the cracks that are there in the movie, frankly.
There's one super memorable kill.
I think when you look at the slasher genre,
one super memorable kill is often enough to make a movie stand the test of time.
And this movie has some stuff going for it.
There's stuff I haven't seen before, vibes I haven't felt before,
but I don't want to see the movie a second time.
We are going to be back with a review of Bratz,
Andrew McCarthy's documentary about the Brat Pack
and the lingering effects of the name Brat Pack.
It's on Hulu if you'd like to watch that before the next app.
And that's all I got.
Miss Pat Season 4 is back and doing extremely well on the BET Plus app,
thanks to those who've watched.
And I'm on Instagram at ThePatrickWalsh.
We are on Instagram at SeeYouInHellPod.
I am told that I keep mentioning the Etsy page
and that there are no Etsy products available,
so I'm sorry for that.
I thought there were.
What am I doing?
I'll be out on the Burt Kreischer tour this weekend,
fully loaded, four dates, including Pittsburgh and Buffalo,
amongst other places.
After that, I don't know what the summer holds
because I have some news about something I'll be doing
that I can't talk about just yet.
This is the hot dog eating competition?
Yeah.
And thank you to everybody for selling out the special taping
on September 14th.
I appreciate that.
Also, too, we announced it yesterday.
Well, as of this recording, it was yesterday.
Thank you to the Taste Buds fans for all these years of laughs
and whatever, and thank you for all the messages coming in.
But yes, we have taken an indefinite hiatus,
and we'll be back at some point.
But it's all love.
It's all good.
It's just everybody's got other things going on.
But this show is going nowhere in many ways.
We'll be back, folks.
We'll see you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.