🎵 I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, and when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams, you know I'll stay. I'll see you in hell, you know I will. I'll see you in hell, you know I will. 🎵
To talk to you about a, I don't know that I'd call it a spring film, but it does take place in the spring, I believe, or in the summer. Sinners? Is it the summer time?
It seemed hot, you know, people were sweating.
I kept saying the title like the gypsy in Thinner. I kept going, Sinners! And everybody with me was like, stop doing that.
I, uh, my buddy Griffin Moore, uh, who is an actor and, uh, and a great guy, just the best dude. But, uh, what am I?
Second best?
I don't know, I'd say second. Come on.
Top ten?
He's a great dude, but, uh, I think I can...
I think I can say this, uh, but, uh, he was...
He killed a woman, uh, he had been drinking too much, and...
Anyway, his name again, Griffin Moore, uh, he lives in...
He texted me last night about Sinners.
Yeah.
Randomly, and he was like, I was in the movie.
I was like, oh, that's funny, we're talking about it on my podcast tomorrow, and I said, who, who were you in the movie?
And he goes, the brother that got turned into a vamp... Griffin's black.
He said, the brother that got turned into a vampire.
And I was like, why don't you...
Why don't you narrow that...
Well, I go, I said it, I, he said, the brother that got turned into a vampire, and I said, why don't you narrow that down?
There were 87.
I was gonna say.
And, uh, he goes, what do you mean, the brother?
Like, Michael B. Jordan, his brother.
He's like, I, I was the, I played him, and then they, like, put his face on me.
Oh.
And I was like, oh, you mean the literal...
I was like, I'm sorry, Gordon, I thought you meant the black guy when you said the brother, and, uh, we were just laughing, it was very funny.
I would see a movie called The Brother Who Became a Vampire.
It sounds...
You ever see The Brother From Another Planet with Joe Morton?
When I was a young child, I loved that movie.
Yeah, good movie.
But I don't remember it at all.
John Sayles.
What's that?
It was with, uh, John Sayles, who I love as a writer -director.
It was Joe Morton, was the brother from Terminator 2.
Yes.
Who's John Sayles again?
John Sayles did one of my favorite movies of all time, new to Criterion 4K, Lone Star, with...
With McConaughey and Chris Christopherson.
I think that movie is amazing.
It's like a novel come to life.
And then he also did Meituan, he did, uh...
He's done a bunch of movies, good stuff.
Baby, it's you.
I got mixed up.
I was thinking of Soupy Sayles.
Who's not as funny as you'd think with that name.
No.
Folks, Sinners has become a real conversation piece, not just the movie itself.
Which we will get to.
But it's become one of these things where any mild criticism of it will get you branded a problem, a racist.
I mean, I just stopped talking about it.
I was like, none of the issues I am expressing about this movie have anything to do with race.
But it's like, this is a moment, a movie, and we don't want to hear a single negative thing about it as a society.
And it's like, okay.
I get it.
Not wanting to harsh your vibe or something, but also, shouldn't we be able to talk about things?
I found a lot of great things about it and some problems, frankly.
I get the...
Nobody's going to expect me to say what I'm about to say.
I get that stance, the counter stance to you with the movie, given what Coogler did with it in a business...
I mean, thematically, too, obviously, the movie's message is relative.
It's relevant and important.
But given what Coogler did to the studios with this thing, this is a landmark moment.
So I get why people might be a little prickly about, like...
But I don't think you're a racist if you have a...
You know, you can criticize the structure of something or whatever.
That's all I would be doing.
I mean, I really did enjoy it.
It's incredible filmmaking.
I just had a couple issues.
That's all.
I also shouldn't have prefaced what I said with the way I prefaced it.
I didn't mean...
I didn't mean everybody's going to be surprised that I'm defending being against racists.
That's not what I meant.
I just meant, like, I'm usually the guy that's like, I'm tired of everybody saying you got to think this or think that.
You know, that's all I meant by that.
I know.
Anyway.
The reason, at least the reason I am always bending over backwards is the lead comment on our iTunes page.
There's two visible comments when you go to our iTunes.
One is like, love these boys.
They're hilarious.
And the other one is like...
These two are racist.
They should never talk about race.
All of their opinions on race are from the Civil War.
You know, whatever.
It's like, probably a troll, but it really bothers me that that's like the representation of our podcast.
Because I feel like all we do is go out of our way to like, be right.
You know, not be right, but be true to what the culture is doing.
Not be, you know, saying shitty things.
And also to...
At least our goal.
Maybe we were 10 years ago, but we've changed.
Also, too, to be balanced and to be able to have a nuanced discussion.
That's, you know, it's like nobody's here to carry water for any side of the aisle, no matter what the aisle is.
It's like we want to...
Look, at the end of the day, we want to be able to talk about movies as movies.
Yeah.
And, you know, that was probably the person that left.
That is probably some...
A 22 -year -old white chick.
Oh, yeah.
It definitely was not a person.
Sitting in, you know, who was an assistant to a pedophile who's going to have a five -picture deal in two years because...
Well, she was there and she bought the lubes for him, but she was very brave because she sat outside his office.
I'm Kerry Becker, assistant to the pedophile.
Yeah.
It's a funny sketch of a pedophile that needs an assistant.
I can't...
Yeah.
I don't need you to facilitate the hangs.
I just need you to kind of look the other way.
I just need a guy that's so busy.
Yeah.
He needs somebody to...
Tell the kid, I can't do 2 p .m. playground today.
It's 3 or I walk.
Yeah.
Where do you see yourself in five years?
Here's where I see myself.
I see myself in a five -year -old, ladies and gentlemen.
Good to be talking about pedophilia again on this podcast.
It used to be a mainstay.
It really was.
I forgot about that.
And you haven't done the, why did you tell...
Well, there's a lot now.
We got a Paul Schrader on our hands.
Oh, no.
Yeah.
What happened with Schrader?
Well, Schrader is interesting because he, much like Shannon Sharp,
but on a much lower...
On a much lower scale, offered to settle, you know,
and Schrader, Shannon Sharps was $10 million.
Paul Schrader's was much less money than that.
But he offered to settle.
It was an assistant that accused him of being inappropriate.
And at the moment when they were about to settle,
Paul Schrader was like, I can't do this.
I'm not paying this woman.
This is fucked up.
I'm not doing it.
Oh, wow.
Okay.
But then, of course, that makes you guilty in today's climate.
And Shannon Sharp was doing the same thing.
Yeah.
She was paying $10 million.
Then she goes, nah, I want $50 million.
And now he looks back.
It was like, if you're not guilty, why were you going to pay her $10 million?
And he was like, to keep people from hearing about my weird sexual proclivities.
But then he has a podcast where he talks nonstop about his sexual proclivities.
Well, I've also heard the defense, the settled defense.
Who did this?
It might have been...
Now, I don't even want to speculate because that sucks.
If it gets attached to somebody, it's not supposed to be attached to you.
But I have.
I have, in recent months, heard the defense where the person that got accused said, well,
I settled because it was the only way to end this.
Yeah.
Like, I didn't think it was right.
I didn't do it.
But I didn't know how else to just make this stop.
I certainly didn't want to go through a three -year process with it.
Yeah.
So I get that.
I actually think it's good.
You said it was bad, optically.
I thought it was good, optically.
The trader said, no, actually, I'm not going to pay you.
That, to me, says...
Because, like, you know, I was going to just try to make this go away because it's bullshit,
but I'm actually not going to do that.
I'm going to fight you now.
To me, that's like, oh, maybe he's not guilty.
But I don't know, you know?
Well, I certainly felt that with Schrader, but I know in my heart it's just because I'm
a fan.
And I try to really be better about that, to not blindly like somebody because I'm a
fan of their work.
And I don't know anything about Shannon Sharp, so...
The Sharp one, he's...
The few details I know...
His response was so swift and demonstrative that I was like, maybe he's clean, man, because
like, you don't...
He responded so fast.
And I was like, wow.
Like, there was no pow -wowing or whatever.
I'm like, okay, I guess that looks good.
Well, she was adamant about saying, you know, he choked me, he raped me, et cetera.
But then...
All their communication is involving rough sex, choking, blah, blah, blah, all their texts,
which is another reason I am very happy to be out of the dating pool at the moment, for
Christ's sake, because the choking is becoming a thing, and it's becoming a problem.
Well, and then the flip side of it is, too, her accounts were so detailed, I was like,
all right, maybe he did.
I don't know.
I don't want to speculate, but it's a dicey, choppy water, so to speak.
Ooh, baby, baby, it's a...
Wild world.
My father sends me YouTube links of songs as communication.
He won't call.
He hasn't called me in years, and he'll text, you know, once a month some piece of information,
usually about his incoming death and what I need to do to be prepared for his incoming death.
But he'll send me, like, Cat Stevens' Wild World.
He'll send me, like, a Bob Dylan song.
You know?
Texan Browns.
There's always a song he likes.
He'll send the same songs 10 times.
Yeah.
No add -on.
No, like, this made me think of you, which is the key to having a relationship with your
son.
It's just like...
And I would complain about it when I was going to therapy, and she was like, couldn't you
just look at it like your dad's trying to connect and reach out?
And I'm like, yeah, I guess so.
I guess so.
I guess I'll just drastically lower my expectations and maybe be happier.
And it worked.
Drastically lowering your expectations of everyone in your life will make you like them
more.
Well, phenomenal advice.
Some of the best advice I ever got, and it's probably a meme somewhere, but it was just
should is the worst word in the English language.
Once you say should, you're in trouble.
This person should do that.
Should have, yeah.
This person should be acting that way.
This should have happened.
It's like, it's just...
That's what marriage is.
Yeah, right.
Both of you going, this person should have for years and years and years until you go
your separate ways.
Well...
If you're on the fence, that's my recommendation of marriage.
On that note...
Oh, we have one other new psycho.
Let's talk real quick about this Netflix...
Yeah.
CEO, CFO, whatever the hell his name is, title is, whatever.
I mean, you know...
It's Ted Sarandos, who's got a real punchable face.
This guy.
And I sent Joe this article, and we can discuss, because it really bugged me, and I thought
the comments were pretty insightful on it, and I keep thinking about it because of how
smug and obnoxious it is.
But basically, the headline, and we try not to just do headlines, I did read the whole
article, but it says, Ted Sarandos says the theatrical experience is, quote, an outmoded
idea for most people.
Claims Netflix...
He also goes on to say something I found absolutely ridiculous.
Just because you live in New York and can walk to a movie theater, most people in this
country cannot.
Like, I've been in every state of this fucking union, and you're never more than 15 minutes
drive away from a movie theater.
That is so stupid.
Yeah, he's doing the classic, let's bend reality...
To fit our mission.
Yeah, he's lying.
It's politician shit.
Yeah, and it's just like, dude, he could have said, hey, like it, or love it, or hate it,
what we're doing.
Yeah.
I view it as this.
I think the landscape is changing, and I think that people prefer to watch something at home,
and we're servicing that.
By all means, we do not want to destroy this other mode of experience.
We're not servicing a film.
But instead, in classic Netflix fashion, and I swear, my opinions on Netflix have nothing
to do with the fact that they passed on my special that's about to come out, by the way,
in June, everybody.
Whereabouts?
On the old internet.
I'll be announcing the specifics.
I hear you make more money that way.
Apparently.
You could.
We'll see.
Yeah.
Well, you joined great company.
I've seen a lot of great specials on YouTube, so...
I kind of have to keep telling myself...
I had to keep telling myself that, because I was pretty upset when I got a no from Hulu
and Netflix, especially when you see a lot of what's on Hulu and Netflix.
Oh, yeah.
But I had to keep telling myself, like, hey, man, Shane and Mark Normand and Ali Sadiq,
and there's a million great comics out there that did the internet self -release thing first
before...
Yeah.
I love Sam Talent.
I've never heard of him.
I loved his online special.
Sam Talent is the man.
What a great comic.
Yeah.
And just a great, great guy.
And one of the...
Amazing author, too, by the way.
He's got a great book.
I think it's called Running the Light.
One of the funniest dudes I've ever met, and just a pure joy of a human to be around.
And yes, I feel that way about you, Pat.
Oh, thanks.
But, you know, in any case...
My opinions are my opinions, but it's just...
You know, my take on the industry at this point is, hey, if they're dumb enough to give you
their money, take their money.
Don't be an idiot.
Give it a shot.
But at the same time, if they say no, at least we have a way to keep things moving.
But, you know, in typical Netflix fashion, instead of coming out with a balanced and
sort of diplomatic take, whatever.
Whatever.
Maybe there's too much diplomacy.
I don't know.
But just the arrogance of him to state it the way he did, and it's coming from the place
that has refused to show numbers of streaming numbers to anybody.
They have continually changed the rules of what a watch, in quotes, counts as.
They've made big changes in the heat of strikes.
You know?
It's all very...
Very suspicious to me.
And also, this coming on the heels of the announcement of they're going to spend $18
billion on new content next year, accompanied by the quote, we're nowhere near a ceiling.
It's just disgusting.
It's just gross.
You should be.
The world is near a ceiling, so Netflix should be.
So...
Yeah, it's...
What bothers me the most about him is the smugness.
It's like what you're saying.
It's impossible, really, in a capitalist society, to fault somebody for finding a fairly
ingenious way of making money, and then to make nonstop money off it forever.
You've done it.
You've made whole art forms much less important and much less impactful, which is not something
to be proud of.
But the thing is, I would assume that Sam Walton wasn't going, they're coming to Walmart
because it is the best.
It is the best store in America, the finest products, the finest quality.
Don't tell me you're making art over there at Netflix.
When I am a massive film fan, and the once a week I log into your system, I can't find
a goddamn movie or a goddamn show, and I usually wind up watching something I've already seen,
if anything.
Or this baffling Mulaney show, which is even more baffling because now they'll have the
occasional brilliant sketch.
And I'm like, wait a minute.
That was great.
And then they go back to nothing.
Anyway.
I was talking to Pinkstone about this, and he pointed out, he was like, you know, how
quickly, he was like, you know, you forget Netflix is the streaming service and studio
that brought us Stranger Things.
This amazing, groundbreaking show because they took a chance and made something cool.
And he was like, they've already ditched that approach.
Like, already.
Already.
The show is still going.
It's not even done yet.
And they've already ditched the approach of taking a chance on a newer voice, a newer
idea, whatever.
They'll say they haven't.
They absolutely have.
I know that most people will turn on Netflix and see, for instance, a new stand -up special
from a person they've never heard of before.
But do 10 seconds of research on that person, and you'll see they have hundreds and hundreds
of thousands of followers.
They already have a built -in audience, and Netflix is just absorbing it and capitalizing
on it.
It's sad to me.
I saw a thing with Tom Hanks.
Again, Tom Hanks, like him, don't like him, whatever.
One of the things I appreciate about Tom Hanks is he's always been a very graceful guy in
interviews, and he discussed exactly this.
And he was just like, look, man, it's a tough call.
He was like, you know...
If a movie comes out in a theater and you say, okay, we got the babysitter, we're going
to drive 15 minutes to the theater, we're going to find parking, we're going to get
there this many minutes early so we can grab snacks and find the right seat and all that
and then sit down, he goes, you are locked into that experience.
And he goes, to me, that will always be an amazing way to see a film.
He goes, at the same time...
If you're saying to somebody, for 25 bucks, you can just do that in your house and not
go through all that, too, he's like, I also understand that.
And his take, excuse me, his take was, to me, the exact right temperature of like, yes,
that's exactly what this is.
You know, we can accept both.
I do both.
I have times where I go, I want to go to the movies, and I have times where I go, oh, Christ,
I'm just going to wait.
I'm just going to wait until I can rent the monkey for 20 bucks.
I do both, you know, and we'd have a lot more arrows in our quiver to argue the side of
theatrical distribution if we had more than three good movies a year, you know?
Yeah.
I am going to have a few criticisms about Sinners.
It's the best movie I've seen this year, you know?
Yeah.
And I'd rank it about a B+.
I mean, we're doomed.
And also, as far as Sinners goes, it's a perfect example of what we're talking about.
I mean, this is...
This is what's killing me about Sinners.
It's like...
And it goes to show how short -sighted and how truly flawed these studios and studio
executives are.
How many times do they have to learn this lesson?
They've learned it now twice with Ryan Coogler.
Yeah.
That there's an audience for black cinema out there, and there's an audience for good
black cinema.
That takes an artistic approach to a genre.
There's a massive audience out there for it.
They learn this lesson once a year with black audiences, and they learn it once every year
with female audiences.
It ends with us, comes out, does money.
Are there women out here going to the movies?
It happens every fucking year.
It's so crazy.
I had a meeting yesterday at T Street, which is Rian Johnson's company, who does the Knives
Out pictures.
And they said to me, the Monday morning after Sinners, like you always hear, like, what
are the studios looking for?
And a place like Rian Johnson will definitely hear, here's what we're looking for, because
he's a top guy.
And he was like, day one, they call, they put the word out, they put the feelers out.
I think we're looking to get back into originals after the success of Sinners.
We're kind of looking to get back into some original ideas.
Oh, God.
Jesus Christ.
It's also so dumb, like, for that to be an M .O.
What kind of movies do you make?
Original ones.
Like, what are you doing?
I mean, that's a good starting point, but you should know a little better about what kind
of movies you want to make.
I'm not talking about Rian Johnson.
I'm talking about the business.
And there's all these things.
He knows very well what movies he wants to make, and he makes them well.
There's all these think pieces coming out now, too, about the Kugler deal with Sinners.
Yeah, fascinating.
Fascinating.
Where they're like.
He's going to break the system.
It's amazing.
He actually is retaining the rights to his own movie that he wrote and championed and
directed as a top director in Hollywood.
Twenty -five years after the studio owns it, rights will revert back to him.
Can you believe it?
It's like, this is how it should be.
Yeah.
Like, we're making.
Apparently, Tarantino got the deal on Once Upon a Time, and nobody mentioned it.
Well, here's the thing.
It's like, what's killing me is just like, that's a great deal.
I'm excited that this is happening for him.
But it's like, the fact that we're like Oliver Twist with the porridge bowl.
It's like, this is a thing they should just be doing.
It's insane that they're going to make millions, if not billions of dollars on this movie across
25 years.
And then, yeah.
Oh, the rights go back to the guy that created everything?
How unique.
It's of course they should do that.
And he's a young man.
You know, he'll be 60 or 65 by that time.
It's just a retirement plan.
It's like, for some reason, the arts, they feel like you should have very different and
not the same rights as everyone else with regards to your money.
It's getting worse by the day.
I think it's a huge win.
And of course, there's lots of directors who are going to be like, well, you want me?
I got to get the Coogler deal.
And that's a good thing.
These places should be scared.
Like, they need to start.
They need to start adapting and paying people fairly, period.
Yes.
It'll be.
And sadly, a lot of directors will try to get that Coogler deal.
And a lot of directors, I don't want to say one director deserves it more than another.
But I also understand, like, if you're newer, you got to play a little ball.
I get all that.
But, you know, the industry rule used to be you get fucked on the first one.
You get fucked on the second one.
But if the first one's successful,
you call your shots on the second one.
That's long gone.
You know.
So this Coogler deal is amazing.
But there are plenty of directors and creators that are going to come in and say,
I want this and I deserve it.
And they're going to say, well, then take a walk.
You know.
Eli Roth is doing an incredible thing.
He's got this new movie company where he is doing a thing where he's selling shares to the public.
And he's like, I forget what it's called, but he goes, I watched an interview with him.
He said.
He said, you know, man, maybe you're a guy that lives in Iowa who drives a truck who said,
I always wanted to be in horror movies and you have no means to get into it.
He goes, I'm creating a thing where you can buy shares in the movies I'm making.
It's not crowdfunding.
You will own a piece of the movie and your money will go towards making the movie.
And if the movie does well, you will benefit.
And he goes, and this is now going to allow me to make the craziest horror movies.
I'm able to make.
And he was like, he was like, I want you to think a hostile and think that that is the tamest it's going to be.
And I was like, this is awesome, man.
I, I, I, yeah, I think that's great.
And I, I hope it really works for him and for the people that are going to partake in it as fans.
Yeah.
That Zach Braff thing that the crowdsourcing thing didn't really catch on, but like there, there's going to be different kinds of funding sprouting up.
There has to be because it's like, as soon as people start realizing they're not the only game in town.
Movies will get a lot more interesting again, hopefully.
Let's hit that corner, Joe.
Absolutely.
I rewatched the Truman show.
Oh, nice.
In glorious 4k.
I had not seen it in decades.
I was, I was surprised by how little, I guess I remembered of it.
It's essentially a science fiction movie almost, even though there's no science in it.
It's it's, it feels like.
It feels like a long form twilight zone, um, in the best way there's lots, there's lots of movies with, that could be a whole episode, like movies that feel like the twilight zone, Pleasantville's another one.
There's a bunch of them.
Um, it's very short, a hundred minutes.
And I remember loving it in the meantime, it has become one of the most acclaimed movies ever.
It came out in this, uh, this kind of Renaissance of the late nineties, 98, 99 was a, was a time of like.
Great growth, artistic growth in movies.
That was when I was coming out of high school and are in high school and just everything that came out seemed to be amazing.
You watch the Truman show now.
Yes, it was way ahead of its time.
Yes, it is a brilliant satire of reality TV and where we are now.
And things only got worse from here.
Um, my issues with it will keep it from being what, you know, everyone always says one of the best movies of the nineties, one of the best movies, one of the best movies ever.
You see about the.
Truman show for me, I gotta be honest.
The issue is Jim Carrey.
And I think it's because he, the man has changed so much that I view him differently and him in that him in a going for the joke.
Ace Ventura is still legendary, but him when he's in that mawkish, I'm looking for a, uh, some tears mode doesn't ring true to me when I watch it.
Now, like his performance in this feels a little big.
He's still trying to do some of his class.
It's a comedy, but it's a much more serious story.
And that that's it.
My, my only real issue with it was those tonal things.
I would have rather seen this with a Tom Hanks with a somebody else, but he's fine in it.
Laura Linney's great in it.
Um, Ed Harris is really good in a part that was originally played by Dennis Hopper.
Um, and the, the script is incredibly tight and well done.
I just don't get passionate about the movie.
The movie doesn't move me.
I just feel like, oh, that's smart.
That was really ahead of.
It's.
Good movie, Joe.
Um, well, speaking of what we're speaking of an independent film and all that stuff.
Uh, I went up to the, uh, oh Christ.
What is that store called?
I can't believe I'm blank.
Vinegar syndrome.
The vinegar syndrome store.
The, um, uh, for God's sakes.
Yeah.
What the hell is the name of the store?
The.
The vinegar syndrome store.
Yeah.
Oh, the archive.
The archive.
Um, I was up in Connecticut doing shows, uh, thanks to everybody that came out by the
way.
Uh, but I was in Connecticut, so I was there.
So I was like, oh, let me go to the archive.
Let me, let me go grab some stuff.
Uh, always a nice experience at that store.
I walked out with two purchases, uh, the 4k of the street trash remake sequel and last
tango in Paris, which as I said to a friend of mine, if you saw that purchase on a police,
police report where I was under questioning, that's all you'd need to see.
But anyway, um, let me get that copy of happiness back there as well.
Um, but anyway, street trash.
Um, this is a, I guess it's a technically a sequel.
Um, it, I bought it on blind faith.
I really liked the original.
The original is completely insane and really goofy.
And I saw it on a Joe Bob show.
Yeah.
And this, this version.
This version is in very much in the vein of that.
Uh, Cineverse is the studio behind it.
I believe.
I don't know if they acquired it or, or were there from day one.
Cineverse also is the, they're behind the toxic Avenger remake.
They're doing some cool stuff.
Um, I'm glad I own it cause I own the original.
I'm glad I have this version of it too.
Um, it works in places.
All of the budget went to the practical effects.
The, the practical effects are pretty astounding in places, legitimately gross in places.
And there are moments where they're doing a practical effect of like a guy's face melting
off and there's like holes in his face.
And I'm, I literally at times it was like, how the hell did they just do that?
That looks so real.
It's crazy.
So, uh, it's, it's well done in that sense.
Um, it takes place in Cape town, South Africa.
It's about a, uh, a.
A sinister corporation down there creating a new version of the chemical that is in the
booze in the first movie.
Uh, and it's in the near future and they're taking that chemical and putting it into drones
that are flying around and basically spraying it on homeless people because they're trying
to wipe out this homeless population because of the economic disparity in, uh, in that
area.
Um, the deaths are wild and over the top.
The plot is serviceable, just like in the first one.
It's nothing that's going to make you go, oh my God.
Uh, but interesting enough.
Um, the, you know, the, the, the place I had a few problems with it is the, it was the humor.
They, they try too hard to be funny.
Yeah.
And.
You know, look, comedy just doesn't work unless you've got.
Yeah.
A true comedic direct.
Everybody thinks comedy is just the writing.
It's not just the writing.
It's got a lot to do with the director and a director knowing if a joke plays and how
to execute humorous dialogue without making it look quippy or whatever.
So it, it falls very short in my opinion in that department.
But that said, if you like the original, you're going to like this one.
Nobody is picking up the, uh, street trash 2024.
K Blu -ray and, and, you know, expecting, uh, uh, you know, on the waterfront or something.
So, um, it's worth a watch, you know, again, I'm glad I own it.
Uh, and I'm sure I'll return to it at some point.
I rewatched no country for old men and glorious 4k, the new criteria on release.
It looks fantastic.
And it's weird with me, with the Coen's it's, it's almost like no country.
It's like, okay, we all can say that's their masterpiece.
And then let's talk about what our favorite Coen movie is.
It's just, it's, it plays like the, even the first time I saw it, it just plays like the
accumulation of everything.
The Coen brothers have been doing throughout their entire career.
It feels like the last time they were truly great, even though did serious man come after,
I think it was before this.
Um, it's the best, you know, it's, it's Brolin.
It's Bardem.
I'm killing it.
One of the great villains.
Oh yeah.
It's, uh, stolen.
The movie is stolen by Tommy Lee Jones in my favorite all time.
Tommy Lee Jones performance.
It's basically his fugitive character on the verge of death.
He's seen everything.
He's experienced everything.
The scene between Tommy Lee Jones and this other old fat guy talking about how standards have fallen, how Tommy, they're
like.
When you stop here and sir and madam, you know, everything else is soon to fall or it's what every couple old men talk about every day.
It's what Joe and I talk about on this show.
There's always going to be old men talking about how things used to be better, but this movie really gets that.
Like we're losing humanity with each passing year and there seems to be nothing we can do about it.
And it's only gotten significantly worse since this movie was released.
Um, obviously.
It's an equal triumph with Cormac McCarthy.
His novel is one of the great American novels, but this is just a masterful adaptation.
It is so good.
The Coen's keep a little bit of their trademark comedy, but they pretty much reign it in and it's all the more effective for it.
It's so good in terms of editing, cinematography, acting, writing.
It's just the best.
It's great.
Joe.
And then also that scene, uh, involves Barry Corbin.
That's him.
Corbin.
Yes.
Um, who's been in a million things.
He's one of those guys.
I should not have just called him that big fat guy.
Yeah.
Barry Corbin is his name.
He's one of those guys.
You see him and you go, oh yeah, that guy.
Um, who was on what?
Major Dad?
Well, I don't know about Major Dad.
Barry Corbin, one of the stars of Who's Harry Crumb.
That's right.
Yeah.
I'm sure he doesn't lead with that, but yes.
Um, but anyway, uh, he's that scene, like Corbin's in that.
No, Corbin's the, Corbin's Tommy Lee Jones's brother, right?
Right.
The guy that when he goes, he goes to that awful house where the guy's just living in
squalor.
Barry Corbin's the guy in the wheelchair.
And I'm sorry to interrupt, but I was referring to the conversation earlier in the movie where
it's Tommy Lee Jones was talking to another cop.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, that thing at the end with, you know, Barry Corbin's going kids with blue hair,
you know, it's the scene that kind of sums up the entire movie.
And, uh, it's one of the, it's, it's, it's great.
Cause he's only in that one scene, but he, me,
he, his character kind of, cause that whole movie is about like, everybody's got their
line of what decency is and what you should do to get it up, up through and including
a serial killer.
Who's insane.
Um, but anyway, that movie's, that movie's awesome.
That, that, you know, I mean, Christ, that that's, you might've already said this.
Do you think it's the Coen brothers best?
I think it's arguably, you could argue easily that it's their best, but I, I think it's
the kind of thing where everyone goes.
That's the masterpiece.
Now let's you and I discuss what our favorite Coen brother movie is.
It's just kind of the, it's head and shoulders.
It's, it's, it's own thing.
It's, it's its own like deep thing.
And it's the same themes as Fargo too, which is like just for money.
It's very like, you know, that's the end of Fargo.
You did all this for a little bit of money.
It's, it's anti -capitalism, but in the most entertaining, brilliant, wonderful way.
And the difference between these movies.
And today's critiques of capitalism is, is night and fucking day.
These, these movies just take real characters, real situations.
They're appalled by the disgusting nature of humanity, of crime, of lust for money,
lust for power.
But it's one character believably stating that, man, I don't like where we're going
as opposed to these current satires of the rich, where it's just like, guys, we got the
point of this.
This five minutes into the movie, you're just going to keep hammering this now for
two and a half hours.
Um, I, I, I, I missed the, the simplicity of them getting their themes across in the
most entertaining way possible.
They're masters.
They're, they're the best.
Um, and the, again, in the independent cinema vein, I watched rewatched, uh, the Spanish
prisoner.
Yes.
David Mamet's the Spanish prisoner.
Very excited for his new movie coming out.
Um, and, uh.
Uh, this is to me, as we talk about what's the masterpiece to me, this is mammoths.
I love heist too.
Um, but I would say probably this is mammoths star, uh, on the resume.
Um, stars Gary.
Well, he wrote Glengar.
He didn't direct it.
I'm just talking about like what he wrote and directed himself.
I mean, Glengarry.
Yeah, of course.
But, um, but as far as stuff he wrote and directed.
This to me is, is, is, is, is as good as it gets.
Um, stars, uh, Campbell Scott, Rebecca pigeon and Steve Martin, which in 1997, when this
came out, we had not seen Steve Martin play a serious person yet.
You know, we'd seen him do some dramatic turns in comedic movies, but he plays a, a,
he, there's no humor and he plays a very slick international businessman.
Um, the, the plot of the movie is Campbell.
Scott is an N is a corporate engineer and he's invented something for his company called
the process.
They never specify what that is.
It's just, you know, and they translate to you, he's, this is a formula that is going
to make his company an extraordinary.
Amount of money.
You never even find out what the company does.
This is one of the things I like about Mamet.
He keeps all of this very vague.
They never say the dollar amount.
They never say what the company is.
They never tell you exactly what this thing is going to do.
You just know that there's a lot on the line.
Um, and Campbell Scott meets, uh, Steve Martin, who is a guy at the top of the ladder that
Campbell Scott's character, Joe is trying to ascend.
And he starts to sort of mentor him and give him insight towards how to protect himself
against his own company.
Suspicions rise, the plot thickens, the con men emerge, and it all kind of goes from there.
I won't, I won't spoil anything because if you haven't seen it, you should.
Um, it's just a great, great flick.
Uh, Ricky Jay shows up as he does in most.
Movies, the late Ricky Jay.
Uh, he's great.
Ben Gazzara.
Uh, I think that Rebecca Pigeon steals.
Well, I think Steve Martin and, and Rebecca Pigeon steal the show on this movie.
She plays such an innocent, passive person in such a convincing way.
Like this all shucks girl next door.
She's great.
She's just so great.
She's so convincing as this character.
She used to get so much shit.
Which was clearly just because she was his wife, but I don't know if she still is, but
they're still married.
Uh, yeah.
I never understood people like, oh, she's staying.
I'm like, what are you talking about?
She's great.
Like, anyway, um, again, it unfolds as it unfolds.
You should watch it if you haven't.
But, but the one thing I really want to speak to that I love so much about this movie, it's
classic mammet, the mammet speak and all that stuff, except for the profanity.
It's PG, which is shocking for mammet.
Um, but the philosophies and insights that they, that they, uh, uh, uh, translate in
this movie are just, I'm just like, God damn it, man.
That's so simple.
And so it's a great line where Steve Martin says, when Campbell Scott becomes convinced
that the company is, is actively trying to steal his process that he's created from him.
And Steve Martin goes, you'll know.
No, because they'll begin to act cruelly towards you.
Yeah.
And Campbell Scott goes, but why would they do that?
And he asks it so innocently.
Why would they be cruel to me?
I didn't do anything wrong.
And Steve Martin goes to suppress their guilt.
It's such a simple little line, but you're like, my God, that's so insightful.
That is what people do when they do something terrible to you.
They act cruelly towards you as if you're the perpetrator, because it's a method to
suppress guilt.
Uh, there's a lot of little moments like that in the movie.
Um, it's great.
It's a great little flick.
I suggest Ed O 'Neill turns up in a cameo, which is great.
Uh, it's a great movie.
Just check it out.
Yeah.
I remember nothing.
So I will watch it again.
Uh, I rewatched punch drunk love on the new criteria on 4k.
Um, obviously a polarizing movie for people.
It followed, um, Magnolia and, and there will be blood and I'm sorry, there will be blood
followed.
Punch drunk love.
That's by five years.
I'm, I'm incorrect on that one, but, uh, I remember being baffled and exhilarated by
punch drunk love.
When I saw it, I was a Paul Thomas Anderson fan.
I love boogie nights.
I loved heartache.
I really, really loved Magnolia and this was super different, but it just grows more in
my estimation every year.
It is such an original.
It is genuinely romantic.
Genuinely.
Sweet.
Genuinely sad.
The characters are deeply fucked up, particularly Sandler in a way that I think a lot of men
can relate to.
Uh, he's just got anger issues and doesn't know where to, where to put them.
And he's, he's, uh, you know, his family doesn't get him.
His friends don't get him.
His coworkers don't get him.
He's lonely as fuck.
Um, it's, it's not a hard competition to be one of Sandler's best characters, but it's
very, it's very much one of his best characters.
And I love how Paul Thomas Anderson was a fan of the shitty quote, shitty Sandler movies,
the Sandler comedies, and was like, what if we took that persona and took him seriously
and put him into a real adult movie?
It, it works brilliantly.
It's so good.
Uh, it's the start of serious Sandler, which has just been paying off for decades now.
I love Emily Watson in it.
I particularly love the great Philip Seymour Hoffman in it.
He's this in, in addition to.
Yeah.
Who, um, along came Polly is his best, like small role.
I love him in this movie as the mattress man.
He's hilarious.
Him and Sandler screaming at each other over the phone.
I rewound it three times.
It's like somebody on letterbox was saying, it's like, um, junior heat, you know, it's
like the movie heat.
It's like two of, two of cinema's greatest yellers yelling at each other.
And it's so funny and so great.
So that scene where Hoffman says, shut up, shut up, shut up.
Yeah.
An incomprehensible amount of times in a row that's become one of those videos you see
on YouTube where like somebody captions it when the guy fill in the blank or whatever.
But yeah, that's so insane and it works.
Yeah.
It's, it's great.
The, the structure of this movie is wild.
Uh, the, it always looked amazing.
This 4k, I was pausing shit left and right.
It looks so fucking great.
Um,
a classic, you know, uh, just like the Collins, Paul Thomas Anderson is a guy where you got
to, everybody's got different favorites.
Most people go, well, there'll be bloods.
The masterpiece.
I don't actually, I think he's, I prefer his more open human type movies.
Your Magnolia, your boogie nights, your punch drunk love is, you know, his more controlled,
uh, Kubrick Ian type movies.
I definitely respect, but they don't get under my skin in the same way.
Uh,
I love punch drunk love Joseph.
I remember when it came out, you know, me and Pinkstone were talking, you know, this
PT Anderson guy, holy shit, boogie nights, Magnolia, what the fuck?
And he said, I read an interview with that.
He said his next movie is going to start Adam Sandler.
And I was like, wait, what?
And he was like, yeah, he said Adam Sandler is brilliant.
And whatever he said.
And I was like, I don't understand.
Is it going to be like a cop?
He's going to do an, because that was back when I was like, I don't know.
I was like, wait, he's going to do an Adam Sandler movie, meaning like the wedding singer.
And he was like, no, he's going to star in Pete.
He's going to do a PT Anderson movie, but Adam Sandler is going to start.
And I was like, it was like when you heard Keaton was going to play Batman, you were
like, I don't understand.
And then you saw it and you were like, holy shit.
Um, that's a great flick.
Uh, my last one is about the movie industry itself and it's a rewatch, but I rewatched
get shorty and just was tickled from.
From as I always am from front to back of that movie, you know, everybody top of their
game, uh, Travolta, Delroy, Lindo, Gandolfini, DeVito, God almighty DeVito is so funny in
it.
And then of course, Hackman, I'm so sorry, Hackman, my God, Bette Midler, but the guy
running away with this flick is.
He is Farina.
I mean, Jesus God, dude, it is a crime.
We did not get more Dennis Farina comedies like it is.
He is so funny in it.
That scene where he's at the, he lands in LA and the car is waiting for him and the
guy spells his name wrong and he just goes, well, I hope you can drive a whole lot fucking
better than you can spell pal.
Yeah, he was awesome.
Him going into that type out of movies.
There's no, there's no one doing that anymore.
Kim going into Hackman's office.
Can I help you?
Yeah, it's me.
Ray Barboni, the dipshit that never gets out of Miami.
Dear God, man, the guy just spins gold out of hay in this thing.
Like it's crazy how funny he is.
And the lines are, they're not jokes.
Yeah.
He's not jokes.
He's just hilarious.
Did you see be cool?
No.
To this day, I still haven't.
I can't.
It ain't good.
Vince Vaughn's funny in it.
Beyond that, it's not good.
Anyway, see Get Shorty if you haven't seen it.
Gosh, it's, and it's right in that era of like, you know, Pulp Fiction and it's like
studios were making indies, but they were sort of still indies and you know, blah, blah,
blah.
But anyway, let's get on to our movie of the day.
Sinners, as we said already, directed by the great Ryan Coogler, starring the great
Michael B.
Jordan, amongst many other, amongst also Delroy Lindo, who I really, really, I love Delroy
Lindo so much.
I enjoyed him thoroughly in this movie.
Love him.
And I thought he had retired until that Spike Lee movie, Defy Bloods.
But it's just, he wasn't really working as much.
He was in every movie in the nineties.
Yeah.
He's one of those guys.
Nobody knew his name, but he was in, I mean, in the industry they did, but the average
person, now I love that like people are kind of like, no, like, oh, that's Delroy Lindo.
Well, he was on.
I really love him in Crooklyn.
I think he's excellent in that movie.
He was on The Good Fight for years.
Oh, you're right.
I think that's why we all thought he wasn't doing anything because it was like he was
on this TV show.
Yeah.
When people go away, like Giamatti, that's almost always the reason they're making money
finally.
But Sinners takes place.
It takes place in 1932 on the Mississippi Delta.
Obviously a very tense racial period in the country.
It's about two twin brothers played by Michael B. Jordan, who smoke and stack.
Smoke and stack.
Rumor has it, it was Jordan and Jonathan Majors.
But since that happened last second, they were like, you know what?
You're going to play both brothers.
Oh, wow.
I didn't know that.
Yeah.
So they play twin brothers who had left Mississippi to go to Chicago.
They were they're gangsters.
They returned to Mississippi because, as they say in the movie, Chicago is just Mississippi
with big buildings and that all the racial problems are just as bad up there at that
time than they as they are in Mississippi.
But they realize they can actually make a go of something in Mississippi.
And finally have their ship come in by opening.
Is it juke joint?
Yeah.
Okay.
A jukebox.
Yeah.
And and, you know, the Klan is everywhere.
And and again, massive racial tensions and issues, obviously.
And look, big spoiler alert.
You probably know it already, but it basically does like a dust till dawn kind of turn where
they.
Get the party going this night and things take a sideways turn when three white people
show up to the party.
We're trying to get always the fucking Irish, always the Irish.
They're trying to get in.
They don't want to let them in because their antennas are way up that the Klan is going
to infiltrate this thing and ruin it and much worse.
So they don't want to let them in.
And it turns out the three white people are vampires and they manage to turn.
Mostly everybody at the party into vampires as well.
And I kept describing this movie as.
You know, there's a lot of talk.
Is it a horror movie?
It's got horror.
I mean, certainly a horror plot and it's got massive horror elements in it.
To me, it felt like if Spike Lee made a horror movie in the way that like.
Shutter Island is a horror movie, but it's like.
But if.
If Scorsese made a horror movie like that kind of thing, you know, so this is.
Yeah, it's a horror movie.
But if it's if Ryan Coogler made a horror movie, he's got his own touch.
He's got themes and.
And concepts that he is going to include in in in most of his films.
And he certainly explores them greatly in this.
And those come first before the horror.
I mean, truly, it's it's it's what you want in a horror movie because it's.
It's steps forward first as a film.
And it it puts the genre stuff behind the characters in the story of what they're dealing with.
Much like The Exorcist or something like that.
So I would get out.
So it's a very, very well made movie.
A little little too long.
I thought it could have been easily two hours.
It didn't need to be too.
Especially because there's a post credits or mid credits.
Scene and that scene goes on for like it's got to be seven full minutes.
Yeah.
And.
I get it.
He's not doing a cheap shot like just mid credits scene.
Like, will there be a sequel?
He's he's he's putting an and it's more of a coda to the movie itself.
But yeah, it could have been it could have been a shorter movie.
But but from from a writing standpoint, from a directing standpoint, from an acting standpoint and from an artistic standpoint.
Because he does some crazy stuff in this visually that you would think on paper wouldn't work.
And it does.
The movie is very, very well made.
It's a very good movie.
You know, my my really only my only two gripes were it could have been shorter.
And I hate that they do that scene at the beginning with Michael B.
Jordan.
Where he's playing.
It's the two twins in the one shot of the two of them.
And they're passing the cigarette back and forth.
And I'm like, guys.
Guys, I get it.
Look, look, look at this in Back to the Future, too.
Yeah.
I'll watch the behind the scenes.
That was the only thing that bugged me.
It's 220 like every movie now.
And it feels like a director's cut.
It feels like you're watching a movie with deleted scenes put in scenes that clearly don't need to be there.
What I loved about it, if I'm being honest, was the right up front sexuality.
I love it.
It's Haley Steinfeld, who I forgot was a little girl from True Grit, but has obviously grown up quite a bit.
But, yeah, there's like there's no nudity per se, but the sex in it felt real and raw and sort of a little more experimental than we're used to in a movie like this, which I appreciate it.
Spitting in mouths and, you know, just some some cunnilingus, even though the woman wasn't clean.
That scene got a lot of.
Screams in the audience, people getting turned on.
I was like, people are very easy to turn on.
I've learned because they don't see a lot of sex these days.
The movie for me, though, the big issue I had and part of it, I acknowledge, is the sound was murky and I thought it was IMAX, but other people saw it in other formats and said the sound was murky.
Sounds great, meaning the explosions and the vampire action sounds great, but the dialogue was tough.
There's scenes in this where like this kid's.
You know, playing the blues and he's singing and for starters, I didn't think he was an amazing performer.
I'm going to say that I disagree for him to be like taking the world by storm and everyone stops in their tracks to hear him perform.
I was like, OK, I disagree.
That might have just been me.
I found the Irish jig to be more entertaining, but there's a there is a big Irish jig dance of like a vampire thing.
He the big swings he takes are all great and really fun.
There's a lot of music in it.
And that's fun and well shot and exciting.
But there's a theme that I think is in there and maybe they just didn't do it or maybe I missed something.
But when this kid is playing the blues, we see in this juke joint in the 30s, rappers, hip hop dancers, soul performers, disco performers.
It goes through the decades of black music in America.
You see represent representation of it.
And so I'm thinking, why am I seeing this?
Why are they introducing this music throughout the ages element into a movie that's already a gangster movie that becomes a vampire movie?
And at the end, I just finally said, well, it's a big gumbo and it was a lot of fun and it doesn't really matter.
But what I want to put a finger on is the theme of this movie seems to be or should be maybe.
And although what am I saying?
But white people come in and vampire vampirize.
Suck the talent from black people.
They have been doing it since the beginning of music.
Elvis Presley, the most famous example.
Led Zeppelin, another famous example.
Am I mistaken or did this movie not really go there?
Because I kept going.
I see what the theme should be, but it didn't seem like they were doing it.
Am I crazy?
Yes, you're crazy.
And I'm actually shocked that you didn't understand what was.
Well, I mean.
No, they're unless that's just what it was.
They say at the very beginning, the opening V .O. is the woman saying there are some people with a musical talent that is able to channel the past and the future.
They say that.
Not only do they say at the beginning, when he starts playing in the thing, when they show everybody the voiceover plays again and she goes, they can channel the past and the future.
That's why you're seeing everybody.
No, I that is not my question.
What?
But you said you didn't get why you were seeing rappers and stuff.
No, my question is, is a why is that in this movie, which is also many other things, because it didn't seem like they could decide on a story somehow.
My question is, are they saying that these white people are coming in and trying to suck the musical talent out?
Or are they avoiding that theme entirely?
No, I don't.
I don't think that the point was that they were.
I think the point was race relations.
Yeah, I guess my question is, why are you doing that in this movie, this music through the ages thing, which comes completely out of nowhere?
Why are you doing that if the movie isn't about how white people steal the arts from black people?
Because it doesn't need to be.
I mean, maybe it was, but it didn't need to be.
My take on that was music in a marginalized culture has always been the mouthpiece.
The mouthpiece for the struggles of that culture.
And it gets, that is always attempted to be stomped out, sometimes by even within the culture itself.
Hence, the blues kid's preacher father saying, put that guitar down, and he wouldn't do it.
You know, them showing all the idea of it channels the past, the present, whatever, that to me represents the struggle.
And you're seeing.
All of these different musicians that represent different genres, iconic moments in history and genres.
And all of it, if you step back and kind of take a look at it as a whole, it's all rebellious.
Yeah.
The blues is meant to be a mouthpiece for the struggle.
It's a rebellious thing.
Funk, you know, the funk representation was a guy that was clearly modeled after Sly or Bootsy Collins, like a very sort of rebellious.
Like, I'm not going to play your game.
I'm going to do my thing kind of guy.
Hip hop, obviously.
So it's like, that's how I took it.
And then I took it with the Irish music when it was the, when they were outside of the barn and they had managed to turn most of the attendees of the party who were not white.
And all, now you have a bunch of black characters dancing.
And Irish jig.
Yeah.
Around three white people that are leading it.
That to me was showing like, it's not, I mean, it could have been a commentary on stealing the art, which I'm sure it was in some way.
But to me, it was more like, this is what happens.
The thing we have that's pure, we get pulled out of it because, because we are convinced by the mainstream that we are not good enough and they have a better way.
And we end up just mimicking them.
And we end up mimicking the majority.
Hence, all of these people doing this Irish jig.
That's just how I took it.
Yeah.
Well, and, and yes, and I bet there are other people who took it differently and that's fine too.
And I need to see it a second time.
I had struggled with the dialogue to be honest.
But that to me, I just, I guess I just felt it was a missed opportunity.
You've got vampires who suck the life out of things.
Why aren't we telling that story when this seems to be?
Saying that white people take the music from black people, the culture from black people.
Also, the Irish were so persecuted at this time that I found making them Irish kind of an odd choice, but that's maybe just because I am Irish.
I didn't think that was odd at all.
I felt like that was, I, in fact, I didn't know that the Irish were persecuted at that time.
And I think that that even speaks to it great, more greatly.
Yeah.
Because it's like a lot of people were persecuted at this time and the persecuted turn on the persecuted.
So that's actually makes it more interesting to me.
I thought the, and I don't know if this was on purpose or not.
I assume it was, but I thought it was an incredibly interesting, there were incredibly interesting details that brought the commentary of the racial themes to life.
I thought it was incredibly interesting that the convenience store was run by Asian people as it often is in, in, in the black communities around the country.
Yeah.
And they weren't bad guys.
They were, they, it wasn't like, it wasn't like the Asian store owners in menace to society where they were racist, whatever they were, they were allies.
I was very surprised to have a couple Asian characters who were like part of this team fighting vampires at the end.
Like there was a lot of cool touches, many, many cool touches.
Yes.
Um, and I liked too, that they, with Haley, what's her name?
Haley.
Steinfeld.
Steinfeld's character.
I liked that it kind of started.
With the take on her being, you know, there's that part where she says, my dad was a quarter black or whatever.
Yeah.
And it's, it's, it's, and, and she's in love with one of the Michael B. Jordan characters.
She's in love with Stack, I think.
Uh, anyways.
No, she's in love with Smoke.
Or Smoke.
And they grew up together and they had a relationship and you can see that he loves her.
Well, anyway, they, they start moving in the direction where you think she's going to be the classic.
White chick coming in, going like, I'm actually one 10th American Indian, so I can relate, you know, whatever.
And then you see, as it unfolds, like, no, she actually does love him.
And like, she does love.
And she's.
Well, I love that they did not make her the, the token classic textbook snow bunny character either.
It was just like, I want that black dick, you know, which is a, is a, is a type of character in these movies.
Yeah.
Um, everything was way more nuanced than I expected.
And it was all the better movie for it, for sure.
And I love the reveal with Michael B. Jordan when he, he, she's resentful that she's married this older white male that she's not in love with.
And again, they're moving in the direction of making you think she's sort of a perpetrator.
And then you realize like, no, Michael B. Jordan's being like, look, I love you too.
We cannot be together.
They will murder us.
Like I'm doing this for your own safety.
Um, and things go from there.
But yes, as you said, very nuanced, I don't want to give too much away.
Uh, but the performances were great.
I went in excited to see the film.
I was a little hesitant because I was like, isn't this just going to be the plot of dust till dawn?
There's obviously some, some similarities, but it is a very different movie.
Um, yeah.
And honestly, people throwing that comparison out, which I've seen a ton on letterbox and from critics.
It's, it's lazy, but it's also, I just think really shitty at a time when everything's inspired by something else.
All they did was it's a movie that becomes a vampire thing halfway through.
Nothing else has anything to do with from dust till dawn.
Like give them some fucking credit.
He came up with a truly original story.
I'm not saying that to you.
I'm saying that to the, I know.
I, but I would, I would actually say that I thought there were more parallels than, than dust joint thing.
For sure.
Yeah.
It takes place.
That's the dog brothers.
Oh, you're right.
Actually.
Yeah.
The brothers.
It takes place in a whorehouse and dust till dawn.
It's a, it's a, it's a, it's a, it's a place that is legal, but there's a lot of heat on it.
This place they're doing a juke joint.
It's it's legal, but there's a lot of heat on it.
They got to keep certain people out.
Certain people are allowed it, whatever.
But that all said, despite those parallels, as it unfolded, it is a, it is a very deep.
Very different movie.
Um, I thought the music was awesome.
Um, both the, both the blues and the Irish stuff.
I liked all the music.
I enjoyed all of it.
I thought the, the vampire, the three lead vampires were great.
They were great.
Bad guys.
I agree.
And they did a great job of, and I've never seen this, you know, vampire movies.
It's always like, don't look into their eyes.
They will hypnotize you or whatever.
But like all that ever is, is like somebody looks at the vampires.
Okay.
And, you know, Bella Lugosi's eyes widen or Christopher Lee's eyes glow.
And you're like, oh, there, there's the way they hypnotize them this because they need
to be invited in the charm that they were showing.
And like when they weren't allowed in the disappointment, like you actually kind of
felt bad for them.
You're like, yeah, man, if this was me and I didn't know they were vampires, I would
feel terrible right now.
Yeah.
They seem like they really are sad that they can't come into this party and like join in
on the phone, whatever.
So like, it was just very, very, very well done.
Um, it's not a perfect movie, but it's, it's a, it's a really goddamn good one.
Uh, and I, I would say my hog is very up for sinners.
Uh, my hog is definitely up as well.
Uh, minor quibbles aside to have a big, strong, original, exciting, fun movie in theaters,
big applause breaks.
You know, it looks great.
It sounds great.
Um, it's an excellent movie.
It's, uh, it's Kugler's best, in my opinion, by a long margin, unless he's got something
I'm forgetting other than the black Panthers and fruit veil and Creed.
He did Creed.
Okay.
I prefer Creed.
I got to give him that.
Yeah.
Kugler is great.
You know, Kugler is, uh, I bet he's not even 40 years old.
He's, he's put together quite a filmography and, uh, can't wait to see what he does next.
I would certainly see another sinners sequel as well.
So hopefully we get that.
Uh, we'll be back with a discussion of, uh, apartment seven, a, the prequel to Rosemary's
baby, as well as the original, which we've never done.
Rosemary's baby, Joe, uh, Joe to Rosa, Joe to Rosa .com for tickets.
I got shows coming up.
Uh, I guess I'm well this coming Tuesday, there's a handful of tickets left.
I'm not just saying that it's true.
I think there's only like five tickets left to the screening of my new special.
I never promised you a Rose garden, 9 PM, April 29th.
That's a Tuesday, New York, New York at the famed Angelica theater.
It will be showing one showing only.
Please come out if you, if you haven't, if you're there and haven't gotten a ticket yet.
And then I have shows starting again in June, uh, in New Jersey and then on to Nashville,
August, I'll be in, I think Rhode Island.
And then there's a bunch of stuff in the fall.
Go to Joe to Rosa .com for show information and ticket links.
And if you're in New York, check out, uh, Joey roses, uh, Joey roses .com.
All right.
We'll be back with Rosemary and apartment seven.
A we will see you next time.
And we will see you in hell.
Bye.