I'm here for Bett Rivers online casino and sportsbook with poker icon Phil Helmuth.
And now thanks to the excitement of Bett Rivers, I'm also a slots icon.
That's great! And a same game, parlay icon. Cool, cool. A blackjack icon,
a money line icon, a roulette. Take it from Phil Helmuth. If you love games,
Bett Rivers is the place to play in Bett. Bett Rivers. Games on.
Must be 21 plus in present in West Virginia. Void were prohibited. Terms in conditions apply.
gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamber.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fancash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fancash,
guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook, winning hits different here.
Monthly 21 -plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberler, offer not available in all
states, terms apply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
Welcome to it. We'll see you in hell. This is your podcast for horror sci -fi fantasy
action. Sometimes comedy and drama, film, discussion, reviews. And once in a while, a little
commentary. I'm Joe DeRosa to my left is my co -host calm the dog and to cons left your three
post Patrick Walsh, Danny free host. Not that co -host means two host. So I've already
fallen apart. Yeah. But hello, Joe. It's good to see you. I popped into the Facebook group
the other day. People said, I am particular with seeming very down. I'm going to try to bring
the positivity on this one. The last episode we seem down. We seem down but it was a specific
mention of my mood and concern for my well -being and folks I'm fine. I'm just
exhausted. Was the last episode the bike horn incident? Bike horn. Yeah. Which I
thought was funny. Now Kahn's ball was squeaking. Kahn's ball squeaking. You can't
get a minute's peace in this fucking city. You can't. And to escape the noises of
the city, Joe just informed me he bought a razor scooter. No, no, no, no, a
mo pet. Like a sit -down scooter. It almost looks like a little motorcycle. Is there an
engine there is but it's an electric engine so you never have to put gas in it it peaks at 30
miles per hour yeah you just plug it in charge it never have to put gas in it okay it's got storage
in it and then you know you get you zip over to the store you buy a few things you zip home you got to
wear like a real fucking helmet with it though any chance of me riding around either you know tandem
style or in some sort of side car. It's only got one seat, but what I'd like to do is tie
a studded leather leash to your neck and tie the other end of it to the handlebars and
have me just run. Yeah, as I refer to you as my pet. That's fine by me, honestly. All right,
well that's the cheapest solution and I think we should get on that. Great. I'm happy about your
purchase. Thank you. I definitely doesn't seem like the sort of thing you're going to be angry
were you bought in three months and returned?
You can't return it.
It's a loss.
If I get rid of this thing, it's a loss.
But I didn't, you know, my license,
here's what happened, my license expired.
I got rid of my car because I was tired of carrying
an $800 a month.
It was just annoying.
It was a lot of money.
And I was like, I'm Uber and half the time anyway.
Sure.
So then during that period, my license expired.
And I didn't renew it right away because I was like, wow, who cares? I don't have a car. I didn't really take it seriously. I should have
And then what happened was I when I did go to renew my license
There's like this three -month fucking waiting period. Yeah in LA because the cities run like dog shit. It is
Do you want him away from you?
No, it's fun. Oh, okay. All right. Now name names. Who in the city council really gets your goat?
Is it Garcetti
That's a great
That's a great dirty like councilman name. Yeah
So anyway, so I would like but it actually is the name of oh, it just sounds like a guy that's on the tape
Yeah, no, I it does but that's the name of a maybe our mayor. I don't know
I don't really follow local politics
So anyway, so here's what it would happen.
I would set the appointment to go get my new license.
Sure.
And then you gotta set it two and a half months ahead of time.
And then, you know, and something comes up.
You're not in town that day,
or you have a work conflict or something.
And then I'd have to cancel it.
And then you cancel it.
And then you gotta reset it for another two and a half
fucking months, ridiculous.
So I was like, I'm not, I'm like, I'm done.
I'm just not gonna get the fucking license renewed.
I don't give a shit.
Right.
But I need a cost -efficient way to get to run certain errands, and the electric
mo pet is the way to go. Now, did you consider these razor scooters, you see
everywhere? The bird scooters. Yeah, but you can't carry, you're not going to get
groceries on one of those things. And I did consider the e -bike. But it looks a
little too goofy. Now, what if you pick up a sweetie at the corner store, would
How'd you be able to get her home?
I think I could squeeze somebody behind me on it, like a tight squeeze, but I think you
could do that.
Hey, die to the better folks, I don't mean that.
I don't mean that.
You rock whatever tightness you've got, you know, fair enough.
It's already a brighter show.
Can I tell you something horrific a man once said to me at a wrestling meet the first one I ever went to
I was like let me guess if there's grass on the field play ball. No, but similar it was
Hey, so I'll pink in the middle brother. Well, it's way worse than what do I know my I was about 13 my jaw hit the floor
Because you were salivating so hard
I mean, just a shocking thing to say to anyone, not alone,
a 13 -year -old, but it was a grown man who said it.
Oh, yeah.
He was like, hey, you think she's cute?
I was like, it's not really my thing.
You know, one of these female wrestlers
that are super jacked at them.
Right.
And he goes, hey, so I'll pick in the middle, brother.
He's a 40 -year -old man talking to a 13 -year -old.
It wasn't my father.
Yeah, I was going to say, one 13 -year -old
to another is one thing.
Yeah.
A grown man to a 13 -year -old is something entirely different.
That's crazy.
Yeah, I'd assume he was there with about six beers in him or something that's crazy
Isn't it was he a coach or something? He was just a dude in the stands. Oh
Hey, you think she's cute like what what
Anyhute
Let's get on with the show
Please don't cough during my on with the show Joe. Sorry, and at the same time on
with the I didn't think it threw it again, Joe.
I like when you just go back to the original ones.
I'm tired of the damn songs.
Well, thank you very much.
No, I was great for a long time, but we did it forever.
I liked it when you changed it.
You changed, you used to change it up every year.
On with the Joe whispered.
You like that one?
Yeah.
Yeah, so you know, that whisper will turn into a gradual madness, you know, and that's
how these work.
I'd like to start with a question.
Why did you tell Brian Singer to repeatedly do what he did over a period of 20, 20, 25
years?
Allegedly, you got to say allegedly, folks, legally, you have to say allegedly.
Well, it isn't allegedly.
I had insider information, so I know someone who was one of his like boys that put up, I think
he was of age.
Not laughing at that, by the way.
Well, there accusations coming from some that say that they were in fact underage at the time.
Yeah. But now it's straight in my head out on this.
All right. Because, you know, I think that's disgusting if he's dittling around with underage
boys. But the same Hollywood saying, you know, that this guy, you know, look at this, he fucked
around with a 17 -year -old as the same Hollywood that gave awards to a movie about a 30 -year -old man
and fucking a 17 year old kid.
And they said that it was...
You're talking about calling me by your name.
Yeah, and I know art's not real life,
but you know, that was not in any,
there wasn't even a discussion about that
being potentially inappropriate.
So I just don't know.
And nobody arrested the kid for banging that peach.
You know what, and that's produce.
That's fresh produce that could have gone to some peach.
What do you mean?
The kid and calling by your name, fucks a peach.
I didn't see it.
Joe I didn't see it. What did I what do you want for me? All right, he fucks a page. It's a very famous thing
You're shooting a thing in adjacent biggs in in a that's a pie American pie. It's a pie. All right
Look yeah, Brian singer look. It's the classic where there's smoke. There's probably fire
I think the guy probably is guilty. I mean, it's you know, it's a lot of vacuations at this point. I don't stand up for any of these people
Spacy who we need to talk about that
video, he posted to the internet, the house of cards thing after this in a moment.
But so, Spacey, you know, obviously trash.
There's many, many people stepping forward.
He shoved his hands down my son's pants, like a nice restaurant and all this stuff.
And a lot of very similar recounts of things that have happened.
But Spacey, the second those allegations kind of hit the paper, he was out of the business.
Hold it.
We're replaced by other actors in this project.
Well, he did admit to it, though.
He immediately admitted to it immediately went, but he was kind of like, look, I remember
his little hazy, but he also used it to come out of the closet and, right, singer his
vehemently.
All right.
I guess that's different.
And I would argue that singer carries a lot more water and Hollywood right now.
Right.
Now, sure.
But it's like, after all the singer shit came out and has been coming out for years and
years and years.
Let's let him direct Bohemian Rhapsody. Well look let's then give him the keys to Red Sonia after even more
Accusation these people are fucking hypocritical pigs you make money. They'll look the other way
I mean they absolutely will yeah, let me there is no fucking way
Everybody knew about Weinstein. They didn't say a god damn thing until they didn't need to make money
Or or or or or he couldn't make them the money that he could this rally malloc today the guy mr.
a robot who played Mr. Fucking robot.
Fucking robot over here are two day douche. Okay. This guy. This guy says I tickled myself
with that one. Rami Malik is like, I had never heard any allegations about Brian Singer
really dude. My mom's heard the allegations and she's not an inside Hollywood player. You've
You heard about it, you wanted the Oscar nom, you got it.
Our good friend of the podcast, James Pinkstone, told me about a meme he saw that was very
funny.
It was Ramy Malik at an award show, and it's the meme said, Ramy Malik always looks
like he's trying to quietly chew his potato chips.
Yeah, I guess I can agree with that.
Now I want to read to you, Joe.
Well, wait a minute, and I want you to read it after I read it away from the space we'll come back to the space video
All right, just don't forget I saw this repost it a lot
Anodized clay post wrote this himself posted it to his Facebook account. So here we go
Is it about how he should have been nominated or something? It dances around not really actually
So now I get worried that my film a star is born got nominated for best picture
Very excited to be a part of that
That.
Lots of typos.
Congratulations to the one and only lady Gaga for her nomination for Best Actress.
She really deserves it.
Bradley was not nominated for Best Direction.
You know what?
Too fucking bad.
I mean, he got nominated for Best Actor, which is what he's really known for.
Couple more movies and then he could get Best Director Thing.
Well, couple more movies and then he could get Best Director Thing.
Anyway, at the end of the day, Bradley is a great actor and did a very nice job with
the directing.
Lots of luck to all of you.
And then three pictures of him taken by himself.
That's nice.
I knew a lady, Gaga.
Every time I took out my prick, she went, Jesus Christ.
That sounds like a dice.
That sounds like a classic dice show.
It's a rough one, Joe.
Yeah, but it's a rough one, but you know, that sounds like a classic dice show. Yeah, it's it's and by the way rest in peace to Kevin Barnett
Well, I'm get it's this is gonna circle back into selfies in a second. Okay. It's very sorry to hear about his passing nice kid great kid
Funny kid very talented at a lot going on
Not you know we weren't close friends or anything, but I was like seeing him and we was always you know
lit up a room, added a little fun to the party, and I'm sad to hear that he passed.
Uh, sincerely, uh, but what is so shocking to me is amongst the, the tributes that he
should be getting online, where people are showing pictures of him and saying, rest in
peace, I'm heartbroken, all that sort of stuff.
There are people now posted, and they do this with everybody that ever dies, ever.
They're posting pictures of them with other people.
Oh, okay, that's different.
No, not even with him, with other people.
He's not even in the picture.
And then saying like,
RIP, Kevin Burnett,
hang on to your friends while you got them.
And then posting pictures of them with friends.
Like, it's people, stop it, you're sick.
You're sick, I can't disagree.
I can't disagree.
God almighty, let a man's memory live for a day
on Instagram without showing something
that about you and you're, oh my God.
Anyway, folks, let's bring it over to Kevin Spacey.
Now on Christmas day, this sociopath,
we're way, way behind on this one.
We are through the looking glass with spacey, but we should have mentioned this a lot sooner
I assume you saw it if you haven't dig it up on YouTube, but spacey
Rumble together a little crew a little budget and on Christmas day
He drops a video of him
Portraying Frank Booth from the house of cards not Frank Booth. That's blue velvet Frank Underwood from the house of cards show
and
He's basically hinting that
He's guilty, but you love him for molesting boys.
So he's like, yeah, you sure,
perhaps I'm out of done the things they say,
but that's exactly what you'd want me to do, isn't it?
And it's like, excuse, are you confessing to a crime?
Well, he first, as a character.
He flip flops, at first he goes,
he goes, some people believe anything they hear.
And you're like, oh, he's saying he's not guilty.
And then he goes, but let's face it.
You want a man with a little dirt on him.
Yeah. Well, wait, sweet. Did you do it? Yeah. What kind of dirt?
It's a wild tape. I said on Nikki Glaser. He's like, he's like baking eggs while he does it too.
He's like, weirdly like, he's like, no, he's carving like the turkey, isn't he?
Oh, that's what it was. The Thanksgiving turkey. Yeah. You'd like to carve me up too, wouldn't you?
Uh, I said on Nikki Glaser's radio show, it is the craziest thing I've ever seen.
He might as well have had the Gwyneth Paltrow head in the box.
Yeah. It's seven sitting next to him. Remember my old friend, Gwyneth?
It was so fucking nuts.
Yeah.
Kevin, don't pick.
If you're trying to do an endearing, you want me back video.
Don't pick a bad guy character.
Yeah.
Yo, want me back.
Don't you?
Frank on the wood.
It's like, no, we're good.
Aren't you going to say your kaisers so say?
You're going to say, yeah, you want me back.
Yeah.
Do one of the, who's one of the nice, I can't even think of it.
Always just play the assholes.
Yeah.
Bobby Derrick's deal.
Remember me lest to burn him from American beauty. I lusted after my daughter's 15 -year -old friend. Wait a minute
Let me try the guy from seven. No, you know, he wanted to ask her for that. Nobody said he was creepy then did they know they didn't
This is a twisted fucking town. It's a twisted town
Spacey
I admire the balls frankly that it took to post this thing and
And just the delusion to think that he'd start this thing with y 'all missed your boy, haven't you?
Like then we'd all be like, oh, thank God, Frank, look, it is a, it is back, gang.
It is a Richard Nixon level of balls, like, it's like you, you have to step back and just admire
the girth and weight of those balls for a second. It's y 'all time favorite television character.
to the guy from House of Cards.
I'm sorry, that's right.
And I'm cutting up meat, okay.
I'm gonna casually confess to sexually molesting chick.
Or did I?
Wait, what?
Insane.
Wearing like a holiday sweater,
you gotta check this thing out.
I, it's probably already seen it.
It's an amazing video.
You know what don't do me when I was watching the video?
I was like, oh, I guess I've never seen house
cards. I had no idea that character talked like that. It's what I had seen the show. I mean,
I've seen three, three seasons or whatever got boring. I dropped out and I didn't drop out
when he did, but a couple years before this show would be like, he'd be in somebody's face like,
I slit your throat, motherfucker. You never charge Frank Underwood, motherfucker. And then the character
will like leave the scene kind of scared. And then Frank Underwood turns the camera and goes,
You see how I handle that back there?
That's how we do things down south.
And you're like, what?
What?
It's Ferris Bueller, but where he's a vicious politician.
Ferris Bueller doing the peppered farm guy.
Yeah.
Except as an asshole.
Yeah, and they start all these scenes where he's like,
like he always does this rib place.
And he's like, hmm, there's nothing like fine Louisiana ribs.
And he's like, unless of course we're talking about politics.
You know stop it just the worst dialogue and then these are the clips they show at the Emmys
Then everyone would jump to their feet like oh obviously space. He's won the Emmy this year guys
There's an actor who wasn't great for a lot of these films. He shows her
There's these shows are just dog shit Jesus Christ. Yeah, they're just dog shit
I have like Kevin space and things don't get me wrong just not children
Hey folks
It's it's a wild time. I've been watching a lot of movies. I've not been getting much sleep. I've seen so many things. I've
been watching shit. I do have three for the corner. Can I take a quick great joke? I saw on Frager today though. Please a
grand shot, if you will. Yeah, he goes into he goes into a gay bar because he's trying to see if the guy that
Ross is dating his gay, and he thinks that that guy's in the gay bar, and his furniture
publisher is the bartender, and he's like, and the bartender's like, Frazier, and Frazier's
like, my God, Simon, how are you? Bet you're surprised to see me in this place, so the bartender
goes, okay, yeah, that's very funny, that's very funny, all right, that's good stuff, I like it.
Fogs, let's, let's go over to the old movie corner. I'd like to start by discussing
two different fire fest documentaries. Oh shit. There's two. I watched them both. There's
one on Hulu, there's one on Netflix. Hulu in a, in a, just a street move dropped their
documentary that nobody knew about three days before the one Netflix had been
advertising for a year. And I'll be damned if the Hulu one wasn't to me a
significantly better film. Who's doing good stuff these days? It was great. And
you know, I can certainly recommend both. The Fire Fest. It was a fascinating
story. And both tell the story pretty well. However, the Hulu documentary has a
long interview spread throughout with the guy who did all these scams, including FireFest,
who shows really no remorse, and much like the Jinx on HBO, one of the all -time great
crime shows, it's just looking into the eyes of its true sociopath.
And he doubles down on everything.
He's super defensive.
He won't really admit to doing anything wrong.
even as they point out the tremendous amount of money he owes people he
owes poor people in on this island in the Bahamas that he just you know
there's there's people sobbing that they've lost their life savings because
they were a chef at the fire fest and he made you think guys you got a chip in
some of your own money but we'll pay you back and then he skipped town it's
graceful sick ship so the whole the whole one has a full interview with him and
he's not interviewed at all on the Netflix documentary that alone to me gives
at the edge, but to add to it, the Netflix one was produced by the fuck Jerry guys, who
are like the fat Jew, they rip off people's accounts, they steal tweets, they steal jokes,
they steal Instagrams, and make a ton of money off it.
It's great that they just get opportunities still.
Yeah, they made this documentary, and not only is that kind of bad enough, and that's how
they make their bread and butter, but fuck Jerry spent a tremendous amount of time and
and energy promoting the fire fest.
And now these are the guys telling you about what a disgrace
it was telling me you didn't make some fucking money off it.
Oh my God.
Honestly fucking sick.
So morally, I prefer the Hulu one,
but also in terms of just viewing experience,
the Hulu one to me was a lot better.
The, all right, fair enough.
I have two rewatches and a new watch.
I'll start with a new watch.
No, I'll start with a rewatch.
I rewatched the nice guys starring Russell Crowe,
love that film, and Ryan Gosling, folks,
if you have not seen this flick, what are you doing?
You gotta see this movie because I'll tell you it,
I know what you're doing, you're doing what I did
when it came out.
I was like, oh, another movie about like 70s cops
where there's gonna be like funk and disco music playing
and it's a comedy and, you know,
Sure, ha ha, you know that that that we've seen that a bunch
I
It is so fucking funny. It is so impeccably acted and
If it doesn't make you hate Ryan Gosling for being on top of everything else. He already is hilarious maddening
But I watched you on an airplane. I was laughing my balls off. I had to like kind of stifle myself
off because I was like kind of out loud uncontrollably laughing, but it's just a great feel
good movie. I can't recommend it highly enough. And it's the movie chain black did before
the predator. Oh, well, I hope you watch that soon because I've seen it and I'd love
to talk about it on this show. I would like to watch it. I was I was waiting for the rental
Because it's not streaming on any of the services yet. I wanted the rental price to drop a bit
So we could do it and then the fans if they haven't seen it could rent it for cheap. Yeah
But we we will do the predator that that's that's that's and it'll be relatively soon
I watched on HBO a little picture called
Life of the party
starring Melissa McCarthy
Okay
the complete back -to -school rip -off.
It is a complete back -to -school rip -off.
It gives back -to -school zero credit.
So, I'll give it this.
It surprised me with its plot right off the bat
because this was conveniently left out
of all marketing for the movie,
but 15 minutes in, and most McCarthy's very likely.
It's kind of like Paul Blart,
where the stuff when she's like a normal sweet lady
or guy at the beginning,
Right is so much funnier than the actual plot kicking in. Yeah, you know, like that's part of the ball
That it's the Paul Blark dies after admit it 21. Yeah, blood alone with his mom
You know that stuff. So I'll actually really funny believe it or not and this movie McCarthy as like kind of a sweet
Clueless mom is just a delight, you know, I she is a very funny woman. Yeah, she's great
I
Had a nice time and I was like all right, you know
I'm watching stupid comedies generally at night kind of cheer myself up, but this thing
Very quickly she goes to her daughters
You know welcome weekend or something and she quickly finds herself enrolling in school there
She fucks
One of this her daughters
Guy friends at school. Yeah, all right McCarthy and this PG the gentle PG 13 movies
He shows up on campus and almost immediately fucks one of her daughter's male friends,
who I guess is 18 years old, okay.
And I was like, holy shit, this thing went a little more raw than I was expecting.
I also step back and thought to myself, I tell you, you couldn't make this movie with
the sexist reverse, where Will Farrell goes to college and fucks his daughter's 18 year
old friend. It was called American Beauty. Yeah. I mean, like the closest you got was
old school, which was a hard R and even Vince Vaughn was like, I can't go through with
this. He doesn't fuck the girl in the movie. No, but Luke Wilson does. Luke Wilson does,
but they made it by a mistake, like even 20 years ago. And the scene is cut out. The bonus
scene is cut out when Luke Wilson says to Vince Vaughn, I could go to jail and Vince Vaughn
goes for what, being awesome.
Yeah, they cut that out of the room.
I kill her joke, but yes, cut out of the room.
But you could tell they were like,
we gotta be real careful about this and real sensitive.
And Luke Wilson was 30 and that girl was 20.
Well, she was supposed to be a high school child
in the movie.
She was in college, right?
No, she's about to keep, because that's the joke.
Oh, right, that's right.
I can't believe my little girl is about
to graduate high school.
Like, that's the big joke.
Yes, okay, yes, I remember that.
So, you know, I think it's supposed to be like,
she's barely 18.
Right barely legal as they say it right in the mags
Well, McCarthy's supposed to be like 45 and she says at the halfway point
She's like he's younger than half my age whatever. It was a weird, but I'm like, okay
They went for it for the sole comedy piece
She continues to fuck him and they form a relationship
And that's an hour of the film and the guys of a charisma void
He's got nothing going on except being kind of attractive. She just keeps fucking him
So I'm like, all right, then about an hour and 10 minutes in, you know, I don't mind
a comedy really having no plot if it's funny, but I was like, is there any story going
to kick in here?
It's just kind of like a weird, gentle, romantic comedy between Melissa McCarthy and this kid.
So she never does the dive that, uh, danger field that she never does the triple in the, there's
no diving scenes, but, uh, with, with about 20 minutes to go in the movie, they're like,
like, oh right, we don't have a story.
And she realizes she's gonna get kicked out of school
if she doesn't raise enough money to pay her tuition.
So then the gals all get together to raise her the money.
And I'm like, who wrote this thing?
Most of them, McCarthy and her husband wrote it.
But I guess they're just kind of given passes.
I mean, this thing was pretty charming and likable.
It just had nothing going on in it.
I just don't get how you do that movie.
and you just, in no way, well, I mean, look, Woody Allen's done it a million times with
like Igmar Bergman movies, he'll just lift. And look, I was always a big Woody Allen fan.
Like I really like this movie. I was very disappointed when I learned that. Like I was like,
this is really shitty. Like, you know, I thought this was some reared crazy movie made and it's
just a fucking copy of an Igmar Bergman movie. So it's like, so it was like, wow, you
You thought you knew Woody Allen, but then you found out that he copied in Mark Bergman.
And he did that before and that's what you know, it's just, you know, stop it.
Sure.
Can I just, can I, can I make a comparison without getting into some sort of fucking Twitter
battle?
You're not on Twitter.
You know what I mean?
You know, but it's, it's how do you, I don't understand how you just remake?
make back to school and you don't have to give it any crap.
I don't get that.
I don't get it either.
They crack down more and more on song sounding alike.
Movies have always been kind of slippery with this stuff.
And it's a little weird to me as well.
Because every fucking hack out here.
It's all been done.
That's the mark of a thief.
Anytime you hear somebody say that.
Well, what I did has been done.
That's a fucking thief talking.
Well, then other movies will, you know,
Sort of have the exact same plot. Well, so movies will have the exact same plot as something and not mention it
And then there are movies that are remakes of other things where almost nothing is similar. Yeah
You're like, what did you really need the name? Yeah, it's crazy. Did you get any money out of having this name?
I never understand second rewatch again on a plane
Was my cousin Vinnie classic
you know, it's just guys with these tough times that we're in right now, I just find
comfort in things I'm familiar with going back to the old stuff. Racism, my cousin
Vinnie is not racist. No, I'm saying that. Oh, you return to the things that I feel
that I find personally. Yeah, yeah, yeah, but yeah, casual racism. No, there's no need
for that word. You dress up for it. It's just a great flick. It's it's it's it's classic
machio. It's classic peshy. It's classic tome. It's classic Fred Gwyn. It's it's it's just
a really fun movie and it's really funny and it's one of those movies that on first glance
if you've never seen it, you would probably think was going to be corny or you know kind
And you know, it's got its slightly hockey moments, but no, overall, it's really funny.
And surprisingly edgy for that kind of movie.
It's a, I mean, it's a, it's a hard art.
I mean, there's a lot of fucks in it.
Yeah. I gotta say I had no, I found none of it hockey.
And what I love most about it is that the legal shit all makes perfect sense.
Yeah, it seems like realistic for once in a legal movie.
The legal stuff is great.
not hokey, but you know, there's definitely the moment of like, what the fuck a grits, you know.
He doesn't know.
There's that stuff in it.
It's funny.
Yeah, he's Vinny.
My favorite scene is when they're sleeping in the cabin and the owl hoots and he shoots up out of a deep sleep and he goes,
what the fuck was that?
Yeah, that's great.
Yeah, it's a great movie and Tomay, you know, people have said over the years that that was like a sort of a, you know,
Tomay is so great, but the my cousin Vinnie Oscar thing was was sort of a generosity.
I don't agree. I think I think she's fucking fantastic in it. Just because it's a comedy, comedy doesn't mean it's a it's not a complex role.
And I mean, she nails that man. She's like, I lived in Brooklyn in New York and everything. Like I'm like, she is that lady.
like I've met that lady like she's she's great. Yeah, she was up against four kind of boring British
actors and kind of forgettable British movies. I might be forgetting one that was good or something
but I think clearly everyone was like oh this was by far the most enjoyable performance of the year
and they were right. I recently listened to the director of my cousin Vinny Jonathan Lin who's
He's a very funny British guy who also directed greedy amongst many other things, whole
nine yards.
He's a good comedy director.
He had great stories about this movie and the studio begged him and begged him not to
cast Tomay.
They wanted anybody else and he was like stop guys like this is the person and finally he
went to peshy.
He showed like three actresses to peshy at their audition tape and he was like it's got
gotta be this one. So he goes, you need to call the studio be sort of vaguely threatening
that it's gotta be this one because they're gonna be scared of you. And let me have her.
So he did and they got the person and she was great. Good. Good. Austin Pendleton as the
stutterer. He's awesome in that moment. He is, I couldn't remember his name. He is, he's
fantastic. Yeah. He's awesome in everything. He's awesome in the movie The Front Page. He
Yes, with Matt Allen lemon. He's awesome. He's on an episode of Frazier. Yes, he's he's great that guy. I'm a big fan
Yeah, Gilbert Godfrey's podcast Jonathan Lynn some awesome my cousin Vinnie stories. I would recommend checking it out
I
So what do I want to talk about Joe? I get one more. I'm gonna go with
What's it gonna be so well you know what I'm gonna go with here's a super underrated
gem for you to check out the freshman we've talked about it on the show have we I mean
I'm not in the movie corner I'm just saying we've mentioned our affinity for the film
on the show well I think we'd also talk about my cousin many but I didn't give you
I'm just saying, you know, I'm just saying, I'm saying,
yeah, I agree with you.
It's not giving you shit.
Come on under my name in front of the fans.
The freshman, which I don't think I had seen since I was a boy.
It was on TV the other night, it's starting up.
I'm like, you know what, fun.
It's Andrew Bergman, who directed for my money,
one of the greatest romantic comedies
of my lifetime, Honeymoon and Vegas.
A hysterical movie, that's also very kind of sweet
and romantic, necklace catch.
and you know he did the in -laws he's done many things great movies great comedy writer and he
only does movie the in -laws the good one right I think he did both sadly but oh okay he just an
awesome writer director he he co -wrote blazing saddles I mean the guys a pretty genius guy and he's
great at late you know doing these kind of like laid back comedies where you meet all these like crazy
funny characters so the freshman is Matthew Broderick is a freshman he gets to New York
Bruno Kirby in a role that could have easily been played by Joe Pesci is like
hey can you do me a favor we'll give you some money he goes to meet Marlon
Brando who's basically playing his godfather role Don Corleone. Matthew Browder
is a film student who's studying the godfather so there's lots of funny parallels
there and he wants him to go pick up a Commodo dragon for him which is a lizard
to Reptile. So, this thing, just incredible. It's all sorts of high jinks, craziness, everything's
kind of funny, everything works, a bunch of great character actors. His film professor is particularly
hilarious in the movie. Who plays the professor again? I'm going to look up his name. You've seen him
in 10 million things. Yeah, I'm going to look up his name. And I will be in Miller at her best because
I never really liked her. I think she's very likable in this movie. I think she's always a delightful,
for a wonderful butterfly, if you will.
I will.
Frank Whaley, who you know and love
from career opportunities, the John Hughes movie,
as well as Pulp Fiction.
He's Brett is very funny.
And John Polito, who you know from the Big Lebowski,
and also the reverse people guy from Seinfeld.
Yes.
Just a BD Wong, it's super funny.
The guy who is the professor's name is,
God damn it.
Why won't you reveal yourself to Paul Benedict?
He was in like all the all in the family and all that shit.
He was, who do you play?
He was just a frequent like neighbor.
You know, I'll show him to you.
Let me see his face.
Oh, that guy, that's Bosley from the Jefferson's.
There you go, I've never seen the Jefferson's.
You've never seen the Jefferson's?
It wasn't in my rerun schedule.
Yeah, no, he's Bosley from the Jefferson's.
Well, there you go.
Yeah, he's great.
I love that guy.
Dude, you never saw the Jevon.
I want to.
If you ever want to watch Sherman Hemsley,
just blatantly rail against white people
and also treat his maid, play by Martha Gibbs.
Marla Gibbs.
Marla Gibbs, excuse me.
Like, just like trash.
Yeah.
It's literally black all in the family.
It's a complete asshole who has no,
Who's completely self -involved and is completely racist? Yeah, except he's black. Yeah, I
Have seen clips, but I need to watch more of it. It's very funny. It's a very
70s reruns. We always got shit 80s reruns where I was from except mama's family, which is awesome
Basically though this movie the twists and turns keep coming a mile a minute and in the end you learn that they want to serve
this endangered
Lizard to these
Rich people who are bidding on the privilege of eating a dying species. Yeah, and it's like holy shit
This is a PG move it was on Turner classic movies
And I was like I forgot this fucking dark twist in this thing and then at the ceremony where there's all these rich people waiting for you
I'm not this is not ruining anything
Bert Parks who was a like a crooner like a gulay type is
Singing there
Yeah, he is yeah, you're come out. Oh dragon. Yeah, this is one of the most insane scenes I've ever seen and I was
Really genuinely laughing the rest of the movie is kind of like gentle laughs throughout but really good dialogue and twist
But by the end I was howling and then Bert Park start singing Maggie's farm the Bob Dylan song. I ain't gone a
No reason for him to be singing a wild movie
Super funny and it's broad rate. It's broadrick back when broadrick
Was funny playing the sort of the the Patsy
Roderick it's kind of the Jason Bateman rule before he put on
48 pounds in just his stomach because he's clearly drinking his way through some something in that marriage
It's got something's going on over there look
Everyone looks different that that was 1990. This is 30 years later, but brought Broughtrick really turned it
Roderick looks like he's living hard. Don't get me wrong. And nobody's ever been more
miscast than Browderick on the Connors. He's. Holy God.
Super unwelcome presence on that show. It is just it's it's it's it's a left turn like
I've never seen. I know. Jay Foxx still looks like Jay Foxx. Yeah.
Yeah. Like he he he. Browderick turned into like the like Mr. Rooney. He did and his
love interest for Laurie Metcalfe. Like you're just not buying it. But I will say the Connors
It is a drama now essentially, but I like Goodman on it. I like Metcalf on it. I love our dear
friend Sarah Gilbert on it. And I think bringing in Jay Ferguson was the smartest thing they did.
He has such great chemistry with Gilbert. I love every actor on the show. Yeah. I think everybody's
very good on it. I am never going to be able to watch it and not see the glaring absence of Roseanne
on the show that she created. It's just it's just kind of weird. Like it's not people kept comparing
it to the Valerie Harper show.
Hogan family?
Yeah.
Well, that became the Hogan family.
It's like, it was on for four months before she left.
Yeah.
You know, it's like, this is the thing I grew up with.
It's just kind of weird.
Like, I don't know.
It's weird.
You know?
It works on me. It's it's kind of a I like I like keeping up with them or something
You know it's nice to have them back on TV
My lap and look and I'm happy for all of them that they think they're working. That's a great thing
my last
Movie corner pick is I finally broke the seal in my Werner Herzog
Box said I watched Nosferatu the vampire
Starring Klaus Kinski as the vampire you know, I've never seen it. I own it. I've never seen it
I really enjoyed it. It starts, look, we're in a Herzog is primarily a documentarian and he's an art house movie maker.
He worked with really low budgets and he did things his own way, which in certain moments in a movie is breathtaking and amazing and then in other moments you're like you couldn't have gotten a better take than that one.
Sure, what I mean, this is the line that you wrote.
Sure.
So, you know, it's like watching any sort of, you know,
like kind of art house flick in that sense.
But it's great.
And Klaus Kinski, who's the most terrifying person
that ever lived in regular life.
Yeah.
You know, they got him dressed up like Nosferatu
and, you know, being a van.
And he's fucking creepy as shit.
Right.
right. And he does shoot it sort of documentary style. It's a lot of natural lighting and it's
a lot of like, you know, there's not a lot of cutting in the scenes and stuff. And he
gives the actors free sort of space to move around and everything. And it's very, you
know, it's very akin to the to the Casavetti stuff. But it's a horror movie. So in moments,
in parts of the movie, it works very well. And then another part should like, well, this
This sort of gun, not gun hose the wrong thing, but you know, gonzo kind of running and
shoot it approach is at the at the expense of suspense at times, but it's a good movie.
I enjoyed it very much.
He does some really, really cool stuff with, with the, with, uh, not just natural lighting,
but when he does light certain scenes, they, there's some tremendously creepy shit that he
does.
I mean, the guy has an eye for a picture.
I mean, there's no doubt about that.
So, I highly, highly recommend it.
It is streaming on shutter right now,
and you can see it there.
I own it in my Herzog box set, which as yours,
as I can see on your shelf, remains unopened.
Yeah, this was me cracking the seal,
and I still haven't literally opened that yet,
but now I want to open it and watch all the other stuff.
I also have a box set of the collected films of whitey Herzog former St. Louis
Cardinals coach right I have a collection of the films of Chris Herzog who was a
guy I grew up with who sells beer now okay gotta get me a discount on the box
set not on beer that's what I want beer Joe Joe Joe tonight is no beverage to offer
We're just sitting here dry. I'm sorry. I didn't know I was a fucking
Shmorgas board. I mean he advised me to his home. I expect a baked bread a brief. Let's be honest
I baked a brief or doing this podcast. You wouldn't be here
Of course though. Nor would you have been welcome to be I would have met you at a local tavern
My god all I can think about is I want to go get shit fake same here. I'm not going to but I want to
Joe and I
We are going to watch Aquaman at my house, so expect that coming up and that's planning
an evening.
We were going to do that for this week's show, but instead we bring you glass.
We bring you glass.
Yeah, Joe and I, again, these are rare occasions, but we saw the movie together.
You'd think it happened more than it does, but it just doesn't.
Uh, and I blame Joe, frankly. I reach out. He be bats my hand away. Time and time again.
Sometimes I'll drive over to your house on my, my moped. Yeah. I'm all pissed just all over your doorstep. Literally.
Okay. I'll say fuck you. Well, suck it. Okay. Um, then I'll go see a movie by myself. I don't like that.
I wish it wasn't happening.
Glass, which is, for some reason, I cannot remember the title of this movie.
I just keep wanting to say split, even though, of course, we already saw split.
I think did split come out last year?
Is it that quick?
A turnaround?
And they didn't shoot them together?
I guess not.
No, they, they, I was thinking about that the whole time I was watching glass and I was like,
okay, clearly what he did here was he went to Blumhouse with split, he sold them on the
movie itself.
Right.
It was his own thing, and then he said, and here's the kicker, I am going to put this
button on the end where Bruce Willis comes in, and if split is successful, it will let
us make glass, and they were probably like, that's fucking awesome, because that's what
I would have been like, and apparently he raised his own money for it, which I found very
interesting.
He wanted all the profit, and now he's getting filthy rich, richer.
good for him. Yeah, glass is done extremely well at the box office. It's M. Knight,
Shyamalan is who we're speaking about. Critics panning it. Yeah, critics are not enjoying it.
It's the third in the if you will loose unbreakable trilogy. It stars Bruce Willis in a performance
where I would say I've never seen a lead actor outside of maybe Chuck Chaplin or Buster Keaton say
less in a movie that they were the star of that's alright though willis says almost nothing after
the first five minutes of this film but that's that character that's all right that's fine
i also uh...
uh... what i also what samlo jackson is returning as uh... what is it professor bird bones
Mr. Glass, Mr. Glass, they call me Mr. Glass, and then your boy James McAvoy plays Splity
McGue. The Horde. So the movie picks up the Horde. The movie picks up where Split left
off. At the end of Split, the Horde is still on the loose. He has not been caught. And we
And it's super human and the movie opens with that character he's abducted some new a new group of women
And then it cuts almost immediately to Bruce Willis
And do they do they make a clear and split that he's not fucking these girls?
He's not yeah, yeah, no, I know he's not and I never questioned that he was
But you're just kind of like you're abducting four cheerleaders and like tiny skirts
I think it's literally so the beast watch them eat them. Oh, okay, I think it's that's it
Okay, the beast needs like blood or something
Or the beast needs to be abusive because then you find out in this movie. Oh, he was abused as a kid
Sorry, there's gonna be spoilers
Tell me now to spoil the freshman from 1990 well, I mean that's not that big of a fucking spoiler
He was oh really the guy that is 38 personalities was was abused as a kid the so anyway
So, you know, we're at the top of this thing, the stage is set, the watcher or the overseer,
that's the character, that's the name they give Bruce Willis's character.
He is on the hunt for this, for the horde.
He wants to find him and they eventually get abducted and brought into a mental asylum
where they're being treated for a delusion of thinking that they are superheroes, and that's when
glass is brought into the mix. To not only be treated with them, but to also help the doctor
understand, you know, the mechanics behind all of this or whatever. So Sarah Paulson plays a doctor
at this facility. Uh, you know, an odd character. And she's an actress who does not do much for me
as we discussed last time. She gets the job done. Uh, you know, most of the actors get the job done.
I truly enjoyed McAvoy Willis and, and, uh, Jackson. I thought that they brought all the great
charisma and mystique back to those three characters that I loved in the first two movies.
I thought the supporting cast, you know, I didn't, I kind of didn't give a shit either way.
They were there just to, to, to, to grease the, the wheels for the characters I wanted to
watch.
You didn't like a old age makeup granny?
No.
Who, for some reason they lingered on her face for like long close -ups when it was not
a great makeup job. Yeah, no. She was, they that looked like a like community theater. It really
did makeup. And yeah, I mean, to me, Willis slip walk through this as he has slip walk through
every performance of the last 25 years. He seemed very sleepy to me in this. But fine, you know,
he's Bruce Willis. Didn't make much of an impression. Samuel Jackson, you know, you know, you just don't
even though it seems like he's in everything,
you don't see him in much anymore.
I guess because I dropped out of the Marvel franchise,
but I love the guy and seeing him in the wheelchair
and the purple vest and all was great.
He was really fun in this.
And McAvoy is killing it with his part.
He's really great in it.
And that's to me a lot of the fun.
I think the one thing it does that is kind of clever,
even though I sort of saw this coming,
They keep setting up a big showdown, a top building that's being built, like the new tallest building in town.
And they hint at so many times that obviously you think the movie's gonna end atop this tower,
but instead it's kind of a small, contained fight in the parking lot of this hospital that goes on for a long time.
But there's a reason for that that gets revealed.
We don't, let's not reveal the ultimate.
Not gonna reveal it, but you know, in the sense of it subverting expectations
of these kind of movies and doing kind of the superhero thing on a smaller scale.
It's in line with what Unbreakable was doing.
But for me, sitting in the theater 20 years ago watching Unbreakable, dreaming of the franchise, this could be,
it's not what we wound up with by a long shot.
This sort of seems like a low budget take on what would have been a pretty awesome high budget movie, I think.
I disagree, I thought it followed the steps of unbreakable almost identically, tonally.
I thought this was exactly what it was supposed to be.
I think because of the complete oversaturation of super hero, typical superhero movies,
people wanted this thing to be bigger and grander and whatever, and I loved that it was small.
Like people were calling the the ending a letdown and I was like it wasn't a let down
It was it was what this story was this was and then he even
This is a huge spoiler
So if you don't want to hear it plug your ears or what are your rules for spoilers?
Joe you're going back and forth. I know I'm sorry
But it's too hard to talk about it without spoiling stuff
Samuel Jackson says at the end
This was not a limited edition. This was an origin story
like so that's and that's what it was when you look back at the entire trilogy it was a three -part
origin story I thought it was very very well done I give the least amount of a shit about split
because that doesn't tie into my two favorite characters of the three but I think it works very
well as a as a trilogy and as a small story and I like the the message at the end of the whole thing
I thought it was a cool concept, I thought there was a little weird, there was a sort of
highly weird amount of sympathy for like Samuel Jackson's character, it's like he's murdered
hundreds of people. Well you do love, I mean I loved him the most. I love me too, I'm just saying
like other people in the movie being like you're spectacular. Right. It's like okay, that's
a little odd, but you know there's some atrocious dialogue and times. There's some really bad dialogue.
Okay. Um, but I, I, I really like the movie, you know, but people are walking out of this
thing saying it's one of the worst movies they've ever seen. They hate it. It's, it's a
bummer. Show a lot who is a huckster, but he said, you know, it's his highest testing
movie, like basically everyone loved it. And it doesn't seem to be the case, but I enjoyed
it. I respected it. What I did not want was like the Avengers 3rd act where not only does
does that bore me so much? No, I tend to leave when they get into that thing where it's
just giant CGI blobs throwing each other or get between buildings. I didn't want that
and I did not want this big tall building thing they promised. I didn't know how the movie
was going to end. I'll just say something about these three guys having like a little fight
in a parking lot. It was a let down to me. I guess what I'm saying is I wanted something
in between. That doesn't mean I needed a bigger action sequence. I just wanted something
different than the ultimate ending you get. The tag, if you will.
The only, the ending of Unbreakable is he goes into a house. I don't, to be honest, I don't
remember. Stopped like a home intruder. That's it. Right. Like it's very, very small. So
I thought that this work, and I thought that that was a commentary. All right, fine. We'll
blow the fucking lid off the, all the spoilers because I don't know how to talk about this
without doing it. I thought it was a commentary on super hero movies that at the end of the movie,
it's them sending the signal out to the world. Yeah. And saying these people exist everywhere,
come forward. That was M. Night Shyamalan saying, like, you've got that already. You've got the movies
where the entire world has superheroes. This is the movie about where it's three people
who are superheroes and it's completely tiny. And yeah, the fight happens there because it
It couldn't have happened anywhere else because they would have been shot to death by police
or whatever.
So, I liked it.
And I actually thought they missed.
I'm sure Shyamalan probably would have thought it was too hokey or whatever.
I would have liked to have seen a button on the end of the three, you know, the overseer's
son, Samuel Jackson's mom, and the girl that gets away from the ward in split.
Yeah, because they're sort of the team now sending the message out to the world of you know, if you're a superhero come forward or whatever
I would have liked to have seen a little button scene where they receive a message and
They say something like I got a message from a kid who says he can see dead people, right?
I thought that would have been really fucking cool. I didn't need to see him
I just thought that would have been a really cool tie -in like I will say I thought there was going to be I across my mind
to a six cents tie in at the end of this as he did with split and maybe he's
considered it I don't know but the twist in this was pretty unsatisfying the
final thing I guess why I prefer split slightly I think they're both B's B
pluses but I prefer it splits slightly because it got my pulse up it made me
scared it made me excited. I remember you had a heart on through that entire movie.
Well, I always do. It's called Priopcism. It's a permanent bone. But there's a, how do you
know what that's? Priopism because I live with it every day, Jim. I tuck it back. Ace Ventura
style. You don't like to say you're suffering from prizes. You like to say you're living with folks.
I got you, but the reason I per split was just that it just got me more
Excited I thought this movie kind of stayed at a certain level the whole time. There were no scares. No real thrills
No real chills. I enjoyed it, but I don't know
I thought you fucked up because you got and it wasn't your fault. You're at work
But you really missed a crucial in my opinion as a fan going in you missed a crucial moment in that movie
Because you showed up sort of like five minutes into the credits, but I asked you what happened and you were like, ah, nothing
Well, we could no, no, I told you what happened. Yeah, I couldn't sit there and be like here's what you know
We're in the middle of a fucking movie and it's it's playing. I would have been nice
I told you what I could, but I will tell you this as that movie started when you when it oh the cold
Open as McAvoy then it goes into the credits and it's playing like the fucking unbreakable. I think it's the theme from a cool with like the
a TikTok shit, and then you see two kids on their iPhone, like using their phones to
videotape them, punching a dude in the face for YouTube, and then going home, and then
you hear Bruce Willis come into the house. Like it was, I got chills. It was awesome. It
was awesome. And that's right, when you walked in, you walked in, when he was coming into
the house. And he let the end of Unbreakable or something. I don't remember the end of Unbreakable.
No, it's not the it's just it's just the setup for what his character does now.
Scours YouTube for videos of people. He bumps into the kids in the street and he sees he has the
vision that they're going around assaulting people for a YouTube channel. So he goes to their house
and beats the shit out of it. So they stop. But like when that happens, it's fucking it's such an
Awesome build up to that in the beginning you came in like right when he went into the house
Well, you really made it seem like it was nothing that I was supposed to do give you a you know
Stand up and mine it out for you in the middle of the fucking movie theater. I wouldn't a mind. Yeah
You know, maybe maybe don't be married to your job. Maybe take a break. I would love to
folks
That's our show folks. That's a show. I want to make a quick recommendation
My old buddy slashed boss when I wrote for Cinematical the AOL movie website
Scott Weinberg. He's a huge horror aficionado a film aficionado and a great follow -on Twitter
He does eat as a podcast with Drew McQueenie formerly of Ainut Cool, I believe formerly called 80s all over and if
You've listened to us and you want another take on things. They are an awesome podcast and
I love the guy. They have great chemistry together and what they do is they break down the 80s one month at a time
So every movie that was released in
January of
1980 they discussed and that's one episode then a month later you get every movie that was released in February
Jesus Christ and it's they're up to 84 now. So they're talking about you know temple of doom and splash and all these movies
But you're also getting all these things that you saw in the video store when you were a kid and we're like
What the fuck is this and they watched it they watched them all they have time to do this well
It's a month. It's a monthly podcast and as far as movies that come out in the month you're getting maybe 20 or less
But I'm saying like
They're watching all that's an incredible. I'm impressed at the commitment of that
I'm happy. They're doing it. I'm loving it and the reason I'm shouting out is a I started listening to it
And I love it but B they had a big controversy this week because this much larger movie conglomerate was basically gonna
to start doing the exact same premise in the nineties. And one of the two that was going
to do this was a fan of their podcast and they were like, Hey, we spent a long time trying
to come up with this original idea for a show. Don't rip us off. The new guys eventually
back down all as well, but they deserve your support. They're great, especially for getting
an original idea. I mean, Joe and I sit in a couch and talk shop, you know, I'll check it
out check it out 80s all over cool kids Friday nights on Fox we're you know we're in reruns
here and there but we got a lot of new ones coming up that are fantastic check us out
and I'm on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh I will be if you're in the Dallas
Texas area I'm in Addison this weekend Thursday Friday Saturday five shows total Addison
I said, sorry, the Addison Levity Live, it's called now.
Not the Addison Improv, but I will be there.
So come on out, Emily Florence.
Our matriarch will be there as well.
She's gonna come out to a show or two to hang out.
So you get to say hello to Emily as well.
If you catch her at the right show,
some hellians came out last time I was there.
I hope to see you guys again
and hopefully a few new faces.
And yes, you are getting a bonus episode this month.
It's gonna drop right at the end of the month,
meaning tomorrow or Wednesday, and that episode.
Tomorrow or Wednesday.
Yeah.
Friday or Wednesday?
Tomorrow or Wednesday, this comes out on Monday.
Do you still not know how our own podcast works?
I'm, you're able to put yourself in the mind space
of a listener on Monday.
I'm not able to do that.
You just it's why it's why I'm such a good actor. Mm -hmm. And I think I'm gonna throw this at you
I'm we haven't discussed it. What do you what do you think of this for the bonus app our Oscar picks great great
That's coming to you tomorrow or Wednesday and that's our show folks and hold on we didn't forget your shout -outs
You thought we forgot for a second didn't you do we forget do we ever forget?
yet, or maybe one time we forgot, but here they are.
And they usually happen on this last episode every month.
And we thank you, as always, for contributing
and supporting the show.
You all are the best.
Helians are the best.
And I'm actually gonna read the names today
off of my laptop instead of off of my phone,
which I'm always like sort of squinting to see
and I'm having a hard time reading and then I thought oh there's a bigger screen I can use
and just a wave of relief washed over me. You know it's amazing how much I don't think of half
the time, all the time. Anyway here's what I'm getting at. Here are your shout outs. Anthony
six inches from my computer screen. I still have to wear my glasses. Oh, God, I'm just deteriorating
before my own eyes. I am old. Katrina Elise Gossett, Andrew Telken. Telken, excuse me,
Preston Anderson, Bryce Buckmaster, Rusty, Martin Murray, Marcus Potish, Ed Minigabo, Scott
Sinjee, Derek Kelsmer, Nicholas Edward Fallon Albeck, Paul Neenan, Evan Barrett,
Neil Dolby, Christopher Klinger, Ken Hanley, Bugmaine, Jaronne Sanderson, Hayton Davidson,
Thomas Breill, Christianson, Whitney Abbott, Marcus McGahey, or McGahey. I don't know which way
you say that, but I gave you both.
Peeve, Jared Pakwin, Christopher Musio, Daniel Paschal, Joe, I swear I'm not racist,
I was just tired and nervous.
Nicole, Will Nolton, Dave Krainsky, Jonathan Sprouls, Chris Simmons, Brian Shactor, Taylor,
Lindy West, Dustin Collins, Kevin Swistowicz, not medium rare. Tom Holt, Justin Tyler, Pat
Walsh's Dad, Babybop and Barney, and Babybops Blanky. Chris Marsh, David Crumholtz,
I had a wife, old friend, Alexander, Alexander.
Monter, let me start that one over.
Alexander, Monterey Bio.
Montereo, Alexander, Montereo Bio.
Monterebio.
I'm so sorry if I'm butchering you know,
I'm doing my best, I promise.
Matt Chairs, Martin Don, Dan Jarchell.
Ryan Peahaw, I'm reading them off the bigger screen. I'm reading them worse than I do on the small screen. Oh my God.
What's going on? Is this the end for me? Christopher Reynolds, Patrick Baxter, Julie Bailey, Violet, you're turning Violet, Violet, Anna, Sam Elliott, Brett Irway, Patrick,
Wathen, Truth Crab, Dave DeWitt, Sadie Bug, Cole Rothaker, Waffles, Stephen Calpa, Sam
Mitchell can't see his toes over his stupid fat ankles. Kelly Amaroso, Beth Gaston,
Sharifa, David Denahee, Devolo, Trevor Gage, Joshua Christensen, KP Flynn, Elva Enriquez,
Lesley Coffett, Jackson C. Lohmeyer, Ash Ogden, Reign, Purple Peacock, Sterling Obrigo,
Christopher Sabayla, O 'nonymous Boner, very good, very clever.
I mean, if that's, if that's, your name is actually O 'nonymous Boner, that's pretty awesome.
But I think that's a play on anonymous boner.
Drew Tiberius Paul, Tyler Lapointe, Steve Smith, Loupé Peta, Pacheo, Tanki Zonjik.
I think I said that properly. Matt Robin, Will Foley, Kevin Ragoti,
where Ragoti, Joseph, Christian Reynolds, Josh Smallridge, Kurt Ziegler, Brittany Ferguson.
I'm sorry. Yes. No. Yeah. Sean Florida, Danny Rudd, Natalie Hartline, Leo Lopez, Emily
Rock, Emily Rook, not rock. I said it. Roger. She spelled it out here. Sorry, Emily. Scott
Thieu, Dave Del Greco, Kurt Zeigler, Chloe Paget, Dennis Ormston. By the way, if I have said
anybody's name wrong, feel free to do what a lot of people do and put the pronunciation
in with the profile name. So that's actually very helpful. Travis Hines, Josh
Weisengruber, Matthew McGuire, Angela Porcaro, James O 'Brien, Matthew Moon,
Jay Fisher, Sean Lyle, John Hollywood, Jake Mick Alvane, Meredith McWilliams,
Channing Chatham, Jesse Janicki, Mike Greenwood,
Brianna Alcair, Matt, supportive guy.
Oops, I said that last one wrong.
You're telling me, Anthony Rodriguez, Chris Passmore,
Casey Jones, Sinji, Robert Haynes, Natalie Hatley,
Will Pittman, Kevin McNannie, Kevin Driscoll,
Jen Wessels, Joe Hoffman, Scott Sweeney,
Jay Miller, Clayton Stamper, Amanda Lancaster, Michael Bowless, Ethan Gammage, James
Guillermo, Derek Adams, Sean Hall, Adam Loundsbury, Vincent Franks, Joseph
I think that's supposed to be in Dennis Leary voice.
Anyway, Sarah Catherine, Paul Merchie, Scott Sweeney, Kara Konini, Chuck Andrews, Tom
Laverick, Tucker Rouch, John Smith, Andrew, Brian Bolarier, Bolarier, Will Helms, Jennifer
for Anna T L. Munholland Jake Bullock. Slay bodies not reindeer zero fox
trot .com Matt Crawford, Richard Deming, Brian Callis, Tim Drain, Michael
Madgerigal. As always, visit Mr. Shoot records. If you're in Lancaster,
Pennsylvania, Richard Howenstein, Breton Fraser, Sean Luke Physiock, Karen Kill
Garif, hello. Listen to my favorite murder. If you already are not doing that, Nathan Baskett,
Gary Myron, Dylan Larr, Phil Borrell, Edmund Dillon, the black magic ninja, Scott Pauline
Surrell, Daphne Kellogg, Tristan Avery, Hunk Masterson, Matthew J. Brown, Julia Guire, Charity Ferguson,
Jackson, Hank from Dancakes, Nick Walther, Alexander Stein, Emily Marvel, John B.
Wat, old buddy, visit John's store, Zambian's horror crafts on Etsy.
Morrie Benjamin, Nicholas Burns, Alex Nelson, Jeremy Kuhl, two fat to skate, Alex Shipley,
Sean Pinnock, Amanda Liebson, Timothy Letso, Shane Nazarene,
Smelly Bubbles, Samantha Kiefer, I love you, David Belinger,
or Belinger, Hunter McDonald, Justin Bowhugger,
Bohagger, Adam Benbenic, Manny Rios,
Damani O 'Rubio, Brandon Gash, Jake Farot, Rob Lines,
James Jacob Barrett, Jordan C. Maxwell Ashcroft, Ryan Kohler, Barb Allen, Chris Bowen, Mike
Gibbons, Donnier Joyce, Michael Dawson, Jennifer Smith, Connor Denney, Anthony J. Guajardo,
Annie Johanison, Timmy K. Megan Lybrand, Scott Blikensdurfer, Brett Wemmer, Laura Sexton,
in Anthony Guajardo, Jared Blair, Richie Verdugo.
I swear to God, I'm having a harder time seeing the names
on the bigger screen.
I think it's because when I do it on my phone,
I hold it an inch from my eye.
Chris Hooper, hopper, sorry.
Emily Florence, our wonderful matriarch,
visit the hog house store on Etsy
that she set up for this show,
but also wish Emily a happy birthday.
day. She just turned 32, I believe. Sean L. Abby Manuel, Jonathan Galat, Michael McBees,
Stephanie Power, Diego Campos, Stefan Musal, Zoe Blaskovic, Aasley Kivinsland, Dan
McCloud, Lorenz Bunganiers, Alejandro Salgado, Tracy Reddington, Sean Thomas, Amanda
Linda Alzemora, Jason Weibel, Mike Curry, Andrew Kovale, Sam Mitchell, Aaron Millinowski,
Scott Nolan, Ben, Misty Zavar, Moli Russell's Wart, Dejane Wilford, hello, Johnny Furg,
Michelle Gold, Danielle Doer, Eric Lamora, Kevin Marcenek, Lawrence Anderson, Jared
Small Ridge, Will Potor, Hello, Will, Kyle Kinslin, the man whose name we must not speak,
Auntie Bobba Duck, Scott Patton, Sam Street, Kevin Stickers at pint services .com, the
block watch, I thought that said the black witch.
My eyes are, I'm done, I'm done, put me out the pasture, the block watch, rage, last name
sounds Asian, Michael, ILO, and Reed, Asthetic. Ladies and gentlemen, as always, overwhelmed
by the the outreach of support, truly a beautiful thing. Thank you to all Helians. We love
you all. And it's a pleasure to do this show for you. And that's it. All right. We'll see
you in February with some new stuff and the bonus episode drops very tail into
this month. Again, we didn't we didn't forget that it'll be out the 30th or
31st. All right, we'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.