I'll see you in hell.
it's we'll see you in hell back on the beat that sweet beat on the street to talk about the heat
Beverly Hills Cup axle F actually I'm very glad we didn't get the trailer with
yeah yeah yeah yeah like a converse high top goes slow motion through the air now
have you seen that speaking of exactly that have you seen the trailer for Reagan no
but you you mentioned it to me please fill me in because I didn't watch it so
there's a movie coming out called Reagan about Ronald Reagan oh Ronald right
yeah you know I'd imagine it's an interesting story sure Dennis Quaid is playing Reagan
that's Quaid's a good actor and he does kind of look like Ronald Reagan I'll buy it
Penelope Ann Miller as Nancy Reagan what the hell all right thought she was dead well the rest of
the cast is is as you read the cast list I don't know anything about Penelope Ann Miller but
but as you read the cast done and Betty lose handbag my sister used to rent that all the time
I was like you got the gun and Betty lose handbag again and the freshman right is she the freshman
she isn't the freshman which is a great movie she doesn't leave much of a mark so as you read the
cast list because Dennis Quaid has has recently come out and said he's is Trump's got his vote
yeah you start you start to realize this is oh this is like a Republican project because like Robert
Davies in it Kevin Sorbo like these known like rip when it was just fine that's their business but
but I'm like this is one of these like we're gonna do a pro conservative movie right okay whatever
you know action companies got liberty in the name yeah yeah exactly yeah but then here's the weird
part halfway see you're watching the trailer and you're just like okay that's what this is whatever
and that but then halfway through the trailer a slow modern rendition sung by a young woman
of everybody wants to rule the world cousin right so so you're just going through the trailer going
like yeah this looks like like a Ben Shapiro movie you know and then and then all of a sudden it goes
welcome to your life and I'm like wait a minute wait a minute first of all this isn't an R .C.
whatever so why are they trying to do the R .C. thing well not I guess that's not even R .C. anymore
but like like wait wait this seems like a very pro Reagan movie why are they playing that song
that sounds like it's about how we're hungry yeah yeah climbing for the throne while I thought you
were gonna say born in the USA but that would be like the Oliver Stone version a little wink to how he
misinterpreted the lyrics blah blah blah yeah so I I don't really understand maybe maybe it's not a pro
Reagan movie I don't know I think it is it's gonna be pro that much I can assure you the reason
I texted you is because this is my favorite of all the caskings casting Scott staff of Creed is
playing Frank Sinatra yeah that blew my mind kind of now I really blew my mind I googled
Scott staff Frank Sinatra it comes up instantly is it does he look like him at all the no pictures of
him in makeup heavily okay I promise you it's two so it's like one scene where he's like on a stage
right you know then it cuts to thank you mr. president you know that's it but they did there's a lot
of side yeah singing yeah one for my baby
so they did all these side -by -side pictures of them and I got to say
he looks way more like Frank Sinatra than I thought he did okay I was like oh he kind of
does resemble him a little bit now Randy Quaid came up at a BBQ I was at this weekend
and I last I really heard of him he had made a sex tape where he and his wife wore clown masks
and fucked in a cave and it was readily available online and he had lost his mind and he was
full trump but also just sort of like calling for the end of society so I wonder if he and Dennis
connect over trump and stuff like are they still in contact do we know well I know when
if Quaid said a few years ago he said I just missed my brother and I in the way he said it I was like
oh man he's he's saying like my brother has like become a guy I don't know anymore and he's left
the country because he said people are trying to kill him and stuff and I don't think Dennis Quaid
is a is a through and through like republic like Quaid is like way like he does videos on his ex -feed
where he like shines up lights his face in like a darkened room yeah and he'll be like and he'll be
responding to some like Fox News clip that went viral where they criticize trump and he'll be like I
see the fiery foxes are at play again and they don't understand they'll get theirs in the it's
crazy yeah I gotta see some of that so I don't think Denny and crazy or less crazy than Spacey's
Christmas Eve house of cards videos I say crazier because at least at least with Spacey at least
with Spacey there would you could be like look regardless of his antics and or offenses like it's
like you at least with Spacey could go the guy's having a hard time he's lashing out the weird way
with Quaid the weirdest way with Quaid that there's no none of that I'm just like he's he's doing like
hobbit poems about the fox dudes like this is insane yeah yeah I'm gonna throw in another one to
look at and maybe we can rank the crazy but Stephen Baldwin Stephen Baldwin not the Baldwin that
pops into mind when you think of the boys but um he has quietly lost his mind and I've also seen him
he's I think because I started watching his feed now he pops up on my reels constantly okay um
so sometimes you see him like in a podcast interview he was telling a story about being on the set
of casualties of war I watched that whole win that one yeah I loved it it was so and you know he was
like Sean Penn starts talking and he's like hey what do you do you know he's doing this like Westside
story accident and Stephen Baldwin goes well I'm sorry cut because he was so taken aback
yeah on Penn doing this crazy voice and Brian De Palma goes you never know God on my
sin like start screaming at him very intense and also screamed you don't question Sean yeah you
don't question Sean yeah yeah wild and uh it was a great compelling story very well told by Steve
Baldwin so maybe he's fine but when you venture into and I need you listeners Joe everyone
venture in there's a lot of stuff of like he's at like did you ever do like the ASL chat rooms
in the early days of the internet and you know you're talking to some fat old man and you're a 13 year old
boy no no no no judgment but no I never did like age sex location that kind of you never
chatted Joe no I never chatted at all much less ever did like chat sex or anything I didn't understand
it until sexting became a thing I would I would when sexting became a thing I was like oh I could have
been doing this the whole time yeah yeah yeah um wait why ain't God's name was I talking about
even Baldwin yeah like this dimly lit like almost like a webcam but like one of those early circle
ones that you put on top of the computer you know yeah cheap he's horribly lit and 90 % of these
is him like talking about how much he loves his wife or Jesus but he'll be like oh
oh like almost like wrestler type weirdness and then he'll be like that's that feeling
then I just got because my my wife drove me to the airport and I realized how much I need that woman
in my life I mean wild and then he'll shiver like oh I just keep thinking and then when he looks up
and opens his eyes genuine tears start flowing from his eyes freely as he talks about how much he loves
his wife or Jesus wow um well I don't know what's going on everybody's going through a lot check out
his page it's it's a it's a snap spill around here everybody's losing their shit the uh yeah I'll
tell you who comes off recording the Adams family theme song the amount of snaps I've been hearing
around I'll tell you who seems genuinely crazy speaking to that interview is fucking Jamie Kennedy
throughout that interview yeah a lot of that generation is gone mentally gone mentally he's
if you if people watch the interview Kennedy's almost like sitting uh I don't know the term of it
it's probably not the PC term anymore but he's almost sitting Indian style like in the chair which is
always troubling when somebody does that he's all like you only really see it with Jim and
Glick you don't see it very much else he's all bunched up in the chair and he keeps being like
wait wait go back to that part go back to that part that part do that part again and you're like
what the fuck happened to Jamie Kennedy this guy used to lead films can I tell you what I think
and I wouldn't have I wouldn't have had a guess I would have said drugs or something 20 years ago
but having lived here in LA a good solid 20 -ish years 20 let's be real uh no close doesn't matter
I think what drives people insane is when once the I should have been bigger talk starts
and everyone out here has it regardless of what you do writers produce everyone thinks I should
be a bigger deal more people should know about me I should be I should have what that guy has
and once you start into that and that becomes like all you can talk about which is a lot of people
out here that's I think when when the mind really starts to go because you're just constantly in this
fantasy world of what could have happened and the truth is you also could have been hit by a fucking
tractor yeah and had your brain smashed all over the road but you're doing fine but a lot of these
people sit and I had to do a lot of work to make sure it wasn't going to be me because this kind of
runs in my family too where you just start rambling and obsessing about these old times and the
people who got you and the people who got one over on you or whatever yeah it's tempting you know
and you're you're obsessed with it because you think you can change the outcome is what my therapist
says you think that by just simply talking about it and obsessing over it every day of your life
you'll be able to will a different outcome and of course you can't no no no no but um it's a
dangerous space to live in yeah there's these people who you know like I the fucking Lawrence
brothers you know the Lawrence brothers ain't had a hit between them in in in 15 years you talking
the Joey Lawrence Brothers Joey Matthew and whatever and yet they got this podcast where they talk
about the old days and they talk about them fondly and with respect and with you know we were on top
for a minute like I had it I'm happy where I'm at now it was fun then I'm glad I had it whatever
you can go that route or you can go the bitter route and it's about 50 50 but the bitter
route is also what leads to uh just people losing their mind when their looks start to go they can't
they can't get a handle on it they can't wrap their minds around it so they just start going nuts
well it's it's why uh and people will complain you know it's like why politicians like people
be like and this politician just go away yeah why do they keep research it's the it's the Hollywood
version of that it's like these people that continue to live in Washington DC yeah after their moment
is up and it's like just go you did it you did it would it be that bad to go work in a goddamn
best buy or something like just go take a breath Jerry Seinfeld is still answering decades later
why you got out and he's like because I wanted it to end while it was good that's not a very
American point of view no one everything to be beaten into submission till it's not funny or
entertaining anymore I just saw an interview with him where he said uh he's losing it too they said
well he's got to stop with the I'm a comedian thing yeah yeah every he's gonna stop talking about
Marcus Aurelius he he clearly made this decision when he made that documentary comedian that he's
like all I am ever going to talk about ever again is that I am a comedian yeah yeah so this latest
interview they're like your marriage you you say it's very successful you're very happy you've been
married for decades what's the secret did you is it something you always wanted he goes no no
the guy goes what do you mean he goes I'm a comic okay let me tell you what comics and like
that shouldn't be the answer to that question that's not factor into your answer to that question
he says any any now for once he denounces a comedian and he goes comedians think we don't need
anybody we just need us yeah and uh and he goes and that's not a good way to be so I got married
because I said let me see if I can do this thing I'm probably not good at you're like right I
I don't think that sweeps your wife off her feet or that it seemed like a challenge yeah you know
but uh anyway uh I'm glad the Lawrence boys are doing well I am happy to hear that yeah you know
look I I don't know and it maybe maybe all they do in that podcast is bitch I'm saying what I've seen
about it the things that uh Instagram decides that I want to see look I'll say this they're usually
pretty spot on but I don't know why you're throwing me the Lawrence's um clips of them discussing
you know on the set of blossom X happened you know uh Matt so Andrews the youngest Andrew uh
uh looks very Joey they've aged they've all aged very differently Joey aged like Hollywood style
like yeah he's got the it seems like he's got a hair piece of some kind he it seems like he's had
some work done yeah uh the middle one Matthew Matthew was the kid in plans transit automobiles and I
prefer nougies yeah he was also now he is uh dating chili from uh TLC wait what he is dating one
of the TLC gals that's wild good for him together like years yeah they seem very happy Matt is also
boy meets world right we don't savage I don't know about oh no no yeah he was also on boy meets world
the two younger brothers of that's interesting yeah uh he also uh is the kid now is Matthew the
kid entails from the dark side the movie or I think that's the youngest one no no that's Matthew two
okay the youngest one aged uh he looks very different I'm not saying it's better good he just looks
different like yeah they all aged differently Matt was saying about Matthew's Matthew age like he looks
exactly the same the youngest one looks very different and Joey aged like Hollywood style but I'm
glad they uh hey I'm I got nothing I got no beef with the Lawrence boys good for them no I was never
a fan but I was also never a hater uh got here look at this Christchurch had hurt Christchurch
had all three of them on oh did it yes together yeah Jesus God is that the last great like really
penetrated the culture catchphrase was Joey Lawrence's whoa maybe another Zingha
what's Bazinga I don't remember though I've never seen an episode I know it's his
Sheldon's catchphrase on Big Bang Theory uh oh well okay I thought the one that ended them all
and it was the last was getter done I was I thought that was like the sort of that was it I'm talking
I'm talking sitcom character catchphrase but okay but a comedian I'm sure a lot of comedians
if you've ever heard of a comedian who had a failed catchphrase that they kept pushing
that nobody caught onto because that sounds like some real embarrassment well the the the one that
comics always laugh at is is hamburger hamburgers incredible though yeah we would always catch on
to this day comics are still sitting in comedy clubs going hamburger yeah shucky ducky quack quack
was another one the love shucky ducky quack yeah that's like I mean forget you don't even need the
joke that's gonna hit every time let's talk films I don't know that there's any big film news this
week that you and I were griping about Joe but we can go to the movie corner certainly well we're
real quick before we do I got to sort of a scary stuff but but we've talked a band we've talked
about on this pod many times we've praised in my favorite band of all time the mighty uh
Foo Man Choo have a new record out called the future sorry the uh return of tomorrow and I can say
without question is one of their best albums holy cow it's a real masterpiece they did a great job
they sound amazing they're playing better than ever it's awesome it's just an awesome awesome record
so if you like Foo you like metal you like stoner rock I can't recommend the record enough
and it's appropriate for scary stuff it's loaded with sci -fi imagery and all that stuff so
it's an awesome record I watched there what's in my bag from amoeba I don't know when it was from
yeah but Scott Hill the lead singer uh and guitar you know the founder of the band
one of the things he grabbed was the DVD set of planet of the apes well that's how long ago it was
was before the blue ray was out uh he got the DVD set of planet of the apes and he said that the
those films were like his favorite films of all time and that they had a huge influence on Foo Man Choo
like the the subject matter or whatnot so okay although that was interesting um but uh it's an
amazing record if you heard it yet have you had a chance I haven't I die now will I now will yeah
all right and I if I may would love to shout out I always warms my heart to see people in the
comments who say that Joe and I are kind of the new sys cool and ebert for them and uh there's a new
book and audio book called opposable thumbs which I highly recommend for all you uh fans I grew up
on sys cool and ebert as we as we've discussed on here many times I'd watch it every Saturday before
mass we've got a Saturday night mass make sure we ruin as as much of the good part of the weekend as
possible um but yeah sys cool and ebert was amazing it's called opposable thumbs colon how sys cool
and ebert changed movies forever it's written by matt singer uh it's very entertaining and you get sort
of dual bio dual biographies you know you as much as I loved life itself you might not sit down to read
like a thick biography of either gene sys cool or roger ebert you get nice concise bios of each
uh on their own terms up to then when they both meet how the show happened um how these guys who
were not tv stars at all became tv stars how a genuine hatred for each other became a sort of
mutual respect and deep love that right up to the end was very hard for them to talk about um it's great
it's a great book if that interests you at all check it out on to that movie corn uh i've been watching a lot
lately i'm doing a rewrite of something and it required me to do a bunch of research so i have a
bunch of kind of dry talking news type movies but some good stuff um let's kick things off with a
rewatch of spotlight um i like spotlight quite a bit and i if it i think it one best picture um so
i was talking this weekend with somebody about how you can't even remember what one best picture the
last five years and used to be able to rattle off 20 no problem um but spotlight i watched that
along with all the presidents men and i'll do them both together i mean they're two sides of the same
coin spotlight is clearly heavily influenced by all the presidents men um but spotlight is about
going into the Boston Catholic Church sex abuse scandal um it stars Michael Keaton john slattery
racial macatams mark ruffalo everybody's good but everybody's kind of in their own movie in a weird
way um the acting's a little flat the movie's a little flat it's got kind of a tv movie vibe
just talking about when you watch it years later sometimes these movies lose a little bit of their
luster but what you can't take away from it is that it's a fascinating story very well told
if these movies are well researched and well acted you know it almost just operates like documentary
i love like a zodiac -type long probe into a subject um i recently saw some interview david fincher
about zodiac and they're like were you shocked by the box office failure of that movie and he goes no
it's a three hour movie there's no it's a three hour mystery without a resolution
i'm not shocked at all that that movie didn't do well which i love like he doesn't give a fuck
i'm sure the people who lost money care but um spotlight is depressing you know as as it's this
great expose and mystery it's of course very depressing what the Catholic church did and has continued
to do uh in regards to this and then all the president's men you know watergate i think is just
um a less icky subject and that plays moral i kind of a cracker jack thriller without that deep
sadness that comes along with spotlight and them talking to the victims and so forth but
i love this kind of movie what what's your favorite one of these like newspaper movies jump
uh i'd go with the insider probably i think i talked about it last week on an incredible movie yeah
i've always enjoyed that film and it's you know that's you're getting you're getting pichino
and crow at their best exactly what you want out of them yeah pro playing a grizzled miserable guy
and pichino playing an explosive passionate man yeah but i love spotlight quite a bit uh i also love i
mean it's this is a cheat of an answer but it's a newspaper movie and i do love it but i i love the
front page with uh man it never opened it never sent it it's got some very very funny moments yeah
it's a very late era billy wilder movie it might be his last movie um if not but uh it's a fun
movie but it is it is surprisingly true to the newspaper trade uh of of you know it's a period piece
but yeah it's fairly accurate in how it and how it's uh you know portrayed so uh but yeah i got
i guess insider probably we're i can't say spotlight's my i love spotlight but i only saw it once
yeah this is my second um all right i'm gonna go with a family theme here which i guess does relate to
today's film i'll start with uh well i'll start with the worst of three that i saw
Owen Wilson and Ed Helms's father figures i have started that movie 30 times never made it
two minutes it's terrible uh it's terrible it's cat Williams cat Williams is kind of funny in it
they don't give them much but he does the most
Ed Helms pulls off they do the running gag you know their mom is played by glit okay so it's about two
kids they find out that their father is not who they thought their father was on the day that their
mother gets remarried yeah uh they never knew their father and they find out they thought their
dad was dead they find out he's not dead he's still alive and she's quite frankly not sure who her
father their father was because she was part of the sort of free love movement in the 60s and they
go on a journey together they're they're sort of estranged brothers that go on a comedic journey
together to find their father and as you can guess folks their fathers are played by an array of
uh uh uh goofy and and somewhat interesting celebrities you got Terry Bradshaw as
himself yeah uh you got JK Simmons as a like weird reclusive former million stockbroker
millionaire Wall Street guy okay uh and then last well then there's another guy that's not as
big I can't remember who the third guy is and then and then Christopher walk in as the final but um
yeah I mean spoiler alert in the end you find out they don't know who the dad is because Glenn
Colossus and even their mom she's the woman that cared for their teenage mom who died in in giving
birth to them it's a lot of twists and turns for a fucking road trip buddy buddy movie but and the
problem is you don't care about any of them it's a very boring film there really are no laughs
there are two laughs in the whole thing there's a running gag where every time they meet like one of the
new dads they do the thing where they're like excuse me sir do you know a woman named such and such and
the guy will be like oh do I ever man did she do a thing with her tongue that you know like whatever
sure sure it's been done that old trope yeah but there's a funny part where Ed Helms like by the
third dad like loses it means like uh -huh you can stop before you talk about her candy nips
or and that part's kind of funny okay and then there's another part where Ed Helms thinks
that he fucked his sister because he didn't know as a sister and you're like that's pretty funny
yeah but that's not a sister of course because the fucking Hollywood movie they won't stick to a joke
like that uh only that's my boy committed heavily to incest and stuck with it what was that's my boy
again Sandler and Sandberg are rated or lost a tremendous amount of money
Sandler playing Sandberg's dad if I'm not mistaken yeah well no is yes correct but Sandler when he
was in high school had fucked Susan Sarandon who was his teacher okay and that that was the story
gave birth at a very young age there's like a comedy version of May December
so I'd skip father figures uh I put it on in the depths of a depression I just wanted something
that wouldn't challenge me and it did not but I was sad enough to watch it just frunked it back man
in one song don't skip father figure the song by George Michael probably his best song
I rewatched South Park bigger longer and uncut new to 4k um truly probably the least essential 4k release
I was excited to rewatch it but I was like oh yeah this it hasn't really looked that much different
since back in the DVD days it's bad animation I guess the colors look nice but um more than ever
I'm impressed with it as a musical I think the songs are fucking awesome I had the soundtrack but like
from a melody standpoint from a lyrical standpoint they're genuinely funny genuinely catchy genuinely
well -written songs um and they're not direct parodies of things they're original music it's really very
impressive I think um south park when I saw it in the theater I mean it blew my fucking mind
I remember my dad trying to watch it and getting very angry south park and jackass the movie both
made him extremely angry um and to where he was yelling at me as if I had made them like he was angry at
my generation for creating this trash and he was just watching it at home on like a Friday night
on VHS just like fuming he turned them both off but um that's kind of the point of south park and jackass
is to piss off people's parents and the movie is really kind of brilliant because they insisted that
it be rated are paramount famously showed them that they would make like each personally they'll like
you'll each make another 50 million dollars if you make this movie PG -13 and they were like nah
what's the point like they can watch that on TV we want it to be a hard R and it is it has an
insane amount of profanity in it um I forgot about Saddam Hussein whipping out his actual dick at one point
there's lots of shocking shocking stuff in it hilarious stuff in it um it's super well written
it's short which is great it's like 80 minutes but it does fall apart in the third act they don't have
enough story to kind of sustain it and he kind of start to get a little tired of it but um especially
compared to like imagination land and those stuff that they were gonna be sequels to south park and then
they wound up just kind of putting them on paramount plus those while funny you know they play like
kind of average episodes of south park bigger lugger bigger longer and uncut is the best thing they ever
did probably I mean it's it's a genuinely good piece of American satire and art and it's still
great I love it Joe uh second film uh this is a pretty it's a decent horror movie it's not great it
gets away from itself but it's called the evil within uh it was made in 2017 it was directed and
written by a guy named Andrew Getty this is a movie he was trying to make for quite some time he was
a he was an oil air a businessman in a philanthropist he died before it's I mean so it got life is
cool uh it says um he owned some historic mansion in the Hollywood Hills he was reclusive two weeks before
his death uh that's anyway he died March 2015 at age 47 this movie wasn't released until 2017 so this
is the one movie this guy ever did yeah and and he didn't even get to see the release of it uh I got
to say for a guy that never made a movie it's pretty well made uh it was well reviewed on rotten tomatoes
uh it's got some flaws it stars uh pet um what's his name uh Sean Patrick Flannery uh Michael
Berryman plays like a ghoul in it the guy from the Hills have eyes yeah uh dynamite dynamire
uh from that's the guy with like the weird eyes and everything right yeah
anybody got a script and was like oh I wonder if I'm gonna play a business man or uh
the romantic lead and then it gets to him and he's like jack comma freak comma every time
it's gotta be gotta be painful uh I've met him and hung out with him and he's very nice he wanted to
do stand there he was really sweet um but yeah I hear you after a while he's like yeah let me gas
yeah the guy in it eats his own snot yeah um I mean I'll be there but but the real star of the show
here is Frederick Kohler who used to be on the Kate Natalie sitcom uh he was in Oz he's in all of the
death race movies uh he he's become just you know not just but he's become a character actor
he was a child starts turn character actor but um he is fucking amazing in this movie he plays a kid
with uh that has suffered severe brain damage and kid he pieced in his thirties in the movie or
to her forties even um who suffered severe brain damage and is very you know mentally challenged
uh and and uh not crippled but but you know his body is very affected by his mental state
and then it's the the basic premise of the movie is his brother who is cared for him his whole life puts
this mirror in his room uh because he's trying to dress the room up and the the brain damage kid
starts seeing a reflection of himself unaffected in the mirror who's quite sinister so this kid is
playing both parts and they do scenes where you can tell from the way it's shot in the way the camera moves
that he's literally going in and out of the parts in the same
he's having the conversation in real time uh he's fucking amazing in it man um it's a pretty freaky movie
uh as you can imagine it's kind of the thing where the uh well his sinister reflection starts
directing him to do things that are pretty heinous and he starts to do them
and then in those moments is when the kid really shines because it's like
they they they he'll kill murder somebody and then like he'll come back and he'll be crying like
you promised me it would hurt would be okay it's not okay and then the image is like
you know pulling the puppet strings and being you know whatever you you get what I'm saying I'm not
I'm not I'm not explaining it very well but uh you get the point uh it's an okay movie I'd say it's
worth a watch um you may love it I don't think you'll hate it uh but uh it was solid I thought it
was solid and I think it's a shame this guy died because I feel like he had more in him
shutter picture no I saw it on um it's only Amazon Prime or something okay yeah it wasn't even
shutter it was on um I should of course now it's not there anymore where is it come on I think it's
on prime yeah prime video um it's a decent film there you go I at long last watched Glee
oh Jesus I had seen Jersey Gureal but never Glee well um can I just interject with the fact that
fucking Jersey girl gets left off of that Glee list is it it pisses me off on behalf of Glee like
Jersey girl is a fucking travesty it's a travesty and Kevin Smith is always like I mean I always knew
at least I was gonna be the worst uh picture with uh I'm like no you work up there uh written and
directed by Martin Brastett ended his career this man had nothing but huge hits and Glee was so bad
it just immediately ended his career he went from his first movie that he wrote and directed going
in style with his old guys George Burns and all them and he did Beverly Hills cop heard of it
the original made like 300 million dollars and he did midnight run arguably the perfect blend
of action and comedy definitive then he did sent him a woman which doesn't hold up but was a massive
critical and commercial success and came meet Joe black which I despised but which did okay
and then Glee and he was out that's how quickly they can turn their backs on you they were like no dude
no you're you've missed a boat um and you get why you watch it and you're like it couldn't be that bad
that it could end this guy's juggernaut career yeah it is um just to read you little synopsis here
Glee who has been aflux he's playing a standard gangster but not playing it up to comedic effect he's
just a guy Glee ordered to kidnap the challenged younger brother of a powerful federal prosecutor
what they mean there is it's Justin Bartha the least interesting character from the hangover the one
who goes missing playing as if he's decapario in what's eating gobert grape a mentally handicapped
godly um and he's along for the hijinks and the adventures um he wants the kidnap him keeps wanting to
be taken to the bay watch which he means like the beach he's obsessed with bay watch and he likes
watching bay watch joe because it makes his penis sneeze and he comes in his pants at various points
in the movie i mean this sounds like a romp oh so far when plans go awry glee's boss sends in rickey a
gorgeous free spirited female gangster we read that again
rickey a gorgeous free spirited female gangster who has her own set of orders to assist with the
kidnapping but glee begins falling for the decidedly unavailable rickey why is she unavailable because
she's a lesbian but by the end of the film Ben Affleck has turned her much as he did in chasing Amy
because he is so charming um and at a certain point she opens her legs to him and says it's turkey time
gobble gobble um all of these things happen these are not things i'm making up there is
one scene with Christopher walk him where he plays it weird certainly but nothing like out of the norm
for him then he says the final three lines of the scene in the most outrageously almost hurtful gay voice
you've ever heard and you're like did he do one take gay and the rest straight and they mix the
takes up why was his character suddenly gay at the end of this scene and why was he
Paul Lynn's level gay oh boy i gotta see this thing um it's all building to an encounter with
Al Pacino yes he's in a completely different movie he does a 10 minute monologue while Ben Affleck
and jaylo just look at him they don't hardly speak uh it seems like he's making up all of his dialogue
the movie's insane martin breast said the studio took it away from him and recut it the fact that you
would do that to the guy who directed Beverly Hills cop and midnight run is insane but he said
and i believe him he had written a more serious gangster movie now look it's still probably
wouldn't have worked but the studio said Ben Affleck and jaylo started dating so we want this to be a
rom -com and he goes well it's not a comedy and there's not romance in it she's a lesbian there's not
romance and they were like make it a rom -com baby and do it fast and it led to honestly one of the
strangest movies i've ever seen in my life yeah i remember the the only scene i've ever seen is the
Pacino scene i feel like i'm floating yeah yeah it's i mean look you can probably much like with
a Nicholas cage wicker man which i do think has its charms i'm sure you can find a supercut of the
funniest uh most ridiculous moments of gilly and save yourself two hours you don't need to watch
the thing but there are moments in it that you're just kind of like well i guess i'm glad i checked
that off you know i'm glad i kind of like tiptoes which i did watch with gary oldman as a little person
it's just kind of nice to check something like that off say i've seen it you know i've been there
oh boy all right well all right gilly uh my final installment uh the best of the three movies i watched
uh still not a movie i loved but the best of the three and i would argue
i would argue probably the final and i'm a huge fan of this man so i'm not knocking him
but i would argue probably the final quality uh john waters movie serial mom loves uh i feel like
john waters i love him so much and i felt that big production budgets never did him any favors
uh and although hairspray is a wonderful movie and crybaby is is is passable enough i don't love it but
i just felt like once he crossed over into that mainstream thing he was never quite able to come back
from it and i don't know that he wanted to he said in interviews like he'll be like
the big people are like do you miss shooting the old movie mess it we froze our balls off and
baltimore and red assembler shooting those things like i think he probably enjoyed having money
and cushiony circumstances or more cushiony at least but uh serial mom i remember when he did it
and it came out i remember an interview with him where he said i'm back in our rated territory where
i belong because crybaby and hairspray were not and this movie has the watersy thing you know
to it uh it's still very polished but it's distasteful in the in the right ways um it's it's
gaudy in the right ways it's it's very funny at times um and it's got a bit of a social commentary to it
which which even a john waters craziest movies i feel like there is a commentary in there so
i like it Kathleen Turner's awesome in it the last time i were i mean maybe i'm wrong it's the
last time i remember seeing her star in something uh and she's acted since but i don't remember her
starring in something um sam waterson's great uh ricky lakes great was fun seeing her in there
Matthew Lillard's a lot of fun in it it's a fun movie uh mink stalls in it uh you know it's very fun
uh it's obvious what it's about it's about a mother who's a serial killer uh but she kills in order
she goes into a rage uh in order to protect her family uh while trying to remain like a Donna
Reed type on the surface um like i said i i enjoyed it it's not amazing i would watch it again i don't
know that i would own it um but it is to me the last really solid john waters movie pecker's pecker's
fine uh it's not bad Cecil be demented to me is not good no and i tried a few times now to watch a
dirty shame and i just can't i can't get into it like i don't yeah i don't love any of those
i don't love any of those to be honest i criteria and kind of goes up to hairspray and stops and
it's kind of where i go to i don't i'm not a big fan of johnny noxville starring in a movie i just
they've never cared i never loved it you know how outside of jackass now right yeah i mean like a scripted
you know i just i don't know it's distracting to me i can't the one i kind of did enjoy at
least at the time was the ringer where he's like working for the special Olympics um i remember one
major laugh twenty twenty five years later and the rest of it was kind of funny right
well speaking of laughs and comedies our movie today
Beverly Hills Cop Axel F Eddie Murphy's return to true Eddie Murphy style r -rated comedy
everybody said dolomite was his return dolomite was amazing and a very wonderful movie
but it wasn't Eddie's return to being Eddie Eddie had made r -rated movies and Eddie had said
curse words on screen yeah but Eddie had not made an Eddie Murphy comedy uh that was r -rated
in a long long long time and it was so good seeing him back being Eddie Murphy again i really enjoyed it
yeah dolomite was sort of you know like dreamgirls him attempting a more serious and indie something
he's not doing for the money kind of project but truthfully that's not where Eddie's heart is and
it's not where it ever has been since his 80s heyday he's a guy who generally um follows the money
to a to a problematic degree at times you're like i mean that the period where it was like metro and uh
you know just ever meet Dave and Beverly Hills cop three yeah Beverly Hills cop three it was just like a
run a holy man i remember being like maybe i'm done with this guy doctor do a little etc and um
just not not clear what he was doing and this is the old return to the classics um but
even though i did enjoy the trailer as we discussed on the show my guard was way way up and i think
it was so far up just because of coming to america because coming to america uh forgot was
to me and analyze that level of of awful in terms of like sequels it was like on hurt of off the charts
bad and Eddie was out making the press tours saying how great and how funny it was and what a return to
form it was so there was concern but i got to see this theatrically and that's honestly my big
is note on the thing is how do you not put this in theaters for July 4th weekend yeah it's a shame
i saw it at the fucking writers guild theater the most reserved kind of nerdy theater in town
and people were clapping and cheering and laughing and when they'd see a character they remembered
everybody's like you know there's a lot of fun so i do if your town is showing it um try to get
to see it on the big screen but it's the closest we've come to one of those summer blockbusters we all
love 20 years ago in ages it's really well done way better than the new bad boys and way better than
pretty much all these reboots and especially for this being such a late reboot it's almost
incredibly successful in every way i would say yeah i agree uh in watching it it felt like i was
it felt aesthetically the movie reminds me of Beverly Hills cop 2 it feels and looks like Beverly Hills
cop 2 but it is much funnier than Beverly Hills cop 2 so i so as soon as i started watching it i was
like i remember renting Beverly Hills cop 2 as a kid and this is how i felt when i was watching it like
this feels like a big important popcorn movie to me and i was you know in the beginning it's funny
something that off put me in the beginning of the movie i realized was one of its strengths later
and there's an opening sequence where he he's doing a bus at a hockey rink it's the big action set
piece to start the movie off it's got nothing to do with the overall plot but that sequence
it's a big fun sequence but they're playing every major hop song that was made famous because of
Beverly Hills cop movies the neutron dance yeah and like the heat is on everything they're hitting all
of them and i i was watching it and i was like god they're really like blowing this this nostalgia load
right off the bat like what are they doing and then i realized like oh they're resetting everything
they're getting you excited that he's back and because then from that point on when that sequence is
any music they play if it's not the actual f theme song it's a new song and it's the new story
and whatever and i was like that was really really really smart that was a really good way it's
almost like a cold opening to a ghost busters movie where all this stuff's going to happen and then
the ghost busters music kicks in and you're like okay this is ghost busters cool um that thing
so that's a really good comparison i'd say that first ghost busters back not the latest one but
that first one back felt like this to me one where you're introducing new elements seamlessly they're
working comedies there the actions there uh not a lot of complaints i've seen kind of mixed reviews
on it but i think most people are are loving it it's just super entertaining the one criticism i've
seen and it's been repeated some people are really hard on it are saying this is just an nostalgia grab
and it doesn't need to exist i didn't think it was an nostalgia grab i thought it was its own thing
yeah i thought it hit the notes it needed to to have common thread with the character whatever
there were some lines that were like callbacks and stuff but who cares like i thought like
it wasn't it wasn't three older men slash old men in a car saving the day
right it wasn't that at all they had they very very appropriately used ashton
grindhold and murphy in three different positions in the movie that all made perfect sense
you don't have a doubt in your mind that eddie murphy is able to do the things he's doing in the movie
john ashton is riding a desk is the chief of police it makes total sense and
ryanhold gets kidnapped and has enough in him to to to to to to to during the last hurrah to play to play
pull it back together yeah like it's eddie murphy and these guys are the same age and they like
when you and i were talking joe he's got that thing with paul riser where he's like we're the same age how
look this much better than you but he does and he's in better shape and he's taken way better
care of himself and etc etc so when he's in the action you're like awesome but he lets the vulnerability
in that movie ends with him walking around like he's 80 years old you know yeah um but yeah these other
guys you know john ashton came out of actual film acting retirement to do the movie and he's got an
amazing hero moment he gets to say cock sucker which i thought was a word that had been scrubbed from
the american cinema um and his character is super funny and lovable he gets big laughs i totally see
why he came back if they wrote him some one -off stupid fucking scene he'd probably be like i'm staying
in bed they gave him really funny character specific shit to do i love same with ryanhold but
as you're saying joe we'd never buy the these three men running side by side through the streets
no they handled them and they met them at their level of fitness in a very smart well done way
and murphy i'm just looking at their ages murphy is the youngest he's 63 ryanhold 67
and uh ashton's 80 uh oh wow he's 85 i just hear it for president
john ashton is 80 no i'm sorry 76 okay so uh so i love that ashton's character i love that he
i mean that they like classic cop movie shit he complains about his wife
yeah the scene where he's on the that that old school exercise like ski machine and he's drinking beer
as he's doing the exercise and he's like what exercise you know yeah
all that was great i love that like the last after everything wraps up in the movie ends there's
that little button scene where they're sitting in the car and it's the mirror scene it's the mirror
imagery of the of the scene in the first movie when there's something the car and that's the scene
in the first movie when any murphy jumps in the car and scares them right and then this one he slides
in going like uh uh because he's been shot and he's healing yeah i love that they did a play on it
where it was like now they're old and that's kind of what's funny and he's just saying like can we
just please go get some food i'm hungry and um but the most important i love Gordon levit i love the
daughter i did too there's a little a very slight side romance between levit and tailor page from
zola who plays any murphy's daughter she's great a minute i love her their little side romance is
believable it's cute it's funny um and the heart of the movie aside from all the sentimentality which
is very well done uh and our you know memories of the other movies is eddie and his daughter and that
is very well done the heart of the movie a it doesn't feel tacked on and b it's kind of moving like
she calls him out for being absent not present in her life an asshole self absorbed and he was like
that character that super like you know fast -talking i'm the coolest guy in the room
character as much as we love watching him and rooting for him they wisely realized that guy would not
be a good dad so he's kind of dealing with not having been there for his daughter in a way that feels
real and earned it feels kind of you know dramatic but also funny and adds a lot to the movie um i got to
shout out my buddy kevin etten who is one of the three writers on this movie um but i think you know
that's where it really shines it's got a really good script they bring back branson pincho that
was in the light seeing pinch up pinchos in real estate now of course he is how great it was in the side
kick uh in the scene padrod they both are really funny yeah if he and if he on crocket who's a guy i
don't necessarily think is is a scream had a real funny uh one -off scene with eddie like the scene
where they go in to the guy who's uh an aspiring actor and he was in jupiter ascending you know that's
a super funny moment eddie murphy is actually in jupiter ascending right is that okay that guy was great
is afian who'd you say afian what does his name afian crocket he's the valet guy that eddie riffs
with for a while that was very funny luiz guzman playing a truly frightening yeah spanic gangster
uh was awesome uh uh and singing the spanish version of man -eater was very funny uh and so odd it
was so weird like that bar they were in and it was it was great it felt like grite grite grite grite li
but you know most importantly above all of these things
eddie murphy is so funny in it it's just like does the movie have it oh christ we forgot bacon
bacon shining as bacon does as a piece of shit yeah bacon you know i from from having seen nothing
of it i was like he's gonna be a dirty cop obviously but they sort of played me they were like not
only as he a dirty cop and your guess is correct we're not even gonna do any sort of bait and switch
he's gonna be an asshole from the moment you see him you know he's doing dirty you know um because who
cares the plot of this thing is not really super relevant much like you probably couldn't remember
the plot of one two or three but um it's got enough of that kind of 80s cop crime backdrop uh and it's
just really funny and likable i'd put it i'd probably go having not seen two in ages i would probably go
one three two no sorry one four two three yes now three got i mean sorry three excuse me three was
obviously panned everybody knows that and a nice little wink joke to how bad it was yes like
when he goes oh boy you think you know so things really went wrong here in 94 you know that's the kind
of wink i like a little yeah not yeah he goes he goes you were here in eighty three you were back
again in eighty seven yeah you came back in 93 not your finest hour right right right but it's in
reference to the to the report and i like that they didn't do the lazy we're just ignoring it he even
says when he sees taggered he's like i thought you were tired ashton's not in part three because he had
they're recognizing no there was a part three and it sucks and whatever um i really i really was
overjoyed seeing pincho and and and and and seeing pincho be funny i was like i didn't know
but uh but god man uh back to uh yeah there was just there's just so many great jokes at it it's not
a perfect movie it's got it's got it's got you know it's got some hiccups but uh it's a really
wonderful movie and i i can't believe it i wanted to watch it again almost immediately after
i saw it i was like i want to watch that again man i even felt like that about a move i was like
finally a fucking legacy sequel that delivers yeah you know like i was like it delivered it was what
i wanted it to be and it was clearly influenced by the movies it spawned there would be no bad boys
without Beverly Hills cop right but they obviously took a nod from bad boys and said let's go bigger
with the action and all that stuff but make it really funny yeah it's uh you know there's no set
formula for how to make these work but like it honored what you love it nods to what you love
doesn't get completely bogged down in it it adds some new elements they make sure those elements
work very well brings back what you want in ways that feel believable everybody's still in Beverly Hills
brought some pin shows character as a realtor totally buy it you know it's just simply
making sure we believe each little thing uh makes all the difference like i think it's
like Joe said it lags here and there the story's not a plus um i thought that kind of hockey
stuff at the beginning was a little awkward i thought we were maybe not gonna get the best
uh re -up of this franchise but i was dead wrong it's super entertaining i loved it
uh my hog is up for Beverly Hills cop my hog is also up busting shots in the air
we uh for our next one we'll be doing stop motion a new film on shutter uh where reality and the art
world blur uh heard it compared to puppet master yes looking forward to that uh we'll be doing long
legs which comes out soon i'm very pumped about long legs and then probably fall guy probably uh waiting
for that to peacock drop uh all right folks uh thanks for listening uh i'll see you uh in September at
the uh old special taping and uh in the meantime i'm writing on uh tires and and lay in kind of low
and just doing that thing but if you're new york hit up joey roses if you will and we added two warm -up
shows actually hold on let me see the dates on these things uh if you wanted to come to the special
but couldn't get tickets uh we have September 10th and the 12th Tuesday and Thursday 7 30 pm on
Tuesday 7 30 pm on Thursday uh i am doing two warm -up shows for the special that shoots that Saturday
at steel city coffee house in brewery uh in Phoenixville, Pennsylvania on bridge street uh these are also
small shows about 75 seats so uh come on down and uh i'll see you there that's it for me he'll see you
and we'll see you next time love you all have a good one