I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, and when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say, I'll see you in hell, you know I will, I'll see you in hell, you know I will.
Folks, welcome to We'll See You in Hell. It's the first episode of the new year. What year is it? 2029, I believe, is it?
You're getting ahead of yourself. It's 2025. You're imagining this fictional Ray Bradbury world where we still exist in 2029, Joe.
Yes.
But I have my doubts.
I am looking out my front door right now. Doot, doot, doot, looking out my front door.
It is the T2 lighting. My little porch is bathed in orange apocalypse lighting.
Yeah.
I keep myself out of the news, which is very healthy for me. I don't really pay attention to politics much anymore.
I know that's a privilege I have, ladies and gentlemen, but I don't.
And I've noticed that I also miss then major things that are happening in my backyard.
Like there are major fires destroying Malibu. I have heard the PCH has been destroyed entirely.
Oh, the Pacific Coast Highway.
The Pacific Coast Highway, like the most beautiful, one of the most famous stretches of road in America.
It's bad. My friends are evacuating Pasadena and I'm like texting them like, oh my God, be careful.
And then I set my phone down and I'm like, Pat, you live 15 minutes from Pasadena.
Like you might want to start getting a little concerned.
Are you worried about the smoke leaking in the door behind you right now?
No, that's the, that's either the mist or the fog, one of the two.
And as we know from the movies, those are always pretty innocent. So I'm not worried.
Yeah. Oh, just Dracula.
Just Dracula.
No, I've had nothing.
Fire wise today, I went to the gym and it was like breathing in ash and death.
So that was bad, but the wind has been insane.
It tipped over a lot of stuff outside and it blew open my back door in the middle of the night, setting off the house alarm.
So that was very terrifying this week to be awoken to your house being like, it was horrifying.
Horrifying.
Uh, and then I realized that.
I have no game plan for if somebody breaks into my house.
Cause what did I do?
I sprinted upstairs with no weapon.
Yeah.
I'd get a gun and then not learn how to use it.
So you accidentally shoot yourself in the foot or something like that.
You know, that always happens to people when they don't train.
But yeah, I don't, I think about that all the time.
I keep a large knife, uh, under my bed in Pennsylvania, like a, like a Rambo style knife.
You got to write a novella that starts, I keep a large knife under my bed in Pennsylvania, but here in Austin, uh, that's what, by the way, if there's an echoey boom or whatever, reverb, whatever you call it, um, I apologize.
I'm just, I, my apartment is, is, is it's concrete and steel here.
It's, it's just an echoey kind of room.
Um, you made this into like a podcasting studio.
It looks like you're, you're giving us a.
A testimonial on like a real world where you're like, yeah, so I hooked up with Janice.
Um, I didn't expect it.
No, I'm sitting when you walk into the condo, I have here to your immediate right in the, there's, you know, there's the entryway area, vestibule, whatever you call it.
And to your immediate right is a built -in desk to the wall.
Kind of like the one you have in your kitchen area.
Yeah.
Um, but it's a sort of a narrow area.
So I'm just, I'm, I'm like two feet from the wall that I'm sitting in front of right now.
So it's enough to, it's enough to have a desk area, but it's not really that sightly for podcasting.
So I'm going to put some lights in and, and hang something behind me.
So it looks like something, I don't know, you know,
yeah, there's an interrogation vibe.
Now you're the only one I do, you know, zoom and then, and then we don't even show anybody what it looks like.
So I guess it doesn't really matter, but.
No, it doesn't matter to me.
It doesn't matter anymore.
Um, well, I'm glad, I'm glad you're safe.
I'm supposed to go to San Diego in two weeks.
Oh, nice.
It shows, but San Diego is losing power.
And yeah, my, I've been very, very lucky.
There's been no power outage, no nothing, but I've definitely got friends struggling.
I've got people who've lost their houses that I know and stuff happens fast.
It's very scary.
It's terrible.
Um,
also terrible.
I wanted to give a quick shout out at the top of the show to my friend, Jeff Baina, who passed away this week.
Um, very, very sad.
He was, you know, he's being reported in the press as being the husband of Aubrey Plaza, which he was,
but that's not really how I knew him or met him at all.
I played poker with him for many, many years, uh, including very early years when I came to Los Angeles.
And he was just one of the coolest and most welcoming and kind dudes.
And I played poker and continue to play poker with these guys who are like bad for the self -esteem.
You know, it's like, it's probably much like hanging out with comedians.
You hang out with certain types of comedy writers, the ball breaking.
I can't handle it.
I think cause I was bullied.
It just doesn't, it, it doesn't bounce off me like it does some people.
And he always just hosted these poker nights and just, I think he picked up on me being,
being uncomfortable at times and was always just, you know, it's stuff that sadly you only think about in hindsight,
but he was a very kind, very good person.
And if you want to watch his entire filmography, you could do it in pretty much a day.
Um, he co -wrote I heart Huckabees with David O.
Russell.
Oh, that's cool.
He had some insane stories about that experience, of course, working with David O.
Russell.
And that's how he got his start.
And from there, he's been a great guy.
And from there, he made a lot of really great, genuinely independent films with his comedian
friends, largely improvisational.
He was a huge movie buff, a huge music buff.
I love talking about those things with him and his movies are as follows life after Beth,
which is great with John C.
Riley and Aubrey, uh, Joshie with middle ditch and a bunch of other great comics.
The little hours is maybe my favorite of his.
It is about nuns and kind of a parody of the decay.
The movie is called Amaran, very strange, very dry, very, very funny.
I haven't seen horse girl.
That's in my Netflix queue now.
And spin me round is definitely Jeff's funniest movie.
I thought that was really, really funny.
It came out in 2022 and it's on Hulu.
Um, anyway, just had to say that he's a great guy and obviously there's a, there's a big
tie to film.
Um, and if you like truly independent, weird offbeat movies that never do what you expect
them to do, watch the movie.
watch any one of jeff's movies he was a great guy and a really interesting filmmaker oh well
that's i'm sorry for your loss i um well thanks yeah i i lost a friend as well college friend
his name was michael hill very good man uh sorry you know um i'm not really quite sure what the
circumstances are but um you know they're not good uh obviously but yeah uh yeah so i'm suddenly on
this thread on my phone with all these guys that i hung out with in college that some of which i've
stayed in somewhat touch with and some i haven't talked to almost literally since college so
god almighty that was over 20 years ago
um but uh yeah very sad man very very sad set of circumstances uh this time of life is
is i don't
mean to get the new year off on the wrong foot here but it's you know it's a tough time of life
that you know you get into your mid to late 40s and you know the the losses become uh fewer and
further uh between and and and much more apparent and you know it's uh it's it's a very telling time
of life uh it is yeah stuff just hits harder and you know everything feels more permanent i think
you're building up a lifetime of regrets you know it's where everything it's rough life is tough
um you know jeff it was reported that jeff committed suicide so i can say that and if you
if you were struggling there's always a place to go that you know all i've done the last several
days is talk to friends who were like what the hell he was the best he seemed to have a shit
together he seemed to be the best dude and you just never know so i'm not going to talk to him
check on your friends ask for help if you need it um we all get depressed we all get very down
that's never the answer there's always something better on the other side for sure
all right um okay let's
and then changing gears entirely of course we are talking today about when harry met sally by the
way a little when pat met joe we're talking about a light romantic comedy and and
you know i think it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's
one of the great new year's movies i actually looked up new year's movies and you got new
year's eve the the gary marshall you got um somebody said ghostbusters 2 which i re -watched
and which barely counts i would say and you got the apartment billy wilder movie which is excellent
but there's weirdly not a lot of new year's eve movies this one uh well this yeah this is a great
new year's eve movie it also
this is this is a holiday one man this ticks every box because there's a christmas sequence
and i think is there a thanksgiving in when i feel like there must be but certainly autumnal
vibes yeah yeah at the very least walks through central park browns and oranges and the hues
of all the movies that make me miss new york city and there are several which i've talked about but
this one is
you know top tier uh this this movie really makes life in new york
appear to be very very beautiful and uh and brilliant uh you know especially around the
holidays so um we'll get to it we'll get to it we'll get to it what's new in the world of
le chini maha um i just watched the golden globe awards or i was in and out of them i hadn't seen
an award show in a while and i was like oh my god i'm gonna be in the world of le chini maha
but i was like you know what what the hell it was uh fairly boring i thought nikki did a good job
as host she was funny i thought the jokes were good i thought they kept it moving pretty well
the winners were pretty baffling overall and i guess i'll get to that in the movie corner
but it's a weird time for the movies you know you just feel like we're not
we're not sending our best as as trumpets
um i uh i think um uh i didn't i didn't tune in i i i feel more out of touch
than i i i almost ever have uh with with entertainment and whatever
you know and i'm also down here in um in austin uh you know so far for the duration of the new year
and uh and i'll be back in a minute
i'll be down here most of the winter i think but you know this is also down here sort of the land
of independent uh booming podcasting and and there's so much here operating outside of the
normal system i feel very very out of touch with what's happening in the world of regular
regularly produced entertainment um you know there's not much coming out that i'm excited about
and uh you know the business certainly hasn't
uh made us or others feel very welcome lately so it's just kind of like you know i don't know
i you know it's weird to me that the golden globes even exists anymore you know it really
is and they're so out of touch with what people watch or enjoy that it's it's kind of insane
um yeah they're they're trying to overcorrect their their previous negative racist reputation
so they're trying to overcorrect and it's all just a damn mess it's weird um yeah these are
award shows are starting to play like government entertainment yeah yeah like you know where you
watch a dystopian thing and and all the the federal government produces all of the entertainment
you're allowed to watch and it's so saccharine and weird and yeah and off you know they were
coming out and walking up so that they were like nose to nose with the camera only i think
seth rogan commented on it but it was so awkward i was like who looked at this shot and said this
was okay
to send out and everything you're right has that weird like i'd include red one in this i i'd
include old navy commercials in this it's this like not real third dimension that we've all
agreed is what the other dimension looks like but i don't like it at all well in the in the uh
you know very very applicable or or appropriate for the discussion about new entertainment
that people may not care at all about but i was sort of excited the we never talked about it the
superman trailer uh yeah we we keep forgetting to discuss it um you know look i i don't know
did we talk about this we neither of us had watched it okay um i think it looks solid
i like that he's sparing us of another origin story yeah um it's it's been kind of hateful
right well it's there was one there was a story that said you know hearsay is the initial response
is negative and then another story came out and it said hearsay is the initial response is it's
as good as guardians of the galaxy okay james gunn does it again kind of thing who the fuck knows
what's true with any of it you know who knows i don't know
i mean it's it's
you know so it's um
i don't know it look the movie look it looks solid you know um and and it's going to be
surrounded by so much uh you know uh conjecture and and and smoke and and and chatter and
whatever else and i don't know if any of it is real or fake anymore that these hype machines
they create around these these big blockbuster movies anymore um you know the the i guess a
good example what i'm talking about is is why i'm so skeptic and believing anything i hear
you know this hype machine that disney kind of created it's real if you watch a lot of the
youtubers particularly in the star wars realm i mean disney is as they say bending the knee all
of a sudden and like you know they were they were leading the charge of saying that everybody that
didn't like anything star wars was a racist or a sexist or both now disney is getting rid of all
the woke star wars stuff they did and completely backpedaling on all of that which when when they
first started doing it
the initial response from fans was nobody is saying this there's like 10 awful people on
the internet that said anything the rest of us just think it sucks and then they started to do
the thing where before the show even got released they would start the pre -attack on fans like
saying it's about to come out and if you don't like it then you're sexist or racist right yeah
and all of it kind of turned out to be a bunch of bullshit it was just a way to create
noise uh you know
around the product itself and to kind of throw up a shield from any bad reviews which is another
thing that's happening right now you know this thing i won't name names but there's a thing
happening now where comedians for instance when their special comes out in the special they'll go
after another big comedian and then all the reviews about the special aren't reviews of
the special it's just people talking about how they took a shot at the big comedian yeah and
it's very strategic like that's a thing you do to kind of get the talk off of the product itself
so when i hear stories about superman and people are saying i hear it sucks or i hear it's great
i'm like i don't even know if that's real i feel like it's an ai bot just saying a thing that they
flood out there now so people just talk about that yeah and it gets the conversation going in
in the coffee shop or wherever
but with all that in mind it looks like a solid superman movie from the trailer
and and i will say the true comic book fans i am friends with seem very excited about it um
and and they're they're people that haven't been excited for a while with what the product has been
in the i was unaware superman ever had a dog so i'm clearly not the fan base i thought it
looked a little hokey a little goofy but it's superman i find him to always be that i find the
to be to appear to be pretty lacking in charisma but i haven't seen much of his performance and i
guess you could say the same about brandon routh but then again we never heard from him again
either i will uh i'll see it i guess i'll say this um they did a very good job finally of making
clark kent not look like superman yeah um like when you see them side by side you're like yeah
i could probably fall for this guy
not being the same person that was cool it seems like they're bringing fun and like the sort of
kid spirit back into superman which was gone with the zack snyder stuff zack snyder was a very dark
take which is fine but this seems like with crypto and whatever and the look of the suit
it seems like they're really trying to get back to like it's superman guys you know it's supposed
to be innocent and sweet and whatever yeah
uh and then also too they're jumping right in with the justice league uh there's tons of justice
league cameos in the trailer and it's a it's not the typical justice league it's not like wonder
woman and you know the first green lantern and and the flash or whatever it's it's it's all
different you know a little lesser in the mainstream sense lesser known heroes so
it seems like it's gonna be kind of cool and i like that james gunn came out and said
we have one hard and fast rule here at um at dc the script has to be ready we will not green light
it until the script is ready because people were like why is your second movie supergirl and your
third movie clay face like why not yeah you know jump in with legacy characters you know like batman
or wonder woman and he said because if the script is ready we move forward and if it's not we don't
and those scripts were great and we're moving forward and we're moving forward and we're moving
forward so i think that's fucking good news to hear if it's true you know yeah so i don't know
we'll see what happens but uh i'm just glad we're getting more superhero pictures
it's about it's about damn time as the great lizzo once sang um joe sent me an article from
movie web that said wolfman director is already prepared for audiences to hate his werewolf
and i'm starting to realize i think that picture of the little like you know almost leprechaun in
the hood style wolfman that you sent me a year ago is going to be the wolfman yeah and i saw
they didn't pat they never said it wasn't like when it hit yeah no i know nobody came out and
said nobody denied it and i saw kind of the final trailer because this thing's just about to hit
theaters but i went and saw the new uh
seven remastered and they showed this trailer and you just felt the entire audience look at
each other in unison like this doesn't look good no we've all been kind of pretending this might
be good but like we're getting down to the wire here there's nothing there's nothing here this
is gonna suck they have taken the most gothic spectacular
set piece
uh you know uh uh what is that called what's the word um for a big a big visual
uh spectacle spectacle spectacle driven horror movies that were ever created yeah and they're
now remaking all of them with micro budgets and two people in the cast a horror this is what's
killing me these horror movies where they're like what if it was only three people and they're like
oh so then nobody's gonna die or maybe one person yeah it's like what are we doing i mean this looks
exactly like what was that first a24 one it it's something something it follows no with edgerton it
comes at night it comes at night hey so do i i didn't make a movie about it folks um it comes at
night is exactly the wolfman i just recently watched it comes at night i thought it was fine
but it looks like a movie that they made because they had fifty thousand dollars you know and three
people and a weekend like this guy's coming off the huge success of the invisible man why is he
why did they cut his budget in half for the wolf man it doesn't make any sense well you know it's
i we we've differed quite a bit on the invisible man um but for this
one of my dislikes was this same thing it felt like far too small of a story to me
yeah um now i know the original invisible man isn't some sort of epic tale but
it feels fablesque it feels shakespearean it feels large in spirit and you're talking about
the chevy chase the chevy chase of course the best of the lot
um but you know man it's it's just it's just when to me when you take that
and you boil it down to um it's it's going to be really focused on two people
yeah and their personal relationship and the struggle of this woman as a result of the monster
himself it's just it's not i don't know it's just not big enough to me it's not interesting
i you know theoretically i get the point i get i get what you're doing and it's an interesting take
you know these things would be cool if they were true independent releases which which don't exist
anymore in hollywood but my point is is if they weren't if they didn't have the universal stamp
on them and you could say well blumhouse it's interesting man they they do these movies that
are like it's almost like a take on the universe and they're like they're like they're like they're
original invisible man but then it's it's a lot smaller and more about the you know people and
blah blah blah and it's not but that's not what it is it's a remake of the fucking invisible man
this one they're not even calling it the wolf man it's just called wolf man because i this has
nothing we've talked about this has nothing to do with the original movie yeah nothing it's like
you don't need a copyright to do a werewolf movie just do a goddamn werewolf
call this something else why are you calling this why are you tying this to the lon chaney
junior classic i mean it makes no sense and i could give a shit at this point i could give a
shit about a terrorized wife and kids trapped in the house with the thing outside it's like
i've seen it a million fucking times guys the movie does look a lot like kujo like it looks
a lot like kujo and way less interesting yeah
way less interesting than kujo way less interesting than other movies i didn't like that
much but i mean it's it's it's a quiet place yeah it's kujo uh as i said i've seen it a million
times now i can't think of anything but you know what i mean we've just seen this over and over and
over again oh my god it's so boring um but but interestingly enough that thing you said where
he came out and said he the thing i sent you he's prepared for people to hate it that's exactly what
i'm talking about they're at a point with these things where they get out in front of it yeah and
say we know you're gonna say it sucks and it's like because you know it sucks right and now
you're gonna blame us like we didn't get your vision your vision sucks i don't know what to
tell you i don't know watch him surprise us maybe it'll be awesome who knows maybe it'll be awesome
it doesn't look awesome i gotta say i gotta say no
and i will say i still think of that throat slitting moment in the invisible man as one of
my favorite horror moments of the last 10 years easy that uh just a collective gasp from the
audience that's what i go to the movies for baby yes and i like the movie itself uh and i thought
it did its thing without being too preachy quite frankly but we'll see i like one now i usually
like his work joe should we go to the corner yeah
i think so let's do it let's do it um well let's jump right into it i saw the brutalist
okay the brutalist folks is 215 minutes long
um that's uh somewhere between the trace and the quattro uh but it's closer to the the 345 mark i
believe there's an intermish which i appreciated and i think it was i know it was the first
theatrical intermission i have experienced outside of going to see like lawrence of arabia or some
old movie um the only one i can remember in my lifetime prior to that had been dances with wolves
which came out in like 90 and beat goodfellas for best picture so it's a long fucking movie
um use the intermission get up walk around do something and then you're done
because you know it's it's fucking long and it doesn't need to be and i saw this guy he won best
director at the golden globes this one best picture at the golden globes drama and he gets
up there and he's like maybe from now on we'll give the director final cut oh and then people
online yeah i mean he look i didn't hate the guy entirely he but he was very kind of smug and
you don't was you know his movie here's what's impressive about it it's an epic a true epic
with like costumes and it spans decades and blah blah blah and it was done on a very small budget
you know all things considered and it was done in like 38 days i find that insane it's very
impressive but it's like just because you shot all this footage you don't have to use it all
um the first half is way way way stronger than the second then there's an epilogue so imagine you
watch three and a half hours of a movie and then it ends and then they go epilogue i mean you can
just feel the audience groan and the epilogue is by far the worst part of the movie it's like the
end of babylon where after this three hour thing that you didn't really quite love they do this
like other stupid thing that makes you feel like you're in a movie and you're like oh my god i'm
really dislike it but all in all i admire the movie i think the first half is well worth watching
it's the classic immigrant story an immigrant comes to america um it's it's adrian brody who's
very very good as a holocaust survivor he leaves his wife and daughter comes to america he's
building a building he's an architect and he's building this giant project for guy pierce who's
believe it or not folks inspired by
donald trump and guy pierce commissions him he very quickly falls into like heroin and you know
the point of the movie because that's the thing it's like for me if i'm going to watch something
for four hours i want to step back and go here's the big message i got from this thing and this
movie is inspired by a lot of these big epics like it looks like there will be blood or it
looks like it was very inspired by the master movies like that these big epics but those movies
reward repeat viewings because they get deeper and deeper as you go the brutalist unfortunately is
not a very deep movie i keep talking to very smart people and they're like yeah i feel like i want to
see it again because i didn't get it i'm like no you're smart the movie is not that smart people
think if it's four hours it's got to be genius that's why it won best picture there's no way
anyone was passionate about the brutalist i'm sorry it's a very cold and distancing movie
the performances are pretty good um the second half really starts to drag and that's the story
i mean it's the first half hour they get adrian brody addicted to heroin so you're just watching
a guy fuck up opportunities in america and it's like okay the usa perverts the immigrant experience
the usa destroys um people when they come here um do we need that for four hours and then when
they hit you with a metaphor in the film you're like oh my god i don't know what to do with this
third act that i'm not going to spoil but you'll know it very clearly when you see it if you make
it this far into the movie you'll be i was rolling my eyes i was like this is a really obvious too
obvious movie um and it doesn't have the nuance and depth it should at this length joseph um
well i guess uh
i'm undecided on what to cover here i kind of want to stick on
the theme but i've got some older stuff that's going to fade out i'll you know what i'll go with
the with the older stuff before it gets too out of dot out of date um my theme today is uh crazy
people okay let's start with jamie fox's oh yeah didn't we talk about this already i don't think we
did all right i don't think we spoke about it play play play play play play
look man i was happy to see jamie fox back uh it's certainly a triumphant story like i didn't
nobody knows what was going on i gotta be honest with you folks i i watched the special where he
talks about it i still don't know what the hell happened to the guy i think he had a stroke i
don't know i'm not sure yeah um uh apparently he was healed by both the hospital and jesus
um there was a lot of
talk of that in the special it had some extraordinarily funny moments like when he
did do material i was laughing really hard uh but it's also peppered with a ton of him crying
and so much crying a lot of crying but i gotta tell you folks as much as i'd like to to to make
fun of that uh i mean i'm i'm in an emotional state at this point i'm crying at commercials
anything sets me off so i guess i can
get why this guy after this experience would be weeping like this in front of an audience um
you know it was it was good to see that he's back on his feet it's good to see he's doing well
and and he was very you know showcasing his talent but i must say there is an element
and again i say it without judgment to be honest i think all of us are like this since
the great
covid disaster slash experiment uh that we all went through i mean i feel like nobody's normal
anymore no so raw nerves i can't i can't knock him for that uh because i don't think i'm much
better off in any way uh but you know it it seems a bit unhinged he seems a little unhinged
um you know so it was it was an
interesting thing to watch it was a weird thing to watch because he's he's back and he managed to
keep it quiet up until the release of this netflix thing which was an impressive feat um
but uh you know given that a week after it came out he needed to get stitches because a man threw
a glass at his face in a restaurant who i think had ties to the jackass crew it's like jamie
stay home a couple weeks baby
don't go out yeah it was wild and i thought i don't know i thought i talked about it maybe i
didn't but it my favorite part was when his daughter comes out plays a three -note guitar
solo he starts sobbing and going play play play play play play play play that was one of the
most uncomfortable things i've ever witnessed as a man well i thought it was interesting that he
talked about the talent of his daughter and how beautiful was that she played guitar for him
when he was in the hospital yeah and then he wanted to bring her out to do this and how proud
he was of her and then he just talked over her playing the entire time because even he knew like
this is dead air not a lot of meat on the bone there yeah
yes baby yes so um okay well i thought if i'm gonna watch the best picture drama winner
watch the best picture musical or comedy winner and i think everyone expected that to go to
wicked just because of its huge success barbie won it whenever that was etc but instead it went
to emilia perez and then they cut to ted sarandos high -fiving the emilia perez team at their table
and you're like oh okay netflix bought this one i got it because everyone dislikes this movie um
letterboxed all my friends give it terrible reviews the critics give it pretty bad reviews
the trans and lgbtq community gives it bad reviews even though that's who it's you know
clearly supposed to be made about um it's just a wild movie and it won a lot of golden globes
zoe saldana won best actress for it um she plays a lawyer who is working for a large
law firm um trying to get criminals off and she's conflicted because they don't deserve it
and she gets hooked up with this criminal this crime boss who wants to become a woman
both because he wants to and also to escape um you know being killed so
so okay fine weird premise i'm trying to even follow what i'm watching
and then they make it a musical on top of that so the clip that i sent to joe and the clip that
i've started seeing i no surprise to me the clip's been circulating widely online now but
it's one of the earliest musical numbers in the movie and zoe saldana goes to this doctor's office
and i'm gonna i'm gonna make up the melody but i'm not too far off from what it is
she's like tell me about transsexual surgery and then he's like
man into woman penis into vagina that that's essentially what the clip is joe am i wrong
i don't i didn't see it i sent it to you i didn't watch it i'm sorry i thought that was a screenshot
oh no i wanted you to watch the clip oh oh i thought that was just you just said i thought
it was just a screenshot and it just said bangkok and i was like what is this well that's it you you
know it's the scene they get there in bangkok and she goes to see this
guy who does this and she goes to see this guy who does this and she goes to see this guy who does this
surgeries and he's like man into woman penis to vagina and you know you're 10 minutes into the
movie and you can't believe what you're seeing so you're like is this supposed to be funny but
no it's a deadly serious movie deadly serious and it is about you know the trans experience sort of
but it's also exploiting the trans experience and it's made by people who are not trans or gay or
um selena gomez is being criticized for not knowing her own language like the the you know
people are like she's you know speaking in this weird spanish accent but it's not real and she's
supposed to be playing a spanish character and so they're having all sorts of like what you might
classify as woke critiques of the movie in addition to it just not being well made and it not being
entertaining it's sort of you know i think there could be a the room style circuit that shows this
thing because of how campy and strange it is but um for it to win best picture you realize we're
just we're living in a simulation folks where ted sarandos makes a couple calls and we just
make things happen i mean nobody would say this is the best movie of any year it's a disaster but
so
fascinating one that you may want to at least watch the first 10 minutes and see that musical
number so the but the the the trans actress in it yeah she then she dresses as a man at first in
the movie and then becomes a woman well i'm hesitant to speculate because i'm not sure
there was a trans actress at the awards who went up that i assume just plays the character
yeah it says that in the in the cast list it says she plays the character as the man and the female
well there you go but it and i thought so i just didn't want to speculate because i was not sure
i'll say something now i'll own all of it so if anybody gets upset this is me talking not
not pat isn't that fucked up though to isn't isn't that the same thing as if a guy dressed as a woman
and you know there are so many complaints about this movie online from so many fans that they may
many angles that it's like oh nobody likes this thing so all right okay to see it win is really
kind of hilarious i think uh my i'm only going to do two my second one uh in my theme of crazy
people was a rewatch of a movie i've not seen since it was in the theater when it was in the
theater i hated it i just put it on one night because i thought i don't want to think right
now i just want something on the background this will do i probably won't care ended up getting
pulled into it and really enjoying it but i re -watched red direct drag excuse me jesus i
re -watched red dragon the uh ratner version the ratner one yeah yeah um i really enjoyed it man
i thought ed norton was great i thought hopkins was great of course route ray fines was great
um emily mortimer was great
is it emily mortimer yeah yeah uh great the whole cast was us frank whaley great like everybody was
great ratner directs it sort of like silence of the lambs like he he does some stylistic things
that link it to that movie so so it feels close enough that it that there feels there's a that
it's connected um you know you got to get past that it's a prequel and anthony hopkins weighs
20 pounds more than he was in the movie
and is clearly older but whatever it's that's that's an easy uh ask um
i just really liked it man i really enjoyed the movie it's got its twists its turns it's
suspenseful um i i i just enjoyed it very much uh the michael man you know manhunter
is obviously a very good film um i just never liked manhunter as much as i felt i should
because i it was this if it's it was you know it was made before silence of the lambs and then
silence of the lambs came out and made this sort of definitive hannibal lecter movie and then you
kind of anything you watch with hannibal lecter outside of that it feels a little weird you know
the tv show whatever regardless of how good any of it is so um i enjoyed this very much i think it
is definitely a better movie than hannibal oh yeah it is you know and not as good obviously
as silence of the lambs but no whatever
it was it was a fun watch i'd watch it again i enjoyed it you had a hell of a cast on that one
oh yeah um i went and i urge you to go while it's still in theaters which i believe is only
till the end of the week maybe next week too but uh they have re -released seven david fincher's
seven on 4k i got my new 4k yesterday and i'm very excited about it it's got
a
you
special features going back all the way to the laser disc edition they pulled over basically
every feature that's ever been available on the movie very um they remastered it in 8k and when
i heard 8k my heart stopped because i was like they better not start pushing 8k on us because
i will not i say now i will not but i also said that about 4k you will you don't make 8k but
it's an 8k transfer and i went and saw that in imax and god damn it was awesome i love seven
i saw it theatrically my dad said he was going to take me to one r -rated movie a month
once i hit 15 that was the first one he took me to and then he said we're not doing that anymore
um there's horrific stuff in this movie there's actually stuff that i thought was not
so severe that when i saw it on the big screen again i remembered like the lust one in particular
when he's yelling get this thing off of me i didn't realize they've got him covered up like
wearing that knife dildo machine like you can see the machine and it's very disturbing
then they show you the device and i was like oh wait he's wearing the device and this was literally
like a speculum type thing that he wore and fucked her to death it was worse than i even
imagined it when i've saw i saw the movie the previous 10 times oh boy it was like christ you
know like this movie is so depraved i took a date to it she writes crime so i thought it was a good
idea but i forgot about that stuff and man it's just such a it's it's about as bleak and
gruesome an r -rated movie as you could have i was also i watched this week true romance and seven
and i realized that brad pitt used to be a much much much better actor than he is now
i'm watching seven when he realizes that that's his wife's head in the box and that she was
pregnant i was crying again i've seen this movie more than 10 times i had tears streaming down my
face when he's putting it all together in his head and he's sick because he knows how bad he
wants to kill kevin spacey and it makes that scene even more effective now that it's kevin spacey
because he wanted to die even more and he's sitting there like oh god i'm gonna kill this
motherfucker because it killed my wife but i don't want to and morgan freeman's going he's gonna win
if you do this he's gonna win i can't believe they let them make that movie with that ending
but it's what makes it a classic
joe mentioned silence of the lambs i would say seven is right below it
i saw somebody say it's an example of somebody elevating a shitty script with great direction
and i think that's so diminishing of what is really kind of an amazing script
that takes a gimmick yes but makes it into like something so cool and interesting and each one of
these crime scenes is so disturbing and upsetting and crazy
i love
seven is right below it
seven is a classic it's an a -plus movie get the 4k go see it in imax if you can joe you know i will
do one more of in my theme of crazy people i watched ghost heads the documentary about ghost
a ghostbuster super fan is called a ghost head i didn't know that so i watched it and
it's a movie where people talk about ghost heads and they're like oh my god i'm gonna die
it's a movie where people talk about the movie ghostbusters and how it touched them in a certain
way and was very special to them in their lives in one way or another and with each of these people
they talk about how the movie helped them through a tough period in life fair enough and then with
each of these people they let them keep talking on camera until they are weeping talking about
their regrets
and
the movie gets to a point where it's you're you're you're going guys you have people spiraling on
camera here they're supposed to be talking about their love of ghostbusters and and let them talk
about what the movie means to them during the the in the wake of a tragedy that's fine but then they
just keep the interview going and you've got somebody crying about like i just never got to
say goodbye to my grandfather and he met he was like a father to me and i don't i it's my greatest
regret and i don't know how to say goodbye to my grandfather and he was like a father to me and i
was like a father to me and i don't know how to say goodbye to my grandfather and he was like a father to me and i
you're like what does this have to do with ghostbusters this is a this guy's personal thing
right so these people all get dressed up as the ghostbusters and they go to the conventions and
things and uh there's a lot of talk of when i'm in my jumpsuit with my proton pack on that's when
i'm the real me uh so it it starts to alternate version of that weekend song yeah it starts to
creep into a place of guys yeah i think you might be losing your
a little bit here i don't know i i mean i feel bad for you that you went through something but
this might be a little much and then finally mid -doc up pops a woman and she goes i am a
clinical psychologist and you go all right here comes the calvary where the lady's going to be
like i think it's good that they use the movie but yeah you know and uh she goes here's the thing
with cosplayers it lets them express themselves and it lets them express themselves in a way that
they don't feel comfortable doing in regular life and you're like okay i'm listening
the psychologist then goes when i'm cosplaying and you're like oh my god
yeah that's my worst nightmare is that my my therapist of 10 years would casually mention
she's a ghostbusters cosplayer and i'd be like i've wasted my life my money my energy um it was
at times endearing and then i'd be like oh my god i'm cosplaying and i'm cosplaying and i'm cosplaying
uh there there's there is a group of ghostbuster guys that like help sick kids and go to the
hospital to visit that was beautiful um there's some interviews with the cast that are that are
kind of cool and ivan reitman and stuff but it was asked who do they speak to joe they speak to
ivan reitman they speak to akroyd oh all right all right they got some uh they speak to ernie
hudson murray's the only one that basically obviously um
and uh and then it culminates with them with with some of the biggest ghostbusters fans on planet
earth getting invited to paramount the paramount lot to see the trailer for the and they're all
excited we're gonna see the new ghostbusters trailer we're beside ourselves whenever i'm like
oh they must be an afterlife and it's like no they're going to see the 2016 trailer and i'm like
oh you guys are in for a real
i mean you're talking about how this movie got you through alcoholism
yeah and you're gonna go you're gonna you're gonna fall off the wagon go straight to the bar
make it a double anyway ghost heads uh i don't know that i'd recommend it but
anyway let's get to our real quick real quick before we do
it's it's a 20 second clip let me play the song for you i got it right here
from amelia perez
press the speaker right to the mic like right against it i mean okay
that's not it's not working now no i'll watch it after okay it's very nice to meet you i'd
like to ask you about sex change operation that's what you just sang
and then he goes man into a woman penis to vagina it's like it's honestly oh my god it is and i'm
not mocking trans people i'm mocking any world that would think that this is helping their cause
you know yeah i agree in its own sort of clumsy and beautiful way the will ferrell
and his trans friend movie will and harper is such a better such a better
representation i would say um folks let's talk about arguably although i would say there is no
argument to be had the great romantic comedy certainly of our lifetime when harry met sally
written by the great nora efron directed by the great rob reiner in the middle of an
unprecedented hot streak where he just could not do any wrong and this went on for quite
some time and i think it's a great movie and i think it's a great movie and i think it's a great
time with him he just seemed to no matter what genre he tried he got it right
and i think for me what i realized in this viewing of when harry met sally is the reason
it's kind of the perfect example of the genre the defining example of the genre
is that it's the exact meeting point between woody allen and his classic new yorker
romantic comedies of the 70s and 80s and the later nora efron classics the sleepers in seattle
you've got mail etc it's that exact meeting point of those two movies and it makes this completely
fresh thing it still feels fresh to me watching it it feels like a brand new movie i watched it
with the commentary um which had efron
crystal and reiner learned a lot about the movie i'd recommend that
um but it's it's the best it's an a plus it's a it's a classic um yeah in fact
the movie was offered to albert brooks yeah he passed he said it's too much like a woody allen
movie yeah which it kind of is i mean it you know rob reiner definitely takes a few
pointers from woody allen it you know particularly the the interviews yes
that are scattered throughout the movie of the couples the old couples talking which
on this rewatch i noticed something because i watched some of the special features as well
and they talked about like one of the things you know that this movie was based on nora efron and
rob reiner's friendship and rob reiner was talking about how he had just gotten divorced
and he was not handling it well and he was just basically fucking a lot i guess yeah which
i
suppose
you make life
so
i
haven't
your
life
has
how he's got that accent it's insane that's true yeah it's insane um anyway
um but i noticed something there was there was there's a there's a very
they don't hit you over the head with it but there's a sort of subtle commentary about men
in those interviews because in almost all of them the man is just talking and the woman
at times looks so despondent you know she's correcting him on the detail like no you're
wrong it was yeah yeah it was that it was this and it's very funny it's very funny there's one
in particular where the guy's like and then she and then she's been a love of my life whatever
and the lady looks like almost dead -eyed yeah well they're all great but i always thought they
were a mix of real and fake and it turns out they're all scripted and they're all actors which
once i learned that in the commentary then you can kind of see it but that's really hard to do
well and they do it really well you buy it it's a great framing device it's so definitive that
you really never saw it attempted again because they nail it so well and it's a nice commentary
on the action i had an interesting experience of my friends who are married comedy writers
they've seen everything but had just missed this one and i asked them what what they watched for
the first time this year they were like we
really liked it but don't quite see all the fuss which i just thought anyone watching it at any
time would just get it that's insane thing to say to them they were like we felt like billy crystal
was this awful miserable vaguely creepy old man who should have been so thankful that meg ryan
looked his way but instead he's like fucking it up at every turn and like i gotta go out there and
better and i'm like well that is you know at their dark core that is men that's the reality
of the movie the dark reality of the billy crystal character but to me for that them to be turned off
from the movie by that and not find it romantic like they were like when he's giving that speech
to the end at the end they're like we weren't even moved by it because we were like get away
from this man and that just might be changing attitudes about men and women your friends are
idiots
an idiot it was an interesting take on it i was just kind of like okay he is and by the way what
do you mean crazy old man they're the same age aren't they i mean maybe they're supposed to be
but he's definitely they joke about that in the commentary too he was at least 15 years older than
her because i think she's only like 26 she's playing 30 but she's like really young in real
life and he was maybe late 30s 40 it all works they give him a lot of time to think about it
wig here uh you know they give her sort of some fluffed bangs there to me i never questioned it
too much he's he's misanthropic but in that woody allen way that i feel like he's always
funny and charming and lovable also too also too to go in deeper on your the commentary of your
your friends sure wait she's no fucking walk in the park either in the movie she's a pain in the
ass she's a micromanager for yeah she micromanages everything she's she's particular she's you know
it's like that's that's the part of it that makes it like she's gorgeous but i can't date this woman
so to reduce it to just oh it's meg ryan and she has puppy dog eyes he should be thankful it's like
no there's more to it than that like that yeah that's the that's the point is is she's she's
tough she's a tough sell but she's really
wonderful and he's a tough sell but he's really wonderful that's the beauty of the relationship
and these two characters they're real characters they are i've never liked billy crystal more
never related to him more never got him more and the fact that he is you know funny goes a long way
yeah he's not a 10 and meg ryan is is an 11 but like he's charming and funny and etc i never
questioned that aspect of the relationship i love them together i root for them
and i think meg ryan has the harder role because she does make this very neurotic
uh kind of strange woman super funny and her annoying aspects are funny and likable
about her which is very hard to do because she does she wants to control everything she wants
to control how how meals are ordered and how everything is prepared and how everything is done
and she wants her life to go a very certain way and she's very particular and she's kind of
clingy but these are all portrayed by her as being lovable like you would love for somebody
like this to cling to you because she's so great in the movie yeah i think kind of her pinnacle
they're both really at their peaks they have amazing chemistry together yeah i'm surprised
they excuse me i'm surprised they never did anything else together uh because they are
really great together this is a movie i would actually like to see a sequel of and see where
these characters are years later but um
let's not forget the fantastic can you hear this noise by the way this construction noise
happening no all right it's driving me up a wall um the uh i i do love the supporting cast as well
bruno kirby and carrie fisher are delightful so good they're two best friends carrie fisher
the the whole thing where she just basically fucks married men
and it's just it's really funny uh and then one of my favorites was 31 and when harry met sally
meg ryan was 26 billy crystal was 41 um people just look different back then i assume bruno
kirby was probably 40 i would have thought kirby was 63 years old in this movie he was uh
how old bruno kirby and when harry met sally it keeps saying 57 that can't be right that's when
i love the no answers he was about 40 all right yeah 42 yeah one of my favorite scenes is this is
the date scene where they try to hook up yes bruno kirby with meg ryan and carrie fisher with billy
crystal and uh excuse me the way it comes into that scene where bruno kirby is just like when
i read jimmy breslin i just feel like he's the voice of new york city
and if you're not familiar with jimmy breslin he was a very hard -nosed
newspaper man in the 60s 70s and 80s in new york very controversial uh very like you know sort of
conservative you know you know take no shit take no prisoners drinking smoking kind of writer
sure and the way they play it in the thing is meg ryan is like she's not offended she's just like
it's not for me and i don't want to talk about this anymore and i don't want to talk about this anymore
but kirby coming in just so hard about how brilliant he loves how much he loves jimmy
breslin and his articles and it's just such it's he's such a writer in that scene it's just so
funny it's such a funny author to reference and of course a writer would be would fall for carrie
fit you can see him fall for her the moment she compliments him and says how much she loves his
writing that's when he really falls for her yeah classic creative person right there as well yeah
yeah um but that's the way it is sometimes you just you know two people can be great on paper
but they get together and and there's nothing but then you know the movie makes you think about all
the big things about love and how people wind up together in a beautiful way because it's a bigger
picture than just the two and it's not just because of the framework of the old people telling their
stories that helps it but it's also that we follow this couple over this 10 15 year period in their
life you think about all the people you've known in your life and the people who've come in and out
of your life and who would have been better for you than who you wound up with and who would have
been worse and so on and so forth uh it winds up being a very deep movie in addition to being a
very funny one a lot like a groundhog day or something where it ticks all the boxes of a
classic romantic comedy but there's also this much deeper almost philosophical thing about
life and love going on in the background that makes it a masterpiece really
uh billy crystal i love the scene where he asks her to go to bed with him at the diner in the
beginning and then she says just let it lie and he gets in the car and goes uh so you want to get a
hotel see what i did there i didn't let it lie like it's classic billy crystal it's why the guy
was so funny um or it's a good example of why the guy was so funny it's a really really funny movie
it's a really really funny movie it's a really really funny movie it's a really really funny movie
i weep like a baby at the end of it every time i watch it um and again it it it could be well no
woody allen did it first but i was gonna say it it's not the first movie to do it but it is a
definitive movie as you know this which has become a cliche now but making new york a character in
the movie like it is the scenes of them walking through central park the scenes of them at uh
the museum i guess it's the is it the moma wood art museum whatever they're at the art museum
the scenes of them at uh what's the store that has all the gadgets
oh uh sharper image sharper image karaoke machine yeah at the time was only in new york i believe
um the the look of the apartments which by the way these apartments they're living in
it's
insane you're like what what what are these billionaires but anyway it's just a really really
wonderful film uh and it really captures a moment of life in my opinion and norafron talks about
this on you and you've got mail in the commentary she said you know one of the things she wanted to
show and you got mail is how special it is to fall in love in new york and she talks about
the scene where tom hanks and meg ryan are sitting on the park bench and she goes it was so noisy
that day we had to cut out so much noise because there was so much activity happening around where
we were shooting and she goes but you don't hear any of it and that's what it's like to fall in
love in new york it's it's there's so much happening around you but it's just the two of
sitting on that bench it's a really beautiful thought and commentary and she captures that in
this as well and in and in as always
the in great nora effron style she writes real characters that don't agree about everything
that have different political views and stances that coexist and like one another and appreciate
one another despite their differences um yeah they're often in the wrong to each other and she
digs way more into character than plot so like most you look at like how to lose a guy in 10 days
it's a fine it's an entertaining romantic comedy but the entire movie is hinging on this
ridiculous plot that nobody should really give a shit about whereas if you fleshed out your
characters and really dug into them like this movie you don't have to tell some big complicated
plot you just have to watch these two people fall in love and it's fascinating and we all root for
them uh it's just because she made these wonderful characters that
remind us of our friends and of us and etc etc i would like to shout out the filmography of rob
reiner to start i mean he starts in 1984 with the definitive mockumentary this is spinal tap
first movie like invents a genre basically uh then the sure thing a decent romantic comedy from there
it is stand by me the princess bride when harry met sally misery a few good men
amazing and then well now talk about the equal amount of fall off well then talk about north
north really did derail everything but he briefly bounced back with the american president which is
good then it's ghost of mississippi story of us which i do like with bruce willis and michelle
pfeiffer then things get pretty bad alex and emma rumor has it stinks the bucket list stinks
i don't know what these are but it's a good movie
last 10 movies are uh and then we got spinal tap 2 coming so we'll see j is in there i believe bj is
in the mix yeah there's something called the magic of bell isle i don't even know what some of these
movies are uh we talked about it on the pod before i said i've never seen of a harder faster fall off
in quality than reiner and diane keaton diane keaton is the same thing it's like it was hit
after hit after hit and then all of a sudden it's like it's like it's like it's like it's like it's
like what the fuck are you doing and they get to just keep working it's wild i mean he's definitely
getting smaller budgets and less stars but yeah i mean he's he's had a fall off i think people
keep waiting for that you got a sort of dread spinal tap too i mean the hope is that it hits
but these these are old men at this point so we'll see we'll see
anyway the man reached
really his peak in that five years where the just five incredible movies in a variety of genres
and i think he did make as as i've said the definitive thriller certainly the definitive
stephen king adaptation with misery i think he made the definitive all -time romantic comedy
with when harry met sally a great movie for the holiday season
hogs are way up for when harry met sally check it out we'll be back with wicked
slave uh later in the month but wicked will be next uh i'm at joe de rosa comedy on instagram
uh i think it's joe de rosa comedian on tiktok but i think that's going away anyway so whatever
the big thing i need you to do is to go to my website joe de rosa .com
check out all upcoming tour dates we start in toronto this coming weekend uh followed by san
diego at the end of the month uh and so on and so forth throughout the country dc in early february
the midwest in uh mid to late february and uh and the dates keep going and keep on coming um
please please please come out and if you're in new york city and you want to get a sandwich
and a drink go on by joey roses joey roses .com the patrick walsh on instagram see you in hell
pod is the pods page on instagram thank you so much for your love and your patreon support
we'll be back three other times this month we'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell
you