I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, and when the sound of your screams becomes
the thing of my dreams, you know I'll say, I'll see you in hell, you know I will, I'll
see you in hell, you know I will.
Folks, it's we'll see you in hell. It's the podcast you turn to when you wanna churn to
what the kids are burned to. Oh no. Now what do you mean churn to? That's where you lost me.
Maybe a masturbation. Never heard it called churning. Well no, I make things up.
You think a lot of people are masturbating to this podcast? I don't know. Who am I to judge?
Why can't I coin a phrase? I have been told I have a sexy voice.
Okay. By me, people. It's been a while. I've been told it.
That's good. Do you churn to that when somebody tells you that?
No, but I churn to recordings of my own voice.
See, it's already become part of the vernacular. It's catching on.
Churn and burn, baby. What's going on at NYC?
Nothing really. It's a bit of an overcast day, but not a bad day. I woke up terribly early this
morning, like 7 a .m. or something. Didn't have to, but just did. And spent the morning,
got nothing to show for it, got nothing done, somehow just paced around. Had a meeting at 12
at the bar, went over, did that, came back to do this, and here we are. Got a show later tonight.
I've been enjoying this all new material that you're putting up on the Instagram,
on the Reels. I know some of them, the jokes are old, but they feel new.
It's unreleased material. Some of it's new, new. Some of it's not. Yeah, I'm just, you know,
finally getting my shit together with getting the clips and things out there.
Is Reels the new thing for a comic to make their way in the world today?
Reels and TikTok.
Yeah, I have neither. Now Reels seem like the stupidest thing in the world to me. I've put like,
one of the kids on the Miss Pat Show is obsessed with TikTok, the character is.
So I've been able to write some TikTok jokes that get big laughs, even though I've never seen them.
But to me, it seems like the one joke was TikTok's a lot more than just a girl in a sports bra
pointing at words, you know? And because anytime I see a TikTok, it's a girl in a sports bra
pointing at words that pop up in little balloons. And they're the least creative, the least funny.
They make the vines look like fucking the work of Orson Welles, these TikToks. They're pathetic.
And yeah, it's not great. The new trend is women, usually women, 99 % of the time saying,
look at all these cute texts my husband gives me. You've seen these? And then they zero in on these
texts. And the texts, like this is how my husband lets me know he loves me or whatever. The text
will be like, should be home in 20. Like the most generic, boring text messages that these women
are getting so little love from the man in their life that to them, it reads like affection.
Like it's that's not the bit the bit isn't. No, I've seen that too. I've seen it where the bit is
like my husband's so romantic. And it's like five texts about how he's taking a shit. And you're
like, Okay, I get the comedic point of this. The vast majority of them are a woman showcasing how
sweeter husband can be with like the most generic. I mean, the ideal not funny version of that
real or TikTok is the husband saying, I'm going to the store, baby, do you need anything?
I'm at work. And I just, I just lost track of my thoughts, because I started thinking about how
much I love you or something. There's a real version. And there's a funny version. Most of
them lie in the sad middle ground, I urge you to look for these texts. They're really tragic.
And it goes to show that the women in this world have very low expectations of the men in their
lives. And maybe that's for the best. I don't know. But like, if you're looking through your
text and picking these out as the jewels of the crowd, I mean, my God,
Yeah, that's, that's upsetting stuff. That's upsetting stuff. If that's passing for romance
these days, you know, throwing my jacket over puddles, for Christ sakes, I wrote three jackets
last week. This is all I got to do. Yeah, yeah. I like to throw the jacket over a big cavernous
puddle so that when the lady steps on it, she goes through it like in a Looney Tunes. Yeah,
I enjoy that too. That's why I laugh at her and I run away. I do sort of that Looney Tune laugh
to where I go. Oh, is that snaggle puss laugh like them? One of them wasn't even looted to
now he's not but you're all over the map. I am truly all over the map. The other the other worst
reel that is maybe worse than all of them. And I'm sure you've seen this one, Joe is
is woman sometimes man lip syncing to don't dialogue from a movie. Don't get me started.
Don't get me started. That's 33 % of these reels and they'll have a million likes.
Don't get me started. It's just this world is fucked. Have you seen the ones where they
don't even get the words correct? It's a it's an eight second clip and they still miss one of the
I mean, it's it's bound you're bound to you see the capability. Record another version.
You see the capability of the average person here, you know, it's you think they're going to
nail these lips. lip syncing is no different than going to the supermarket and dealing with
the staff there you get you get three out of 10 are going to be helpful. I mean, it's true job.
So true. I saw the I saw the collapse of everything yesterday in almost real fucking
time. We have a distributor. I guess that's the term for it. I might be saying the wrong term.
But anyway, a supplier, excuse me. Yeah. You know, when you when you when you have a bar
that is food and liquor and stuff, you got to have a supplier to bring and you have to
you have several suppliers that bring you all different types of products and brands and things.
And one of our food suppliers is I won't name names, but it's just not getting the job done.
And when he leaves us hanging, which means he shows up with missing several items, he said he
was bringing to us and just doesn't give us any heads up. You just order and you're like,
where are the 12 turkeys that we needed? You know? And there's just no accountability.
None. So when that happens, then I get the call from the kitchen guy. He's like, can you drive
to Queens and go to restaurant depot, which restaurant depot is basically Costco for restaurants.
Okay, not look, it comes in handy in a pinch, not a place you want to spend a lot of time.
It's chaotic. It's you can imagine the version of that in LA is in Culver City. They have all
those restaurants. It's like you can get anything you need for a restaurant in a big warehouse,
right? Yeah, basically. Okay. So when I get that call, I'm always like, God damn it, man,
because it's like, it's last minute. It's like, the delivery showed up. These things are missing.
Can you any way you can go today? And you're like, Yeah, I guess I'll have to figure this out.
And it's a pain. So anyway, in real time yesterday, I see the collapse of everything.
Kitchen guy calls distributor or supplier, drop the ball again. Why did supplier drop the ball?
Because there are supply chain issues. This guy doesn't give a shit. We're at his mercy. Why should
he do his job properly? You know what I mean? Yeah. So it's like starts with the supply chain,
shit rolls down to the supplier supplier basically tells us tough shit, you know,
whatever. We're in a take it or leave it position. Then I have to rearrange the day
drive all the way up to Queens to go to this place you get out to this place.
There are lines wrapping like literally from the registers all the way into the aisles. You can't
tell where the lines begin, where they end. It's utter chaos. There's like,
is that supply chain shit? Or there's dude, there's like five empty registers. There's
employees walking around doing nothing as far as I can tell. Yeah. You know, a lot in banks
these days in particular, a lot of employees sort of walking around congregating behind the desk.
Yeah. Looking up annoyed as you walk. Yeah. Why don't you tend to some of these empty windows
here that that, you know, for the 63 person line here. Anyway, it just was the whole thing
in real time. You're just like, you're like, here it is. This is the collapse. I'm watching
the tail end of the chain of dominoes that starts with the supply chain and ends here
at the restaurant depot, where nobody is doing the job. And I'm not disparaging restaurant depot.
It's happening everywhere. You anywhere you go, you're just like, nobody is doing their job. And
then you're like, well, the person above them isn't doing their job. And you're like, yeah,
but then the person above them isn't doing their job. And it was just, it was fascinating. It was
infuriating, but it was fascinating to see yesterday, like a literal direct chain of three
industries, sort of not functioning properly that ended resulted in me standing in a line for an
hour. Yeah. Yeah. You know, trying to buy six heads of ham, whatever the hell you call them.
I don't know what they're called, but you know what I mean? Big chunks of ham.
No, I went up to the liquor store today. I got three friends from Missouri coming out this weekend
and there's a giant sign up that says, please bear with us as we deal with the supply chain.
I walk in, it's just me and the guy working there. I grab what I need. I go up to the counter.
He's like, can you just give me one second, man? I'm like, yeah. He goes over and he's undoing boxes.
Opening and unpacking boxes like unreal. He could have scanned my two items and I walked out the
watch and then I'm like, do I just leave? Like I'm here? I don't want to go somewhere else.
And I think basically there's so few people are working that everyone knows they're not
going to fire you and is acting accordingly and trying to get money for just being around.
I guess it's one and a half to one and a half jobs to one person right now.
Okay. Which is wild because the economy is not good or is it good?
Is everyone not working allegedly because they can't make a good minimum wage?
I think it's, I think it's everything coming to a head. I'm not, I'm certainly not blaming,
let me be clear. I'm certainly not blaming, you know, the workers solely. Like I think after
pandemic, a lot of us had that reflective thing where it's like, what am I doing with my life?
Why am I working so hard? Like, why is, you know, like we should be living like this.
So I get that aspect of it. I get the aspect of it that a lot of people are underpaid.
I get the aspect of it. Now it's very hard to run a business. And, you know, like, you know,
I try to see it from all angles, but I think it just finally came to a head here. And I think
COVID is what put it over the top. And it's just like, you can't, you can't function at this,
at this tick, like for this long, like we're too bloated, right? It's too bloated of a country.
It's just too much. Yeah. And, you know, if you, if people know, like, I don't have to work,
if I don't want to, well, why would you work? I mean, my whole life is based around that fucking
approach, you know, like, you know, I never wanted to be a punch the time clock guy.
So I get that. But, you know, unfortunately, whether we like it or not, it's going to slide
the other way. And then it's going to be like, there's going to be a dearth of jobs. And,
you know, and then the, and then the bosses and everybody and the, and the corporations are going
to strike back and treat people even worse because they can, because people are desperate for jobs.
And then when it switched swings back into the workers, to the workers advantage again,
even more people will be like, fuck you. You treated us like garbage, right? Now you need me.
I'm not going to be, it's horrible. It's a terrible, endless cycle. But I really do think
it's coming to a head. Like, I mean, this is wild, man. Wild, like, it's bad news. And I don't know
if you saw Biden fall off that bike. Yeah. I mean, that to me will just really be how I think of him
going forward. We're not in good shape. No, it's just, I mean, it's your, your textbook, like guy
who's wobbly at the grocery store and you put your hand on his lower back and like, you're all right,
sir. Can I help you out? You know, like that, that's what's running our country. It's, it's, it's,
it's my friend, uh, the phrase he used, and I agree with him. He goes, this is elder abuse.
This man should not be in this job. Like he's being propped up by this is abuse. Like,
and I agree at this point. Yeah, it ain't good. And I think, well, people don't want to hear us
talk about politics for Christ's sake. We're not talking, we're talking. Yeah. Um, we're talking
fear here. I'll tell you one thing though. Um, this is a screaming in, I'm trying to write a
bit about this. Yeah. Uh, I read a, I read a story induced. Uh, let me start with this story.
I once got, I was in a bar and I went into a photo booth that was out of order to do cocaine.
Okay. With a friend of mine, I came out of the photo booth, bouncer came over. He's like,
you're out of here. I go, where are you now? A club or something. What's that? Where are you?
Where you were a club. I was in a bar in LA. Okay. And I went into an out of order photo booth,
the thing with the little curtain with a friend of mine to do coke. Yeah. And, uh, we came out
and the bar bouncer came over and he goes, you're out of here. And I go, why? And he goes,
you're doing coke in that photo booth. And I go, no, I wasn't. We were trying to take a photo. And
he goes, the photo was out of order. There were three of you in the booth. I know what you guys
were doing. You're out of here. And I go, no. And he goes, you were doing coke in the photo
booth. And I just went, no, no, I wasn't. Yeah. And he was like, yes, you were. And I was like,
no, I wasn't. And I just kept saying, no, I wasn't until he got frustrated enough that he was like,
fine. You weren't. And he just walked away. And that was the end of it. And I was like, wow,
you can do that. You can just deny something until you're right. Uh, give work for the Republican
Party for quite some time and that nobody is going to jail for anything. So anyway,
this approach to life, which I thought could only be applied to just doing coke in a photo booth.
Yeah. Now everybody's approach to everything in life, like nobody's guilty of anything anymore.
So I'm reading like this. This is the word to scream and end. I'm reading this thing about
the Simon Pegg thing about Tom Cruise. No, it's the Jesse, Jesse Smollett. He was like,
I was shocked to see all the bad feedback I got on. It's like, you lied. What are you talking
about? That guy's clearly just one of history's greatest sociopaths. I mean, they gave him a
directorial job soon after he's directing a film and it's he's doing the coke in the out of water
photo booth. He's like, yeah, I didn't lie. And they're like, no, no, no, you did. And he's like,
I didn't. Yeah, no, you did. He's like, I didn't. And he's like, they're like, all right,
you can act again. Here's another job. It's fascinating to me.
I worked on and off with Simon Pegg for quite some time. And he told me this, I asked, like,
what can you tell me about Tom Cruise? And I wouldn't have reported it, except he just finally
said it to a reporter and I saw it become like public knowledge. But he said, Tom Cruise told him
the key to becoming like a big success where you have power and people listen to you and
Tom Cruise basically, he said, is never under any circumstances, admit that you were wrong
or that you have made a mistake. So he's like on one of these Mission Impossible movies, you know,
like Tom Cruise will clearly make a mistake. Like he'll do something that's just wrong,
a stunt or something like that. And he'll just look people in the eye and be like, no, I didn't,
no, I didn't until it goes away. And then Pegg was like, he does the same thing to me. Like if I ever
say, Oh, I'm sorry, I messed up that line or something. He'll pull me over and be like,
you don't say that. You don't say that. So like, I love that Cruise passes it around,
shares the way, you know, it's not just applicable to him. He's like, no, this is for everybody.
Well, I'm sure he's not saying it to, you know, the guy at the grocery store. But if you're famous,
you might get that advice from the TC. You think Tommy's doing his own grocery shopping, huh?
Maybe not. Maybe not. I think when he goes on his first date with whichever unsuspecting woman has
been assigned to be his wife for that three year period, he tries to do like a fun, go to the
grocery store, buy a bottle of wine thing. Yeah. Yeah. Tommy, how was your weekend? It was great.
Had a date with subject 339. Yeah, he's single now, right? Cruise,
who the hell knows? You just got to wonder what goes on in that man's bedroom. You just got to
wonder. I think nothing. I think the guy wakes up at like four 30 AM. He sleeps upside down like a
bat. Yeah. Yeah. Absolutely. Goes from sleeping upside down immediately to hanging awake upside
down to do some sort of exercise. Yep. Then submerges himself in like an ice bath. Definitely a
cold shower or ice bath. Yeah. Hikes like 25 miles comes back and goes right into the office
for whatever movie he's working on. You know, if he's not shooting, he's writing. If he's not
writing, he's producing. If he's not producing, he's editing. It's not editing. He's promoting.
I think that's his day, man. Like I, you know, it's like probably eats, you know,
raw vegetables twice as his meal. Yeah. Goes down into his basement dungeon and tases
Shelley Miskovic, who was locked up in a chain link cage down there.
Allegedly, we have to say allegedly. Yeah.
Fascinating stuff. And have you seen Top Gun? Mr. Maverick? Yep. Couldn't give a rat's ass.
I thought you were intrigued. It's an entertaining picture if you like planes flying around.
It's it's one of the rare movies to be released in the last five years where it seems like people
tried, you know, okay, big budget level. I think we're finally back at the point where it's like,
we're enough through COVID that you could make like a movie soup to nuts again, like, yeah,
where it's not like, you know, halfway through, you see that a pandemic hit and then all of a
sudden, everybody's acting in front of a green screen for no apparent reason. Right.
Even in comedies for a while there, that there was a period of like that vacation friends on Hulu,
the bubble, the Apatow movie, everything that was coming out was like
Fred Armisen in front of a green screen doing comedy at a budget of like $170 million.
Just rough stuff. A dark era for movie comedy. What was that show? Oh, Coastal Elites.
Wasn't I familiar with Coastal Elites? Now, you know, it was the one that was on HBO,
and it was White Lotus. No, no, no, no, no, no, the zoom one on HBO. And it was like,
I didn't watch that, but it was called Coastal Elites, I believe.
I got a lot of that middler, right? That middler on zoom for 90 minutes. How does that sound?
If somebody was like, Hey, do you want to do a 90 minute zoom with that middler,
I would probably get out of it. But now I'm paying to watch it as premium content.
I didn't see the film that is. She's somebody I feel like I'd love to meet. I feel like if I met
her, she'd be like an aunt, you know, she'd be like the aunt that you always loved. But then you see
her in a, in one of those things, you're like, Oh my God. Like you see, I get along with that.
I really do. So, you know what I had when I was a kid and I never got a straight answer as to why,
but I had your standard books, you know, like monster at the end of this book, the Grover
classic, you know, your standard kids books, Berenstein bears, et cetera. But then I had one
called like the divine baby M. And it was a book where it was Bette Midler as a baby,
a picture book that one of my parents, I guess, bought for me, I guess, in the hopes that I would
become a homosexual, but like, I mean, no kid knows who Bette Midler is. What are you doing?
This was part of your conditioning training. Yeah. I had the, uh,
Judy Garland through headphones. Yeah. Most people go to the camps to convert you
straight. I went the other way. I, this new movie, by the way, another bonus scream in it with, uh,
Kevin Bacon about the gay convert horror movie slasher movie called the about a gay conversion
camp. I liked that great idea for a movie, but I mean, I don't know what anything about it,
not just a great idea. I mean, the title is they them, right? Right. Which is a, is a sort
of ominous title already. Uh, but then it's, you know, it's, it's stylized with the slash
and it's pronounced they slash them. And I was like, whoever figured that out, like the writer,
when he realized, oh my God, they, them is technically pronounced, they slash them. I'm
going to do a horror movie called that. I was like, he must've written it in fucking 90 minutes.
Like you're like, what a gold discovery, man. Like Jesus, like I was jealous of that one.
So I'm, I'm looking forward to seeing it. Bacon return into horror and returning to the camp
genre. Two things that's a camp slasher with bacon. So I'm into it. Bacon has done a lot of camp
movies over the years and a lot of horror movies and sometimes they mix.
I, uh, I always root for him and said what my, mainly because they're a Hollywood couple that's
lasted for whatever 40 years, 30 years, but also because they got taken by Bernie Madoff.
He like brought them down to zero. You might say made off with all their money, but he took their,
uh, like life savings basically, which makes me root for those two even more. I've always
liked them both. They paid off made off. Yeah. Uh, the name of that book. So you can know,
I wasn't making it up. It was written by Bette Midler and it is called the saga of baby divine.
I know that it's real not to be confused with their other children's book, baby with the huge
hits that this review that I'm looking at says, says Midler rivals Dr. Seuss in creativity,
timing, rhyming, and pages full of animated color. Does she also don't know if that's,
I mean, fuck my, my, my hat's off to, to, to Sue's, I guess, but I'm not that impressed.
No, it's not that hard of a thing to rival. I don't think,
you know, Doc Seuss is real name trivia question. Uh, Jim Varney, that was Ernest. Yeah.
No, or Geisel, the real name of lead or Geisel. I've been watching, uh, the classic
Carson's late at night. It's about the only thing my brain can handle.
Uh, it's a terrible show and the guy just bombs wall to wall, but it's,
but it is enjoyable to watch soothing. Well, the other night was Bob Newhart, which was great.
And then what's really good about it is the second guest is always somebody that I guess was big at
the time, but you have no idea who it is. So they brought out like the fourth female lead from Miami
vice. And what's so refreshing about watching talk shows from that time is this woman has no idea
how to be on a talk show. She is a, she, I don't remember her name. She was pretty lady,
complete disaster. Carson has no idea what to do with her. They got like a 19 minute segment.
She's clearly not well mentally, but you just sit and watch it. That's the beauty of the old Carson.
You actually come away from an interview, knowing something about somebody,
whereas now you know what their publicist wants you to know.
Well, I mean, excuse me, you want to talk about a different world.
This guy used to interview authors and I don't mean like, just like, you know, fucking, uh, uh,
Sagan or Sagan or whatever, you know, all if there's never heard of it would never hear of
again. Like, this was like, like people bitch about cord and driving around singing karaoke
in a Chevy. And they should. Yeah. Well, sure. But try to sit through one of those Carson interviews,
the guy that wrote, you know, the, the, the book about plate tectonics or whatever. I mean,
it's just fucking brutal, man. Yeah. So how much like, I mean, he will just flat out,
I guess Letterman did this too. And Conan, if we're being fair, but Carson will just undress
some woman with his eyes. You are, you are absolutely stunning. You are just absolutely
stunning. Look at that. Look at that. Look at all you've got going on there. Uh, and that in that
blouse, you know, like just insane things and the audience all cheers. It reels back with every
generation. So like Carson, like would basically say, uh, nice tits to a lady.
Letterman squeeze. Yeah. Letterman would be very flirtatious. Conan brought it back to like
barking at her where he's like almost making fun of the concept.
Ferguson then was like, it was like a tick behind that where like, he would make like a joke about
a woman being hot, but it wasn't quite as obnoxious as barking at her. Like it gets a little
softer each time. And then James Corden, I thought was gay until a year ago that I thought that he
was married. I thought he was gay this whole time. No whole time thought it. No. Well, he always
plays gay characters in movies because he's also an actor for some reason. I guess that's what it
you know, what's interesting is speaking of that. So Tom Hanks just said, uh, I, you know, in this
day and age, I don't think it would be appropriate for me to play the part I played in Philadelphia
and, and that's his stance on it. But it got me to thinking with all the, um, controversy around
straight actors playing gay characters and with as woke as, uh, Rob McElhaney has become,
how does he get to keep playing gay Mac on it's always sunny? Uh, you know, he's been pretty,
they get to do everything because they were grandfathered in. Well, they have the benefit
of their show having been on who was grandfathered in that changed, you know, that's true. I mean,
I don't, I don't know what has changed. I know, um, on cool kids, we had a gay character,
Leslie Jordan, and we wanted to give him an arc of a love interest. And we tried to get Victor
Garber from alias, who was, who is a gay man, great actor. Um, and I w I was really gunning for him.
I remember Fox saying like, you know, he's more of a dramatic actor, multi -cam. We kind of like
to go for, you know, big comedy, whatever. And I saw on the list, Jerry Burns, who eventually played
the role, excellent actor from dear John, the old Judd Hirsch sitcom from Breaking Bad from, um,
justified great act hell of a guy. You're charming, great on the show, great chemistry,
et cetera, but a straight man. Now I opened it up to the room and I said to our gay writers,
I was like, I hate to have to do this and make you guys speak for your people, but like, what do you
handle such a situation? And the gay writers in the show were like, it's totally fine. Uh, it's
totally fine to have a straight guy play a gay actor. No gay man cares. No gay man cares. Now
this was, this was three years ago, four years ago, but I find that very interesting. Do gay
people care? I don't know. I think it's personally, uh, fine for anybody to play anybody
because that's what acting is. Yes. Um, but I also do agree that when it's at the expense of people
from these groups, representative of these groups who are trying to crack into the arts and they're
not being very well represented, then that's not, I get that too. Yeah. I kind of get both sides of
it. Emma Thompson is, is getting, I mean, look anymore. They say that, you know, backlash and
for tweets, right. But the, because she's in a fat suit and Matilda,
so she's getting shit. And it's like, why would you not cast a fat actor? Now look, I get it.
I agree. There is something weird to me that like, we're going to take Charlie,
Charlize Theron and make her gain 40 pounds or, or put her in a fat suit and, and then like
rougher up to play the serial killer and monster. I always had a weird thing about that. I find it
odd at the same time, everybody's going to take a breath and go, guys, it's also still a business.
You know, and sometimes you go to every fat actor, for instance, who could do the part and is a big
enough draw to, to fulfill the need that you need on this thing for it to make its money and get the
views or whatever it is. And they say, no. So then what the hell are you supposed to do? Everything
can't be a no name. You know, it's just not that that's not how that works. So no, it's where I'm
at now. They need a name actress to play the lead in my movie, which is an overweight character.
And I'm supposed to say fat is what you're supposed to say, which is surprising, but
it just, the, the actresses who fit that description are uncomfortable with playing it.
And the actresses who do not fit that description, don't want to wear padding to play the part.
I really kind of shot myself in the foot, but it's just going to make for less interesting
products. I think, cause people are going to say, well, I don't want to do a movie with a fat lead
because I I'm living proof. It's almost impossible to get it over the goal line.
Well, also too, what happened to the good old days of like,
the actors really going for it. Like I gained 70 pounds for that role. I lost 30 pounds. You know
what I mean? That's, that's all gone now to probably more due to the studios and insurance
and fear of lawsuits and things, but you know, that was a thing, man. It was like,
well, Macklehoney did do that. He did, he did do it. Uh, and you know, it'd be like, it'd be like
three months to gain 60 pounds. You know, the, the, the most recent one, I think is a bail,
you know, in the machinist, right. Eating one can of tuna fish a day to get that skinny,
you know? Well, yeah. I mean, there's Ben Foster's doing this Holocaust movie now and he's,
he lost a ton of weight and it still goes on. It just, they wind up not being as discussed as
they used to be. But I mean, and I'm not, I'm not being flippant. I'm really, and I realize this is
an extreme example, but where does it stop? Where do you stop with this? Let's say you want to make
a movie like the woodsman about a recovering pedophile and a guy who's trying to do the
right thing with his life and he's made some terrible mistakes in his past. You got to hire
a recovering pedophile to play that part. You know what I mean? Like, and people will scoff and go,
well, that's absurd. It's not that absurd at this point. Well, it's definitely the way writing
jobs go now is like, Hey, I really love this pilot and I would love to write for that show.
That used to be enough for a guy at my level to get a meeting on a show. But the follow -up
questions become what, what exactly in your past and your background enables you to have an inside
edge for this show. And it can be, you know, I actually heard about on the Willy Wonka show
that's coming up, they're doing another Willy Wonka show. What the fuck could the life experience
possibly need to be for the Willy Wonka show? The Willy Wonka show they required, because I was
briefly in the mix for the show. They required that there be handicapped people on the staff
because of the Oompa Loompas, who I never would have considered as even being handicapped,
but I guess handicapped. So that that was what the call that was what the cast or their writing
call was. The call was like, we need handicapped writers or disabled writers who understand the
plight of the Oompa Loompa in the writer's room. And you're like, why don't you just have little
people? You would think you would think I think they thought were maybe there aren't any so we
cast a wider net and get a disabled writer. I don't know. And I, I can't stress enough that
the heart of these people I'm sure is in the right place. No, it's just like you're 100 % wrong.
They're they're disgusting duplicitous. They're posturing. Yes. They don't give a shit about
who hurt gets hurt by what they care about keeping their fucking jobs that they're no,
I won't go with you on that. Yeah. But yeah, it's, it's, it's a very big thing. Now we had,
we had an all Hispanic writers room, or we, you know, and it's like, cool, but now it feels almost
like, you know, a lot of people can't get work, say that or talk about it. But things have things
have undergone a very major change to the extent that now it makes the most sense for me to work
on a black show like Miss Pat show. And fantastic. I'm happier there than I've been on a show in 10
years. But you have you can only really get jobs when the showrunner looks different from you sort
of and it's it's just it makes an already very difficult needle threading almost impossible
because the odds of a job opening while you're available that you are exactly right for, but
also the racial makeup of the room requires me a 40 year old white guy, which no room requires.
It really, that's why people complain. And then immediately the response is, oh, shut the fuck up.
What do you know? And everything else. But of course, it's a real thing. You know,
it's interesting. It's very reflective of when I started in standup. Yeah. Yeah. When I started
in standup, a lot of the clubs I would go to would say, you're just another white guy.
Okay, so I will even more of that now, right? I don't know. To be honest, I kind of don't.
I don't know. But but I did. I got embraced very well. I started in a black club, but I got
embraced by the black circuit and stand up, which is wild that it was when I guess still is sort of
that segregated in many ways. But but I got embraced because I was a white guy that could
do well. Yeah. On those shows. And it's exactly was exactly the same thing you're saying. Yeah.
You know, from a writer standpoint, it makes a little more sense to me. It's like, it's like,
yeah, let's not have six 40 year old white guys trying to write the red and meth sitcom,
you know what I mean? Like, completely agree with that. Completely agree with that. Yeah. So and
hey, we're doing Dallas Buyers Club, the TV show, you need some people on the staff that
that have done heroin that struggled with addiction that understand how this works or whatever. Yeah,
that that kind of thing makes a lot of sense to me as a as a from writing standpoint.
The acting thing is where I start to really scratch my head because I'm and I get it,
people shouldn't be on stage and black faces, you know, obviously, but like,
you know, the whole point of acting is to become another person. It's the whole idea. Yeah. You
know, it was applauded that, you know, somebody would do Henry the whatever it is Shakespeare,
and it was like, how was his limp? Right. Part of the character, you know? Yeah.
You know, there's talk now about
um, wait, what was I going to say, Joe? God damn it.
There's talk. What were you saying? Become other people. Henry VIII has to win.
And nevermind. I don't know what I was gonna say. We should go to the movie corner.
Yeah, I got a lot of crews in my corner today. Oh, well, you can call it cruise control. It's
Yeah. Um, I is here. I'll do some docs. I watched some docs, all of these on Hulu. First off,
my favorite of them dead asleep. A nice tight 90 minutes. A lot of these documentaries pad
90 minutes of content to like a 10 hour event. Dead asleep is tight. It's really,
interesting subject. There is a guy who's about 1920, kind of pudgy, kind of not too cool. His
girlfriend is sorry, a friend of his is this very bubbly, attractive blonde girl. And one morning,
he basically says, Hey, before you head out of town, come by, I want to give you a gift.
She drops by on her way out of town. She winds up murdered.
The theory is that he sleptwalked and killed her. This is a guy who had been sleepwalking
his whole life. So stabbed her like 100 times. But the argument was this guy's a sleepwalker.
I think he slept, walked and killed her. I love shit like this. I love shit where you kind of see
all sides. You're going to form your own opinions of it. To me, this girl showed up to get the gift.
He revealed his dick to her, pulled the blankets down and showed his dick. She didn't want to fuck
him. He was embarrassed and killed her and tried to blame it on sleepwalking. Doesn't mean I'm
right. I do hate how so many of these things don't ever give you the real answer, but really
interesting subject and a really great documentary. Check it out dead asleep on Hulu. I'm going to do
submission and possibles. You know what, I'll just do I'll bang both two of these at once.
Um, all right. So, okay. I love the mission and possible movies. I'm excited for the new one.
It had occurred to me the other night. I had only ever seen part five and six.
Really? Yeah, I thought I had seen more. You never saw the OG Brian De Palma.
I thought I did, but I didn't. So I watched it. That was big in theaters, man. That was a huge
movie. Yeah, I watched it. It's great. It is great. It's great. Um, I think it's my opinion
that mission and possible as we know it as a franchise does not start until part four
because or part three, I guess, because that's when like Simon Pegg comes in whenever Simon
Pegg comes in because it becomes just a different franchise. The first movie is awesome, but it's
Brian De Palma movie. It feels like the Untouchables where you're watching a Brian.
It's stylistically a thousand percent different than the other movies. It's a lot of beginning.
The idea was, and I think it's a great idea was to do the Bond thing, a different director
for each movie. And they did that for the first three. And I don't know why they latched on to
Macquarie. He's awesome, but I kind of would have liked it if it kept going. And we got
Scorsese's version and Spielberg's version and all that. That would have been cool. Um,
first one's great. I do think it is blasphemous what they did with the, the Voight, you know,
the character of Peter Graves or Peter Graves is the actor. I'm sorry, but whoever Peter Graves
played in the original show, that's insane to me that he becomes the traitor and the bad guy.
And I'm like, what do you guys say? Peter Graves was asked to do the movie, which would have been
really cool connective tissue. He's like, I'm not doing this. This character would never do this.
What are you doing? Uh, so I do agree with the fans, uh, that that was, that was blasphemous.
But other than that, awesome, awesome movie. Um, I started to, uh, it's so stupid. I couldn't get
through it. I was like, this is so such a gear shift. I'm just like, what is happening like right
now? Like, uh, I remember thinking it was pretty cool, but I do remember them doing the face
removal thing about 50 times too many. I just couldn't, you get two permission impossible,
maybe three. I still haven't seen. I want to now that movie is all about Philip Seymour Hoffman,
who is the best villain in the franchise. Maybe the only memorable villain in the franchise.
And then I saw ghost protocol, which was the other one I found screen streaming, which is the
highest, uh, grossing next to the one that had come out most recently. I don't know why they
didn't hang onto that director. Maybe he said, I don't want to do it. It's Brad. I think it's
Brad Bird. Uh, well, Brad Bird did three. He did four now. Wait a minute. And then I think
everything since has been Macquarie. I'll tell you a second mission.
I'm a huge fan of the franchise. No, no Abrams did three. You're right. Abrams bird did four.
Yeah. Bird did four and then Macquarie comes in and five. So four at the time was the highest
grossing in the entire franchise. So I don't know why he didn't stick around anyway, but four is
when Renner comes in. Um, he sticks around for a little while. Ving Rhames pops back up in part
four, uh, uh, briefly to advise Tom from a seated position. Ving Rhames plays a character
in these movies who, as far as I can tell, is sick of the bullshit. And they just let him sort
of sit to the side and type on a computer. But, um, four is awesome, but, uh, you know, these
obviously get bigger as they go. I mean, five blows the roof off of this fucking franchise.
And then six is just as crazy. Seven and eight, I'm sure will be nuts. Um, but I really enjoyed
four. I thought one was awesome. Um, well, and the new one brings back, uh, that guy, Henry Zerny
from, uh, like clear and present danger in that who always played like the suited villain.
So he was in the original Mission Impossible and they got him in the new one. He looks older,
of course, but I guess they're trying to connect it back. Who's he playing in the original?
He's kind of the main nemesis. He was always the nemesis of the hero for like five years
in the early nineties. He plays. He's like in cahoots with Voight in the first one or something.
Yeah. Yeah. So he's, he's playing Kittredge.
Does that ring a bell? Oh, Kittredge. Yeah. No, he's Kittredge. He's not the bad guy. He's a,
he's the agent that thinks Tom Cruise is guilty and then realizes that he's not. Oh, okay. All
right. I haven't seen that guy's great though. Oh, that's awesome that they're bringing Kittredge
back. Well, he, they sort of build to him in the trailer and it's like, I think as much as everybody
loves those movies, they might not remember all the characters going back, but, but I could be
wrong. I don't know. By the way, you go from Mission Impossible one, which is directed by
with a score by Danny Elfman outside of the original and Mission Impossible theme to Mission
Impossible two, uh, with an opening theme rendition of the song by Limp Biscuit.
You're out the door. I'm out the door. I'm out the door. I remember that having a pretty rough
soundtrack. What was the Metallica song from that one? I disappear, which is, I kind of like that
song, but like, it's not a movie that you want contemporary music in. That's not what you want.
You want like the, the, the orchestral suspenseful. That's what you want. You know,
feel like if you watch Indiana Jones and there was, Hey, hey, hey,
but you know what I mean? It's like, you don't want to watch Indiana Jones and hear like,
you know, pop songs you want, you want like the score. Hey, on the friend, there's a burn
and the screen has a fire. And there's a, the rock radio station here in Atlanta plays only
Rob Zombie. Oh God. And only Dracula. We're not, we're not sampling all his hits. It's either
Dracula and then every other channel is hardcore rap. I am wildly curious to see this Munsters
movie PG family friendly comedy Munsters reboot by Rob Zombie. I'm terribly curious what this
is going to be like. One of the people that I would say least qualified to direct a comedy,
a man whose movies have never had a shred of humor. And when they did, it was terrible. Yes.
But I don't, he, this is his dream project. He's obsessed with the Munsters. He's wanted to make
this forever. I mean, I buy, he loved it as a kid. I just wish he had some kind of twist on it,
you know, but we'll see. No name cast. I don't want to twist the lesson. They did a Munsters
twist. It was when Jerry O 'Connell, it was like the serious version. Oh yeah. I think that was
on two episodes. Yeah. Eddie Izzard who decided he was a man for that week so he could play
grandpa monster. What a terrible show that was. I saw a captive audience colon, a real American
horror story. I think we're about done using various combinations of the word American
horror and story in our titles. There are billions of them at this point. Jimmy Savile,
the title of it is a British nightmare. So it's like, there were so many great titles.
You should have been Jimmy Savile, man of the people. Like there were so many titles
they could have put that had this weird spin on what he did. Yeah. Anyway, go ahead. Sorry.
Uh, the movie is too long. As I said, oftentimes these things are, but it's really interesting.
It is about a young boy who in 1972 left his home in California and his family searched for him.
But eventually he escaped. It was a room situation like that movie Room where he was the kid. The
guy brainwashed him. He had Stockholm syndrome, et cetera. At some point he realized that he
needed to get out of there and it was when the guy brought in a second boy, he was sexually abusing
both of them. And the older boy who had grown up now in this house eventually snapped and said,
I need to get out of here, took the little boy and just ran and wound up making his way back home,
being reunited years later. Great story. Now in the background, there's a serial killer doing all
sorts of insane shit that they keep tracking. And you're like, why do they keep following this guy?
I don't get it. Serial killer turns out to be the boy's older brother who was jealous of the media
attention he got upon returning home from this house he had been sexually abused in. So said,
I'm going to be as famous as my brother and just started murdering people and killed lots of people
before being apprehended. One of the wildest stories I've ever heard. I don't know how I
missed this story. You know, maybe it's something they did on My Favorite Murderer, one of those
podcasts. I don't know. But really a good story and interesting. The only problem I had with the
documentary is that there was a made for TV movie done about this in the 80s, 90s. And Cora Nemec
played the boy from Parker Lewis Can't Lose. It's a show I used to love. They have Cora Nemec.
That's right. They have Cora Nemec and others from the TV movie read
actual like trial transcripts from the real people. So the actor who's now 50,
who played this guy as a boy is now reading his actual words. And they go to this
device a lot. The actors from the made for TV movie reading the actual quotes from the people
in it. And it's not done in any sort of like interesting blurring the lines way like the new
HBO Staircase does beautifully. So that really let me down. I would have cut out the, anytime
they're doing, as Joe and I always make fun of on this show, animation of documentary generally
sucks. And anytime you're doing recreations, it makes you feel like you're watching Rescue 911.
Makes the thing seem cheap. So the story is great. The execution not perfect, but fascinating tale.
Check it out. My last one is in the vein of Mission Impossible. I rewatched Burn After Reading.
I love it. I love it. This was always a movie that I thought was a really solid Coen Brothers entry
after this last viewing. I think it's literally one of the best Coen Brothers movies. It's
thanks to John Malkovich mainly and George Clooney and it's yeah, Francis McDormand's hilarious.
And Clooney, a bike with a dildo on it that always sunny stole so blatantly. Yeah, I know.
And I never really heard them give credit. I know Clooney is the most surprisingly funny in this
because you're like, I've never seen him funny ever. He's great as a dumb ass. That's his kind
of like him and him and Pitt. That's where they shine in comedy. Otherwise they can't do it.
Fantastic. Everybody is so good in this movie. Richard Jenkins, but the star of the what's her
name? Francis. I said her Tilda Swinton. Tilda Swinton is wonderful. But the star of the show
is Malkovich. I mean, just steals. I mean, it's just him and Sledgehammer, David Rash. Yeah,
Rash, J .K. Simmons and a great small part. The scene where they recap the movie at the end
is the jewel of the crown. And I think because I watched it as part of the Cohen brother marathon
at a theater over pandemic. Right. And it really like it's shown there, too. But I think it's
because it's start. It was so prescient about how fucked up the government would become.
Well, I never quite understood what the movie was about until this in this watching. And at
the beginning, when when Malkovich is talking to his his like Katonik father, Katonik father,
actually, I feel as my friend pointed out, the only person willing to listen to this man,
like because he has no choice. Yeah. Yeah. He says the agency just isn't what it used to be.
It's all policy and no mission. And then at the end of the movie, I was like, when this for some
on this watch, I was like, that line is more important than I've ever given it credit for.
And then at the end, he's like, you know, he's like, what did we learn here? And he's like,
what the fuck? Nothing. And in the off camera, you hear J .K. Simmons go, Jesus fucking Christ.
They have no idea what the point of any of it was. Yeah. Everybody is wrong about the other
person. There is no mission. When Clooney's going, I shot a fucking spoke when he thinks he
shot like the ghost guy, ghost agent, like none of it is accurate. Nobody has any information.
Nobody has any real goal. And then in the end, it's all policy. He's like, pay off this lady's
procedures, make sure that the guy in the coma never wakes up. And none of this ever happened.
Like, that's how we sweep it into the rug. And I was like, oh, that's, that's what it's about.
Like, it's like, that's what this has all become. It's very nihilistic. It's about how
just fucked everything is. Yeah. But but I mean, the scene, you're right, that that scene at the
end with the two of them is so funny. And then book ended and rivaled only by the scene at the
beginning with Markovitch coming in. This is a fucking crucifixion. I drink too much. Yeah.
No, I have a drinking problem. Yeah. Fuck you. You're a Mormon.
Yeah. Great stuff. And that David Rash is he's like the 15th lead on succession now,
just like he was in Burn After Reading. And I guarantee they cast him off this movie because
he's equally great on succession as the guy who says three lines per show,
but they're always like, classics. I love that guy. He's awesome. I actually might, if it exists,
might buy a sledgehammer complete series box set. I mean, when I was a kid, I was obsessed with
that show. I love that. And I love Max headroom, but I don't I remember Max headroom more than I
remember. Sledgehammer. Sledgehammer was basically, you know, police squad. Right. Yeah.
I was, uh, was it that that Zany? It was definitely slapsticky. Um, there it is.
Complete series, 20 bucks. Add to cart. Yeah. I'll, I'll, I'm going to take a, yeah, I'll take a dice
roll. And then here, how weird is this? The second Fairlane was the dice roll.
The second image available on Amazon, the second preview image is David Rab in front of a TV
where he's on the TV as Max headroom. Yes. That's very strange. Directed by David Rash. No,
wasn't Matt Fure? Who was it? No, it's a gag on the show. Like they have him as Max headroom on
TV or David Rash, whatever his name is. Uh, Bill Bixby directed several Max headroom was a digitized
head that did what I realized. I don't remember anything about that either. It was, it was way
fucking heavier than you think it was. It was like, it was like they were like solving like
fucking crimes and shit. It was not like a Zany show. Okay. Huh? Yeah. I gotta look both of those
up. I think even as a kid, I was kind of like this blows. All I want to do is see like the,
the graphic from the, you know, cause it, cause it was a Pepsi thing before that.
Well, I hated weird Al did, uh, Beverly hillbillies to the tune of money for nothing.
Yep. And he kind of parodied that style as well. And I always hated that video.
Well, the original video for money for nothing is that too. It was. Yeah. Yeah. I hate dire
straight. It's awesome. I love that song. There's like four dire straight songs. I love
that's more of a sting song than a dire straight song. You're you're you're all right. Uh,
I'm going to grab my notes on alligator, but introduce us to the film, Joe
alligator. And I want you to know people. I actually read up on alligators
while I was watching this movie because I thought to myself,
if I had to be trapped in a room with one, what would I rather be trapped in a room with alligator
or crocodile me and my vanity picked crocodile. They have a sleeker look. And I thought maybe
that means they're a bit nicer. I was completely wrong. Apparently alligator crocodiles are far
more vicious. Alligators are what they call opportunistic eaters, which means they won't,
if they're not hungry, they don't attack unless they're provoked. So if you ever are given that
choice in some sort of James Bond villain death game, uh, choose your fate, pick the alligators.
Um, alligator 1973, it might be 1970. Uh, this was a thing that they were doing a lot of back
then creature features, uh, where I see, and like, this is a thing they've been doing since
the fifties, but, uh, I guess the, there was sort of a resurgence of these kinds of creature
features in the seventies. Um, this one is about a baby alligator that gets flushed down into the
sewer and grows, uh, at, to an astronomical size, uh, due to growth hormones being injected into
dogs and then dogs being, once they're dead, being thrown into the sewers and then the alligator
eating the dead dogs. This is all very, very loosely explained in the movie. I had to do a
bit of reading to be honest. Well, yeah, I thought it was outrageous that we were seeing dog corpses
because it would be so easy to just have them depositing of these growth hormones that don't
like their toxic waste or something in the sewer and eliminate the dog element. I mean,
we're seeing dead dogs be thrown into the super heavy, heavy in, in my favorite sequence in the
movie with the pets, a crooked pet store owner. Yeah. Who goes to the Joe DeRosa role. Really?
Yes. Played by played by one of our favorite characters from deep cover, the guy that's the
I love also, he plays like as wick or something in one floor over the cuckoo's nest, but he's
very memorable in that movie too. Yeah. He has the voice of every Disney. There's like, he's,
you know, he's, his voice is probably in every Disney movie ever. He plays a crooked pet store
owner who goes out and kidnaps stray dogs on the street, then brings them to a doctor for money.
Who's doing questionable growth hormone experiments. And then when the dogs die,
this guy has to then take the dead dogs and throw them into the sewer. Yeah. So he's the first
killer. That's his job depositing of dead dogs. Yeah. So there's a great sequence where he's in
a sewer, throwing the dogs over the ledge down into the water and he's going, yeah.
And, and one of them hits like the slab of cement next to the water. And for some reason,
he thinks he needs to go down and pick it up, throw it down to the actual water. It's if anybody's
going to go fucking look. Right. And then it ends up him getting killed by the alligator, but
the alligator apparently has been feeding on these things for long enough that it's ingested and, and
assimilated these hormones in its own body. And now it has grown to prehistoric size.
Well, right off the bat with this movie starts with the, the dad who's like scared of animals
or something, flushing this baby alligator down the toilet. And then when 12 years later
appeared across the screen and we were about 30 seconds into the movie, for some reason,
that always makes me laugh at 12 years later or like a Cairo, you know, like when, when the
movie just started and you're already like lost that shit. Yeah. So the credits were barely done
and it was 12 years later. One of my favorite uses of that as in for love of the game, which is a
romantic baseball drama, Kevin Costner, Kelly Preston, and they do flashbacks within flashbacks
in that movie. You're watching a flashback and then somebody remembers something and goes back.
It's like a parody of this shit. But the movie, it, I thought it was, it had a sense of humor
about itself, which is important when your love of the game or alligator alligator. Okay. It was
written by John sales. John sales has long been one of my favorite writers of movies. I think he is
awesome. And he does his own thing. He makes small independent movies. He made what I consider easily
one of the 10 best movies of the 1990s Lone Star, which I recommended to Joe this week. I'm
recommending it to you now, Chris Cooper, Francis McDormand is in that too. You got Elizabeth Pena,
Matthew McConaughey, Chris Christopherson and a real nasty villain role, Joe Morton. The Lone Star
is amazing. It came out the same year as Fargo and all those, it was the year indie broke,
whatever they call it. And Lone Star got a little lost in the shuffle. It's not streaming anywhere,
but check it out. Anyway, sales for a long time has been a script doctor for big Hollywood movies,
like Apollo 13 and shit. But early on in his career, he did a lot of these low budget monster
movies and I think he makes them all really funny and interesting. And I love that it was set in St
Louis as a St. Louis and there's very few movies set there. I didn't even catch that. I thought it
was LA the whole time. No, no, they might have probably filmed it in a little bit. Sales is the
shit. He's great. He did early on, like he did the screenplay for Piranha, which I enjoyed. He did
the screenplay for The Howling the year after The Alligator, which is obviously a classic.
And then little by little, his career becomes just these amazing, very small budget character
studies. But he's a guy to check out and an unsung hero, check him out.
So we do the 12 year jump at the beginning, just so you know, that the alligator that was
flushed as a baby, it's 12 years later, it's now grown. That's the assumption, you know,
what you're getting into with this film, going to really at 12. And by the way,
surprised didn't even know it was in it. And for Robert Forrester as a hard -boiled cop,
of course, Robert Forrester looks so horrible in this movie. Jackie Brown was 15 years later.
He looks a million times better. He clearly got his hair plugs in, but all attention to it.
They do in Jackie Brown. Yeah. And they make fun of this movie. That's what I'm saying. They call
attention to it. And this, the, the, the love interest touch Robin Riker, I think is her name,
the actor's name. She touches his hair and he like gets angry. And he's like, I'm sorry. I,
I suffer from male pattern bald, the man with the thickest Chicago accent of all time. Can't
drop this fucking accent to save his life. Him and Farina. Yeah. They, they, they referenced it
several times as another guy who like basically tells them you should do a comb over. And like
that never happens with stars today, mostly because they all have fake hair, but it's like
you rarely see a balding star and you would never ever have it called attention to. And they call
attention to it in Jackie Brown, where he admits he got hair plugs and they call attention to it
here where he looks like shit. He also looks very hung over in this movie, which is very hung over,
which is suiting for the role. But I also think that's where he was at. This is like,
he's kind of on the down slide in this. This is, he's entering into his anonymity.
Yeah. He's literally up against a large plastic alligator head that they just move along a sewer.
So this is one of the strong suits of the movie. This is not a grand slam movie,
but it's fun and it knows what it is. And as Pat said, it doesn't try to be anything. It's not.
And for what it is, it's, it's, it's fairly well done. There's some great sequence. There's a
sequence at the beginning where an alligator trainer gets attacked and it's cut and shot
and put together so well that I was like, Jesus Christ. Like I had to rewind it. I was like,
how the fuck did they make that look so real? Yeah. So it has its moments. The practical effects
for the most part are good. There's some cringe moments where they put a life -size alligator on a,
on a miniature set and it just walks around. So it looks like a giant alligator has walked through.
That's pretty bad. Yeah. And there are a couple daylight shots of the alligator head
and body that don't look great again. And I've said it before people, you're going to have a
monster. You got to make the monster glisten. If the monster is not wet, it doesn't work.
But for the most part also goes for making love, by the way, I agree. Listen to the
glass is not wet. You're not ready to go. But for the most part, all the down sewer in the sewer
effects, which is where most of the alligator action takes place. They're pretty good. The dog,
the dead dog corpses are effective. They're gross and they look real. But the thing that I think
works best about this movie is they take time to make the characters real. Like, like they make
a real character. Like he, he, he talks about how his partner got killed and it wasn't his fault,
but everybody thinks it is. And, and you know, his, his past relationships and these things that have
nothing to do with the story whatsoever that make him a three -dimensional character.
Like when he snaps, when he starts to get close with, with the female
reptile specialist lady who's helping him figure out this case. And she, like, he hears that the,
that the reptile, the big game hunter that they hired to try to find this alligator got killed.
And he's like shocked and she puts her head on her shoulder and she goes, I understand how you
feel. And he just snaps at her and he goes, don't try to understand me so quick. And like,
it's got nothing to do with anything. You're just like, it's like this moment where you're like,
this guy's got some fucking baggage and they used to take the time to give you that.
I mean, I, that to me, that's, that's sales. He, he wanted to do these intense character studies
and tried to inject little moments into horror, which it's all it takes to make a horror movie
memorable. And so few people do it. You know, you got him at the beginning when he's going
into the pet store to get the new dog. And that's how you meet the pet store guy for the first time.
And he's like talking about how his dog ran off and you get attached to your dog. And he's like
being really affectionate with the new dog. You're like, just little stuff like that adds a lot,
having a weird pet store guy. You know, you made the better call Saul reference earlier,
but it's like, it's the same kind of thing where it's like nine times out of 10, the writer would
have the doctor paying some kid out in the back alley to like, you know what I mean? Yeah. Some
you forgot about in two seconds, having this whole thing where you see the pet store owner
actually give a shit about animals in his office and then have this underside to him where he
goes out and treats them terribly. It just adds so much to all of it. Like,
and it takes what's essentially a glorified B movie and elevates it to something where you're
like, okay, I could see this playing in a theater and, and being passable. And you know, you know,
being your Saturday night popcorn romp. Well, it really steps up to when they pair him with
Michael Gazzo, who I had to look up, but he's the guy with the giant eyebrows from Godfather two.
Yeah. And it's the, it's the rare double gruff partnership where both partners in investigating
the crime are gruff, crusty old men, but they have a great chemistry and they're fun together too.
And then you also have, hold on. I'm blanking on his name.
Yeah. You got a lot of great, as you pointed out when we were watching it.
Oh, you got Jack Carter is the mayor, which is Carter, Henry Silva in there as well.
Henry Silva. Her name is Robin Riker who was on, she was on, um, get a life. Yes. Um,
well, Tarantino says that this character that Robert Forster is playing heavily inspired
Max Cherry. He's the same guy. No, I know, but it's why he wanted Robert Forster to play the
role in a show. No, no, I'm saying, I'm saying I see the connection of the characters, not the actor.
Yeah. Well, I, I, I scoffed at that at first because Tarantino always says kind of stupid
like that. But then I was like, no, I bet it was. Um, I love Forster in this, the guy Lewis Teague,
who directed it. This sometimes when you look up a director, you really see how brutal Hollywood
is, but this guy did alligator, Cujo, Cat's Eye. So clearly they're just letting him do animal movies
or movies. Alligator, Cujo, Cat's Eye, Jewel of the Nile, the huge sequel to Romancing the Stone.
Then collision course with Jay Leno and Pat Morita. And it all came to a halt.
The gravy train slowed way down after that. Um, one of my favorite scenes also in the movie was
when Henry Silva is trying to get Intel from some neighborhood kids on if they've seen an alligator.
Oh, so he buys them beer because they're, they're supposed to be minors. Every kid has a mustache
and almost full beard. Um, I loved when Robert Forster has like a map of the under map of the
sewers basically. And there's a plastic alligator toy that he reveals and he looks at it and he
goes, where are you? So any moment like that is always going to make me smile. I mean, it's a lot
fun. Sidney Lassack is the actor's name. Okay. That plays the pet store guy. His character's
name is Luke Gutchell. What a great name. Um, yeah, it's, it's, it's, uh, I'll tell you my hog is up.
Oh, and then by the way, last but not least, Kane Hodder plays the alligator. That's correct.
That's correct. It's not a humanoid alligator. They got Kane Hodder crawling around the
streets. This, uh, alligator is on shutter now. I would be shocked if Joe Bob doesn't do it before
the end of the season. Um, they also have alligator too, which I have heard is terrible,
but I've never seen. I'll probably give it a try. Did you know this alligator too, made exactly
11 years after alligator one. And this movie ends with the new baby alligator going into the sewer.
I wonder if they planned it like that, if they were like, no, let's really wait
like everyone turned down the pitch. And then finally they were like, it's been 12 years. We've
got, we've got to strike again. It's a, it got terrible reviews. Part two, one is, is, has become
at least as a, as a fondly remembered as like piranha, but maybe not as much as the howling.
And I think that's about what it deserves. It's a mid -level really entertaining B movie with a great
Forrester performance. Uh, alligator to the mutation stars
Joseph Bologna. Oh no. Oh no. And D Wallace. So you got horror movie royalty in there with D
Wallace, but Joseph Bologna that's as detective David Hodges.
I'll bet Joseph Bologna has played detective David Hodges four different times that a character
named that in four different movies. All I would think I've really seen him in is blame it on Rio
where him and Michael Caine go to Rio to fuck underage girls and cheat on their wives.
This is also not a good sign. The director and writer of alligator to do not have Wikipedia
pages. That's never a good, no, no. I know James Cameron wrote piranha to as an early way into the
business. So maybe that one's cool. I don't know. I'll tell you Walsh, I'm going on Amazon right
now. I'm going to buy alligator. I want to add it to my collection. I enjoy the arrow version of it.
I'll tell you in a second. Alligator. You got to get the blue ray. Of course you need to see this
thing in high def. I remember the, uh, the garbage pail kid, Al E Gator, which was just a kid with
an alligator head, not an arrow release, but a very, very cool. Um, this looks like a Korean
release. Very cool box art. Um, 20 bucks plus shipping.
Folks, my name is Patrick Walsh. This is the, we'll see you in hell podcast. I'm not going to
force you to listen to Joe make an online purchase of a DVD. Uh, thank you for coming.
I apologize. I thought people would like to always, uh, do we have official ticket links yet for the
coming? I promise it's coming. I promise it's coming. I promise it's coming, but it's official.
We are doing a live show September 10th in New York at the, uh, black cat coffee house, which is
right literally next door to Joey roses. After party bash will follow at Joey roses.
Um, ticket link will be available soon. We will make it exclusively available first
for the, we'll see you in hell folks. And then before we open it to the public and there's only
going to be about 50 tickets available folks. So I have a feeling they'll go very fast and that'll
kind of that be that. But, um, but that's, that's the, uh, that's the inside info on that.
I mean, what are we trying to do? We trying to be like a, uh, start a cult around us or what? Why,
why are we only booking a 50 50 seat spot? That's all we got.
Well, I mean, you know, you only want to complain about it now and make people think we made a bad
decision here. I mean, I, I was expecting Madison square garden. Yeah, no, it's a great little spot.
You know, theater at Madison square garden, not the main usually do 50 to 60 seaters. And I know
it's, it's right for our show. And it's right literally next to my bar where we're going to
have a massive after party. So, yeah, all right. You know, we're in it for the funny, not the money,
baby. Um, very excited about that. Very excited to get to New York, see Joe, see the shop, uh,
nothing really to plug, but you know, where to find me, Twitter and Instagram, the Patrick Walsh.
Thank you to Emily for all you do check us out at see you in hell pot on Instagram. There are still
people who pop up and go, I had no idea the show is still going on. So spread the word and thanks
to all of you who do. Thank you folks. Uh, go to Joe DeRosa info .com for tickets, links, uh,
and info about my upcoming shows starting in July. I'm hitting the road pretty hard. Fairfield,
Connecticut, San Francisco, California, Los Angeles, California in August, Atlantic city,
uh, September, San Diego, uh, Somerville, Massachusetts in October, Wilmington, North
Carolina, Las Vegas, Nevada for Skank Fest, November or Michigan, uh, and more dates coming
soon. So come on out. And if you're in New York and want to come to Joey roses, it's