I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell,
and when the shine of your screams
becomes like a dream, I'm a dream, should know I say,
I'll see you in hell, you know I'll see you in hell,
you know I'll see you in hell, you know I'll see you in hell,
We're here with a special Q &A episode part one of two
Paddy Walsh and myself back at it again
Hello, everybody. We've gotten a tremendous
Tremendous amount of questions via patreon instagram twitter etc
I'm more excited to just tear into them. We don't do segments on these special apps. So let's just get into it Joseph
You ready?
I'm ready Pat
First question
Yeah, I think these are in order or that might be the last question or the first. I don't know but anyway
Milan asks
If given the keys to any franchise you desired minus comic books and Star Wars
Which franchise would you choose and what would you take be either as a reboot?
Or legacy continuation? I would choose in a heartbeat creep show
I think the
continuation of it through the series is
Occasionally hitting the mark, but not overall getting the job done unfortunately creep show to me
Is the greatest horror trilogy of all time meaning creep show one creep show two tells from the dark side
I love anthology horror more than I love most things. I
Would love to to be at the helm of creep show or tell some the dark side or
Tell some the crypt
Now you mean specifically the shutter animated series creep show, right?
The yes, I'd like to take over the animated holiday specials of creep show
With the budget of upwards of a hundred dollars per app could all be yours
You know what I'm gonna say
Weirdly just because I don't think I would care to have any of these big action franchises is the godfather
They had those two shows about the making of it. It's odd again
We had a pretty bad sequel in godfather 3
Godfather 4 has been discussed for decades to cap real was involved at one point
I don't know they haven't done enough to really damage that franchise
I think they could pretty easily do like a next -generation
And make it pretty awesome. I think enough time has passed. That's my two cents. All right
Michael asked Joe. What are your thoughts on the bad religion album into the unknown?
Michael I own the album. I bought it on vinyl. I found one of what seemed to be fought four available copies on the internet
Of the long out of print disgraced bad religion album. I paid
a
Embarrassing amount of money for that record. I
List I bought a pristine copy with all the original inserts and everything I listen to it once
It is terrible. I put it in the sleeve. I put it back on the shelf. I will only use it now to brag about never listen to it again
What's the deal? Is it too poppy or something? I wonder if they're really hated. They tried to do a prog rock album
They're follow up to their hardcore skate pump debut and everybody was like what the fuck are you guys doing and
It's not like oh they were good at prog rock people just didn't get it
I thought that was what was gonna be when I heard it and then I was like Jesus Christ
All right, anyway
Kevin Kevin asks who would win in a movie battle royale fight
Gladiator meaning Russ Crowe I assume
Jason meaning Jason Indiana Jones creature from the black lagoon or the xenomorph from alien
PS mid -summer stinks does a great cup
Well, you're gonna immediately take off the gladiator indie Jones the creature, right?
I mean these are just men
No chance of winning this fight
So it comes down to Jason versus alien, which is a pretty decent movie. I must say
I give it to alien Joe. I give it to alien
Jason's got some root strength to them, but that alien's got the acid blood. It's got more arms. Yeah
Best that's Jason gonna do is managed to cut off. I mean the aliens are taking down predators sometimes that Jason ain't got a standard chance
Yeah, true. I would like to see the flick
All right, that sounds fun
Codex asks hey guy. Hey guys English guy here. Oh, sorry since you guys are both single and free
You folks ever gonna do a Europe tour or what?
Also ever seen demons and demons too by Lumberto Bova. They would make a great episode
Um, I have seen and own in 4k demons and demons to demons and demons to and 4k
I have on pretty good authority is going out of print so I'm leaving it in the wrapping, but I like those movies quite a bit
Yeah, they're great movies. I've seen them both
I'm gonna buy the 4k's and how you said that
Yeah, I mean we would go to Europe if we thought more than three people cared
I mean if there's if there's a demand to come over to Europe we're coming to Europe. I mean nothing
Nothing would stop us from doing that. I don't know. I don't know I'm no idea when I go into
Going to London, Ireland. I mean it would be we would be a blast. We would love to do it
But yeah, I don't know if we got the listenership
I have talked to a few fans from across the pond
But I don't know if we got the numbers frankly if there's any way codex to get us. Yeah, some kind of
Idea of the interest over there. We would certainly consider it that's sincere Rachel
Maybe if we start doing an episode by episode doctor who podcast?
Just thousands of episodes
Incarnation actor black adder. Don't even know what that is, but we'll do that one
I'd love to go to England and just do an episode about how much mighty Python stinks
Right in the heart of it right right in front of one of those guards at the castle
Rachel asks favorite harflick favorite sci -fi pick favorite villain or demon well
Heart flick. Let me just cheat by the way. Let me just cheat. I mean that this is five questions in one
I agree and we've also answered it many times, but in case you're new to the show Rachel
exorcist
creditor
Darth Vader
Yeah, my favorite horror flick
Holtergeist my favorite sci -fi flick, you know, that's gonna vary, but I think I got to go with
Aliens
My favorite villain or demon
I mean Jesus Christ
They're hard ones I'm gonna say Annie Wilkes misery not my favorite but the one that's popping into my brain right now
I love her
Rick Hayton why are you always Hayton Rick you guys are the only good film -based podcast true not a question, but true
My question is if Pat or Joe ever considered living in the Pacific Northwest once the country goes Mad Max in the next year or ten
also
Where would you guys go in general once things go more to shit keep up the hate for the mediocre guys?
Yeah, I would I would yeah, I like the Pacific Northwest absolutely beautiful. Uh, I don't know anybody there, but sure
Excuse me
And then I know Chalmers big and tall men's shop is a is a big outlet chain in the Pacific Northwest
Also, would you guys go and I don't understand the second part though. Would you guys go in general once things go more to shit? What does that mean?
Um, where would you guys go in general? I guess meaning like oh the Pacific Northwest is a blaze. Where would you go if you had to leave the country all together?
Oh, I already know I would go to the Netherlands or Ireland. I've already made my mind up about I gotta be to be honest with you
I don't even need it to go to more to shit if I can figure out a way to just go without losing all of the income I make
I'm gonna fucking go. I don't give a fuck anymore. Yeah
Yeah, I kind of agree
I would live in the Pacific Northwest. I would probably live in Seattle. I like it there
And as far as leaving the nation
You know, why don't I go live with Joe and Ireland? I have family there
I can't understand what they're saying, but it might be a fun to start over
I like Ireland and you can drink yourself the death pretty easily
Yeah, then we can have a real a real banshee's of initiating moment where we stop speaking
Oh, I would imagine that'll be within the next five years where we have a stop speaking to each other incident
I'm throwing bloody fingers at Pat's door
Yeah, somebody walks up. Oh, you guys aren't talking what no, we're great terms. What do you talk?
Let's come on to Joe having sex with my donkey. I'm like this didn't happen in the movie Joe. There's there wasn't a sex with the donkey bit
Um, it's Pinkstone ever gonna be on the pod the fabled Pinkstone is as elusive as max headroom
Cngs. Yeah, yeah, we I've talked to Jimmy. He he wants to come on. We've only had two guests ever ever to date
We haven't announcement about a live show coming very soon and that one we might have a live guest on or a guest on it because it's a live show, but
Yeah, we would have Pinkstone on Pat and Pinkstone get along very well and
We just really have the opportunity is
Below it says can we also please get a Karen Kilgareff episode or a Matt McCarthy
I haven't talked to Karen in in quite a while, but due to no
Beef between us. I just haven't seen her
Um, but next year we just don't day
I haven't oh, did she take that? No
But I also don't know if she has the same difficult about that we lost we lost touch not because of anything
With the pandemic as you do you kind of lose to you know, you kind of it was a lot we lost track of all yeah
Well usually one person in a friendship is gonna be the one who reaches out more and
Unfortunately in a partnership with me and Karen or Joe and Karen. There's no real person like that in the group, you know
We're both kind of standoffish
But we love all these folks. We just don't normally have guests, but we'll consider it. We we have enough sparkle on our own. It's how we see it
Uh, and they're absolutely yeah, yeah, for sure. We love these people
Eric asks in the early days of the podcast you guys rift about ending up as two bachelors living together golden girls style
Any chance this could happen. I think we just said it's gonna happen in Ireland
And if we were lucky enough to have this be a reality TV show, what would it be called? I would pay a hundred dollars a month on patreon to watch that show. We'll shit
Let's have Eric fund it. You're an EP air
You get a couple people willing to pay a hundred dollars a month on patreon that ironland conundrum is fixed
Yeah, we're already paying more than the studios
Little political jab
Uh, um, no, I think if people would would pay for something like this, there's no diversity unfortunately enemy and joe reality show
So that's not great. Although joe does claim to be hard Egyptian
Um, yeah
Arab
Um, what would it be called joe? Do we got any ideas?
Well, well, we'd call it the hog house obviously. Oh, sure, sure
Right. I was thinking maybe two broke men
Two broken men
Two broken men. I like and you put the Ian you put the in in parentheses so then they know it's right on two broke girls. I like that. Yeah
Uh, Ryan asks how do actors director slash directors that haven't worked in a while survive? What what what is this a TED talk? I don't fucking know
Um, they do podcasts. I guess uh
Like Richard Kelly is Richard Kelly living off down. He dark our residuals is Michael rapaport working at the bodega
Um, rapaport does rapaport works constantly. He's got stand -up podcast
He's I just watched justified which was a few years ago, but he was on a season of that
He's always a character actor and stuff you might not see
Yeah
But um, yeah, that is how actors directors who haven't worked in a while survive is residuals and they're going away
That's that's the issue. I mean you can read about this stuff
We won't waste too much time and I've talked about it on the pod too, but
Yeah, Richard Kelly has directed a movie and at least a decade at very least a decade
And yeah, it's down. He dark our residuals. It's he probably got paid money early on to like
Pitch on big movies and like you know right up drafts of I know you wrote domino and stuff like that
Um, but it's it's down to residuals if you're not working
That's about the only way movies coming in because I don't think he's rewriting scripts that we're not seeing
I think his career is just pretty much over unless somebody pays him to do tiny dark coats
That's what these are so important. It's our it's our retirement fund. So here you come
Sean asks this is interesting Sean says hey boys after listening to the Indiana Jones episode
curious if either of you remember trailers for Temple of Doom at the time
And if it was promoted as a prequel to Raiders or not
I don't think it was I think that was just a little
wink to the to people that might have noticed or not. I don't remember it ever being promoted as a
prequel and in fact
I don't remember anything ever ever being promoted as a prequel until
Star Wars and when when phantom menace came out I remember that's kind of when they said like this is called a prequel
I don't know if I'm correct in that or not, but that that's the first time I remember it, but
That feels right to me when I saw the new Star Wars was the first time I remember a prequel being marketed as such that feels right to me
And this is cool Sean plays Indiana Jones at the stunt spectacular at Disney World. Oh
Awesome. That's really cool. I'm going to go on stunt spectacular. Don't watch out for those fire bursts
Yeah, maybe we come down and watch the Disney I like that it's a Disney world too. That's the better of the parks
I'll only come down if
Sean will whip me out of the audience and then tore me into his waiting arms. I'm going to say
I'm going to say this out loud
The Rachel Rachel the balls on this Rachel lady she asks a three -part question then slips in a second question
outrageous
But it's and it's also not a question. It says someone would be poisoned after 20 days
I think Pat would live and get away with it. What the hell does that mean
That I don't know unless it's in response to us living together or something
Oh, look maybe Rachel had a few pints before sitting down at the patreon page. I don't know
Um Michael. Yes. Yes
Inspired. Let's just alternate Joe and make it easy. I'll do one you do one. That's the way to do it
That's instead of each of us reading each one in you
Michael gas asks inspired by Pat which sexless movie would you like to have seen get the touch of Bob Gucci only
You know what I'll say
It's one of the most sleazy sort of sex feeling movies of all time spring breakers
But if I'm gonna have Gucci on come in and just make me an x -rated sleazy disgusting version
That's what I'm going with harmony karen's classic spring breakers
I want just a a version that makes me sick to my stomach
Michael Madrigal an old friend of mine from college and still as a friend what is your favorite what was your favorite video store chain
Uh chain or mom and pop I I can answer chain and mom and pop west coast video was the best as far as the chains went in my opinion
There was something really fiery
Exciting about west coast video. I think I did a lot to do with the colors that was bright red and bright yellow
Uh, and then mom and pop videoville was one
Was that was our store that was our place was videoville it was awesome and I already gave my opinion on into the unknown
Um, my favorite chain was called far more
Uh, which was just a grocery store, but they all offered on Friday nights six movies for 99 cents
Um, I don't know how this could have been a a a feasible market strategy
But we went in there every Friday and rented six movies for 99 cents
um
I also love the feel of a blockbuster. I worked there for many years
I don't have a lot of hatred for them even though they let me go on ceremoniously
Well, I'm also destroyed video destroyed mom and pop businesses as we know that maybe maybe that's the reason you hate them versus your own firing
destroy the family video
Family video was our local chain place with the saloon doors and you went into the back and found the porn section and so forth
That might be a worldwide chain to family video. I don't know
Um, it's your turn. Sorry. No
You're right. Damn it. Sorry. Too fat to skate
asks what's your most sentimental possession and can I have it
Um, Joe, you're a much more sentimental guy than me. You go ahead and I'll think
My most sentimental possession and I can't believe
Uh, I had this in my bar, but it's my Star Wars 83 machine
um
You know that machine was certainly the biggest investment I ever put into my love of video games and nostalgia or anything like that
That game meant meant and means an incredible amount to me because of how enamored I was by it as a child
I have the tattoo of the death star from that game on my bat on my arm and I paid for that tattoo with a hundred dollars
My mom gave me for my birthday once because I said I want to
Get something significant for my childhood with this money
So that's it
Uh, for me even though I haven't had it since childhood. It's it's my most sentimental possession as far as this type of thing goes that we talk about on this show
and uh, no you can't have
Pat
Um, I truly believe that just about anything in my life if it was burning in front of me. I wouldn't bad and I
um
My life has been set up for so much failure and loss that I just don't take these things seriously or personally
however
um
Something I'm looking at right now that I love is that when the Queens of the Stone Age came to Saturn Night Live when I worked there
Josh homie
gave me a cowbell
Uh, Will Ferrell came out and played a little sister. He was the host. He played the cowbell with them on little sister
And Josh home gave me a card that said thank you for making this something to remember
Patrick
Signed it and gave me a cowbell and I kept that and I love it. It means a lot to me. It's very cool
Um, and it's a reminder sort of in this world of where I'm interacting with these monstrous celebrities that like
Somebody I truly idolized could take time out of his busy day and schedule to do something nice like that
You know, he didn't know I was a huge fan of the band. That's all
Boss
Brandon asks we'll pat ever going to taste buds please
Yeah, we just we only ever do in -person guests, but if Pat
Ever comes back to New York ever again. We will try to figure out a taste buds recording
It's an easy ask would love it would love it the little clips always make me laugh out loud. Um
Tony glossic will you guys ever do an episode on the sleep away camp franchise?
No, I would I own sleep away camp unopened and it was just thinking I would love to rewatch it
I haven't seen it in 20 years. We've done so there's no way we have not discussed sleep away camp on this show
We did sleep away camp because we talked about the big ending with the dick
We a hundred percent talked about that
I think it's more like 50 percent, but somebody will let us know maybe we did maybe we didn't
Um, but I don't think we did what does this mean?
He asks we'll see you in hell shits on taste, but oh he likes this better
But instead of just giving a nice compliment. He has to turn it into a competitive thing between two things that I love
I thought that meant that we we would shit on them like in a fight or so. I didn't understand it. Well, maybe
Anyway
maniac
I think that's supposed to be
What are your top three underrated slash hidden treasure albums?
Any genre um
Good question. That is a good question. That's a tough one. That's uh, that's why I side because I was like Christ
I'm gonna have to really think
Uh my problem is when I get it to name the three
I always try to think of the definitive three and I need to just start focusing on ones that I like and that fit
So I'm gonna say one first
Because I heard a song from it the other day and I was like god damn this is a great album that nobody knows about
telekinesis is the band
And the album is called you turn clear in the sun
They are a pop punk band this album not really pop punk more like an early weezer type vibe
Uh, this album came out in 2011. I have named it wrong. It's actually called 12 desperate straight lines by telekinesis
It's a great like power pop punk kind of album check it out
That's one
That's one then you can alternate
I yeah a run DMC tougher than leather is considered
The
By a lot of people like where they start to dip. I think it's a masterpiece album. I think it's them
Taking on a more modern at the time sound and I think
It doesn't get anywhere near the credit it deserves and how amazing of a record that is
I love it. Um, I am going to mention
Dwight Yoakum's gone
Uh
An album about a breakup a divorce whatever you want to call it. I believe his breakup from Sharon Stone
He was definitely batting out of his weight class at this time
But um, I saw Dwight Yoakum early on in my stay in Los Angeles
And I was standing in the audience. He's my favorite modern country singer by a thousand percent
And I turned to my right and realized I was standing next to Dennis Hopper
And I didn't know what to say to him, but I was like wow, this is amazing
And then he turns to me and he goes you a Dwight fan and I said yes
And he goes two blessed country albums of all time
Number two is Dwight Yoakum gone
And I said what's number one and he goes I ain't telling you
Super weird interaction
But uh, I got to agree not enough people know Dwight if you want to just listen to his best of you're gonna hear a thousand great songs
But his best overall album is probably gone. Joe
Uh, I will go with another rap pick ultra magnetic MC's critical beat down
Just a groundbreaking hip -hop album
Real fans hardcore fans get it and understand why it's so important
But as far as a record that should be getting mentioned
On way more lists and things that shaped
innovations in the genre
Uh, the approach to to what what we now know is independent and underground rap music
Horror core
Anything that's
You know character driven in hip -hop
Cinematic sort of hip -hop, you know all that stuff
They did it all first on critical beat down and it and it deserves more praise
I love it um, and I will shout out a band that has gotten a little bit bigger
But still not quite where they belong always always with a double V instead of a double
You
Um is probably my favorite sort of modern
Pop rock band female singer
I just love all three other albums greatly. I think my favorite of theirs is anti -socialites
But you can't go wrong with any other three albums. Check them out
And I'll shout out a friend of ours uh band
Uh vince april's cross control
They just put a new record out called try and survive which I have on vinyl here
And uh cross control is a if you like traditional classic
Awesome aggressive hardcore. You're going to love cross control and they're a band that
People are enjoying but deserve their
Firm footing in the annals of hardcore music and I don't say that just because they're friends of mine
I think they're an incredible band that that hardcore fans should be
Listening to as a whole
Yeah, I'm excited to see them live. I have not yet. All right
Uh, I think you're most
Christen asked most unexpected TV or movie crushes not that the actor is unattractive
But just maybe characters who aren't supposed to be a hard throb or romantically interesting her example is lieutenant Dan. Okay
I
Joe's really enjoying the lieutenant Dan
Pick um unexpected TV movie crushes
I mean for me, I got to say holly hunter and raising Arizona
Um, it's not that she's not supposed to be attractive in that movie or something
But she's not playing like a babe or uh or uh
Whatever you want to call her she's actually playing somebody who's sort of unhinged
But I have always been deeply deeply attracted to holly hunter uh particularly in the movie raising Arizona
I gotta tell you lately I keep thinking about having sex with that mom from alph
Since we talked about it episode two ago. I can't we can double date
I'll go with alph and you take the mom being rebooted by Ryan Reynolds by the way bringing it to his network that he has
I saw that it's not rebooted
Just showing the old episode. It's like only Ryan Reynolds could get it in national
Why can't I say national get a national announcement for bringing alph reruns to his stupid network
Uh christian asks hey boys fuck Mary kill balky ed cizerhands wet bandits uh
Well, I'm gonna kill edward cizerhands. It's just too god damn creepy
Uh, of course you fuck the wet bandits. They're crooks. They're gonna know how to give you a good good one
And then you marry balky hard to gold
Yeah, I mean just you get an immediate threesome with the wet bandits. So that's appealing
And as much as I like edward cizerhands, I can't stay married to somebody with weapons for hands
So I gotta kill him which I guess leaves me married to balky which is great
Next live show in chicago. Please we've done a live show in chicago
Two places we have done a live show
Well, maybe he just wants another one. That's okay. All right
Regis was bugs. Thank you. It was a good time. Thank you
Michael Berks asks have Pat or Joe ever watched the endless no
Or any of Justin Benson and Aaron Moore heads other cosmic horror films. No
Not haven't even heard of them would love to check it out
I in fact will cosmic horror sounds like a lot of fun so
uh
Brendan
Raiden
opinion on louder milk if either of you have seen it. I've not seen it, but I will also look it up
Yeah, I haven't seen it. I like Ron Livingston. There's a clip that pops up in my reels every day where he's ordering coffee in an amusing manner
That's annoying to me, but maybe I'll check out the show. I don't even know where to find it
Uh, Matthew Arobco asks Joe have you any plans to tour Western Canada in the next while specifically maybe Alberta
No, I'm Toronto's coming up. I was just out in um
uh, where's uh, what is that damn city uh, out west there
Oh
Rice I can't believe I'm forgetting the name. I'm sorry, but uh anyway, I was out in western Canada
A few months back, but no not at the moment, but I hope to get there and please keep your eyes peeled. Thank you for asking
uh Warren
Joe, what is your favorite horror theme video game? Easily uh devil's crush uh, satanic pinball game
For the turbo graphics 16 worth quite a few bucks at this point. I'm very proud to own a copy
Pat what is your most memorable movie theater experience
Um, um, I've talked about selling this show, but far and away. It's June 11th
1993 open ignited Jurassic Park. I mean, just the fact that I remember the date um, but when they finally pulled back the little
red carpet thing the loud ash and let everybody run to the theater
Uh, because they weren't assigned seats at this time my feet were off the floor wedged between two people
I was like carried several feet um, never experienced anything like it at a movie theater before it was fantastic
Christian Reynolds asks what do you think is the biggest Oscars oversight? I don't put much stock in award shows myself
But I'm still upset that Val Kilmer wasn't even nominated for tombstone sure
There's a million of these um
The biggest to me and I don't even hate dances with wolves like a lot of people do
But I think dances with wolves beating good fellows for best picture is gotta be number one
And I think driving Miss Daisy beating do the right thing
Which wasn't even nominated is number two
Uh, I'm gonna go with
Pacino not winning
For I think you got nominated for the godfather and I think you got nominated for Glen Gary
Didn't win till sent of a woman
So woman is great, but but for him to get overlooked and those other two was crazy to me and then um
Uh, Denzel not winning for Malcolm X, but winning for training day. He's great in training day, but Malcolm X is
I mean it's masterpiece. So
Uh, that's my take uh Dakota asked how are you guys feeling about the upcoming DC
Universe under James gun
Especially Superman leg is I've lost all interest. I'm Superman and Batman doubt
I'm burnt. I could I could care less at this point. I hope they do a nice job with it
Maybe my interests will reignite, but I couldn't I couldn't have less excitement in me about it
Yeah, obviously I have no interest, but I like
The Guardians of the galaxies more than most of these type of movies. So maybe he'll do a good thing fingers crossed
Melanie St. George inquires what are your thoughts on David Gordon green doing an extraceous trilogy
Look, I think I'd really love David Gordon green and his comedy work with
dynamic bride I think you know that we all hear it
We'll see you in hell hated the new Halloween movies and I certainly don't have any high hopes for this new extrace
Did you see the trailer? It's in front of Oppenheimer
No, no, it's only in theaters in front of Oppenheimer
Look the posters are scary
They look like a throwback to the original
You know, but so did the Halloween thing that he did so you know look I think the problem is bigger than
David Gordon green, you know, you got a bigger issue, which is Blumhouse and Blumhouse. Yeah, I'm sorry. I don't think they're making a good product
So I
Hope it's good. I do like a lot of what David Gordon green has done, but I did not like that Halloween thing
At all
So you know, we'll see I mean, you know think what the extraceous is
There there are three already doozy sequels to this thing and then a
One decent season TV show one who gives a shit season of the TV show
It's not much worse you could do at this point
Anyway, Thomas Ili
I'm not going to read the whole paragraph, but just have you ever read the Colin Trevor row star wars do with the fate script
No, I didn't read it, but I did read this the plot of it and yes, I did think that it made a lot more sense
as a sequel than
uh
What they ended up doing
But it's public knowledge at this point that what they ended up doing was rushed in order to meet the needs of the board of investors
Which is fucking heartbreaking
But that's what they did
And that's why I'm glad Dave Filoni and John Favreau
Have their own little piece of the franchise and are trying to write the wrongs of the
Cinematic mistakes they made
There you go
Corey Freeman asks in tradition of when you review entire franchises
Did you do episode that discuss originals and their remakes such as don't a dead 78 and 04 the blob 58 and 88 etc
Um, it's a great idea. I think we have done the don't of the dead remake. I think we have done the blob remake although I'm not 100 % on either
um
But yeah, the only issue with that is like it requires twice the homework
You know when we do a franchise thing
We got to watch like we got to do 12 hours of homework or eight hours instead of just watching one movie
But um, yeah, totally. I think that's a great idea and I'm sure we'll do one at some point
All right
Max well asks
boys
What do you think your strongest
Lift is out of bench squat? Come on guys
Oh, it's a weight lifting question. Yeah, I mean
Yeah, um, it's probably squat. I do a good squat. I don't even understand the fucking question
I'm not trying to be a dead
I just
Can I read another one?
Georgia
Devon boys, if you had time
If you had them for more
Jesus Christ if you had them for one more project as a collaboration and they came back in their prime
Which duo would you pick from a horror film in a writer director collab
Stephen King and John carpenter
De Palma and Hitchcock
Um, well these are all just these are all just directors except for Stephen King
He directed maximum overdrive and these aren't duos like these people never work together co -directed it with cocaine
But yeah, yeah, I'm not quite getting the question, but I mean, I would really love to see a Stephen King John carpenter movie again
absolutely
Also, Joe, thanks for turning me on to Ramsey Campbell from years ago. I don't know who Ramsey
What am I not remembering
uh
I look King and carpenter are still around like I would just like to see them work again. De Palma is still around Hitchcock is the only one that
That uh
Yeah, I don't know. I'd like to see King and Romero again together. I think that'd be good
Um
Eric Irwin oh wait no burger and tobe hopper. Yeah, there you go
Eric Irwin asks curious if you guys are still planning on doing a special app on interesting alternate casting ideas for films
um
Yeah
Yep
Yeah, we'll do that. We'll do that
I did pitch pat a special app the other day
Hey
He said uh
That my idea gave him anxiety
So we did a fair most things give me anxiety so we didn't do that one
But maybe we will do that one but that wasn't the recasting thing we'll we are planning on doing the uh
Yeah, the recasting thing
All right, Joe the news salsa windfall single is a certified toe -tapper. Thank you
You guys have made me fall in love with why I appreciate movies
That's this is about us now not the band and being a collector of physical media all over again. Thank you
My lady and I have now dedicated Saturday afternoons on the back porch to drinking the sauce and blasting the pod
Thanks fellas. That's very nice. Thank you. Thanks, Grant
I love like a state image. I like a statement one. You don't have to sit you don't to answer it
Matthew toddy asks the two of you have just collaborated on your first film and it's a comedy masterpiece who is starring in it alive or dead
It's easy who Joe uh lemon and in math out
Oh sure they're the greatest comedy duo. That's as good as it gets
Like you know they inherit a long lost son played by Chris Farley
Oh wow and they have to take a road trip together the three of them
I don't like the road trip part. I like keeping them in one place
I was just meant well there's nothing more road trip than uh
Uh
Nothing more one place than a road trip. They're in a car together as well. I'm saying. Yeah, but um
The posters them packed in and Farley's got him kind of pushed up against the windows because he's had he's fat
Are you laughing at that
Yeah, yeah, I'll laugh at that
He wouldn't like that, but I'll laugh at it um
I want to know about Patrick's music projects from when he was growing up
For instance pta
Hey
Was that an anagram and was there are beetles on Sullivan moment for him wanting to pick up the instrument
Yeah, my band the pta was not an anagram although the first show we played the guy was like
So what is that pussy titan s and I was like, oh wow. I didn't even think about that um
But no it was supposed to be like the police like
A sort of nerdy um
Group that was flipped into becoming rockers
Uh, so it was just like the parent teacher association
I
Uh
Got my first guitar. I think because my friends were into guitar really just a standard reason and I always was into music
I learned to play by teaching myself
And I'm not amazing by any means more of a rhythm guitarist
Um, but yeah, it was a lot like jukebox hero
I had three friends that all worked at blockbuster video
I walked them one day and I was like we're making a band baby and we did pretty well considering
That was our origin story for guys who work at blockbuster um
Ecrats asks what did you think of under the silver lake and have you tried to rewatch it?
I absolutely love under the silver lake
I own it and as I pointed out to Joe several of the scenes take place right by his own
When he lived in Los Angeles
I never saw
It's great movie. Don't know why
Just had zero interest in seeing it, but maybe I'll watch it another time
Uh
Kenton
Excluding NYC Chicago and LA rank your top three cities in the US with the best food
Uh, well, I'll filly
Easily Austin is a good one
With the best food and then San Fran I would say it would be the three that I think have really nice nice food options
I'll let your answers stand Joe. I don't have anything better than that not Missouri having been there this past weekend not Missouri
Okay
um
The Gore lock speaking of Missouri asks how do you fellas? What's one of your guilty pleasure musical artists bands or albums
Geez, I mean, I don't necessarily love the term guilty pleasure
Two of my big ones are obviously gin blossoms
Uh, and Abba I love the music of Ab
Geez, I don't I guess offspring is usually my go -to when I'd say it's my guilty pleasure. They still get me going
I still get excited when they put a new record out not to buy it necessarily, but that there will be that one
Banger on it and usually there is so I'll go with the offspring
Uh
Mac asks what are your opinions on the Howard Stern show? I think Howard Stern is a fucking hack and a half
Well in a bully and a hypocrite
Uh and Scientology I couldn't care less about Scientology uh
It is what it is um I read the two huge books that came out five to ten years ago on Scientology going clear
Which was made into a documentary and Scientology inside Scientology
Thought they were both completely fascinating um, I do think at some point the master was kind of it
Paul Thomas Anderson's the master, but I do hope at some point they make a origin story for Scientology movie
um
And it's very hard for me to call any religion stupid. I think all religions are in some way stupid. Our religions in some way have value
Um, Scientology is more controversial than most, but I don't think that it's origins or that stranger than any other religion
Um, and I really enjoy the Howard Stern show. I love listening to his interviews
I love that he does the long form
You know, whether he's the best at it or not
I just think he's the only one whose celebrity sit down for three hours and
Uh talk freely about things. So I get what Joe's saying, but I'm a fan of the guy
He's a master interviewer, 25 people in another room feeding him things on a computer screen that he never gives credit to
Yeah, he's a fucking genius. Anyway
I
Sorry, go on. It's your turn. No, sorry Greg Wyman asks have you rewatched nope?
The review missed a lot of plot points and I wonder if a revisit is in order
Pat, can I take this nope? I just
please yeah
I wanted to do this like lawyer style pet can I take this if I may your honor?
I will never rewatch nope
I
If plot points were missed it was because we didn't feel the need to discuss them and a revisit is not an order
That's how I feel sometimes you just don't like something. I mean, uh, there are movies
I liked a lot less than nope. That is a movie that if somebody was like hey, I'm putting this on
I wouldn't be furious with them, but um, yeah, I don't have any desire to see it again
you
Steven Scott asked joe what's your favorite original twilight episode twilight zone episode and why
minds the fugitives
Pat what's your favorite new criterion you got from the sale?
I will have to say bad lands is pretty incredible. Yes, it is and damn you for inspiring me to buy so many
um
I'm most excited to watch the new film in Louise 4k. I love that movie
um, I'm sure really Scott looks great in 4k and that's the one
I'm most excited to watch and after hours in 4k the score says you movie of course
um
God
Favorite twilight zone you know, I used to be able to answer this very quickly
I think the howling man is always going to be my favorite
You know, it's certainly not the
sharpest
episode as far as like a social commentary is concerned
It's one of the ones that goes a little more just for fun horror
but it's super fun and super creepy
And it's just a great episode, you know a guy manages to trap the devil
and and all he has to do is convince somebody don't open that closet because you'll let the devil out
And he tells his story as to how he managed to trap him and of course his story is about him discovering people that had the devil trapped
And they said don't let him out and he did
And now it's his burden to keep it trapped and now this
Person he's telling not to do it will do it and so the commentary is just the
The Pandora's box and and crippling curiosity of man
And uh how it will lead to our own demise, but it's just an awesome episode. It's a lot of fun. I like that one
Love it
Yeah
Okay, where is my oh god damn it Pat
Can you read the next one? I fucking clicked I wanted to look up something
From one of the questions that I clicked off the god damn thing by accident damn it
Damn it Ryan Martz asks
Yeah, when is Pat's taste buds episode gonna happen need some of that husky voiced ruffian talking at me about a keen walk
Uh, I'll do it
You know when I'm in NYC. I will do it
Abram Wright inquires since you both collect physical media
Is there a recent movie that went straight to a streaming service that does not have a physical blu -ray available that you would like to own
4k hubi Halloween maybe
Um, good question. I feel like
You know the big netflix titles each year are going to criteria on lately
It's not like I need to own who lose hell razor in 4k
But I'm sure there's a title that I could think of
Um
Not hubi Halloween either
Maybe not. I mean the Irishman. I'm glad that came to criteria and that's probably
You know one of my favorites. We are gonna get to a point where
Movies are only on streamers and not available to own and that will suck however are we missing that much with these streamers
I would argue maybe not
Joe do you got one? No, I can't I can't think of anything
That I've you know gone to try to purchase that wasn't available
Yeah in some capacity uh, whether it's
Especially anything new
So no, I honestly I can't really think I well
You know, I watched I
Subscribe to screen box and I I was been watching the toxic Avengers
cartoon the toxic crusaders which is actually very funny
And I went to buy it and it's out of print
And it's only on DVD and because it's out of print the DVDs are way more than you want to pay for DVDs
So so there's been a few things like that. I once tried to buy the swamp thing tv series like the complete series. You can't really find it
Um, so yeah, there's a couple things but nothing like quintessential um
Matthew asks I know you're both fans of Ron Livingston and the fairly brothers work
But I don't recall you guys ever talking about louder milk
Yeah, we never we never saw it
Uh, but maybe we'll check it out with louder milk. It's the second louder milk question
Let's go to the next one would love to hear the movies the boys wish they would have made or starred in
Well look up Matthew to Sama and see if he created the show louder milk. That's what I'm curious about
Um
What movies they wish they would have made or starred in
For me, it's just this it's the smaller movies. It's you know, it's hand in our sisters
It's Glen Gary Glen Ross
It's stuff like that. I really like things that address characters that are character driven that are simple that are direct
And speak to the human condition
Uh, that's the kind of stuff where when I watch it, I really you know
I could watch the empire strikes back and be blown away by it and enamored by it and enthralled and
And I will be
But it that's never something where I'm like it's so gargantuan. I can't even imagine it
It's when I see something that's a little smaller
That somebody pulled off. I'm like and and it's about the characters and it plays a little more like a play
Which of course Glen Gary is based on play
That's what I'm like. Oh wow. That would be very cool to you know, that's those are mine
And those are also the movies I'd like to act in
Yeah, I was kind of thinking boogie nights just to see all those amazing actors in their hey day, you know, like a young Philopsy more Hoffman, etc
um, and just a 27 -year -old
Paul Thomas Anderson coked out of his mind, you know, be a fun set to be on see all the egos and everything
And I was thinking of Glen Gary as well just to uh act with those titans be a lot of fun and there's no women on set which is nice
um
Bob Yuzaka asks what are your favorite mid to late 90s Quentin Tarantino
Reservoir pulp inspired or knockoff movies there were a bunch
There were a bunch my favorite by far is go
Which is like the teenage pulp fiction. I fucking love go
Um, and not a lot of people know it somehow, but it's a great movie. That's mine for sure
uh
Joe where you would destiny turns on the radio man. I well know it the one I always say I don't know if it's 90s
Which is why I pause, but um
Well, I always like things to do in Denver when you're dead, which is a very old Tarantino. We
fun movie and uh and and and um Jerry and Tom
She's way more of a man it
Mammot rip off but but uh love it Jerry and Tom
Um
When are we getting a movie done by you guys even a short i'd i'd go as far as they never
Probably never
I get never now you never know you never know
Matt Garcia asked what is your favorite anthology movie and or series preferably horror themed
Also, can we get a sport -a -loose app would love to hear your analysis? I don't know what sport -a -loose is
Neither
Um and my favorite anthology movie or seer I mean
Series and I haven't even seen them all but I got to go the OG twilight zone
my favorite anthology movie is probably
The original creep show
Yeah, I already said creep show and then tv shows so I was known as my favorite tv show of all time so
Andrew asked by the way the question before that was from Seth sorry Seth
Andrew asks why did I like comedy movies before
But now I can't stand new comedies and think they're all horrible. Andrew, I'd say this is more of a you question than an us question
But um, you know, I guess because a lot of comedy look comedy is
Is is always going to be reflective of society at a certain time. It's always going to be evolutionary
and um
You're gonna hit points in time where you don't like the comedy
That is reflecting the society you're living in and and
You know that just it might be that you're in one of those times right now
Which is why it makes it so special
When something truly unique or irreverent comes out
Which there is stuff out there now that you could point to I'm sure
Maybe this damn louder milk everybody keeps talking about but
uh
You know those things can't stand out if everything is just great and I also don't think that
I think if we lived in the 80s and we're experiencing all that as adults in real time
We'd be like rolling our eyes like oh cool another beach tit comedy like I'd be like this is stupid man
You know, so it's all it's all perspective
But it's not just you we talk about this every week comedy is going through a very very bad time
Um john wolf asks what are some dream double or triple I guess bills for you too if you were planning a movie night
Um, you know one of the best ones I ever saw was a simple plan and fargo at the new Beverly about five years ago
Because I feel like everybody there was seeing a simple plan for the first time
And a simple plan plays like fargo without the laughs. It's just brutal
And they those two wound up being a perfect
complimentary evening at the movies
Uh, I'll go with the you know not to be repetitive but I'll go with the creep show trilogy
That'd be a great triple bill. It'd be a hell of a night out and it would stay exciting and fun
And I'd love to take somebody to that that's never seen any of them and
Watch them experience it for the first time
Uh
What I actually did see though was was evil dead too and cabinet in the woods, which was pretty excellent
Uh, yeah, I mean phoenixville
At the famed uh movie theater there
That I am somehow blanking on the name of even though I grew up next to it. Jesus Christ my brain is done
Oh
God, what is it called you guys know what I mean the blob theater I've talked about it before
Dirk asks why don't you comment on each other's
Corns more often
What does that mean movie corners
We comment on each other's all the hell are we talking about here? I think
He's asking why when I say like oh, okay, I watched home alone this week. Why doesn't joke comment on it as well
Uh
I think the only times I don't comment on Joe's picks are if
I haven't seen them that's probably the reason more often than not and I probably watch more obscure stuff that Joe hasn't seen
Uh, so you know, Joe's probably just not listening
To be honest with good chance. I'm talking now. He's saying particularly. I don't do this uh, I don't know
I look at it as it's Pat's time to talk about something
It's not my time to
To jump in with my own review
You know, if if I also had watched it recently then I'll jump in and say like okay, that'll be one of my entries as well today
But the whole point of the movie corner is to let the other person kind of talk about something they've watched
And just kind of talk about it like that's why we have picks
And it also breaks up the show. It's like otherwise. It's it's the same thing the entire show where we're just
Both discussing a movie like the movie corner shouldn't turn into what the back half of the show is you know what I mean
That's my thought you're always welcome. You're always sure the voice and opinion
Uh, Robert Haynes asks is there a single streaming show or a movie that will be talked about 10 years from now or did the movie industry get
Destroyed for nothing in a four month span in 94 we had usual suspects because you know heat and seven
We'll never see that again, and it's beyond depressing
Yeah, I mean it doesn't seem likely that we'll get that run of great movies again
But you never know they probably said that in the 80s too, and then those movies it came out in the 90s um
Streaming is there a single thing that will be remembered
I
Don't know I think movie -wise probably not and I think show -wise, you know
There's some streaming shows that would rank among the greats perhaps, but was it worth it? No, obviously not
Uh, I think your answer pretty much sums it up. I don't think uh, I have much to add to that um
Okay, there's just too much content now. That's the one thing I would add. There's too much content you we have
We absolutely have runs of memorable movies like this we just can't keep up with any of it or
Uh
Single any of it out because
It's there's too many streaming things. There's the theater. There's it's just too much. So that's my take on that
Uh, Samuel asks what is your favorite horror movie premise that you wish was better
Was executed better
What is your favorite comedy premise that you thought was funnier
Um, no, and then do we like death metal extreme metal? No, I don't like death metal or extreme metal
stay metal and
Thank you Samuel. You stay metal too
Uh
Favorite horror movie premise
The exorcist sequels
The two prequels they did were really cool ideas like we're gonna go back to when father marion first encounters presuzu and they made
Well, first of all they let Paul Schrader do one who I love Paul Schrader, but he's gonna be like the horror is in the
Reflection of a man and when he looks in the mirror, you know, you're like Paul
What a fucking demon into the thing please about Catholic guilt. No, Paul. It's not that
I don't always have to be about Catholic guilt Paul
Uh, and favorite comedy film premise that you wish was funnier
Uh
I think you could and I like these movies
Well, no, I'll go with summer rental summer rental is always a movie. I want to be awesome
It's not funny. It's got two laugh out loud gags and then it ends with a fucking boat race
And that whole movie should have been
There that movie should have been money pit at the beach
They're in a bad house and everything's going wrong and instead
They're like no, we're actually gonna kind of make it about how John candy has to enter into a boat race
You're like what is this
I'm gonna make my answer for both nothing but trouble if nothing but trouble had gone the Texas chainsaw route and been a great horror movie
I would have loved it
If it had taken that insanely perfect comedy cast and done something better with them
It might have been a great comedy
But you're left with kind of a fascinating disaster. So that would be my pick for both
Um, Lee Ellis asks would you ever entertain the idea of one epa month zooming in a hellion to talk movies with you
We did that with Dana Gould and I don't think it was any
Uh, slight on him because he was great on the show, but it didn't seem like fans liked us having a guest to be honest with you
Um, most of the comments were negative
Also, do you think the steward Gordon movie space truckers could ever get a bigger budget remake?
No, and just how do you feel about the original? I've never seen uh space truckers, but I love steward Gordon
We've talked about him often on the show
Uh, I'm open to having more guests on here and there. I think people
Negatively reacting to it is a little harsh. We're not changing the format of the show
We're just kind of breaking things up here and there. So and it is interesting to talk to these people and get their perspectives on work
They've done
Uh, especially at a live show. So uh
That's my take on that space truckers
I think who could get remade if
And only if some hot shot
You know like James Gunn has to would have to be like I love space truckers
And I got the rights and I'm going to remake it if it's not that then you can't do it
Uh, or would just wouldn't get done. I mean
Uh, Ryan asks when will Joe finally start releasing his solo video game podcast
Uh, I don't know the we we had something that looked like it was going to happen and then it didn't
Uh, I'm hoping something will be coming soon in the meantime. I'm trying to keep the collectors the show and yellow videos coming on Instagram
uh
And uh
You know, those are mainly records now and music, but I'm I I will get into video games on those but uh
Keep your eyes peeled if look if I'm gonna do a video game thing
I'm gonna I need I want to make it unique and I want it to be
Released properly and in its proper place and I apologize for teasing it and then they're being this long hold up
Uh, dick dirk dirk we already took one from you, buddy
Uh, I love eels. Uh, I didn't I didn't know
I like eels to I've met the guy friend of mine as a friend of his I haven't read his autobiography
Yeah, but I I like that band and I would recommend Mark Lanigan's autobiography. I feel like rocker by
Uh, I want to say though as a rule guys. You can't ask two questions. There's like so many questions from so many fans
And like we're already have to make this four parts literally four episodes
Uh, not in a row which is great
Not yeah, not in a row, but we got to put the Facebook questions aside
And do two more full episodes. So we get to those so
We can't we can't answer two different questions. So thank you. It's nice of it to be excited
So I sound like too much of a grump. I don't mean to sound like a grump. I'm just trying to be fair to everybody. That's all
We understand you
Thank you
Fellas feelings on smashing pumpkins. I always hear Pat mention how
Nirvana and those bands. He's a huge fan of
I've never heard him talk about sp specifically um
Well, and then it goes on from there as smashing pumpkins. I have never loved
I don't like them as much as sound garden. I don't like them as much as Nirvana
I don't like them as much as a lot of those men
I don't even like them as much as stone temple pilots to be honest with you
I do like them more than say red hot chili peppers and other bands of that era
I think they have some great
Undeniable just all -time all rock classics. I just don't find myself listening to them much
I find Corrigan a wine and a boar and I don't like his voice is my biggest problem with them
And I really only think like a lot of those bands they have two or three great albums and then a bunch of shit
I agree. I agree
Uh, I met Billy Corrigan on the Jim and Sam radio show
okay
he was
Funny, but kind of a dick and like he he he did it under the guise of I'm just messing with you man
But they had a new album out and I go
It was he was there to promote it. I go Billy. I'm just curious like which
Version of smashing pumpkins does the new album sound like the band has been through so many
sonic
In carnations, and he's like oh, oh, you're going to be one of those fans
Oh, great. Let me ask you the question everybody asks and I was like wow
Okay, dude, sorry dildo
And then he's like I'm just messing with you man. So whatever he's fine. What am I gonna be bad at Billy Corrigan
He's a whiny bitch. No, you should have done is is licked a napkin and then pretended you were trying to wipe a spot off his bald head
Well, we were on zoom
But uh, sorry Billy. I thought I could have gotten
Joshua asks uh, what do you guys feel what are your what are your feelings on the new James Bond series
I couldn't care less
About any franchise as little as I care
About the James Bond franchise. I've I've never even seen a Sean Connery Bond movie. I don't give a shit
What they do as big as big a film buff as I am and even though I own the entire collection on blu -ray
I have not seen half the James Bond movies and that I don't even understand how that's possible, but
I gotta say I don't care really either. I like I've seen one of each person's you know
I've seen I've seen some Connery some more some everybody some Dalton some las and bees
Well on las and bee
But um they're all just kind of the same and I think mission impossible has beat them at their own game
I don't care about who they pick for the next one. I think um
You know my favorite Bond film you're asking here is probably
I thought Cassino Royale was about as good a reboot as you're gonna get
And as far as the old classics. I probably love uh gold finger the best
All right, yeah, I just don't think that I don't think we're your guys for James Bond
Yeah, I uh, I feel the same. I got nothing on that one Kieran. Oh, no, that's you sorry
Um Kieran asks I watched and loved fatso are there other films that are personal favorites but seem to get zero credit
Yeah, I do those on this show from time to time um
And as this Joe we all we like to shout out lost favorites since we have Paul Schrader in the air
I'll I'll do one of mine which is affliction if you want just a miserable drama about depression and
How it gets passed along. I love affliction
uh, you know, I know he's not a
A mainstream favorite these days, but I think there are a lot of Woody Allen movies that
Got panned and I don't understand why like scoop with scarletial handsome
I find to be delightful and very very funny and a classic
Woody Allen movie like like meaning like him playing Woody Allen in it and he plays a magician who's kind of bumbling and he's it's very
He's very neurotic. It's very funny
And I'm always and and anything else
With him and Jason Biggs and Christina Ricci
Is in my opinion a moment as good as one of his movies can get and it got
Fucking panned and I just I'm like I don't understand why
That's Tarantino's favorite Woody Allen movie. It's an awesome movie. So those are my two picks
um
Eric
Says if you gentlemen could each write and direct a biopic of any American politician
Living or dead and you could take as many liberties with the material as you desire
Who would be the politician
Who would you cast in the role and what's the filthiest thing you would show them doing in history um
Look I I liked Clive Owen as uh Clinton in the many series. I actually thought I did a decent job
But he was wrong for the part and I think you knew it. I'm gonna say McConaughey Bill Clinton
With the cigar in the Lewinsky Puss
Uh in the oval office
Uh
I would like you know what all right. I would like to do
A J F K
About what a piece of shit
That guy actually was they never make that that version of it
Yeah, because of the tragic death
but like
I want to make a Kennedy they did it in uh in blonde the mon row biopic
They definitely had a shitty version of jfk and that one
I would do that. I'd have a murdering Marilyn Monroe
I'd have his
Rum runner father
pedaling illegal booze and
I would do that and I would make them look like hard hard people and I would cast as jfk
Uh
Was it living or dead? I would cast Marilyn Monroe as jfk as an extra fuck you
That's what I would do
Okay, the corpse of Marilyn Monroe proper
Hectic daily on great name asks was wondering if Pat would ever consider doing a solo podcast or maybe one with guests
I love Joe and his other podcast and all you guys appearances
Solo movie corner is great, but I feel like I need to hear more of Pat. I love this guy. It would be awesome if it were to happen
um
I think all the time about doing a solo podcast on my own um
But I just don't do it. This is already kind of a bit of a time suck in a good way get to see my old pal Joe
But um no, I'd like to do one for sure. It's just
I haven't um
And I do enjoy a lot doing the solo movie corner you guys can listen to that of course
That's an hour of me rambling on various topics
but thanks hectic
Martin asked what's your biggest ever laugh from sign felt the show but no putty
I got married
The great I've said it before on the show the greatest line ever in all of sign fell is
And what was all that stuff about artistic integrity? You're not an artist and you have no integrity
It's just such an amazing line
That's
But biggest laugh
I would that's my favorite line
biggest laugh I got to give to are you crazy?
This is like discovering plutonium by accident
When he what he says he won't do the threesome
Yes, yes
Yeah, my biggest laugh including putty is feels like an arby's night
That's the hardest I've probably ever laughed in my life um
But my other biggest
I gotta think it might be a newman
You know something to do with newman
um
Viall weeds I'm gonna one when he eats the broccoli
Yeah, he forced somebody to eat
Yeah
Um, there's really too many to count
I mean that since I saw my mom this weekend
I still my mom wasn't even a sign felt watcher
But the hardest I ever saw her laugh at the show was when
um
Jerry's talking about his girlfriend who doesn't like George and George is like what did she say exactly
And Jerry goes I don't like him
And his delivery of that line had my mom laughing for like an hour
And I remember it very very well. It's it's the very funny delivery
I also love when Jerry laughs when he says let's go watch him slice this fat bastard up
And that is your mint episode
That is just coffee into his mouth to hide his laugh
Um, all right next up
James asks let's say you were both freaky
Frighted with each other. How would you spend the day
Walking in each other shoes. You know, I would just have Pat
Smile for once
I mean this would be the worst movie ever me and Joe switching bodies and just taking on each other's
Red threat level anxieties
Uh, so they would be different anxieties, but equally difficult to deal with
Um, I guess I could learn what it's like to run a bar. That might be fun. It's not
It wouldn't be fun
Oh pickens ass is there a piece of physical media either of you regret trading or selling
Yes, please do an episode on Argento's deep red the 4k is stunning
I know you'll likely shit on it, but I still dream of some Argento apps
I love Argento and have a lot of his 4k's so I will I will I'll watch that soon
And I like deep red
Uh, he's a physical media that you regret trading or selling Joe
Well, every video game thing I got rid of as a kid because I didn't think I'd care anymore
Uh, all my star wars toys
Uh, and and and also a huge one my VHS collection, you know, I was very
I wouldn't say shortsighted, but you know
Back then you didn't know that media would be worth anything
Uh, or that you'd ever want to revisit a lesser
In quotes form of it, so
You know, I got rid of my VHS collection. Why? Because I started getting DVDs
I'm like, I don't need these bulky VHS tapes anymore. It's kill to have that right now
So yeah, well, there's a lot of regret ditching
Unless the VHS are worth something. I don't think they are. I probably wouldn't care, but
An entire basement at my parents house of VHS
And I said to my dad at look
If you want to get rid of them, that's fine, but you have to let me know and give me the opportunity to go through them
And he didn't he just dropped them all off at goodwill
So um, yeah, there's probably something in there that's got some value
But does there are any VHS worth anything? Oh, yeah, they got it. They got to be new probably, right?
No, it's just you know, it's print
There are Star Wars VHS copy, you know, because they have a fox red label on them
They're worth a lot of money like it's you know, it's stuff like that
Um, I don't care so much for the value. I just care for the
The coolness of it, you know
The integrity of it also anyway, go ahead
Um
Hat years ago you stew asks Pat here's a go you said you had a lot to say about that first
animated spiderverse movie, but you held back because Joe thought you two might do an episode about it. What were your thoughts?
Joe seems pretty adamant about not doing the spiderverse movies at this point
Um, I love I thought the first one when I saw it gave me a horrible headache. It was annoying
I couldn't stand it and then when I watched it again
I fucking loved it to the extent that it is one of my favorite superhero movies and it's not even close
I think
It's got a similar level of invention
To it that look that all those guys stuff has the 21 jump street movies, etc
Um
Whereas even if I'm not loving every minute of it
I'm just kind of in awe of how much time and effort and passion they put into every frame of their shit and spider versus awesome
I think the villain sucks
Kingpin is a worthless villain
And I thought that's not true
In at least in that movie he brings nothing to the table. He's just a big fat mobster. There's nothing to him
um
And then spiderverse to I love but like the less and that's simply because of the running time that that style of animation that sort of like crazy
Hit you over the head like something going on and every inch of the frame is a blast but not for two hours and 45 minutes
um
Still I love what those guys do. I think they're operating at a completely different level of creativity and they make the other superhero shit look
Beyond lazy it makes them look pathetic to be honest with
I'll never watch them. I couldn't have less interest as far as spider -man animation is concerned
I love the old cartoons from the 70s and 80s
Uh, but that's that's kind of where it ends for me
Hammy asks what's your favorite 4k transfer of a classic movie a horror movie and an action movie
Uh predator for action or total recall
uh for horror
Um
I don't even know if I own a 4k hard for 4k classic. I mean the it's a wonderful life is really
Just a gorgeous gorgeous transfer uh
Well, I'll put predators a predator can count us horror and then and action total recall
Yeah, I won't divide them, but my favorite uh older like classic transfer has been marathon man
From the 70s. I just think that a the movie is a masterpiece and the transfer is just incredible um
Other than that flash Gordon, which I saw for the first time
I think that if I was honestly asked to show somebody
The glory of 4k and what it can do. I might throw on flash Gordon. I think it looks incredible in 4k
That's a good call um there's a creep show 4k. I gotta see if it's worth grabbing
Re -bought this movie eight fucking times at this point. So
But that's nothing but like true raves about the new creep show 4k. Okay
Uh
Sarah asks will taste you in hell crossover app possibly people are interested. Yeah, you want to take it Lauren
Lauren curry asks reboot of heat with a black cast actors can be living dead or too old and can you do it in under 60 seconds?
I mean you gotta go
Denzel
um as deniro as deniro. Yeah, and
And well
Denzel would also work as butchino
I think you gotta have Denzel's deniro you need Denzel doing the whole like
You will not I am not going back to jail. I you know what I mean you will give him another chance like you know like
What about Sam Jackson and the butchino rule?
Uh, that could be interesting. I also think um
Tiffany had a
Hey
What's uh, what's the kid from uh, because he had a great dick
Who's the kid from uh
I'm blanking on his name. He's in he's in get out
He gets possessed and get out. You know, he's in a gluia
No, no, no, not the main guy that side guy Keith stand film. I think he'd be good in the butchino role
He's got an intensity to him. That'd be very interesting. Yeah, I like him to
It would be great. I would love a black heat. I'd love latifa all a black heat
I'd love clean latifa in the Dennis Hayesbert role
I think that'd be awesome
Yeah
Love it
Let's put a John David Washington in the Kilmer role. Oh, yeah, get him with get him with this. Yeah, we're talking baby
All right, um, this next one is infuriating Nick says are you too aware that the hellians don't care about the movie reviews at all
Nobody listens to this podcast for the reviews some of us might have started watching for the horror reviews
But the patrons are here for the Joe and Pat friendship you wouldn't lose one patron if you stop reviewing movies
Kind of the worst part of the pod. Oh, thanks Nick
Then Robert says the reviews are the best to play play before
Yes, the reviews are the best part and it's not even close. I hear five or six quick reviews of things three minutes each from opinions
I respect you'd rather hear a 20 -minute story about some horrible customer service experience
Not me. Don't ever stop the reviews
Um, so look
We're gonna do whatever we want probably it seems to be working pretty well for people
But thank you Nick for shitting on us. I agree
Nigel Faulkner
Sorry if you could go back in time to see a film for the first time on opening weekend and a packed house. What would that film be
It's either anchor man, which was the most unhinged
I've ever heard an audience or it's as I mentioned that first Jurassic Park showing
Star Wars
There you go 77 how on earth do you both dislike space balls? It's a classic well, we we
I don't think we said we disliked it
I think we said it in hindsight it kind of stinks
Which it does oh yeah, I always loved it till I watched it over the pandemic as an adult man
And I was like this uh
These jokes are bad
And you know that I don't want to feel that way. You know, I love John candy. I just don't like it anymore
What's your opinion on Ted lasso the most boring who fucking cares
event and television fucking history
That was designed for people that not only eat white bread, but our white bread you're fucking white bread
I don't know if that's a fan you are
or not, not, no, yeah, and Pat
You said you would check out cunc on earth
cunc she's funny. Did you did you get to it in what's your opinion?
Yes, I was completely unfamiliar with cunc on earth
I did I was not aware that was a joke title. I was just like what is this shit and when I watched it
I found it very funny. Yes, it is
Good British awkward fake documentary comedy. She was very funny. The show was very funny. I recommend it
Brad Pitt boy 88 asks what is your favorite Brad Pitt movie and why
Love the show. Oh my favorite Brad Pitt movie and probably performance is seven unquestionably
I'm gonna go with killing them softly
Okay, love them in that love the movie and that's tied up with
Once upon a time in Hollywood is oh, yeah, that's a tough one to beat
Let's take a break here and come back in the next episode part two of the Q &A
We've been at it here for about an hour 20 or something like that so
We're gonna pause
And we'll be back with more Q &A
We'll see you next time
We'll see you on how