Welcome to We'll See You In Hell, the movie podcast you know, you love, and you're familiar
with. My name is Joe DeRosa. Usually you build, you know, you know, you love and you're familiar
with know and familiar with mean the same thing. Yeah. I mean, just, just like you don't
try, you know, take the intros. I don't, I don't know what else. Don't let me every time
you're just start. I know. I'm sorry. That's fine. Go ahead. Give it a shot. Let the let
the folks peek behind the curtain. I'm fine. I'm fine, Joe. See, it's not so easy, is it?
We're today we're here today to discuss wrong turn one and two.
Wrong turns one and two. I've never seen them. Weirdly, like Joe's mom loves horror. My mom, to
my knowledge has never seen a horror film. But her and her husband, my stepdad, love the wrong
franchise. And I was never seen them either. Especially watching part two, which is really
disgusting. I'm like, and I got to talk to my mom about what made her like this. And also, I feel
like I should recommend more horror to her because there are better options. It's these are these are
a wild. Well, we'll get to it later. But we'll get to it. But it's a very popular franchise. And we
thought it was deemed worth discussion. I've had all six of the original films on my shelf for
my mom bought them for me for Christmas. Like six years ago or something. I didn't even know
there was six. I thought it was only five. Because the set I asked for was parts one to five. I was
like, I got to get these in my collection. It's a franchise I'm unfamiliar with. And then my mom and
then I opened it, there was a six. And my mom was like, Yeah, there's a six. So I got you that one,
too. And she's all right. So these they've been sitting on my shelf for about six years.
And I was happy to finally dig into them. So we'll get back to it. In the meantime,
I mentioned last episode, I had another scary stuff. I've I'm holding back a belch a gas,
which makes you sound like Woody Allen. I just realized if you're holding it.
Anyway, I
had a scary stuff. We've talked we talk about this usually every year when it comes around,
but it's here. And I believe you have another two days to get into it if you if you missed it.
Criterion 50 % off sale is happening on the Barnes and Noble website and in the Barnes and Noble
stores. I just hit it up real good. The other night. I got some good titles. Do you hit it up?
I didn't because I had just they just had the sale through the Criterion website. So I had
I had gotten everything that I needed. And I still I still have every Criterion offering. And I've
been watching them a lot lately catching up on stuff because I haven't seen so many of them.
But my recommendation, I know we have some fans and listeners who work at Barnes and Noble,
because I've met at least one. But the Criterion website, I like to go there because you're
supporting them directly. You know, it's certainly I like to buy their over Amazon. Barnes and Noble
is kind of hanging by a thread, I think. But if you buy from the website to the benefit is that
every, I think $500 you spend, they give you a $50 gift certificate, which is a really good deal.
And it never expires. So you can kind of keep it in your email for the next time they have a sale.
But I love the Criterion brand, you know, I love everything they do. I love that they've kept the
price essentially the same. I don't know what sort of maniac buys these Criterion things at
full price, you know, everyone I know just waits for the sales. But I imagine their their graphs
for like the year just look like skyrocket up and then immediate skyrocket down for the whole year.
Yeah, yeah, that's that's it's like that thing in a Tommy boy when he's where does your face hurt?
Not here or here, but right here. Yeah, exactly. Yeah, that's what they're great. So I got what
I get. I got the innocence. I got quite on. I got the brood. I got deep cover, which I'm very excited
about. Excited to watch. Yeah, I've seen I saw it a long time ago. I love deep cover. I had no idea
it was in Criterion. Yeah, I got video drone. Finally. Excellent. I got the new Citizen Kane
4k Ultra HD. I got repo man. And I got a 4k TV. Yeah, you do. You should get one. And then I got
you notice the difference. We've never really talked 4k. No, I can't tell the goddamn difference.
I just I just Citizen Kane was one of the only things I ever was like, oh, a 4k black and what
I mean, like, the greatest movie arguably ever made that looks stunning on a DVD. Like, let's see
how far we can take this thing, you know? Yeah, just seem like the ultimate version to get. And
then I got two copies by accident of all that jazz. I got to bring one of those back now.
Or gift one, gift one. Who doesn't love all that jazz? A lot of people. But I'm shocked
people have never seen it. I mean, I only saw recently for the first time. Yeah, it's a great
one. Yeah, I recommended quite on to Joe as well, which is a very interesting horror movie that I
talked about last time on the solo corner. But they got some great shit in there. I mean, their
horror selections are slim. But some of the ones they have are really cool. Yeah. And a lot of the
Cronenberg for sure. Yeah. Yeah. A lot of the I don't think they need to have every Wes Anderson
movie in the Criterion collection. Well, I tell you, I cannot force myself to see this new one.
I came out of the movie. I was at the movies the other day watching Antlers, which we're going
to review next month. Yeah. And as I was coming out, very nice gentleman who was a fan came up
to me and said, Hello, we were talking. And then I said, Would you see? And he said, I just saw the
French dispatch. And I said, How was it? He said, All right. Like he didn't give it a bad review.
Yeah. And somebody who likes my comedy, I would have expected would have been like,
it fucking sucked. Some dumb French movie, you know, but like, yeah, he was he was like,
I was like, All right, you know, but I don't want to see. I've never like strong with the only one
his I didn't like was Darjeeling limited and and the Isle of Dogs. I think he's got a pretty good
track record. It's just I can't think of a single director who's done the same thing for this long
period of time. And it's getting really boring. And I don't know how he isn't bored because
why wouldn't a director want to expand a little bit, especially one with all that success?
He's a new Woody Allen. He's the new Woody Allen. He does the same thing repeatedly.
Yeah, with some of the same themes like, you know, like Anderson has some child sexuality
themes in his movies and incestual things. And, you know, like it's it's, you know, and it's about
that sort of, excuse me, upper crust socialite society kind of thing. And, you know, I think
it's just starting to get, you know, just like with Woody Allen, like after the first 10 years,
people started to be like, All right. And then he swings back up with something that people really
like again, and then it dips again. And then, you know, and I think that will just be what's
happened now with Wes Anderson, who also is a painfully white filmmaker, like Woody Allen,
like it's just, yeah, he met Jeffrey Wright and decided like now he's fine because he has Jeffrey
Wright say five lines in every one of his movies. So that checks it off. But yeah, he needs to he
he's obviously as artsy fartsy a guy as you can find in the directing world. But
he keeps writing with other artsy fartsy. And he needs to get back to Owen Wilson. I mean, the
reason those first three bottle rocket Rushmore and Tenenbaums are the most beloved is because
they're the most funny and they feel the most human and alive. Because I think you have to assume by
looking at him that that's what Owen Wilson brought to it. Now he writes with Roman Coppola,
who's another artsy fartsy guy who's never made a good film. And this the movies just kind of sit
there. I liked Budapest Hotel, you know, I love I love Budapest Hotel. I thought it was incredibly
fun. Like you're going to the the art museum, you know, at a certain point, that movie was definitely
one of his better ones. And I love going into his worlds once every year or so. But I don't know,
I just it also would be such a news story if he broke from his thing he does. And did he doesn't
have to do Rambo or something. But any variants from his formula would be big news. And I don't
know why he just won't do it. Don't know. I I'm a huge Yeah, I really like Budapest Hotel. I love
Rushmore. I liked Tenenbaums quite a bit. I didn't ever want to watch it again, because it's so long.
It's kind of like sitting down to rewatch The Godfather. Again, a masterful film, but you don't
often want to just sit down and put it on. Tenenbaums is less than two hours.
No, is it? For sure. I always maybe I didn't enjoy it that much. Then I thought it was like
two and a half hours. And to me, it feels fast as hell. Or maybe I should revisit Tenenbaums.
But that's that to me is his masterpiece. I mean, it's hard. Rushmore is so funny.
Oh, wait, I'm getting mixed up with Magnolia.
That's Paul Thomas Anderson. Yeah, we were talking about last time. Yeah,
sorry. Yeah, Tenenbaums. That's a guy who definitely makes a different movie every time out.
Anderson, I mean, yeah, different genres, different everything.
What what else is there? There's what's the third one is the third?
Steve's Steve, that's where he started to lose. I don't I never really liked bottle rocket. I
respect it. I think it's a well made film. I don't find it very funny for whatever reason.
But Rushmore and Tenenbaums, I thought were laugh out loud, funny. And then Steve Zuzo
is where I started to not give a shit. I agree. I agree. It's a big step back.
I like Fantastic Mr. Fox a lot. I despised all of dog. I love dogs. Did not like Darjeeling.
The the reason bottle rocket hit me and I think so many other people so hard is that it was
if you were if you saw it in the theater and if you were, you know, following it at that time,
was your first exposure to Owen Wilson. I was like, holy shit, who is this? And I think most
people's first experience with him was Meet the Parents, which he also just stole. I remember
everything he said and meet the parents. The crowd was just like going nuts.
I think there are two kinds of people in this world. Yes, there are swingers people and bottle
rocket people. I've noticed that that's fair. I'm a swingers person. But the way I revere swingers
the way a lot of people revere bottle rocket. Yeah. Yeah, I love them both. I got no no issue
with either one of the films. But if I had to pick, I'd probably go swingers as well. Oh, okay.
Yeah, no. He's made two, two all time classics Rushmore Tenenbaums for me.
Speaking of swingers, Vaughn Vaughn coming in swinging in this new curb.
Uh, doing all the Vaughn shit. I loved it. Fucking love it. He's weirdly a great fit. You know,
he's a much better fit than Jon Hamm is I I don't I couldn't believe it. When I saw Jon Hamm again,
I was like, Why would you feel that you need to bring this back? But I was watching the other
night and like, I've become such a curmudgeon. And I'm sitting there like, God damn it, it's,
it's a 47 minute episode of curb, like, God damn it. And then it ended. And I'm like, Oh, man,
could have gone for another half hour. Why do I Why do I mind? It's just pure entertainment,
you know, even when the scenes aren't aren't hilarious. You love hanging out with these
people. Yeah, I love it. The Yeah, Vaughn's responses and that the things he's ad libbing
him like, God, it's so, so funny, man. When Susie's like, get yourself a drink. And he's like,
Okay, that's reasonable. Such a weird thing to say. But it works for some reason. It's funny,
the pitch of the minibar. Yeah, contents, which by the way, I liked Larry David's pics for the
minute. I thought they all sounded pretty good. And what they were bad on a thing you could imagine,
Larry, you could imagine the real Larry David now spending weeks trying to put together a
minibar for no money, which is a great thing about the character. It's a it's such a weird,
specific character. And it's just him, basically. Yeah. So but anyway, folks,
PETA, here's a new psycho for you. PETA is upset it. Once you read the article, it makes a little
more sense. But I read on movie web .com today that PETA is is asking for a boycott of Clifford,
the big red dog, for Christ's sake, for animal mistreatment. And I was like, what could this
I don't understand. And then as you read, they say, it's not about the fake dog. It's about some
real animals that are in the movie that they feel are being mishandled. One point is a monkey.
Then they've got problems with this monkey handler who worked on the movie or whatever. I mean, look,
brother of Chelsea handler. I don't look you're never going to get any Hollywood sympathy out of
me. I'm never going to sit here and defend the decency of any of these studios or production.
At the same time, PETA, for Christ sakes, I mean, it's just it's like when we talked about
Scarlett Johansson thing. It's like, I don't even know who to root for here. Yeah, I hate Disney.
I hate that she's suing. I hate the whole thing. You know, every exchange now, I feel that way.
I'm like, I don't like either of you. And I think you're both wrong. And I want you to go away.
Yeah, it's upsetting. And then another new psycho, Pat and I disagree on this, but
they released the final trailer for Ghostbusters. And it gave me full chills.
Just the end of the trailer, when you see the torsos of you don't see their faces,
they're really playing this well by not showing you them yet. But you see the torsos of Ackroyd,
Murray and Hudson, and you see the guns go up and you hear Dan Ackroyd go, did you miss us?
And then the Ray Parker Jr. Ghostbusters kicks in. And for the first time in all these trailers,
you're like, oh, it's going to be Ghostbusters. I haven't seen this new trailer. Yeah. But okay,
all I've seen is reviews that range from good to bad. You know, the plot of it that they reveal
in this new trailer, they play Ray's monologue from the first movie about the apocalypse,
Armageddon, in the book of whatever the book is in the Bible. And when he's reciting it,
and you're like, oh, my God, they're connecting it to the first one. This is and then you hear
Paul Rudd said, I think we opened a gateway to hell. You're like, oh, they're doing the thing
that they thought was happening in the first movie. Yeah. Yeah. Like, I'm really excited, man. I feel
like it's going to be two movies. I feel like it's going to be the first half of like, oh, this is
kind of a new cool Ghostbusters movie. And then the second half is going to be like, oh, this is
Ghostbusters part three, because now the guys are back and they're doing the thing. I'm fine with
that. I pray I'm excited to an extent. We'll be covering it next month. The big discourse this
week was Jason Reitman was like, yeah, you know, I really had, it was an inner struggle. Like,
am I brave enough to take on the reins from my dad and me and my dad have a difficult relationship,
whatever. And I saw 8 million people dunking on him for nepotism and everything. It's like,
guys, the man's first movie was nominated for Oscars. There is nepotism. Yes. But
he's not a hack. He's made several good movies. Yeah. And made several good movies without the
help of his father, as far as I can tell. You know, like, and by the way, who the fuck thinks
Ivan Reitman is some like Weinstein of Hollywood? This guy's not a power mogul. He made like five
movies. It's like, you know what I mean? I developed a movie with Ivan Reitman and
I've met funnier insurance agents. Bill Murray used to say that all the time. He was like,
the reason Ghostbusters is funny is us. It had nothing to do with Ivan Reitman. Like talk to him
for five minutes. The man's not funny. Yeah. I mean, you know, it seems like a nice stuff guy,
but I just love this concept that like Ivan Reitman has this, this, you know, this, this,
this system in play or this, or this, I'm using the wrong word. God damn it. You know what I mean
though? Like, you know, like he's able to just pick up a phone and get anything done. Yeah.
Reitman called, I was on my buddy Dan Dunn's podcast last night called What Are We Drinking?
Where you drink on it. And the sponsor was a Japanese whiskey that I'm blanking on the
name of right now, but it was delicious. Santora? Yes. Speaking of Bill Murray,
that was what he drank in Lawson Translation. In fact, somebody said that on the panel.
Yeah. But we did a live show and they were, so there were, there was a rep from the whiskey there
and Dan was a bit caution, concerned throughout the show because Jay Okerson and I particularly
were making a lot of off -color jokes. Okay. And he was like, he kept making the joke of like,
well guys, now that my podcast will be over forever, any last word or whatever.
And then finally, the end of it, I just humorously, but I yelled at him and I was like,
Dan, who the hell do you think is hearing this over at Santoro? Some fucking intern is going
to screen it. The top dog is like, get me the Dunn podcast. Yeah. The amount of time we've
stressing over things we've said on the podcast and then it is a narcissistic thought. It's like,
no one's listening to our podcast in terms of like moosers and shakers.
By the way, the, the, when I went into the group last week, I, at one point I think I made a bit
of an off -color joke and I said, I'm sorry guys. And they said, Joe, can we tell you finally,
we love all of the jokes. None of it is offensive because they, yeah, they, they've heard us
apologize so many times and get nervous. Well, we live in fear. I mean, I don't have much career
left to lose, so it might be time to just pull a bull worth, you know, I got nothing. I mean, I'm,
I'm about to start selling ham sandwiches. So I think it's the most exciting development you've
had in a long time. I mean, you're changing your life up and the time was here. People got to
I'm thrilled. Don't get me wrong. It's just a funny joke to make. I'm thrilled, but I'll tell you
what's tough is balancing that and the comedy now, you know, like I'm going to go out for a few dates
with Sal in December, which will be a lot of fun because we're friends. And then it'll also be a
good way to plug the, our podcast and everything. And, and by the way, everybody in the group wants
another us to do another live one. I want to do another live one with you. I think we should do
live one from Joey roses personally. I love it. Yeah. So, um, but anyway, you know, going at it's
like, I'm having like major anxiety about leaving town for two nights. You know, it's a, it's a weird,
it's going to be a weird thing to balance, you know, but you just need a trusted right hand man
or woman, which I would hope you have. Um, I, we, we have a great, we hired a great GM. She's
and I, and I do trust her immensely. And I trust my partner immensely too. So, you know, they both
were like, it'll be fine. Don't worry about it. But it's just, we gotta remember most people who
own a restaurant or a bar are never there. You know, you'll, you'll get to that point. Yeah.
I saw Joe's, uh, sign for the storefront. It looks incredible green and, uh, green and white.
I told him it makes the whole street around it look like dog shit. So hopefully it lures in the
people. And I also get to say it's been a lifelong dream and I look forward to it. I will get to say
this, this week, finally, for the first time in 44 years, folks drinks are on the house. Okay.
I've never gotten to say that. Are you going to say it? How many, how often are you giving out?
Well, at a, at one of the private events when we have like the investors and whatever, you know,
I'll get to see your private events where you just have cops in that can't find a place to
really be cops anymore. That kind of thing. Yeah. Yeah. You hear my voice over. They thought they
had a place where the shit couldn't touch them. Joey roses. That's kind of an, well,
maybe I shouldn't say this on here, but what, what about a movie where it's like Donnie Brasco type
thing, where a guy opens up a cop bar, but he's there to like, he's like Serpico, you know, like
he's like, this is a place where we can all discuss our, our issues, but he's there to actually
bust them or some sort of undercover operation. That's kind of what I mean, it's not exactly
Copland obviously, but that's sort of what Copland is, is there's a good cop in the mix
and they have the cop bar that he hangs out in and gets all the dirty information. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I guess, I guess so. There's not really an undercover element to it though. Mangold. Yeah.
Directing and writing from scratch, the new Indiana Jones film, which I guess they're almost
done shooting at this point. Do you think there's going to, do you think because it's Mangold,
there's a chance it's going to be pretty solid? For my money, Mangold has made one bad movie,
Kate and Leopold starring Hugh Jackman and Meg Ryan, one of the worst films ever made.
And everything else he's made has been good to great and excellent in the case of Copland.
And he knows how to do action. He did. Yeah. It was great. I love the car movie Ford versus
I think he's a good director. Maybe, you know, Spielberg producing, which I prefer Spielberg
in a producing role versus a directing role. I gotta be honest. Well, that's what I was going
to say is like, what has Spielberg given us in the past 10 years? That's, that's a great movie.
I still of course have mass respect for the man, but I don't know when nobody's talking about
Bridges Spies or, you know, Ready Player One or any of these, the new West Side Story to me is like,
who was this for casting Ansel Elgort in West Side Story? It's like, who decided this kid is great?
Who? The kid who looks like a Nazi, the kid who played baby driver.
I never saw it. And he's got some me too shit going on, but it's like, he's the most
nothing actor and I don't get it. But West Side Story was about Hispanic gangs. It is, but they
made a, you know, she falls in love with a white guy. Oh, that's the, okay. I got it. The original
West Side Story is one of the most beautiful movies ever made. And this, this one just kind
of looks like lesser in every way, man. If it's a musical dude, you gotta really, it's musical.
I mean, you, you gotta get, you gotta get me there with a lot. Well, you gotta really pull
me in with a lot, man. You gotta give me, uh, Judy Dench in a cat suit, licking herself.
Yeah, that's, that's, that's about what it takes. Speaking of, uh, well, this isn't well, music,
I guess, sort of, I should have brought this up in the last episode. I guess this, it doesn't
count as the scary stuff. It's just a fun thing. I bought the, uh, Albert Brooks comedy album. He
interesting, but I, I'm not crazy about it. The first one is called comedy minus one,
and it's supposedly one of the great comedy albums of all time. I didn't know it existed.
I'm listening to Kevin Pollock's audio book called How I Slept My Way to the Middle,
where he talks about the album, uh, as, as it just being one of the greatest comedy albums ever. So
I was like, I gotta get this thing. So I bought a vinyl copy of it. It's out of print. It's not
streaming anywhere, but I found a cop for like 20 bucks on eBay and, uh, take it out of the box.
Front cover says Albert Brooks comedy minus one. And then the tagline says introducing the new
comedy team of Albert plus, and then parentheses over, and you turn the record sleeve over and
there's a mirror and it says you exclamation point, your script inside. And I cackled out loud
in my apartment and I was like, that's the first and only time a record sleeve has made me laugh
out loud. Like we're probably off to a good start here. So I'm excited to listen to it.
I've never heard it myself. I would love to listen to it as well. I bet it's on Spotify
actually, but I feel like it's not on, I couldn't find it on Apple music. I doubt it's on Spotify.
But you can check his other one is though a star is bought, which the concept of that one is he
tries to make a record that appeals to every genre of every type of radio station. And it's funny,
but I get the impression he was smoking a lot of weed at the time, cause it's, it's really crazy.
And at times I'm like, I don't understand like what this is, but it's still funny. Um, but this
is more like, it seems like more of his bits, like rewriting the national anthem, like what
she would do on late night shows and stuff like, so I'm excited. Huge fan. I, uh, I'll listen to,
we'll discuss, um, let's go to the movie corn, the movie corner this week. I would be remiss
if I did not kick things off with a picture called cop. It's on Tubi. I was texting Joe about this
the other night. I still got to watch it. I'm sorry. This thing much as I talked about my love
of 10 to midnight, the late period Chuck Bronson movie that opens with him shoving a dildo into a
man's ass, uh, and rescuing a 13 year old daughter from getting fucked. Um, this movie is so sleazy,
unbelievably sleazy. And everybody talks about the seventies as being the great time for
exploitation and all that kind of stuff. But for some reason there's this late eighties underbelly
of movies, 10, the late Chuck Norris's, uh, and now I'm definitely adding cop savage streets, vice
squad, you know, all these movies that are just like filthy and they feel scummy. Cop is a new
classic in that genre. It's based on a book by, uh, why can I, why can I think of the guy,
James Elroy, who wrote LA confidential and the black Dahlia. And they tried to film it
numerous times, but the, like even Hollywood producers found the book too disgusting, too
violent. Um, cop is James woods at his filthiest. And I put this thing on and I'm like, okay,
James woods is an executive producer. I've never seen him produce his own stuff. So I'm okay. This
was an important movie to him. I wonder if we'll get any of his hardcore Republican views in the
film. The opening scene pretty much, he goes to this woman's house. She's hanging. What year is
it from 89? He's not Republican yet in 89. No, he's still Democrat. Holy, he didn't become
Republican until late. Like he was like around like nine 11 or something. Like he was late.
Okay. All right. Interesting. Um, no, he goes in, there's a woman hanging from the ceiling,
you know, bleeding everywhere. He looks at her. He's like, Jesus Christ doesn't cut her down.
Kind of leaves her hanging there and starts looking around her apartment. So for he finds
her bookshelves, which are all feminist books. And he's kind of chuckling to himself. Like, here we go
takes a book off. That's got bloody fingerprints on it. And the book is called a rage in the womb,
which is a feminist text. You flip it over. There is a very homely woman with a bowl,
glasses, who has written the book and the author's name is Pamela van dyke.
It's like James, James, James, he didn't write the thing. He didn't write the movie. I know
he could have been a little more subtle with his thing, but right at that moment, I was like,
wow. Okay. All right. I got it. His partner is Charles Durning. Uh, again, and this is
another cop. Durning played a lot of cops over the years. Remember that one you and I
saw with Burt Reynolds, Sharkey's machine where he was a cop as well. So movie that I've that I've in
the greater distance I get, the more it becomes a masterpiece. I know I want to watch it again.
But, uh, I jotted a couple of things down here. This opening scene where he's talking to his
partner, generally the scene in a movie where you like your heroes, you know, you like the two cops
and they have a moment where they connect or whatever, before you go onto the action,
these two come off as so unlikable. And it took me half the movie to realize that it's intentional.
It's like a training day. It's a bad cop movie. Um, that was not clear to me at first, but
what happens is Durning says to him,
your daughter better hope that she has huge tits because that's what really makes a girl succeed
in this world is a girl having huge tits. And James would laughs, uh, his daughter who we see
in the next scene is five years old. Oh boy. And him and Durning are Chuckling like, yeah,
she better hope she's got some big tits, you know, uh, James woods tells a bedtime story
to his daughter that, uh, that's a very funny scene, but it involves like horrific crimes
that he's just talking about his time on the police. Right. He doesn't know that you can't
talk to your daughter about that goes into his wife's room and does this big speech basically
about how much he hates women. And he's like, the reason women suck is they all have expectations
and they all think that things are going to be good for them. Like just re it's so misogynistic
and crazy, but when you realize that they're not making him out to be the hero, right. It's same
thing as a, as a Bronson and 10 to midnight, he's screaming about how much he hates Asian people in
every scene. And you're like, but, and yet we're rooting for him, you know, like they intended cop
to be a new dirty hairy franchise. And it wound up not making good money, but, um, it's the same
kind of uneasy thing of your, you do want him to get the victims or they get the people who have
raped and killed and everything else, but at the same time, his methods are so disgusting.
So, uh, in the scene with Durning, James wood says, and I wrote this down,
he's bitching about his wife, the Durning and he goes, why can't they fly?
Why can't they fucking fly like us? And Durning says, no wings kid. It's the way they're made.
I mean, all right. Yeah. You know, you know, now if that's a movie you're going to love,
or if that's a movie that's going to piss you off, but I, I mean, it's wild. The amount of times
I sent Joe a screenshot, he refers to West Hollywood as a F sewer.
Wow. Jeez. I mean, it's, it's, it's full of hateful shit. And then I kept hearing
the ending will blow you away. It's got one of the most amazing fade to blacks in movie history.
And even knowing all that, I'm not going to spoil it for you. The ending had me howling on my couch.
This it's on Tubi. It's honestly, it's better on Tubi because it's so sleazy. You want it
with the commercials. It feels like something you're watching like late at night in the,
in the late eighties. Uh, strongly recommend cop. You got to check it out.
By the way, there's a scene Leslie and Warren is talking at length about
being raped. And the entire time she's talking, James woods is checking his watch. Jesus Christ.
He's, he's like, I mean, it's, it's one of the scummier characters I've ever seen.
Check it out. I watched a couple more Halloween hits. I really packed a lot in and Halloween.
I watched Batman, the long Halloween parts one and two. Uh, they're obviously meant to go together,
but they are full feature length, uh, films each one. Um, but direct continuations, it's just such
a long graphic novel. Yeah. They had to do it properly in two parts that they released
at the same time. Uh, DC has done a really good job over the years of adapting
their graphic novels into films, uh, animated films, uh, especially with the Batman titles.
Sometimes they've dropped the ball, like with the killing joke, which was terrible. Um,
and it's a shame, but out of every graphic novel ever to feature Batman, uh, and there are many
great ones. I think the long Halloween is arguably the greatest and man, they did this thing
perfectly. It's amazing. It's such an awesome, well done, well directed, well written script is
magnificent. The voice acting is great. Yeah. Jensen Echols is Batman. He's doing a good job
as Batman. You've got, um, what's his face, tad Hamilton as Harvey Dent. And he's great.
Josh Duhamel. Oh, okay. I thought you meant the fictional actor from when it did with
Ted Hamilton. I was like, what? No, um, it's just a, it's just a very, very, very well done
Batman story and it features all the villains, all your favorites. Yeah. Um, you know, watch it. It's
on HBO max streaming. You know, if you have that, you can check it out. Uh, but I would say first,
read the graphic novel, the long Halloween. It's, it's a riveting piece of work and a very dark,
very adult, you know, the way I like my comics. Okay. Uh, I rewatched hadn't seen it since the
theater of the edge, which I know Joe is a big fan of. And I really loved the first time I saw it.
I liked it quite a bit. This time I saw it. It's Anthony Hopkins and America's sweetheart,
Alec Baldwin. They are two men who basically Baldwin is a photographer who takes kind of
provocative photos of Elle McPherson, who was Anthony Hopkins kind of younger trophy wife.
You learn throughout the course of the film that Baldwin and McPherson are having an affair.
They get lost out in the wilderness and you're never quite clear if Baldwin is going to try and
Anthony Hopkins and take his wife or what's going on. There's also a bear in the mix trying to kill
them. The scenes with the bear are what people talk about with the edge and what they remember.
And they're fantastic. I think the only time I remember it being bettered was probably the
revenant when they just had, you know, more options to, or more, more special effects at
their disposal. But, uh, the bear stuff in this, the bear like tracking them because it gets the
scent of the guy it kills. It's awesome. It is great. And it's Harold Perrineau from Lost
kind of filling the standard black guy who's along for the ride who knows just going to get
killed. And he does. And like, there's weirdly almost no reaction to it in the movie, but
Hopkins and Baldwin are awesome in this thing. They have great chemistry. I sent you Joe,
I don't know if you read this link to an article called Wilderness, which was in Vanity Fair.
I didn't read it yet. Uh, it was in Art Linson's book, What Just Happened, which I read and which
became the De Niro movie, What Just Happened, which is not good, but, um, they really go into
how difficult Baldwin was and is apparently he showed up with his giant beard and really fat.
And they were like, Oh, they already, the studio didn't want him because he was not a proven box
office name. And he showed up and they were like, fuck, well, we're not going to let him do this.
They made him shave the beard and lose some weight. Oh, and that's the Bruce Willis thing
in the De Niro movie. And De Niro called Baldwin and asked him, do you want to play yourself in
this movie? And he's like, do I want to play myself in a film where I'm an asshole? No, I don't think.
So, uh, yeah, it's, that article is great. It, you know, it's a great kind of companion piece
to the movie. It just is a great article about the craziness of moviemaking, but, um, yeah,
wanted Dustin Hoffman. They wanted De Niro. They wanted Pacino Hopkins feels like the right choice.
He's really good in this. I mean, everyone knows he's great. He's a great fucking actor, but
there's so much variance in his performances. Like he's, he's not Hannibal Lecter in this,
you know, it's like a, he's a, there's something really interesting about his character. David
Mamet wrote it, who of course, uh, is a fantastic writer, a fantastic writer of dialogue in
particular. And it's not just anybody, anybody, um, hesitant. Some people don't like Mamet because
of the Mamet speak stuff. There's not a lot of that in this. This is one of his more mainstreamly
written films. It's got a couple of quippy lines that sound very Mamet -y, but it's not right. If
you didn't know he wrote it, you, I, you wouldn't know he wrote it, but, um, but I, I love Mamet as
a writer and I think he did a great job with this and, um, Hopkins, you know, like you said, he's
not, uh, Lecter. Yeah. But when it's time for him to get serious, he carries the same weight
that Lecter has. Like when he says like kill the motherfucker. Yeah. With the bear, you're like,
he's going to kill the bear. Like you have no doubt in your mind that he's going to kill the bear.
Yeah. Even Baldwin's like, all right, dude, go hang out here. Yeah. But, uh, but yeah, it's an
awesome, it's, it's just an awesome movie. It's just, you know, I'm not, I'm usually not big on
survival. You know, we crashed in the wilderness type things, but this, I've always loved The Edge.
I really think it's great. It's a genre I like. There's so few great ones though. Um, like when
I was a kid, I loved Hatchet by Gary Paulson, which is about a kid who gets lost in the wilderness
with only a hatchet. He just died, Gary Paulson, but that was a book I was obsessed with when I
was a kid. I like it when it's done well. Um, and I think The Edge is one of the better survival
movies. It's great. Do you think, oh, go ahead. Sorry. I was, well, I asked you via text and you
didn't respond, but do you think, I know Baldwin tells Hopkins that Elle McPherson didn't know
about his plan to kill Hopkins. Do you think McPherson didn't know? Cause they had that kind
of tense scene at the end where Hopkins goes up and he's like, I could call you out now,
but I'm going to let it go. No, I don't think she knew. I think she was having an affair as
trophy wife might tend to do with a husband. So, uh, much to her senior, uh, in a, you know,
Baldwin does look kind of strapping. I guess they got him in shape enough for the movie. So
it makes sense. But I think that's also what that last line of the movie is about. How did
your friends die? They died saving my life. Like, uh, Hopkins in that moment is also realizing his
vanity and his mistakes. Um, and that, you know, despite the horrific way where he had to come to
realize them, he still realized them. So, um, and I love that even after Baldwin tries to kill him
and falls in the bear trap by accident, he, uh, that's a great line to watch the trap.
He's still, you know, and he falls in, but even then like Hopkins tries to save his life.
And like, they actually have a moment of reconciliation when he's like,
why did you do this for me? I was going to kill him. You know, it's great. It's a really good
movie, man. Um, I watched Vince, our friend, Vince, April shout outs, sent me a copy of the WNUF
Halloween special. Do you own this? It's on, it's on shutter. Um, but I've heard it's great. I've
never watched it. McCarthy was telling me the same. Hello, Matt McCarthy. I love Matt McCarthy. I love
Avril. Um, Vince sent me a hello, Matt McCarthy. I didn't say I love Matt. Oh, you're right. I didn't
say it either. I didn't say that. Uh, anyway, uh, Vince sent me a copy of this. Um, thank you,
Vince. Um, it was, um, it's very well done. It's very well done to the point where aside from one
or two or three, maybe poorly delivered lines where you can tell that was written
or the actor is trying a little too hard to mimic this style of 80s news program or whatever.
Right. You would not know that it was fake. I mean, it's, they, there's commercial after
commercial in this thing that they, I guess they had commissioned several directors kind of like
did with grind house with Rodriguez. They commissioned several directors to, to give them
commercials that a local news station would be running. And the commercials they're
unbelievably, like they just hit the nail on the head. I remember watching news at this time
with my parents and like seeing these types of commercials, I'm like, my God, these seem like
real places. So it's fascinating in that sense. It's very, very well done. Um, the payoff overall
is fine. You know, it's, it's not like it, look, it's a kitschy fun thing to watch. I don't know
it's some, if it's something that you'd return to, um, many times, but maybe every Halloween you
throw it on or something like that. You know what I mean? You know, there's, there's, you know,
I also, I'm not going to return to Emmett Otter's jug band Christmas frequently either,
but on Christmas I'll put it on, you know? So, and I think it serves a great purpose and holds a nice
place in that, in that pantheon of, of Halloween specials that you could watch every year that are
just kind of get you in the mood and whatever, but it's fun and it's well acted and it's well
executed. And the basic plot is it's a Halloween special where they're going to go into a supposedly
haunted house and guess what? Things go wrong. Where did it ever air? Was it even released on
VHS or how did it premiere? No, I think it just released on, I mean, it might've been released
on VHS, but I think it just, you know, it got these guys made it and it went to streaming or,
you know, whatever. Oh, it's a recent thing. I thought it was actually made a long time ago.
No, it's made and they, that, that if you didn't know again, it's one of these things,
if you didn't know any better, you'd think it was, but it's, it was made like seven years ago. It's
like, okay, I'll check it out. It looked like it was like this unearthed thing from the eighties.
Yeah. All right. I'm going to close with a big disappointment last night in Soho directed by
Edgar Wright. Edgar Wright, you know, just like we were talking about Anderson. I mean, his first
three movies, it really, for me, it's just hot fuzz and Shaun of the Dead. I I'd love to rewatch
World's End, but I didn't like it at the time. You know, I think those are classics. I've liked his
other stuff, Scott Pilgrim and so on. Baby Driver to me kind of lost the thread. I think the big
part of my dislike was Ansel Elgort, who is a nothing. And also Kevin Spacey as the villain,
probably regrets doing that right before he got caught. But, um, I just felt like something was
off with Baby Driver and the story didn't quite work for me. And I, and I, I was let down and
frustrated by it. And that feeling extends even more to last night in Soho. I it's odd, you know,
and maybe it was his, he was pairing with Simon Pegg or he paired with the right people and now
he's not, I don't know. But this movie for me was kind of dull. The first half is much better than
the second, which everyone I know has said, even those that like it. But the gist is this a young
girl passionate about fashion design is mysteriously able to enter the 1960s where she encounters her
who is the girl from the Queen's Gambit and a Taylor Joy, a dazzling wannabe singer. But 1960s
London is not what it seems. And time seems to be falling apart with shady consequences.
There's a lot of sexual assault stuff in the movie, sexual assault themes in the movie.
And I know Edgar Wright co -wrote it with a woman, the lady who wrote 1917, I believe. But, um,
it's just that thematically, it doesn't work. It doesn't hold up. What it's trying to say
seems murky at times and almost offensive at others. The story goes so far off the rails.
It's one of those. Well, like everybody knows, like Suspiria, the old one is kind of considered
this work of art, but moment to moment, it doesn't necessarily make a tremendous amount of sense.
This seems to be trying to be kind of an homage to Suspiria and so forth. But I think they were
under the impression that this not only made sense, but was a big important statement. And it does
not work at that at all. I don't know. It's, it's got me concerned honestly about Edgar Wright,
because I feel like he's losing the thread as opposed to becoming a better, stronger director.
I hate to say it, but, um, yeah, this didn't work for me really in any way, aside from the soundtrack,
the visuals kind of carry you along for about a half hour. You know, you're sort of like, okay,
all right. But the performances are, are not anything special. And the story, as I said,
doesn't make sense. The themes don't work or coalesce in any sort of satisfying way.
So let down for me. I had no interest in it. It looked, uh, it looked like that, that, uh,
what are those two movies that came out like two years ago? The one with Margot Roby
that looked like super Tarantino. We rip off, you know, uh, and then there was the other one,
the hotel, like birds of prayer. No, no, no, I know. You watched it and I hadn't seen it.
Or there was, you know, and then that other one, a night in the whatever motel or whatever,
I don't know. Like it's just L Royale bad times. Yeah. It's just like these things to me, just like,
you know, it's, it's a lot of style. And, but I just, it feels when I was watching the trailer
for last night, what is it? One night and so, or last night and so, wait, last night. So sorry.
Yeah. Last night, when I was watching the trailer, I was just like it, everybody in the trailer
looked like they knew they were making something cool. Yeah. The best way I could describe it.
And I just was like, I don't know, man, this is annoying, but, uh, well, I read a review the
day of maybe the night house, maybe something else, but it was just talking. And I, boy,
it was a great sentiment that I agreed with so much where it was like, why is all horror now
just simply connecting metaphorical beats or thematic beats. And everyone is acting in it,
not in a way a human being would act, but in a way that you, in a way that makes the theme work,
you know, like the night house is basically one extended metaphor.
And last night in Soho is also kind of one extended metaphor. So you're not really watching a story
being told or characters act in a convincing way. You're watching people hit hit plot points that
service this kind of overall theme. It's like they decide what they want to say and try to say it,
but they're forgetting all the other elements that make a film compelling. Like it used to be,
you know, it's like Texas chainsaw massacre. Everybody says now after the fact, you know,
that movie was about Vietnam and then you can watch it and go, Oh, interesting. Like you can
watch it with a new lens, let's say, but now the themes are so thoughtingly obvious and discussed
at such great length in every one of these movies that there's no room for nuance or interpretation,
you know, and it's just kind of sucks. It's an every pitch now in Hollywood has to be,
okay, fine. That sounds funny. But what does it say about our collective trauma? You know,
like everything has to be about a big issue. And I think people are servicing the issues now instead
of the story, the plot, the characters. And that's why a lot of these movies are just so
unfulfilling. And the greatest example of the greatest recent example of it being done right
is of course, get out, right, get out, you know, you can watch it as strictly a comment on race
and be blown away by it. You can watch it as strictly a horror movie. He never forgets to
make you a fun, thrilling, scary, funny horror movie while also hitting you with all kinds of
great thematic material to chew on and makes it a much deeper richer movie than most. But you can't
set out to make a movie that's just, you know, lecturing people with with no fun.
It's the it's the it's the Friday the 13th commentary. When you know, when they discuss
and they say this, the commentary is, is that this was about the moral majority and kids that
were doing things like having sex or cursing or smoking weed, we're going to be punished,
right, an evil force. And you don't think that when you're watching it, you just know the fact
Oh, yeah, that's interesting. Right. I agree with you.
It's if you want to if you want to make that mental lead great. And if you don't great,
but like, you know, it's also the themes are so simple. And like the theme of this movie is
sexual assault is bad at the end of the day. And it's like, we know that work from there and make
us a fun movie, but they just didn't do it. Well, a movie with no as far as I can tell theme will
be my final entry. Yes. Joe dante's the hole. Own it never opened it bought it for $2. I love
Dante bought it for $3 or so on Hamilton books. Same blue ray. Should have known that might have
been a red flag. Watched it was excited to watch it at Halloween time. Why about three kids who
find a hole that's a gateway to another dimension sounded a lot like the gate. Yeah, same.
I love the gate. The gate to is outrageous, but still enjoyable. Even though it's not good.
This was like if you took the gate and filtered it through a CW strainer,
and then like shuffled it over to RL Stein to clean it up even more. I mean, it was just so
sanitized and boring. And I just didn't care at all through the entire movie.
The kids find a gate. Bad stuff comes out of the gate. They've got to close the gate.
Why is the gate there? Yeah. Why can the gate be closed with padlocks? If it's supernatural forces,
none of it really makes any sense. It doesn't seem to be a ton of thought into the script.
It's a well -reviewed film, which I don't get. I guess if you watched it through the lens of,
hey, man, this is a younger audience's thing. This is so you can show it to your kids.
Then maybe it works. I'm just a little too old. Unless it's blatant. Unless it's blatantly that.
You watch something like the new seasons of Are You Afraid of the Dark? Those are blatantly
engineered for a younger audience. And aesthetically, it makes sense when you watch
it. This didn't feel engineered for a younger audience to me, but apparently it is. Bruce
Dern's in it for about five minutes playing. Is he like, you got to stay away from the whole kids?
Yeah. I was just going to say the most stereotypical character you can imagine.
Anyway, look, if you're a Joe Dante completionist, check it out. But Dante really,
to me, and I hate to say it because I'm a fan of the guy, but I just don't like anything he's
done in recent years. His episodes of Masters of Horror, one of them is, I don't care. And then
the other one, I was like, this is like laughably bad. The homecoming about the dead soldiers coming
back to vote the Bush out of office or whatever. It's like, this is cringe -worthy, man.
I know. I've seen everything he's done except this box. I'm a big fan. Well, but the hole,
if you listen to his podcast, which I tried to do as a huge fan of Dante, and it's like them
talking about some of their favorite movies and guests and everything. This is one of the most
bitter men I've ever heard. He is so he has, he's a director for hire. Now he does like episodes of
Hawaii five Oh for CBS and stuff. And in his mind, it's like, why am I not being offered Lord of the
Rings? You know, he still feels that way. And he's, he's aged out of it. He's kind of lost his bite,
whatever. But God, he's so bitter. Actually, I listened to a couple episodes and it was actually
very helpful for me to say, remember this and don't become this guy. There's so many people like
this in Hollywood who are just sitting around bitching about what could have been or whatever.
It's not, it's not fun to listen to it for anybody, you know? So it's a shame. I mean,
the man has made unquestionable great films, but it's like Tarantino says, you know, people
age out of things. So. So let's move on to our movies of the day. Also two films that have no
social commentary as far as I can sell. Just, just a guy saying, you know what? I like that
Texas chainsaw massacre. I'm going to just do that. Yeah. Yeah. The first one is very much a
combo of sort of deliverance in Texas chainsaw massacre. It is beautiful people, including,
holy Lord, Alicia Dooskoo. My God. I've, I've loved her forever, but yeah. She used to,
I shouldn't even say this, but she used to train for the, that dollhouse show
outside, right outside the always sunny offices on the Fox lot. And it was the kind of thing where
every day at like 2 PM, they'd be like Dooskoo stretching.
We'd all run over and watch her stretch. I don't feel good about this people,
but it was a different time. I mean, she's great. I always liked seeing her. I love her.
Bring it on. I just had a quick flashback to bring it on and it's almost started sweating, but yeah,
movie is, you know, it's teenagers get, get lost. And then there's teenagers and a 43 year old
Jeremy Sisto who's really funny in it. I know he was funny. He's great. I feel like he was
improving. Sisto is great. It's, it's cliched to a crazy degree. I mean, it's like, it's the kind
of thing where they're driving up and then they stop at the general store and the guy's like,
you're going to be in trouble up there. I mean, it is beat for beat. Just the most generic,
by the numbers plot. And yet, Stan Winston designed the mutants, right? They look really cool.
There are some suspenseful scenes, the scenes where they're like chasing each other through
the trees. I thought were kind of an interesting set piece that I hadn't really seen. Wild. So I,
I really, let me, let me just say, I really, really enjoyed wrong turn. I thought it was a
lot of fun. I think if I had seen it at the time, it would have been a little lost on me
because I would have been like, ah, it's kind of more of the same, right? But seeing something
like that now, I just thought it was a lot of fun. And it kept me guessing, you know, like,
like we're not guessing. It just kept me on my toes. Like, like there's a scene where,
these deformed, you don't really get the full story. It's one of those like seven opening
credit sequences where it's like showing like cuts of newspapers and you just see where it's like
deformed. Somebody breaking a nail up close. Maybe tweezing an eyebrow up close. I guess that's
scary. Yeah. So it's, but basically there's the bunch of inbred, I guess, deformed cannibals that
live in the forest. Yes. And these kids get stranded because they are sabotaged by these
cannibals because the cannibals, this is how they trap their prey. And the chase is on. That's it.
These crazy lunatics are chasing these kids through the forest, through the whole thing.
But when I say kept me on my toes, it was like, as soon as they find, there's a point where they
find a watch tower and they climb up inside of it. And as they're climbing up, you're like,
no, it's wood. They're going to set it on fire. And sure enough, they do. And there's this,
there's this whole thing where it's like, we have to jump out of the window and hope the branches
just catch us. And then that leads to a treetops chase scene, which, which you brought up, which
is wild. Like it's like something out of like fucking Rambo or some shit. It's crazy. But I
really, really, I just really enjoyed it, man. I just thought it was wild. I thought the gore
were fantastic. Like, you know, it's not a home run film, but I give it a solid, solid,
I'd give it a solid C plus B minus somewhere in there. Oh, okay. I thought you liked it even
more than that. But I mean, I, for me, it was, it was pretty average. I think had I seen it
during this period of time when all these horror movies were coming out, I don't know how I missed
it. Honestly, I used to go see, and I hated horror at the time I'd go see like the Texas
Chainsaw reboot and despise that and wish I could leave the theater and everything. So I never got
to Wrong Turn, but yeah, it's, it's solid. I think it, it's basically the descent meets Texas
Chainsaw, meets Evil Dead, meets Cabin Fever, you know, you could go on and on. But there are,
there are worse ripoffs. It's, there's, there's a fun to it. It's a well -directed movie.
Wrong Turn 2, I had heard was superior. Immediately, you can tell you're dealing
with a much lower budget. The movie looks like it was shot on, you know, early DV camera, you know.
Yeah, directed by Joe, this one's directed by Joe Lynch, who's a very nice guy. Met him once on
Doug Loves Movies. He also directed the movie Mayhem. Yes, I think it's still streaming on
Shutter, but Joe Lynch has done some cool stuff. And he's a big fan of the genre. He's a big fan of,
you can tell, of splatter and, and fun and horror. And that comes out in this, despite the lower
budget. You, you really. It's a totally different ride. Yeah. Tone. Yeah. I mean, it's, it's much
more, A, it's much more gross, but it's gross. And that kind of fun isn't this gross way. And
yeah, it's, it's a totally different tone and style. It was a hugely successful directed DVD
movie. Like one of the most successful directed DVD is in what led to the huge franchise. I've
only seen one or two, but two is the highest rated in the franchise. Yeah. Critics liked it too. I
mean, it's a, and it does kind of have something to say because it's a parody sort of, of, of the
big reality boom, reality television boom that was going on at that time. So it's a reality show
hosted by Henry Rollins, who, you know, is solid in the movie. It's not like you ever forget. He's
Henry Rollins, but he's, he's solid in it. He's solid. And he really nails, they nail like they,
the fake reality show is called the apocalypse. Yeah. And you have to survive the orchestrated
apocalypse. Yeah. And Henry Rollins plays an ex Marine survival master or whatever. And they
nail every element of like what a show like this would be like from the way they shoot it
to the segments that they show you to the way Henry Rollins acts as the host.
Yeah. It's a very smart move to, to, to make it that because it, it lets the low budget kind
of shabby nature of the filmmaking compliment what they're doing. It sort of looks like a reality
show. So that that's a good decision they made. I think it's not a found footage movie. Let me
be clear about that. It's just, the plot of the movie is that there's a reality actually a lot
like a Halloween resurrection. Yeah. At the beginning, there's this woman driving along
talking to her agent who was voiced by Patton Oswalt, which I recognized immediately.
Yeah. And the, yeah, there's some attempts at comedy in there that were just not landing for
me. And I was getting kind of uneasy, but then, you know, when she gets killed, they, they rip
her in half bone Tomahawk style. They're carrying half of her body away. And I was like, okay,
look, that was crazy. You know, and one slice an ax to the head straight through. Yeah. Yeah,
and by the way, more deformed cannibals unrelated to the family in the first,
but still in West Virginia, same setting, I guess this forest just loaded with these people. Well,
I mean, it's supposed to be inbreeding caused this years and years and decades of inbreeding.
So I guess there are some out, I mean, these, these people seem both dumber and smarter because
they set traps. Like at one point, this is a really dark scene, but the, the mutants are trying to
basically fool them. So it looks as though one of the mutants is raping one of their female friends,
but then take a wig off and you realize it's just a mutant fucking another mutant.
Well, not just that a mutant fucking his sister, his sister. Yes. Yeah. And she's just wearing the
for fun or whatever of the dead woman that, that, that mutant who's fucking the sister
was masturbating to, and you see him spit into his hand and you see the spit into the hand.
It's intense, man. Yeah. And it's like, it's weird because this horrific stuff does happen,
but it's a comedy and it doesn't, this one seemed to be leaning more into a Texas chainsaw to vibe.
However, it never gets anywhere near as disturbing as to, but it's a similar kind of
uneasy blend of comedy and really violent gross stuff, which to me was kind of a fun thing.
It made it feel more fresh than first wrong turn. I think I probably liked it slightly more,
whereas wrong, wrong turn is unquestionably a better movie. Wrong turn two is more fun to watch.
Yeah. Yeah. And it's disturbing. I would say it's pretty, I mean, you want to talk about Texas
chainsaw ripoffs. They just go for it. And this, they do the whole thing where they make the normal
girl, they tire to the table as they have the cannibal family dinner. I'm like, you guys aren't
even trying to act like you're not mimicking it at this point, but that's pretty gross when they're
feeding her the human meat. Just the way it looks is really disgusting. It was. Yeah. And you're
imagining the smell through the entire thing, which is pretty gross. Yeah. But I'll tell you,
my favorite part of the movie or aspect of it was Rollins gets abducted two things. Number one,
Rollins has a scene with a woman or very early on where he says,
your boyfriend doesn't see something in you that I do. You're pretty, but you're a lot tougher than
you think. And you go, what a corny, obvious way to set up the final girl. Like, yeah, this is stupid.
And she dies unexpectedly like 11 minutes later. I was like, he fucking got me, man. I didn't see
that coming for a mile away. And then Rollins gets abducted. And this is my other favorite aspect of
the movie. And then there's this whole full Rambo, like, I'm going after it. And it's awesome. It's Henry Rollins as a crazy, not crazy, but like a very skilled,
like, angered Marine because of what these guys did to him. And it's awesome. That scene is great,
dude, where he's in the cabin talking to the old man who he doesn't know yet is connected to the
Billy cannibals. That old man deserves like an Oscar. I was like, did they pull this guy out of
the woods? Like, and I looked it up. And it's like, no, he's a Canadian actor. He's been in a lot of stuff.
But, but that old man was was so good in that scene. And so convincing. And I was just like,
this is great. You know, he blows him up. And he's like, say hello to the Mrs. For me.
You know, like it's a, it's a wild picture that we haven't even discussed the, the, the nudity and this
thing and the sex, but like a lot of nudity nudity. Yeah. And it's just that it's that period where it
was especially in a directed to DVD thing, just nudity for nudity sake and closeups of the nudity.
But that girl blows and then fucks the cameraman on the reality show in hopes of getting more
time. It's like, Oh honey. It's like the old joke about, you know, she's the stupidest actress
in Hollywood. She fucked the writer to get ahead, you know, the cameraman on a reality show.
I think he's the director. I think he's supposed to be the director, but still it's a, and then,
and then that's the, that's the guy that's dating the girl who had her own says you're tougher than
you think. And then she witnesses the boyfriend cheating and then is dead within minutes. You've
got a character in this that you couldn't get anywhere near a script these days. That guy
that's like constantly hitting on the lesbian through the, to me, he felt almost like, and it's
like the, the, the Will Poulter character in mid summer, it feels almost skirting the line of a
parody of the horny guy in a teen movie. And I feel like that was kind of what they were going
for here. Cause he's so it's like, there's no nuance to it at all. He's just fucking like,
well, like, you know, if somebody says anything, he's there with some really lame sex joke about
it. And, and I thought it was a sort of a tongue in cheek, but I could be wrong.
I felt that all the characters were in their own way. I love that. I love that the surviving
woman is a vegan who's forced to human flesh. Yes. You know, I, I, you know, and I love that
that guy dies hanging the, the, the sex pot guy dies hanging upside down with the lesbian who he's
been harassing the whole movie and they die together, like supporting each other with an
arrow through their heads. I mean, people were dying in this thing that I was like, there's no
way they're going to kill the lesbian character. Like she's going to make, and like, they're just
offing people through this entire thing, man. Yeah. So I, I, I really, really liked wrong turn two.
I dipped into wrong turns three and four afterwards. Within minutes of watching wrong
turn three, I was like, something's wrong here. This is not good. Yeah. And I looked up a review.
I believe it is the lowest reviewed of the entire series. Okay. And the first review I said,
I read was if wrong turn two up the bar, wrong turn three brings it right back down again.
And I was like, I couldn't even sit through it. I was just like, this is the same exact plot again,
like, and it's just not as good. And they, and they also, they shot it in England,
clearly for budget reasons. And you can tell that it's English people trying to sound American and
it does work. Yeah. And then four is called bloody beginnings, which they said was a prequel about
the family in the first movie. And I thought, well, that'll be cool. The problem though is,
is then it starts in the sixties and it is kind of interesting. And then it time jumps
to like two years before the first movie. And you're like, so it's just going to be
goddamn first movie again. It just, you know, but they just want to get these characters back.
And then, I mean, what would the prequel be like a brother and sister, like starting to develop
attraction to each other or what it's the three adults from the first movie as teenagers in the
sixties in a, in a sanatorium. Okay. Because they are inbred and violent, but they get into a little
bit of like, but no, they're very smart, but they play dumb. And that's how they trick people.
And whatever. But again, I was like, kind of thought it was going to be this cool origin story.
And it was, it just turns out to be more of the same five. I haven't dipped into yet. Six apparently
is the second best received, I think. Well, and then they remade it this year,
didn't they? Wrong turn. They remade it this year. And clearly because of new PC standards,
they were like guys, it's not okay to say that people in West Virginia are fucking their sisters
and it's not okay to make fun of deformed mental patients. So now the bad guys are a cult who have
been living off the grid for many years. And when outsiders breach their territory, they kill them
because they're, they, they don't want to be discovered or something like that. And although
it looks a little creepy because the cult people wear this, they were like goat masks and shit.
It's just not as cool. Come on. Did you see it or not?
I watched, I read about it and I watched some trailers and stuff, but I, it was, and you know,
it's, it's, it's not the same thing. Did you see the recent cabin fever remake? I didn't watch that
one either, but it's like this weird thing where like almost nobody notices, but they've remade
like pretty recent horror movies a lot lately. Did I tell you ever tell you this story? I must
partners with and all my scenes and acted with and all my scenes. We were in the booth one day doing
ADR stuff. Yeah. And he said, we, we, I was telling him about our podcast. It was fairly
new at the time. He said, yeah, do you like cabin fever? And I go, I gotta tell you, man,
I don't give a shit about cabin fever. Like it was okay. I thought he did himself on hostel and
really got there again. I think cabin fever is very, whatever. I think the jokes are bad
and I can't believe they're remaking this fucking thing now. And I go, do you like cabin fever? And
the kid goes, I wrote it that lead to a big laugh or no, he was a good sport about it. He was laughing
and he was like, sorry, man, I wasn't trying to like set you up there. And I was like, Jesus,
I feel dumb. And, uh, but you know, one of those situations, all you can do is just own it at that
point. What am I going to do? Oh, I'm so sorry. I just was like, yeah, sorry, man. I didn't, you
know, I wouldn't have said that if I knew. See, I think in the, the cabin in the woods, rip off
genre of movies, I prefer that to wrong turn. I slightly prefer cabin fever to wrong turn.
I need to rewatch cabin fever. I think that was a little unfairly harsh on it as I am on a lot of
movies. Um, I just for the makeup effects alone, I'd like to revisit. So anyway, my hogs are up
wrong term one and two personally. Yeah. I mean, they, they both have pros and cons. I, I think
that at the end of the day, they're average horror movies to me, but I definitely had more fun with
wrong turn too. I have to say any fan of horror would be making a right turn if they picked up
these movies at their video store. All right, folks, that's our show. We'll be back next month
with Ghostbusters and we're doing Ghostbusters after life. Yeah. And, uh, and antlers antlers
may even be available to rent by that time because man, that movie was in and out of theaters in like
a week. Yeah, it was, um, fast. Jesse Clements and, uh, love Clemens. I've heard good things.
And, uh, Jane, Jane of our Jane, the Virgin, no Joan of Arcadia, Joan of Arcadia, Carrie Russell
is that Joan of Arcadia? What was her name? She was Felicity. That's right. What the fuck was
Joan of Arcadia was, is David Cross's wife, Amber. Oh, okay. Something Liddell Aladdin.
Yeah. All right, folks, we'll see you next time. And we will see you in hell.