I'll see you in hell.
Welcome to We'll See You In Hell, your favorite podcast that discusses and reviews genre
of films. My name is Joe DeRosa. Next to me is my dear, dear friend, Patrick Walsh. That's
sweet of you to say, Joe. Yeah. Well, it's good to see you too. It's great to see you.
It's a Friday night. I don't give me the bullshit. Oh, right now I'm kidding. You know, we're
living the dream. It's Los Angeles palm trees right outside. And we're here to talk to you guys
about the picture show. Uh, yeah, there's a palm tree out there, isn't there? Many several.
What are you doing tonight? You said you're going to go meet the lady, the wife. I'm meeting the lady,
the anchor, the support system. I mean, yeah, I feel like we'll probably get dinner and watch a movie at
home or something. I mean, I, I, there's not much I like doing anymore that you know what this city
needs other than an animal is a mini golf. You know, like in Missouri, the options were go to see a
movie bowling or mini golf. The closest bowling alley is 30 miles from here. The closest mini golf
is 100 miles away, but it's beautiful weather all the time. And I'm fucking sick of it. I want to play
mini golf. Uh, I would, I would take a drive in over miniguff. There, I, well, I used to go to the
driving all the time. That's maybe we'll do that tonight. There's one, you know, it's, it's a little
too far, especially because when you go to the drive and you want to have a couple beers or something.
But it's a hot dog. That's like, I love that. There's hot dogs and hamburgers there. Well, I told you,
we were going to go and then we just never followed through with it. But there's a drive in roughly
40 minutes from here. You see a double speech. You sneak into that third speech if you want.
It's beautiful. I'm looking at what's playing because maybe I'll take in a film myself this evening.
Yes. Uh, I'm not trying to pile on here, but I'm scrolling down this list. The kitchen is almost
nowhere to be found on the list. The kitchen bombed hard. You know what? 21 % on Rotten Tomatoes. Good
boys at an 83 % which I don't understand. I couldn't have less interest in seeing that film.
Lion King 52%. I wish it was lower to be honest. You don't want to see where do you go, Bernadette?
What the fuck is that? Or the Kate Blanchett thing? Worst title I've ever seen. Worst billboard
I've ever seen. She's in it and then I see Kristen Wigg in the trailer. I'm like, all right, I like her.
And then I find out Richard Linklater directed the thing. I got to tell you, there hasn't been one
god damn Richard Linklater movie I've ever wanted to see. Not one. School of rock.
No zero interest. You've never seen it? No. It's hilarious. It's genuinely hilarious. I'm telling you
every trailer I've never seen a Richard Linklater days and confused. You've seen days and confused.
I have tried several times to watch it. I find it very boring. I don't like it. Everybody wants some?
I tried watching that because my buddies in it. You know, it wasn't intolerable but I didn't want
to finish it. I didn't care. And boyhood could give two shit masterpiece class couldn't give two
shits. Wow. The three or four flicks where Ethan Hawke is walking around bridges with the sun behind
him. Each better than the one before it. They're all great before sunrise sunset and midnight.
And then they're great. Look, I'm not saying the guy makes bad moves. Wait, you like Bernie though.
I know you like Bernie. Yeah. That's what you think, Letter. That's Linklater. Yeah. That was
the only movie he's ever made that I was like, oh, I want to see that. I'm not saying the other ones
are bad. I just they they just don't spark my interest in any way. I'm not going to try to force you
but I would strongly recommend School of Rock which is just a comedy classic. It's fantastic. Ready or
not. Oh, okay. I was going to say it's not Margarita. Yeah. That's that's got a hundred percent
right now, which he didn't open yet. That's why. Don't you love that fucking trick on Rotten Tomatoes?
Like before the movie opens, it's got a hundred percent and half the time. Yeah. What is that? Yeah.
Yeah. Nothing is playing. Angel has that's not open yet either. Blinded by the light has a 94 percent.
What is that movie about? Has that another fucking Beatles movie? No. Although I could talk for
four days about how bad yesterday was but uh of course it was. People let it go with the god damn
Beatles already. Listen to a new band that has come out in the last 50 fucking years. I love the
enough already. I love the Beatles and has nothing to do with yesterday which was an absolute
portion of the film. Could you imagine if they never existed? Yes, I can. Yes, I can. We had the
beach boys. We had the stones. We had a lot of other bands that did great shit. Give it the
fuck up already. I can't. If I you're one more fucking person, talk to me about the Beatles,
I'm going to puke. Sorry. Go. I'm saying the movie's bad. I have no issue with the Beatles. But uh
I'm saying it's bad because the premise is fucking absurd. It is absurd. Stupid. And you wouldn't believe
how bad that movie. Well, you would of course. Blinded by the light is a uh from the director of
Bendit like Beckham and it's a it's a kid. Um uh who finds himself through the love of Bruce
Springsteen. But I do think the movie looks cute. I like Bruce Springsteen. I'll probably see it.
Oh, isn't it like a kid in Scotland or whatever? Well, I'm confused. Bruce speaks down
on what we go through. No, he's the kid is Indian, I believe. Oh no, it's India. That's right. I'm
still somewhere else. Yeah. I don't know specifics. Uh yeah. It's like he's like this guy is singing
about us, even though he's singing about Jersey. Correct. Yeah. Okay. I, you know, I'll probably check
around. But it's not a great time for the movies as we all know. However, these movies we're talking
about aren't super hero movies. They, you know, they're trying something else. Yeah. Look,
what are you going to do? Let's look. I'll take a blinded by the light over another fucking biopic.
Right. Absolutely. I still don't want to say it. But at least it's a different approach. Uh,
I, again, I can't believe good boys has an 83%. I can't believe Angry Birds 2 has a 73%.
Jesus Christ. I didn't see the array out of the house. The original Angry Birds came out years
after the app was popular. I mean, I don't know who's saying these things. Uh, it's not a great time.
Those are the furious presents Hobbs and Shaw. That's the full title. I didn't know that.
Well, that's got a 66. How does it do? I'll talk about Hobbs and Shaw in tonight's Pat's movie.
Well, why don't you take us on over Pat before I continue to scream about every movie in its rating.
I'm happy to, Joe, because I saw fast and the furious present Hobbs and Shaw. Well,
do you start us there, baby? Hobbs and Shaw in this economy. I was and Ryan Reynolds yet
another a plus plus celebrity in a cameo that should have gone to a struggling fucking actor
that needed a part. Yeah. People. The middle class is gone. It's gone. I guarantee they gave
them a million dollars for one day of work. Right. It's from the director of Deadpool 2,
um, which is a, I finally watched, by the way, it's very fun. It's a fucking masterpiece.
It's really a fun movie. Great jokes throughout. Uh, so look fast and the furious. I've seen most of
the main series. I don't think I saw Tokyo drift. It's not a racial issue. I just think I missed it.
And I don't think I saw the last one, but each one of them blends together into sort of a gelatinous
blob of cars and girls' asses. And I can't say I loved any of them. The Paul Walker won. They did
everything they could to make that kind of moving and it worked. There were people crying. But like,
when Vin Diesel and these movies is talking about family and the importance of family,
and you look around at these audiences and people leaning forward in their seats, like nodding their
heads. Oh my god. I mean, I'm blown away that these movies, I mean, we've got nine of them at this
point. And now we're spinning them off like it's Star Wars. Now, does anybody in this entire
franchise, excuse me, does anybody ever once say gas, grass or ass, nobody rides for free? If they do,
I bet it's in the first one because the first one is entertaining. And it's like a, it's more
along the lines of a much, much, much, much, much better movie called End of Watch with Jill and Hall
and Michael Pania. Wait, fast. And the furious one is like End of Watch. It's a small subdued
like crime thriller. Oh, I didn't know that. With some car action in it. End of watch I think is
great. It's nothing. It's nowhere near as good. But they just immediately got bigger and bigger and
bigger. And now they're like James Bond. I mean, it's cars flying through the sky. It's, I mean,
that thing with Idris Elba, like where he like, like hip slides down the side of the building. I'm
like, guys, for Christ's sake, can we keep it someone on Earth? Well, the reason he can do that,
Joe, is because, and I'm not spoiling anything, Idris Elba is portraying a cyborg. They've brought
cyborgs into the mix. He's a cyborg. So, by the way, people, while we're on the subject of a film
that stars the rock, I am desperately trying to find one piece of advertising, print advertising,
that doesn't feature the rock or shack. If you can find it, please send it to the end doing
commercials, too. Just every, every, every, is there a product in the store that is
insponsored by shack at this point? They got, they got Kevin Hart now advertising like deodorant. Yeah.
I mean, Kevin, give some money to the others. I'm telling you, it's the middle class going away.
Yeah. And here's what's interesting, and I talked about this today with a friend of mine.
The places, what used to happen was a George Clooney type, or whomever, would have to go to Japan
to secretly do a commercial where they got a lot of money for it. It's the plot of
lost in translation with Bill Murray's character. Right. And now it's happening here. These
A -list celebrities are doing commercials, and look at where, look at the direction our economy is
heading in. It is literally following the trend of countries in Asia. Yeah. It will be, you will be
immensely wealthy or dirt fucking poor. There will be no in between. Yeah. And now, and now our
celebrities are doing here what they were having to go to Asian countries to do, which was secretly
promote products over there. Right. Because over there, that's what celebrities do. Right.
Now they do it here too. Anyway, sorry, I'm sorry. I'm taking away off Hobbs and Shaw. I'm in a real
socio -political mood tonight. The rock portrays Hobbs, Jason Statham portrays Shaw.
When the rock appeared in, maybe fast five or whatever, I don't remember, I saw it with Pete,
I recall. But that one was kind of good, and they brought the rock in, and that's when they started
putting the tongue in the cheek. And they weren't taking it so seriously, and that one was kind of fun.
So this one is really leaning into the quote fun, the entire movie Hobbs and Shaw are telling each
other how ugly they are, how much bigger each other's dicks are than the other. It's a lot of ball
breaking kind of a 48 hours type thing. None of these jokes are really land. They're not that funny.
They do have a little bit of chemistry. The plot, as it were, is there uniting to save the world
and stop this vicious cyborg. But the movie ain't good. Where it kind of gets interesting is that
they're like, how are we going to get out of this? And they zoom in on the rock's face and he goes,
I got to go home. For reasons not quite explained, he takes them to his homeland of Hawaii.
And there he encounters his entire family where they all bond together to help get out of this thing.
So at the end, it's the rock, I'm sorry, Samoa, maybe, but it's the rock and all these Samoans in his
family. And I'm sorry, I don't, I don't want to be wrong. Is he? He's Samoa. Okay. So
that's a little fun. And at the end, all these guys hook their trucks together and they're pulling a
helicopter. And there's a train of vehicles flying through the air. It completely abandons any sort
of reality. But it's kind of a cool stunt. The audience was lapping it up. I saw it in IMAX,
which added a little something. If you do the AMC stubs, always go in IMAX or 3D because you feel
like you're getting your money's worth. But ultimately, I cannot recommend Hobbs and Shaw, you know,
who I did enjoy was Jason Statham's sister, who the rock really wants to fuck. And her name is
Vanessa Kirby. Helen Mirin is in this thing. It's, it's fine. You know. Okay. Okay.
Oh, this is my fear that the John Wick franchise. That third one was a lot of flash and the least
substance of the three. Yeah. And I'm like, here we go. There's going to be like eight John Wicks
now. Instead of getting this really cool closure tight trilogy or whatever, they're just going
to keep making these things and they're going to get more and more ridiculous as the one started to
already. Oh, John Wick will be in fast and the furious territory very soon. And then there'll be a
crossover, I'm sure. Yeah. So anyway, I watched the production house called small time monsters,
small town monsters, excuse me. They do a lot of documentary about small town monsters, big
foot, lockness, the bellwitch, Jersey devil, that kind of stuff. Right. In America, I like a lot
of their stuff. I just watched back to back big foot documentaries that put out one I think was
called the story and one, the second one was called the search. So the one was just getting the
history of big foot and and sightings and all that sort of thing. And the second one was about
them actually going into the search with the most legitimized and dedicated big foot watch group
in the country. Okay. Who is hellbent on not help. They're not I don't that sounds crazy. I don't
mean it like that. But they're set on killing a big foot so they can and they don't want to kill
it. But they're like the only way science is going to believe us is if we bring them a god damn
body. This is a documentary. Yeah. Okay. And then they're like that's what we're out here to do. We
want to kill a big foot so we can protect. It's an interesting approach. They're like so we can
protect the rest of the big foot because we believe these creatures exist. And as we overdevelop
land, they will have no home. But they're overdeveloping the land that we think they live in because they
have no proof. And the only way they'll believe these things exist is if they see a body. So we
actually have to kill one to save the rest. Yeah. I got to stop watching these things because they
never find the god damn big foot. This is what drives me. Oh, they didn't. I watch these things and then
halfway through I go it would have been in the paper if they found the damn thing. Of course. And I
just keep watching because I think well, maybe this slipped by the authorities. And it didn't it didn't
there's no big foot. There's no nothing at the end of this thing. There's just a guy saying why
not believe do they try to whip up any suspense of like they're in the woods and you think you might
see one. Yeah. Yeah. There's there's interesting they have audio clips and things where they're saying
like look they like so that there's a there's a there's a thing that happens with big foot
where it called rock falls where if they sense people are in cabins, the animals will surround the
cabin and throw debris onto the roof. Okay. I think almost as a like warning like get the
fuck out of here. And they said every time you you show a sign of you moving towards them,
they disappear into the forest. Right. So they do have audio for instance of like these rock falls and
and they have audio of like we think this is the grunt of one or whatever. Right. And like here's
a photo of what happened to a tree when we were chasing one. You know, it's stuff like that.
I saw a similar documentary where Bigfoot moved in with the Henderson family. Yeah. Yeah.
They get into that. They interview the Henderson. Yeah. Yes. John Lithgow was there. And what's
interesting is the Henderson say you know he hated being called Harry. Sure. Sure.
I watched a movie that was my god. It caused a bunch of controversy last year. I remember it was
in theaters for one night and they were trying police were trying to shut it down. But it's Lars
Von Trier's the house that Jack Bill police were trying to shut it. Why were they trying to
shut the MPA said even with the cuts you have made you cannot show this film in public why they found
it too disturbing too violent. So call it non -rated and you what the fuck is going on anymore. People
this is as ridiculous as the goddamn argument that Canada was banning the movie about the that
was like pro life. Yeah. It's like yeah guys. I don't agree with it either. I think it's bullshit.
You can show the movie. I agree. I mean Jesus fucking Christ. This is absurd anymore with this shit.
So he had done Nymphomaniac which was a I enjoyed certainly aspects of Nymphomaniac but it was
a very intense movie with a lot of graphic sex in it. This movie didn't really cause any controversy
but for some reason the violence and this thing really stirred people up and the deal is this.
It was an unrated version and the MPA said it broke ratings rules. I don't even know what that could
mean because why would it. So the MPA on November 28th is calling out IFC films over tonight's One
Night Only Screenings of the House, the Jack belt. The trade group says the showings violated its rules
because rather than being the abridged R -rated version that hits theaters in two weeks they were
of a decidedly gory or unrated directors cut. And what is the problem? I don't understand what the
problem is. IFC paid to make the movie. They're saying we're going to show it in our own theaters
for One Night Only. If you want to see this gory offensive version come on in. If you don't don't
what the fuck does the MPA have to do with this? So that's the screening of an unrated version of the
film and such close proximity to the release of the rated version without obtaining a waiver
is in violation of the rating system's rules. The effectiveness of the MPA depends on our ability
to maintain the trust and confidence of American parents. You didn't grease our palms. So we're
picked. That's what that means. I thought it was kind of crazy too. What I saw and I guess it was on
Amazon Prime, I think it's where you can see it. Lars von Trier loves stirring up shit. That's
nothing new. The movie is two and a half hours to me. I thought it was pretty great. I thought it
flew by, especially for being so long. How is Dylan in it? It's the best Matt Dylan performance since
there's something about Mary, which I do consider a fantastic performance. I loved him in the Bukowski film.
I like that too, but he's essentially playing a very similar character to the guy in something about
Mary. Pat Hilly, if he were a serial killer, which he almost kind of pushes that vibe a little further.
He's playing a dork and man, he's good. Dylan is an actor who is not always good, but he was great
in this movie. What it is is he's a serial killer. As with a lot of Von Trier movies lately, it's
divided into several segments. The first two or three segments are dark as fuck, but they're hilarious.
The first is Uma Thurmond's car is broken down. He picks her up and she is a nightmare. She is
annoying the shit out of him and eventually, you know, each of these segments ends with somebody being
killed, but tears loves those segments, but that guy loves to show a black screen with the same title.
Yeah. Yeah. The Thurmond segment is very funny. There's a segment with, yeah, her name is like
Slobhan Fallon, who you'll definitely recognize from being in every sitcom. She's the lady in
Seinfeld, who was like, yeah, buzzed up a jewel thief, Elaine. Oh, okay. Yeah. That roommate. Yeah.
Oh, yeah, she's great. He goes into this woman's house. He's pretending to be like a meter reader
and this scene is very violent and very dark, but it is extremely funny. And especially when the
police show up and Dylan is trying to like talk his way out of it. Honestly, the first half of
this thing plays like a hilarious dark comedy. Maybe that's just my sense of humor. I don't know.
At a certain point, the story's turned darker as you might imagine. He goes, he's dating this woman,
Riley Kyo, who was the star of the girlfriend experience, which is Sutterberg show on stars,
which I like the lot. She's beautiful. That scene gets very graphic. Even in, and I believe I
did see the R -rated version, even in this version, he cuts her boob off. You know? That's upsetting.
You don't want to see that. But well, here's the thing. I know the initial backlash about this film
was the violence portrayed against women. Okay. Is there a chance that this is some sort of
commentary on the on the sickness of men? Is there a chance that it's a commentary on the mistreatment
of women? Also, the women in the movie don't have a fucking problem with it. They did the movie.
Correct. So why are you trying to fuck their shit up? So now, Uma Thurman doesn't deserve to make any
money off of this movie she did. That might have been a very trying experience for her. That was
a, you know, that was a chance she took as an artist or whatever. It's her second movie with them. She was
fantastic in Infomania. She doesn't get to make any money off of the movie because other people
decide it's too, don't go see the fucking movie. When the fuck did art fans and artists become the
goddamn ministers and preachers? This is the shit that we used to rail against in the 80s and 90s
when fucking preachers would get up and say we had to ban rock albums. Yeah. This is PMRC shit.
What the fuck is wrong with everybody? It essentially did not get a release and Lars von Trier
like give the man the benefit of the doubt. The man makes very serious, interesting movies. They're
not for everybody. But he clearly thinks about his subjects a lot. I think the reason people turned
on Von Trier to some extent is that he goes to these festivals and says things to wind people up.
He says like look Hitler had some good ideas. That kind of stuff. That's not great. But this movie
especially where it ends up. It's Bruno Gans from the Wim Wenders movies, Wings of Desire and all that
is basically Matt Dillon's guide into hell. The end of the movie basically takes place in hell.
Oh wow. The sets in this thing on a low budget are absolutely stunning. The movie is
intentionally button pushing. It's disturbing in spots. But it's I think unquestionably a piece of art.
I thought it was really a good movie. Seek it out if you can. And von Trier always makes movies
that get you talking at least, which is not nothing. Why don't we commend that anymore? I agree.
I'll lighten it up for a moment. All right. I'm a big honeymooners fan as you know. Sure.
If you haven't seen the set of the entertainer version, I tried. I didn't want it bad.
Yeah. I saw I found these honeymooners specials from the 70s that I didn't know existed on Amazon
Prime. Yeah. There's a Christmas one of Valentine's one and a one called second honeymoon.
Okay. The entire original cast except the actress that played Trixi and the replacement is
identical to her. So I'm only imagining the original actress actress either died or said no.
Okay. I think her name was Jane Randolph. All right. But anyway, it's the rest. You know,
the other three are it's the it's the it's the original cast. And I'm a sucker for this shit.
I mean, it's a little dated seeing them do this style of comedy in 77 when this came out.
And it's weird seeing it in color. Right. But I watched the Valentine's Day one today. And it's like
Alice has a secret job that she's not telling Ralph about because she wants to she wants to secretly
save money to buy him this great Valentine's Day present. And then the job is doing like an
operator switchboard thing. So she she has these call lists for work. And then he finds the call lists
and then also finds like a new insurance policy. And and then thinks that Alice is trying to murder him
because she's having he thinks she's having an affair with somebody kind of a leap. But okay.
It's fucking hilarious. Right. The whole thing is it's there's a part that the gift she's buying
him is a tailor made suits. She's got to try to secretly get his measurements. So after he's
already paranoid that she's trying to murder him. He's like sitting and eating dinner and he doesn't
want to eat it because he thinks she's poisoning him. And she starts measuring his shoulders and
shit while he's sitting there. And he does the classic Gleason -like wide eye. Yeah. Yeah.
It's I'm a sucker for it. It's you know it's it's it's great Gleason. I love Gleason. I just love
him. The guy can do very little wrong in my eyes as an entertainer. He does a lot of not great shows
and not great movies. But I'm a sucker for him. You ever see the sting too? No. I've never seen it
either. But I'm curious. Here's the great tragedy with Gleason to me. He didn't get to do more
drama or maybe he chose not to do more. But if you see him in nothing in common with Tom Hanks.
It's great in him. And you see him in record. Yeah. Requiem for a heavyweight. The Rod Sirling
script. Yeah. With him in Anthony Quinn. My god almighty. The guy is fucking tremendous in a dramatic
role. He's great. The hustler of course. Yeah. He's just tremendous in these dramatic roles. And he
just very, very rarely did it. And I wish he would have done it more. Great line in record for a heavyweight.
Where he's talking about how scummy the boxing businesses in Gleason goes. They'd call these
things in sewers if the ceilings were high enough. I always felt that applied to stand up comedy.
For sure. But if you're a Gleason fan and you're a Honeymooner's fan, these these three specials
are worth checking out. If you're not, you're not going to like them. All right.
I saw Stan and Ollie. Oh, how was it? I want to see that. I think you'd like it a lot. I liked it
with some reservations. But I love old Hollywood. It is the story of Stan Laurel and Oliver Hardy.
And what I liked the most is about how it went into how a partnership like that can go bad. Just
like a marriage, a comedy partnership can just go bad things that things are unspoken. Things you
think are totally cool. Somebody might be harboring ill will about for 20 years. And I didn't know much
about the history of Laurel and Hardy at all. I didn't know they had problems much like Dean Martin
and Jerry Lewis. Yeah. But those two guys really had some issues. And much like Martin and Lewis,
their wives factored in as well. Because that sort of thing happens. You know, like they they
talk to their wives and the wives talk to each other and then people find out stuff and blah blah blah.
But ultimately, it is a story of friendship. It is a story about friendship surviving Hollywood,
which is very tricky. And what I can most recommend it for is the amazing performances of
John C. Riley and Steve Cougan, two of our great actors. I love them both so much. Riley is in
prosthetics to be as fat as Hardy. But I got to say, they're not noticeable. They're not distracting.
And usually with prosthetics, you can kind of lose the humanity of the person with all the
shit on their face. But Riley, he nails the impression, but he's really, really great in the movie.
Like, you know, sometimes people just do the impression and lose the humanity. He nails it.
Cougan is more like, it's amazing how much he looks like the guy, which you don't even think about,
you know, until you see it. But it's like, wow, he looks identical to him. They had a great chemistry.
It's a sweet story, a sweet movie. I recommend it. It's certainly entertaining.
I definitely want to see it. And I found it hilarious that that came out in the same month as
Holmes and Watson, which was essentially another biotech. With John C. Riley. With Jesse Riley,
one had a 95 % and Holmes wanted to set had like a seven. Yeah. I haven't seen it.
The fact that I haven't seen a Riley Farrell movie that's been out for a year is a testament to how
many people have told me that they, you know, just like me and some night, I'll do it too.
I'll watch it. When it hits Hulu or something, I'll put it on to see. But I gotta say,
many people have been like, I just thought to myself, fuck you. Critics don't like comedy.
There's no way Riley and Farrell did a bad movie. And they started watching it and were like, holy shit.
Uh, Farrell, I'm a huge fan. He's, he's, uh, I'm afraid potentially has turned that corner
where it's like, and I think it's going to happen now. Melissa McCarthy too. So fucking funny.
And they turn this corner where they do too many goddamn indie. And as I'm saying,
Gleason should have done more drama. There's a balance to it. And it's like they do
enough of these goddamn indie things that when they start going back to the comedies,
they don't give the comedies the attention to detail that they give the indie and gritty or stuff.
Yeah. So then they start doing these paint by number comedies. It's what fucking have it with
Sandler. Yeah. So you'd go off and do punch drunk love. You're like, oh my god, this is fucking brilliant.
And then he goes back and does like, like Mr. Deeds. And you're like, what are you doing, dude?
I will say Mr. Deeds was the last sort of truly funny of those. I think Mr. Deeds is great.
Trotoro is awesome. I'm having a hard time thinking. I remember you saying that. I'm having
a hard time thinking of one of these several of you, but you know, you hear what I'm saying.
Absolutely. He go off and do spanglish, which I don't think looked like a good movie. But
spanglish is okay too. You know, but there's many that were terrible. No, my point is it's
spanglish was clearly him trying to do something heavier with more emotion and whatever. And then he
turns it in that does a little nicky. You're like, dude, put the same attention. Like Billy Madison had
spanglish attention. Yeah. You know what I mean? Like, like, bridesmaids McCarthy nominated for an
Oscar. Yeah. You know, and it's like, and I hope I hope she doesn't fucking, I hope when she goes back
to comedy again, it's, it's good. But, but like, Ferrell, it's like, you know, he does like the
like, stranger than fiction. Fucking great flick. Yeah. And turns around and goes and does kicking
and screaming. And you're like, dude, what are you doing? I can almost guarantee it's agent bullshit
mixed with actor insecurity. And they'll be like, look, all right, man, do it. But you're going to
lose your public. And then when they say do a comedy, it's like, do some lowest common denominator
shit so you can keep earning. You don't want to lose that $20 million payday. So then it is do the
most broad down the middle thing you can find on God's green fuck. Would you not do stepbrothers too?
Well, the studio studio won't fund it. How?
Apparently the scripts written studio won't fund it. They were going to do it in Sacramento.
They needed a budget of $60 million. They wouldn't pay for it.
I don't, I don't, but they will do homes in Watson. They will do. Okay. You know, because that's
what the world need. It was yet another homes in Watson. How many fucking times we're going to tell
this goddamn story? I just read they're doing fuck guy Richie's doing part three with Downey junior.
I hate those movies. I mean, Jesus Christ. How many fucking homes in Watson? Are we going to?
And how many franchises like Downey, it's time for Downey junior is doing eight for them. None for him.
Like do something good. How many franchises do you need to be in? How many hundreds of millions of
dollars do you need? But Ferrell, you know, it's it all it all depresses me. These guys just kind of
flame out. I think if Anchorman two had grossed more, we would have gotten step brothers to Anchorman two,
I thought was funny enough to warrant its existence. It did not match the first. Nobody's going to argue
that, but it was funny. Here's the thing. Watch the alternate cut on the DVD. That's like the completely
different version. It's hilarious. You know, like why is this not the version in the movie? It's got
the scenes from the commercial. Right. Like when he meets, when they can't deal with the black
co -worker, you know, all that shit, like it's fucking so funny. And it's like, why is this? Why,
why would you release this version of it? The problems with the problem with following an Anchorman
or following a step brothers is that people love those so much. They've seen them a hundred times.
That anything less than that funny is seen as a failure. But even the even the version of Anchorman two
that I saw in theaters twice had so much more laughs and good jokes and funny performances
than almost every comedy that comes out. But you ask anyone about Anchorman two, they're like,
it's fucking suck because the comparison is to one of the all time great times. He's doing a
Ron Burgundy podcast right now. I haven't heard that. I saw a commercial for it. The commercial was so
not funny. Yeah. I can't believe I'm saying this. I've never listened to the Ron Burgundy podcast.
I know. I know. Because the commercial was so not funny. And I was like, I think he's gone. I
think he's in Jim Carrey territory. Yeah. Who's the king of this? Jim Carrey Tory. Yeah.
That he's the king of this shit. Yeah. It's like Jim go talk with your ass again. Yeah. People
like it. Every third movie talk with your ass. Will Farrell, every third movie be the guy that flips
the fuck out all the time? The issue is they chase the Oscar for so long, which is what they all
care about, that eventually they become too old and the comedy becomes sad. They waste their prime comedy
years because Jim Carrey talking out of his ass now at age 65 is not going to be great. So it's
a bummer. If he made an ace venture or three, I'd be there in two seconds. By the way, speaking
of podcasts and, you know, Lord knows it doesn't need our fucking help. But I will say a real
treat has been this Conan O 'Brien podcast. Oh, I heard it's good. I've been listening to it. And
maybe it is that it broke my heart so much watching him implode over at NBC that I kind of stop watching
the show. But I mean, he was, he's probably my top comedy influence. I used to watch that show
every single night till 1 .30 AM and go to school at 6 .30 AM. And just to hear him talk to people
and kind of be real because Conan is one of those comedians who for better or worse can't shut it off.
To hear him just connect with people, the Howard Stern interview is fantastic. He's a really solid
interviewer and it's also very funny. I do recommend it. Great. I'm sure it's making him more and more
money. Oh, this fucking, the fucking onion AV club, they showcast 10 podcasts a week. We can't,
we haven't got to mention in five fucking years. We never get mentioned in these things. No, nobody sick.
That's why we took it to Patreon, baby. That's right. The, uh, my friend Marina Franklin was just on
the Conan O 'Brien podcast. Oh, really? So listen to her episode. She's a dear friend and very funny.
My last, you know what? I don't even need to do my last one. I was going to do House on Haunted Hill
because we both saw that. Yes. Not great. It's, look, I enjoyed it. The origin of the original. Yeah,
we saw that at the, at the horror marathon thing that Pat and I went to where we saw the thing
from another world. Look, I enjoyed it. I always enjoy seeing Vincent Price. They did some cool
directing work and it was that a, uh, that was directed by the same guy. What's his face? Castle,
right? William Castle Castle. Yeah. Uh, he does some really fun, exploitative, like sort of camera
stuff that was big in the 50s. You know, it was in that time period of putting, you know,
uh, uh, the gags in the, in the actual theater to scare the audience. Who was the basis for the
John Goodman character in, uh, Matt and I. Yes, he's Matt and I, um, it's an enjoyable film. I
own it. I had never watched the DVD that I own. I, I liked seeing it in the theater. I thought it
had some legit jump scares in it, uh, for that time period, which I had never really seen a good
jump scare in the, in the late 50s, early 60s, but I thought that was pretty cool. Um,
the movie, uh, all in all is a little lackluster, but I, I did enjoy it and I, I, I thought it was
a fun watch. Yeah, I didn't hate it. It was just kind of silly fun, I guess. Um, but it shouldn't
have been the kickoff of this festival because it put me into a, a sleep, uh, quick, uh, I got my third
job. Now you did it already. You went first. Why do? You did, you went first with, uh,
Tobs and Shaw. Now you're right. All right. Um, quick, uh, scary stuff. Yes.
Just read an interesting graphic novel called Batman White Night. Okay. I wouldn't say it's great,
but it's enjoyable and it's worth reading. Um, the premise of it is the Joker gets put on
medication and becomes sane. Okay. And Batman is running around Gotham being like he's a fucking
maid. Yeah. Yeah. Don't trust him. Uh, he's done all this horrible shit. We just don't have proof of it.
And then Batman slowly becomes the villain in Gotham because people are like, who's this judgmental
vigilante asshole playing by his own rules? Right. You got to give people a chance. Okay. Uh,
it's, it's an interesting commentary on this current climate we live in, uh, the, the tables
turning. Uh, you could probably guess where it goes. I won't tell you. But it's a fun read. Uh, I
would have liked it a little. My own personal taste. I would have liked to see you go in a different
direction ultimately, but I thought it was a really interesting read. Uh, and I love that Mr. Freeze is
a supporting character in it because he's my favorite one of my favorite Batman villains.
Um, you like the Schwarzenegger portrayal? Uh, to me, that defined it. Yeah. I feel everybody
cheers. Yeah. Pinkstone does a really funny impression of that. We'll get really drunk and really
stone. It'll go. My name is Freeze. Loin it well. Uh, yeah. He doesn't, he really exaggerates it
when we're really fucked up, but it makes me laugh really hard. Okay. Okay. Yeah. Uh, well,
should we get to the picture? Let's get to the picture. All right. Um, yeah. The picture is
scary stories, scary stories to tell in the dark directed by Andre Orvidol with the, with the line
through the Oh, which like, how do you get that? Do you have to clear that with somebody? Uh, look
man, I love motorhead. Every time I'm typing it, I'm like, if this auto spell doesn't put that
fucking room, I don't want the room. It's, it ain't getting up there. Yeah. I, I don't know how to do it.
No, I don't, I know there's a way. I just don't know how to do it. Yeah. Uh, produced by Gilear
Del Toro. And Joe and I saw this together. And I got to say, I again, and again, I'm, I'm doing
the, the personal training three times a week and I'm on a medication and I get tired. So I was like
confused sort of by, by the book, the book that's writing itself throughout this movie. And the
other night when I saw a picture, I, I walked in after and watched the last half of scary stories
telling the dark again. I'm still not sure what happens in this movie.
You're not sure? Well, the plot, okay. So the plot is, walk us through the plot is it's a bunch.
First of all, let me start with the setting. 1969 in a small town called, I think it's called
Mill Valley, Pennsylvania. Right off the bat, I'm in. You got a small town, Pennsylvania, Halloween
movie. Yeah, about a bunch of kids in a simpler time. I think you're thinking of Hill Valley, but
I think it was called Mill or Mill Creek or something. Um, okay. Anyway, I was 100 % in from the jump
once I saw that. I was also a big fan of these books as a kid. You're right, Mill Valley. Sorry.
The way the book, the way the original books, the stories, we know, how do they make this into
the stories in the movie? There's a, there's a, there's a legend in the town of a haunted house
that this woman lived in who was apparently trapped in the basement her entire life. And she would
tell stories to children. And when she told the stories to children, the children would die.
The way that they, the way that the character in the story died. Right. They go into the haunted
house. They steal one of her books. And the stories in the book start writing themselves.
And the reason they're writing themselves, which is eventually explained is that her, her ghost
is writing is still writing these stories from the netherworld. Why to get revenge on what her family
in this town did to her? Okay. That's, that's how the book works. Right. So they, these are the latest
group of kids to be involved with the book. So she starts writing stories about these kids.
Of course, the stories reflect the stories from the original books that we read as children
and kids die. And they bring to life many of the very cool visuals from the artwork from the
original books. They do their own versions of the stories. They do new takes on them. Like I,
I went out right after we saw the film to Barnes and Noble and bought the three books because I
wanted to immediately read the stories they used in the film to see how much they were similar
that they add a lot of detail to the stories in the, in the film. But it's the same basic gist.
I will say what I think this movie is that it's core. And I think it worked very brilliantly
was this is an anthology horror film where they put more emphasis on the wrap around story than they
think that by doing that, they were able to create a very real and believable world with characters
you cared about in this wrap around and, and within this wrap around able to jump into these little
essentially vignettes of how each character gets haunted by the story and dies or whatever it is.
I loved that they said it in the 60s. They had no real reason to do that. They just did. I thought
that was a really cool setting. I thought that up the stakes. Yeah, it worked well for Annabelle and
which we talked about. Yeah, it works well for this too. I loved the kids in it. I loved that
they were real kids. They were relatable. I loved that it had funny moments without it being goofy and
stupid. It was a, it was one of those perfect four character dynamics. It was like you had the,
the girl who was the leader. Then you had the one kid who was the scholar. Then you had the one
kid who was the jester. Then you had one kid who was the rogue. Like I thought they did a really great
job doing that sort of fellowship of the ring dichotomy or whatever or dynamic, excuse me.
And I really liked it. And for a PG 13 movie that's geared towards tweeners,
Jesus Christ, man, there were some really fucking intense scares in it. Like there were some really
raw scares in it, which I was shocked by. And I was just enamored when Pat and I were walking out
of the theater. I said, if nothing else, I am so happy that they're making movies again like this
for kids. Yeah. Because when I was growing up, one of my favorite movies was something wicked this
way comes. That's an extremely dark. It's awesome. And it's extremely dark. And there's danger
and people die. Right. But it's for kids. Right. And I was so happy that they didn't pull any punches
with this and made a dark because these books were banned. They were very controversial. Yeah.
My favorite thing about this was that that it is sort of giving birth to that genre. I am quite certain
that the success of it helped that because it was R rated. I'm sure a lot of kids saw that movie,
but it's a R rated scary movie about kids, essentially, the first it. This was testing those PG 13
waters. I hope that it brings the genre back because a lot of my favorite movies when I was a kid.
And I was a pussy when I was a kid. But I loved all that shit. Your, your, your lab rents, your return
to Oz. I liked a dark kids movie. This is dark. And I admired that my issue with the movie is.
And I know that anthology movies rarely make any money. They're almost all bumps. Even when you do
like four rooms and something outside of the horror genre, they lose money. I would have preferred this
as an anthology because I had suction affection for these books. I used to obsessively read these
books. The illustrations were incredible. What this movie does really well is bring those illustrations
to life. I remember, I don't remember what I had for breakfast today, but I can remember the girl squeezing
the zit and the spiders coming out of her face and that book. I remember the kind of the fat ghost
woman that comes down the hallway. I remember her very vividly and seeing them brought to life was
a lot of fun. I just couldn't really sink my teeth into the wraparound story. Not enough to say this
was bad or something like that. And I like the kids, particularly the lead girl and the nerdy guy.
But like right off the beginning, they come out and they call that the Hispanic kid a wetback. And I'm
like, okay, we're going to get into, especially with Del Toro. I'm like, we're going to get into some
interesting shit with this. And we really kind of don't. For me, the wraparound story was not
particularly compelling. I think I would have liked it more as each of these four kids having their own
story and not just having their little moments of terror, which work well. But for me as a whole,
I wish the movie had been a little more something. As an adult, I would have more enjoyed a
straight -up anthology. I agree. As a kid, I would have been way invested in their story.
That I said to a friend today. I go, I was jealous that I wasn't 14 when I saw this.
I hope kids are going to see this thing. It's doing well. It was like scary goonies.
It really rests in the sweet spot between the spielbergness of stranger things and the hardcore
cut edge of it. It rests really. And I got to be honest, the scares in this were scarier than the
scares in it, chapter one. The scares in this were, I was more freaked out by the monsters in this.
It's not to shit on it. I'm just saying on it, no pun intended. But I thought they did it. I was
really surprised at like, there were people in the theater at one point, audibly after a sequence
going, oh my god, just because it was just like intense. It wasn't gory. It was kind of gory.
It was kind of gross at times. And I love that they didn't pull any punches. I love that they
made the asshole's cop in the town be racist towards the kid. That was realistic to me.
I love that the asshole kid was drunk driving. And right when I thought they weren't going to talk
about it, the mom goes, are you drunk as he's getting out of it? I like that they didn't pull back on
any of that stuff. I was like, yes, this is stand by me. Give it to me. Make the bullies are fucking
cock suckers in this movie. They are fucking cock suckers. And for me, you know, bully Stephen King
does boys better than anybody. But like I was bullied for years and years. I always have such a
more fighting interest in these kind of movies. If there's a great bully character. So when
spoiler alert, the bully is removed from the picture very early. I felt it lost kind of some urgency
for me. But I agree. But I think I think they were very aware like we can't just do it. Correct.
So had the bully been right or die till the end? Yeah. And had they delved more into racism
and whatever. Deeper and deeper themes like that. It's like they would have just been
copying it at that point. Right. Well, this season of Stranger Things, you know, was more adult.
There was way more profanity. The scares were way more intense. I liked it. I had my issues with it.
But I think they're learning that kids can take a lot more shit. It's all the stuff trying to
protect kids. It's like, do you know what the world is like? Like that doesn't go away. Kids are
kids are facing horrors all the time. I saw a lot of kids when I went to see it. Ultimately, I thought
that this movie was roughly on a par with it. My expectations were lower going in. So it kind of
balances out. But I thought the movie was solid. I wish. I don't know. I think that the
the connective tissue, I think you're right. That's going to lure kids in. Kids, we're not going to
fall for an anthology thing. They don't get into that kind of shit. So it works better for them.
And I hope this leads to a lot of these movies in this franchise and a lot of scary kids movies.
I desperately hope so. Ultimately, I wanted more attention paid to the to the spider's it to
but maybe these stories didn't have legs. Maybe they I'm sure they tried to do it as an anthology.
Well, I realize these aren't really stories. They're moments. They certainly made the stories much
more involved than they did. Yeah, I mean, I've read they were a page long. Yeah, that night when I bought
we went right to Barnes and Noble. I bought the trilogy. I went home. I that night read every
story that was in the movie in about 12 minutes. Yeah. And you're like half of them end with just like
and then the thing was gone. And you're just like, okay. Yeah. But there are some great, great
stories they didn't cover. And I'm sure they're going to do more. They'll do more. How it could work
and all this stuff. So I hope they do a sequel. I look forward to that. And I love that I just was
really disheartened in this in this last 10 years or whatever films where any it was either a movie with
kids that didn't have any balls or a movie with kids that was rated are that a lot of kids weren't
going to get to see. Right. I love the return to dark fiction for children. I think it's fucking awesome.
I was in a, you know, a came out closed or it's closed. I don't know most of them. Okay. I was in one
that was closing in Burbank recently. I mean, the one over by the grove looked like they were about to
set it on fire for the insurance month. Yeah. Yeah. It was like thunder dome in there. The one in the
one in Burbank was closing. It's closed now. And they did everything in the stores for sale including
the shelves. You could buy the shelves. That's what they did with the grove one too. So but I went down,
I went in one night, I was killing some time and I went into the toy aisle. Like maybe I'll find
something cool for 50 % off. Yeah. And I was and I was thrilled. Every I took pictures of all of them.
Every fucking toy for like 12 to 13 year olds was like try to stop the nose from exploding. Not all
over everybody or try to stop the toilet from exploding. Right. Or be careful before the guy with his
butt out farts in your face. I was so happy that the kids were going back in that direction again
because that's what I was into when I was a kid. It was a fucking slime pit and dissect an alien.
Right. Right. And you know, build a zombie and all that shit. So I think it kind of goes hand in hand
with this movie. And I hope we get more movies like this. And I loved it. I agree with everything
you're saying about the genre. Love is too strong for me. I would say my hog is, you know,
when you're real hard, it's like facing up to your chin. And when you're soft, obviously it's
pointing down to your shoes. Yes. My hog is pointing straight out. Two hogs. My hog is is neither
up nor down three o 'clock hog right now. Right now. And that is the sequel. I've been secretly working
on to three o 'clock. Yeah. Great movie too. There's fun in it. There's high points in it. I
certainly recommend it. But I didn't, I didn't have the love you did. And that's okay. That's our show,
folks. Joderosa comedy on Instagram and Twitter. Catch me out there when you can. I hope to see it
a live show. Joderosa info. If you want to know where I'm performing at. See you later. The Patrick
Walsh very rarely on Twitter and Instagram. We will see you next time. We don't know what we're doing
next, but we're, we've stockpiled a bunch of good stuff for you. And we hope you stick around and
join us on the Patreon. Thank you all. We love you. We'll see you next time. We'll see you in hell.