Girl I see you and Elle.
How I see you and Elle.
These, Joe DeRosa and Pat Walsh here today discussing the film, Dragon Slayer, not Dragon's
layer, the video game, which I wonder if that's a play on that, but Dragon Slayer, and
not Dragon, not Dragon layer about people who fucked dragons, either.
No, I would agree, no.
This is a different kind of picture.
I had never ever seen Dragon Slayer, this was a first, I got the 4K edition, and we'll get
there.
We'll talk about it.
What's going on in your world, Joey?
I thought I was sick this week, I ended up not being sick, I thought I was going to have
fucking COVID again, and I didn't, and I got to tell you, it was almost a disappointment.
You almost, at this point, welcomed the five day break from this horror show, we're all
forced to live in, and no COVID hits people a lot harder than that, I'm not making light
of anything, but for me, it's been a five day pass to sit on the couch, get McDonald's
delivered and watch TV, and sometimes it's all you need, it was just allergies, I went
down to Austin, I was down there for a few days, my allergies just kick up like crazy when
I'm down there, so I saw some friends, I didn't do any stand up, I just hung out, and I had
a good time, I had a good time, ate some food, I mean, not just to eat, you know, eat
food every day, ate some Austin -type food, got some great breakfast tacos, and some barbecue,
I think I'm losing my flair for barbecue, I don't enjoy it the way we used to, I like it
anymore, I like it, but something about it, I don't know, this last trip, I had it twice
and I was just like, the second time I was like, you know, I don't know, it's a real
distinct, you know, it's heavy, you're dealing with a heavy, it's not grilled food, it's
barbecue, you know, it's smoked and it's heavy meal, you know, the sauce is full of sugar,
people forget the sauce being full of sugar, I usually do no sauce, yeah, then you're
good, that's the skill living, to an extent, yeah, you know, I've always loved Austin, I
still do, I saw some friends, like I said, went to the comedy clubs, but didn't perform,
just kind of hung out, it was a good time, what about you, Pat, oh, you know, I'm supposed
to be in Atlanta, so I'm just kind of trying to adjust my year and figure out how that's
all going to work out when I'm going to go to Atlanta, when this works with my other projects,
etc. Okay, due to the strike, but that's about all that's going on, I've been, I stopped dating
because I felt I was being pretty reckless in a variety of ways, I do have a date this
Sunday night, but you know, there's not much happening, there's just not much happening
in my life, I wish I could tell you there was, I'm working on a couple projects, even though
you know, we're not technically supposed to work, I'm allowed to think, and so I'm thinking
and getting ready to think about what my next project shall be, okay, that's it, but you know,
I had things happening with momentum and now we got to see how long this strike's going to be,
that's all I can do, it's all anybody can do. Yeah, it is a bitch, I'm sorry, you know, you know,
sounds fun to, you know, not have to work and, you know, like I was just saying, you know,
oh, sit home and fuck it, you know, but it wears, I got enough of that during the pandemic,
I had enough sitting at home, not working, frankly, so, but it's got to be done.
Um, I sent Joe the other day and I'm not going to watch it, I don't think Joe's going to watch it,
but I'd love to hear either in the comments or through Emily or whatever it may be,
a review of this movie called, I Mordecai, you'll remember Mordecai with Johnny Depp being,
maybe the movie that was the final nail in his career before we got to the amber herd business,
but I Mordecai, the poster of this thing is four actors that are not even in the same room,
clearly, it's one of those posters where they superimpose everybody, you got Sean Aston, Judhersh,
Carol Cain, and I don't know the other folks, the premise is Judhersh, a Holocaust survivor,
it's movies of comedy, Holocaust survivor born and raised in a different time, must face the realities
of modern world. When confronted with an unfamiliar object, an iPhone will Mordecai be able to fit
into a world that has changed so much around him. I want somebody out there to watch this movie and
give me a little review, either in the Patreon comments or send us a little message or something,
I need to know what this movie is about and what's happening in it and how are we doing a comedy
about a Holocaust survivor? Well, you could do a comedy about a Holocaust survivor. Why not?
Getting an iPhone and it sounds terrible, but you know, it sounds like suburban commando except
instead of an alien, it's a Holocaust survivor, like that to me does not add up to a good movie,
but I might be wrong. No, no, I think the movie sounds terrible. I was just answering the inquiry,
how are you going to do a movie about a comedy about a Holocaust survivor? I was saying, well, you
could. Yeah. Well, I guess life is beautiful was sort of like that for, you know. Did you see life
is beautiful with Roberto Benini? Yeah, I saw in the theater. A lot of people I found out after the
fact were very offended by that movie. I heard the same. I liked it. And there's been three at
least Holocaust comedy type movies about a guy trying to bring laughter to the concentration camps.
There's been life is beautiful, which I remember liking at the time, at least years ago. Jacob
the liar with Robin Williams, where he was like basically doing good morning Vietnam to Jews and
Auschwitz. And the other one is the day the clown cried, the legendary film with Jerry Lewis, which has
been seen by very, very few people. But that movie was buried essentially. It's one of the most
legendary lost movies of all time. It's supposed to be in horrifically bad taste. And it's unavailable
to find anywhere. It's I've heard of legend legendary, you know, fabled screenings of that film.
Yeah. By like, you know, Harry Sheerer. Right.
It's a guy that always, you know, that apparently has a copy of it. I've never seen it. I would like
to see it. The Lewis. I didn't know about. I didn't know about screenings. I know that they read a
copy of the screenplay at a live thing. And that Jerry Lewis tried to sue and have them not do that.
But hopefully someday we get some weird arrow video release of this thing because I'd love to see it.
Why have we been talking? Oh, because of I'm more a guy. Yeah. Jerry Lewis. There should not be. Yeah.
No, it's gonna say Jerry Lewis is an infamous dick. I respect what he did in comedy and entertainment
greatly. But he's not a not known to be a great guy. That said, I would I kind of get where he's
coming from with the suing. It's like guys tried to do a thing. He didn't work. Yeah.
The fuck alone, please. Like I had it buried for a reason. Like why do I have to keep fighting the same
fight? You know, how much of that piss you off to? You know, you're like a fucking, you know, you're like
a legend. And in the bunch of smarmy brat packers come out like, like, you know, oh, so, so, so, so the
stoner crew with Jason Siegel are going to go read my thing and make fun of it. I built the fucking
road for you. Yeah. He did about 100 movies. He literally came up with the way to act in movies while
directing them. He came up with that system. Yeah. Didn't he create video village? Didn't he
invent that? Yeah. That's basically the same thing. That's what I'm saying. Yeah. So my point is,
is like, I get why he's like, all right, I'm going to sue your little fucking table read. Go fuck
yourselves. Yeah. No, I get it. But if you you can look up some great interviews with Jerry Lewis on
YouTube of people asking him questions that insult him or bother him and him lashing out at people.
I mean, he was a miserable guy. Well, yeah, yeah, not too long ago, but, you know, he, there was
that the one right before he died. He's doing the press kit or press, yeah, or not, no, I'm sorry. He's
in his house and like the today show or something is there. Yes. And he's like, they're taken forever
and like the kid keeps fucking up the lights or whatever. And he's being, he's not like screaming
at anybody, but he's being, he's being a dick. Yeah. And people watch this thing. I remember my friend
being like, boy, what an asshole, huh? And they go, no, this is his 57 ,000th one of these fucking things.
He's 92 years old. They're in his living room. And they can't get their shit together.
I would be a fucking dick too. Like it's like, guys, I hear you. Price shakes. Get it together.
You know, it's, it's just, you know, so I get it. Anyway, anyway, Pat, anyway, I haven't been dating either.
How do you date? Generally, you just ask girls out cold. You don't do any apps, right?
I usually, what I will do is I'll walk up to women in the street with my pants unbuttoned,
unbuttoned, unzipped or just unbuttoned. Unbuttoned with a half unzipped.
And I'll say, okay, I'll open with the line. You got your detective glasses on, sweetie,
because you might spot something that needs some solving. And then I'll,
I'll not look to my crotch. No, I don't know. How do I meet women? I just, I, I guess I've seen you approach
women. You definitely are better at it than I am. I meet women the old fashioned way. I don't do the
apps. I'm staunchly against the apps. I always have been. I meet women in bars, you know, sometimes my own.
Usually, you know, shows, whatever it is, I just, I, you know, we're just randomly that parties,
whatever the hell it is. But I just do it the old school way. I meet people. If we connect and
start talking and they seem like there's a spark there, I will ask them out. And that's kind of
but, you know, also look, I'm very lucky at times to live in New York City. At other times, it's the
worst thing ever. I can't really, you know, tell you, tell you which outweighs which at this point.
It's kind of hard. I've been in New York now long enough that I'm just kind of like, yeah, yeah,
might be time for a change. But, but New York, but this is, but this is your illness, Joe.
Illness is your illness. What are you talking about? You, you, you, you, you, you, you need to change
your, your habitat yearly, yearly, it's when you're given New York since 2019. No, I know, I know,
but you moved a bunch here. Where are you going to, you're going to move to Austin? No, I don't know.
I just said it might be time for a change. Let's talk to me how you feel about LA after you've
been burgled, and you need, your city needs a rat czar. And it's still, it's no judgment. I just
tell you the type of guy who, well, yeah, the type of guy who was always like, I bet if I move, I'll be
happy. And that's not what I'm saying. It doesn't change anything. That's what I'm saying. I'm saying,
I think it might be time for a change. Uh, okay, let's not reduce it to a judgment of my entire
genetic and personal personality. It's not, it's not that joe. Jesus. Yeah. I know. I know.
We always used to tease you out here because you would move and break leases and leave. Well, there
was a reason for, I know, but there was also a reason for that in LA. LA's the worst city on the planet.
And I kept thinking it would get better somehow. Uh, also, after visiting every friend's abode,
including yours, and seeing all of my friends living in better, more lavish environments that I
was, I kept trying to think on my budget, I could better my living situation. And apparently that is
impossible. You're never going to have a lavish living situation of any kind in New York City. The
only people who have that are people with, you know, I would say more than $2 million. The only
way you're going to be able to buy like an apartment where you walk in, you're like, holy shit. This
is incredible. I've gone over to very wealthy people's apartments in New York and they look not that
different than anyone else's apartment because I agree. If you want a top of the line place in New York,
you're talking about a $10 million dollar Taylor Swift, like downtown loft, it's just not possible
there to get ahead. I don't think unless things have changed and I live there. I don't think that.
No, no, it's, it's New York is, as I always say, uh, it starts here. This is the example that the rest
of the country will follow your town or city. It's only a matter of time before the disease reaches you.
Yes, uh, COVID was the perfect example. It started in New York. Everybody condemned New York. Oh,
it's so gross there. You're all on top of each other. That's why you're all sick and that's why the
COVID numbers are spiking. Sure enough, it's spread. And eventually it got to the other side of
the country and it was just things were just as awful over there. That is the metaphor for for anything
in New York. So what's happening here will eventually, uh, poison everywhere else. It's just a matter of
time. Uh, and what's happening here is is landlords are allowed to run absolutely wild. Uh, they are
unregulated completely. Uh, it is a city that is trying to make every fucking dime they can
off of every single citizen and business that is subsist here or they exist here. And it's creating
a dynamic that's making it virtually impossible for the middle class to continue to survive. There's
and it's not sustainable anymore. So you either devise a method in which you can accrue enough money
and means that you can survive or you just say, I've had enough of this. It's too much of a headache
and you move on or worst case scenario you're destroyed. Uh, I'm, I'm feel very lucky to not be in the
worst case scenario position in theory. I could be in the best case position of, of succeeding to a
point of getting to the lavish thing eventually eventually. Um, but I don't know if I feel like it.
And just that, you know, it's just kind of like your spirit of, you know, I keep saying to people,
like, you know, people go, oh, New York's always big tough. You should have been there in the 70s.
I'm a bad. And it's like, yeah, in the 70s, it cost $80 a year to live here. You know, it costs
thousands and thousands and thousands of dollars a month to live here,
nor like, like a normal human being. Um, it's a, it's a first class,
uh, they've created a first, they've created an airport culture here.
You're going to pay for first class if you want to live here. And first class by the way,
when you pay for it is just going to be moderately comfortable. It's not going to be anything special.
So, um, that's why I'm saying, like, I'm just getting to a point where I'm like, I don't know if I
want to just keep spending the money on this and like, it's exhausting. It's fucking exhausting.
And the, the city also is, it's just, it's getting, it's getting dirtier. It's getting grosser. The
infrastructure is getting worse. Our mayor is terrible. I don't even know who the governor is.
You know, uh, it's bad. It's a bad scene. It's about, you get tired too of like, every time I got
to find a new doctor, it's like, Jesus Christ. It's, you know, like, this guy can't see you for two
months. This guy, nobody answers the phone. This place. It's a, it's, it's, it's listed. But you,
but then it's, it's out of business. It's just, it's exhausting, dude. It's exhausting. You get tired
after a while. You know, going to start in three years. I left never. I had never had any desire to
live there again. So, I don't know. What should I do? Well, let's go to the next place and tell
miserable there. You know, as you said, well, I mean, it seems like an untruth. There's not
an untruth to what you're saying. And it wasn't a judgment either. But I mean, I think you, you
have to go to a place where you can get up every night. Correct. Do your stand up.
I care what now Austin, New York, LA, pretty much, right? Uh, yeah. I care a little less about
that than I used to. I'm, I'm moving in a new direction with comedy where, you know, I've really been
props. Yeah. Yeah. More character -driven stuff.
Silently -driven prop comedy. Yeah. Yeah. Um, no, I wanted prop comedy.
So I'm going to do social commentary prop comedy. It's not supposed to be funny. Stop laughing.
Yeah. A prop comic where he's, you know, he's great. Yeah. I'm serious. Yeah. Yeah.
No, that's a really funny concept because there's the comic that gets on stage in bombs. And he's like,
he's like, oh, it's supposed to be funny. It was about a point. I'm like, trying to say something
up there. It's funny to do that as a prop comic. I'm sure that's happened. Yeah. Bombing. Anyway,
uh, my point is I did see Carrotop once at the Rio. I left before the end of the show, but, um,
they were giving away free tickets and he came out with this little chest, but he's in an angry place
too. Like, he blows up at the audio. He's not at Gallagher's level, but he's very angry.
Um, I would imagine you become the butt of the, the cosmic, you know, or absolute comedic joke
for this many years and devote yourself to getting buff. And everybody just makes fun of you more.
You, you, you get your body like perfect. And then everybody goes, now we, this looks even worse,
we hate you like this. He's had a lot of facelifts. He looks just crazy. He's been a joke for 30 years.
Yeah. I feel bad for him. Oh, yeah. The facelifts with the clown air is not a good look.
And also too, like your, your life is in Vegas. It's like you're, you're like, that's,
that can't be Jesus Christ. That's like living at the Galleria.
Like in those apartments about the stores. I have said, I've said to so many cab drivers,
you mean the grove. I've said to so many cab drivers, that's like, what's the, what's the,
outdoor thing? Isn't that the Galleria? That's the Americana or the Americana and the grove.
I've been in so many cabs in Vegas where I've been like, I don't know how anybody could
fucking live here. And then as I get out of the cab, I realize in my drunk state that the driver
obviously must live in Las Vegas. But I couldn't because I'd be broke very quickly. But it's also like,
after four days in Las Vegas, you want to die. I mean, three should be anybody's limit.
And living there, especially somebody who likes to gamble who lives in Vegas. I mean,
you might as well just plan your death. I guess that's what leaving Las Vegas is about,
you know, except that guy didn't really gamble much. I was lucky enough to get to have a,
have lunch with the amazing Jonathan before he died. And he told me about when he was at his peak
and he was doing the Vegas residency. I forget what casino he was at. But he was like, so they gave
me the penthouse suite. And he was like, just driving the suite to me. It sounded fucking insane.
Multi floor suite with a goal. You know, all glass floor to ceiling windows looking over the whole.
It was like the Elvis. It was the Elvis suite or whatever. That's what Ron White had when I'm out with
him in Vegas. Yeah. Yeah. And he was like, I didn't drink, but they gave me a stipend every day
that I had to spend before midnight. And he goes, I had the greatest bar of all time because I could
spend the stipend anywhere. And he goes, so I would just spend it at the liquor store in the casino
every day before midnight happened. And he was like, it was absolute. Like, you know, it was, what's that
term? Uh, uh, not eating. Uh, he, uh, Sanadu, not heen it is. I'm not paradise. God, damn it.
I swear to God anymore. I thought I was getting sharper with these vitamins, but I'm, I still feel just
as dumb, whatever the stone shoubles. Whatever that term for the place to Barney's every day and nothing.
Um, a place where he, I mean, he didn't, there's a miss the name. That's a, that's a resort where
you have like sex and alcohol and, or maybe that's what it works. Maybe that's what he said. I don't
fucking know. Anyway, he, he said it was why. So he was buying, he would buy alcohol on the liquor store.
He said he would just buy a bottle and take it upstairs. No, no, he said he would call down.
And he said he got like a, I think he said it was $500 a day or something like where he could
just spend it every wanted in the casino. Just on top of his, it was just like a per diem every day
that he got as a part of his signing deal. Right. And he said, um, he said, you know, he's like,
I never used it because I didn't really eat in the casino restaurants enough because you got tired
of it. And he goes, and I also didn't drink. So I never spent it at the bars here. So every day,
I would just call down and tell them that I would spend it all on liquor so I could have this massive bar
so I could have these like raging parties like. And he was like, my bar was insane that I had
like the supply of booze I had. And he was like, and the irony was I didn't drink, but that was like
the most sound thing to spend the money on every day. So I didn't lose it. So, right, but just sounded
awesome. But even that, I was like, Jesus Christ should become like the, remember in the
right night remake when the, you know, the magician is living up in that, the guy that played
doctor who was living up in that fucking suite and he keeps drinking that. What's that green
shit, that green liquor that tastes like, uh, apple, not absence. No, the, the, the stuff that
takes, no, no, no, apple, pucker. Oh, yeah. Pat, what do you want me to make? Green stuff that tastes like
apple, uh, is apple pucker. It's a sweet green. Here it is. Uh, uh,
Oh, for God's sakes. Madori. Fuck. Madori sour. Okay. Yeah. Son of a bitch.
Anyway. Yeah. So anyway, that was it. That was the thought. It just sounded like that.
Like, remember that guy's like living up there and he's like miserable. Jonathan didn't say he was
miserable. It just what he was describing to me sounded like eventually you would be like, I'm
going fucking crazy right now. Like I'm, I, I, I, I, I pace around here, looking over the city,
like some kind of fucking super villain, you know. Yeah. Um, I spent a week in Vegas.
Luckily, I had no money at the time. But I was the judge of the, one of the judges of the
Las Vegas film festival back when I was a movie critic. I think you're going to say, and a weedy,
bitty, titty committee. What's that? Like that shirt that the, like guys used to wear it,
where it'd be like, it'd be like, I'm a, or girls would wear it. I'm a meeting inspector.
I'm the, yeah, bikini inspector or I'm a member of the itty, titty committee official boob inspector.
They all kind of went together. Also with the rubber balls and liquor shirt, so the big dog shirts,
where it's like, fucker in the back. Like sometimes they wouldn't even be a joke or a pawn. It would
just be like, fuck her in the ass. You're like, what, what's the joke here? Yeah, liquor in the front
more crazy back. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Liquor in the front poker in the back is could be the greatest
playing on words ever. It's not. It's not. It's very good. It's very, very good.
I was, I was judging the short film competition and they sent me a DVD with all the shorts and I
watched it at home. And I got there and I was like, so what do I do here all week? When do I go to
the screenings or whatever? And they gave me this list of all these shorts I had to go see. And I
said, I've already watched them. And they're like, oh, well, then just enjoy Las Vegas. We'll see
dinner every night in a casino restaurant after party at a casino club and then after after party
at a Vegas strip club. So it should have just been non -stop fun, but with no money. Man,
it was just depressing as hell. Everyone in Vegas seems like they're just at the end of their
rope. And I still love to go. I can't get enough. I don't know what it is. I enjoy, yeah, I enjoy
two nights in Vegas. Yeah. That's it. Two nights. A third is always like, I'm like,
what am I going to miss if I leave? And then that fourth morning, you're like, God damn it.
Yeah. Should have left. Agua Caliente, which is a casino near Palm Springs about halfway to Vegas.
So I've gone there a couple of times and they hit me up now to try to get me to come out. And they
I laugh every time they try to entice me with some of the worst musical and comedic acts in the
history of time. I mean, it's look up Agua Caliente coming attractions. I mean, it's always hilarious,
but they're like, yeah, we'd love to get you to come out to see, you know,
Los Lonely Boys or whatever is, you know, it's just wild. And they have really bad comedy. And I
won't name names because I'm sure Joe knows them, but they, they go ahead. Please, you went out.
My, my buddies and I saw Kevin James and Dennis Regan opened up for him. And it was just too rough.
Sets a comedy. I got to tell you rough. Um, Regan, I've never, I've never met Dennis Regan.
Yeah. He seemed, I don't know his comedy. James in later years has become a little too like
I don't know like where the hell of all the real men gone. Like that kind of stuff, but like
and then yeah, you know, like stuff like that, but his, his older standup is very funny.
When he was joking about his weight, he was hilarious. Talking about like, you know, you know,
when your belly is shaking, when you brush your teeth, it's time to start working out. It had a great
set about being a fat guy. And I heard at some point on King of Queens, he was like, no more fat jokes.
And like that's still what he does. He like doesn't, he doesn't know what makes him funny anymore or
something. It's, it's odd. But yeah, it felt conservative and gross. And I did not enjoy it.
Um, it felt gross. It was that conservative.
Just, you know, that vibe where it's like, um, you know, well, my, my pronouns are fucking you,
honey. Like, you know, I don't know what I'm saying. He said that exactly. But just where you're like,
come on, man, like just hacky. Yeah. Close minded shit that you've heard a million times.
And blah, blah, blah. I, uh, how do you get almond milk out? How do you get milk out of a nut?
You know, it's like, there's, uh, the avocado toast, you know, there's a few hack things that
those right -wing comedians go for where you're just like, all right, dude, like, give me a fucking break.
Yeah, I live in the most liberal city in America. I've never gone out to eat with anyone,
where anyone ordered a piece of avocado toast, but they're really zeroed in on it.
Patently untrue. You 100 % have. No, no, I absolutely have. I've seen people order it repeatedly.
I just don't think it's the fact that they still talk about it as like, this is like a,
a, a main characteristic of the liberal left -minded person is that we all love avocado toast is,
to me, one of the craziest things I've ever heard. I, I never quite understood it because I'm like,
I just thought it was a dish that people liked. Uh, yeah, you know, I never, like,
is the criticism that it's expensive? I don't know. I mean, I, I, I was thinking even if I
were a right -winger, I would still enjoy avocado on a nice piece of toast bread.
I never quite understood the anger of a almond milk either. I'm somebody that enjoys a non -dairy milk
because I can't drink milk, but um, the, the opening line of the ranch, which was, I only watched the
first five minutes of the ranch because we were looking to try a higher director or something, but
it's Sam Elliott, our boy, he walks out, he opens the refrigerator and he goes, almond milk,
how the fuck do you get milk out of an almond? It's the first line of the multi -cam sitcom,
The Ranch on Netflix. Right. Like guys, guys, how many times we're gonna do this joke?
I'd like to point out too. We're like in LA, huge laugh. I've seen the clip. It destroys.
Yeah. Which is so interesting going. It's so interesting because I'll watch like some of the,
I'm a big married with children fan, but I realize that there are times where it gets very
base and you're like, all right, guys, for the love of God. Yeah, but you got to remind yourself,
this is shot in front of an a Los Angeles audience and they are eating it up. You're like,
who are those people in LA? It's strange. The right -wing people in my family are always like that too.
Like, well, when are they just gonna dump LA into the ocean? Like, fuck you guys, but my uncle has
actually said that to me. The truth is there are just as many right -wingers here as pretty much
anywhere else, maybe not in Beverly Hills. Actually, definitely in Beverly Hills where they have all
the money, but the areas surrounding LA, like maybe not Silver Lake where I'm at, maybe not Los
Filos. That's probably 80 % liberal at least. Where they also have all of the money, yet they try to
pretend like they don't. Yeah, exactly. They dress like they don't, but you know, the valley and
all surrounding parts of Los Angeles and certainly Sacramento and San Diego and stuff. I mean,
there are tons of conservative people, like Manhattan Beach, Orange County, and I think the people
that are going to a multi -cam taping are generally from the valley and they probably love hearing
LA get shot on some. Okay, that's interesting. I remember Harlan Ellison saying that all of the
Republicans lived in the valley. Yeah, but his take on his take on LA also confused me because you
be like, this town's got all the smoke and vigor that New York used to have. It's like Harlan on
its best day. And I don't mean to shit on where you live, Pat, but on its best day, the energy ain't
touch in New York. Stop it, Harlan. Stop it. You write some good stories. Stop it. No, it's true.
I mean, I will say the energy of New York in 030405 when I live there as opposed to now is night and
day, but it's still New York. This whole like the city that never sleeps aspect of New York is real.
New York and then especially Vegas, those truly are cities that never sleep on a weekend in particular.
But LA shuts and I'm in, I'm in silver like you could not find like the the Hipper quote part of LA.
Everything shuts down at 910. You know, you got the drawing room and a couple bars that hang
until two, but it's not much. LA's a great place. I will say this and this is one thing that I do
miss about it. I know I make fun of LA a lot, but there are things I miss. I do miss the driving
aspect of it. I really do. I always like to being able to drive to a place and do what I need to do.
I got tired of the suniness every day, but you know, you haven't have rainy days in New York. You will miss
some consistent sun. But and I miss obviously most of all the people that I was close with there.
And believe it or not, Pat, you're one of them. Yes, but but one thing. No, it was great. I got no
drinking buddies here. I got I got not a one, which is good for my health. But you know, I don't
really have guys that go out and drink with. I could I could hook you up with a few guys. I still got
my guys I tap when I get out there. You know, I can meet somebody for a drink. There's just few people
that got that dynamic we have where it's hey, when you want to go grab eight up at the the
roots tonight. And I can reliably guess that you will agree and go with me. I don't have those
people. I will say the one thing I primarily did appreciate about LA that I do miss is it is a good
place to focus on work. Yeah, it's a good place to kind of put the blinders on and go, okay, look,
if I'm going to go to the first standup, if I'm going to go to the club tonight, I'm going to go
in. I'm going to do my set. I'm going to leave. I was just talking to Tim Dylan about this. It's a good
place where it's like, you're not going down to the store to just aimlessly kind of hang out and
see what's going on. You're going down to do a set. And if hanging out is happening, that's a great
bonus. But New York is different. New York. Well, New York is less like this now, which is a good
thing. And it might lead to me doing a little more standup to answer your question from earlier
about needing to go up all the time. I just, I've been approached ever since I started working on
this new hour and the new hour became a one man show and really focusing on what that was and what
it meant to work on something like that versus standup. I mean, I haven't really done sets in
New York since New years. And that's not exaggerating because I haven't been working in that way. And
when I do start to work in that way again, it'll be great to have the resource to be able to go up
all the time. And I actually am glad now that it's a little less of a hang because it was it was a hard
thing to just dip in and out of because, you know, you go to a club do a set and five of the funniest
people you've ever met in your life that your friends with are hanging out there. It's like, what are
you going to do? You're going to go home. Right. It's real hard at that point to be like, I got to go
keep working. You know, you want to hang out now. And then God forbid they're drinking.
Yeah. And they probably are. Let's be real.
Anyway, that's a little life of sad misery. I got a quick scary stuff. I just started slowly
replenishing my Nintendo switch collection since the initial one was stolen from me.
And one of the first games I bought was Zelda tears of the kingdom, the new legend of Zelda,
a direct sequel to Breath of the Wild. I was very on the fence about this game when I started.
There were aspects and elements of the first of tears of the kingdom. I didn't really like that
were new to Zelda. I didn't like that the weapons broke. I didn't like that alchemy was such a big
part of the gameplay. It was too much of a hard turn left for me with Zelda. And I didn't,
I appreciated Breath of the Wild, but I didn't enjoy it because it wasn't my style of game.
I decided to give it another shot with the new game knowing that it was elements would exist before
I got into it. So number one, I was prepared for them. I started playing the game. I liked it.
I was on the fence though because I was like, I don't know, these things just might be a deal break.
Why is everything so challenging all the time? And then literally last night as I was playing,
it clicked. And I was like, I was trying to get to this village to do something. And it was so
arduous to get there. And I just realized I feel like I've gone literally on the journey that the
video game person just went on. And I was like, there's the reward. This is why this game is awesome.
It's a really excellent game. It's a little more streamlined than Breath of the Wild,
which I appreciate. It feels a little more like a traditional Zelda game, which I appreciate.
But it's still the same style. The storyline is awesome. The gameplay is great. It's pretty much
a flawless piece of work. And it also has some really, really cool, creepy elements in it.
There's this stuff that has come up through the cracks. The palace of Hyrule,
where Prince of Zelda lives or whatever, something happens at the beginning of the game where that
gets sucked up basically into the sky. And this happening causes all these fissures and cracks or whatever
around Hyrule. And out of the depths of Hyrule has come this, I forget what it's called, but it's like
demonically possessed. And if it touches you, it's deadly and all this stuff. And that new element
of the game has added all some really cool horror elements to it. It's a cool game. It's a really,
really cool game. I look forward to being lost in it for a very long time. So check her out,
the legend of Zelda tears of the kingdom. That looks some real nerd shit to me.
Yeah. Do they do Zelda ocarina of time? Is that something?
Why does that keep popping into my head? Is it a game? My favorite Zelda game ever.
What's an ocarina? Is it like the macarena? No, it's a little like flute thing.
Oh, okay. And you get it in that game. And when you play certain melodies on it, you travel back and
forth between time periods. Oh, okay. I take back what I said about it, seeming nerdy.
That seems really cool, actually. He says this to me as he's got 8 ,000 criterion blue rays behind.
That's right. That's right. And he sells the old Panidropper collection.
Let's get to that movie corn. Let me just play a few notes on my flute and take the movie corn.
Well, you want to talk nerdy at video game collections. I've seen people that have created
with 3D printers, the ocarina. Flutes that existed Zelda. And then they'll be in the garb,
dressed as characters playing them. And that's the sales pitch. And if that's not odd enough,
oh, there's a line to buy these things. Yeah. Have you ever gone to a renaissance fair?
I'm thinking about going on a wall. It's here in LA. It's one of the, no, it's horrible.
No, it's horrible. I went with like my eighth grade class or something. But I see a lot of pictures
of friends. And I'm like, maybe that's what I need to start being happy is to go to renaissance fairs.
It's fun to get the giant turkey leg that you can also get a Disneyland ride it is.
Yeah, that's it. No. And then that thing halfway through it, you feel sick.
No, it's horrible, dude. And people like, people in that and makes you sick.
When you watch the people staying in that character, it's like that episode of a curb
where he goes to Tony and Tina's wedding and he's like, all right, Charlie, we can drop the
enough. It's just me in the bathroom. It's like that. It's except a much more sickening display
of acting. And this is funny. You bring this up. As I was rewatching Dragon Slayer last night,
I was watching the scene of like the ceremony feast they have before they're going to go like face
the dragon the first time. And they're all dancing to that like loot music with ribbons in their hair.
And they're all wearing like the garlands and things. And I was like, yeah, some there are
people out there that are such fucking dorks. They watched this scene I'm watching right now and said,
let's make our wedding like that. And they did it. Oh, yeah. Yeah. And that's what renaissance fair
is. You know, do you want to watch a fake joust? Who the hell wants to watch this?
At least at any of the times. Yeah, you're like, we'll go get shit -faced at medieval times.
It'll be, you know, and middle evil times is like trashy. It's, you know, it's like, that's fun.
Like going to a renaissance fair, you're expected to act appropriately. What are we doing here?
I would be, I would be a jester. I would just keep approaching groups and doing jokes and juggling
and stuff like that. Where are one of those hats with the four, like octopus legs that come off with
the bells do jingle. Yeah. That's how I would go. The jester. Wait, you would dress up and go to
this thing? I think you have to. No, you know, I didn't. Everybody I see online is dressed up. No,
you can just go normal. You're allowed. Oh, okay. It's like going to, you know, will you? But then you're
going to, but then you're going to have people come up to you and be like, excuse me? What are you from
the future? Pat. What I said stands the whole experience makes me sick. I hate it. What are you,
some sort of sorcerer? Is this denim material around your legs? You call them chains, do you?
God, in the new Star Wars video game, which I won't review because I went on a tie -rate on Twitter
about it. You go to a planet called Cabo. And Cabo is a frontier, frontier planet. And the aliens
in this fucking video game have Southern acts like Midwestern and Southern accents, which made me
furious. And at one point I'm talking, I'm talking to a alien on Cabo in the Star Wars universe
who is wearing, I am not kidding, denim overalls. I almost threw my fucking PlayStation across the
room. It made me so mad. Yeah, yeah, that never makes me mad. That's a youth thing. But I get that,
I get it. I understand. It just doesn't bother me. Anyway, I watched a brand new movie. It was just
in theaters and they just brought it out on Amazon to rent for six bucks. It's called Sick of Myself.
Sick of Myself also a great Matthew sweet song. I urge you to check out. I know Matthew sweet
is not great anymore, but he had a good run. Sick of Myself is a movie about a woman
who is dating a man who starts to get some fame in the art world. And this woman is a narcissist
and she becomes very jealous of her boyfriend and wants the attention that he is getting.
And so she starts doing really crazy things to try to even the playing field and be as popular and
in discussion as her boyfriend was. This movie is, geez, I want to say dutch.
Let me see it. Sorry, I want to tell you what country it's from at least first, but this was a dark
fucking comedy. All right, help me out. Like Christopher Borglie. What what what country is that, Joe?
All right, I don't know. Oslo is Sweden. It's a Swedish movie. Okay, okay. Oslo pictures. My
guess is it's Sweden. I should know more about this stuff, but sorry, I don't scan the Navy in Norway.
All right, good. Anyway, this is a super, super dark satirical movie. I did not know where it was
going at first, but this woman sees that a one other woman gets attacked by a dog and everybody's
like all of like, oh my God, are you okay? And like giving her a lot of attention. So she starts
slapping a dog in the face, trying to get it to attack her. Like this woman is ill mentally ill.
And she's just trying to have people notice her in the way they're noticing her boyfriend.
When the dog thing doesn't work, the dog's owner comes up and is like, you're slapping my dog?
Like, what the fuck is the matter with you? It calls her a cunt. Then she really starts to double down
and starts taking these drugs that she reads online cause you to have horrific facial
disfigurement. And she starts popping them like smarties. And the entire plot of this film is basically
this woman like sweeping the art world and becoming more popular than her boyfriend,
because her face looks absolutely disgusting and is like melting and pussing and
pushjilling and falling apart. So you've got this woman who's like the toast of the art scene. She's
always smoking and like being like miss cool, but her face looks more and more hideous with each
passing scene. She goes to do like photo shoots and we'll just puke all over the floor.
Over and over throughout the photo shoots because she's deathly ill and she's doing it to herself
just to be as popular as her boyfriend. So it's a satire. The woman said that she had this idea for
the movie and was having a little trouble making it until she came out to LA. And then she saw
like the influencers and the narcissism and the people doing their online TikToks and everything.
And then she was like, I need to take down this society. So it's a Scandinavian take down of LA
culture. It will not be for everybody because some of the makeup they do with this face is absolutely
disgusting. There is a lot of vomiting in the movie. A lot of like blood flowing out of noses and
ears and stuff. But to me, that stuff was hilarious that she's willing to do all this to herself
to be in the cultural conversation. It's a good satirical comedy. Check it out if you like
that sort of thing. All right. Netflix apparently has a movie called Blood and Gold that boasts
to be a wild good time of crazy Nazi killing. What a coincidence Netflix that that comes out
right as they would see so. Yeah. That's what a what a weird coincidence. Anyway. Yeah.
Well, and maybe the other way around maybe Netflix had the idea first. I don't know.
I don't know anymore. I don't trust anybody anymore. I don't have the idea first. He was the first to
kill Nazis. It's not true. I guess the mode. Well, he was the first. I feel like where it was like
it's going to be like a Nazi kill and shindig, you know. Yeah. No, I mean, yeah, I'll see see soon.
I hear see sews good. I'm excited about. Well, they're saying this Blood and Gold is also very good
on Netflix. All right. I got two family comedies. I watched The Family Stone, which was excellent.
Loved it. What an ensemble cast. Diane Kate and Craig T Nelson right off the bat. Anybody
you'd rather have be your parents if it wasn't your parents. Would you be mad if your mom and dad were
Craig T Nelson and Diane Kate and I'd be fucking thrilled. I've been watching parenthood for the first
time that the NBC show and Craig T is the perfect dad and that he's a fuck up, but he's you still
wanted to be your dad just like in Pulitzer, guys. Then you got the kids Rachel McAdams. She's amazing
in this even playing a wholly unlikeable person. She's amazing and you lover awful in it.
I love her. Yes. Durant more Rooney. Charming is all hell. Bit of a prick, but great.
Luke Wilson stealing the show as like the podhead artsy son. He's so funny on this man. He's so
funny in it. And then the kid, the actor, I put the plays the deaf son. I don't remember his name.
I don't I wasn't familiar with him to be honest with you. No, he's also wonderful. Then you have
the people playing their interests led by Sarah Jessica Parker who plays extremely conservative,
tightly wound woman. Again, a sort of unlikeable character, but she's really great in this.
Claire Danes coming in like a ray of light. And then the actor that plays the deaf son's boyfriend
who was also great. It's just a wonderful film. Christmas movie. A sort of dysfunctional but highly
loving family with their eldest son bringing home and a very liberal family with their eldest son
bringing home a conservative woman for the first time or his girlfriend for the first time she turns
out to be conservative. The clashing of everything starts. It's very funny. It's very heartfelt. You
this is going to be her last Christmas. It's very emotional. I wept many times throughout the movie.
You see how a dysfunctional family truly operates. You see how a dysfunctional family can also very
much love one another. And you see a very fair and balanced depiction of conservative and liberal
viewpoints. No despite the fact that at times they hate one another and they hate with the other person
is saying or don't understand with the other person is saying they get past it as human beings
and accept one another that they're from different walks of life. You know the way a society is
supposed to work. I don't know if anybody remembers when society existed but there was a time. Anyway
yeah we got we got I talked about this when I recommended the movie to you with that dinner table
scene which is kind of the centerpiece of the movie where Sarah Jessica Parker is saying you'd never
want your son to be gay. Would you? And her point is your son will have a much harder life as a
gay man. And you get that. I got it when I saw it then I got it when I saw it now but she says it
wrong. They all get very upset and angry at her. The thing is it works itself out but that's seen
in a movie today. Sarah Jessica Parker would have to be painted as the ultimate villain or nobody
understands her point of view. And also they would never make her a part of the happy ending of the
movie. They would she would have to be a villain. Just simply saying don't you think your son growing
up gay he's going to have a harder life. I don't know how you don't how you don't get that but
she was trying to be understanding and connect with them and it blows up and that scene is perfect I
think. But we've lost that and that that that's type of scene is what we need now more than ever
where you just see examples of people interacting about touchy issues and understanding each other.
Maybe it blows up but they reach a place of understanding. We don't even see that represented
in the arts anymore. If you say something that a liberal person would not agree with you have to be
portrayed as the villain unless you're doing like a Larry the cable guy movie or something. And you feel
bad for the son when she's saying it because she's saying it in a bit in an awful way. Of course.
Of course. Understand why Craig T Nelson explodes for her to stop talking. You also then understand
why Dermott Rooney doesn't back her but also doesn't condemn her because he's in a weird position.
Right. And then there's that beautiful. Yeah you get why Diane Keaton is so mad and Diane Keaton like
slams her hand down the table and she's like that's enough. Like start yelling at Sarah just
Parker. And when I watched it this Christmas I was like. Diane Keaton is being way too hard on her
here but then when Craig T Nelson explodes and he's like hey he's right it's like okay Diane Keaton
you're coming at this with a little too much anger but then when she doubles and triples and quadruples
down and Craig T explodes he's right in that moment. It's like no I was trying to side with you and be
sympathetic but you won't shut the fuck up and this is my family's Christmas. You it's a very
important. I just I really love how it's written in that exactly like you're saying Joe you understand
where everyone is coming from even if it's not exactly how you might react all the characters are
acting in believable understandable ways at all times. And that's what makes the movie work.
The beautiful scene of Craig T going back and saying I came to apologize you're like oh that's
surprising and then her given the picture at the end Sarah Jessica being the one it's fucking
just it's heartbreaking. I have friends like that. I have friends in my life that are that are
extremely good at business and not great at showing emotion and not great at cutting loose and yet
that's the exact kind of gift they would give because they're perceptive and that and they shock
you in ways like that. It's just such a beautiful moment. The what's it going to say? The um
and then we'll again Luke Wilson just being he's just awesome. He's the one that's just like no
matter what no matter who does what he's the only person that never gets angry and like there's
that awesome scene you know why probably because he's high all the time. There's a lesson to be
learned there and he takes her to the uh dive bar and uh yeah you know when he when he when he sits back
he's gonna freak fly flag you just don't let it fly you know like it's yeah I got damn it I love
Luke Wilson. Why is Luke Wilson not starring and worth why wasn't Luke Wilson and Stan and Ollie?
I love that scene. I love when him and Craig T go sit on the bleachers and share a
going out in the snow whatever there's just it's just great scene after great scene after great
scene. I think it's one of the more underrated movies uh of my lifetime in terms of like Christmas
comedy. It's like it's it's great. It's it's awesome. It's going into the rotation. I will probably buy it
uh it to own it because like when Harry met Sally and like love actually and like
um Hannah and her sisters I think it will join my uh it'll it'll enter my repertoire now of
of holiday or seasonal movies that I not only enjoy not only find very funny not only I find very
relatable and real plane strains is another one but that will also make me weep and remember when
life and society was better. There you go uh to give you an example of how underrated the
family stone is if you are going to buy it you will be buying it on DVD because it was never made
available on Blu -ray. Yeah all right. Strange um I watched you know and look there's not a lot of
competition but uh probably my favorite movie of the year so far which is surprise the hell out of
me Blackberry. Oh I want to see this. Yeah after shooting on air for being a movie about a brand
you know I was in no real hurry to see Blackberry until I realized that this movie is
it's being marketed as a comedy but it really is a character study about two men very very very
different and it features two amazing performances from actors that I love and kind of know but just
and even though I knew they were great I just did not really I didn't know that they had this kind of
shit in them uh and that is Mr. Glenn Howardton who I love and have known for many many years
he needs to get nominated for this movie he's absolutely incredible and the he's incredible
and the other surprise is Mr. J. bearishel who's an actor I always enjoy but um I love the bear
bearishel is playing and it's not it's not Apple it's not like Steve Jobs and where you know all
these people's names but Blackberry even though I never owned one was you know it was everything until
the iPhone came along and then it looked like shit so the story here and the movie by the way the
third lead in the movie is Matt Johnson who also wrote and directed and I didn't know who this guy
was but he directed this movie called the Dirties that he also starred in which I've never seen
and I think Kevin Smith produced you ever see the Dirties Joe it's like a found footage horror
sounds like getting revenge on bullies your uncle asks you if you want to do on your bachelor party
when you go down and watch the Dirties you should go see the Dirties yeah um anyway that went
right into my watch list I'm gonna watch that next I'm excited to see it because this movie's great
I just fucking loved it and and it's laugh out loud funny I think marketing as a comedy is wrong
it's basically the social network it's it's a slightly funnier version but um what it is is
J. bearishel and Matt Johnson play two nerds Matt Johnson is the goofy um hey let's all watch uh
Star Wars kind of classic nerd and bearishel is more the genius type of nerd and they come up with
this idea for a blackberry but it's not perfect and they're not business men
Howard's in plays a monster of a businessman who only operates and understands in the world of
business he has no human emotions um drives to work listening to joy division with a frown on his
face every day uh the only pleasure he seems to have in life is watching hockey but they give him so
many little great character details like he goes to a diner to have breakfast with these guys nothing
for me thanks like there's so many moments where he just gets like no enjoyment out of life he's all
business and he meets these guys and says look if you guys pair with me I'll take you to the top
and he does but you know in that moment that a guy who's this driven and business oriented is
going to fuck over these two nice guys what you're not expecting is that bearishel eventually starts
changing into Howardton he starts becoming more monstrous don't ruin that Johnson because I want
to see it no yeah okay well it's a true story I mean it's a good character study but I'm not
spoiling shit okay okay um it's it's your in essence it's your standard biopic type of story it's
the story of two young guys who have a big idea which takes over the world and then as we all know the
blackberry does not stand the test of time but um we're we're talking about two a performances here and
really just to Joe's point about actors not getting the the chance they deserve the part that
Howardton plays I I would have to imagine that he was the first to get offered it because he's just
perfect in it but it's such a scenery chewing screaming juicy part that it really could have gone to
some of the biggest actors out there and I think this is a great example of what Joe's been talking
about which is giving Howardton that chance to really shine and are you know he obviously plays a great
douche on always sunny he's great but just toning it back a little bit and making it a real person as
he does in this I think he's got a big future in terms of character parts and bearishel has never
been anywhere near this good all bearishel does even though I like it is him going like I don't know
you know that whole thing this is a real person and a character he's playing and he's more
than up to the challenge blackberry check it out right moving I only have one more to another family
comedy sorry I'm sorry Joe one last thing I want to mention because we talked about him on this show before
Howardton brings in this 300 pound monster to start watching over the company and like
threatening people and being an asshole uh that is another amazing part played by Michael Ironside
remember Ironside yeah I would I would have assumed long since dead Michael Ironside from like
standards he's 75 he looks like he ate the old Mike Ironside he's 300 pounds at least and he
destroys in this movie so I don't know if this is it was low budget and this is the actors they could
get my guess is this movie was cast very very carefully with like actors that this guy really really
loved and knew would excel and man they do it's just people who never get these type of parts
killing it across the board nobody plays evil like Ironside I mean it's he's so good in this yeah he's
he's great yeah all right I only have one more uh it's the the opposite of the family stone yet
similar in so many ways the big wedding which joins the ranks of worst named movies of all time
as you all know my number one will always be hotel for dogs this one ain't too far off the big
wedding what a terrible title for a movie the wedding is the show told me the the a list cast of this
movie and I have never heard of the film never heard of it this is a movie that stars Robert De Niro
Diane Katen again yeah Susan Sarandon so Kathleen from knocked up I always want to say Kathleen Hanna
and it's it's not her hogel hi Kathleen Hanna Kathleen Hanna is the keeny kill that's
Catherine Han is Wanda vision Catherine Higel is in this uh I mean I almost said Hayden Christians
and Tofer Grace yeah um oh and and uh Mama Mia um Merle Street no Amanda Seafry Amanda Seafry
here's how have a cast yeah uh it's a movie about there and then there's a key player in this it's
he's played by an actor I don't I'm not aware of or familiar with this starts out with
De Niro doing a monologue oh no a voiceover about marriage and what marriage means and and you know
after 10 years or so you wake up and you realize you're not married to the right person
and hopefully you can both understand that and and even though you're parting
realize you've created something together which is beautiful children and he's talking about
the children and his ex -wife played by Diane Keaton and and they have two kids and then an adopted
son from Mexico so you're watching and and you learn that the adopted son is about to get married
and this is the big wedding that's happening and you're scratching your head going why the fuck
is there an adopted son from Mexico just so I'm thinking this is a ploy for diversity in the movie
and I'm going just make it a Mexican family like just make the family Hispanic I don't understand
why you're going so far around the bend do you need white people in this this badly that you've written in
this absurd adopted thing for no good reason and then I realize no I'm completely wrong this is the
plot of the movie because the kid's biological mother who the family has kept in touch with long
distance for all these years because you know how that happens right with every adoption
as an adopted kid I'm very familiar with that yeah it's coming to the wedding thanks that she's
extremely religious thinks that divorce is the ultimate sin and because of that the son that
deniro and and Keaton adopted has been lying to her saying that his adoptive parents never got divorced
and now here she comes they have to pretend to be married for a full weekend I mean Jesus Christ with
this plot I mean this is like they just redid this with this fucking George Clooney whatever thing
what Julie Roberts thing yeah and Susan Sarandon is the step when do when do balky and cousin Larry
enter this insane balky and cousin Larry you're being generous this is that this is at an
habit of Castello fucking level in my opinion yeah yeah yeah yeah uh Susan Sarandon as the stepmom
feels dejected but says to her stepson I love you very much my gift to you is I'm going to
disappear for the weekend and not complicate this and then she starts showing up in random places like
they go out for the pre you know the wedding the the rehearsal dinner and she suddenly is the waitress
because she's trying to like work her way into things and spot this movie is so fucking bad shit
I don't know if there's one laugh in it and then to further complicate things you find out
Diane Keaton once fucked the husband of the father the father of Amanda C. Freed's character
she once had an affair with him she fucks Danero on this thing while Sarandon's away then you find out
her and Sarandon her best friend then they forgive each other then Danero proposes to Sarandon
because they're not married yet this it's it's a mess it's a mess about Robin Williams is in this
oh yeah that's right I forgot Robin Williams is in it too he plays the priest Robin Williams plays
the priest it's insane I think of this cast and by the way they do like that sitcom joke with Robin
Williams we're like you're like guys this is a much more grounded film than this than this joke
but Robin Williams does the joke to them of like oh divorce okay so you're both fine with
burning in hell then and you're like a priest would never say that ever yeah ever and and it's fine
it works on a sign felt episode it doesn't work on this this is supposed to be like a grounded
thing about him like Catherine Haigel's plot line is she's trying to get pregnant and she can't
like yeah that's another whole other fucking loaded thing
and everything of course comes together and works out for every single person
and every storyline gets resolved where at the big wedding Pat you want to hear another storyline
of this Toe for Grace is a 30 -year -old virgin who's also a successful doctor who loses her
on his virginity where he looks like Toe for Grace so how do they explain him making it to 30 without
having sex he's just a virgin uh and he loses his virginity where Pat at the big wedding
wedding yeah and when he loses virginity too his brother is adopted brothers biological sister
okay this thing is insane it's insane it sounds like one of the worst movies has ever made it has
there's no reason given for Toe for Grace being a 30 -year -old virgin dude the thinnest version
possible it's like you know you know i'm waiting to fall in love what can i say it's like one of those
things you know okay it would have been great it would have been great now what they would have done
in the family stone type of movie this has a i'm trying to look on rotten tomatoes this is a 7 % on rotten
tomatoes okay uh what they would have done in a movie like the family stone with the virgin is they
would have been like he was very sick his whole life and he's finally better and he's getting to be a
young man for the first time and he's embarrassed like he's never at sex and he's embarrassed and it's
like a it's a hard thing for him to get into because because he he battled leukemia into his into his
teenage years or whatever it's there's a million really interesting ways that that could be written
and no it's just in there as a dumb fucking gag so when he meets his brother's sister who's the
smoking hot Hispanic woman uh -huh and she's like this sex bomb he you know there's like a scene where
she's like giving him a hand job under the dinner table at the rehearsal dinner and then Diane
Keaton's catchers catches that happening and then of course there is but like again like that's
like an anchor man type of joke you know i mean yeah or like a 40 year old virgin type joke this isn't
that kind of movie this does try to be like a grounded movie about a family that's a little different
than your family but still a family it sucks it sucks i turned it on because i wanted to watch more
Diane Keaton and then well she makes four movies a year now too and their my mom just saw a book club
too for my mom to say a movie sucks and she boy she had some things to say about book club too
you mean the second chapter excuse me book club the next chapter yeah sorry which uh
let me hand it to her we get to our film that's a great that's a great title if you're gonna make
it sequel to book club that's a great title yeah you should call it the next chapter i'll give him
yeah let's go let's talk dragon slayer a movie as old as me him out in 1981 i have never seen the picture
directed by math who robins and written by him as well robin said kind of an odd career
i thought if you're coming out the gate with dragon slayer he must have all i thought of him as being
this big successful director he did batteries not included which i loved as a kid anyway you
used to rent it constantly at one of the worst was i've ever seen pat i'm sorry i got to cut you off
for a second just your second i apologize the rudeness i looked up book club the next chapter on rotten
tomatoes yeah top critics it's got a 43 percent audience rating of 85 percent so somebody likes this
top critic rating fresh by mister rex read read and enjoyed book club the next chapter
this man he's just playing tarantino he's trying to be devil's advocate gave it three out of four
wow his blurb it's the kind of film that exists for the sole purpose of entertainment which it provides
consistently wow okay i'm clicking on some review i'm bookmarking it we might read that next time
all right let's go ahead i'm sorry mat robins his biggest movie is dragon slayer he did batteries not
included he did the legend of billy gene which i never saw but i remember he did bingo which is one
of the worst movies ever made about a runaway circus dog who helps a young boy i used to
rent that when i was an extra my sister rented and i was like yeah god bingo again what the fuck
my sister used to get bingo and folks with tom selic and danamichi i was like why are you renting this
but we would watch them again and again oh um and then he's written a bunch he wrote the new
del Toro Pinocchio so he's still working he wrote close encounters the sugarland express he's
worked with spielberg but an interesting career for the guy um and i think where dragon slayer really
shines is in its writing in direction it's like i don't like these kind of movies they're never for me
i'm not a lord of the rings type of guy but i really kind of like to this one i like the characters
in it i like the vibe they keep it moving it's always clear what's happening and the biggest
pro of the movie is the amazing effects of the dragon which look better than modern day dragons on
game of thrones it's uh ilm ilm did the dragon pat i'm just gonna drop a screenshot of bingo
into the chat okay please explain remember i've seen it many times what the hell seen this
is this is one of the first screenshots that comes up with bingo of a man holding a gun
of the dog's head yeah no that that's in there around the time of like the movie is like a a scary
kids movie about an escaped dog and it's uh their comedic elements but it's also very scary
all right uh ilm did the dragon slayer yeah well they were created at ilm yes but so i found
this kind of interesting it was the first use of ilm outside of lucas film and this is a new animation
technique made for empire strikes back called go motion which is a variation on stop motion stop motion
is like claymation like the california raises and stuff so go motion to me especially for a 42
year old movie this movie looks great and it's 4k of course it looks like the effects are off the charts
and why did we get rid of go motion so quickly why don't we bring it back today it looks incredible
is not working it looks incredible uh they look interesting fact they lost that special effects at the
at the Oscars two raiders of the lost arc which was the only other movie nominated for best
special effects and also was ilm ilm beat this uh beat itself um this movie this is this is this is
this is one this is this is a this is i mean what a gem dragon slayer is it is from the wonderful
very very finite period of the early eighties dark days of disney films when they were churning out
like the black hole they were doing dark shit for a little while and that stuff was awesome you
still had the mirage of disney in front of you there was we were all still mystified thinking disney
was wonderful and magical and all this and they started putting out these quote kids movies
unquote um that were extraordinarily dark and this is the disney movie with with nudity i mean
there's a they they revealed to you early on in the movie that a character that you think is a boy
as a girl and you get to see some button boob you see some side tit there um you get um this the
simple is the story is very simple there's a wizard and he lives in a kingdom that is being terrorized
by a dragon he is uh known for more of that wizard played by the great great Ralph Richardson
he's awesome in it some asshole minions of the king who also turns out to be an asshole are sent to
summon the wizard the wizard inexplicably at first challenges these guys to stab him so he can prove
that he's magic to them and he dies yeah and Peter McNichol who plays as apprentice is then given
the mantle and the amulet that gives him the powers to be a wizard he then has to take the wizard's
place and goes on a journey he also has his task with bringing the ashes of the wizard with him
to bury them in a quote lake of fire um he's accompanied by an actor who i can't remember the name of
or i don't know the name of who seems like he's only allowed to play parts in fantasy movies he plays
the weird like gnome in never ending story he's in this he's great in this um they have to go now across
the land to to find this dragon and and to destroy it um and as they do they you know they
are accompanied by this band of warriors that also wanted to destroy it they're from the
they're from the they're the townspeople that this king resides over um and you learn that there's
a lottery happening in the town where the king is taking two virgins per year from innocent families
and sacrificing them to the dragon to keep it at bay and the townspeople are sick of it so
and that's why this girl is posing as a boy is because it's where her father's way of protecting her
so she doesn't ever get selected in the lottery um which is paralleled quite brilliantly
later in the film by the king's own daughter who sacrifices herself to to go into the lottery
because she thinks it's unjust that she's not that she's been kept out of it um
there uh you know a lot not a lot happens actually it's a pretty straightforward point a to point
be journey and until this confrontation with the dragon you do not see the dragon until
almost the third act of the film i mean talk about a reveal by the way the reveal of this dragon
is only in my opinion in cinematic history as far as a reveal of a monster goes it is only rivaled by
jaws i've never seen another movie that did such a good job of baiting you for an anticipating to
finally get to see what the fuck it is that they're against yeah the shark popping out of the water
and jaws is number one i would put the reveal of of pejorative whatever the fucking dragon's name is
as number two in dragon slayer it's it's an awesome reveal Peter Jackson has said that it's the
greatest dragon ever committed to film i agree it's what he based smile gone and um the hobbit
yeah it's why i watched the entire hobbit trilogy i just wanted to see what this dragon business
was gonna be i was so excited to see what they were gonna do with it uh i love smog and i hate
every other thing about the hobbit but i did love smog i agree i agree uh i
having never seen it i i guarantee if i had seen it as a kid i would have a lot more fondness for it
but i did like it quite a bit um my one question that i asked you joe and i wondered if you
had an answer after watching it again why does the the guy on the journey keep trying to fuck up
the hero's quest to kill the dragon because he wants to be the hero he wants to be the hero that's
why he tries to kill peter mcnickel when peter mcnickel has already been sent to kill the dragon
he he he wants he wants to be the one to do it yeah he wants to be the big shot here he wants to prove
that the it's it's because it's either that or it's because he knows he can't do it and he wants
these people to fail but either way it's his ego it's his ego he just you know he wants to be the guy so
this movie is violent man i forgot as a kid how much it disturbed me when the princess
yes peter mcnickel frees her from the set you know when you get sacrificed you get chained to a post
and he frees her and she willfully runs into the dragon's lair because she's like no it's not fair
and he when he gets inside he finds her body being eaten by the dragon's babies it's gross
amazing and those those baby dragons looked awesome too i love them yeah they were awesome
the and the way they humanize the dragon too like you know it's a it's a mother fucker it's killing people
and it means yeah only harmed the humans but they do that great scene where the dragon is pushing
the dead baby with its nose and it makes that noise and you're like you feel sad for it for a second
you're like oh yeah it's just another living thing that has a baby it has babies
yeah they do a very similar thing with cocaine bear i bet they had seen dragon's lair because
they show up when it's all these baby bears and it's like well we can't kill them they're just doing
what they're taught to do it really they remind me of it a lot uh this is all building to a finale
where peter mcnickel realizes the lake of fire is the burning water inside the dragon's lair that's
where he has to bury his masters ashes he does it yeah and it brings his master back to life and
peter mcnickel realizes he is the wizard that has to destroy the dragon i am not a wizard i've just
been being granted powers through him from beyond because he's been with me the whole time he just
couldn't make the physical journey of this and he's he rises from the grave so to speak
and there's a big showdown between the wizard on a mountaintop and a dragon where the wizard
creates a storm this fuck the visuals in this third act are fucking like you want to talk about like a
heavy metal wet dream you got like shots of a wizard on a mountaintop surrounded by black clouds
lightning and like drag like a dragon swooping in from the distance and like it's fucking awesome
this is by the way this whole third act is everything i wanted the green night and the northman to be
this is like what i thought we were going to see in those two movies and we didn't and i was very upset
but i think the northman kind of got there but yeah the ending of this is is it's a wizard versus a dragon
it's 40 something years old and it honestly looks and feels better than almost all special effects
that we see today it's just like part of it's that the handmade quality of it that we always talk about
loving but it also just looks great and the thing with this 4k is that oftentimes it makes old
special effects look worse because it's kind of shining a spotlight on them uh that's not the case
with dragon slayer it survives the new transfer beautifully and i actually want to reading a lot
about this go motion it was developed by Phil Tippett who did mad god which is that very famous stop
motion thing that's on shutter right now um but he used go motion it involved putting petroleum jelly
on a plate of glass in front of the camera lens like old school movie magic this is how they did the
tauntons and the adats in empire strikes back the uh creature the demon creature and howard the duck
the wing demon in the golden child the flying machines and batteries not included the dragon and willow
with two heads um and then they used it for certain sequences in indiana jones and et now in Jurassic Park
Spielberg was hiring Tippett studio to use go motion entirely to make the dinosaurs
but in the end opted to go full CGI and that is where go motion ended and it is not used anymore
which is nuts because it looks great i agree well i mean look part of why it's not used anymore it's
probably because look at some themselves kind of got rid of it yeah yeah for CGI so uh this movie looks
the way i think you know there there was a famed failed attempt sort of somewhat famed failed attempt
to adapt the the Lord of the Rings by Stanley Kubrick yeah this is kind of what i thought like when
you go you know or when you think of what that might have looked like i think this is what it probably
would have looked like you know when you hear about your dalski's you know failed dune this is the
kind of thing i think we would have seen and it would have been amazing and it's such a shame we didn't
get to see those but whatever uh i have hogs way up for dragon slayer um i wish this guy would
have i wish this team of people would have made more stuff like this but but it's nice when you find
something like this and know it's out there if you've never seen it see it this is one where i'd say
also two and this is the last thing i'll say about dragon slayer i feel like any medium you watch
this and it's going to be a treat you do a vhs viewing it's going to be that classic 80s vhs everything
you want into 80s vhs you do the 4k it's going to look stunning and crisp and amazing
where you just do a dvd that'll be somewhere in between but you're not going to be let down by any way
you watch dragon slayer yeah the the 4k is a really beautiful transfer of it my hog is up it's not as
high as jose i am just not into sword and sorcery type movies but this is definitely one of the
better ones i have seen uh urge you to check it out it's you'd almost call it a cult movie at this point
it lost money at the box office probably because it starred peter mcnickel but um it is a beloved movie
by your your people making fantasy nowadays by Guillermo del Toro who does commentary on the film
on the 4k by the way and um as joja said peter jackson et cetera it's well worth checking out
we will be back next month and i am very excited to be saying this with a review of indiana jones
and the dial of destiny probably later in the month well that doesn't actually i don't know what else
not to cut you know it doesn't it comes out june 30th i don't know if we'll make the cut it'll be
hero it might be early july but we also have june july hopefully the flash i'm excited for the
flash uh i'll see that flash you got kittens return um we also have maybe cesoo we keep talking about
maybe doing that um yes you so whatever the hell you say it anyway uh we'll be back folks see you next
time and we'll see you in hell