Welcome to we'll see you in hell the podcast covering all your favorite genre films and thumbs
of other genres for that matter my name is Joe DeRosa and my name is Patrick Walsh and on this
week's show we'll be talking about color out of space which I always want to say color and the
shape the best food fighters album but it's color out of space it's on shutter it's a shutter
exclusive so that I believe is the only place you can find it and at least you know streaming free
it's got Nicholas Cage and it's based on the HP Lovecraft story which Joe have you watched any
Lovecraft country no I don't have HBO Max okay so I'm missing that I hear there's a lot of hard
butt -fucking on it really I'm too in I haven't seen butt -fuck -one apparently there's a real
real hard butt -fucking shoot I better get better get watching and choose what you'll do when
you watch it what I I remember I tried I when I was in eighth grade or whatever it came out
93 my buddy Ryan and I were racing to read Jurassic Park before the movie came out and we barely did it
um and it was one of the few cases where the movie is better than the book then we were racing to do
it for the stand when it was on CBS the next year in 94 and I remember I I crapped out at like page
112 of 4000 and we were like let's just watch the movie um and this Lovecraft country I was reading the
book I'm about halfway in and I realized in watching the first two episodes that it's following the book
pretty closely um so I'm kind of doing that now I've only watched two I think they've aired six but
it's an interesting show it's got Courtney Bevance who I love uh it's clearly a very expensive show it
it's fun it's it's kind of scary it's kind of zany I thought I was going to hate it at first because
there's like this big um it opens with like aliens attacking earth it's a fantasy sequence or a dream
sequence all these aliens are attacking earth and then Jackie Robinson in full uniform steps in and
like fights the aliens and I thought well I'm just gonna turn this off basically but um it very
quickly writes itself it's a good show and uh I recommend it I don't know why I'm I'm starting with
that but uh Lovecraft and Lovecraft yeah and because they go in at length to how racist Lovecraft was
which is sort of a big problem with his work I mean he these drop in hard end bombs all the time
and uh the book I don't think he dropped I don't think he dropped end bombs in the books or anything
I don't think no he he I mean unless I would assume these guys did their research but it's discussed in
the book is he is he in the show no not Lovecraft himself but um the lead character and his uncle played
by the great Courtney Bevance are both obsessed with horror fiction and they love HP Lovecraft
but okay they they have a real issue with him and that they like him so much because he's a notorious
racist so yeah there is the the one major criticism of his work is that he that he is
it's discussed that he is dealt with uh I guess particularly black people in in in in what
has many of them to be as a racist way yeah I have in place has seen the counter argument that it's
he's not saying that he's saying that this is what the characters think but then I've read some
of it and then I've been like no it does seem like it's more like he's saying this you know what I mean
like it's a little more it's a little less in the dialogue and a little more in the descriptions
so that's when you're kind of like yeah this this feels like this is maybe his opinion
I mean this uh my mic just put this up here he has a poem that's what I was kind of trying to avoid saying
I couldn't remember the name of it but he has this poem or story called on the creation of
N words uh oh okay Jesus you know that I'm if you'll read this here it's real bad I'm seeing words
like semi human beasts uh etc filled it with vice and called the thing a N word uh Jesus Christ
it's it's pretty intense and that and that passage I believe is in the book so
look H .P. Lovecraft is cancelled I want to start by saying that but um anyway the the book is
really interesting it's written by a white guy uh which I think complicates matters a bit but the uh
it it's a good um Joe what's new with you I wanted to share I received an email this morning
are you getting constant phone calls and emails that are spam and trying to get you to give your
information your money oh yeah all the time uh like the small business administration is calling
and telling me my loans been approved and it's not the actual small business administration it's
yeah I think about how how terrible this must be for old people who get calls and don't know
what to believe you know yeah I know many an old person that has happened to uh have
mistakenly given their money away but uh very sad I mean you've got to be a real sinister son of a
bitch to do that kind of thing without thinking twice I mean it's just it's just incredible how cold you
need to be yeah we wanted to do a cool kids battered in the network deemed it too depressing even
though they often thought the show was too funny so there really no way to win but um that seemed
like an actual problem that old people would deal with so of course we didn't want to do that um
um the I was waiting for an incontinence episode I was mad at that never I I said day one I was
like old people have taken enough for for decades for centuries and we're not going to do jokes about
them wearing diapers we're just not going to do it and I said I'll allow one Viagra joke out of 22
episodes we didn't even do it but I was just like that's what people want this to be and that's
not what it's going to be well but let me let me let me be clear I didn't want diaper gangs you
just wanted a full riveting episode of a man coming to terms with dealing with his incontinence
and the embarrassment you know I'm not a man anymore like you know soliloquies about his
his younger life and that sort of thing I think for that you want the war with grandpa starring Robert
they do make it they make two diaper jokes in the trailer I think woo um anyway I got one today
that just really tickled me because I get daily ones from Netflix and the one I just about fell
for where it was like you didn't pay or you need to update your credit card information and that
would usually get me I got that one today I got a text today your latest Netflix payment didn't go
those are coming hard and fast but now I'm at a point where it's three four spam one fourth real
and it's driving me nuts yeah but I got one today that it was basically telling me I have you know
this credit card issue and I got to take care of it and blah blah blah but it was pretty much
convincing you know I I didn't fall for it but I was like this one actually looks really good
the one mistake they made was they started the email by saying hello deer comma everything
else was so convincing I almost put my credit card number in there and hello deer they always missed
something the key is to look up the email address it's coming from and if it's like got 18 ,000
at symbols instead of an email address then it's probably fake well what kills me is is somebody with
the scheming and mechanical brain yeah to concoct a hustle because these are fairly sophisticated you
know hustles mm -hmm yet not figure out how to get everything translated into appropriate English
that's the part I don't get sure there's always some translation issue like you said hello deer that
gives it away where it's like we wouldn't say that here yeah so it's just such a weird let you know
it's like the nor Mcdonald joke about the murderer going through all the trouble and then burying the
person in the in the shallow grave like right like it's just such a it's just such an oversight after
you did all this other work it doesn't make any sense I agree yeah that's that's an amazing
normal Donald bit for sure it's incredible I had a couple of screaming ends so one my sort of
biggest issue today with the way that these things are the movie business is structured is that like
nowadays and I've talked about it's on here before the common brothers would make blood simple
and they would in their next project would be a Marvel movie you know they'd be like holy shit these
guys really know where to put the camera these guys know how to make an exciting story pop let's
give them a Marvel franchise you'd like to think the common brothers would say fuck you I want to do
my own thing but who knows you know who knows how many great filmmakers we would have lost because of
this so a recent example is John Watts who did cop car and I was like wow what a cool movie with Kevin
Bacon I was like this guy wrote directed it this is awesome I love this movie this guy's gonna go
places his follow -up was Spider -Man homecoming right then Spider -Man far from home now in 2021 he'll be
doing untitled Spider -Man sequel and that is now his career we will never know what that guys right
you know what his art would have been and I think it's a damn shame so today there's there's another
one of these and this one has an even more uncomfortable element because it's a great black filmmaker during
these times you know and it is Barry Jenkins who did Moonlight which I thought an amazing movie
and clearly a very personal movie but he signed on to do the Lion King sequel the live action
sequel to that Lion King that like nobody liked it's gonna be telling Mufasa's backstory
and it's for Disney who allows no creative expression really of any kind
so gives a shit about the Lion King I didn't care when the first one came out who cares I know I know
I liked the cartoon I know I'm the cartoon I'm saying even okay who the cartoon hit when I was you
know 1314 and I liked it but I definitely didn't need the live action reboot or a sequel and I also didn't
care about the internet workings of Mustafa and what made him tick but Barry Jenkins is a great
director and I have to say you know maybe he's he's looking to do a one for them one for us plan maybe
he's looking to get rich and that is no crime I mean people need money want money maybe he's wanting
money so he can do big beautiful things with it I mean it does seem depressing to me when this happens
and it's it's great that black filmmakers are getting shots at these giant tent poles but and I
know they can't all be Spike Lee you know just making like you know amazing movies about about race
really and and also do it you know taking time to do the occasional crime caper and stuff like that
I just worry about where this business is going and where it is putting all of our artists if you
will they're all just going into this machine I mean look at you know we've we've talked about it
but it's like look at look at commercials yeah I'm watching TV today you know you had Jennifer Garner
you know Huck and I think it was capital one or so it's like yeah fuck man you really yeah you need
that what could this possibly be paying you and and on top of it it's like you you need to work
this badly like this is what you want to do with yourself I just have I'm hard pressed to believe
that Jennifer Garner is in a position where she desperately needs the capital one gig I'm sorry
I just don't buy that but but you know and it's it's it's the same thing with Clooney with the
fucking coffee machines and you know Anna Kendrick it's like my god almighty pump the brakes
you're in two TV shows at the same time not counting all the movies you do and you and you got to
also sell Hilton hotels like what what so I think I mean people must just know the the money is
gonna dry up at some point it's it's also easy to criticize which and I know it's easy because I
do it all the time it's also easy to criticize somebody going for the payday and and it's hard to
know if you would do it yourself in that situation sure but you do just kind of hold these people
up to higher standards and it's just a bit of a letdown you know um yeah it's yeah so I mean but look
there is the chance of a circling back around I mean plenty of indie guys went in and and gave the
studio thing a shot been turned by West Craven's a great example uh Soderbergh's a great example of
somebody who does exactly what he wants to do and sometimes that's a 300 million dollar movie
and sometimes it's made on his iPhone you know right right so you know Craven's thing was swamp when
he did swamp thing and right wanted to give that whole thing a try carcorder with the thing
which ended up being a blessing in disguise it was trash at the time and now it's considered one of
the greatest star in film as well time um you know I think Romero he did one uh you know you know
they he kind of danced around with that's just the studio stuff in the 80s a little bit yeah life
force in that well life force is hooper oh you're right to be hooper and to be hooper is another good
example so you know even like Tarantino was saying he and he's now he's not but he was going to direct
the Star Trek movie it's like yeah you know um there's there's the possibility that that this guy
or whoever else will circle back around to doing uh something a little more interesting than the Lion
King sequel but we'll see I just and the the dream is always that you bring your thing your style your
spirit to the big budget project and you you infuse it with your sensibility and make it more
interesting but I don't think nowadays people are allowed to do that and from everything I've
heard from people who work in the Marvel system people who work in the Lucas system is that we basically
bring in these filmmakers who have one small success because they'll do what we say you know they
they they want somebody directing the new Marvel movie who's never done a big movie because they
want to say no this is the way we do things you're making a Marvel movie you're making a Disney movie
you're making it on their terms you might be able to inject a little bit of yourself into it
but I think Lord Miller probably tried to put a lot of their style into it which is not a style for
everybody you know it's a very joke dense comedy and I think they're very creative guys but
from by all accounts Lucasfilm was like no and they went with the safest choice possible which is Ron
Howard somehow out of those ashes came a entertaining movie but usually that's not what's gonna
Howard's a great director he absolutely is he absolutely is that's wrong with me to say but he's
a safe guy with they know what they're gonna get sure but he's also Ron Howard also I would say too is
and I think the reason that worked is because Ron Howard is a he's like Spielberg he's able to mold
he fits different molds yeah you know if you if you tell Spielberg it's this kind of movie he
understands like okay this is how you do this right you know I think Ron Howard is similar in that
sense for sure anyway good that's it I just I hope that doesn't keep happening to our great filmmakers and
I hope that people don't start making great little indies in the hopes of being the guy who does the
Iron Man you know it's just 100 % what's gonna happen it's a bummer it's a real bummer and then we'll
just have no movie at all no movies at all um go ahead uh well and you know but look hopefully it's a
strategy it's like you look at a guy like Steve Hashemi uh who did actually do his fair share of
directing independent films yeah but mainly known as an actor and you know when he popped up in
con air you're like what are you doing dude yeah you're not the con air guy you do way cooler shit
than this you know when even with Clooney when Clooney popped up in Batman and Robin and it was like
this is terrible dude like you make better movies than this uh actors like he said yeah he was like
I he goes I made enough money off the terrible movie that I can do whatever movie I want now
correct so like maybe that's what it is we'll see um I have a scary stuff because we mentioned his
name already and I already had this down to talk about but convenient uh it's not really scary but
it's a cool product to check check out nor Mcdonald's book uh based on a true story loved it
there is an audiobook version available now on audible that he reads uh along with Tim O 'Halloran
who I guess worked on the book with him I don't know if the did you read it or did you just listen to it
I did the audiobook and with somebody with a voice like Nor Mcdonald's you have to listen to him do it
you can't yeah it's so the audiobook version is unabridged and it plays like a movie um because it is
a very heightened hyper realistic realistic version of his life mainly his career um it's completely
exaggerated there's tons of fake shit in there for humor whatever it's very very funny
but then there's a whole subplot in the book of the guy writing ghost writing nor Mcdonald's
autobiography um starting to pose as nor Mcdonald and then you start to hear it from his perspective
it's kind of a trippy uh ride but it's really really funny and then there are some chapters that are
super like dark and like somber and it's weird it's really weird uh but you never really know what's
weird and or when what's real and what's not which is kind of fun yeah yeah and he's a hell of a writer
he yeah he really knows his way around with words so uh it's just a great listen I guess it does fit
the the under the umbrella of scary stuff because it is sort of a fantasy book um very very worth
listening to um and my favorite chapter is that when he talks about meeting Don Rickles and how
disappointed he was because Don Rickles kept insulting him and he's basically just recounting
Don Rickles doing Don Rickles shit where he's like yeah why don't you go suck sand and then but then his
reactions to it nor Mcdonald's like I was incensed everybody laughed but it was that kind of nervous
laughter where you know a man's made a fool of himself it's just it's just so funny it's just such
a weird take on a Don Rickles story like I'm gonna be the one guy that pretends I took all the jokes
very seriously right it's it's a similar vibe to his amazing uh roast of Bob Sagitt which is the
funniest roast of all time of course yeah but um huge subplot in the book that he does liquid morphine
all the time although it he's the kind of like normal Donald also always jokes about being gay
and famously turned down El McPherson and has had no real girlfriends he has a son but yeah like
I think sometimes his jokes are just him plainly stating what is the facts I think he is some sort of
drug addict he claims to be a T totaler who never touches drugs and alcohol but everyone I know
who's worked with him on shows as you just pops pills all day and you know yeah I've heard that
these are these are tales out of school but I'm just saying he is he's the funniest there is um
and I wonder how much of this book that he's that the average reader is gonna be like oh he's
kidding might be real you know there's also another joke I mean spoiler alert I hate to ruin jokes but
just they're just funny uh there's one there's one thing where he talks it's this chapter we're at
length he's talking about these guys coming out to in a bar and they don't know who he is but they're
like we know you but who what's your name what do we know you from like one of those things
and like 20 minutes into the story he's like so finally I point to my own name on my
SNL jacket that I'm wearing yeah it's this odd detail that comes from out of left field and it
sort of colors everything else where you realize throughout this book he's been wearing this SNL
jacket everywhere with his own name written up it yeah I mean he's a comedian almost unlike any
other because the telling of a story the telling of a story can be five minutes long he's he's
perfected this on Conan and literally nothing funny can happen in the story the punch line is
always worth it at the end of the five or 10 minutes the punch line is always like you're laughing
on and you just can't stop laughing right and the journey is fun because he has this insane way of
speaking and uh he just there's nobody like him he's he's a true original yeah yeah it'll be a six
minute story that ends with like and then you suck my dick you know yeah yeah it was very funny
yeah some some cheap uh ending to it I've never seen that I've never seen anybody make Conan laugh harder
than nor Mcdonald throughout the years those are always great appearances Dennis Miller Dennis Miller too
if you watch the highlights in the Dennis Miller show it's like the hardest I've ever seen Dennis
Miller laugh there's one with him David Spade and Dennis Miller together that's I will have
he just shits nor McDonald's just shitting all over David Spade and it's it's it's it's pretty amazing
yeah the one of the worst Jiminy Glix is David Spade because he clearly had this chip in his shoulder
is before he got kind of humbled and spade like does not get the joke and it's really uncomfortable to
watch but fun um if you get the McDonald book which you should I think it is the funniest audio book I've
heard the only one that can give it competition let's say you need another one to fill out your
cart i partridge the autobiography of Alan Partridge has read by Steve Cougan is a masterpiece
and Alan Partridge nomad is almost just as funny yeah the partridge book is relentless relentlessly
funny the spade books are excellent they are the the Matt Berry uh funny toast on toast book where he
reads it as Stephen Toast and is belching throughout the book as he reads it
you know the toast one let me down a little because just because it wasn't hitting those Alan
Partridge heights but um that bit is so funny throughout the book is that he'll be like then I walked into
oh excuse me and then just continue reading and it's it's weird it's like it's like those weird
like really airy bubbly burps it's not like a belch it's like a guy trying to like suppress it
right um yeah the toast on toast is not as good as the partridge books but but it is it is quite funny
and enjoyable listen to i i'm i'm i'm a so amazed by the partridge books that they there will
sometimes be two jokes in a sentence like it it's it's so impressive to me those books and nobody
funnier than Steve Cougan is is wow i mean just god damn it man all almost all the Alan Partridge
stuff is on hbl max and there's it's all good the only ones that aren't as good are the ones
that are like a one -off special but all the seasons are good yeah the newest one is amazing
uh really funny you know the two the two season one that's like the legit one camera sitcom
yeah where it's him doing the you know the overnight radio show and then like his life in that hotel
that he lives in and it actually is a laugh track it's really fucking funny though man yeah um
the uh anyway uh hey what about you i'm real quick i got to say one of my favorite lines of
Alan Partridge no mad that i just heard is he's basically doing one of these things where he's
walking across the country in the footsteps of his father it's called in the footsteps of
father in no mad and it's just him walking from town to town and one of the funniest things about
the partridge books is that he talks sometimes for entire chapters about the most mundane
slights that he's been given in his life it's amazing but um he's talking a bit about how his dad
used to throw stuff at the tv and now when he throws stuff at the tv he always thinks of his father
whatever but he's like oh all sorts of things could set daddy off like uh you know he'd be watching
the news and he'd be so upset because you know a politician did something wrong or the newscaster
was black uh these things would just upset him and that's the style of humor it is every joke is like
in the middle of a sentence and you're like did he just say that like he's uh he's something else
no he's the best my favorite Alan Partridge gag is in alpha papa when he's working in his
great no it's well that's great but no my favorite is when he's in his like he's like he has that like
converted shed that's like his office or whatever and he's in there working it's like toward the
beginning of the film he's in there working and uh his assistant comes in and he like
snaps to you know from his computer and he scolds her and he's like I told you I'm working I am not
to be disturbed and as he's chastising her in the reflection of his glasses you see the porn
on his computer screen yeah strongly recommend they'll cheer you right up yeah it's you can't be
to and there's the last thing I'll say about Alan Partridge my favorite part and I'm a
Jervais fan but my favorite thing about Alan Partridge is it never goes into that fucking and here's
where the character gets real and it gets sad yeah it is nonstop like this guy is an idiot
he's an ass nobody likes him right he's got no fucking clue yeah it's it you're right it just
cheers you up immediately it's just like this guy has it worse than me finally somebody who has it
worse than me right um I had a piece of scary stuff as well and I had this does fit and I think it's
probably the best one we've ever done um even though I haven't done it yet criteria on channel
which has been serving me up some great film history over this quarantine they are doing for October
and you will be hearing this probably around October 1st so you got the whole month on October 4th
they are dropping 29 films under the banner of 70s horror and in looking at this list I have not
seen a lot of them so I'm very excited to watch but um the movies are I'm not gonna read them all but
you can look them up you know they've got big giant movies the Texas chainsaw massacres in there
some early Kronenburg shivers some early crave in the Hills have eyes I would recommend if you
haven't seen it the invasion of the body snatchers that Philip Kaufman did with Donald Sutherland
it is better than the original it's one of the best horror remakes of all time I love love that movie
particularly the end of that movie I agree they also have another amazing Donald Sutherland horror movie
and I mean he only made a couple but they're both great called don't look now directed by Nicholas rogue
you know I have that I'm I just got the screen factory blu -ray yeah and I also have a VHS and I've
still haven't haven't watched either and I've been meaning to watch that forever I you know I
feel like almost embarrassed that I've seen it it's great it's very disturbing there is what has
long been rumored to be an actual sex scene of Donald Sutherland having sex in it um if you want to see
that but uh the movie is great a lot of these are and a lot of them are new to me I remember seeing
Stephen King talk about let's scare Jessica to death I've never seen that movie but I know it's a
favorite of Stephen King um coma Michael Criton's uh directorial effort which I recall being kind of
good and Joe's one of Joe's lost favorites the witch who came from the sea if you remember Joe
discussing oh yeah oh yeah movie cool oh that's a great one they got black Christmas they got the
wicker man uh death dream which Bob Clark did after black Christmas which I've never even heard of
I think I think I think I own death dream okay I shoot dude I'm it's embarrassing at this point I
ordered uh about 15 screen factory had a huge sale on Blu -rays a few weeks back I ordered about 15
yeah and then and then it was like right when I was starting to get ready to move so I'm like packing
thing uh my DVDs and as I'm packing I'm running back to the computer and canceling I cancel it down
to like six DVDs because I already owned ten of the ones I had ordered I always do a check for it
because I don't you know what I mean because it was like they were on like I never watch shelf and I
didn't it was I'm like I got to stop I just got to stop buying media I've put a plug in it I have
so much I just need to catch up on but I it's it feels a hole you know it does that Godzilla set up
there mine is also prominently displayed I haven't even broken the seal on the fucking mine still sealed
yeah couldn't wait to get it had to have it I have to sell it selling stuff like crazy though like I've
been I've been selling records and and old Blu -rays stuff because so much is going out of print for
whatever reason I guess because they're done with physical media but um Larry Cohen's it's alive
is a lot of fun Brian DePalma sisters a lot of fun theater of blood with Vincent Price is a lot of
fun you know there's a lot of great stuff in here so check it out it's definitely worth you know
a two -week trial if you if you are unsure but criterion channel usually packs the channel with a lot
of good shit I recommend um why won't recommend is images Robert Altman's horror movie believe it or
not Robert Altman not very good at directing horror it sucks and there are people like there are
people who just can't admit when a great director made a bad movie so you know images is really an
interesting like it's like anyone else made this you think it was absolute horrors shit it's a bad
movie it's an interest it's more of a slice of life I'd say right right uh I'll give you one more
scary stuff too something fun to watch this Halloween I didn't even know this existed and I believe you
can see it on night flight the night flight app it's either on the night flight app or the shout tv app
both are free no it's on the shout tv app and it's which is totally free you can just download it and
you it's free um but did you know about this there was a show called full moon frite night
hosted by none other than William Shatner okay and it's a joe bob were el virus style horror show
okay where he hosts 13 movies I I'm assuming they're all full moon movies
you know from the production company right uh and I watched one or two of these episodes
I what's not to like it's a joy it's a campy horror movie with Shatner doing the wraparounds being like
you know oh I'm sorry I I said my mommy you know you know you know that kind of shit I mean it's
mummy yeah yeah you get it I mean I don't have to you know it's not sure but uh it's it's it's very charming
it's very fun to watch and I think around this time of year October leading up to Halloween
in for me in particular that type of horror watching is my favorite like something that's
that's got a bit of fun or or camp to it uh a bit of you know something with the host uh it's just
it's just really fun this is a great season for this is a great time here for tales from the crypt
yeah uh the HBO version um you know tails from the dark side like this is like the kind of stuff I
really get excited about right duck tails duck tails tail spin tail spin uh American tail an American
tail uh Jonathan tail or Thomas trying to think of a porn version of an American tail I couldn't
think anything anything that's probably just called an American tail yeah I thought I could the girl
with uh American flag paint on her ass I'm sure that's that exists that's a good point right does that
exist uh search point on your work computer for us please Mike um our movie today oh wait no we're
gonna do movie quarters you gotta do movie career yeah um I would like to start with also on the
criterion channel all of Albert Brooks's uh early amazing movies they have everything from real life
up through mother um I'll just do mother I think that's the lat to my opinion the last great Albert
Brooks movie uh and they're it's interesting because I liked I saw it in theaters and I've probably
seen it once or twice since but there's two things that I found kind of strange in this time hey I always
thought of it as kind of being his sitcom movie like just less deep and less interesting than his
others but it's not a really great and interesting stuff about the parent child dynamic in this movie that
I just must have overlooked I think it's a much better movie than I remembered the jokes are great
I mean they're really really funny the one thing that kind of stands that keeps me at a distance from it
is that Albert Brooks is great and Debbie Reynolds is great I do not understand how Debbie Reynolds is
Albert Brooks's mother it doesn't make sense to me why I just I mean Albert Brooks reads Jewish man
to me like he that that's so much his persona in the same way that Larry David or Woody Allen has
that persona and Debbie Reynolds is miss apple pie that there doesn't seem to be let's see she
wanted more ethnic thing just say it wash well I got you you're expecting a little bit more of a
New Yorkie kind of like almost like Michael uh Myers and coffee talk kind of lady yeah yeah you know
I can't imagine that Albert Brooks's actual mother it is anything like Debbie Reynolds then I learned
that he wanted to cast Nancy Reagan which would have been nuts but like clearly he was going in a
different direction so it's very possible he has a Jewish father and a and a non Jewish mother I don't
mean but look at his brother look at a super Dave yeah I would if Debbie Reynolds I would think that
Debbie Reynolds was super Dave's mother but then also I am always hard pressed to believe that they
were brothers like that always used me yeah Albert Brooks really leaned heavily into that Paul
riser steep Richard Lewis Woody Allen like 70s New York absolutely Jewish guy thing you know and
that that's all I'm saying it you know it's obviously a little dodgy to discuss but like it just
doesn't quite sync up for me however they have a great chemistry um and I wound up just being
delighted by mother it there there is a sitcom me vibe to it but it's not in a bad way it's just
great jokes one after the other it's great one of my favorite Albert Brooks scenes ever is the scene when
he first gets to the house like the food scene where she's like taking the cheese out of the freezer
and everything so funny and then that in the scene where the brother is like what what's wrong with you
and he's like I am having sex with our mother your brother's going you're sick that's sick that's a sick
well and they also really have Rob Morrow kind of play up their neuroses and all that it's just
it's strange you know they're both these dark -haired guys and then Debbie Reynolds is just not that
that's all I'm saying but they they are all funny together for sure I watched that movie I'd
seen it and I when I was visiting my folks I said mom we have to watch this together because she's
so much like my mom and my parents were in hysterics like I've lived that fridge scene with my mom and
dad where I'm yelling at them like what is wrong with you throw this away right so it's such a
wonderful film to watch like with your folks yeah or not with your folks but yeah I really I really
like that movie a lot I do too Joe all right uh you know what uh here's a great comedy
I rewatched back to school uh Rodney Dangerfield love it it's it's the man's uh it's his white
album I've always said I truly believe that it's his white album people would say it's his greatest
work I disagree easy money is the sergeant peppers in my book but it's just a tremendous movie
catty -check catty -check I love catty -check I don't consider it a danger field movie uh saying when
they gave him the ball and said you run with this now I do think he's at his funniest in catty -check
though he's amazing in catty -check yeah but it's it's more of a it's very much a supporting role in catty -check
ladybugs terrible meet Wally Sparks meet Wally Sparks is is the third best of his uh if if you know I
don't remember it I just remember it looked like he was dying while they were filming it's it's it's
yeah but I mean that's that one is is how about my five wives do you ever see that one I've seen
them all okay I've seen them all there's another one where he plays like a mob mob uh some fuck I
fucking I can't remember anyway back to school if you are hesitant to watch this film here's
why I wanted to bring it up first of all don't be it's a wonderful film and yet another movie where
the where the fantastic Williams vodka plays the asshole wins apka yeah or zapka excuse me plays the
asshole I mean that this was a string a movie critic one said they they need to release a box set of
his movies where it's just every movie he was in because it like called like the bully box set
or whatever it's like just one of the guys the karate kid back to school um the movie is just great
the kid from Christine it plays Dangerfield son Robert Downey Jr. you very young Robert Downey Jr.
in the film very funny in it you got Harold Rammus an actual comedy writer guiding the ship as
opposed to like whoever wrote those better your field pictures uh Bert Young playing Dangerfield's
bodyguard yeah but of course it's the the spotlights on Dangerfield and if for no other reason you need
to watch this movie for the house party sequence that takes place about 15 minutes into the movie his
wife played by Adrian Barbo who hates him and he hates her uh their rich she throws a house party he
wants nothing to do with it it is a crash course in comedy writing I mean I have never seen so many
jokes concentrated into such a short space uh uh in a film and of course the the greatest
the greatest joke in any Ronnie Dangerfield movie in my opinion is the guy from son of a
beach jerk would something his name Dick Benedict or whatever
Dirk Benedict on that show but he was uh I don't know his name in real life he got submitted to me
as as a TV writer so I guess he's out there right now uh well he's Dick Dietrich wasn't he
Dietrich here yeah nice to see he's looking at a painting at the house and this is right after
Dangerfield catches his wife cheating on him uh in the other room and uh and he walks and did
for walks up and uh Dick Dietrich goes Mr. Mellon and he like he's looking at the painting he goes Mr.
Mellon your wife was she's Mr. Mellon your wife was just showing us her clipped uh -huh I remember
what Dangerfield goes big deal she shows it to everybody and he goes well she's very proud of it he
goes yeah proud of I too I don't go way we get around it parties and then a guy goes it's an
exceptional painting and the danger goes oh yeah the painting yeah yeah uh damn it it's a
fucking masterful sequence this entire thing Jesus Christ you got Kinnison as as the oh no it's the
teacher that's another scene where the girl gives like the very PC like liberal answer on what
Viet Nam was and then and Kinnison just starts pacing around is she right because I was there
yeah I own it and I'll be watching it probably right after we stop recording because it's been
five years at least for me great movie I love back to school wonderful film um
I while we're talking Zabka I would be remiss if I didn't shout out uh three of my best friends
three of the best people in this business uh John Hurwitz Hayden Schlossberg and Josh Heald
I've known them separately and together for about 10 15 years John Hurwitz was the first person I had
lunch with here in LA uh and the three of them what I'm getting to is they created and run and
right and direct cobra Kai very nice which was on YouTube red and uh you know that made it
hard for even me as a good friend of theirs to even check it out it just seemed like even though it
was easy it seems like something where you wake up you're like I'm not gonna figure out fucking
YouTube red today you know right so now it has moved over to Netflix where it always belonged um they've
already shot season three I assumed the move to Netflix means they're gonna get a lot more money
it's already been a huge hit for them but it's great it just shows you how sometimes something really
great can just be on the wrong platform and never get seen or talked about by anyone um and it's a shame
but it's just a hard fact of life you gotta pick your streaming service carefully because otherwise
if you're on peacock probably nobody's gonna see your thing and that sucks but um for now things could
always change anyway cobra Kai is about as fun and true to the spirit of the original on update as
you could possibly do they've been talking about doing this they've been talking about doing it so
long that it was always like a joke like they were like we'd love to get them to do it and just like
have them still be obsessed with all this karate bullshit as for as 445 50 year old man and I was
like that's a really funny idea and it was always much more comedic when they would talk about it
but they went the right way it's like one of the rare shows where you can just imagine
whole families watching it and loving it and the adults being entertained and the kids not being
traumatized and the messages are good without being preachy the fight scene that ends season two is
one of the all time great fight sequences certainly on television that I've ever seen I'm very proud
of my friends for doing it check out cobra Kai I think the new season premieres early next year
so catch up now it's a very fun show very good I will stay on the comedy course and then also a
TV show I finally got to watch when I briefly at HBO max curbure enthusiasm season 10 which is the latest
season I loved it man a lot of people said that they didn't think the season was that great I thought
it was really funny I thought he falsely went head on with the me too stuff I was shocked at how
directly he handled that stuff and also he comes across in each scene as being disgusted by the
whole movement which is a wild thing to put out in the world you know I'm saying yeah and then
like when the misunderstanding happens with him and though because of course it's curbure enthusiasm
a misunderstanding happens and now he's going to get me to and the woman is saying you know I want
this money and this apology and which is also a very policy thing to present premise wise at the time
especially that this came out and then him just kind of taking the approach of like I am going to
be Larry David about this and not pay any money and then when I go to do the apology I'm going to make
it even worse because I'm gonna fuck that up because I'm Larry David or whatever but I loved the
season I thought it was really funny I loved the idea the premise basically is aside from getting
me too he opens a spiked coffee shop to piss off a guy who won't let him drink coffee at his coffee shop
anymore I thought it was a really funny idea some really fun cameos Vince Vaughan who I am a huge fan
of kind of wasted though in the thing I don't he's in it yeah but like they don't I don't know if he
said I'll do it but I don't want to be like Vince Vaughan or if they just didn't give him much to do
but like his first scene when he comes into the show he's kind of doing the Vince Vaughan thing and he's
being pretty funny and then after that he just doesn't really have any funny stuff to do which was kind
of a bummer because you're excited that he's in there it was also very confusing to me that he
wasn't playing Vince Vaughan he was playing Marty Funkhalzer's brother so weird it was odd it was
distractingly odd but nonetheless I was happy to see him in there and Gene a world where I think in
the same episode you have John Ham playing John Ham it's like yeah it's tricky to follow all this I
didn't like John Hamman Kirby either but I liked it I thought I thought that was funny and charming the
way he like had to emulate Larry David but but I will tell you the I hate to call it a lucky accident
Jesus Christ so sad that that Bob Einstein has died one of the great comedic actors of our time
and one of my favorite people on the show for sure as Funkhalzer but talk about lucking out I guess
when he because they started shooting the season before he passed and I think just to kind of
make up a storyline about why he wasn't around they said he's in China
so now when they come back with season 11 they're just clearly going to say he died of COVID
he got coronavirus so right obviously that's I was like my god what are the odds of that
unless I'm mistaken and they went back and added that so they could retrofit the storyline in but
you know even if they weren't going to do another season he's got to do COVID you know he's got to
do COVID I want more than anything the you know my one of my favorite episodes of it's always sunny ever
is the gang quarantines with the bad flu season I'm praying that they do a sequel to that with the
COVID quarantine probably yeah or do a whole season where they're just quarantined in the bar
right and like because those are my favorite episodes when it's like the four of them locked
in the bar together it's almost how I feel about like most big comedies for like my entire life
is that I always want to stay in that initial 30 minutes where everybody's hanging out and being
hilarious before the plot starts you know what I mean like that those are my favorite sunnies too
where it's the four of them and their chemistry and they're just sitting on stools you know or whatever
it may be I look for some reason plots are sometimes a drag to me in comedy because then
they have to be following the plot instead of the laughs the laughs are an afterthought at that
point so I realize every movie can't be people sitting around a table talking but I'm saying those are
my favorite parts of the movie I text you the other day and I said I they I want them to do an
episode called the gang rename the redskins where it's just them in the bar pitching new mascots
right and of course it's highly offensive right so I want I suggested the Denzel Washington's right yeah
and I said the Colombians yes right yeah there we go my last one is this is going to be a first
for this show well actually two things Joe I wanted to tell you I famously I didn't realize how
famous it was till Joe brought it up like a year after the fact that I had to stop hellraiser two
halfway through and didn't finish it so then when Joe Bob did it I was like okay I'll try it again
that scene is still traumatic and I feel like it's too much even for a horror movie where the guys
cutting himself and maggots are coming out and it was the edited scene that they had to there was
the scene they had to cut down to get to an R rating yeah I was you know in a bad place when I
first saw it I was like I don't need more of this I just can't watch more degradation or something and
now I'm so numb I guess that it didn't even bother me and I really loved hellraiser two yeah
you wonder what would have been with the budget that they originally had but it's a really
creative and interesting movie and a perfect sequel to one but I'm happy to finish that review now
a full year or more later another review I'm gonna just do the first half of and review again is
Charlie Kaufman's new movie I'm thinking of ending things and the reason I am not able to review it
now is I don't know what to say about it I don't know what I thought about it it's the same way I
felt when I saw a connected in New York I I'm going to need another viewing and maybe I'm dumb
but I know a lot of smart people who have no idea what to make of this movie that said
it creates it certainly creates a fucking mood it is weird as hell it feels almost like and maybe
it's just because Tony Collette's in it but it feels a little hereditary -ish at times there is horror
in it there's long you know 30 minute discussions and cars in it is it a comedy at all
did you say that it's not but it kind of is it's a bunch of genres I don't you know it's Jesse
Plemons who I love and Jesse Buckley as this couple going to visit their parents but it's also not
really that at all there's a parody at the end of it of like beautiful mind type movies where
everybody's wearing old age makeup and like slow clapping that like just seems like Charlie
Kaufman doing a sketch almost I mean coffins is the opposite of what we were talking about earlier
here's a guy where they're like it's weird or whatever the fuck you want and well I don't know we'll
figure it out like yeah I don't know how these films make any money but animal and I'm Alisa you know
he was starting to lose me and yet there was something very fascinating about that movie he's
he's very gifted but I think he gets less and less commercial every time out and he was already
about as weird as commercial filmmaking can get with being John Malkovich so this movie to be honest
made no sense to me and I'm eager to watch it again and see if it starts to grow on me or what but
right now all I can say is I've never seen anything like it and I'm eager to see it again I will close
out with a rewatch of a Brooks title since you were talking about we were talking about Brooks defending
your life classic classic it'll I'm sure to be part of this criterion thing that you were talking about
it's on there yeah um you know what and if you've never seen a Brooks picture and you're
going to enter in I'd start with defending your life I think that's a good starter movie
um and then I'd go backwards from there um it's not my favorite it's a lot of people's favorites
it's a lot of people think that that's his like sort of Annie Hall or whatever um it's a wonderful
little film uh you know as you said a classic but by by most standards um rip torn is great
Merrill Streep is is wonderful yeah it's a really lovely film um and there's some really really big
laughs in it but my favorite it's not my favorite of his films because it's actually the reason why
is because it's the most this is not a criticism it's the most fantastic of his films
all his other films really deal with like a real life situation and how funny and tragic that
real life situation is and I almost never like a fantastical comedy it's not my thing at all so
that's why I I like it less and he's nicer in it I like him when he's more fucked up like he is in
loss in America or modern romance or something like that yeah like he yeah he's not enough of an
asshole in this he's just kind of a dumb guy uh you know that's seen in in loss in America where he's
like lecturing the wife after she loses all the money you're not allowed to say the words nest or
egg yeah when you were in the forest you need a point to the bird and say he lives in a round stick
I mean it's that crazy the only reason that that scene wouldn't have people walking out is that he is
so funny the jokes are so funny in it but it is a man screaming at his wife in an enclosed space
that somehow is hilarious yeah so anyway but but but I think defending your life is a good like I
said a good starter picture for sure and then I would go back from there um I'd go life
then uh modern romance lost in America then real life because you get this great yeah a real life
is a little artsier than the other ones but very funny and then I would do mother yeah so life is
kind of an extension of his early uh SNL short films that he would do which when you watch them now
are about 500 times funnier than the SNL sketches that they're doing that are supposedly so legendary
but you would just be super dated now and his stuff never does is you ever watch the trailer for real life
you know watch it on YouTube okay it's it's it's it's he does his whole thing where he's like he's like
I'm going to present this trailer to you in 3D and then everything turns blue and red and green of course
the jicag is you don't have glasses right and he keeps throwing things at the camera and then
there's another great trailer you should watch where it's it's the promo he did for for online
to say that all his movies were streaming on Netflix for a while uh huh and uh I've seen that yeah
yeah and he goes how did they get on Netflix I'm just gonna say I don't condone kidnapping in any way
yeah but the right person's child who's holding the right position helps
I'm surprised Brooks never worked with Charles Grodon again because they're so fun together
and I'm also wish right now that I could see Albert Brooks on Jim and he click and there's still
time I guess but I'll probably never see him he's a private man I want Brooks so badly to do like another
I want some I think he's great as a dramatic actor he's the uh you know we talked about Chris
Rock on the last episode yeah he blew me away and drive I thought I was gonna start a whole new
career for him and it just didn't he pulls it off man but it's like I but I just want to it's that
Tom Hanks thing I want to see before I'm dead another fucking Tom Hanks comedy yeah I want to see
another burbs or league of their own where he's like stressed out and crazy and screaming at everybody
like it's he's great I want to see it again I think what happened is lady killers is he was like
I'm gonna go back be funny again he's really funny in that movie which I do feel is lesser
Cohen brothers but underrated um I think that was his nail on the coffin he was like I went back
they don't want to see me do comedy anymore so I'm done but that wasn't like and even that though
was like he's doing a character in a way yeah it's like I want to see like big Tom Hanks yeah sure
you know like you know those kind of big things though are kind of not
as funny the older you get I think I think a screaming and frustration is like a young man's
game unless you're Larry David but I don't know Tom Hanks now I think we know too much we know how
much money's in the bank you know it's easy to distance yourself when he's in bachelor party and like
I you know I need this now whatever but now it's like just call somebody Tom you're very rich
maybe that's knowing too much sure uh real quick I should say the the great Timothy stack
played uh Dick Dietrich on Nightstand with Dick Dietrich which was his old fake talk show fake
Jerry Springer type show and it's so weird is my buddy uh Ben and Mary so wait that's who the
guy is in back to school that's his real name Timothy stack yeah okay he was playing a character
and son of the beach and uh he had a bunch of show yeah but my buddy Ben and I used to be obsessed
with Nightstand with Dick Dietrich and then you've once in a while find somebody who remembers seeing
it but Ben is gonna be at my house in a half hour which is crazy uh he's driving his way up to uh
northern California stocking nice and drunk tonight with him now he's here for like an hours
and it'll be a socially distance masked hang all right well you get drunk after he leaves again
sure I probably well I'm actually the plan is to take October through uh
Jan October November and December off see if I can do it why what during this what are you nuts
I'm I I've been drinking too much yeah we all have there's nothing to do I know I'm just seeing
if I can do it I'll probably be back on the horse October 3rd oh boy all right uh let's talk about
the film at hand Joe color out of shape uh a fine production from spectra vision who
also brought us you know Elijah Woods company who's brought a brought us many a fine
indie horror slash genre film uh particularly of note today is Mandy which was a wonderful
vehicle for Nicholas Cage fabulously directed and a tremendous visual use of colors uh in spectra
vision followed Mandy up with color out of space different director this time it's uh what's
his name Richard uh Richard Stanley Richard Stanley who famously uh was the director of the
island of dr maro remake who was that was his dream project he was removed from the project
essentially sort of banned from the set um it's a famous story uh there's a great documentary about it
you should check it out um but this was his first directorial effort since then
not the documentary meaning since the island of dr maro I think it's super cool that spectra vision
got behind this guy and let him make movies again because clearly in my opinion he's a great filmmaker
and this movie was a perfect follow up to Mandy uh in my opinion for Nicholas Cage
even though Nicholas Cage did a bunch of other shit in between I just mean like for
you always forget about the eight movies he did between the ones you know about
yeah so um it's based on an hp lovecraft story of the same title um and the basic premise is
a meteorite lands uh in a in the yard of a family's uh home where that is sort of a remote
home in a very small town the sheriff and others are not happy about this family living there
because they wanted to buy that property and develop it uh but the family refused
because it was a house that Nicholas Cage's character grew up in and once the meteor lands
things start to get weird and people start to act strangely and it all sort of unravels from there
correct um that doesn't that that is exactly what happens and yet this is a movie that kind of
really does its own thing past a certain point um i'm surprised it is as weird as it as it is
and makes as big a choice as it is when you think about Richard Stanley getting a shot to direct
again after you know 25 years it's like you think he'd go for something a little more safe and down
the middle but um my guess is Elijah Wooden them said here's a pretty decent budget like go nuts have fun
and and and we got your back and that's what people need to do to make good stuff and i think he really
did it feels kind of homemade it feels like the effects are all way better than what you would normally
see in a big budget action horror movie they all i think because they probably did them on the cheap
and more practically look so much better and more realistic the like you know creature and mutation
effects are all really horrifying and sick and memorable and he seems to have kind of taken a cue
from steward Gordon who is without without question the best uh adapter of hp lovecraft he really
gets him and gets the sixth sense of humor at the core of a lot of his stuff because i think this movie
is pretty funny and yeah it's very funny a lot of that is Nicholas cage and Nicholas cage
for the first half of this movie i was like boy you so rarely just see him play a normal guy kind of a
dork and he's so great in it um he had me really laughing hard when he's watching himself on the news
and he keeps going like oh what the fuck nobody talking about my fucking hair right my god i look like
you know like it was so funny in that you know very like relatable and then at a certain point to
signify that the the alien has has tapped into his brain in a way or the the life force is is getting to
him he starts doing a trump impression i don't think there's any question that that's what he's doing
and when i looked online it pretty much backed that up to show that he's like getting sick in the head
he's doing trump that to me seem like that that's very funny though if you watch it again you can't
not know it i mean he's so in that um Paul Schrader movie doggy dog with cage and willum defoe for the last
20 minutes of the movie Nicholas cage does a Humphrey Bogart impression and there's no reason given
it's really nuts but it's like clear like hey what do you bang you know it's it's very obvious and in
this one he's doing a whole different voice and accent and i guess sort of an in joke on trump but
again how could Richard Stanley allow that unless cage was just like that's the only way i'll do the
movie but i found it distracting i thought cage was basically giving two different performances one great
and one kind of annoying and hammy but i love cage and he makes i think he makes the movie work he's
he's always doing it for real you know Tom Hardy sometimes seems like he's standing outside the
character and Nicholas cage at least always inhabits it he's got another great scene where he goes nuts
and screams like he did in mandy with the vodka this one he's like punching the roof of his car
screaming he flips out for like a minute i mean he's he's great the movie once it goes nuts i mean uh
i really had a blast with it but i also like the first half where it's just like playing a real
family and weird things are happening there's almost an ambulance quality to the first half
and then the second half goes completely out of space if you will yeah well it's it's interesting
because i didn't i didn't i when cage first starts going a little bad shit i was like why is he doing this
like is he kind of winking to camera and then as the plot develops i go oh oh they're all losing
their minds right then it's sort of retroactively justifies everything by the end of the film so uh
but i i i i i enjoyed his his crazed acting just for the emotional peaks and valleys he would do
where he'd be like screaming and then be like okay honey i'll see you later then you know what i mean
like right he would really do like these weird emotional swings i thought it was pretty funny um
but the practical effects i want to talk about that see you know and this is what happens when you
have a production company and a director that know what to do with their budget they clearly knew
look we have a couple effects in this thing one of them is uh these animals in a barn
becoming mutated and going crazy and the other is a hard thing where a young child and the mother
are morphed together yeah and have to become this hideous creature right uh really fucking disturbing
really just some really like crononburg fly level esque disturbing body harsh itness to me
yeah which i love he's he's watching his son fuse to his wife i mean it's a horrible thing
it was disgusting um but anyway you know Stanley clearly knew like this has to look good
so let's put our money there yeah because the other stuff the color out of space the color that
everybody keeps seeing that's making them crazy there's a way to do that affordably there's a way
to do that with with post -production uh imagery and whatever they really do it with a lot of
neons and it just winds up looking awesome yeah so i wouldn't be surprised if some of that stuff was
shot that way using strange you know lenses and filters on the cameras themselves or whatever
and then it just sort of enhanced and post but but they just knew where to put the budget they knew
what to do with it they knew what was important uh my only real criticism of the film is the pacing
of it is a little strange because it's not you know what a pacing is the wrong word the construction
of it is a little strange because there's like there'll be like a scene where the daughter is
packing her suitcase and being like we all got to get the hell out of here right now we're in trouble
we're in danger and then like five scenes later when it's like apparently the next day yeah she like
has her suitcase like okay i think i'm gonna leave now and you're like wait what right you know like
so it's it's a little confusing where you're like i think that scene was supposed to be
after the other scene but they had to split them up because maybe they didn't have enough footage or
film was running too short and they had to spread things out or or something i don't know but um
but that's my only real criticism i really liked it it's the first in a trilogy of HP Lovecraft
adaptations that Stanley's gonna do is next one is the Dunwich Horror which uh
i very much look forward to and i hope he gets to make it and i hope he does it with spectra vision
but i mean my hats off to all these guys my hats off to cage my hats off to spectra vision and my hats
off to Richard Stanley to keep the spirit of this kind of thing alive and to keep doing this kind of
thing and uh just just repeatedly nailing it way more often than not nailing it uh when it comes to
this sort of thing so i i'm very impressed by all of it same here i uh i think Nicholas Cage is one of
the saddest in a way stories because i used to just love that i knew i'd get to see him in a movie at
least once or twice a year right um and almost overnight i know it took longer than that but he just
became this uncastable guy who has to kind of make his way in the fringes Bruce Willis is kind of
going there too a lot of stars are um where it's all direct to video stuff but where that's a bummer
when you see all these movies with like Nicholas Cage and John Cusack running down the street with
their hair pieces bobbing around shooting at each other um what you get some of those and maybe you
don't check those out but you also get some really really cool work that he is getting made by lending
his name to it and also he is upping his cool quotient by making by beating the big studios at their own
game i mean mandy is such a better i i i never it's you know uh one of the best horror whatever you
want to call it sci -fi action movies of the past five years and it came from some nobody who got
Nicholas Cage and made this movie for probably a million bucks you know so i love that uh
cage is still out there i love that they're still doing as you say this kind of
80 style horror and i think that there's a big market for it when i went and saw this in the theater
the one night it was out just sold out and they added another screening i think there's a real hunger
for it i just don't think the people who make the decisions know about the world out there whether
there is a hunger for it so you have to have horror fans do it and find these people uh and that's
Elijah Wood apparently and his crew are great at that there's a lot of people who are great at kind
of finding the old uh people to honor their heroes who they came up on right so that was
a quite a ramble but i liked color out of space it felt uh original and homemade i guess in a way
that you just don't get much anymore and i liked it a lot i agree with that and also too it's it's a
strange um it's it's unique to see uh a movie and story be told with such a typical plot line but
for them to do it in an interesting and different way now i know the source material is
fucking christ a hundred years old at this point yeah uh but you know uh but that was very
interesting to me because we've all seen the immediate crashes and shit goes wrong
right story before but this one was a really original take on it and i really liked it um
i think Stuart Gordon would have been proud so uh you see alpacas fused together screaming you know
that's what it was alpacas i can't remember the kind of animal uh what another weird plot line when
he like Nicholas cage being like those alpacas are the way of the future yeah alpaca milk get the alpacas
yeah just a strange addition to the film um anyway folks thanks for joining us today that's our show
joderos a comedy on instagram and twitter joderos a comedian on facebook
i'm the patchkwalsh on twitter and instagram next uh not even next month we'll be back in two weeks
with two new episodes and those will be veratica which is glen danzig's erotic horror movie which i
have yet to watch but i'm very excited too well you're in for one and the other joe helped me
the other the other will either be the lodge or the devil all the time one of the other it'll be
yeah yes i've seen both i can do either um but yeah we'll we'll be doing those and i just said hell yes
what are you hell yesing like what are you excited about the lot whatever one you say we'll do
overall yeah it doesn't help us make the decision but thank you it's a scene like i'm real excited wow
have you seen veratica yeah i ended up producing an episode as act show for it it was wild okay yeah
we're pumped to watch it it's i saw about the first half i don't want to say anymore uh for now
but anyway we'll be back and uh thank you everybody for the support thank you so much thank you as always
for you guys uh coming along with us on the patreon we will see you next time and we will see you
in hell