I'm here for Bet Rivers online casino and sportsbook with poker icon Phil Helmuth.
And now thanks to the excitement of Bet Rivers, I'm also a slots icon.
That's great! And a same -game parlay icon. Cool, cool. A blackjack icon,
a money -line icon, a roulette. Take it from Phil Helmuth. If you love games,
Bet Rivers is the place to play in Bet. Bet Rivers. Games on.
Must be 21 plus in present in West Virginia. Void were prohibited. Terms in conditions apply.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another, no other sportsbook has
an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning, or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
winning hits different here must be 21 plus gambling problem called winning 100
gambler offer not available in all states terms apply see fanatic sports book
app
Welcome to We'll See You In Hell. You know that it's part of the Fangoria podcast network.
And if you need the info about the network including other programs or how to follow
this show and find past episodes of our show, just visit Fangoria .com. Welcome to season
3 episode 2 of We'll See You In Hell. Hey gang, we reversed. I know we were saying we're
going to return with Blade Runner. We kicked things off with tremors because we wanted
to start with a spirited discussion it developed into a passionate argument about vacation a movie
I think we both felt exactly the same on but still managed to argue about and today I'm sure
we'll wind up screaming at each other as well talking about a movie we both despise called Blade Runner.
This is it folks, Blade Runner. The movie that some critics have called
boring as shit, Pat Walsh, Walsh Weekly magazine.
Misunderstood when it first hit theaters, the influence of Ridley Scott's mysterious
new Noir Blade Runner has deepened with time. The only thing that's deepened is the
horse shit around this fucking thing. It's a terrible movie, a visually remarkable
for achingly human sci -fi masterpiece.
Now look, visually beautiful, yeah.
Absolutely, whenever I try watching it,
because I never finish it, when I hit pause,
I'm like, boy, that would be an amazing,
framed painting in my house.
Almost every shot in Blade Runner.
And I can respect that.
To call it achingly human, suck my dick.
Who said that?
Now, achingly human.
If someone said that to you, when you're drinking with them at a bar, you would pay your tab and leave without saying goodbye.
Now, Sheila Benson of the Los Angeles Times, at the time the film came out, called it Blade Crawler, which I quite agree with.
Yeah, go on, Sheila.
And Pat Burman in the state and Columbia record described the movie as science fiction pornography.
yeah I had to agree with that too it's it's it's I mean but I mean look at these
accolades British Society of Cinematographers best cinematography nominated it
won best cinematography it should win best cinematography all right no one is
arguing that this isn't a a wonderfully filmed wonderfully art directed
wonderfully visual movie and I love Ridley Scott and of course you know I love
Harrison Ford the man who wrote it David Webb Peoples wrote
But unforgiven, unquestionably one of the best screenplays of all time.
How this movie is this praise, I'll never understand.
I saw it in the theater, when they re -released it, the final cut, I fell into a deep sleep.
I bought the DVDs, the blue resin that came out, I was like, well, this has four cuts on
it.
Now I'll definitely watch the good one, because I never remember what's supposed to be the
best one.
I sit down with my buddy Ian, we're going to sit down and watch this thing.
the two of us snoring on a couch sound to sleep within about ten minutes. I tried
to watch it for this podcast that it would be fresh in my mind and folks I was
asleep before the credits had finished. I cannot stay awake till the end of this
movie. I know there's a unicorn at the end because I usually wake up around the
point. There's a unicorn running across the screen. Darryl Han is in there
somewhere. Somewhere you got Sean Young in there. Sean Young. The plot makes no sense. I guess
unless you're just a huge fucking nerd then maybe it makes sense to you. There's a version
with narration that everyone seems to think is worse because it's like, hey I don't need this
movie explained to me. No, well Harry. I do. I love Harrison Ford. The narration is bad.
Oh he's dozing off during the narration. You can hear him falling asleep during the narration.
And and of course he would. It's I mean it's I'm a big believer than any movie that
needs four or five different cuts is probably not a great movie. Sure. And the movie is
you won four or five cuts of you're not getting them. No. There's there's a three hour cut
of plan strands automobiles that John Hughes turned in and was like you guys kind of you
know help me figure out what to cut here and they cut half of the movie an hour and a half
right the blue ray comes out it's supposed to have all these deleted scenes they're not on there
right supposed to have a commentary not on there right so where's that hour and a half
of my favorite movie that I'll never get to see you're not gonna get to see it because you want to
see it whereas if you need the blade runner five disc ultimate collector's edition I own it
uh you know you can go grab that at best buy right now uh they are releasing finally the
The Exorcist III special edition on Blu -ray, and it's going to finally have the William
Peter Blattie director's cut, which is supposed to be great.
And I love the other version too, but you know, it was one of our first hangs, we watched
this.
It was our very first hang, and I believe there was a little mutual nap during that, not out
of disrespect for the film, but we just had a big day, the two boys.
Not a big day.
It's, I mean, the cast in this movie, and I've said it many times over, I mean, you know,
look, forget the cast, Harrison Ford is really all we need to focus on here.
This is a science fiction movie that came out in the early eighties that was directed
by Ridley Scott about cyborg, humanoid, androids to things that starred Harrison Ford.
It came out like the year after Reddress of the Lost Ark.
It's literally like if you were at a spinning wheel of elements you could put into a movie
that you'd love, I'd be like why I just hit the pater, like I don't need to spin this wheel anymore.
Yeah. And time after time, I mean it's at a point now where I literally, if I say I want to
take a nap but I need noise on, I put on blade running, I go to sleep. Yeah. And you're right,
the plot makes no sense. Who gives a shit if the robots are walking around amongst the people?
Why do they need to be terminated? I don't even understand. They don't seem to be doing any harm.
No. That guy in the beginning is just doing the interview. He's trying to get through it.
I have seen that scene, that interview scene at Blade Runner, 65 times because every time I'm like, oh fuck, I remember how bad this shit is.
My father was just visiting and it was a surprisingly fine visit, but when he left, I was so energized.
When your parents leave, you're like, oh god, I'm so excited to do anything in the world.
And at the time we were going to record this podcast we got delayed and push back right but I popped that Blu -ray in
More energized than I feel like I'd ever been right and I was snoring on the couch
I don't fall asleep during movies my like Heather comes in my girlfriend. I was like
Pat like woke me up. I was in a deep slumber. It is it's like having a music box play to me
It's it's terrible and and the I mean the you this is how bad the
voiceover is it's it's painfully bad as you said he's you have
monitoring to tell if he's doing off but then it's just I've it's just not
needed like you talk for our podcast and I'll do Blade Runner narration
over it. So there's a dog barking outside right now. Pat was talking into the
microphone about how a dog was barking outside. For some reason he cared
about dogs. We heard the ice. I didn't care about dogs. I cared about my
paycheck and never see in the face of the chief of police ever.
Yeah.
Well, you know what?
It's a huge frustration of mine because narration can be a crutch.
It can also be kind of thrilling.
Good fellas.
Everyone's narrating that movie and it's like it's a blast.
Yeah.
It's Chris Azee.
Real big in the Good Fells in Casino.
Yeah.
There's that part in Casino where Frank Vincent starts narrating at one point.
And I love it.
And Goodfell is when Leota is on the stand and then just starts walking to the camera and narrating it
It's like I remember when I first saw that I was like it was like the first time I saw porn
I was like what a cool thing that just
Narration can be so bad when it's done poorly you and I both watched the duo
Or I finished it with Sandler and Spade. I still didn't finish it. It's it's okay. It is what it is
But there are times when it's the same thing Sandler's it's a comedy. It's dumb comedy
And Sandler and Spader narrate in this thing and it's like guys, we know
The Sandlot the narrator's yammering on it's kids playing baseball. I can follow this plot who narrates the sandlot
Leota I think it's Leota. No, he plays the father. Uh, and
Sandlot's a fantastic movie. I mean narration. It's a character names and played runner annoy me go on Chris
Yes, that's Darryl Hannah's name in the movie but Gaff is Edward James almost his name terrible
Roy Batty which sounds like he should be in a Scorsese movie or in like midnight run or something like that
Zahora
Which is just you know come on. No, but this guy Brian Dobbson there right at the sound. I'll put really out of play the dad
Look
But, wait, Ray Liotta, he played the -
Dennis Leary was the dad, was it?
Yeah, you're right.
What movie did Ray Liotta play the dad?
The field of dreams is the base for movie Ray Liotta, soon.
He plays Kevin Costner's dad that comes back.
No, for sure.
Yeah, you're right.
Back from the dead at the end in a ghostly game of catch.
No, I just -
I mean, it's a stunning film to look at, not the Sandlot.
I wonder if people are just getting really stoned.
I mean, if I were to be stoned, I would be asleep before I place the blu -ray on the
blade.
But what are people enjoying about it?
And I wish we had that, you know, maybe we start bringing guests in here, somebody
who's passionate about Blade Runner because I almost don't believe that you love Blade Runner,
folks.
I don't believe it.
I believe that you think it looks great, but I don't believe you love the plot of Blade
Runner.
It feels like one of those movies that you're supposed to like and people say they like it
Yeah, even though they don't really like it. Yeah, it's up there to me with gone with the wind
Which is like I like gone with the wind. I've never not watched it in two two days. Yeah, I mean it's
It's a trudge through
Sure shit for four hours that fucking thing just keeps going terms of endearments another one. I like I love terms of a
We're gonna disagree now. I mean you got it. I mean I look I thought I was having a real nice time here
But I'm just trying to name movies that ever
There was that weird beep again. There's a beer is a beep happening in Joe's house that is so loud and I don't know what it is
Do you think it's the smoke alarm being like hey, I'm low on batteries or something? That might be it
It's disturbing terms of a deer man is a tight two hours. It's a funny movie. It's a sad. I never saw terms of a deer man
I'm gonna be honest with you. I never saw terms of a deer man. What are you doing? I never saw terms of it?
Yeah, sorry when I was nine. I didn't see turns of a deer. I don't care that you haven't seen turns of a deer man. Why are you?
I'm honestly saying that I'm taking blind swings for other movies that people love that I thought might be bad
I pick one that genuinely is bad that you can't think of one
I thought I've gone with the wind and then I couldn't think of another one all right, but it can't just it can't be bad
And people it's like going with the winds a good example to me where it's like I'm sound of music's another one
Here we go. Oh, what a masterpiece. I hate this fucking movie. I think people just like it because they're supposed to like it
I do like both of those, but there I mean there's lots of examples
I know a lot of people hate citizen Kane. I think citizen Kane's really good
But it is really good. You know if somebody were to say to me. It's boring as shit
I'd be like, okay, I'm in fine. I don't
Spanglish is another one
You think spanglish is a beloved movie now. I'm Jeff. Why do you have it out for James L Brooks? I always just a funny
It's just a funny movie to reference. Yeah, this is fine at best. Uh, you know what one is magnolia. Oh, I fucking love me
That's one of my favorite movies. Jesus Christ almighty. Magnolia is one of my favorite movies of all time
Well, Pat, I mean cry when they sing the song you cry when they sing the song into the cake. Yep. That part makes me sick
Nah, I cried when I saw it makes me furious great acting, but I I've never I watched it once I will never watch it ever again
I've seen it 20 times.
I'll tell you another one that gets praised, it doesn't deserve it.
Life aquatic.
Life aquatic, I guess I liked enough in the theater and then I never revisited it.
So maybe not.
I like Wes Anderson.
Boring to piss me in the same buddy, you know, I tried to watch Blade Runner with during
a massive blizzard in new york city
we had to get out of the uh... the apartment we wanted to go see a movie
suicide on life aquatic
hopefully i haven't told the story of the podcast
it was movie phone
and i call them up
and i go uh... they go look what movie you want to see
go uh...
the life aquatic
i'm sorry
uh... the life aquatic
the life aquatic ends in the bathroom when he comes out i'm going
The life aquatic trying to say it in like different ways right veins pop
We have been cooped up in this apartment for like three days and I was screaming into the phone right the life aquatic in like different accents
Trying to get it to register and then he and goes isn't that movie called the life aquatic with Steve's as Sue
Right the life aquatic was Steve's as who seven forty five yeah nine ten went on for about five minutes
Right, and the scary part of the story folks is this took place three years before a movie phone was invented
That's how long they'd been cooped up. Yeah, it was rough. If you get what I'm saying. Yeah, it was real rough now
Here's the weird part about Blade Runner. I'm
Excited about the sequel. Is that happening? Yeah, it's definitely happening. So he's making alien. Oh, no, uh, the other dudes make an alien
Five the guy who made shopping he's doing alien covenant really Scott
Well, then what's the guy who made chappy doing?
He's making a different alien covenant is the sequel to Prometheus. I like Prometheus. I thought it was terrible
Okay, but I am excited to see alien
Yeah, show me an alien prequel doesn't have any fucking aliens in it. There was no monster in the whole movie
I'm like this is fucking boring
I don't give a shit about the organisms that eventually give birth to the thing like sure show me some fucking come on man
This is stupid. I thought it was a step up from resurrection
But so is anything. I mean what that's so yeah, and again kind of visually cool. I thought the oblong camp
Chappies deal
Because by the way, I don't know district nine, but after Chappie district nine does not exist to me
No, that guy made Chappy and that's it.
Look, I thought the one about like that you could go live in the clouds without
the answer or whatever the fuck it was.
I didn't see Liseum and after Chappy.
I will not see Liseum.
Liseum sucked.
Chappy was an F minus to me.
Liseum was like a hard C or maybe at best.
All right, D probably.
He is making Alien 5 which is essentially Alien 3.
he's doing a sequel to Alien 2 as if Alien 3 didn't exist.
And Ford didn't exist.
Alien 3 is really underrated in this.
It's not a good movie, painfully boring.
I bought it without having seen it on your say so and I'd like to club you.
It's it's fincher, it's it's a well -directed movie.
It's not great, but I think if it wasn't following up Alien 1 and 2,
well you didn't even like Aliens 2.
I can't even just talk about it.
Aliens is whatever alien aliens is an a -plus alien is an a -plus alien is an a -plus alien is an a
You're out of your fucking mind
You're out of your fucking mind aliens. So I think aliens is is is is plenty
Plenty fun or whatever it's it turned a suspense horror sci -fi movie into a into an action shoot him up
It might as well been fucking Arnold Schwarzenegger in the movie
that's fine to me alien that's not fine to me that's how it appears in the same this it had been one movie well
I don't like the direction of the sequel I don't know what to tell you it's like you know that alien one was very
suspenseful with some slow bits near the beginning although I think it's an excellent
suspense movie and I love alien one aliens two is non -sub -action for two hours twenty
Yeah, and way way more fun to me way more exciting and a way better movie. I mean we've discussed it before you like a simple -minded film
I don't think aliens is a simple mind you like you like something spoon -fed alien is lots of banging bang bang bang
Alien is a woman being chased by an alien. That's it
But it's scary and it's just spent for and you don't know what's going on. I really agree. I'm telling you
I love the movie. I'm saying aliens is a much better movie. It's aliens is to alien with Terminator 2 is Terminator and Terminator 2 you mean better?
No, no. Terminator 2 to me is an unwatchable fucking mess of the movie. You hear what he's saying, folks.
When you hear what he saw Terminator 2? It's been five years at least. Yeah, try watching it again. I guarantee you won't get through half of it.
I guarantee no, I'll finish it. It's terrible. That may be an alien for a long
It's gonna turn you off so quick that you're gonna be like what am I doing watching this right now? He always did and you
I've watched all the alien movies within the last year with my girlfriend. We both
Fell in line with I think most people I know so many people who aliens two is their favorite all -time movie
Alien one is a really terrific movie and also a kind of a trend setter. There's so many people argument
We'll never work with me. I know it never does, but it's also like you're always so convinced that you're right
And I'm just saying like because I'm right
There it is folks
Like I'm very often like okay, that's your opinion and that's cool
But I find myself having to argue in a way. I don't like to argue
What do you mean you won't?
You just say you're right and that's it if somebody's opinion differs with mine, especially on movies
I'll go all right cool, but you have a feeling of
You're an idiot if you disagree when I'm saying one movie is great and one movie is a little better than great
That's not what I'm saying. That's not what I'm doing when I'm saying is I think your opinions are idiotic
And they're not convincing me of anything different if you said something that resonated with me
I might think differently
I don't know what you want me to say all I can really say is that I liked aliens to more and so do most and I think
It's a dumb thing to say and a ridiculous opinion to have. Yeah, that's exactly what I'm saying
Don't agree with you. It would have yet to what it sounds like to me is that you think that aliens I
Wish these movies had different fucking titles so you could tell what we're talking about
I think alien one is great and aliens two is a little better than great and you think that
that alien is a little better than great,
and aliens too is great.
So I don't think aliens is great.
I think aliens is fine.
I think that -
What's your rating of aliens?
B minus C plus.
See, that is so stupid.
That is so stupid.
Looking through your shelves right now of DVDs.
Why is it stupid?
If you're gonna put aliens too
up against every science fiction horror movie
ever made you feel it ranks somewhere near the middle listen is that what you're
saying listen to me is that what you're saying no listen to me with this is what
I'm saying I am not a fan of James Cameron I am not a fan of his work I find
that he does the same thing over and over again he has thin characters he has
lousy dialogue he has unconvincing acting and he pads it with a lot of cool
effects. Ripley was so much better fleshed out in alien. That's because the
mother daughter thing was so much more compelling. That was now first of all that
doesn't count for two reasons. Not a first of all, not only of all. Doesn't
count for two reasons. That was laid out for him already. So I'm not giving a
guy credit that he was able to take a tremendous foundation and somehow build
another couple floors on top of it. He didn't create Ripley. Okay. But Ripley in
the first one, she's like the third lead of the movie. Which is what she's the
one is a lot. That's why it's awesome. But you don't really know much about her or anything.
My point is this. That's what you're saying paper thin characters. She's a way thinner
character in alien one. My she's not a thinner character. Are you swayed because you can see her bush in alien one?
No. No. Why would you say so like that? It's a matter with you. Her bush is coming out of her underwear now.
It's I'm just telling you something. James Cameron's movies are not good movies.
Sometimes he hits the mark accidentally, okay, but a movie after movie I couldn't
Avatar titanic show the abyss. I think you must know that I don't think avatar is a good thing. I'm saying this is
I think his me saying aliens is a is a masterpiece in my opinion an action science fiction masterpiece
Has nothing to do with my opinion of the pathetic avatar, but I'm saying to you that I think that aliens
Ranks in the same sort of feel and vibe as all James camera movies do where I go
Yeah, there's explosions and there's some cool action stuff
But once you take that away, I don't give a shit anymore. There's nothing here for me to sink my teeth into
There's no suspense. There's no real build. I think aliens too has tremendous suspense in it
I don't agree. I think it has tremendous suspense in it and also tons and tons of action in it
Ali and one is a is a very clear suspense tense movie and it works
Fantastic alien is she's she's she would be you know, she's not a paper thin character and either
But she's way better developed into way, but I'm not giving him credit for that. That's like saying that's like saying hey Joe
What's a popular movie that's out right now? I can't think of anything captain America. That's not a sequel already
Well, then you're I'm gonna have to give me an hour
Because they don't exist. You know, it's like hey, you know look
I love the exorcist, okay, and you go hey Joe exorcist too wasn't great sucked
Give me a favor write a sequel to the exorcist and then I write it and you go my god Regan's character is so
Develle I mean in the first movie she's possessed half the time you know barely anything about it and they go yeah
Well, it's pretty fucking easy when all the god damn works been done already the same characters
but he made it a much deeper and more resonant character which is the only goal
of a sequel maker and I would consider Aliens about his perfect a sequel as
like the godfather to here it takes as far as you're insane you're insane you're
insane what was laid out for it that's insane and it develops it further and
makes it a better movie it's insane and there are plenty of alien fans that would
agree with me that say the the heart of that franchise it was in the first
movie and it was and it was stripped away but from on this in the second film and after that
subsequently every alien movie has been a bullshitty action movie. Well I don't know how you
could say that the heart was stripped away when there's infinitely more heart and two. I don't
agree that there's more heart. Are you talking about her relationship with her cat and the first one?
I'm talking about the the heart of the franchise. What what makes the thing interesting? What makes
the pulse pulse what makes the heart mean to me one movie comes out with no
thought of there being a sequel or anything else then you take that movie as
what it is when the second one comes along I don't always feel like you have to
be lining them up and comparing them and saying what is better or what is worse
he took a terrific formula and terrific characters and to me made them better
and stronger and added new people into the mix right I just feel like it's a
terrific sequel and I think most alien fans would agree they might say one's
better than two they might say two is better than one I think this I think
that when you look at what came after when you look at resurrection for Christ
say I don't know how you can be so harshly critical of aliens too resurrection
it is dog shit yeah I mean just because there's other dog shit doesn't mean I
can't say that this piece of shit isn't as good as so you think aliens to is
dog shit I don't think it's dog shit I just said it was a good
My point is is you can't tell me just because there are movies out there that are dog shit means it makes this movie good
Know what I'm telling you is that I think aliens to is the best of the series
But I'm also saying like for you to be this angry about aliens to I mean it's just nothing about the other movies in the franchise
Which are terrible just aliens to was maybe a man who really fucking gave a shit and was like okay
If I'm taking on this classic property
I better at least try to make it better and he's one of the rare people who in my opinion succeeded
Somebody likes alien a little more than two. I get that completely. I mean just even the put I'm looking at the posters right now on my iPad
The even just from poster to poster. It stinks
Alien one the poster talking about the poster, but I'm saying even on this base of a level
Alien one the poster you got an egg. You don't know what the fuck it is. It's leaking. It sounds like some kind of ooze out of it
I'm saying if you've never seen the movie you see the single what the fuck is that?
It just says alien and then it says in space. No one can hear you scream. That is a brilliant fucking tagline
Alien aliens with the taglines podcast aliens alien aliens trailer is incredible the original aliens aliens
It just says the word aliens. There's no picture and it says this time it's war
He stinks
James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James Cameron, James
Water turning into shit. I don't care about it. Well, I'm talking about the nearly three hour cut of the abyss because I like the director's cut
I mean, you know, Avatar is embarrassing. I didn't say I Titanic. I loved in high school. I don't know how I feel about it now
Titanic you loved in high school
This is the movie you loved in high school. So Titanic
No, I'm not saying this is the only movie I loved in high school. I'm saying I loved it and I was the matter with you
Well you were in college and now I'm sick of everything when you see Titanic. Titanic is not a movie for a cynical person obviously.
And if I was to know I'd probably like this is garbage but it's technically amazing and you know obviously people enjoyed it.
I mean this guy's track record is I mean he's made the highest grossing movies ever. These are the movies James Cameron's made.
Geno genesis I've never seen piranha to the spawning the Terminator
Pretty good. Yeah, I think we could probably kick things off with the Terminator aliens
The Abyss unquestionable sci -fi masterpiece the Abyss I would throw a terminator to terrible true lies a lot of all
You think true lies is terrible. Yes. I don't know what to say to you Titanic. You don't like movies and
Then Avatar
are. That to me is a pretty impressive track record. Well, if you're talking about box office
numbers, it's incredibly impressive. Uh, he's also been married six, five times probably
because because these women saw, saw his films and said, I gotta leave. I mean, he's been
married five times. You're going to do, you're going to do what with water in this movie?
It's gonna it's gonna appear to the sister from Scarface in the shape of what and it's called the abyss
Wait, what happens? I'm done. I'm out of here. I'll see you later. Bye
I'm not a fan. I'm flabbergasted here
Aliens we're talking about how many wise alien I throw up my hands of alien
Alien is Richard Donner Superman aliens is Brian singers Superman returns and
And that's all that there is to that.
I'm not sure I even follow.
I didn't like Richard Donna Superman that much.
It's a matter of his is terrible.
Yes.
With some fun sequences.
I don't even remember what those would be.
I think aliens is just a it's one of the only times
that a woman has been nominated for best actress
for an action or sci -fi movie.
Maybe maybe the only okay, there's probably been two I just want to we were as incredible an aliens to well
You know, and that's the thing too is who's the girl that plays a newt? No, who's the girl from
X -Men
There's 25 the main girl in the new X -Men movies. I don't know the place the old so speak
The main chick Jennifer whatever the fuck are you yelling at me and you don't know the answer
Jennifer Lawrence. Yeah, Jennifer Lawrence. Guess what? She's the only woman's
ever been nominated for a movie about a lady who invented a mop. Does it mean it's a great movie?
She was nominated for Joy about a movie. I'm gonna say he's a bad director if he directs
Sigourney Weaver like and and deserved you get away from her. You bitch. You don't kind of throw your
fist in the air at that moment. I'm not saying the movie isn't fun. I'm not saying it doesn't have
exciting moments. I'm not saying the special effects aren't great. I'm saying as a movie, it is
nowhere near the work of the first movie. Okay. Because it's typical James Cameron. It's a lot of
flash and very little substance. Get away from where you bitch is a catch phrase as far as I'm concerned.
It's a one liner. I think aliens too is packed with substance. I would I would argue more substance than
one. And I don't necessarily even need substance in an action sci -fi movie, but it has it.
It's not supposed to be an action sci -fi movie. It's supposed to be a sci -fi horror suspense
movie. That's my point. Don't you tell James Cameron what it's supposed to be? I'm gonna
God damn tell. Here's what it's supposed to be. No. No. And I bet if everybody hated aliens
too, it would be your favorite movie of all time. No, because everybody hates alien resurrection.
And I think that's dog shit, too
She has sex with the alien in that one rap. It's I don't know I couldn't even get through it and I'm a big fan of
Joss Whedon. Yeah, it's a terrible movie. It's a terrible terrible movie. That's really bad
I just saw Serenity do you ever see that no big fan never watch Firefly or Serenity watched all Firefly
Benj watched it and then watched Serenity and I loved all of it you think Serenity is better than aliens, too
I enjoyed it far more I cared way more about the characters all right folks
Just drop that down in your tally sheet.
Well, you're not going to win any nerd points distance serenity.
Maybe true. I've never seen it.
I don't think even your hardest of nerds would prefer serenity to aliens.
But okay.
Who knows? Look, it's, you know, just sort of an, these movies that you would think are just undisputed classics.
You find a way to make them seem like they're dogs.
I mean, you know what else are supposedly undisputed classics?
everything in the criterion collection that fucking series I tweeted the
other day I hope one day to make a movie so shitty it becomes part of the
criterion collection there's I watch as much as I'm like are they fucking with
me right now it's like they have like these campy b -movie piles of shit
that look like people made look like high school kids it's like the kid in super
rate made it. It's terrible. I'll admit I haven't seen a lot of them. I do own every criteria
in collection blu -ray because I got in the habit when I needed to make rent. I would buy these movies
for 20 bucks. Then when they go out of print they jump up to two three hundred dollars. I have the
entire collection. I think they release some great ones, some stinkers. I love the care they put
into it, the packaging, the extras, etc. Sometimes the documentaries on them are infinitely better than
the movie. Nothing beats the packaging. Yeah I can't tell you how many times I've bought a god damn
fucking criterion collection. They'll really lure you in. And I can't wait to get home from me
but wherever I bought it and crack that packaging open and I put it in and it looks like it looks
like something Kevin Smith pre clerks would have made and I want to kill somebody. Yeah. I've usually
had pretty good luck with criteria and I really love the company. I love that there are people out
they're doing it. I own the entire collection as well as a criterion mug. I will not shit on the
criterion collection. Well, you kind of just did. No, I'll admit that not everything that releases
an masterpiece, but I don't think it's supposed to be. They're shining a spotlight on forgotten
or an under -appreciated films. And sometimes they're just releasing classics that have gone out of print.
Let me just read you something about James Cameron's recurring themes here. I don't need to hear Wikipedia's thoughts on James Cameron's recurring themes.
Just saying, what's he working on now? Avatar 2?
Oh, two, three, and four. Okay, well that's stupid.
And the fact is he's retread the same bullshit so many times. They had to put a recurring themes section in his Wikipedia page.
Most which I have never seen I just watched the Brian to palm a documentary which I fucking love
There's a guy who follows many many many many many many things
I've threw every single movie he's ever made
He's also contributed to
Follows themes throughout moose. He's also Cameron has contributed to several television series including dark angel and
Onto Raj, you know those fucking masterpieces. Well, I think he had
And an episode of Entourage that he acted in, he didn't like write Entourage.
So did Scorsese, I think.
Like all kinds of great people were on Entourage, doesn't mean they wrote the episode.
His writing tomato Scorsor off the charts sort of, Terminator has 100 % which I don't understand.
That's crazy.
Aliens 88 %.
No, we'll say.
Me and my dad when he was out here watched 45 minutes of Terminator 2 on cable before he went
to bed.
and I was like, this is awesome.
The effects still look great
and I had a great time watching it.
It's not awesome.
You, so you go, I was 11 and couldn't see it.
You're, I saw it as a 12 -year -old 14,
whenever you go to see Terminator 2 and you think.
Oh, my fucking mind.
Okay.
All right.
And then I rewashed it in my 20s
and I, I was so excited to watch it
and then I sat there with my friend Pinkstone
and I made fun of it the entire movie.
I go, this is fucking terrible.
Okay.
We got Stone rewashed it.
It ends with a soliloquy
Where Linda Hamilton talks about how a robot taught her how to be human. It's cheesy. It's a bad movie
Eddie furlough's gonna teach you how to be human
Eddie furlough's in his dirt bike, and he's got a public enemy T shirt on like I mean the
The symbolism is just slapping you across the fucking face his step parents are literally like
Nobody's can tell this kid what to do. It's it's they're basically almost say like it's like he's gonna lead an army or something one day
It's a terrible movie the any furlings best friend of the movies they read head from salute your shorts if you remember that show cares
You have to cast people and things salute your shorts was big. They're like essentially nobody dies friend with three lines
Let's get the guy from salute your show essentially nobody dies Linda Hamilton's a bad actor. I love that like okay
Why is so bad? Look his red -headed friend with three lines is in salute your shorts
I've already made all the good points that I've been moving. Now I'm getting into my
new shift. If you want a really nitpick, I'm gonna rewatch it. I know for a fact I won't
hate it. I think it's a awesome action special effects side by kind of moving. I didn't
say it didn't have awesome special effects in action in it. That's my point. If you take
that away, there's nothing left. There's nothing left. Now, you look at the whole thing,
a boy and a robot and they're teaching each other and learning from each other.
It's cool.
A boy and a robot.
Think I'll watch the Iron Giant.
You fucking queen.
Yeah, I love the Iron Giant.
I don't even like cartoons and I love the Iron Giant.
This is ridiculous.
The arguments I have to put off with on this show.
All right, and then oh, folks, what I would love to do and I won't is just to sit and
read you the titles and Joe's DVD collection.
Read them.
Do you own Terminator 2, by the way?
Yes, I do.
I own Terminator 1, 2 and 3.
Okay, and you love 3, too.
I think 3 is awesome.
We got some great action in it.
And I think the plot twist and 3 are the best plot twist ever, and I don't remember.
I remember that.
Truck saying being awesome the truck seems the best action sequence I've ever seen ever in an action movie now
What happened you guys? What titles you take on bridge with over here? What happened to Jonathan Mastow?
Who the hell is Jonathan Mastow exactly?
He directed break down with Kurt Russell, which is fantastic and he directed your precious Terminator 3 rise the machines
All right, you think you'd want to I'm thinking about what he's been up to I'm gonna look him up in the meantime while I do this
I want you to take on bridge with some of these titles we own open water what you talked shit about in the last
I bought it on blind faith and I didn't like it
But I didn't feel the need to throw it away or sell it. I it wouldn't be a podcast without me mentioning tower highs
You own norm it, which I'll admit is funny. Yeah, but I mean like I I don't believe that you think these movies are better
Terminator 2 looking I didn't say they were better than Terminator 2
Okay, but you talk and get so angry about these things because Terminator is that you despise them because the general consensus on Terminator 2
Is that it is a brilliant masterpiece the general consensus on Norbit is that it's a pile of dog shit sure
I watched her and I go this is not a pile of dog shit
This is way funnier than people gave a credit for and I watched Terminator 2 and I go this is not a brilliant masterpiece
piece, it is very, very flawed and nobody calls it out.
You can't argue it.
You go, not you, that's not me in person, I'm a person, but you can say it's very good.
It's okay to say Terminator 2 is very good, but you don't just is.
I don't think it's very good.
I think it has great action sequences, it's an action move, but yeah, but so is Predator
and I care about the characters in Predator, I don't care about the characters in Terminator
2, I just don't, I do not care about them.
You care more about Arnold and Predator
than you do about Sigourney and Aliens?
Oh, 100%.
100 % percent.
That is so crazy.
110 % percent.
I'll go a step further.
I care more about Carl Weathers in Predator
than I do about Sigourney and Aliens.
Folks, I hope you're taking notes.
Because this buys me 1000 dumb statements
over the next season of this pocket.
I can say pretty much whatever I want it to say.
I can become a hall of cost denier and still be winning
Stop it, yes. That's ridiculous. Jonathan Moss, you've yet to pick out a bad title, by the way
Here's the horror sci -fi section. What do you see that's bad there? Now let me just ask you here because I think you despise this movie too
Why do you have love actually a movie I like? I love the film. I worship it. Oh, okay. I must have missed it
I really live it emotionally every Christmas. Yeah, it's great. Yeah, I cry
I have to watch it every year with my parents and I have to walk out of the room so I can cry in the other room and not be embarrassed.
I used to do that when I was a kid. I did that with plants and all of them.
And I do that with grumpy old man every time it gets to the part where he goes to the hospital.
Great man.
But you see quality up here. You see moon. You see westworld. You see John dies at the end. You see the black hole.
I never thought he'd end up there. Or the black hole. I maybe I'll borrow them.
They're great fun.
I agree with a lot of your clips, but I'm just saying the movies you have you can't think they're better than Terminator 2
But I guess maybe you do I would put in
that
Blu -ray player over there
95 % of the movies I own before I put in Terminator 2
Okay, I love the character of the Terminator. I love Arnie
Yeah, I love the concept. I don't think it's a good movie
Would you say that that's a movie made by somebody who doesn't care though?
That's made by a movie by somebody who really gives a fucking shit about making a good
movie.
Not saying he doesn't give a shit.
I'm saying I don't think he's good at it.
All right.
I decide I don't get the hatred.
I get the hatred now, certainly.
I can't name one James Cameron movie that I think it's great and the guy is responsible
for the biggest blockbusters of all time and I'm just like these movies are not good.
I feel the same way every time I watch one.
Here's your guy.
I've said my piece. I mean, Terminator 2 is a low budget masterpiece. Terminator 1.
Terminator 2, just really in the same way of aliens, takes that great
kind of gritty thing and makes it bigger and better. Terminator 1, I enjoy, I think it skates a
lot of it, skates by on 80s. It's just a fantastic premise, both movies. And you know maybe there are
lot holes in them. I certainly didn't see them when I was 16 watching it.
After Terminator 3 rise of the machines, your buddy directed surrogates. I don't know
what that is. That's that Bruce Willis movie where like everybody has like a fake version
of themselves. And then a movie called Hunter's Prayer, which how do you do breakdown then
Terminator 3, then those? This Hunter's Prayer cast is really difficult or something.
hurting too. It says it's an upcoming action movie. Ready for this? Yeah. Sam
Worthington. Where's that guy been? Followed by Alicia Silverstone. Okay, that
won't even get released. Do you do U571 Jonathan? Yes. That was kind of cool.
Joel Kinnamin. I like Joel Kinnamin. Oh wait, I like him too. I thought he was
somebody else. I don't know who anybody else here is. It says it's scheduled for
release September 30th, 2016. Look, maybe it'll be good.
Alicia Silverstone coming back into the mix. Maybe she's going to make it come back.
I just watched the crush the other night.
Is that a good movie?
It's not, but it's part of a genre that I have a lot of affection for, which is the
trashy erotic thriller from the 90s.
Is that the one with Wahlberg where he's the crazy boy?
That's fear, which I think is an excellent movie.
I've heard the best of the genre.
I've heard that from the director of Lingerie Glen Ross.
I don't know about a movie being better than it needs to be.
That movie is great.
you should watch it right you'll hate it i'm sure
uh... i love gling gargling ross uh... the crush
i'm sitting there watching it there's these shots where it starts at her toes
and pans up her body and she's in a bikini carry l was his watching her like
you know practically jacking off
and there's so many of these shots that i'm like how old issues i started to feel
a little weird i looked it up and she was fifteen when the movie was made
how do you get away with that
They're not doing anything illegal.
They're not showing her naked or anything.
Yeah, I guess that's true.
Right.
I mean, how do they get away with, in Moonrise Kingdom,
how the fuck did they get away with the 12 -year -old kid
touching the 12 -year -old girl's boob?
And then her talking about his hard dick.
I was like, that did you talk about his hard dick?
Yeah, she goes, it's hard.
No.
When they hug, I'm like, what the fuck?
Look, that memo is PG.
Yeah, maybe a 13.
Pat look, it's been a pleasure talking to you. It's always nice to be screamed at about a movie that I think we both enjoy
again
What do you want to plug buddy?
Well
This is definitely not going up before this Sunday who the hell knows I have a samshur. Oh, you know what?
I'm going to be on episode nine of showtime's roadies
Created by mr. Cameron Crowe congrats
that should be on I believe end of August be on showtime I think that's it for
now all right my short fiction my short horror fiction column some severe
situations will be out it's probably out already on the Fangoria website so
go check that out please I know how to fund right in those stories and gonna release
one a month for the next year comedy wise I'll be a double -in at the end of
of July for the Comedy Festival and then for the Fringe Festival in Edinburgh all of
August in Scotland. I'm on Twitter via Instagram at the Patrick
Walsh, Joe is Joe DeRosa Comedy. And as always, we have a very loyal and devoted fan -based
tweeting at us. We'd love to hear from some new voices. If you love to show, tell us, tell
your friends, leave us those five star reviews, comments. We already have the five stars, which
is great. We'd love to keep it. Thank you all for listening and for talking about us and
treating us so nicely. This has been We'll See You In Hell presentation of the
Fangoria podcast network produced by Thomas DeFaio and executive produced by Ken
Hanley of Fangoria Entertainment. For press opportunities advertising inquiries
and information about We'll See You In Hell contact Ken. It's Ken at Fangoria .com.