I'll see you at hell, I'll see you at hell Bye, bye Bye, bye
Hey, when the sun blows your screams Hair comes like rain on the dream
You know I'll say, Hey, Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
and Dix. Oh, my name's Pat Walsh. I was not prepared to talk about Dix, but I can.
Fort Dix, I should have said that specifically. I'm not prepared to talk about Fort Dix. I know
nothing about it. Is it in Texas? No idea, but everything is bigger in Texas, including my Dix when I
did. That's great. That's all I got to say about that. What's new with you? What's new? Well,
that in between episodes here, I went and I peed. How'd that go? Good. And I ate three pieces
of sausages as fast as I could. That would be good. Something in my stomach. And after this, I have
to go do my friend Josh Adam Myers podcast. Yeah. And then after that, I have to go to Joey Roses,
my bar to meet a potential new employee. And then after that, the night is mine. You still do all
hiring yourself? No, I usually let the some of the guys on staff take care of it, but I do feel like
I should go meet the guy that's coming in. Okay. Okay. Yeah, I'm excited to see the store. I'm excited
to be in New York on September 11th. Always a special time to be there. We're doing our show
September 10th. Yeah. Show Z. I'm excited for all of you coming out. But yeah, I feel like I'm in
sort of a strange holding pattern. I'm waiting to hear on things, which is always stressful, but you're
always waiting. It's all the businesses is waiting. Yeah, I never, never ends. I'm waiting to hear
on stuff too. And a pilot that we shot. And yesterday, I got email. I won't get into it, but
it's incredible. All I'll say is this, the asks that you get from a network. Yeah. I mean,
you're trying to get something made that are so pointless. Yeah. And literally
this busy work stuff where it's like, yeah, but you know, we could just, you know, would help
if we just had a cutaway at minute seven to the object you're talking about. It's like,
guys, we're past, we're internal. Yeah, we're all talking internally. What is there that you
you understand what this is or you don't? Right. Who are we trying to impress? You're not
shipping this off to somebody that has no idea we're up to this to try to get their take and okay on
it. We're all in on this. Yeah. What the hell are we doing? So nuts.
I never know. You know, the beauty of this mispatch show is that when the executives offer a note,
mispatch tells them they need to get laid or should be like, oh, just shut the fuck up. Some of
us trying to get, she goes on tour with this comic who's considered like a big legendary, you know,
if Eddie Murphy was a monster type comic and she gets to open on him, open for him, excuse me,
and the third season. So she goes out on tour and learns very quickly that this guy is a monster
behind the scenes. He's abusive. He's cheating on his wife. He's a co -catic, whatever else.
So while he's talking to Pat and her sister who's a recovering crackhead, he keeps doing these
lines of coke and it's a very funny scene and they were like, we don't want to see him doing coke.
This is an unedited R -rated show. You think it's too much to actually see this guy doing coke.
And then, you know, some of this is behind the scenes stuff but, you know,
Ms. Pat will come back like, this really happened in my life. Being real is important to me. So,
fuck off. And man, who it's based on? No, I'm not saying that here, but I don't know. I'm asked,
yeah, no, she's had some experiences with people that were not kind to her, et cetera.
But the beauty of Ms. Pat is she said this during an interview the other day. So I feel fine saying it
is that the father of some of her kids knocked her up when he was in his 30s and she was like 14.
And it was very important to her. She demanded that BET take up a giant ad for the Ms. Pat show
across from his place of work. So she put a big ad up that he has to pass every day on his way and
that kind of spite always appeals to me because I have it myself.
Canis and did that with when his one of his records came out because he had such a beef with
Mitzi, sure, of the comedy store, he put the billboard across from the comedy store and advertised
this album on it. What was his beef with her? That she's fucking awful. Oh, okay. I tell you who must
I've heard very story relationship with the comedy. I've never met her. But you hear
Mick very mixed stories. Yeah, any any I will say this. I like the comedy store. I hang out of
the comedy store. I sometimes perform at the comedy store. But any club with that level of ego
and there are a lot of them out there. I'm not picking on the comedy store. That's coming from somewhere.
Sure. Yeah. You know, that's all. You know, she might have been lovely. I don't know, but go ahead.
I was just going to say somebody who must be very well liked by these stand -up houses is
jokoi because driving around every stand -up place in LA is wallpapered with ads for Easter Sunday,
starring jokoi. Easter Sun. We have officially made a movie about every holiday now. Easter Sunday,
finally, I think completes a cycle. There hadn't been an Easter movie prior, but now we've got it.
I think that completes the the infinity stones of holiday movies.
Folks, I want to talk briefly about the dating apps. I assume a lot of you are on them or at least
have been this is my first time as a 40 -year -old man getting on the apps. And what a it's just like
everything else in American history. We have something so perfect that could finally fix a lot of
loneliness and sadness in people like the internet was can make connections. You know, spark new
connections with people you'd never meet otherwise, etc. But it's ruined very, very quickly. And I got in
so far past the gold rush. I mean, Jesus Christ, I'm looking at minimum 40 % fakes, just fake profiles.
Oftentimes you'll be on a 10 -minute scroll. You'll see the same set of pictures two, three times
with different names each time. So you never know if you're talking it, you match with somebody
and you're like, oh, okay, this is a cool person and they're pretty and I like their interests, whatever.
You match with them and you're like, hey, how are you? Then it comes back like
America four years interested in trying new trade. Meet question mark and it's like, okay,
this is a fake person. About 20 % of the people don't live here. They're looking for you to pay for
them to move here from, you know, some country overseas. I don't know if they see it on 90 -day
fiance and think this is their way in or something. But I have set my filter so many times to just
people within 10 miles of me, most of the people I see are in Japan. And it'll say right there, 10 ,000
miles away. And how is anyone supposed to use this shit? I'm paying for a fucking Tinder membership.
It's a disaster. I've met with a few people and I knew two of them where it was just like, hey,
this is funny seeing you on here. Yeah, I'm single now. You want to go out? Sure. But it's just like
it sucks. It sucks. Half the women are saying, you should know exactly where and when we're meeting.
When you approach me, tell me, meet me here at this time. The other half are saying like, don't
just tell me where we're going. We have to discuss and approve. So everyone's coming at it from different
places. All the men I assume are just looking to fuck 100 % of the profiles say, but why do you assume that
because they're men? Oh, stop it. Stop going for brownie points. I'm not going for any brownie,
but I'm going for myself also. I mean, like, that's why people go to Tinder. Maybe not in. That's what it
was supposed to put. Listen, Tinder is was an act created for just that. It was supposed to be,
let's meet. Let's fuck. Let's go. And the selfish lazy pig people in this country that think
they're owed everything for nothing, have turned it into a romance. I want to meet my soulmate app
by swiping right or left. Go fuck yourselves. You deserve to die in anonymity alone. If you can't put
more effort into your fucking life than that. That's hinge. You go on hinge and it's it's some girl in
like a floor -length sundress and a bonnet who's wondering why she's single at age 56, you know,
that's for hinge. Tinder is supposed to be, you know, people in your age bracket who look like you look
or look like you like at least. And you meet up, have a couple drinks, you either make out or you don't,
but it's this, this, I don't need to fuck either by the way. I'm not a guy who like says hello and
fucks somebody. I can't, I can't really do that. I'm just looking for some sort of fun on the app.
And it's, it's as much of a chore as anything else in life. You're a, you're, listen, I say this with
love, but I say it's criticism. You're a damn glutton for punishment. I told you to not go on that app.
You asked me about it several times. I told you repeatedly, it's going to annoy the shit out of you.
Don't do it. You meet enough people in real life and you do. No, why are you giving yourself the extra
headache? It's like going on Twitter and being mad about it. It's like because I had, I had never
done it. I do have a problem with a cold approach or a cold ask out. And I thought that this would work
for me. But even the initial thing when you match, it's like, I looked at some girls profiling the other
days. She was like, don't come sliding into my DMs with high. I live here. How are you? How's your
summer? I'm like, what do you want me to do? You don't want to photograph of my dick. You don't want
me to slide in and say, hi, how are you? Isn't this a great period of time we're going through?
I mean, it's just what you want. There's no good answer. And what it really is is I'm not your exact
dream, which is why you what you think you're going to find on these apps. So you're discussed it with
everybody. But God, the attitude you receive, usually the first time a girl messages me where she's
actually revealing her personality, I just do an unmatched. I'm like, are you fucking kidding me?
Then there'll be there'll be women on there. And look, I'm not a 10 myself, okay? But there are
women on there who should know that they're not maybe going to get the pick of the litter. This goes
for men too, but all I see is women. And they will write on this thing. Do not all caps speak to me if
you are not minimum six foot two. You know, it's all this shit. It's like, what are you doing?
It's actually what are you doing? It's a beautiful thing that you're using in the wrong way.
Let it eat itself. Let it destroy itself. This is yet another tool gifted to us by the devil himself
to allow us to destroy ourselves. Enjoy. It's right there with Twitter. It's right there with
Venmo. All right. It's right there with the Amazon wish list that you make public. It's right
there with everything. I got an email today from Bank of America telling me I needed to upgrade
my Apple operating system because for security purposes. This is where we're at people.
This is where we're at the same thing. And I'm like, why would I listen to you? The major banks are
in cahoots with the device that is running your life. It's over. You are owned. You have no
chance. So get out of it. You can. And there are people that want to accelerate this process by stepping
on the gas pedal. And those people are the people that are using Tinder in that sense and putting
don't talk to me of XYZ. These are the people that live on Twitter all day long.
God bless. If you're looking for a hookup, do not DM me. That's most profile. It's like somebody
in mind is like, they'll say it, but you can still fuck them. And then I'll be. And that's true too. But
it's like, how dare you? Like you're on the app for hookups. At least be open to the possibility.
Why do you hate fun this much? Where are we going into human sexuality? Like it's a miserable
thing. We both have to turn a key at the exact same time. And it's just I talked about this on my
hour special that you missed the taping of a few years back for a lot of eventually, for comedy central.
And as usual, I was on the exact right side of history. And here we are. This is what it is. It's
what were you talking about there? Tinder. I said all of these things in the bit about like, you're
on the app to fuck. That's what it's there for. Right. And if you're on there swiping left going
or right, whatever one is saying, why haven't I met my Prince Charming? You deserve to fucking die alone.
You do put some effort into your life, spend $30 on a real dating app. But people can't even be
bothered with that because everything's owed to them. Yeah. Go read, go read YouTube content,
comments for an hour and see where the fucking average mentality and ego of the average person
in this fucking country is. I mean, it's disgraceful. It's disgraceful. But again, you can choose to
partake in that or you can choose to step back and say, guys, I tossed the hand grenade into the room.
You can all fight over it. I'll be over here in the other room where there's cake. I have chosen to go
to the cake room. I'm not doing it. I'm not doing it. I mean, I had to try. I had to try. You got
to see it for yourself. Now you've seen it. You know, I'm doing hinge and Tinder. They want me on
Raya, the friends are on Raya, which is like the entertainment industry one. And it's like, why do I
want to then go out with people that I might encounter in my day to day life? You know, you never know.
Maybe you get a hot date with Jonathan Silverman. Yeah, friend of mine average looking guy keeps going
out with like known celebrities, like big actresses off of Raya, just for that, just to see if I can
get a Rebecca DeMorne. Yeah, like a childhood fantasy. Sure. Somebody on the tail. Oh, somebody on
the back to distract myself all day lately. And it helps in that regard. But in terms of actually
meeting up with people and having a good time, that has not been on the menu at all.
Well, and then you know, they'll do things like, okay, first picture. Wow, this is a and look, I'm not
all about looks. I have other interests. But it's like, okay, this is a attractive looking woman.
Second picture, by the time you're at the sixth part picture, it's a different human being. 12 years
have passed. So you're like, why are you putting out this picture from, you know, 2004 as your
kickoff? Are you lying? Because I have to meet you then and be disappointed. And it shouldn't have
to be this way. Why you shouldn't do it here. And I understand that you had to try it. And I'm not
free. I'm not I'm not man -splaining if you will. But the there's an inherent thing in us that makes
us think that people will have some sort of dignity to not apply certain tactics to a certain
aspect of their lives. And it's not true. Yeah. People apply real estate tactics to their dating profile.
Yeah, I think they think you better see the house swept away by their personality that you'll
forget they look nothing like their photo. And it's like, no, your personality sucks dick too.
Well, and also to shit. And also to to take the sympathetic or empathetic route. It's very sad
that people are this desperate that they're swindling one another into an attempt at romance. It's
very sad. Speaking of which. And this is the way you like coffee and wine. These aren't things to
lead with. Everyone likes coffee and wine. If your personality is don't talk to me till I've had my
coffee or if it's night time, my wine. All these that should be its own app. People who love coffee and
wine cannot fuck each other for the rest of eternity. But leave us fun people alone.
Well, maybe get on a plane, but take a trip or something.
Well, a vacation from ourselves. Yeah. I'm going out of town. Well, speaking of romance,
this is a news cycle. Well, so I think you'll appreciate. So Alec Baldwin is saying that he was
fired from another job because of the rust incident. Yeah. His quote is, I've been talking with these
guys for months and they told me yesterday, we don't want to film this with you because of this.
I guarantee you that is not what was said to him. That is way too much of a risk for them to say
that to him directly. But I can't find the article. He went on record somewhere saying that if it wasn't
for his wife, the fucking wing nut that she is. He wouldn't be in the entertainment industry anymore
after all of this. He'd he'd have moved to the Midwest and started selling real estate. Don't you
love how he is now? Alec, you need this. You swine. You need the attention. Shut the fuck up.
I'd be in the Midwest for what a week tops. You wouldn't fucking idiot. He is a fucking idiot.
He's so full of shit. And the way that he has turned this whole thing into the plight of himself,
he's now saying also, or he has said, excuse me, ever since Trump said I might have killed her on
purpose, I feared for my life, it's like, hey Alec, do I think that's a fucked up thing to say? 100 %
Do I also think you brought it on yourself by going on national television weekly and calling
this guy every fucking thing you can think to call him? You fucking junk it. Trump to strike back
at some point. I mean, that's all he does. Ooh, the snake bit me. Yeah. Well, that's what snakes do.
What are you doing? Oh, I was choking it for four years. But then out of the blue,
it bit me. Shut the fuck up. Alec Baldwin. He's an idiot. But maybe this will put a smile on your face.
I'd love to sell a ranch -style homes in St. Charles, Missouri. That's what I'd like to do. If this wife
didn't keep making the babies, I would be working at a tasty freeze. He's such an idiot. He's such an
idiot. God, that's a fucking idiot. I go home for four days every year at Christmas and I want to
stick a gun in my mouth. You think you're going to live in Missouri, Alec? You think they got,
you know, $400 dinner delivery at one in the morning when you decide you want your top of the line,
caviar, whatever the fuck you want. You have fucking spoiled pizza shit.
You'll like this bit I was doing all weekend in Atlantic City.
Tell me what I like. Well, it's got to do with alcohol. I opened every show by saying
good to be here in Atlantic City, the Steven Baldwin of gambling cities. I thought it was a very good
one -liner. Good, yeah. And it was a very late -night style one -liner before I then went into an hour,
my new hour of comedy that ends with, well, I can't tell you how it ends. I don't want to spoil it,
but let me just say that it's being described as hopeless. Yeah, that's how I would describe it,
I saw. No, you have not. Oh, well, no, it got darker. You did see it anyway, but it's gotten darker.
It's gotten even darker. Anyway, maybe this will live. Is Steven Baldwin the lowest of the
Baldwin's? I chose Steven because to me, he feels like the Atlantic City of the Baldwin's.
You're well, see, I mean, I mean, I'm not questioning the line. I think it's a very funny line,
but I'm wondering if Daniel Baldwin might not be the... He's 100%. Daniel Baldwin's 100 % the lowest.
Steven is the second highest. Steven is above William. William was in back draft though,
right? Or is that Steven? Nobody remembers William. Steven still stays in the mix. Yeah, that's true.
Who's the the the the Trump supporter? Steven. And Steven's also got a daughter that acts in a lot of
stuff and is like popular. So he's still kind of in the mix. Okay, he needs her. Yeah, so I mean,
I got to say, guy seems happy as hell. Every time I see him, it's something smiling. He's having a
good time. Like God bless. All right. Feel good. Maybe this one. Why is Haley Bieber? Is she related to
Steven Baldwin? I think that's his daughter or something. Oh, interesting. So he's doing great. He
probably hitting up her for money. I don't know. Maybe this will lift our spirits. This is the fourth
time I've said it. Go ahead. I resist my spirits being lifted. That's why I keep cutting you off.
New Rex Reed, baby. Fresh off the presses on the observer. We're out in that fresh. It was from August
4th. Ready for this headline? What's the film? It says it in the headline. Okay, of the review.
Bullet Train might be the worst movie ever made.
I'll be discussing Bullet Train in today's movie corner. I think that's a crazy thing to say,
but I get why he's at the point where he's willing to call it the worst movie.
Well, let me read you some of this and then we'll move on to your review. Please. Bullet Train features
the worst assemblage of bad acting ever collected in a single film. There is also a poisonous snake.
Wow. Doesn't we know that you can't say everything is the worst ever or your words don't really
have any meaning? God bless him. He gave it zero stars. Okay. That's the first. I haven't seen him give
him zero yet. Okay. Just when you think you've seen the worst movie ever made,
along comes a pile of toxic waste called bullet train. It's an action thriller about an army of
incomprehensible assassins. I'll try to kill each other on the famous arrow, aerodynamic marvel that
travels three or 20 miles from Osaka to Tokyo in just a few hours. I can cost $90 billion to build
and charges $132 for a one -way ticket during the course of the interminimal or interminimal
Jesus Christ. Wow. Sorry. During the course of an interminimal and unimpeachably excruciating two
hours and six minutes. Yeah. This abomination of a movie not only kills off almost every on -board
everyone on board, but demolishes two of the world's most miraculous trains as well. So he's giving
a vulgar, vile, violent, and vomethis. The end of the line is just the beginning is the kicker
for the ads. Let's hope that's not a deadly promise for a series of unwanted sequel.
Brad Pitt of all people trashes his talent and diminishes his usual reliability as some kind of secret
agent hitman called Ladybug. So far he's on point here. He's pretty on point. I mean, I thought Brad Pitt
was doing what he could. I mean, he's basically playing Deadpool. It's the guy who did the Deadpool's
and it's that vibe. He goes into the plot here, which I'll skip. Thank you. But I'll read some of
the character names. White death played by Michael Shannon, who I've lost all respect for at this
point. Yeah. He must have gotten divorced or something. I mean, he's in this thing for four minutes.
He's clearly bored out of his mind. It's a wild performance. He's going to become our walkin'.
You know, he's just somehow just giving up on being one of the great actors and just taking paychecks.
God, this cast is terrible. The wolf played by bad bunny. You know how we all wanted to see bad bunny
in a movie, right? Oh, yeah. Well, you know, I had never heard a bad bunny song to my knowledge. He's fine.
He barely speaks in the movie, but he's got a look. He's got a charm. Rex Reed says it's not advertised
as a comedy, but full of training is so demented, misguided, and abstruse. What is that word?
Maybe a mix of abstract and obtuse? I guess. That you find yourself laughing at it in spite of
yourself. Did I forget to mention there's also a poison, a snake on board slithering beneath his
seats and waiting to strike? You mentioned it. His new lips, machine gun stabbed, poisoned,
and finally bitten by the reptile. Rad pit emerges with nothing more than a bandaid.
Vanchilotli expressing he's glad he had his morning dose of snake venom and he
I mean, look, Reed at this point is not paying attention really to the movie. He's saying some
things that are just plainly untrue. I have no no desire to defend bullet train, but he's he's wrong.
The movie is a comedy. The movie is not an accidental comedy because it's so stupid.
It's more of a comedy than even snakes on a plane was. It's designed to be
in the style of like a guy, Richie, it's Brad Pitt back in kind of snatch mode.
It's, what was that pole, Gianmari?
It's that's one of it. Yeah, shoot him up. This last paragraph is magical in my opinion, all right.
Here he goes. He brings it on. And an earlier sub mental abhorrence this year called the lawsuit.
Again, an average movie. God. Brad Pitt made a cameo walk on to boost the box office intake
for his pal Sandra Bullock and Channing Tatum. In bullet train, they return the favor.
They should all be forced to burn their membership cards in the screen actor's guild.
Nothing happens. It is true. It's it's such nonsense. Nothing happens worth writing home about
except some of the irrelevant special effects. The director is stuntman David Lecht,
or leaked, how you say it, who brings the assignment, zero knowledge of form, craft, or discipline.
The script by Zach Oakwitz is boring, witless, and in an inbacillic.
No character is developed seriously or deeply enough to reach more than the most superficial
surface identity. That includes the star. You could call it an actual performance, but Brad Pitt makes
the dumbest appearance of his career. Call it a celebrity sighting. Wow. Come on, Rex. I feel like
Rex needs to get a dick suck. Jesus Christ. I feel like he is. I feel like he's in an apartment where
he is like fur covers on his base for radiators. Rotation of twinks that come by. Yeah, there's a guy
on deck just to make martinis 24 hours a day. He doesn't even do a bare minimum of research.
David Lecht made his directorial debut with John Wick. He has some action credibility.
He directed Atomic Blonde, which is an awesome and very well put together action film.
Deadpool 2, which is hilarious, proves he's adept at comedy as well. And then he did Hobbes and
Shaw, which suck. But look, as far as these action directors go, that's a really, really strong resume.
Bullet Train just kind of sucks. You know, it's overstuffed. By the time you get to a Channing
Tatum cameo and a Sandra Bullock cameo, it's right. You're watching friends hang out and
pay each other back for favors, like it's cannonball run two. And that starts to feel a little cheap,
especially because Channing Tatum's entire character is a guy who thinks Brad Pitt is hitting on him.
So he keeps saying like, ooh, I love being on the bottom and stuff like that. And it's like,
aren't we past this? Just jokes about a macho guy being gay? Aren't we beyond this?
But Michael Channing is ludicrous in it. Brad Pitt is in guy -richy light mode.
The script is a mess. There are some decent action sequences, some decent fights.
You really feel that two hour, six minute length. But Reed is being way too harsh. Bullet Train is not a
movie I'd recommend to anybody, but it's not the worst movie ever made. And it's far from Brad Pitt's
worst performance. All right, fair enough. Excuse me. I don't have anything for the movie
corner this week, but I had a new psycho. And I had the Rex Reed, which took the place in my movie
corner. And I'll end with a quick scary stuff, but it's a monumental moment as far as I'm concerned.
I almost think it's a book. I almost think we could do an episode about the book reviewing it after
after we we both read it, but Heat 2 finally came out. Yeah, I have it, but like a lot of books,
it'll probably sit unread for a year, two years. I've been reading it. And all I'll say is it is
awesome. It delivers on all fronts. It feels exactly like a sequel to heat. Yeah, it moves exactly
like a sequel to heat. And the moment where the cat, when the characters first give you exactly what
you want from the characters, it's you hear it in your head. It's awesome. It's just awesome.
There are, you know, Pacino's first, or Hannah, who Pacino plays the movie. Vincent
Hannah's first big scene in the book, like, you know, there's some smaller stuff with him, but his first
big scene is him interrogating somebody. And he starts doing, he, you know, halfway through the scene,
he's like, you know, I'm paraphrasing, but he's like, great. Yeah, he's like, he's like,
does that ring a bell and the guy that he's interrogating goes, bell, and he's like, bell, ding, dong,
you fuck, ding, you know what I mean, like, and you're like, this is fucking awesome. Like,
this is like exactly heat, the Nero's character, Neil. When you first meet him, he's like setting up
a job, and he's talking to a guy that's going to supply them a truck, because it's a prequel on a
sequel. He's talking to a guy that's going to supply them a truck and the guy's like, what do you
need the truck for? And the character's like, what do I need the truck for? You do not ask me any
fucking questions. I tell you what the fuck I, and you're just hearing it in your head. You're like,
this is it. This is heat. These are the characters. This, the story's awesome. It works very well as a
prequel in a sequel. Uh, it reads fast. I'm loving it, man. I'm loving it. And the fact, again,
that it's called heat, too, is insane. Very excited to check it out. Does it focus mostly on
Kilmer, as I've heard? Uh, it, uh, well, I mean, the sequel story is about Vincent Hanna and what's
left of his team hunting down Kilmer's character? Okay. Um, but I wouldn't say
I don't know that I would say it focuses on Kilmer. It's, it's that character is obviously
prominently featured. Could they make it a movie? How old is Pacino's character in this book?
It's the day after. Oh, so no. No, I mean, because the budget would be too big, then you'd have to
lead the age everybody and blah, blah, blah. I mean, the bigger issue you have is Kilmer,
it's sad, but he looks like a different person now. Of course. Even with the aging, it wouldn't work,
but, but, uh, but the, and then the prequel takes place, I think, five years before the movie.
Okay. So it's the prequel story. You'd have to get new people. Yeah. It's like Neil and his crew
going like hard, but Hanna, Pacino's character and Kilmer's characters are in both the prequel and
the sequel story. Right. Okay. Uh, it's great. It's great. It's a great, great book. I cannot wait to
read it. I watched Watcher, which is new to you can buy it on Amazon for pretty cheap. This was
just in theaters. It stars Micah Monroe and Carl Glouceman, who was sort of new to me.
Burn Gorman thought that was a fake name, but I recognize that guy from a million things.
Movies plot is a serial killer stalks the city. And at the same time, a young woman notices a
mysterious stranger watching her from across the street. Uh, it's solid. It's a very
slow burn. There's not a lot of suspense, not a lot of scares. This was another very well -reviewed,
horror movie. It's by Chloe Okuno, who did a segment in VHS 94, which I thought was hitting
Miss like all the VHS's. But, um, yeah, I don't know. As a guy who's trying to get a movie set up
that is about a guy watching a young couple in a house, I felt like, why did this get made?
The most generic possible version of this story, while mine is facing a pill battle every step of the
way. That's an unfair criteria to judge a movie on, but that's how I judged it. It's very, very
paint by numbers generic. And, you know, it will be on shutter or a streamer soon. It's an okay
90 -minute thriller, you know, but, um, the raves, you can just go ahead and ignore. It's not some great movie.
All right. Watch her. You got, you got three in a row. I don't have any.
All right. For my final, for my final, I'm going to shout out a picture called
Titane. A movie I had already talked about on here. I recommend it to Joe. He won't watch it.
It's everywhere. You fucking bitch. You bitch.
I want to watch Hulu. Um, it, especially on a second viewing, it was my favorite movie of its year,
which I guess was last year. It's just a movie that's alive in a way. Movies aren't anymore.
The first half feels almost like a brine to palm a horror picture. The second half
gets into some very sort of deeper and strange territory. It seems to be a movie about trans rights.
Honestly, even though it never mentions that, that's just something that became clearer to me on
this viewing are about the life of a trans person. Um, but even if you just look at it as a movie
about a woman who fucks cars and develops strange powers, you know, it's, it's awesome. I love
the way it's shot. I love the soundtrack. Uh, there, there's weird, memorable, violent, crazy
shit in it. And I wish every movie could be like Titane. Check it out. Hold on one second,
Walsh. Sure. We've got a little camera issue here. I'm back and that's the magic of recording.
Quick pause in and out. Oh boy. So that comes where we're at the movie of the day, correct?
We are, yes, at the movie of the day, orphan, colon, first kill. Now, the first question out of the
when the first thing they do, after you meet Esther in the, insane, or whatever the fuck the
thing that she's in, yeah, utility, they tell you she's already killed a bunch of people.
Yeah, I was called first kill. Joe, I don't know. Um, this is another one that people are
raving about, you know, and I'm like, what, what is going on? Like when everybody's raving about
a comedy, I'm like, okay, they want a job. This I don't get and I looked up what's going on in terms
of rotten tomatoes. This has a much better rating than the original orphan, which to me is a diamond
in the rough. I was blown away by the first orphan, a rare twist that absolutely works that holds
up rate performances from for mega and scars guard. Uh, they just elevated a great B movie to an A.
I think orphan is fun, scary. I revisited every couple of years. This movie is worse in every way.
Well, let me just say real quick before we move on. I disagree. I think I've always thought orphan
was a passable horror film at best. I own it. It's solid enough. I thought the twist was laughable.
Like when I, the twist and when I saw it in the theater, the twist got a laugh because it was like
everybody was like, oh, give me a break. But in hindsight, I'm like, it's kind of out of discomfort
and appreciation, in my opinion. Well, that could be, that could be true. My biggest issue with
the first orphan though is, and this is going to apply to this review. The a twist ending that wild
and that campy and that whatever you want to call it did not line up with the tone of the rest
of the movie for me. The rest of the movie felt demonic and sinister and dark and upsetting and all
these things. And then this wild twist came in that was a drive in movie fodder. And it didn't,
that to me was the disconnect. So that, that's all I'll say about the first one. Go ahead. I'm sorry,
the interviewer. No, that, I mean, my take on it is different. Of course, I consider orphan to be,
you know, when you say best that, you know, comedy and horror are not always genres where best means
what it does in terms of drama. I just mean one of the most purely entertaining horror flicks that I've
seen in recent years. And to compare this to that and to have it emerge as a much better reviewed
movie, it really has me just throwing my hands up in terms of of where we're at critically. I've
always said Rod tomatoes is not to be trusted. But who thinks the second one's better than the first
one? Are you going to surprise me here, Joe and say you loved orphan first kill? Excuse me. No,
I'm not going to say I loved it. I will say that I think, well, orphan first kill is a lot like,
let me start with the positives. When we first heard they were making this movie, we were like,
what are you talking about? How are you going to make a movie with the same actor playing Esther
that doesn't have D aging and CGI technology. That's insane. This doesn't make any sense. Right. When I
saw it, I very much admired how they did it. I was like, they're doing like Hitchcockian
in camera stuff to make this work. And I thought that that was really cool and very refreshing to see in
this day and age and cinema. So that I actually liked I actually did buy that she was the kid after a
while, but you know, you do have to kind of go through that little like like the Irishman like grace
period, where for a minute you're like, this looks weird and then all of a sudden to get used to and it's
fine. So, so I want to lead with those positives. Do I like it better than the original orphan? No.
I thought the acting in the original orphan was better. And I always think it's better if you have a
child that a child is playing the child. I also thought that orphan was doubly disturbing
because of how convincing she was as an actual child in that film at being like a psychopath.
Also, the scene where she like tries to fuck Peter Sars guard, I remember I looked up
how old she was after I saw it in the movies. I was like, that was like,
the way she like breathes in his ear, I remember the everybody in the theater was like, oh my god,
you know, so there were moments in the original movie and there were aspects of it that I think
certainly solidified it a little more as a work of a certain level of, I don't know, art,
whenever you want to call it. It was better directed, you know, blah, blah, blah. But
this sequel I think as a whole, I can't even say that with any, like I said, my biggest issue with
the first movie was I didn't think the ending and the tone of something like that matched the rest
of the movie. This one, I feel like tonally, it's more even because they're steering so hard into
being self -effacing and being, they tried to make a drive in movie with this. That's what this is.
So tonally, this is a little more even for me, I guess. But I did appreciate the sort of Texas
chainsaw massacre two aspect of this. I liked it. They were like, we're just having fun here.
We're being absurd. We're from the jump. You know her secret. So we're just going to have fun with it.
But then like I'm looking here, Jezebel, so take that with a grain of salt. But the headline here is
orphan first kill. Out does its predecessor with the deliciously trashy twist. And you read and it says,
this movie manages a twist so delicious. It even out does the first one. And it's like, no, it doesn't.
No, it doesn't. Like one is a truly innovative twist that I hadn't seen before. And this movie's twist
is generic. I had to kind of look up what it even was. It's like, what are they considering the big
twist? I don't know. I just, I feel, well, the twist, the twist in this one is in the middle.
Yeah. Yeah. And it's just not that, I don't know, it didn't do much for me. I did, I did think as I was
watching it until you hit that first, only twist. And the twist in this one is that the family is
actually evil. Right. And they're going to give her a run for her money. Right.
Leading up into that reveal, I was like, something's going on here. This family is going to be evil.
There's some secret. They're all acting way to without with with such little emotion to this daughter's
return. There's something odd is going on here. Like, and then sure enough, when the twist comes,
you find out the brother who's an asshole killed the sister. So Esther, sorry, we didn't establish.
Esther poses as a woman or sorry, a little girl who's been missing for four years. Yeah, to an
American family. And that's the, the, the reason you buy it is because she looks enough like
the girl that's missing if that girl had aged four more years. Right. And Julia Styles plays the mom
and the family and she goes to get her. And then when she brings her home, the only one happy to see
the daughter is the dad. So you start to go like, what's going on here? Why is Julia Styles not a
moding or anything? And then I started to go, wait a minute, there's going to be a twist where the
family is fucked up. And then sure enough, that's the twist. The brother killed the daughter. She's
not missing. Julia Styles knows something is up that this girl is that that an imposter is posing as
the daughter. And she knows that by allowing this charade to happen, she will somehow rekindle the love
in her marriage that's been gone since they lost the daughter. It's a hard sell or it's a stretch of a
sell. I'm willing to go with it. You know, it's like we talked about with X where it's like,
oh, how convenient the people making the porn or movie ended up on a farm where people have a sex
issue and are super crit when you're right. You're going to have to make some jumps. But it wasn't such,
such a leap that I wouldn't go along with it. And TV writing used to have a guy that would say,
I'm going to use the buy it phone. And he would place a call and like, do we buy it and then
pretend to get an answer from somebody. I feel like a movie gets one of those big swings. Sure. And look,
you know, I didn't have an issue with that aspect of it. I just sat my pulse exactly the same for
90 minutes. Sure. I thought it lacked the thrills, the cheese, the fun. This like we're just going to
have fun to make it a drive -in movie that you're describing. I didn't have that experience. I am
starting to wonder lately if it's just my general mood is is keeping me from enjoying things.
Or if it's just things are bad. And maybe it's both. But I just felt this movie was lacking a pop,
lacking a pulse. I don't know what to tell you. Well, I thought Julia's style sucked. I never
like her. I don't know why. It wasn't for me. She's not great. She's okay. Yeah.
You know, that guy who I had never seen before is the son of Donald Sutherland.
Yeah, so I did know that. And I guess the brother of Kiefer. He's kind of,
he's, I like him, but he's, he's a weird, I didn't buy him as a dad. No. He's too, there's
something about him that's too like Brooklyn. You know, he comes off like a, like a, like a, like a,
like a, like a little bit of an older hipster from Brooklyn, his demeanor or something like that.
I wasn't buying him as a dad. I bought Julia's styles enough as a mom. But look, a lot of
what this movie lacks is the fact that now when you see Esther go, go fuck yourself, whatever,
to the brother, you're like, why no, she's 40. So who cares? Yeah. I mean, those, my, my initial
thinking of why the sequel wouldn't work is a big part of why it didn't work. If you know
that twist going in, you're, you're dealing with a very strange premise of just a grown woman
pretending to be a girl. And it just, I don't know, it didn't add up. I guess there's only so many ways
you could do it. This is one, I'm not saying it was nonsense. You know, I think that they,
they pulled off the assignment of give us a sequel to orphan that isn't completely ludicrous.
Fine. I just, to me, it was missing that pop in a big way that orphan had. It's all I can say.
Did you, did I, I was laughing at points where I wasn't sure why I was laughing? But like,
halfway through this thing, when the, when the reveal comes out that Julia styles, let's,
let's ester in on the secret. And then it's like, and I know that you're an imposter too.
So we're going to work together and you're going to make my marriage better and all this stuff.
It turns into like this like she deviled kind of, it becomes like comedic works. These two women
like warring. Yeah. Against one another. I, I thought that was an odd choice. But again, I kind of
felt like they were just trying to have fun with it. Maybe. Yeah. Also, what's going on with why is
this movie in a couple of theaters, but also Paramount Plus? What are the rules anymore?
What do you mean? Like, what, why is this movie on Paramount Plus, but also in some theaters? Why are
some movies only streaming and some not? Why is prey only on Hulu? But you know, how do they decide
this? Because the, because the studios are, the studios try to decide with each project what
will make them the most money because they're still being run by fucking idiot morons. Yeah.
They try to strategize, you know, how business will work and they misfire all the time. You know,
it's like, I get it guys. Somebody needs to be the business mind. Somebody needs to be the money.
I get it. I, I don't know how to do that in this field of distribution and all that stuff.
But they're making, these mistakes they're making with what goes the streaming, what, you know,
these modern day mistakes, they're, they're not new mistakes. They're just new versions of the same
mistakes. This is the same stupid. This is like back in the day when you go, why did they bury this movie?
This is a great movie. Like, why didn't they give it a proper ad campaign? Why did they sell this one
as a comedy? When it's not a comedy, you know, so I mean, this did not deserve to be in theaters.
I don't think it doesn't have any box office draw whatsoever. I know very few people who were clamoring
for an orphan's sequel, except for the day like it would have been a directed to DVD in the old
day. Yeah. And by those standards, I will say it's successful. But, you know, as a sequel to a movie,
I really admired now. The, what was I going to say? By the way, the actress that plays Hester Hatchimachi.
I watched some interviews with her in real life. I was like, dear Lord, you're able to be attracted to
the orphan after all you've been through. She is gorgeous. How old is the orphan? She's like 27 or
something. Okay. So on the interview with her, she got blonde hair. Wow, she's smoking.
Not for me. I don't know. I just, it's just, it's just not a, I didn't hate it. I enjoyed it more than
I thought I would. You know, and look, I'll say this in closing. Guys, you pulled it off. You got decent
reviews. The movie was a moderate success. You tried to do the unthinkable, unthinkable and impossible
with bringing the actor back and all that stuff. And you did it. You did it. You did it.
Shut the fuck up now about where Esther goes next. There's nothing else to do here. Don't, they'll do this.
They will. They're already talking about it. They're already talking about it. And this is the
fucking mistake. And listen, I love, I love Michael show Walter. I love David Wayne. And I thank them
greatly for the opportunity that they gave me with wet hot American summer. But I said through that
whole fucking process. You did it. This is it. Like when that came out and it worked. Yeah. I said to
myself, you did it boys. Don't go back to the well. This was impossible. And you did it. And of course,
now let's do another season now. And now Bradley Cooper can't be here and we'll make it Michael
Scott. And now it's, and it's just guys. Wait, when did they do another season of it? They did two seasons
of that show. No. Yes, they did. No. And who's Michael, you're talking about Steve Carell?
Wet hot American summer. They did two seasons. In the second season, Bradley Cooper wasn't there.
And he was replaced by Michael, or I'm sorry, Adam Scott, excuse me.
I said, Michael, first, first day of camp and 10 years later, these are two different, two different
projects. Yes. The first, the first, the second one is so fucking forgettable. Oh yeah, I'm not
trying to knock these guys, but it's like, you did it. Leave it. Leave it alone. Oh yeah. Okay.
So do that with this. You did it. Leave it alone. What you're going to have this fucking broad
going to another family and murder them again and protect you as a kid again. Like you got everything.
So that's anyway, my hog is about straight out for orphan first kill. And mine is down. My hog is
way up for the original orphan. And maybe I went in with too high of expectations, but I didn't have
laughs or thrills or anything with with the new orphan. We will be back finally doing everything
everywhere all at once, which I have seen a Joe is not. And we will do something else coming down
the pike. Some point. I am on Twitter and Instagram, the Patrick Walsh. We're doing two live shows
in NYC, which will be released 10th or 10th. Yeah, they'll be released on Patreon, audio or only,
obviously. And we don't know what we're doing for those yet, but we'll try to do something
relevant to, right? Yeah. Sure. Yeah. Maybe Jason takes Manhattan. We'll be there. I feel like
we've talked right at the 13th. The death. But that's a shame. That's a fucking shame. That would have
been a, that would have been fun. That would be good. Thank you all for listening. Thank you,
Emily, for your help. Thank you to all Patreon supporters. We love you, Joe. I got nothing, Pat. I
love you. And I thank all of you. We'll see you next time, folks. And we'll see you in hell.