I'm here for Bet Rivers online casino and sportsbook with poker icon Phil Helmuth.
And now thanks to the excitement of Bet Rivers, I'm also a slots icon.
That's great! And a same -game parlay icon. Cool, cool. A blackjack icon,
a money -line icon, a roulette. Take it from Phil Helmuth. If you love games,
Bet Rivers is the place to play in Bet. Bet Rivers. Games on.
Must be 21 plus in present in West Virginia. Void were prohibited. Terms in conditions apply.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another, no other sportsbook has
an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning, or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
winning hits different here must be 21 plus gambling problem called winning 100
gambler offer not available in all states terms apply see fanatic sports book
app
this is a head gum podcast
Hello everybody and welcome to season four episode four on our new home head gum.
This is Will see you in hell.
My name is Patrick Wall, show the Missouri Walsh's and now on with the show and on with
the Joe.
Oh
Pat how are you Pat? I'm fine spirited intro from you tonight walked over here got my got my exercise two three miles
Nice it's a beautiful evening here in Los Angeles. Didn't even have to remove my jacket. It is
It's crisp. Yes. It is a gorgeous meaning that cold air hits you like biting into an apple
It's like the full of York peppermint patties. Yeah with that hot sun behind it. It's like it's like a it's like a woman's sweaty body as their cool lips
hit your forehead. You know what I mean? She places an ice cube on your smoldering
taint, right? You get that mix of hot and cold on your taint. You may know how you
make love. You made it dirty. I was doing a kissing forehead because I was picturing
an ant. Welcome back to you made it dirty with your host, Pat Walsh, Joderos. This is
we'll see you in hell. Our movie this week is The Neon Demon.
As promised.
And I want to give you a little heads up for next week because this is one of the rare
occurrences we know what we're doing next week.
We've heard you loud and clear you want to go back to some classic horror titles and we
start this week with John Carpenter's classic question mark, Christine Stephen King's, it was
very ballsy that the credits, well we'll talk about it next week, but it's John Carpenter's
Christine. All of us moving. Stephen King gets a shout out. All of those, all of his movie.
Oh, I see what you mean. Save it. Save it. Save it. Another guy who does that, Nicholas
Winding Reffen, who directed the movie that we are going to discuss tonight. It says Nicholas
Winding Riffens, Neon Demon. It says Nicholas Winding Reffen presents. Oh, God. All right.
Let's, and let's save this till the, till the meat. Because I'm, I'm going to dig into
this guy like like a like a all you can eat shrimp buffet tonight. So you mean carefully
because you don't want to get them shells or them turds. Let's get into let's get into
to your movie corner pet. What movies have you seen? The rundown as we call it. We don't
really catch up with each other anymore. It's just there's no four play at all. It's just
just a raw ram.
I can't remember what at this point,
what's been talked about on this show,
what hasn't been.
We usually talk about our week or our day.
How was your day?
I'd like to talk to you about the elephant in the room,
or should I say the dog in the room.
I heard, Joe, that you purchased a second dog.
Is this true?
I did.
Walk us through it.
It seems like you can't handle one.
I adopted a second dog because I want a con man here
to have a friend, a partner, and I had the dog for three days, and I said, fuck this,
and brought him back to the no kill adoption shelter, where he was safe and sound, but
he was just too wired. He was too crazy. He was like, you should probably not have kids,
Joe.
Well, I swear to you all I thought the whole time was, my God, what happens if you have a
kid and this is your reaction? You can't take them back.
You can't take them back.
So I'm never having kids.
I made an appointment to get the SNP done.
You go on, got to get the cigarettes and never come back.
You know, I get it now.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I never didn't get it.
My dad used to leave for hours at a time for like rage drives.
I apologize to any listeners out there whose dads went out to get the milk and never came
home.
But I mean, man, do I get it?
I mean, I just, I don't, I don't understand like, I just felt so trapped.
And this is a dog I just adopted and was allowed to they were you know the policy is always bring them back
If it's not going to work and I and I did it wasn't going to work did it get along with comp
Conn wasn't too hot on him. Sure. I would grab them when he came near him and I
Just could tell con kind of cons kind of his own man and sure we we we're gonna live here together and sin
And not you know we don't need to bring another dog into it. Yeah
I mean, the lady wants a second cat,
and I'm just like, we struck gold with this fucking cat.
It's quiet, respectful, it hasn't scratched anything.
I was really worried about, you know,
we got new furniture recently and shit,
I was worried about it.
It's just been the most chill, perfect cat.
They'll sleep at the foot of the bed and not bother you.
Right.
You get that second one in there.
It's a wild car and you don't know what's coming in.
And if they hate each other, you're really fucked.
Well, that was the thing, man, was...
No, no, judgment, I understand.
That was the thing was, you know, when I got this other dog in here and saw him bouncing off the walls
I was like, oh, I just kind of got lucky with my other dog. Yeah, I mean, because caught me and not even that lucky, frankly
Come on dog shot on the floor and you know season premiere. Well, it was in all fairness. It was oh, no, it wasn't
I was gonna say that's the episode we got in the fight deleted. Oh, it was pride. Uh, he had just come home
He was a little shaken up, but he uh, but you know how bark when you come to the door
But once you're in, it's fine. Look at him. He sits there. He doesn't bother anybody. That's true. He doesn't even like
He doesn't like going to the dog park. He doesn't want to hang out with other dogs
He just wants to lay on the couch and chew on that thing. I mean God bless him. Fair enough
Would it so that was my week more or less just more realizations about how I'll never be able to commit sure
I'll die alone in this apartment to some sort of animal eating my face. Yeah
What else happened? I
I, uh, no bought some records.
That's about it.
Oh, and I'm playing Super Mario World on Super Nintendo.
I bought a Super Nintendo.
On Super Nintendo.
Okay, I think I'm, well, I was known, I played Mario Kart.
I'm playing Super Mario World and it, the obscenities,
it is pulling out of my pattern.
I mean, it is so fucking hard.
Is it one of those, you know, get the mushrooms
in each world or get the stars in each world or what?
It's, it's typical Super Mario brothers.
Yeah, you go from point A to point B and you get the mushrooms and you grow and you get the feather and you fly in the fire ball flower
And all that stuff
But God damn it. I'm on a stage now where there's wizards that appear and throw things at you
And then they disappear and sometimes they reappear like right under you and you die. It's very frustrating. I
Really love a Mario style game or like you know really the games that aren't fighting and shooting really are all the games that I love
but especially since I enjoy the occasional weed,
I can't have them in the house.
I don't need another vice to lose hours too.
You know what I mean?
I don't play it for hours,
because usually by minute,
I think I would.
Minute 14, I mean, such a blind rage
that I shut it off.
So I've been talking to this podcast
about me and my old roommate,
how we, for like two weeks,
tried to beat Weemario World.
We'll play Weemario.
The side scrolling one.
Yeah, I think it's gotta be the best reviewed game.
I mean, it was the most fun time of my life.
It's a great game.
I realize how sad that is.
But, it's a great game and it's easy as shit.
It's not easy.
It's child's play.
No, because you have to.
Don't you come in here talking about we, Mario,
get sit there with some of that fucking shit
that I got over there.
No, we did it where we had to go back into each level
and get the three hidden stars,
which is nearly impossible.
So we play, we listen to music,
we played for about 12 hours a day,
we were both unemployed.
We barely spoke to each other.
Had a ball, went to bed at like five a .m.,
wake up in noon, just pick up the controllers.
Maybe order food here and there.
And then when we finally beat it, also silently,
we both stood up, turned to each other.
And for maybe the first time in our roommate ship,
hugged.
Oh wow.
And then we both went to bed at about 4 p .m.
Wow.
And it was maybe the best time of my life.
Oh my god.
If I were to edit the highlights of it together,
the music over it would be,
I've had the time of my life really yeah, it wouldn't be the boys are back in town
No, I think that's overdone all right fair enough the
You know, we're talking about these light things dogs Nintendo yeah real dark undercurrent under all of it though
Isn't there there is I mean I I did a lot of thinking today because I rewatched the neon demon and I'm not gonna
I'm not gonna get through it again today. I love the film
I can't wait
But I was it made it's a movie about you know aging and how everybody craves being young and I was really just kind
of like you just get older and older and then you die and I was kind of like the whole like youth
thing is over for me you can sort of pretend you're still in it but you're not no you're absolutely not you're
are not in it anymore. You know, though, we, uh, we accept it. What can you do? You know,
you just get older. That's it.
Very somber note. There's no going back. This is our life. We are the gray hairs of your
beard scrape against the mic. It's true. Microphone. Uh, all right. Well, we've caught up.
I don't feel any different than I did even 10 years ago, so I guess I shouldn't really
complain.
I had my fucking health.
Well, it's just kind of pad, it's, it's, it's, they, they say you're only as old as
you feel.
That's true, you know?
I mean, I've always felt like a cool 60, but I mean, I, I just mean, I don't like get
tired early.
My joints don't ache.
My back doesn't hurt.
Yeah.
I'm good.
but I've had the same or similar problem. I've always just felt I haven't reached my appropriate
age yet. People say I feel older than I am. I feel younger than I am because I'm still waiting
to be an old, angry man. Yeah. Well, it's coming. Yeah. And there, I mean, there are flashes of it now.
Certainly. Can we get into your movie review or your movie roundup segment because I saw something
today that I really want to talk about? Sure. I mean, again, I've been very busy and I have not seen
anything except I watched the Dave Chappelle at the palladium special, which was hilarious.
Heard it was great.
I have not watched that, or man, oh yeah, I'm trying to treat myself and space him out
a little bit.
But man, it was just so funny.
And the people who are upset about it, you just really got to be like, shut up.
He talks about some controversial things.
He always has, folks, and he's a 42 -year -old African -American man, talking about how
he sees the world, which is the job of stand up, quit, quit getting upset about everything.
It's there you are, and I don't believe you are.
It's their job to say the things we think, think because they see the world from a different
angle.
Yes.
Right, Pat?
Folks, you said folks like an AM calling show, folks, that's what he's always done.
Get with the program.
It's just irritating.
I mean, he does a pretty lengthy bit about how, oh boy, Gays and Transsexuals, we're throwing them the rights right out of the gate.
No, it took Black people a very long time. And then people are like, well, you know,
don't you know that Gays and Transsexuals have been around much longer than this and blah, blah, blah.
Of course, he knows gang. He's a comedian making jokes.
folks. And sometimes you exaggerate things to communicate a fact. Christ. So all over
the Twitter today is driving nuts. Who was saying it on Twitter? Anybody we know? I'm
not going to name names. Oh, that's a yes. I'll get it out of you later. You can get it
out. I mean, look, pen I have been a few drinks right now as usual and then we're going
to a party. So I'm going to corner you at this party and we're going to, we're going to
down to the realtor. I'll have to tell you and I understand people's point of view. I especially
understand it if you're a homosexual man or woman and you have issues with what Dave
Chappelle discussed and that special. What I am not really going to tolerate is the white guy who's
going to tell Dave Chappelle how to talk about race because it bothers what he thinks is appropriate
treatment of homosexuals, was he?
Now he is neither.
Was it Jamie Kielstein?
It was a Jamie Kielstein.
I just like, you don't have to like,
I don't know.
It's these people who come to everyone's defense
or whatever, it's like nobody asked you
and they don't need you.
And what it comes from is decades of watching
Matthew McConaughey save Samuel Jackson
in time to kill, or the white guy come in
or Matthew McConaughey and that slave movie
that just happened.
It's a sneaky or it's a sneaky or thing
than that. It's, it's most of the time a guy thinking that he will get laid by looking
super sensitive. You know, that's the dark truth, but in that is Jamie Killstein, of course.
But folks, folks, they say, I'm just saying like, you know, we were all on the same team.
We should help each other out, but sometimes it's like, you know, it's not, it's not your
place that's all I'm saying white man white man and now I will tell you I did see I saw somebody who
was upset about it who was a homosexual man that didn't bother me in the slightest I'm like yeah
you're living that life you get to speak about it sure you know that's just it sure but you don't like
the white I don't you know what the truth is I don't like the whites and when I see people online
talking about you know I hate you know middle -aged white man or old white man or whatever I'm like
I do too, and that's what I'm trying to fend off, you know, but the funny part is still
going to house parties at age 36.
The funny part is, is the savior bleeding heart white guys are as annoying as the right
wing fascist white guys.
I mean, it's, it's just, there's a real problem with the right side, but yeah, they're
definitely equally as annoying.
It's, it's a real, it's a real thorn in the side situation with the white guys these days.
It is but hey, what are you going to do?
The I want to tell you about this movie I saw please
Saw today on the lifetime channel
Now this is a little bit of a game. We're going to play here title of the movie double mommy
Dope, why are you watching a movie called Double Mommy?
Because it was called Double Mommy.
All right, who was in it?
Uh, the only name I recognized in the entire thing was Bruce Boxlitener, of Tron fame.
I can't even picture Bruce Boxlitener, but I know he was in a great deal of movies.
He's the other guy in Tron.
I never saw the bridge of Tron.
I only saw the Tron, like, Tron, uh, Emerald Legosi.
The, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the,
He's the guy that is like at the company board meeting that tells Jeff Bridges kid to go find him.
I thought I'm completely interrupting him.
I thought Tron Legacy was pretty sweet.
I saw it in 3D.
And when I went to Mexico with my lovely fiancé, went to this place called Coco Bongo.
And if you ever go to Mexico, you have to go to this place.
It's an immoral legacy restaurant, isn't it?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, but they go from nine o 'clock till five a .m.
They do these 15 minute shows.
So the first one will be like Beatles and Personators.
They're always Mexican, of course.
And they'll do like a hard day's night and play like another Beatles song, but, but, but, but
it, but it'll be L hard days, Nido, right?
Yeah, exactly.
Let's do that bit.
Then, uh, no, let's, I think we're done.
Then out comes like Beetlejuice and then they do shake, shake, shake, sonora and they fly through the crowd.
And this is just like a packed nightclub. And when you walk in, your total is $80 if you want unlimited like vodka with an XXX on the bottle.
Like literally ever clear.
When does the Emerald Legacy impersonator come out?
Or you pay $100 and get top shelf, which I'm sure is watered down probably.
So because they're Mexicans Pat you're racist. I mean I'll get it. You don't like the white nights
But you don't got to go in the other direction right now
I think it was watered down because we both wind up wound up violently shitting the next day. Oh, okay for hours
Okay, that's why I think there was some water in it. Maybe they slept you one of those
This is a bad joke. You ready? Yeah, maybe they sit slipped you one of those new date rape drugs. They're called dookies
Oh boy, it's a bad joke, I'm sorry. So anyhow, good. We get drunk. I see like four of them.
They do a beetle, like I said, Beetlejuice. And then they do tron. And the tron one, these
guys are literally like flying motorcycles around the venue, like through the air, flying
motorcycles. We're a P's artist. And folks, Brooks Bachleiner is in this. That's how bad
So they offered him a free meal and he went down across the border.
But it was like one of the greatest shows I've ever seen, except the next day I realized that
Heather was like, what about that crazy Elvis one? What about that crazy Beyonce one?
What about that crazy Jay Z one? And then I was like, oh, I blacked out for almost the entirety
of this event. Oh, and speaking of blacking out during an amazing event, yeah, we buried the
Ali, Pat and I saw Wu -Tang clan the other night.
We did, I didn't black out at the Wu -Tang clan.
I didn't black out, but I left going.
The next day I was like, it's a very short show.
They only played about seven songs,
and then I started having jarring memories come back
to me of, oh no, they did all these songs
from the jizzis album.
They did all these method band songs.
They had old dirty bastard son come out.
I had forgotten all that.
They did all the Ray Kwan and Ghostface solo stuff.
Yeah, it was an amazing show.
It was really really good, but yeah, I mean, you could have easily gotten high in there without smoking anything. Oh, we were
Yeah, we were pretty high smoking things eight two
Edibles and smoked a lot of weed and drank a lot. Yeah, it was fun. Anyway, but I wore the closing of my store
I'm sorry that I interrupt the your store to tell my story. Wow. Is that welcome to Hollywood? We went to
to another island in Mexico and not another city in Mexico and we were walking out and
I was kind of bummed out that I had missed the show and I realized we were out walking
around that there was a second cocoa bongo and there's two locations in Mexico right
I said Heather would you hate me if we saw it again we saw it again this time they did a
groundhog day number this time I drank much less but if you're ever in either of these
cities that I can't remember in Mexico. Just Google Coco Bongo because it's going to be your
best night there. I had an absolute blast. Folks, go to Mexico and just Google the two most Mexican
words you can think of. If you look up Coco Bongo, you'll find it. It's the best hundred dollars
you'll ever spend. All right. Now, I'm sitting on the couch today. I'm flipping through my sling TV
app. All right. I come across the lifetime network, which I don't usually come across because it's
way down at the end of the dial, but I went down to No Man's Land.
If I'm coming across, I'm watching Cinemax After Dark movie.
Yeah, that's clever, No Man's Land, Lifetime,
to the No Man's Land.
Get it?
That should have been their slogan, it's okay.
It should have been, right?
All right.
I see a movie is currently playing, it is called Double Mommy.
Yeah, I say.
Like, double whammy?
Double Mommy.
But is that the pond? Well all right now here here's my thought double mommy. There's some sort of zany
twin -mother
switcheroo thing happening like big business
Yes with that middle -air and Lily Tom. Yes, and I just watched baby boom the other day
Which doesn't have any twins or any switcherooing? No, but it's still a nice heartwarming comedy about motherhood
so I say I'm in I'm hooked on the title double mommy I
hit the select button, which first brings you to a screen where it gives you a breakdown
of the film.
Yes.
Synopsis, if you will.
And it also gives you the option to start where it is or start it from the beginning.
I immediately after reading Synopsis shows start from the beginning.
Double mommy.
You want to take any wild guesses what this film was about?
She's a mom with a double life.
She has two families.
not even cool let alone warm then tell me she's pregnant all right okay with
twins all right here we go we're on our way to a zany kind of affair what's the
problem well here's the problem her twins have two different fathers okay I'm
listening. All right. I'm listening. One's gonna be Jim Belushi. One's gonna be Harvey
Firestein. I don't know. Wow. But the you you get where my head's going. I do. Here's
the next sentence. One is the man she's in love with. The other a product of date rape.
This is the plot of the movie. It's not a comedy. So it is a it is nowhere near comedy
and it's called double money.
All the time doesn't really do comedies,
but was she watching, she was like walking
to the store with her husband's jizz in her
and then she got raped, is that what happened?
She was dating somebody and I guess it was very convoluted
the plot, the friend of the boyfriend
that she just broke up with was consoling her,
then he date rapes her with the Rufi
and then she gets back together with the boyfriend immediately
And then she has twins, but then but then one of them is fathered by the boyfriend, but once it's an imposter
It's an insane type of a film so it wasn't based on a true story. I would guess not
I didn't wouldn't both nuts have to be inside of you
If for that to even be feasible, which it isn't pat you're focusing on the wrong aspects of this film who portrayed double mommy
Who the hell knows?
All right
It's a juicy role.
Not with this writing.
I'm going to look it up.
It's a really, really bad and I found out that it's an unofficial sequel to a film lifetime
did called Double Daddy.
How would that work?
Double Daddy was about a guy that got two women pregnant at the same time and then one's
going to kill him because she's angry.
This movie is, this movie is Double Mommy which doesn't make sense because Double
daddy is two mommies and double mommy is two daddy's. But here's the thing. I can't believe
I was sitting watching a lifetime movie on a Saturday. Here's how the here's how the the guy
that she says he raped me and he's the father of one of my twins. This is a new film. Yeah,
2016. This is brand new. All right. This is how he's going to this is going to clear his name.
His plan is to murder the mother. Wow. So she can't say he's a rapist anymore. Okay. So if I murder
heard all be fine. We're insane film. Look, I'm very interested in it now. It's got
about two stars on your IMDB charts. All right. So, you know, there's one to watch,
folks. Double mommy. Double mommy. Watch this whole thing. No. I watched it until they
would let me wouldn't let me fast forward anymore. Okay. Because it got up to where it was
playing live on TV and I couldn't fast forward anymore. But I watched enough, Pat. I got
the gist of it. The giz of it. Ah, don't come on. All right, look, we're 24 minutes, 25 minutes in
here. Let's, do you want to get into our, let's do it, our, our meat of the, of the podcast.
Yes, we're talking about the 2016 film much like double mommy. The neon demon
directed by Nicholas winding Reffian, written by Reffan and two ladies,
music by the great Cliff Martinez, which I really feel to be a star of the film.
Another character.
It's Cliff Martinez.
He didn't do the music for Drive, though.
He did do the music for Drive.
But he's got a stage name that he goes by.
I believe.
He does the score, but I mean, there were other artists that had songs in the sound.
But like all the synthy...
I think it's just Cliff Martinez.
No, no, no, there's an artist with a name that's not Cliff Martinez
is who has songs and drive.
It might be Cliff Martinez's sort of stage name.
All right.
Anyway, give us a synopsis of the neon demon, if you will.
Well, it's easier said than done.
I mean, the basic premise is L -fanning,
co -fanning's little sister, comes to Los Angeles.
She's 16 years old.
She has a dream of being a model.
She meets up with some women who are models, they are immediately jealous and caddy toward
her because she is so youthful and beautiful and they are aging out of the modeling industry
even though they are beautiful and probably only in their late 20s.
She very, I mean, it's hard to even describe what happens next.
I don't want to spoil anything.
And also it's sort of open to interpretate.
Let's spoil it.
We they are essentially vampires trying to get her blood and the hopes that it will make them younger now
I didn't I didn't take that from it. Mm -hmm. That's fine, but that's also something that's revealed
You're talking the last 15 minutes of the film or something like that. Yeah, I mean there are blood suckers
Well, they eat her. Yeah, they eat her whole at the end of the film. Yes, and then vomit her up. Yes
And the one that doesn't vomit her up gets to keep working correct
And the one that does vomit her up can't hack it and whatever. So I guess yes, the point is is they eat her and they'll be good now
Here's your
Linchpin this is this is what the whole movie is hanging on David Linchpin. Yeah, it's a lynchian film folks
I mean this this this wasn't even a David swimmer pin for me
The but the whole movie is hanging on this if this is what it's all building up to this is what the whole point of the film is
And this is my problem with the film. I have many problems with the film. We'll get into all of them, but my biggest problem with the film is
There is absolutely nothing
Nothing
I'll say it again. Oh Jesus nothing
That hints at that
That builds toward that
That foreshadows that in any way
it's literally like you're watching a Bret Easton Ellis movie depicting the
shallowness of Hollywood and then all of a sudden there's a scene where
they're going to eat her and essentially because she won't fuck Jenna Malone
Malone. Jenna Malone tries to sleep with her. She has a negative reaction to it and
then they murder her and they don't even show you them eating her. They just show you
Maybe they're sort of bathing and they're, what you can assume is her blood, showering
nakedly in her blood.
Which doesn't make sense.
How was the blood being brought into the shower?
Because they kill her in the pool and somehow the pool drain is filtering to the shower head
somehow.
I mean, you're already approaching it completely wrong.
Why?
And I'd also like to add, you watched this on your phone, correct?
No, I watched it on my iPad, which is a plenty big screen.
No, it isn't for a movie like this.
Yes, it is. This is really a movie to see in the theater or with certainly with great sound
I had my headphones buried in my ears. It was the sound was plenty good
I mean, it's just not a movie to watch on a plane. Yeah, the movie to watch on a plane is like a legal drama or something
I don't agree. I enjoy films on a plane
I mean also you're watching completely naked women shower and blood
Surrounded by people. That's an odd move. Yeah, you should have seen how the guy next to me what he was doing
Yeah, folks, you went to the bathroom three times if you know what I mean if you go and like, you know, drive is a much more
Narrative movie. I know you hate driving a shit film
But yeah
It's okay. Listen, we were real nice the first couple episodes. Let's get into this
I mean drive is one of my favorite films of the past five years. It's an insane man talk my favorite films the past five
I've seen it ten times. I never get bored of it glorified music video. That's all it is and so was that well
It's what we also call in the film world pure cinema
Because
That while certainly film school my professor Roy Zurich
Pure cinema is it's Hitchcock these are the moments that don't require dialogue
Which is not even really supposed to be these movies the point that the me I'm I'm can I say this?
I am a and I didn't say that like you weren't letting me talk. I'm just saying like sure. Can I say what I'm about to say?
Of course. I am offended that you would put this man anywhere near
Hitchcock in a sentence let alone in in the field. Well, I'm not putting him up against him as though they're their equals or something
But I think he is a true
Outdoor in that his movies sort of look and feel the same much like a John Carpenter who will be discussing next week with Christine
And I'm going to compare him to him as well both musically the music in these movies and also just in the way he shoots things
I think it's this movie much more than drive is really supposed to be like an art exhibit
I mean it opens on like a minute shot of what just appears to be an art exhibit in a museum
Okay, you know what you're watching on your iPad. You know what you want it to be a fucking art exhibit
Go hang it in the fucking museum of modern art downtown. You know it. Okay, he and he good, but here's the thing
They have a film division.
I go down to the museum of modern art.
I look at the video displays and the video exhibits and stuff.
I think they're fascinating.
They're crazy and they're weird
and they're more visual than anything else.
And I love them, but put it in a fucking museum.
This guy wants people to go watch his goddamn movies
like their movies and they're not.
They are fucking extended music videos.
And that's what bothers me.
Well, silence is not an option.
I mean, drive is an action movie drive drive isn't I could see I could definitely see finding the neon demon boring or not
Satisfying on a narrative level drive is a fucking action movie drive is thoughtful wanted that drive
Let me let me say this
Drive is in it is not an action movie drive as action sequences drive that's an action movie Joe. Okay, fine
We well, I'll give you that. I mean wasn't a comedy had a bunch of jokes in it. We'll call it an action movie fine sure, but
But when it comes to the writing in that film, it is piss fucking poor.
And I don't care if Albert Brooks got nominated for an Oscar or not, I'm a huge, huge
Albert Brooks fan.
I thought he did a very good job with that material.
I thought he was convincing.
But one of the lines in drive, literally, is Albert Brooks, who's supposed to be a gangster,
Even though they never really show anything, like of how he's a gangster, they just say he's
a gangster.
Fine.
So it was Ron Proman, and it's proven by a scene where there are, for some reason, all
in tuxedos after hours in a pizzeria dancing with women because you know that's what gangsters
would do.
Anyway.
The big...
This is what gangsters and the movie drive did.
It's not what you expected or wanted it to be.
That goes for drive and the neon demon. So you hate it. No, no, no, instead of letting yourself go
I'm gonna check this out instead. No, no, no, no. In the scene. See a demon's face in the big scene
I'm not mad about that in the big scene and drive where they're supposed to finally show you their business
This is the dialogue. This is a baffling gripe with drama. This is the dialogue missing the point you ready for the dialogue. Clearly ready for the dialogue. Yeah
Yeah, I did that for you
Because I wanted to take care of the business back east
That's a line in drive. That's literally what I would have written when I was 14 years old.
Joe, that's not the point of drive. What's the point that Ryan, that Ryan Gosling is beautiful
and can be silent in an interesting way? Is that the point of drive? No, they removed his
dialogue, which I think is very interesting because anything he'd be saying would be stupid.
Well, and the gangsters, they give them very minimal suggestive dialogue. It says they're trying to
do almost a silent movie.
It's terrible.
And they weren't trying to do a silent movie.
I don't buy that.
Well, it's just wall -to -wall music.
I think calling it a music video is needlessly harsh.
Every action movie to some extent is a music video.
And they on Demon, even more so.
Yeah, explain to me then the silence of Demon Demon.
Every character is quiet for long periods of time.
You're supposed to just, what the fuck, that whole thing
with like there's a panther in a room
or whatever the fuck that was?
Yeah, well, I mean drive at least holds there's nothing that happens in drive that is like oh, I don't believe this could happen the neon
demon is in a heightened
World and the panther and shit you're just supposed to make what you want out of it
I think the panther if I had to say what it represents and this is always kind of jerking off
But it represents these predators that are going to try to fuck her and and take her soul in Hollywood
Which they will which should be a message you're relate to I get the idea of predators
I get the idea that in the end she is becoming the predator, yes, and then literally she's eaten.
It's just not very strong. It's very tried to me. It's very obvious. It's very on the sleeve.
It's not very smart to me. Now the guy can shoot the fuck out of a movie. I'll give him that.
The guy knows how to put a picture to music like nobody else.
But to me is very important like that it how is that not a a top two for you and going to a movie?
It is important, but it's not it doesn't it's not all that there is
Scorsese knows how to do that. He also knows how to deliver a good script
And interesting guy is doing something different. Why can't that be okay? Like David Lynch was doing something different
Let me tell you something when they make a movie when they make a this would piss me off about this
as guys fucking movies, okay?
Is because the intellectual types, right?
They go, oh, he's doing something different.
It's brilliant, it's daring, it's this net.
If you did what this guy did,
except in another direction, it would be fucking commando.
It would be like a bad Schwarzenegger or Stallone movie.
It would be all flash, no substance.
His films are all flash and no substance.
But I think he would love that comparison to commando.
God bless him.
He's clearly obsessed with 80s music, movies, et cetera.
And like to me, it follows as like horror drive.
It's just a beautiful movie and it's kind of a mood thing
and it kind of washes over you.
And the message there, you know, about STDs
is pretty obvious as well.
But.
Explain that to me because I did miss that.
I'm not being smart.
What?
The STD miss.
I'm talking to it, it follows.
Oh, and it follows.
Yeah, I mean, they take the wonderful thing
and they run with it.
But the neon demon and I as I said, when I saw it, I would never recommend it to anyone.
When the second the lights went up at the end of the movie and it's a it's a big anti -climax of the movie.
This guy behind me said to his girlfriend, you're never picking the fucking movie again with no humor in his voice.
He sounded very angry with that.
Now, doesn't that mean anything to you that you would never recommend the movie to anybody, even though you love it so much?
Does that mean that I shouldn't love it?
No, I'm just stupid.
Does that doesn't that mean anything to your understanding how somebody like me could hate it so much yeah, but not drive
I think that that drive is a movie that like like Ankerman like Lebowski like you know various other movies
I think Frack is kind of ruined. They took it too far and
You can't see it as anything other than some meathead fantasy, but when I first saw drive knowing nothing about it
I went back in and saw it again right after
And I brought our buddy Pete to say it.
It's his favorite movie of all time.
And people love that movie.
Then he had demon people love too,
but it's kind of a smaller group
because it is designed really
to be completely non -rewarding to the viewer.
I mean, there's no real payoff to it.
Pete also thinks the nationals
are the best band that's ever lived.
But you know, a lot of people like the national,
as do I.
But I'm not saying they're bad,
I'm just saying it's not the best band.
I mean, I didn't I didn't love it when that that Halloween three years back when every guy in Silver Lake was wearing the
Gosling jacket either, but I think there's there's a reason that movie became so iconic and so beloved is that it's a fucking awesome movie
I will say this I will say this a I will give drive and other chance plate you should look at that look we're making progress here
Yeah, I will give drive and other chance b. Fuck the neon demon for all time. Doesn't matter that I watch it on my iPad
It's a piece of shit. Well, it doesn't matter that you watch it. It doesn't it does not it absolutely does not to me
That's so insulting as as a film fan. I don't even mean just the man
Insulting it is insulting that you can claim to be such a film fan
But also say you can watch any movie on your iPad. It doesn't matter. It's a goddamn retina screen. It was a nighttime flight
It's dark. I have my headphones smaller than like the TV you grew up with it like it's a tiny
any surface to watch what should be on a giant screen with the best possible sound.
I am. Well, sorry, Mr. War bucks. We don't have that opportunity, everybody.
I mean, when I was sitting in the theater, granted pretty high.
I saw I intentionally saw it alone and I just sat in that center seat and had the most
wonderful fucking time just watching cool images and listening to cool music.
And that to me isn't more than enough. So when 95 % of what I see is absolutely terrible.
Okay, so visually and this was the same argument you made about Zach and Miri need wedding dates or whatever that fucking movie is called
Zach and Miri made a no make up the world Mike and Dave need wedding
Mike and Dave need wedding dates. This is the same argument. The point was it's comedy
I laughed enough for me to call it a successful comedy now, but here's not a great move. Yeah, but here's the thing
Here's the thing sure pat if I was high out of my fucking mind. I wasn't when I saw you
Mike and I know the other one neon demon. Yeah, if I was high out of my mind
It was not on my mind, but if I was hot can we not split hairs if I was high in a theater sitting in a dark cool movie theater cool meeting temperature wise
Watching this thing with the sound blaring and all that stuff. Yeah, I might have liked it
You know what else? I might have liked fucking radio heads last three albums if I listen to him in that circumstance
But you put them on in my living room. I go turn this the fuck off. It's boring
That's all I'm saying and you can't you can't define a movie's quality by the circumstance with which you need
to watch it. It needs to, it needs to transcend that. It doesn't need to transcend it. Certain movies,
as I said, a romantic comedy, a legal thriller, these are all movies that you should watch and can
watch on your iPad. An art film, which I would consider this, maybe you don't consider it art,
but it's an art film. It would rank in the art film section of Blockbuster.
Well, then that must mean it's good. No, I just said it doesn't mean it's good or a blockbuster
I don't want to blockbuster would put it in the art section. There are certain movies that you should say in a big screen
And for somebody to be a movie fan and and not think that's true is ridiculous. Frankly, it's stupid
How much I love Star Wars, right? Would you watch that in an iPad for the first time?
Yes, that's stupid. It's not stupid
It is to think but here's why it's not stupid because if you want Star Wars on your iPad the first time
You would still go. That was a good movie. There were plot points. I don't know. There was a story
There was character development this doesn't have any of that if I'm watching Star Wars on my iPad
Then I'm like oh God somebody just came out of the bathroom and now it stinks in here
Then I'm looking up at the guy who's falling asleep on my arm that I'm like that. Yeah, you know what?
I will take a coke. Thank you very much. You're paying no attention which is a problem with this generation
This isn't me. Well, I was paying attention if you're fully engrossed on your iPad to the neon demon for the entire runtime
time. And you had great sound on this six inch screen, then more power to you. I don't
buy the iPad speakers. I had my earbuds in. The sound is the worst sound quality in the
world for God's. The iPhone earbud, the white ones. Yes. There's no worse sound than those.
Okay. There's no worse. Only the way I listen to it. At least get a beat by Dre or something.
I have beats by Dre headphones. You know what? The earbuds sound better. That's the truth. They definitely
They only do not 100 % they're tinny and shit because you can't focus when a guy takes
a shit doesn't mean that I can't do do do the I think you're not I mean you can't you
can't hardly focus on Logan in a movie theater. All right bouncing around I focused on the
Neon demon how a sign was going. Why don't you meet me part way here because I meet you part
way I'm gonna give drive another shot. Meet me. So out then I'll remove a time that I watch
drive. No, I'm saying meet me part way and say you gave Neon demon a shout you shot
You didn't like it. No, I'm giving I already said I said you wouldn't like it before you even saw it, but can I say an act?
Can I say a nice thing about this man? It's for smart finish. Oh God. Yeah, you you you fucking people drive and they have a smart
People would ever heritage you are. I mean whatever heritage are you fucking people the this is and you know what?
I loved only God forgives. I didn't see it which everyone hates and that's that's kind of the action of drive mix with the art
filmness of the neon demon. I would like to
upgrade to the director Nicholas
Wyning Refian. Bronson. Great movie.
One of the best movies I've seen in a
long time. Okay. One of Zerli films.
I loved it. I wish Bronson visually
spectacular. It was.
It was wonderfully acted. It was
beautifully framed. Everything looked
like a painting, but there was a
story. There were words. I don't need
it. Oh God. And I don't need it with
Lynch either because when I watched
This was not Lynch, it was, it was lesser Lynch, but it was Lynch, because when I go to a
day of Lynch movie, I go, I'm going to be in a dream for two hours and see amazing
shit and listen to amazing music. And when I went to the neon demon, that's exactly what
I did. And I felt like I was watching a dream. I didn't, it didn't always make sense to
me. I didn't give a shit. But you got a shit to what you're saying. Certain moves you got
to shut that part of your brain off. You're saying right now. Films do not have to be, they
You don't have to make perfect sense to you.
You're saying it didn't make sense to me,
but I didn't care.
Therefore, it's right.
That's exactly right.
Movies don't have to make sense to me,
and they shouldn't have to make sense to you.
You should open your mind a little bit.
My mind is open.
Look at those shelves.
Show your mind is one of the least open minds of all time.
I've got a hell of a collection over there.
My mind is open.
I watch a lot of different stuff.
What I'm saying is I do not like a movie,
and I said it about,
and I'm saying I do like a movie.
But I also said it about the Argento Suspiria and inferno films. I said, are they terrible? No, but it's a lot of visuals at the at the expense of logic and I don't like it that much.
Okay. I mean, I think to sort of prove that he likes having fun with people and kind of fucking with people.
Hey, you can watch the documentary about him and his wife on Netflix that I love because he seems like a really fascinating and kind of funny dude.
who's extremely insecure, winding ref and I'm talking about.
But he's remaking Maniac Cup.
I mean, this is a guy who likes schlock.
I mean, when I heard that, I was like,
that is perfect to me.
He's the guy remaking it.
He's remaking Maniac Cup.
Listen, now I will say this.
Yes.
You know my love for Maniac Cup one and two, I know yours.
We did one live in Littleton, Colorado.
I will be there.
an opening night. I can't wait to see it. I think that he is an extremely exciting visual
director. And if and when, because Lynch only did it a handful of times, straight story
elephant man, if and when Reffian decides that he wants to make like a really, you know traditional
narrative film, because he could get the Blade Runner franchise or something like that easily,
if he wanted it, I think that that will be extremely exciting in a great mix of art and commerce.
In that meantime if he wants to fuck around and this is the result couldn't be happier. All right, fair enough for me. Fair enough
Pat Walsh everybody
He likes colors
Flashy. I do honestly. I like I like neon. I love that. I love enter the void and I like do you see enter the void
Into the void enter the void. No, what's who's that? That's a movie that almost nobody has seen and everybody should do it
It's about five years old.
It's completely nuts.
It's a gas bar no -e movie,
but there's a lot of sex in it and everything else.
But it's all very like neon.
There's lots like extremely long takes.
At one point he fucks her and it's done
from the point of view of the dick,
like a camera attached to an actual dick.
It's one of the wildest things you've ever seen.
They basically take acid and you're on this journey
with them throughout the night in Japan, Tokyo,
I believe, check it out.
Yeah, but that's a movie too where you got to be like I'm gonna have an evening here. I'm not gonna be following a plot
To me that's great to Joe that's bothersome and that's what makes this country great
That's homework for me and everybody else. I will check out this film. You're talking about
But I almost are going to for extra credit rewatch drive and I will we will return to this please do
I think I think you'll appreciate drive. I mean the first 25 minutes is one of the best action sequences. I
Loved it. All right patty
Let's wrap it up you can follow me at Joe DeRose a comedy on Twitter and Instagram and please folks do me a favor
I got all these shitty reviews from these trolls go and go and give me give me some five -star reviews on the albums
All right go to the albums on iTunes and Amazon stand -up albums give me some nice reviews other than that
That's all I got right now
Yeah.
Folks, thank you for everything, by the way.
You hate me for everything?
No, I said thank you for everything, the people.
Oh, yes.
The fans.
Uh, I thought that Joe was closing his time by saying, Pat, I hate you for everything.
I can't do that.
I didn't know.
That's why I acted so, uh, so scared.
Um, folks, I'm at the Patrick Walsh on, uh, Twitter and Instagram.
Uh, again, we love the comments, um, we're taking them into consideration.
obviously we're doing some, some older movies now, I mean, really, what's so great about
the comments is that somebody would be like, when are you guys going to do a new movie?
When the next comment will be, when you guys are doing old movie, everybody likes different
things.
So we're trying to reach everybody.
Next week is Christine, John Carpenter's and Stephen King's Christine, folks, thank you
very much.
This has been a head gum podcast, we'll see you next week.
That was a head -dum podcast.