🎵 I'll see you in hell. I'll see you in hell. And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say. I'll see you in hell. You know I will. I'll see you in hell. You know I will. 🎵
May. May, May, May. I thought it was June. I thought it was July. I don't know what the hell month it is anymore.
We're in spring. Spring has sprung. Easter. That happened already, I think, yeah?
Yeah. Awful holiday. The lowest. Comparable to like a Labor Day to me. Like just a non -real holiday that nobody does anything on.
Yeah, it's up there with my parents' anniversary. Just like, who cares?
Yeah, Pam, when you're a kid you look for eggs. That's kind of fun. But even by the time you're 10 years old, you're bored with that shit.
Yeah, that is true, man. It is true. Every year my mom says, are you going to come home for Easter? I'm like, what are you, nuts? Are you going to fly for this?
Well, I got you, you new bonnet, Joey.
I guess I used to like the Easter basket. I remember eating all my candy one year and vomiting en masse. Not en masse, like a lot of it. I just mean I threw up at church.
Was there a scene when you puked at church, or was it quiet?
No, it happened all the time. Happened all the time.
So nobody cared? Nobody was worried about it?
I'm just noticing I'm getting like a gray temple. I've never noticed it before, but it's happening.
It looks distinguished to me.
It does. I'm looking very distinguished.
And the white in the beard looks nice. It's just that one little patch.
Maybe I'll remake The Distinguished Gentleman with me in the Eddie Murphy role.
And I'm going to announce on deadline, I'll be like, look, I just think it's time to bring back colorblind casting.
You know? I don't even know if I saw The Distinguished Gentleman. I've seen every Eddie Murphy movie, but.
I'm going to give you a twist to throw at it.
Yeah.
Update the version.
And you make it about a guy that works, a lowly fish factory worker who gets yanked out of the fish shift
and has to pose as a politician because he looks exactly like him, like a Dave thing.
But the problem, it all takes place in the same day, and the problem is he reeks like fish.
You call it The Distinguished or The Stinkfished Gentleman, even.
I thought maybe you were going to say The Distinkfished Gentleman, but I was like, he's not building up to that.
There's no way. But there it was.
I kind of liked it.
I think it adds an urgency.
Maybe do my tool biopic, my biopic of Maynard James Keenan, which is called The Distinkfished Gentleman.
I think you just do that as a porno movie, and you call it a day.
I don't know why you haven't done that yet.
Can't fathom a worse or a less appealing song title than Stinkfished.
It's what kept me from listening to Tool for my entire life.
I was like, whatever they're doing, I don't want any part of it.
By the way, the follow -up single to Prison Sex.
Which is somehow better.
Are you following these Diddy updates?
And more importantly, why did you tell Puff to do the things that he did, Joe?
I couldn't take the songs anymore.
I thought he had never really made a good one.
I thought I told you that. We won't stop.
Kept threatening to not stop.
So I stepped in and stopped him.
Yeah, these updates are insane, as Crazy Eddie used to say.
They're hourly.
You know, like my TMZ, which is, you know, it's pathetic,
but it's replaced drugs and alcohol for me as these stupid gossip rags
and other addictions that flare up when I turn down my other ones.
But there is an update on Cassie and Diddy every single hour.
And then when you look at the comments, here's what boggles my mind.
We do have a man problem in America.
That's not being exaggerated.
The comments, by and large, are men going, sounds to me like she wanted it.
Oh, boy.
Like, there's millions of those.
It's like, okay, Diddy didn't pay off all these people.
These people actually believe this.
That's tough stuff.
Yeah.
That's not what you want to say at the dinner table.
Absolutely not.
Well, also, it's like the stuff coming out today was more like, you know,
it was text to Cassie like, I don't even know who this woman is
before this trial.
But it's stuff like her texting Diddy, like, loving positive things.
And then his lawyer, who's a woman, being like, so it's interesting.
It seems here like you really liked him.
You said, I can't wait to see you tonight.
So it doesn't sound like he's abusing you.
It's like he dragged her down a hallway by her hair and kicked the shit out of her.
Like, when you're with somebody, you're going to say, I love you at some point,
but things turn.
And you can also be in an abusive thing and still say nice things
while the abuse is happening.
I don't know how people don't get this.
It doesn't make sense to me.
They do get it.
You're right.
They get it.
Yeah.
She's just, I mean, dude, you'd think the logic would end here.
We saw the video.
He apologized for the video.
He not only apologized, he shook his head throughout the apology
and said how ashamed of himself he was.
Now he's saying the video was taken out of context or re -edited or something.
And it's like, then why would you have apologized if that was the...
It's just nonsense.
Oh, I thought you were saying the confession video was edited.
No, no, no.
Yeah.
I mean, in this world, a man is...
And look, I'm saying street smart, as Pete did.
I don't know anything about his intelligence,
but he's obviously a great businessman and he's street smart.
You can't really argue that.
You don't, the day after an accusation like that,
upload yourself doing a YouTube apology video.
I don't know how his team let that happen.
I just don't get it.
What did he do then?
I mean, I think you want to apologize quick, right?
But no, is that bad?
Yeah, I mean, maybe his team was like, you better get out there.
I really don't fucking know.
But I am surprised they haven't gone with the AI defense,
and I wonder if that's going to start popping up more and more.
This didn't happen.
This is AI.
And do we have the technology, I assume or I hope that we do,
to distinguish or distinct fist what is real and what is AI?
Because it fools me.
Which, by the way, folks, brings us...
Well, we're not going to talk about it just yet,
but we didn't say what we're talking about today.
And we are today talking, I think, right?
We're doing...
You want to just move right in?
I've seen them all.
We can do whichever one you want.
Well, today's topic is Black Mirror season...
Seven.
Oh, Christ.
There's only been seven it is?
Seven seasons, yeah.
And the sixth season was only four.
But wait a minute.
Is it seven since it went to Netflix or seven overall?
It's got to be more than seven overall.
No, it's seven overall because they moved the stuff over
whenever that happened from Britain.
Something that is not AI, very real.
Every other year, we get a new season of Black Mirror.
Yeah.
And we'll get to it.
But yeah, that defense is going to be absolutely happening left and right.
Yeah.
It's very dark.
This is a...
Well, I don't think an episode goes by anymore
where we don't say this is a terrible time to be alive.
You have to acknowledge it.
And it feels...
There's just an ominous feeling in the air
that things are just about to get significantly worse that I feel.
Personally, mood -wise, I feel kind of OK.
I just feel like the world is coming to an end.
And it's not really an exaggeration anymore.
I don't see smiles on the faces of the people anymore.
I just read a Neil Young...
I've been listening to Neil Young the last couple of days,
and I was reading an interview with him.
And he was just talking about the state of the...
just the society.
Yeah.
He usually is talking about that.
And he just was...
Even Neil Young is like...
Well, not even Neil Young.
It was just...
He just was like, yeah, man.
He's like, you know, let's talk about the real problem.
Everybody is accusing everybody else.
Everybody hates...
Nobody trusts each other.
This is the real problem we were having.
And I'm like...
I mean, that's what scares me.
I guess that's why I said even Neil Young.
You'd hope an 80 -year -old would be the person being like,
guys, calm down.
I've been around this son quite a few times.
You're going to be...
Everything is going to be fine.
No, the 80 -year -olds are being like,
this is the absolute worst I've ever seen anything.
I'm like, Jesus Christ, man.
Yeah.
I mean, my parents are in their 60s.
I asked them, has it ever been worse?
And their immediate answer is no.
You know, it's like...
It just hasn't.
Yay, yay, yay.
So, anyway.
Black Mirror, by the way,
it's the title of an Arcade Fire song.
And I was working at Conan O 'Brien
when Arcade Fire came to Conan to promote their first album
and that first giant single.
And I thought they were fucking incredible.
They were all wearing helmets and hitting each other with bats
to make, like, percussion and stuff.
And I was, you know, 30 people.
Conan Stage is, like, tiny.
They had so many people up there.
And I was like, man, these guys sound incredible.
I've never heard anything like this.
And then their second album was great.
That third album, I was like, eh.
And then they just lost it so hard.
Each one just kind of gets worse and worse and worse.
But they were on Saturday Night Live on Saturday Night.
And I think it's the worst musical performance I've ever seen.
Really?
They were embarrassing.
They're dressed like, you know,
he's wearing, like, little plastic girl sunglasses
and then this, like, big colorful jacket
with all these expressions written on it.
And they're all dressed up funny.
And I'm like, look, when you guys were 25, it's fine.
You're 50.
Like, they weren't singing well.
The songs sucked.
It was just terrible.
And he also got canceled.
He was accused of consensual lots of weird stuff,
some of it kind of on the line,
but nothing that would, I guess, end the career.
But it's like...
Wait, that was Arcade Fire?
That's the one where it's the husband and wife
and the guy got accused?
Yeah.
So then it's the husband and wife
singing a duet together on stage.
It looks like they have not talked in a while.
I was just like, everything about this I hate.
It's actually worth watching the performances to see how...
I'm not able to explain.
You know, like, if somebody's out of tune or something,
you can explain it.
All I know how to say is you'll watch it and you'll get it.
You'll be like, God, that's awful.
And you feel it the second the performance starts.
Like, they're just off.
When Butler, as the lead guy,
I don't know anything about him at all.
No.
Outside that he's in Arcade Fire.
But he just looks.
I mean, the look is wafting off of him.
Yeah.
He reeks of a man who uses feminism to get laid.
And I know that.
I know that he was very outspoken about rights
and all that sort of thing.
And then he gets popped for...
But you know what?
I'm not even going to talk on it
because I can't remember what he got accused of.
I do remember.
Yeah, it wasn't, like, hardcore.
It was numerous, like, talking up fans.
You know, I think he intimated that he was separated
when he wasn't and wife, you know, infidelity.
Infidelity is a thing that, you know, destroys lives,
wounds people.
But it's kind of hard for me to ever think somebody
should lose their career over it,
especially because so many do it and never get found out.
Well, look, a lot of people lose careers
over things they shouldn't,
but it's hard when you build your career on a credo
and then you betray the credo.
So I think that's...
Sure.
You know, they're playing SNL.
He's fine.
But you know, that's what happened with Ellen, right?
Ellen didn't do anything illegal or unforgivable.
It's just like you can't be the person that says
be kind all the time and then be an asshole
and nobody wants to hang out with you anymore.
That's just it.
Totally.
We're about to do, on one of our May episodes,
Henry Johnson, a title I hate so much.
I just want to say Henry Thomas every time the kid from ET.
But a title that's a man's name,
I never need to see that again.
Do better. Do better.
Do better, David Mamet.
Oh, come on.
I looked up, of course, LeBouf because I'm always like,
where is he in terms of his cancellation?
You know, I see him being interviewed sometimes.
Henry Johnson was a play here in LA
that I wanted to go see and didn't get to,
that LeBouf was in.
And I remember a few articles about it,
like why are we welcoming him back or whatever.
But here's the difference.
Wynn Butler, at least to my knowledge,
never stepped forward and said,
I'm sorry, I did something wrong.
I cheated on my wife. I feel bad about it.
They did the old let's ignore it,
wait a couple years and come back.
And it seems to have kind of worked,
except it was so fucking shitty.
I'm not saying I prefer one to the other
or one person is better than the other,
but the way Shia LeBouf handled his crimes,
which were more severe,
FKA Twigs, who was a singer I actually love,
said a lot of things about him,
said it was a relentlessly abusive relationship,
that it got sexually abusive,
that he was shooting dogs while he was in character,
et cetera, et cetera.
And his response, and you can watch this interview
with him and John Bernthal.
I don't know where this John Bernthal
interview show is airing.
I just see clips of it on TikTok in black and white.
YouTube. It's a podcast on YouTube.
But he seems, he's so fascinating in that interview
and you just, you root for him.
You believe it and you root for him.
Now he could be a complete fucking sociopath
and none of it could be real and he's a monster.
I don't know.
But I like the way he addresses it,
which he's like, I put that woman through hell.
I owe her an apology.
Not everything she said is true,
but I'm so glad she said it because it killed my ego.
It made me a better man.
It made me realize I can't keep living this way.
It made me rediscover religion, my Catholicism.
He talks about this big fight he was in with Alec Baldwin.
He's like, that would not happen now.
I'm not that person.
And me and Alec now talk about how
we're not those people anymore.
And that to me is just so much more valuable
if people are willing to hear it than to ignore it
or to be like, ooh, we got away with it or something.
I respect it more.
And it's way more risky too.
We talk about all this risk in Hollywood about,
if you show a tit, you're so brave or whatever.
Brave is coming forward and being like,
I have massively fucked up my life
and numerous people in it with my actions.
And I'm actively working to repair it.
It's hard not to support that.
It is kind of interesting that somebody
could do something worse.
But the humanity they might display in reacting to it
puts them in your better graces.
That is an interesting thing.
And it does happen.
The guy, Wynn Butler to me, just has this,
it's like you said, like I didn't do it.
And it's also, the fact that it's a husband
and wife in cahoots,
it feels like the teachers at the school
that aren't upholding the discipline
they inflict on all the kids
and then just kind of get away with it
and don't show accountability for anything.
It's just kind of gross, man.
It's annoying and it's shitty.
Yeah, and also too,
whether I'm right or wrong for this, I don't know.
I give, I don't excuse any behaviors,
but I do give a little more rope to a former child star.
It is a sick fucking environment.
And it is not an environment any child should be put in.
And it's an environment that will and has and does
turn innocent souls into psychos.
It just, it does.
It's a sick, sick thing to expose a child to.
So, you know, there's that aspect of it as well.
But more on Shia when we get to Henry Johnson.
By the way, People Magazine today
did an article about how he tweeted out some emails
that Timothee Chalamet sent him.
Yeah.
Because Timothee Chalamet went to the play.
I saw that.
Yeah.
And in the People Magazine article,
clearly written by AI.
Always now.
Yeah, Shia was starring in a play called Henry Jones.
So not only do they have AI writing the articles,
they don't even bother to have a competent human being
proofread it anymore.
It is fucking pathetic.
We deserve all that is happening to us.
I read on Deadline three days ago an article about
Huge Jackman.
You're an entertainment reporting magazine
who are reporting on one of the top ten biggest stars
in America who is in the news every day.
And you call him Huge Jackman over and over.
There's your porn name to star in.
The Distinct Fist Gentleman.
I mean, Huge Jackman.
How is that not a porno star?
In the Distinct Fist Gentleman.
I don't think you could go Jack on.
That's a hat on a hat.
You could go Huge Jackman.
And Jackman has a ring to it.
It does, you're right.
Speaking of child stars and cancellations,
we have an extremely light cancellation for
Hayley Joel Osment.
And that story, I've always liked him.
I mean, obviously as a kid,
that performance in The Sixth Sense
is like a top five child performance ever.
Yeah.
And he grew up and now he was in that
shitty Zoe Kravitz movie we covered
and he's a supporting actor in a lot of things.
He's in some Kevin Smith stuff.
It's always good to see him.
To me he always seemed like a really sweet,
like he handled it well.
I've met him, I've drank with him.
He's a nice guy.
Yeah, I believe it.
And then all of a sudden, there's him on a ski lift
and I'm reading through it and I'm like,
he's drunk on a ski lift.
His house just burned down.
That makes sense.
He's getting drunk.
That's what I would do.
And I'm reading through it and I'm like,
Hayley, you didn't do anything wrong.
I'm like, okay.
The news story here is clearly a child star is drunk.
All right, fine.
And then I get to the end and he's doing Jewish slurs
and I'm like, God damn it, Hayley.
Well, he also calls, in the same breath,
calls the guy a Nazi.
And honestly, weirdly, that might save him
because it shows to me that he just was on autopilot
and not making sense and who amongst us.
But he apologized quickly.
I believed him when he said,
I cannot fucking believe I said that.
I don't know what the hell I was talking about.
I believe him.
And I hope he's okay.
That one didn't bother me too much.
I got to be real with you.
But then the next day, what made me laugh
was I see a picture of this kid and I'm like,
who is this kid?
I click on it.
Jonathan Lipnicki is out saying,
it's time for a comeback.
I'm just putting the feelers out.
I'm ready to get out there and start acting.
He saw Hayley Joel go down and was like,
this is my chance, baby.
Who the fuck is Jonathan Lipnicki?
He's the kid from Jerry Maguire.
Do you know the human head weighs eight pounds?
Never saw it.
Oh, Joe.
I couldn't be, let me, I can't put fine enough a point
on how little interest I have in that movie.
I honestly don't think there's a chance
you wouldn't love it.
I am not a huge Cameron Crowe fan.
I think he's talented, but I'm not,
he's not a guy where I'm like,
I got to go see the new Cameron Crowe.
You know, I like Cruz,
but I like Cruz swinging from helicopters.
I usually am not like, let me get Cruz on the ground
and in a living room.
I love Jay Moore and stuff.
And who else is in it?
Zellweger?
Zellweger, Cuba Gooding Jr.
Do you like James L. Brooks shit
or not your thing either?
I could care less.
I don't know.
I mean, to me it's like,
it's one of the great romantic comedies
and I do think you would enjoy it,
but what can we do?
I was going to ask you the other day,
I know your soprano's thoughts,
but have you never seen The Wire either?
No, not out of anything other than I just never saw it.
So there's no stance there.
It's just, you don't...
No, I never tried The Wire.
The reason I'd never watched it
is by the time people were telling me how amazing it was,
it was like four seasons in or something.
I was like, I don't know.
I'm not starting it now.
So I would give it a chance.
Absolutely.
I just never...
I feel like too, if I watched it now,
I would be like, yeah, it's good, guys.
I don't know,
because I wasn't part of the initial phenomenon wave of it.
I think a lot of these shows...
Sure, MTV has gotten significantly better,
or at least it was for a while.
There's been shows that equal it.
At the time, there was like three shows on the air
that you were like, I've never seen anything this good.
And since then, we've had equal.
Now, did Lipnick...
Hold on, we glazed right over that.
Did he...
Was he ever been in anything else besides Jerry Maguire?
He was in some movie that I saw when I was a kid,
which is crazy,
because Jerry Maguire came out when I was like 16 years old.
I have no idea why I saw this movie.
But he was...
I think it was called The Littlest Vampire.
Oh, that's right.
It was a kid's vamp movie.
And I don't know what else he's been in.
Other than my bed.
Yeah, that's right.
I'm dating Jonathan Lipnicki.
Lipnicki. Lip...
Yeah, he was in Stuart Little, like Mike.
But yeah, he just...
You know, sometimes the cuties don't grow up to be so cute either.
My friend, Fred Savage,
looks identical to how he looked when he was a little boy,
but that's usually not the way it plays out.
It is odd, isn't it?
Yeah.
I've never met Fred Savage, but he looks exactly the same.
It's weird.
He truly does.
And it's not even like...
It's like a cute little baby face with wrinkles in it.
It just looks like the same kid, but taller.
Yeah, if Michael J. Fox didn't get hit with the Parkinson's,
he would still look exactly like Michael J. Fox.
Yeah, I believe that.
There was zero aging happening.
Macchio was another one.
He still looks crazy.
That blew my fucking mind.
And by the way, Zapka don't look bad either,
but Macchio, I was like, holy cow.
He's like 63, isn't he?
Yeah, oh yeah.
And no offense at all to Macchio or Zapka,
but you would think if you have a pretty lucrative career in the 80s
and then nothing for 35 years, you'd be living pretty hard.
I would.
I would be devastated that I lost my career,
but they kept it together.
The people who just sit and they're like, you know,
I had my success and I hope it comes back,
but we don't know how they were in the off season,
but that's the healthiest way to do it.
I mean, the people who lose their mind lose hard when they're not working.
I met Macchio.
I think I've told this story on the show,
but Bobby Kelly and I pitched him a show.
Oh yeah, you told me that.
And he played himself in the show
and we were going to be agents that scooped him up.
Because the whole idea was that we had an agency
where we went after those that fell from grace
and realized there was money to be made on these people.
And he liked the idea, but he was adamant in the meeting.
He was like, guys, I'm serious about this.
One thing I will, it's a deal breaker for me.
I walked away.
I did not get booted out.
I chose to leave.
I chose to move to Long Island and raise a family.
That needs to be clear.
And I was like, okay, cool.
We get it.
So maybe that's why he's got money.
Maybe he had the money where he's like, fuck it, I'm good.
Yeah, I believe that.
Now, he was kind of the third lead of my cousin Vinnie.
I think that's the last time I saw him.
Maybe things were cooling down a little bit, Ralph.
But I respect that, if that was your choice.
Why don't we get to that...
Two utes.
Yeah, let's get to that movie corn.
I would like to start, if I may,
with...
Well, first off...
No, see, I shouldn't do that.
Sorry, I'm not going to do that.
Let me bring up my letter box so I know what I've seen.
Can I talk about the Four Seasons on here?
I don't think so.
I watched the entirety of the Four Seasons,
which is a new eight -episode series starring Tina Fey,
Will Forte, and Steve Carell.
It's been getting average reviews.
I would say, especially for a Tina Fey project.
And it just got picked up for season two,
so it's coming back, which is kind of exciting,
because I really liked it.
It is not a masterpiece, but it is comfort television
of the highest order, you know?
Like, I watched all eight half -hours in a day.
I had a really good time with it.
I liked the performances. I liked the stories.
It's four couples.
I watched this movie over the pandemic.
It was Alan Alda written, directed, and starring
in this movie with Carol Burnett.
And basically, it's four groups, four couples,
who are all friends, go on four trips a year,
one each season.
So you have to kind of get past the annoyance
that these people are much richer than you are.
But they go.
The first season, Steve Carell is there with his wife,
played by Kerry Kenny Silver, who's from Reno 911,
also two broke girls, you may remember.
She's a hilarious actress, and she rarely gets a chance
to be, like, front and center.
And she's got a great part in this,
but she's Steve Carell's wife.
These people are all really close. They're friends.
They're like a big family.
Coleman Domingo's in the cast, as well,
as part of a gay couple.
Tina Fey and Will Forte are married,
and then Carell's with Kerry Kenny.
And he comes back the following season,
and he's with a much younger woman.
He's with a woman half his age.
And he's dumped or divorced his wife, Kerry Kenny.
And it just basically goes through
what that does to the friend dynamic.
And the only reason it got made has got to be Tina Fey,
because it's a small story about characters,
and they really don't make those anymore.
But it's really good.
I mean, I think that's a great premise.
To me, that's such a simple premise.
It's not high concept, but that sort of simple premise
has just gone away, you know?
But they wind up being so much richer
when you've got just this little dilemma
that you dig in on,
as opposed to aliens and shit blowing up.
So what this does is it blows up everybody's relationships.
Forte and Tina Fey start bickering
and disliking each other,
and they've been this perfect couple this whole time,
but they start getting insecure.
She's like, well, you're going to do what he did
and leave me for some hot 30 -year -old,
and I'm going to be high and dry.
And it starts bringing out kind of the worst in people.
It's funny.
It's not hilarious.
It's in kind of a fun locale each time.
You know, it's four seasons,
so you get all different vibes in all different locations.
But yeah, if you like that cast and what a cast,
it's pretty great.
I thought what they did with Carrie Kinney
was pretty sad at first.
She goes on the trip and is spying on them,
and I'm like, that's really sad that, you know,
her husband has dumped her and is there
with a hot younger woman,
and now her whole story is like pining after him.
But they handled her character really well.
I knew Tina Fey would not do that.
She always supports her characters,
particularly her lady characters.
I love her writing.
I really do.
I think comedically, she's one of our all -time greats
in terms of her joke writing.
I love her as a presence.
No matter how big she gets, she never bothers me.
I just, I always like her.
And I thought this show, while not 30 Rock,
was really, really entertaining and worth a watch.
Joe?
On topic with today,
I rewatched The Manchurian Candidate.
The...
OG or Denzel?
The Denzel one.
Both great.
Eh, it was okay.
I really loved it when I saw it.
Man, did I love it.
The first time I saw it.
And, you know, it just plays a lot more cliche
than it did when it first came out.
The direction in it isn't quite that interesting.
You know, it's Jonathan Demme.
Demme?
It's fine.
It's, you know, it's fine.
It's, you know, Denzel's great.
Everybody's great.
Sorry, it's Denzel, Meryl Streep, and who's the third?
Lev Shriver.
Oh, yeah, yeah, okay.
And Jeffrey Wright.
Anthony Mackie.
There's a lot of great actors in it,
and everybody does a nice job.
And the movie is plenty serviceable.
It's just...
I don't know.
It's okay.
It's like, you know, it's fine.
It plays, like...
Maybe it's because reality has become so insane
that the concept of this movie is so palatable at this point
that you're just like, oh, yeah, okay, yeah.
Well, they brainwash them.
That's really crazy, I guess.
Whereas 20 years ago, you would have been like,
it was nuts with the subterfuge, you know?
And it's like, maybe that's all it is.
I did think, though, from a directing standpoint...
It's not poorly directed by any stretch,
but my point is Demi is masterful, obviously.
And it played a little more to me like a Ted Demi movie.
It felt a little more like a guy that watched movies of this ilk
and then directed it in turn,
because that's kind of what Ted Demi always did.
You know, blow is...
Without Scorsese, blow doesn't look like blow.
It just doesn't.
Ted Demi, while underrated,
and I thought pretty much made nothing but solid films,
was almost like a cover artist.
You could always pretty much point to the person he was ripping off.
He's like Taika Waititi.
Sure.
He's great at being like, I'm going to make that movie,
and then he does it.
So anyway, you're not going to be upset
if you watch this Manchurian candidate,
but I don't think you're going to be...
Maybe I'm wrong, but I think that is my issue with it.
I think reality has become so insane
that this doesn't play as tragically and shockingly as it once did.
But it was enjoyable enough to watch.
You're friends with Tom Segura, Joe?
I am friends with Tom, and I have done his pod,
and I hope to do it again to promote the release of my special.
Sure.
No, no, no.
I know that question seems like I was about to shit on him,
but whenever he pops up...
I've never seen a stand -up special, I don't think,
although I did see him at the Cosmo in Vegas once,
but I was pretty much blacked out.
I was handed tickets.
But I always like him.
He seems more like a funny friend than a stand -up to me,
but that's kind of the vibe with a lot of the stand -ups these days,
and I like his vibe.
I like him and his wife.
They have great chemistry together, obviously.
Yes.
And he's got this new show, which is called...
I wanted to say poor things, but it's called Bad Thoughts, yeah.
So it's six episodes, half hour each.
It's sketch comedy, but each one leads into the next,
so there's like a to -be -continued at the end of each one.
He is saying it's a comedic Twilight Zone.
It doesn't feel like that at all.
It feels a lot like I think you should leave
or something of that nature.
Yeah.
And I didn't necessarily know what his sense of humor was.
I mean, you see Kreischer and Segura talking and laughing
and having fun, and I'm like,
these just seem like guys you'd want to hang out with,
riffing and talking.
So I didn't necessarily know what his vibe was,
but apparently, judging by this show,
his vibe is really gross and dark.
A lot of shit, a lot of semen,
a lot of people fucking people they do not want to be fucking.
It's a sketch show, so it's going to be uneven,
but when things hit, they hit, and they were really well directed.
There's a segment, a long segment,
where he meets this gorgeous French woman.
She invites him up to her apartment,
and he's like, I can't believe this is too good to be true.
I'm going to fuck this hot woman,
and she takes her clothes off, whatever,
and she reveals that she has a head,
much like Total Recall, growing out of her back,
and it's covered in warts and played by Tom Segura as well,
and she's like, you can't fuck me
until you fuck this creature coming out of my back.
Most sketches are something like that,
and they all go on for absurd amounts of time,
so the ones that really don't work,
I've heard him in his bit about how Garth Brooks is a serial killer,
but when they sketchify it, that one didn't really click for me.
By the way, some Tim Robinsons don't click for me.
That's what sketch comedy is, people have different tastes,
but sometimes the premise would be kind of funny to me,
and then when they would stretch it out for 15 minutes,
it would just keep building and building.
When that's really working, like Family Guy does that well sometimes,
they used to, I haven't seen it in a year,
they just won't let a joke go.
I admired that, like he gets his teeth into something
and pulls every laugh off the bone,
and the show is not perfect by any means,
but I would definitely watch a second season,
and I was surprisingly very impressed by it,
just how dark, how non -PC or whatever it was,
without ever resorting to aren't liberals gay comedy,
which is honestly what I was expecting from it,
which is maybe not fair to him at all.
It had nothing to do with that, it was all like premise, crazy,
it was nothing to do about politics and what's going on in the world today,
and I really appreciated that.
A lot to recommend about the show,
if gross out humor and shitting your pants and etc. is not your thing,
don't watch it, it's pretty juvenile, but it is funny.
Juvenile is exciting right now, we don't get that kind of comedy anymore,
I think that's why I responded to it.
Joe?
Yeah, it's just funny for the sake of funny,
and who cares if it's gross or dirty, I agree.
I turned it on last night,
I only got through the first two sketches of episode one
because I got distracted and I was like,
I don't want to sort of half watch this,
so I'll wait until I have time,
but I thought both were funny,
but I thought the A24 sketch was really funny,
where it's the guy getting his ass eaten by all the old people.
Yeah, it made me laugh.
It's the details he puts in,
where I was like,
to me this is where you can tell a comic did this,
and not just a guy with an idea.
It's funny that he's getting his ass eaten, that's funny,
but the fact that he's laying there and he's going,
spit on it, spit on it,
and that extra gross detail,
that's to me where the stand -up comes in,
is like, no, let's make it the worst version of this
we can possibly do.
So I really like that.
Anyway, I'll do one more on topic with today
and the idea of the terrible future
and technology and all that,
but this one comes from the 80s.
This is George Romero's Monkey Shines,
because this is what Black Mirror used to be.
This is what it used to be.
It used to be like, guys, in the horrible future
they will inject monkeys with a serum
that will turn them into murderous servants.
This is the future I want to be seeing on TV.
They're not giving it to us anymore.
The premise of the film is,
a guy who has a seemingly perfect life
gets paralyzed.
They do a very good job
in the first five minutes of the film
of showing his idyllic life
and then up to the point where he gets paralyzed.
He is fully paraplegic after this.
He has to do the mouth thing on the wheelchair.
He can't move anything.
And his friend played by
the guy that played Ira Buckman on Mad About You.
I can't remember the guy's name,
but he plays his best friend
and who's a scientist,
and he's doing this experimentation
with making monkeys more sentient and aware
and capable of learning and whatever.
And he basically gives him this...
And then he finds a woman that trains monkeys
to help people in disability situations.
So when the two experts meet
and work on the monkey together,
it becomes a super monkey.
And the super monkey then goes to serve this guy
and it turns his life around
and makes him want to live again
because he's suicidal after the accident and everything.
And then the monkey falls in love with him
and begins to murder anybody that stands between them.
It is a wild plot.
Now, for a plot this insane,
the movie is surprisingly well acted.
It's surprisingly well directed.
The script could use a little bit of work.
And it's far more enjoyable than you think it would be.
I was gonna buy...
I was in Waterloo Records the other day
and I was grabbing a couple movies
and they had the Monkey Shines 4K
and I was gonna grab it, but it was like $40.
And I was like, you don't need the Monkey Shines...
Just step away.
Yeah.
But I enjoyed it enough that if it was like 30...
This podcast could be called
You Don't Need the Monkey Shines 4K.
Had it been 30, I would have grabbed it.
Yeah.
So I enjoyed Monkey Shines.
It is...
It's one of those movies where it's like,
it's not a good movie,
but it's an enjoyable one.
That's the best way I could put it.
I saw it not that long ago.
I remember feeling roughly the same.
It's weird.
I mean, we talk about this phenomenon all the time,
but quality control is so gone
that movies you used to dismiss,
when you revisit them, you're like,
it's pretty fucking good.
There's just no quality control anymore.
Oh, and you got Stephen Root in there
playing a sinister scientist,
which he's always great when he plays.
He's great at anything, but when he plays a bad guy,
it's very good.
He's very sinister.
And that guy's name I just remember is John Pankow.
Yes.
I watched my new 4K of a movie I hadn't seen
in probably 20 years, King of New York.
Oh, wow.
Directed by Abel Ferrara.
I like a lot of Ferrara's movies.
I don't think he's ever made a classic, per se,
but he makes great, gritty,
disturbing New York late -night movies.
The Addiction vampire movie with Lily Taylor.
I love The Funeral with Chris Penn and Walk -In.
Miss 45, one of his first movies.
A woman gets sexually assaulted
and becomes like an angel of vengeance, basically.
He's made a lot of really interesting,
kind of thought -provoking shit,
and he pushes the envelope.
He loves, you know, and I like this,
as we all know on the show.
I like a movie where they'll randomly be a naked woman
walking around in a scene in the background,
and we don't even have to comment on it.
And there's quite a bit of that here in King of New York.
It's Christopher Walk -In.
Considered one of his best performances,
and I see why.
There's flashes of his insanity.
The Schoolie Dee does a lot of the soundtrack.
There's a lot of Christopher Walk -In dancing to hip -hop.
That is awesome.
And it feels totally natural
to see this 55 -year -old white guy dancing to hip -hop,
because Walk -In is so fucking cool.
The tagline is great.
Not everyone who runs the city is elected.
It's a former drug lord, returns from prison,
determined to wipe out all his competition
and distribute the profits of his operations
to New York's poor.
So it's kind of like a modern Robin Hood.
Supporting roles, you got David Caruso
back when he played a great little Irish prick.
You got Laurence Fishburne.
You got Victor Argo.
You got Wesley Snipes.
You got Steve Buscemi in a little part.
Giancarlo Esposito.
It just feels super early 90s indie New York.
It's Ferrara working with a little better budget
than he normally does.
And I've seen a lot lately
of people considering King of New York
like one of the best gangster movies.
You see it on lists with Goodfellas
and Casino and Godfather and stuff.
To me, it's very much a second tier.
It's definitely below even a, you know,
a great movie like Donnie Brasco or something.
But it is really entertaining
and Walk -In fucking kills in it.
If you've never seen it, check it out.
Well, that brings us to
the show of the hour,
Black Mirror.
Now we've got, what, six episodes this season,
was it?
Yeah, so like where bad thoughts,
you could watch six episodes in under two hours.
Black Mirror has six episodes
ranging in length from 50 minutes to 90.
You know, it's...
They've lost control in a way.
Too much.
These things have budgets.
Like, just, well, I read,
I just finished the space episode,
the sequel to the episode with Jesse Plemons
and Christina Migliotti and Jimmy Simpson.
And I don't remember anything about that one
except it feeling kind of like Galaxy Quest.
And I remember thinking it was pretty entertaining.
Apparently, they were going to make that
into its own series as of 2023.
They were just about ready to start developing it
and then it fell apart.
Didn't happen due to COVID or funding fell out
or something.
I can't imagine they were going to get that whole cast back
for something so frivolous,
but maybe.
And when that fell apart, they decided to put
all the ideas they had for that 10 episode season
into this movie.
So I understand the length on that one.
I don't.
Maybe we should start there
because that's probably the most high profile
episode.
I don't understand the length.
It was fine.
It was entertaining, I guess.
Jimmy Simpson had some funny moments.
Yeah, at times I'm like,
what is this, like some dumb comedy all of a sudden?
That was strange to me.
The plot is at the end of the previous episode,
which they have to show a 10 minute recap of,
and you're still kind of confused.
I watched the recap twice.
I was like, what?
So the premises is that Jesse Plemence's character
had created an online, massive online multiplayer game,
the most immersive game experience ever.
You put a little disc on your temple
and it makes you go unconscious and go into this world.
It's like the ultimate virtual reality.
They have now, by the way, used this disc,
the temple disc, in four episodes.
It's in this episode.
It's in the prequel episode to this, so that's two.
It's in the episode, five episodes.
It's in the episode where the two guys do VR gaming
and have sex with each other in the VR world.
Striking Viper is one of my favorite episodes of the show.
It's in the episode where, in this season with Giamatti,
where he's got to go back into his memories or whatever.
And then it's in the episode in this
where the lady from Awkward has to remake the old movie.
Yeah, insecure, not awkward.
Or insecure, excuse me.
And herein lies my biggest issue with Black Mirror at this point.
It is so up its own fucking ass.
Once they did the episode where the people went to the roadside museum
and it was all the Black Mirror stuff.
Oh, boy, did I not like that episode of the show.
Oh, boy.
And this is the problem that went,
this was one of the problems that was wrong with the new Twilight Zone.
It's not supposed to be self -aware, guys.
And look, it's Black Mirror, I forget the guy's name who did it,
but he does the whole thing and it's his show.
Charles Brooker.
He can do whatever he wants, but when it becomes self -aware,
it starts to become a podcast.
It's like, guys, this is now just for the diehards.
Yeah.
People just kind of swooping in are going to be a little lost.
I hated in The Beatles when John Lennon was like,
the walrus was Paul.
I hated when David Bowie in Ashes to Ashes is going,
Major Tom is coming.
I'm like, referencing yourself,
why don't you just fold your dick back and insert it into your own ass?
Also, you're David Bowie and The Beatles.
We all love you, except Joe.
You need to accept that, embrace that.
By the way, sorry to interject.
Oh, I love when I'm right.
Big clip going around the social media right now.
Black musician, drummer, can't remember his name.
Billy Preston?
Don't remember, but he's like, there were four drummers in The Beatles,
and Ringo is not one of them.
He did not play on one song.
I've heard that.
And I'm like, oh, spill the tea.
Let's get it out in the open that this band was fucking so overblown.
It's ridiculous.
Paul McCartney, a genius.
George Harrison, a genius.
The other two?
Beat it, boys.
Well, John Lennon's a hell of a songwriter.
As much as he annoys the hell out of me.
Listen to the solo records.
They're terrible.
I like them.
I even like the one with Yoko.
I love double fantasy, and I listen to it all the time.
Ringo is a hack.
I don't know.
I mean, we can't just believe what this guy said on TikTok,
but when I saw McCartney at Dodger Stadium,
he brought Ringo up to play drums.
The place obviously went completely insane.
And he only let Ringo play drums with his drummer.
He didn't tell his drummer to step down.
Ringo's taking the next song.
They both drummed.
And that, to me, was like, oh, shit, this guy might not be good at all.
Biggest band in the world of all time never toured?
Oh, I wonder why that is.
All right.
I mean, it would be fascinating.
It would be crazy with all the written material about them
if no one uncovered that ever until now.
But I'm certainly no Ringo defender.
Anyway, so anyway, sorry.
Back to the plot of this episode.
I apologize.
No, all right.
We should say, by the way, the original was called USS Callister,
and this one is called USS Callister colon, into infinity.
So he's got this thing.
He goes into it.
So he's also doing a thing where he takes the DNA of other people
unwillingly, without them knowing,
and creates avatars of them inside of his own game
that he can control and whatever.
And Christine Miliotti is a girl, his work that he's in love with,
and he puts her in the game so he can sort of control her.
So in real life, he's this awkward nerd developer,
and then in the game, he's this tyrannical Starfleet captain
because the game is a space game.
At the end of that episode, they destroy the Plemons character,
but the people that he brought in to be his crew are stuck there now.
Their alternate awareness or consciousness is stuck there now.
They can't get out.
So this one picks up with them in that world.
I mean, this is...
You know what?
If we sit here explaining the plot of every one of these Black Mirrors,
first of all, we're going to be here until Wednesday.
Second of all, we're going to bore the listeners to fucking tears.
This one in particular is so fucking convoluted.
I mean, without a notepad, I wasn't going to get to the end of it.
It had four writers on the thing.
I mean, I feel like it was written with an Excel sheet open.
It was complicated, but not in any sort of fun way.
I'm like, what am I even following?
Where are we?
At the end, it's like inner space all of a sudden.
They're inside our body.
We're in two different worlds.
I guess I pretty much got what it was.
I was just kind of like, till what end?
Because if you're going to do it feature length,
if you went and saw this as a movie in the theater,
you'd demand your money back.
Don't take 90 minutes of my time and give me this kind of like...
I don't know.
This one is only outdone in the brainless department
by the one with the woman from...
I almost called it awkward again.
What is it called?
Insecure.
You're thinking of Aquafina, and it's coming into your mind.
Yeah, Aquafina.
What's her name again?
Sorry, I'm blanking.
We'll go to that one next.
That one is called Hotel Reverie.
It is Issa Rae, who I loved in Insecure.
She's not good in this at all.
And Aquafina, who I have liked in exactly one thing,
which was the farewell and everything else.
I'm like, ugh.
Every time I see her, I'm like, oh no.
This episode sucks.
Yeah, it's a bad one.
This is about an old woman who owns a film company
that owns all these old movies that are classics.
Doesn't know what to do because she doesn't have the money
to compete in the modern market.
So Aquafina presents to her this new technology
where they can insert a relevant new actor into an old movie
and resell the movie based on that.
And the way they're going to be able to afford the top -notch A -lister
is because they only have to do...
It only takes 90 minutes of their time.
Why does it only take 90 minutes of their time?
Because they put the person into the movie
and the person just does every scene in sequence.
And they have to do it every scene in sequence
as far as I could tell without any retakes or whatever.
So you're supposed to believe that an actor comes in
and has a 200 -page script fully memorized.
At that point, you're just simply making up rules
so that you can tell your story.
You're not making up rules and telling the story to suit the rules.
You're creating rules that make no sense in the real world.
A lot of these things are just mild stretches of believability.
We're heading this way with technology, with this stuff.
It shouldn't feel like this,
but it felt like they were just pulling shit out of thin air.
No actor would do this and nobody would go see it.
Casablanca's coming out and we put Ryan Gosling in the Humphrey Bogart role.
Who would pay to see that?
No one.
And I guess on some level,
it is a commentary on how far things could go
in the repackaging department when it comes to Hollywood
and what Hollywood does.
But my God, for a show that will take 90 solid minutes
so they can spend 35 of those minutes setting up characters
and the plot device itself
before getting into the rollercoaster of the actual story,
this one does none of that.
You meet Issa Rae's character for three minutes.
Next thing you know, she's at the studio.
They're like, so you know what we're doing here?
She's like, no, I don't understand what we're doing.
We're shooting a movie, right?
This is an A -list actress in the show.
I mean, she's playing an A -list actress
who has never stopped to say, who are my co -stars?
What's going on?
It's so insane.
She then goes, oh, well, you didn't get the thumb drive
in the envelope we sent you?
Long story short, it's a life -threatening technology.
Where they have to submerge you into this alternate reality
of the movie itself.
And a million things could go wrong,
and they're doing it all slapped together
and haphazardly and willy -nilly,
just so they can tell the story with some sort of threat
and some sort of, you know, so problems can occur
to create intended drama that doesn't land at all
or intended stakes that don't land.
And you know, I was talking to Pinkstone about it last night,
and we were both saying we hated this episode,
but he was like, I guess they were so careless
because maybe that was a commentary on like,
the people in charge keep declining with intelligence,
and eventually people that just don't give a shit
are going to be running everything.
And I was like, yeah, maybe, and he was like,
but yeah, but they didn't really land that.
And I was like, I know.
If that was their intent, then they would have landed it
with a joke or something.
And that's the problem with a lot of these Black Mirror episodes.
Black Mirror never was a guessing game.
Black Mirror was, there were three phases of Black Mirror.
The first phase was, it predicted what was coming
right around the corner, and it was haunting.
Then the second phase was, holy shit,
I'm watching Black Mirror, and this is happening in real time.
That's freaky.
And now this third phase is, we've got to keep the show going,
and the stories are going to be more dud than not.
In season five or whatever it was,
when they did the whole episode about the robot attack dogs,
I remember I hated that episode,
and I remember again talking to Pinkstone about it,
and he was like, well, I thought it was a pretty cool
action -y kind of Terminator thing.
And I go, yeah, but that's not what we're watching Black Mirror for.
I'm watching Black Mirror for these eerie predictions
about where we're headed
and what technology is doing to our souls and all that stuff.
And I was like, this was just literally just an action thing.
I hear that, but I don't mind that in an anthology.
I don't mind them throwing me different genres or something.
That's fine.
But my point is that was an episode that was so in the minority
that I was shocked to see it.
Now, this entire season, aside from two episodes,
the first episode and the Giamatti episode,
were stories like that.
The second episode is a girl has an amulet
that can control dementia.
I was like, what the fuck is this?
Like, who cares? This is stupid.
There's a suspected serial killer or whatever the hell it was
that I don't even remember what the hell the plot of that one was.
I apologize, guys.
I'm trying to be responsible here in my...
I want to touch on each. I'm looking at them.
It's called Plaything with Peter Cipaldi, the old Doctor Who.
Yeah, that one left me pretty cold, too.
It's stunk.
Did you like that one?
No.
Yeah, that one's like, again, it's a video game.
Journalists, they capture him.
He's telling the story.
Will Poulter is always in these black mirrors,
just playing like a little supporting role in this one,
which is weird because he's becoming kind of a bigger star.
But yeah, it's a simulation game thing,
the kind of thing they've done multiple times on the show before.
One of my least favorites, and to be honest, I watched this a week ago.
I'm not sure I recall what happened.
Beta Noir, where...
You remember that one, Joe?
I mean, if you tell me the plot, I might.
I don't remember by title.
It is the one at the Chocolate Company.
No.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Where they go into the alternate reality or whatever, right?
Yes.
Something like that?
I mean, I'm looking at it now, and it seems sort of new to me.
I couldn't pay attention to it.
I don't know why it was the second episode.
There's nobody in it, and it wasn't good.
These black mirrors, they're becoming like throwing darts at a spinning wheel.
It's just like, what's this one going to be about?
Alternate reality and robot, and they want to get pregnant.
Okay, there we go.
Yeah, I mean, two, three, and four, Beta Noir, Hotel Reverie play thing.
I was like, this is an awful season of the show.
But what we are left with is the two pretty good episodes of season seven,
which are Common People and Eulogy.
Common People stars...
Chris O'Dowd.
As he popped up, I said, you know, I love the IT crowd so much,
and I thought this guy was so great.
And then they put him in Bridesmaids as the love interest, and I was like, perfect.
We're going to get a great comedy star, a romantic comedy guy that we actually like.
And the man's been in nothing.
He's been in absolutely nothing.
He's in a lot of stuff, and it all flies under the radar.
You know, he was in that Christopher Guest...
It's always like a British show.
There's a show where he's got like an imaginary friend or something.
I don't know.
The Christopher Guest show he starred in, the docu...
Yeah, that wasn't great.
And Rashida Jones plays opposite Chris, and they're very good in this.
They play a married couple who...
Now, this is the season opener.
I was like, wow, we are off to a start.
Yeah, I like this one.
And it's got Tracy Ellis Ross as this, you know, the head of a...
It's always the head of a tech company.
But basically, they are...
And it's taking shots at Netflix,
but it's like you need a subscription service to survive.
Rashida Jones needs a subscription service,
and they keep making them update it.
Oh, I see.
You've got the basic plan, and you need, you know, Mind Plus or whatever.
Well, yeah, but hold on.
Yes, the subscription service, though, is based on...
They get into a car accident, and she's basically going to be brain dead.
Yeah.
And this woman comes in and says, look, for a nominal fee,
I can put her consciousness on a server
and feed it into her brain via a device,
and she will be herself again as long as the server is running,
and you pay a subscription fee.
And it's an affordable fee.
It's expensive, but it's affordable enough to them.
And then all of a sudden, they go out of...
They're driving to go to a restaurant, and she goes like blank,
and he doesn't know what's going on.
They find out, oh, the service radius is only this big,
but if you want to be able to go further and not go offline,
you do an upgrade.
And they're like, well, that really sucks,
and we can't afford it, but we'll figure it out.
So they do that.
Then she suddenly starts talking,
she starts doing ads to people in the middle of conversations,
and they don't know what's going on,
and then they go back, and the lady's like,
well, there's ads now on that tier if you want an ad -free tier.
And it is Netflix making fun of Netflix.
But by the way, that bothers me,
because Netflix made fun of Netflix last season, too.
And just because you're calling yourselves on your own dog shit
doesn't mean that it's okay.
That fucking really irritates me.
I hear that.
I mean, it's not Netflix writing the show.
It's them approving it, I guess, but I'm sure they love it.
Of course they love it.
It's making them money.
I forgot that Rashida Jones co -wrote a Black Mirror episode
and a really good one.
She co -wrote it with Michael Schur,
with Bryce Dallas Howard from season three,
and that was the one where you rate people.
You're able to give people, and that was a really good one.
Rashida Jones is basically a screenwriter now,
and maybe because she went away for a bit,
I was pleasantly surprised to see her.
I liked her.
I liked Chris O'Dowd.
I believed their relationship.
I liked Tracee Ellis Ross.
I liked the story.
Common People is one of my favorite songs.
I liked the title.
And while I didn't think this was excellent,
I was like, oh, oh, great, Black Mirror's back, baby, just like you.
And then we went into three just piss poor episodes.
And then the other part of this, though,
is in order to keep up with the subscription rate,
they're very desperate for money.
He's working overtime.
He can't do anymore.
Eventually he gets fired, and he succumbs to going
on to a service that's sort of like an OnlyFans,
where you do terrible shit to yourself for money.
And you drink piss or knock your teeth out or whatever.
And I thought every part of this episode was amazing.
I thought it was the story.
Both of those devices of the servers and the online thing,
the internet thing that he does for money,
I thought all of it was so brilliant.
The two, they made these two different haunting realities.
It's two great Black Mirror's mashed together.
It works.
And then they take a lot of time to introduce you to the couple,
get to know them, whatever.
And then at the end, spoiler alert, she decides she's done.
They can't afford it anymore.
But they can choose when she goes offline, and they do it.
And she dies.
He has to kind of kill her.
But she says, wait till we go out.
Basically she says, when I go into a commercial break, kill me.
I can't do this anymore.
And it's haunting.
It's sad.
It's beautiful.
It's a perfect episode.
It was such a strong opener.
And then as Pat said, then you go into three shit balls.
And then Giamatti pops up.
And why is the Giamatti episode good?
For the opposite reason.
Very simple story, completely character driven, emotional.
Point A to point B, few twists and turns in there to keep you
interested, and that's it.
Yeah, that's a Giamatti showcase.
I mean, you throw some British twat in there.
The episode probably just runs together like everything else.
But I thought Giamatti killed it, as he has done in every
performance he's ever given.
And the episode itself, I think, only stood out in comparison to
the rest of a very lackluster season.
But I did enjoy it, as where it would rank in all of the black
mirrors, probably somewhere in the middle, whereas Common People
is closer to the top.
Everything else is at the bottom, unquestionably.
Common People also feels like such a more complete and whole and
satisfying story at 58 minutes than did this USS whatever the fuck
at 90.
There's a lesson to be learned here.
I would imagine that spaceship episode of the show cost four times
what the other episodes did.
And you don't feel it.
It just feels expensive for expensive's sake, because the story
doesn't really involve you or hook you.
It also, too, is a thing that's been done so many times.
There's been so many parodies and satires of Star Trek.
So many.
And it's just like Christ almighty, like down to Plemons in the
original doing a Shatner impression when he's in the alternate
world.
And you're like, guys, calling the sequel into infinity, that's a
phrase that's been used as ad nauseum in space adventure.
One of the new Star Trek movies was called Infinity.
It just feels like somebody with a cursory knowledge of that stuff
just being like, and then you do this, this, and this, and this.
That's how those shows go.
And it's boring.
It wasn't interesting.
And then you take the Giamatti episode, and it's a guy whose ex -girlfriend
who was the love of his life and he's been very estranged from for many
years, dies.
He has to speak at her funeral.
He doesn't want to because he can't remember much because he's blocked
out the memories because of the pain of them splitting up.
And they send him this device that will go into his memories and help him
find the things to say.
And then as they do that, you realize his story about her and being callous
and whatever towards him is bullshit.
And he actually was the problematic one.
And through all that, he finds reconciliation and shows up to her
funeral.
And there's a beautiful ending to the thing because you see a man redeemed
through what?
Technology, but also his soul and spirit.
It's a very good episode.
Got a Scrooge vibe to it.
Exactly.
So there's your black mirror, people.
I think we were thorough enough with these episodes.
I don't think we need to go too deep in.
But I would say My Hog is down for the season.
It's incredibly up for episode one and episode, I guess it's five with
Giamatti.
I'm in the exact same boat.
I felt the exact same way.
And I think that going forward, if the show continues, and I don't think it
will because it's got to be very expensive to produce basically seven
pilots a year for the show.
It's a whole new world for every episode.
That's expensive.
And the show was in and out of the top 10 within a week.
So this might be it.
But if it were to come back, I think I would switch to the model of I'm going
to see which episodes are the most beloved and watch those one or two.
But I don't necessarily want to waste another 10 hours on another season of
Black Mirror.
There has been some incredible high points in this series.
A quality dip in season seven, I think, is to be expected of any program.
But yeah, it's kind of run its course.
We're just basically like looking through a cliche Rolodex at this point.
There's only so many stories about this kind of thing you can tell.
Anyway, folks, that's it for us.
We will be back.
Well, we've got three coming up this month.
We're reviewing Friendship with Tim Robinson and Paul Rudd.
We have, believe it or not, a guest.
We do it very rarely, but it's always somebody special.
And this time is no exception, the great Joe Ramone.
And we will also be discussing, help me, Joe.
Henry Thomas.
Johnson.
That title will not stick in my brain.
Yes, Henry Johnson.
OK, I watched it today and I don't remember the name of it.
So that's what we got coming up.
I'm on Instagram, never at the Patrick Walsh.
The Miss Pat Show just dropped on, actually, the new season's not out yet.
They just dropped on old fashioned BET, where I don't recommend you watch it.
It's edited and not as good.
But that's all I got.
Joe, you?
Yeah, folks, finally, finally, finally, the release date is here, July 21st.
My new special.
I never promised you a Rose Garden is debuting.
It's coming out.
It will be available for roughly a month prior for early access pay -per -view.
And then it will go out to the general public on July 21st.
YouTube?
Yeah, yeah.
And I'll be soon announcing my new YouTube channel and all that stuff.
So, you know, details to come, people.
Stand by, like the Proud Boys folks, stand by and stand up, whatever the hell he said.
Yeah, what was that?
Something like that.
Yeah, stand by and stand proud, stand tall.
Yeah.
In the meantime, I've got live shows, details to come, but I've got live shows coming up.
June 6th, I'm in South Orange, New Jersey, Saturday, June 6th, I think it is.
After that, I will be in Nashville at Zany's for a few shows.
I, in August, will be in Rhode Island and also in Denver.
Comedy works in Denver, Comedy Connection in Rhode Island, and other dates in September, October, and so on.
Go to joderosa .com for tickets.
If you're in New York City, stop by Joey Roses, joeyroses .com.
Get yourself a sandwich.
That's it, folks.
We'll see you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.