🎵 I'll see you in hell. I'll see you in hell. And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say. I'll see you in hell. You know I will. I'll see you in hell. You know I will. 🎵
And that's where we're going to see you when you join us for the review. Today we're reviewing Dungeons and Dragons. What's the subtitle on this thing, Pawpat?
Honour Amongst Thieves.
I was going to say Thieves Tavern. I couldn't remember.
Thieves Tavern.
That movie would have made half as much if it was called Thieves Tavern.
Why?
Well, I just learned that there was another Dungeons and Dragons franchise, which I didn't even know. Apparently there were three Dungeons and Dragons movies before this, which is why they had to add Honour Amongst Thieves.
You didn't remember the Marlon Waynes Dungeons and Dragons film?
Wow, no. Not at all.
Is he the star?
I believe it's more of an ensemble piece.
Oh, Jeremy Irons.
Yeah.
Marlon Waynes. Look at this.
Maybe I saw it, honestly. I mean, 2000? What do I know? I might have seen it.
Waynes plays, or I'm sorry, Waynes plays. Irons plays the bad guy, I remember.
Well, no shit.
But let me ask you this.
I'm the hero.
And I am going to restore goodness to the valley below.
I come in the man that exudes evil.
Yeah, it really does waft.
But that leads me to my first question about this movie.
Why not, in a world where we're just renaming things the same thing three years later, why not just call this Dungeons and Dragons?
I felt like it made it more confusing.
You don't need the Honour Amongst Thieves. That's not really even what it's about.
Why not call it D &D?
Yeah, that's a good point.
There was another movie called, in 2005, Dungeons and Dragons, Wrath of the Dragon God.
You can't put dragon in the title twice.
You just can't.
Yeah.
These people should all run their movies by me. I need 10 minutes in a conference room before you release each movie and I can solve all your problems for you.
We've got a 40 -word title and we use the word dragons twice.
Yeah, okay. I have a few notes.
And who was in that one, Joe?
Bruce Payne?
Do you know who that is? I don't know.
I mean, hold on. I'm trying to find out if it's a sequel to the Jeremy Irons one.
Or if it's just another...
I thought they made three in that franchise, what I read yesterday, but I don't know if that's confirmed.
Are you a player of the game?
No. I wasn't allowed to play it as a child because my mom said it was a devil game. I had one of those parents.
I kind of didn't, and yet there were certain things like I remember I had a quote bad influence friend who was a little older.
And I came home and said that he was playing the black album for me, Metallica, and that freaked my parents out because I think they probably talked about that on like 2020 or something.
I'm on the wiki.
Yeah.
For the 2000 movie.
And it's not even making mention of...
Oh, wait. Yeah, here we go. Despite not being a box office bomb and critical failure or made for TV sequel, Wrath of the Dragon God was released in 2005.
It's not even mentioning any of the other...
Wait, that's the sequel is Wrath of the Dragon God. You ready for the title of the third one?
Obviously.
The Book of Vile Darkness.
All right, I like that one. I like that one.
I don't recall this movie being released. I honestly don't. Starring Eleanor Gex.
Who's that?
I don't know, Joe.
I mean, oh, it's a direct -to -DVD, not only direct -to -DVD, but British. So like an exclusive British release.
Thora Birch also starred in the 2000 film.
Yeah.
Jesus Christ. Did you know her dad was Jack Birch that was starred in Deep Throat?
And her mom is the woman that was in Deep Throat, Carol Connors? Those are her parents.
I did not know that, no.
Wow.
Wait, the main woman in Deep Throat's name was Linda Lovelace. So she was what, a side performer? Not even the lead of Deep Throat?
Thora Birch's parents are the supporting cast of Deep Throat.
Yeah.
Where's she been? Where's Thora Birch been?
Can I ask, and this is off -color considering we've mostly been talking about dragons up to this point, but
do people like the choking and gagging, deep throating? That's something people enjoy outside of pornography?
People certainly like it out there in the world. That's a big demographic for porn.
I mean, again, I've fallen back into dating a lot again. People will be like, oh, he must want this.
Like, first thing. They're going straight to like, argh. It's like, no, no, no.
Don't you ever say to the guy, I don't like that?
Say, Bruce, baby.
Tell me about this third D &D movie you were in.
Yeah. No, it sucks. Literally. It's just kind of, I mean, it's not everybody, but there's this type of girl where it's like,
I think if you like listen to, maybe if it's girls watching porn and thinking that must be what guys like,
and granted there are guys who like this, but God, it's off -putting.
That's like something you do like 20 years into a marriage because you can't feel anymore.
You know, you can't be busting that out date one.
I have noticed at times that some people are prone to go to certain moves in an almost paint by numbers way from porn
where there's no like organic thing to it. They just do it.
Yeah. It's kind of like if you ever watch somebody, it's like watching somebody dance that's not feeling the music.
You're just like, oh, you just have these moves that you do. So yeah, I hear you. It's kind of weird.
It's also like I finished by the gentleman going slow.
Yeah, you know, slow and I'll say it. I'll go, hey, just slow down.
Like if you go to finish, you got to slow down, you know, but it's like, no, you're a guy.
You must love me. Just, you know, going a mile a minute.
And it's like, no, I feel I feel nothing there. You could do a lot less work and make me feel a lot better.
I don't know. And I, I appreciate a lady guiding me, you know, because everybody's different.
I understand that.
But yeah, it's like this, this sort of like, but wait, you're a guy.
You must love it like this. You must love it violently.
No, no, you're wrong. You're incorrect.
Buck her gently as tenacious D said.
Exactly.
I'm not. Yeah. Once in a while, you know, dad had a couple tequilas.
You know, we can throw down, but come on, let's take it easy.
We're getting to know each other.
I don't mind fast or slow as long as it feels good.
You know, the problem with either for me, that should be the key.
Yeah, I be the key.
I was going to, man, I had something real good to say.
Damn it. I forget.
But, but on a side note, I am on Thor Birch's Wikipedia.
Did you know?
I never even heard of this.
Did you know there was a she was in it for one episode.
There was a sitcom in 1994 starring Henry Winkler called Monte.
I remember it. Yep. Not well, but I do remember it.
Yeah. That was my days of reading TV guide when it would arrive cover to cover.
It's wild, man.
The blood on the sitcom floor is millions, millions.
It's crazy, man.
Like just, just crazy.
Like how many sitcoms?
I miss this.
I miss these days.
You turn on a damn sitcom.
Oh, that's what it was.
I was going to say per your thing about the rough thing.
Shane Gillis, his new special is out.
It's called beautiful dogs.
It's very, very, very funny.
I hear raves. I haven't seen it on Netflix.
It's great.
But he has a bit about that where he talks about porn has ruined, uh,
women watching porn has ruined sex because now two people are trying to do
it porn style in the bedroom.
And he's like, it was bad enough when just the guys were trying to do it.
Now the girls are trying to do it.
You know, he's like, you know, belly to belly missionaries, just fine.
Like there's nothing wrong with that.
You know, it's very funny.
Um, um, but, uh,
the, the sitcoms, let's go back to the sitcoms.
The, uh, I miss that.
What was the, what was the premise of Monte?
I'll tell you Monte.
Uh, American sitcom aired on Fox 1994.
Ooh, just the juicy days of Fox, man.
Well, then it's probably a really racy show.
Uh, Richard's.
This doesn't say where.
Oh, he's always playing Morton Downey Jr.
Is what it seems like a loud obnoxious conservative TV commentator.
So yeah, David Schwimmer is his left leaning son.
That sounds great.
Do you think the miscasting was Henry Winkler as a loud mouth conservative?
I mean, that's, that's not, I love Henry.
Oh, David Krumholz in the cast.
We got to ask him about this.
Holy shit.
Uh, my doorbells, my doorbells buzzing.
Hold on.
Okay.
Yeah, we got Krumholz playing another son here.
Winkler, Schwimmer and Krumholz.
I want to watch this.
This sounds great.
Hope to capitalize on the same dynamic that made All in the Family a success.
Okay.
The danger of that.
And you could just, you know, people say you can't do it now.
You just literally could not.
But the danger of trying to do an All in the Family is that it's such a delicate balance.
And if you err on the wrong side of it, your show is just racist, you know?
And I'm sure that's what Monty and a lot of shows that have tried to be the new
All in the Family have done is you forget the heart and soul of the show
and you just focus on this guy saying crazy racist shit
and you just wind up with a racist show.
It's probably what happened having not seen it.
I called.
Well, I'm surprised though, if that's the case, because it was 94 on Fox.
You know, you're, you're knee deep.
You're in fact approaching the end.
Well, maybe not the end, but you're knee deep and married with children at this point.
Right.
You're in the juicy, juicy years of the Simpsons.
You know, they were pretty.
I think I got to, my guess is it's miscasting.
It's, it's Winkler just, I don't buy him in that role at all.
But I never saw it.
Warmth and kindness.
I think you could find a, maybe the pilot on YouTube, but I've been talking,
and Krumholtz said you guys talk too.
So I'm going to ask him.
I've been talking to him all week.
I called Krumholtz the other day.
He texted me at eight 30 in the morning.
I was awake because I had to go down.
He texted me too, except for me, it's five 30.
I was awake from a cold sleep.
Because I had to go down to PA to look at the house.
And he said, he said, how you doing?
And I said, I'm good.
And we were texting back and forth, you know, and it's like, I miss you, buddy.
Miss you too.
All this stuff.
So I'm in the car eventually.
We're still texting.
I just call him.
Yeah.
And, uh, he's like, Oh buddy, it's good to hear your voice.
Within four minutes of the call, he's like, you're an idiot.
And let me tell you why.
Started talking about the strikes.
Yeah.
And, you know, we were, we were both on the same side on the right side of
history with the strikes, but I offered my opinion for, uh, I think it was
about how I thought that there should be a boycott of services, but you can't
get people to do that.
Cause the average Joe wants to watch his Netflix or whatever.
And he disagreed that there should be a boycott of services.
And I think called me an idiot.
Uh, and then when I said that, uh, normal people don't care about this strike
cause they just think it's rich people.
Yeah.
Pitching a fit.
They don't understand what it is.
He said, will you hang out with scumbags?
I think that's what he said.
Yeah.
Uh, I love it.
I love when the three of us went out to dinner.
Last time I was in New York and there was, there would be like a minute, a
minute that would flare up where it's like, are we going to start throwing
food at each other?
That's the kind of friendship I enjoy.
And then by the end of it, you're all telling each other how much you love
each other.
That's what I like.
Yes.
I love the man.
I had a great time talking to him and, uh, and then his very come to our
New York show, by the way.
So get another reason to come to that New York show of, uh, it's also
windfall.
He told me he's out of town.
Oh shit.
Is he fucking with me?
Um, no, maybe he just didn't put the two and two together.
Also, can we announce who our special guest is or no?
No.
Okay.
Cool.
The one I was working on.
I don't know what's happening.
I'm waiting to hear.
I'm still waiting to hear.
Uh, I was just going to say the special guest is you, the fan.
Yes.
That's all I was going to say.
There might be a special guest.
Let's put it that way.
There will be special guests popping up that night regardless, but there
might be a special guest on we'll see in hell.
So, uh,
Yeah.
We're, uh, one of Joe's songs, uh, there's going to be a special guest
verse by ice spice.
She'll be there, uh, performing, which is very exciting because she's,
she's a big deal.
Ice spice.
You don't even know I spice Joe.
Oh, I do.
Let me, yeah, I'm going to be an artist.
Looks like a clown with a giant ass, a lady clown with a giant ass.
I love an artist that comes out and goes, let me pick the two most
generic overused words in music history.
Yeah.
Ice and spice.
What is she a spice girl?
Yeah.
Exactly.
It's, you know, I was a, I was a kid that grew up listening to nothing
but rap.
And I remember when the joke, when it became like a joke on like in living
color, like to call yourself ice, anything like that was like a running joke
when you did a sketch about rap music was the guy's name was ice, whatever.
Yeah.
Uh, that and, uh, Snoop Snoop, Dizzle Nizzle.
That went on for 25 years.
Good Lord.
It did.
Yeah.
Jesus.
It did.
Um, what else is going on in the movies people?
I, uh, I, well, shit, man.
Did we talk about the Masterson's thing?
I mean, it's, there's not much to talk about, but 30 years, that kid's going
away.
That's it.
That's a wrap there.
I mean, but, but the, the thing to talk about is, did we talk publicly about
Kutcher and Kunis's teleprompter apology?
That was fucking bad.
Holy shit.
I saw this thing.
I mean, the lack of awareness in these celebrities is so stunning to me.
They thought nobody would find their, their fawning letters, praising Danny
Masterson.
They finally get released.
Then it's like, if he was not sent to jail, they'd be like, yep, we knew it.
That's our boy.
But because he went to jail, they do a seemingly filmed on their front porch,
reading off a teleprompter apology, Kutcher and Kunis.
Um, sorry, we didn't know, you know, it's a, we hate, we, and Kutcher runs an
organization helping victims of sexual trafficking, sexual abuse.
Like these people have publicists.
Are you thinking at all?
Just, just stupid.
I know the guy's your friend and I don't know how people don't get that someone
can be your friend and be a piece of shit.
It happens all the time.
Most of my friends are pieces of shit.
And it's that, it's that, but it's also, I said this to you in a text that I
said, look, you're allowed to, to, to think you're, you're allowed to support
victims and then also think your friend is innocent.
That's not an easy stance to take.
In fact, if you're going to take that, by the way, it wasn't just Kutcher and
Kunis, Mary Jo Sperber.
Uh, yeah.
They wrote letters, uh, uh, what's his face, the dad.
I think it's Deborah Jo Rupp.
Okay.
Who's a Wendy Joe Sperber was lady from bosom buddies.
That's what I was thinking of.
Uh, and then the dad is what's his name?
Uh, Kurt Wood Smith from Robocop.
You know, other people did too.
And I would go as far as to say in this climate, if, if, if you truly believe
your friend who's been accused of something, this heinous is innocent.
That is not an easy stance to take.
So you took it.
You took a chance and you have to stand by it.
Yeah.
So stand by it.
That's exactly right.
You don't roll over on the guy as soon as he gets convicted.
Because now it's, it's just so transparently trying to protect your own
ass.
It's so gross.
And God damn kutch turn to the wife and go, Mila, babe, I love you.
Memorize the fucking apology or at least try to do another take.
Holy shit.
Let's get the gist.
And that that's what you got to do.
Memorize your speech and then speak from the heart.
You know, you can't just literally you see her eyes going back and forth.
It's, it's like at a time when everyone is starting to realize, and I really
think this is happening even in like, you know, cities where people are, they
just see the movies as something fun that comes to town and leaves and they
don't care about the, how the sausage is made.
I think everybody is realizing now that these celebrities are shit.
You know, there are so many of them that are shit and people keep getting outed
as being not what you think.
So, you know, don't, don't keep adding to that by giving us generic shitty
apology about something as serious as this.
It's ridiculous.
Then did you see Kutcher and Kunis on Rosie O'Donnell back in the day?
That clip.
What was that?
Kunis starts, Kunis starts telling Rosie about, she's like, yeah, well, I come
to find out, you know, when the show started, Ashton was 19 and I was a
14 year old little girl and I come to find out that Danny and Ashton are
betting on like, who can get with me first?
Like who can tongue kiss me?
And Ashton Kutcher starts going, no, no, didn't know that didn't happen.
The crowd is silent and she keeps going.
Kunis keeps talking about how they kept doing shit to her even though she was
14 and she had to like tongue kiss and make out with people all the time.
And Kutcher keeps trying to shut it down.
Meanwhile, Rosie O'Donnell's like, why would, why would you need to tongue kiss
a 14 year old girl, Ashton?
I don't understand.
And he's like, well, it's like when you act, I mean, actors kiss and she's like,
but only a certain kind of actor would need to tongue kiss, especially with a 14
year old girl.
Rosie O'Donnell just being level headed, just stating facts and Kutcher is
bright red sweating.
Kunis just, it's, there's all kinds of shit like this.
I was talking with Joe last night.
He was talking to me about this Robocop documentary.
He's watching and you can tell the story if you want, Joe, but the, you watch
it in the corner, but I'll wait.
Wait, wait, say that again.
Say again.
Cause I talked over you.
Sorry.
I said I was going to do it in the corner, but sorry.
I talked over you.
I didn't mean to.
Okay.
Well, when you watch these behind the scenes, you know, like American pie
making of a 25 minute, like behind the scenes on American pie, as an example,
you will see some of the most horrific things and then just kids laughing about
it.
That's just, it was the norm.
Was it right?
I don't know.
Probably not, but it was the norm and they'll do things like you'll, and I, I
don't have specific examples, but it'll be an interview with, let's say Clooney
from 99 or something.
He's like, well, obviously, you know, I'm, I'm just a red -blooded man.
Everybody wants to have sex with Jennifer Lopez or whatever.
I've made that quote up.
That's not a real quote, but people will say stuff like that and not
bad.
And I, because that was the culture.
You could say whatever you want it.
It was kind of beautiful.
The, uh, I, uh, I, I w I'll, I'll, I'll start the, I'll start the, uh, what's
it called?
Movie corner.
And I will, uh, review this, uh, docu series.
I have three docu things to do today, but yeah, robo doc, the making of robo
docu series, whatever that very well, I've, I'm watching it on scream net.
It very well may just be a bonus feature from something.
Two of these that I've watched on scream net, I was like these docu things.
I'm like, I think this is just the bonus thing that like scream factory made, but
still it's feature length and it's good.
Uh, this one is particularly well done.
Uh, and it's very long.
It only focuses on the first movie and each episode is easily an hour.
So they really go in deep said the title yet.
No robo doc.
Yeah, I said it.
So they go in pretty deep.
It's very thorough.
It's great.
The, they interview everybody who is alive and breathing that was involved in
this movie one way or the other, every actor, no matter how small the part is
in the film, uh, the only person we don't get to hear a lot from is Miguel
Ferrer because he has passed sadly, but they managed to get behind the scenes
footage of him on set.
Uh, and there's a segment where he's on Peter Weller cause Peter Weller, once
he went into the suit, he was like, you have to call me robo.
I'm not coming out of character and it cuts to old footage of Miguel.
And he's like, yeah, Peter's real great.
Yeah.
Real great plays a mean jazz trumpet.
Lot of fun.
Is he on this floor?
No.
Yeah, no, I really do love working with him.
And I'm like, whoa, boy.
Uh, so there's tons of footage like that.
There's tons of current day interviews.
Like I said, with everybody involved from, from the director, Paul Verhoeven
to everybody and everybody speaks candidly.
Everybody speaks candidly.
The assistant director is just like, you know, paraphrasing, but he's just like,
yeah, Paul Verhoeven is a fucking dickhead.
Uh, but he's like laughing about it.
None of it is scandalous.
None of it is like I'm upset.
He's just like, yeah, he was a fucking asshole.
Uh, can I give you a quick pause?
Joe quick pause to interject.
When I said it was a beautiful thing this time, what that's what I meant is that
people spoke freely and would shit talk to other actors and discuss having
problems.
There's a great documentary on the alien three DVD about the, how, what a
disastrous shoot that was warts and all.
Right.
I'm just saying that kind of reporting.
Yeah.
I agree.
Obviously I'm not saying it's, it's great that, uh, a guy would say sexually
harassing things to other actresses.
That's, that's not what I meant.
Carry on Joe.
I, yeah, I didn't think you meant that.
Um, thank you though.
Uh, but, um, it's just a great documentary and the story Pat was referring to is
Kurt would Smith tells a story of when they're shooting the scene with him,
Miguel and the two models were prostitutes and the, they interviewed the actresses
that played those parts and they even say, they're like, it said we were models.
I don't know.
I think we were hookers.
We're not sure.
Uh, but they're laughing about this story.
Miguel, I mean, uh, Kurt would Smith is, is sort of laughing like, but he says
like, they do the scene and at one point, uh, uh, uh, Paul Verhoeven goes to the
cinematographer and he goes, he goes, when the bitch says this line, where do we
want the bitch over there over there?
And he goes, they're just going back and forth saying the bitch.
And then it cuts to the women and the women are like, he did say that.
He said it so sweetly though.
I just don't think he knew what the word meant.
And I was like, God, that's so crazy.
But then I realized why he said it.
Or I think at least Kurt would Smith comes into that scene and it's one of the great
lines in the movie.
He comes into the scene and he goes, bitches leave to clear the room so he can murder
Miguel.
Uh, and I was like, oh, that's why I think he was saying that was because the line is
that bitches leave and he's like, oh, they're, they're, they're the bitches or whatever.
And he was like, and he was talking about their exit and, uh, but at the same time,
maybe he didn't realize the weight of it, but the women are laughing again, just like
Pat said, I'm not saying, oh, what a time you could say bitch to a woman.
It's just a funny story.
Um, and then right after that, some guy is talking about Kurt would Smith, one of the
crew guys.
And he's like, yeah, he was always humming.
I don't know.
I think the guy's on the spectrum, but wild, just wild.
The, the, the assistant director at one point is like, let me tell you about Peter Weller,
real pussy hound.
He was always fucking in his trailer.
It's just nuts.
It's just crazy nuts.
But, uh, the shoe, it's amazing to me that, that people don't skim through these old
things, these old behind the scenes docs that were shot at the time because they could
bring people down.
And when you're done talking Robocop Joe, I'm going to talk about something we've never
talked about on the show, that Ed O 'Neill video that you and I have both watched.
Oh yeah.
But by the way, scan, nothing.
These are interviews from like a week ago.
They're saying it.
These are new interviews.
They're all just saying this about each other.
They ask.
It's possible.
Weller's retired and it's like, yeah, I mean, I'll just tell the truth.
I'm not even an actor anymore.
Maybe.
I don't know.
He's got the Robocop video game coming out.
It's about to come out where he plays Robocop in the new video game.
Yeah.
They ask him and he's just like, he, he, he goes, yeah, I don't know what to tell you,
man.
Movie sets like a city and your trailer is the house.
And sometimes you bring a lady back home.
That's the docu series starts with somebody saying, nobody in the history of Robocop said
they had a good time working on the movie Robocop.
That's where it starts.
Yeah.
And it sounds intense and hellish and insane, but the beauty of this doc is the stories
are crazy.
It sounded like a hell shoot, but nobody is, is going like, you know, poor me.
It was terrible.
They're all kind of laughing and just being like, it was a fucking scene, man.
Like yeah.
And hey, I wish every movie had an in -depth documentary or book written about it, especially
if it went badly, because there's so few times that Hollywood had let the guard down
and show you there's a, the emperor's new groove, oddly enough, has an amazing behind
the scenes documentary only available on YouTube because Disney has tried to kill it a million
times, but about what a disaster making that movie was.
Alien three, like I said, has it as a perfect documentary where Fincher's just losing his
mind with Fox every day.
And then there's a couple of books.
There's a great one about bonfire, the vanities called the devil's candy.
There's a great one about lady in the water.
That's a, that's a fascinating one because Shyamalan has been this golden boy and everyone's
scared to tell him, Hey, your last three movies have been awesome.
This one is not.
And it's just, it's the best it's, it's about how, you know, people will just suck up to
Hollywood people at the expense of losing hundreds of billions of dollars because nobody
has the balls to say nobody's going to like this movie, dude.
But it's rare.
Hollywood doesn't like that shit getting out.
So I love it.
I would also.
Yeah, go ahead, Sergeant.
No, it's it's it's just it's just wild.
And I was just agreeing with you.
I think that there should be one of these for every film.
But what is the story you just said you were going to tell about?
Oh, oh, the Ed O 'Neill.
Well, I had to, but yeah, the Ed O 'Neill is, um, I don't, I don't watch like long
interviews with people usually.
I don't know what possessed me, but I found this three hour interview with Ed O 'Neill
tracing like his birth to the present and every, you know, going real in depth with
his career.
And I was fascinated by it.
I told Joe to watch it.
It's on the Emmys site, like the Television Academy site.
It's just up for all to see.
And Joe had already watched it.
He was, I've watched it many times, but it's Ed O 'Neill.
He's speaking very, very candidly.
He's like, there's a point where he's talking about a former agent of his and he's
doing like a real gay voice.
That's tough.
You know, he's like, there's several moments where you realize that this is a guy
who has not been affected by, you know, the, the wokening of Hollywood, let's say.
But the craziest part is that he's telling a story about married with children and
Amanda Bierce was, uh, what really at the time, one of the few out lesbians in
Hollywood and she played the neighbor on married with children.
Yeah.
She doesn't get enough credit for that.
She deserves like Ellen levels of credit for that.
I couldn't agree more.
Yeah.
Couldn't agree more.
It's all, it's all only Ellen did it.
And it's like, no, years earlier, this woman was doing it, but, um, maybe they
don't want to call attention to that because there was 8 million lesbian jokes
made about her on the show, but still it's exposure in some way.
She, um, and she's not the villain of the story in my opinion at all, but she
invited, she invited the cast of married with children and a lot of the people
behind the scenes to her wedding and she was marrying a woman now, not that any
of this makes it right, but, uh, uh, a lesbian wedding in 1989 or whatever was
big, it seemed insane.
It seemed like something you were just not familiar with ever seeing or hearing
about, but, um, she's asking everybody and Ed O 'Neill is telling this story.
He goes, so yeah, I find out me and, uh, I think it was Faustino.
Yeah.
Didn't get the invite and I'm like, you're going to invite
everybody on set, but not me.
And here's where Ed O 'Neill's honesty was so like bracing to me is even in just
the stuff that's not the scandal part.
He's like, no, that's just rude.
If you're going to invite everybody and not me a, but B it's just stupid
from a business standpoint.
Cause guess what?
Ed O 'Neill can walk up to the producers and say, get this lady out of here,
get her off the set and they'd fire her immediately.
It was stupid to not invite me.
Like he's acknowledging that he's got more power on the set, but, um, he's
like, I go up to her in the trailer makeup room and I'm like, Hey, what gives?
Why didn't you ask me?
And he goes, she looks at me and she says, Ed, that was a very hard decision
to make, but I just can't have this most important day of my life, this wedding
to this woman I love so much.
I can't have it ruined by you sitting and laughing and making jokes
about how silly it all is.
Well, it was specifically because she was wearing a tuxedo.
You'd laugh at me because I would be wearing a tuxedo.
Yes.
Right.
And Ed O 'Neill goes, and look, the truth is I would have been laughing.
That is silly.
Let's be honest.
A woman in a tuxedo getting married.
This interview was from like four years ago.
It's from modern family.
Like, yeah, it's wild.
It's wild.
He goes, the exact quote, we want to watch all of them.
The exact quote is he goes, he goes, cause she said, if you see me wearing
a tuxedo, you're going to laugh.
Couldn't think it's funny.
And then he goes, cause it is fucking funny.
He yells that at the interview.
He tells the other story too of, I mean, they fucking hate each other, man.
I saw a recent interview with her where she was just like, she was at a con of
some kind and they're like, what was it like working with Ed O 'Neill?
And she goes, I was raised that if you don't say anything nice, don't say anything.
So the next question.
Yeah.
Like they, they still do not like one another.
I don't know.
I'm curious to see if they work together on this cartoon reunion or whatever.
I'm sure they will, but, but yeah, there's another part in that
interview where he's like, he tells about getting into the beef with beers.
And he goes, you're not very smart.
Are you see you have a button and I have a button, but if I push my button, you
get fired and you're like, Jesus Christ, man, like, yeah, what, what he is
describing is it's a, it's a textbook example of what is now known as abuse of
power in the workplace and the entertainment industry.
Like we discuss that stuff all the time.
His doesn't have the sexual element of, if you don't suck my dick, I
push my button and you're fired.
That goes on all the time.
It used to go on all the time, but yeah, it's, it's intense.
And as much as I really love Ed O 'Neill, I have been on these sets where the
dinosaur actor abuses everybody and makes gay jokes that are, oh, isn't that funny?
And you're like, no, man, it's, it's his lifestyle.
Like you, what are you, what are you talking about?
Like, um, I've seen that and you think you're above the law and you can say
whatever because you've been on sets your whole life and everybody caters to you.
Cause you're number one on the call sheet.
Um, so again, I love that O 'Neill.
My guess is he was probably fairly abusive on, on that set in the eighties.
You know, if this is what he's saying to us, the home viewer, it was
probably pretty rough on set, but yeah.
She said that he was very, uh, she says in the interview that he also, that he was
very unhappy toward the end of the show and that she was also directing most of
the episodes, which, you know, I'm sure that was a hell of a clash, uh, you know,
so, um, anyway, all right, there are still actors who like, there are older actors
who like with a female director, like don't listen because they don't feel
that a female should be above them.
That still goes on too.
Well, and I'm not even, I'm not even saying that that was his stance.
I'm saying like, if they didn't like each other and then he's the star
and then she's directing, it's like, Jesus Christ, you're in a, you're in a
pretty layered, uh, scenario at that point.
Anyway, what do you, uh, what do you got for, uh, for us here on this corner of ours?
Well, have I told the very brief tale of my connection to Danny Masterson?
I don't think I've told it on the show.
I was a 2006 or seven or something.
I was a judge at the Las Vegas film festival because I used to be a film
critic and I went out there, I had $0 in the bank, so I couldn't really have any
fun, but every night we would go to a club for the after party after the film
screenings and then we would go to a strip club for the after after party.
And everything was kind of comped.
So it was a great trip.
I got to see all the nightlife of Vegas, but I'm at this club one night.
And since I didn't know anybody there, uh, I was indulging in the free bar
to the extent that I was out on the dance floor, just dancing drunk by myself.
And part of it was that I didn't know anybody.
So I was like, I'm just going to have some fun and I'm out kind of dancing.
And out comes Bijou Phillips, Bijou Phillips, the actress, the daughter
of the mommas and the papas, et cetera.
And I recognized her because I hate to say this, but I used to pause
the movie bully all the time.
Ken, um, what's his name?
Larry Clark's movie bully, which is an excellent movie out these delinquent
teenagers who beat somebody to death and try to cover it up.
And can I say something?
Can I say something?
Bully has a thing in it that I cite all the time.
It's, it's one of the best acting things I've ever seen.
It's Nick stall plays the bully when they stab him literally in the back the first
time, which is quite metaphoric because they're setting them up when they stab
him in the back, he just goes, Oh, and I'm like, that's such a real reaction.
Like it's just, I'm like, God, man, that's so cool.
That's so natural and real how you would react.
Like what it's almost funny.
He's almost like, what the fuck, you know?
Um, the two, the two most real stabbing I can think of a bizarre thing to, to
quote, but it's bully because I remember just being like, am I watching a man
being murdered is how real it felt.
And the other one is, um, Zodiac that's seen at the lake and so when he
stabs that couple that, that to me, I still, when I think back, it, it almost
feels like I witnessed something in real life is how that for that scene hit me.
When I first watched it anyway, I loved bully and there's so much sex in it.
It's Larry Clark, who was essentially a pornographer, but Bijou Phillips has
this, this sex scene involving candle wax that I just used to, you know, it
was, it was my thing for a long time.
I was very attracted to her and I saw her and I wanted to say, Hey, I know
you, but I didn't want to say, I know you from this very provocative movie
because it basically means I'm introducing myself by saying I've seen
you completely naked, so I just kind of smiled and waved and I was like, you
know, did what I normally do, which is not approach the celebrity and instead
she approaches me and she goes, can I just say I've been watching you dance?
You were hilarious.
It's like, okay, not exactly the compliment you want when you're dancing,
but I was like, Oh, thank you very much.
And she's like, would you mind just like, do you want some company dancing?
And she's like, I mean, you're just out here dancing alone.
And I was like, sure, sure.
So we kind of started dancing.
We're talking.
She's funny.
After about 30 seconds, we start making out.
Jesus Christ comes up, this girl comes up to me on the dance floor.
Now this was, this was hot stuff.
You know, I was, this was pre -camera phones and shit.
We're just making out.
I was like, damn, this really worked out for me.
Her friend, this other hot girl comes up, taps her on the shoulder and she goes,
Bijou, what the fuck are you doing?
Like with disgust and she grabs Bijou and they walk off.
And for years, I was like, God, it just made me feel so bad.
It's like, not just, not just stop.
Hey, let's, let's, let's go stop making out with this guy.
It was like, why would you make out with this guy?
That kind of vibe until I realized years later, she's
married to Danny Masterson.
She was married at this time.
And, um, she stuck, she stuck by him.
She was with him at this trial and everything standing by his side.
But now that they're, I would assume getting divorced.
Now that he's going to jail, I hope my phone lights up.
I hope Bijou remembers me from 20 years ago and reaches out because I remember
her, that's all I'm going to say.
All right.
There you go.
Beautiful woman.
Beautiful.
Um, let's go to that movie corn.
We're here.
We're already in it.
I already did my first one.
Oh, okay.
Um, I saw her.
Look, speaking of Vegas, speaking of Verhoeven, I just rewatched showgirls.
I got in my 4k edition of showgirls.
Oh, Jesus God.
You might, I might have to call a sponsor of some kind.
Come on.
You bought a 4k of showgirls?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on.
Well, I love showgirls obviously, but the, um, the 4k had been highly
touted and with good reason it's, it's again, it's an amazing transfer of the
movie, you know, my love of Vegas, anything Vegas is going to, is going
to be a dream for me.
I love why obviously casino or anything set in Vegas.
I I'm there.
I love showgirls and it's because, um, Verhoeven is such a sicko.
Verhoeven pushes everything to its extreme.
And I also think Verhoeven is very funny and it usually takes 20 years until
people realize that his movies are supposed to be funny, a la starship
troopers and a la showgirls, but, uh, and Robocop, you know, people didn't
really see it for the satire that it is until later, I think Verhoeven's
beyond ahead of his time.
I love the man.
He is one of the few directors who knows that a big reason people watch
movies is to be turned on.
And I don't think there's any shame in it.
Um, so I love showgirls.
It's over the top.
It's camp.
You can't tell me that like the way Kyle McLaughlin and Gina Gershon and
people are playing their scenes, they don't know that this is camp.
Um, I think Elizabeth Berkeley's great in it.
I think the movie is sexy as hell.
I think it's got a lot to say actually, you know, in the same way that magic Mike
is kind of this critique of the way America uses people for money.
Um, showgirls did it first, you know, and I love the movie.
If you love the movie, it's a great 4k.
It's got a million bonus features on it, but, um, I'm a fan.
I'm a fan.
I do remember when it came out, it was 96 and I was 16 or 15 and wanted to see
it so badly, but it was that NC 17 and I couldn't get in, but a friend, uh, woke
up in the middle of the night.
This is what you had to do.
People, his dad rented it.
He woke up in the middle of the night, burned a VHS tape because some people had
two VCRs so you could make dubs of your favorite movies.
Um, and he had a dubbed copy of showgirls on VHS that got passed around for years.
And I'm that, that to me, Joe, I think, I think this generation has lost so much
from not having to, from not having to look for things, nothing is hard, you
know, nothing's difficult to access and therefore nothing is special.
I agree.
Excuse me.
Where else?
I remember that now 25 years later, I'm, I'm thinking back to like, we, we
sit almost like I'm a meeting around a table.
Like how are, how are the four of us going to see showgirls?
You know, it gave your life purpose.
It was fun.
It was exciting.
And then you see it and you value it.
You treasure the experience.
Yeah, I, I completely agree that passing around and hiding of porn and porn
adjacent things is, is a lost art form and experience for, for kids.
Uh, I feel bad for these kids.
Now they're just getting it right in school.
I know.
And if I could go a little further and I honestly think it makes you
appreciate sex more because sex is this.
God, I would do anything to see a woman naked at age 15, 16.
There's something really innocent about that.
You know, like what, what can I do to, to like see some boobs or whatever?
Yeah, it's a little sleazy, but like, that's what you're supposed
to be doing when you're 15, 16.
Now it's just full on porn.
Like from, from the day you can access the internet.
And if you're for, if your parents block it, go to your friend's house.
You know, what bothers me about these bum absentee fucking parents is their
kids are getting to the porn cause they're not monitoring their own kids.
And now the porn sites want to do these age verification things.
And it's like, I'm not uploading my driver's license to X vids.
So it's like, so now you dumb ass fucking parents ruined porn for everybody
else because you losers can't keep track of your fucking kids.
It really bothers me, man.
I hear you.
I completely hear you waiting, waiting, you know, 20 minutes for a picture of a
topless woman to print on a color printer.
Also watching the door of my family's office, little office room with a
computer praying that my mom or dad doesn't open the door and see what I'm
printing, you know, that's, that's excitement, baby.
That's that's feeling alive.
Uh, I agree.
Yes.
Okay.
I got, uh, just desserts, the making of creep show.
I can't remember if I ever watched this.
I feel like I must have, but I don't know.
Anyway, this was also on screen box.
Uh, and it's great.
It's a making of creep show.
It's one of the, it's one, it's what I was referring to earlier when I was like,
I think this might've just been the scream factory bonus feature.
And then they put it on screen box, but it's great.
It's really, really great.
Uh, again, interviews with, uh, a lot of people that were involved in the film.
Unfortunately, you don't get to hear from too many of the cast members, but you do
get to hear from some key people, uh, Ed Harris for one, uh, there's a lot of
footage with Romero.
Um, uh, Adrian Barbeau does a lot of interview, uh, in, in this funny enough.
Have you ever in his 40 year career seen Ed Harris smile or even smirk?
That's what's nice about this interview.
He's laughing.
And he's like, cause they're talking about how goofy is dancing is in it.
And he's like, I don't know, man.
He goes, he goes, uh, George just told me to have fun.
He's certainly no help in the dancing department.
So I don't know.
I just had a good time.
I was there as a favor.
What do you want from me?
And he's like laughing.
Um, Adrian Barbeau, such the crush on his wife.
Um, Amy Madigan who plays uncle Buck's girlfriend and uncle Buck.
And she's, uh, she's Kevin Costner's wife and feel the dreams, man.
I had a crush on her back in the day.
They're still married too.
I dated a woman that looked just like her at one point.
Uh, uh, I don't know what happened to her.
Uh, the, uh, but, uh, what the hell?
Oh, anyway, um, Adrian Barbeau once again says, she also said this in
the bonus features of swamp thing.
She's like, I got an offer for creep show.
I had no idea who any of the people were, but my husband, John Carpenter
was like, it's George Romero and Stephen King.
You have to do this, you know, and she's like, I'm not a big horror person.
What can I say?
But I had a blast and she talks a lot about how she did.
She approached that character she plays.
She's great in it.
She plays the drunken wife of Hal Hallbrick, who's beyond verbally
abusive that they eventually feed to this, to this, uh, uh, crate monster.
Um, they get into the special effects, a lot of, a lot of talk from
Tom Savini in this and how they did this sort of stuff.
Tom Savini said creep show was a pivotal moment for him because it
was a chance for him to go from being the king of gore into actually being
a guy that makes creatures.
And he said he really wanted to do that as an effects person.
And this was the movie he got to do it on.
So, um, I really liked creep show quite a bit.
Uh, I mean, I love the movie.
It's one of my top 10 movies ever.
Uh, so seeing this doc was really great and, uh, it's enjoyable.
Give, give it a watch.
Very light, very enjoyable, very fun.
Uh, on the 4k kick, I've all, I've heard nothing but raves about the creep show
4k, which I have yet to buy because it hasn't gone below like 30 bucks yet.
But, um, I was watching, which is, it's a very reasonable 20.
And if you own a 4k player, this should be honestly your first pickup.
Uh, the new Nightmare Before Christmas 4k, it just came out.
Obviously the appeal of this movie is how it looks.
I've always, since I was a little kid, I've been obsessed with
the stop motion animation.
I was so into these old rank and bass specials.
And this it's just a beautiful looking movie always has been.
But the 4k it's, it's a, they call it reference quality, which means like this
is as good as the format can do.
And I would say that's what Nightmare Before Christmas is.
I've never seen it look like this.
Um, there were times I reached out to the screen and I'm not kidding.
Where you're like, man, it looks like you can pick up the things and play with them.
You can pick up Jack Skellington and play with them.
It is so cool.
Um, and I'm wondering if Burton is just great on the format because
he used to use all practical stuff.
Like my, another one of my favorites is Beetlejuice.
The colors on it look so amazing.
The cheapness of the model that Beetlejuice is standing on looks, it's
funnier, but also looks better in 4k.
So I don't know.
There's something about practical effects that really shine in the format.
My issue with Nightmare Before Christmas has always been.
They've got the premise, which is the man who runs Halloween town
is now obsessed with Christmas.
They don't really have the story.
It's not a compelling story.
And the songs, you know, even though they were written by Danny
Elfman and everything are pretty, but they're not quite sticky enough.
They don't, you don't quite remember them.
They don't stay with you.
Those are my only issues, but in terms of visuals, it's one of the best
looking, uh, transfers I've ever seen.
And you got to pick it up.
It's almost like, like a hallucination when you're watching it.
It's really, really cool.
And even though the story leaves me a bit cold, the movie's 77 minutes long,
which is another thing that I've always loved about it.
I feel like all cartoons should be about that length.
Joseph.
Uh, my last one is, uh, what the hell is this called?
Oh, for God's sakes, come on.
Dreams and nightmares, Hollywood dreams and nightmares.
The Robert England story.
This is a documentary about Robert England.
I actually paid to rent this.
It wasn't on any streamer.
Uh, I really just wanted to see it.
Uh, I find what is his level of pretentiousness throughout?
Oh, honestly, almost zero.
He's very, very just.
W but I've heard since I've watched it, I've mentioned watching it to some people
that have worked with him, who I will not name who said like, Oh my God, the guy
is just thinks he walks on water.
And I was like, well, I didn't get any of that from this seems to have a really
wonderful relationship with his wife.
They seem to love each other very much.
He seems to be extraordinarily grateful for this footing that he has in the
business as an icon.
Uh, I gotta tell you, you know, and it goes through his whole career.
He's in a ton of movies.
I never knew who he was in pre Freddy that I was like, Oh, I want to see that.
One of them is a Clint Eastwood movie.
Uh, or I'm sorry.
One of them is an old Burt Reynolds movie.
And he tells a great Burt Reynolds story where he shoots Burt Reynolds in the
scene and the air blast blows Burt Reynolds to pay up in the air.
And he's like, he's like more Robert England is mortified.
Sure.
That like, he's going to get like fired because nobody knew Burt Reynolds
were to pay whenever.
And he said, like Burt Reynolds pulled him in the trailer and was like, that
was great kid, don't go easy on me.
Come right at me in this thing.
Like maybe love Burt Reynolds even more.
Um, so it was, you know, the one thing I, I really, the one movie I really,
want to see with England that's from this is the Toby Hooper, uh, the one he
did after chainsaw massacre.
I want to say, I want to say dead or alive.
I think it's called, um, I'm blanking on it.
I'm going to try to pull it up, but they talk a lot about that movie.
And then obviously the meat of it is Nightmare on Elm street.
They managed though, to pull some information in the interviews that you
know, I've seen times already, so I thought it was still worth the Eatin'
Alive is the Toby Hooper, Hooper movie.
I still thought it was really worth the watch.
Uh, I really enjoyed it, you know, and I guess I don't need to shit on anybody,
but the one irritating thing is there's, you know, when they get to Freddie
versus Jason, they're, they're obviously talking to the Kane Hodder.
Yeah.
And again, from Kane Hodder, the goddamn story about how he was supposed to play
Jason, but they didn't, you know, call and I'm like, Kane, this movie, I mean,
he can't help who, what they're editing in, but it's like, guys, this movie
isn't about him.
I get it.
He wanted to play Jason in the movie.
He didn't get the part.
Like we've heard this over and over again.
Uh, why is it in Robert England's documentary?
So, um, anyway.
And it's not told, it's not in there with any sense of like, cause Robert
didn't go to bat or Robert should have, it's not anything like that.
It's just the story of him not getting the part.
Cause the studio didn't want him because he wasn't tall enough and that's it.
So anyway, it's a, it's worth a watch.
It's a fun watch.
Uh, I watched the outsiders colon, the complete novel on 4k.
Um, look, I'm excited about the new Coppola movie like anybody else, but I, I
do whenever I revisit his stuff, that isn't Godfather conversation, Apocalypse
Now, Bram Stoker's Dracula, for sure.
I'd include in that list.
The man's got a lot of movies that just don't hit, you know, they're just not
great and I'm not even talking about his, uh, his lost period where he's doing
like Jack with Robin Williams and stuff.
Um, I, I never liked the outsiders as a kid, you know, I, I liked the book, I
guess, S .E.
Hinton's book, but I want the, the documentary on this is pretty interesting.
It was a, a grade school class of kids who wrote a letter to Francis Ford
Coppola in the early eighties.
And we're like, this is our favorite book.
We want somebody who won't mess it up.
We love your films.
Would you please direct this movie for us?
And Coppola read the letter.
He had never heard of the book.
He saw it out the book.
He was like, you know what, kids, I'm going to make this movie for you.
I love that story.
That's, you know, probably no other movie has that journey to the screen.
It's very cute and interesting.
Um, the movie leaves me a little cold.
You know, it's, it's, it was always a 90 minute movie.
And, uh, Coppola said, Coppola now releases different cuts of
every one of his films, you know?
But he said, people had asked him for years, you know, why did you
cut so much from the book?
He said that was simply Warner Brothers looking at the movie and saying,
look, this is a movie for young people.
Two hours is probably a bit long.
Let's make some trims.
So the complete novel is just what it says.
It's the entire book, which was shot and it's about two hours.
So it's about a half hour extra footage.
I didn't know the movie well enough to know what's new and whether or
not the footage added much to it.
I just think the movie is pretty corny.
Um, the original version of it, Coppola's dad did the score and it's very like,
even Coppola says in the thing, he's like, look, my
dad wrote the music, but he goes, it's too schmaltzy.
The movie comes off as too like manipulative and emotional and schmaltzy.
So he replaces all that music with like fifties music, like Elvis
and stuff like that.
And you know, it just plays like a little period piece.
The outsiders is nowhere near as effective as like standby me or other similar
movies where it works is as a showcase of all these people who in a few short
years would be the biggest names in Hollywood.
Tom Cruise, Patrick Swayze, Rob Lowe, uh, C.
Thomas Howell, Matt Dillon, Ralph Macchio, Emilio Estevez, Diane Lane.
You know, it's an amazing cast.
Um, I just think the outsiders is a very average movie.
It's not, it's not a primo Coppola and it's not some great coming of age
movie either, but worth a look, you know, it's got some interesting stuff in it.
I think the extended really does the movie to service.
It's, it becomes too weighty.
Meaning it does.
Yeah.
Uh, I like the original, um, you know, about our rumble fish, rumble fish.
I'm just saying why beautiful.
That's even arts here.
Who?
Yeah.
When you're a kid, you want like, like everything's dramatic.
It's like when you're a kid and you watch John Hughes movies, they don't seem
corny because like, that's what it feels like you're like, Oh God, I'd do anything
to date this girl, whatever it may be.
Um, but yeah, this outsider stuff, this greaser lifestyle is just so
unrelatable to me, like, you know, putting grease in your hair and walking
around with a switchblade comb and getting into fights is like not anything
that I can relate to at all.
So it just doesn't hit the same way.
Other movies might.
it's also something that people could relate to for five years.
Yeah, exactly.
It's a, it's a small demographic of inner city kids.
Uh, and I guess some of it is farm country rural, but it's a small
demographic of kids and it was a phase that didn't last that long.
And they made so many movies about it.
Like, uh, you know, the wanderers and that streets of fire and stuff.
There was all these like gang movies.
It's very weird in the eighties.
Um, let us get to our picture at hand, which is Dungeons and Dragons, colon
honor amongst thieves, uh, starring Chris pine as our hero, Michelle Rodriguez
and Hugh Grant as the villain.
Hugh Grant largely plays comedic villains these days.
And I gotta say, I'm here for it.
You know, if, if it's between Hugh Grant, uh, mugging and Jeremy
Irons doing the same thing he's been doing for a hundred years, I'll take
Hugh Grant, I still find him funny.
Um, as for the plot, you know, like I said, not a Dungeons and Dragons
guy, it's essentially a quest movie.
You know, there's not much sense talking about the plot.
It's, it's a quest they're trying to get from A to B.
It's like Lord of the Rings.
You know, they just go from set piece to set piece fighting dragons or, or
encountering magicians or wizards or whatever else.
Um, the tone of the movie is what I would say sets it apart.
They said a big influence was like Monty Python and you feel that there
are funny bits in the movie.
I think the guys who did it, um, uh, it's actually the kid from freaks
and geeks, uh, and Jonathan Goldstein, John Francis Daley and Jonathan
Goldstein are writing partners.
They did game night, which I think is one of the best comedies of recent years.
It's a very, very funny movie.
Um, they also did the vacation reboot, which I think is very underrated
while not being great, but that's the difference between this and other
Marvel movies, uh, sword and sorcery movies that come out lately or whatever,
is that it's essentially a comedy and at times, you know, bordering on that
Monty Python style of broad comedy, which Joe, we'll see if you appreciated that.
I didn't mind it because I hate this kind of movie.
So the comedy I thought at least was pretty solid.
Most of the time, I just didn't give much of a shit about the movie.
What'd you think, Joe?
Uh, well, I watched it on an airplane and I remember texting you immediately
and saying, Hey, I'm watching Dungeons and Dragons.
It's surprisingly very good.
Maybe we can do it for the, for the, uh, show if you feel like it.
And then about 30 minutes later, I texted you and said, nevermind, you know,
I'm going to stick it out, but I don't want to make you watch this.
And then you, you said, well, I'm going to watch it anyway.
So here we are doing it, but look, it starts, it starts truly funny,
like truly funny, uh, not just we're going for the gags.
Like I was like, that's Chris pine is, is, is very good at his timing is good.
His delivery is good.
Like he was a Ryan Reynolds type, you know, so the opening scene where, where
he's like, you know, he's, you know, been captured or, you know, whatever.
And he's kind of pleading his case and he keeps talking about, well,
now when Jonathan gets here, he'll be able to explain to you guys that
that's a funny scene for sure.
And like, even before that, when he's in the cell with his partner played by, um,
uh, Rodriguez, yeah, Rodriguez, Michelle Rodriguez, uh, when he's in the cell
and the, and the new prisoner comes in and he's like, let me give you the tour.
There's the bucket we urinate in and that's pretty much it.
Like there's it's really funny.
And then like you said, he's telling that story to the, to the probation
board or whatever it's called.
And he keeps going, they, they keep telling him Jonathan's not coming.
He keeps depleting with them that Jonathan needs to be there to give them
the, to, to help, because it's, it's the fairest way for them to plead the
case because he has sympathy for them.
Um, but like 10 times, almost like a family guy bit, like he's, he's
narrating a story and then it'd be like, and again, if Jonathan were here, he'd
really love this part of the story.
It's a very funny thing.
Yeah.
And then Jonathan shows up and he's like an Eagle man or something.
Also, yes.
Yeah, a giant, a man size Eagle named Jonathan is unquestionably funny.
Right.
And then they grab Jonathan and crash through the window and he, because he
has wings, flies them to the ground.
And then they are free.
So, uh, that's how the movie starts.
They're busting out.
Here we go.
So it's all to a good start.
Uh, at this point though, is when I immediately start to realize,
you know, they never call, there is no threat.
It bothered me that immediately there's no threat from them busting out of a
prison, you're expecting it to be like, the clock is ticking as they have to
achieve this goal of theirs, they also are up against the fact that they're
being hunted down by the captors and, and, and they don't do that.
And you're kind of like, okay, well, I guess it just didn't matter.
Then who cares?
Uh, the plot or main focus of the characters and protagonist in the movie
is he wants to get back to his daughter, who he was taken from his wife died.
He wants to get back to his daughter.
When he finds his daughter, she is in the custody of Hugh Grant, who was one
of the members of their thieving gang who promised to take care of her.
Uh, you find out that Hugh Grant in fact betrayed them, which is why they got
caught and that he's filled the daughter's head with lies about her father.
And so now Hugh Grant, basically, did you find it Hugh Grant wanting
to raise somebody's daughter?
Were you going to a place of like, is this going to be him fucking this girl?
Or, I mean, obviously that's not the tone of the movie, but you wonder why
somebody it's an odd motivation for a villain to like want to raise someone
else's daughter, you know, it's weird.
I think it was just, it was just, I just took it as, you know, that's, that's
big in like the, some of these, that, that style of movie, you know, we haven't seen.
You don't see a lot of air or whatever, right?
Yeah.
They want somebody to teach.
They want an apprentice, you know, I'll never have a child of my own, you know,
I've grown, you know, whatever it is.
They always want the firstborn child and the deal, you know, there's
always some thing like that, but anyway,
I just think making Hugh Grant's character infertile or impotent, you
know, one line about it might've helped that for me.
Like I always wanted a daughter, like just, it's easy to say.
But carry on, carry on.
All right.
It weirdly was a big question for me.
Like why would this like 50 year old, like fun, loving guy want to
raise somebody else's daughter?
I don't get it, but okay.
That I get the idea of raising a child disgusts me.
So I don't understand what he gets out of it.
That I get exactly.
But, uh, the plot of the movie from here, and I can't quite remember if, if Hugh
Grant manipulates them into doing this, or if they do this just so they can
eventually best you, Hugh Grant, but the plot of the movie is, is they have to
pull off now this impossible heist, which involves finding this relic that
can bring a human being back from the dead and they have to put together a
new crew and it goes from there.
And I gotta say, it goes nowhere from there.
None of it is interesting.
None of it is that dynamic.
You're never in fear for anybody.
Um, it's the whole goddamn, this is one thing I don't get.
The movie is lit up like a goddamn Christmas tree.
Dungeons and Dragons was like mysterious and, and I never got to play it, but I
knew enough about it to know it's mysterious, it's dark, it's cool.
The cartoon adaptation of Dungeons and Dragons in the eighties was a cooler
approach to Dungeons and Dragons than this was it was darker, it had, it had
more edge, it still had some humor, but this seemed to me to put comedy first.
And then in moments where you really wanted comedy, it wouldn't do it.
So for instance, Michelle Rodriguez is talking throughout the movie about how
she broke up with her husband and her husband is no longer, uh, I don't know.
They, they hint that it was not an easy breakup and, and that it's not something
that anybody should ever bring up to her because it's so painful.
So, you know, and it's something that also that her character
really just needs to get past.
So, uh, eventually there's a moment in the movie where, uh, amidst their travels,
they come to what turns out to be her old home.
And, you know, she's like, look where we are.
And, you know, there's like, you know, Chris Pine kind of, you know, there's
like this shrug of like, oh boy, don't, don't go into there and see him because
it's just going to bring up too much and blah, blah, blah.
And she's like, I'll be fine.
I'll be fine.
And she goes to the door, the door opens and the man opening the door, who, you
husband or lover or whatever you want to call it, is, I don't know, a foot and
a half tall or two feet tall.
It's, you know, and that's the first gag is that this big sort of brawn, uh, like
warrior woman who's super tough and who's, who's, who's ass kicking ability
has been established throughout the film was married to this, the guy that she's
heartbroken over is like a foot and a half tall.
So that's the first guy you're like, all right, that's pretty funny.
And then on top of it, it's a cameo.
It's Bradley Cooper.
And I got excited.
I was like, oh, this is going to be really funny.
This is going to be really funny.
And no, I'm so glad you're bringing this bit up.
What was this bit?
It's what was the bit?
Well, my point is it's not a bit.
It's a, it's a pretty serious scene where they have this conversation
about how much they loved each other.
And I'm like, guys, you're going for gags throughout this entire movie.
This is a gag.
Do this as a gag.
Don't do like, I thought, well, the bit is okay.
It's, it's one of the most handsome guys in Hollywood, Bradley Cooper,
but he's only a foot and a half tall.
Okay.
Great comedic premise for a scene, even though I generally do not like
celebrity cameo comedy CCC, but he's a straight man.
I, and they paid him a million dollars for the cameo guaranteed.
Just what, what was the point?
Like talk about a scene that could have been edited out of the movie.
The only reason it's in there is because it was played by Bradley Cooper.
They give him no jokes, no comedic angle to the scene.
I completely agree with you, Joe.
I was like, why is everything in this movie funny except the scene
that seems designed to be funny?
I, it was very, very confusing.
One now one, one bit that did work very well was when they go to summon the
dead bodies to find out where this relic is, that scene was straight out of
Monty Python, a great scene.
Yeah, it was great.
It reminded me too of, uh, of like labyrinth.
Yep.
Jim Henson, labyrinth.
And, um, yep.
You know, and you say labyrinth, Joe, I didn't, I didn't hate the movie.
My, my favorite aspect of the movie is the fact that even when they use CGI,
which is probably most of the time, there was a handmade quality to it.
So especially when they get that giant fish out of the water and that's like
a robotic, that was practical effects.
They have this fish and they bring this dead cat out or the, you know, bring
this cat back to life that the fish had swallowed or whatever that scene.
It really kind of warmed my heart because I thought, okay, here's some
guys who, even though the studio is probably making them do all CGI, they
took a few moments to make like fun, old fashioned, uh, effects.
And I liked, I liked some of the creature designs a lot.
The scene, and it made me laugh too, but the scene where those
walking brains walk by them.
And the guy's like, be careful.
They, they sense when, when mental energy is strong around them and they
strike and the brains walk right past them and the crispines like, well,
that was kind of hurtful, whatever.
There's funny bits throughout.
And I really liked the creatures.
I really did.
I thought they had like the fat dragon.
I thought was funny, like a big overweight dragon.
My issue with it though, is that when the fat dragon comes out, they
cut to Michelle Rodriguez going, that's one pudgy dragon.
It's, it's four wisecracks when you needed one, you know, it's, I don't
need wisecracks as a dragon is about to kill them, you know, it's, it's.
They don't, they don't, it's a weird thing.
You know, I, even though they're going for pure comedy, there are moments
where you have to sell the drama and the suspense and the action and
you can have people quipping.
This is a common complaint of movies these days, but this is, this is always
my two hour and 15 minute movie.
You can't do a two, two 15 comedy.
Um, your action beats have to land your suspense speeds and story beats have
to land and they don't, when everyone is quipping the whole time, like
their Chandler on friends.
Well, this is, this is, uh, my issue with, you know, this type of movie.
Uh, usually this is why I don't like it.
This is why, you know, this is why, uh, the, the, the, the, you know, you, you
already said it, I'm just going to echo what you're already saying, but it's,
it's putting, ouch, it's putting humor before everything else.
And that's just all there is to it.
Uh, you know, it's just that that's what it is.
So it's, you know, and everything suffers because of it.
So, you know, unfortunately, what's weird is that game night, which is a big, a
it's serious beats more seriously than this movie does, you know, and that's
why game night succeeds so well as a comedy is like, they strike the balance
perfectly, they strike the total balance perfect and it is frustrating.
Like nobody wants two hours and 15 minutes of quips.
No, you have to, you have to, you have to strike a better balance than that,
especially because your jokes are funny when they hit, they're funny.
It's not, it's not like, you know, Marvel movies where like, nothing's
making you laugh out loud.
This had some great bits and I think those would have hit harder if it was
around it, took itself more seriously and the serious beats would land harder
if you didn't pepper them with constant comedy.
It's just, they were, it's the movie to me is like a three out of five, but man,
there's, there was so much potential for it to be more.
And since it lost money, I don't think we're going to get a sequel, but I
referred a D and D to most of the superhero movies I see, um, simply
because I liked the vibe.
I liked the sense of humor.
I liked Chris Pine and whatever.
Everybody seems to be having fun, but yeah, it's, um, it's ultimately
just not the hit that you want.
It kind of leaves you wanting more.
So, well, does it work for D and D fans?
Are they like, this is accurate to the game?
I doubt it.
I mean, also though, and tell me if I'm wrong.
What, were there any dragons?
I don't remember there being any damn dragons there.
Well, there's the fat dragon and then there's like two more that pop up,
but briefly you're right.
It's like maybe, maybe two, three minutes of dragon time, which is crazy.
Yeah.
And you mentioned the fat one.
I forgot about that, but you know, I don't know.
I I'm curious.
I don't know enough about Dungeons and Dragons.
I'm curious if the anything in this movie, and this is what I started
to wonder as I was watching it, I started to wonder, is anything in this
movie even from Dungeons and Dragons?
Right.
Like, or is it just, you know, one of the, one of the people I know that
I saw review this was Emily Gordon.
She not review it, but she, she left a pretty glowing thing on Instagram about it.
And I thought, well, Emily is, is certainly like, you know, a pretty reliable nerd.
So, you know, if she likes it, I'm imagining there's there's stuff that's
to the actual brand or references to the actual brand in the books or whatever
that I'm not aware of, I don't know, but it all just seemed a little too bright
and a little too fluffy and none of it really ever seemed too threatening.
Um, so it was really, really tough to tell what was what.
I don't know.
Um, anyway, my, my hog unfortunately is down for Dungeons and Dragons.
I did not like it.
Yeah.
Um, my hog would be down, but in that stage where, like, if you, if you were
in a move, like say you're Jason Siegel and forgetting Sarah Marshall and you
fluff it, like you jerk it to where it's plump almost hard and then go, all right,
we're ready to shoot the scene.
That's where it's at.
Um, it's still hanging, but it's plump.
All right.
Because I did enjoy certain aspects and I thought it had honestly more laughs
than most comedy releases these days, which is, you know, not that big a deal.
But I thought what's, what was funny about it was funny indeed.
And I liked it.
Um, but overall, uh, you know, not for me, we're going to be back
with a special episode for sure.
We're planning on doing talk to me at some point.
Um, of course we're going to be doing the new Exorcist and we'll go from there,
I think in the new Insidious.
So, you know, just keep up with your horror and we'll, we'll get back to you.
We're making some, we also have, um, we also have two more Q and A apps coming
your way, uh, cause we didn't have, you know, we couldn't get through all of
them in the first two, so that's happening.
And then we also have an idea for a theme app that I believe we are going to do.
Uh, and that may be this month or next month.
Killers of the Flower Moon coming out October 20th.
I think it's safe to say we'll do that.
I'm trying to read that book now, by which I mean, I'm on page five as
I have been for a year and a half.
Uh, all right.
Uh, folks come out to the live show October 28th, Arlene's grocery, uh,
us salsa windfall, esoteric and seven elves, our face, stumble bums, other
people, 80s dance party, good times.
And I am on the road with dates starting this weekend.
Evan on New Jersey, followed by Toronto, Ontario next week, followed by, uh,
November 9th I'll be in, um, well, October 28th, we've got to our show.
And then November 9th, I'm doing a show for the New York comedy festival
called selected readings, where I will be a KGB bar in New York city, where
I will be reading excerpts from my audio book that I just did with, um,
a special thing records.
Uh, I will be November 11th at the theater of the living arts in
Philly, November 17th, Pittsburgh, PA.
November 18th, Buffalo, New York, 30th of November, Denver, December 1st,
Phoenix, December 3rd, Salt Lake city.
Hope to see you out there.
And as always come by Joey roses, Joey roses, nyc .com open seven days a week.
And all tickets and info for my shows are at Joe DeRosa .com.
That's all I got much everybody.
See you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.