I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, and when the sound of your screams becomes
a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say, I'll see you in hell, you know I will.
I'll see you in hell, you know I will.
Folks, it's We'll See You in Hell, the podcast where we talk about movies, movies, movies.
I'm Joe DeRosa. And I'm Patrick Walsh, and we're doing two Satan -themed pictures today.
The first is called Late Night with the Devil. Yes. The second is called The First Omen. Yes.
Now, in two separate episodes, you're not getting both in the same episode.
Correct. Don't let these people think that we're giving them a two for one. No.
Because that'll be it. That'll be, that'll be it. We gotta do that every time then,
because that's how - Mousa Cookie, she's gonna want a whole cake.
That's how capitalism works. It is. Joe, you said you're in a state today. What's the matter?
It can't be that sharp haircut. Thank you. Haircut is nice.
I have a nice man cutting my hair. He's very sweet. You know, I saw a thing. I saw an interview
with a scientist, a reputable scientist. Yeah, excuse my coffee sound. Your what?
Can you hear that? My coffee loudly brewing? No, no, I can't hear it at all.
Okay, good. I saw a panel, clip from a panel with a reputable scientist, and Neil deGrasse Tyson
was also on the panel, and they were talking about physics and all that. And the subject of,
do we live in a simulation came up, and a staunch, a scientist who is a staunch believer that we,
there was no way we were living in a situation, was on a simulation, excuse me, was on a project
researching this and said, I have changed my stance completely. We have discovered binary code
in the layers of the cosmos. I believe 100 % that we are living in a simulation.
Hearing that from a reputable source, seeing that it's gotten zero traction in the media,
whatever, it's just this piece of information floating out there that nobody seems to care
about because, you know, it's not about what's happening in the new Snow White movie or whatever
the fuck people are arguing about now. And then realizing, what if we do live in a simulation?
None of this means anything. Why am I even trying? I don't even understand the point,
like it hit my existential thing into high gear, kicked it right into high gear. I'm now
simultaneously panicked about my mortgage, you know, not panicked, but worried, you know,
concerned about my mortgage and paying the bills and retirement and all those things that you're
concerned about. It's always a good sign when you have to decide between the words worried,
panicked, and scared to describe your mood. Yeah, I'm not quite panicked, but you know,
that's a good day for me. Panicked is a good day. So I have the normal concerns and anxieties
of a man my age or a person my age and the things that you should be concerned about that
sometimes keep us up at night. And then that's being met equally with it doesn't matter.
So you want to talk about your head being in a fucking tailspin right now and then couple all
that with I'm 46, I live alone. Yeah, I spend way too much time alone. Yep. I'm like,
is it over? Am I not gonna, is there not gonna be a companion at this point? Am I just gonna kind of
navigate this all by myself? I don't really want to, but I don't really know how else to do it
I've done it this way for so long. And then, you know, just, just the aging, it's just a,
it is a, it is a whirlwind. So I find myself, you know, it'd be a midlife crisis if you were
going to live to 92. I think if this is the midlife, I think this is it. I think I'm,
I think I'm officially having the midlife crisis. I try, I think about writing and I'm just like,
I have all these great half written ideas. I'm not sitting down and working on them. Right. I'm
working on my new standup enough, like more than I'm working on anything else. And I'm happy with
it. But like, I should probably be sitting down more with that, you know, and I find myself night
after night, like if I'm not, if I'm not going out to do a show, or if I'm not out getting drunk
with friends, the nights are spent home. You cook dinner. And then I don't even like, watch,
you know, one of the movies on my movie shelf, or play one of the 9 ,000 video games I've accumulated
over the years, or read a book. I just put on like, I'm like watching TV, like I'm coming home from
a day at the factory, like where I'm like, I just can't even process anything right now. I'm
exhausted. And I'm like rewatching Married with Children reruns for like this 20th time now,
because I'm like, it just comforts me and I don't need to think and I don't care. It's terrible.
It's a terrible, I don't like where I am right now. And I know we've talked about this before
in the past, and I'm not trying to lead us down a road of everything is so terrible and all that.
It's just, it's man. I'm just like, I can't get that charge as to what are we supposed to be doing?
No, I hear you. I hear you. With this movie collection, and I whittled it down,
I sold off a lot of out of print stuff and valuable stuff. And I was like,
no, I'm just going to really sit and watch this stuff. I have not been doing that. I watch,
uh, honestly, lower than Married with Children reruns. I'm watching like TikToks. That's where
my brain is at. Like just zombie out TikToks, quick little jolts of adrenaline, little jolts
of humor. That's about all I got time for. And then I do have projects, but they have all been
in the waiting stage for so long. I've lost my own excitement for my own projects
because everything takes so long. Just read a big article today about how
it used to be the one thing that would get a project sold was a big actor.
And now there's all these major projects, Meryl Streep, De Niro, just getting passed on by the
God, it's just, so the fears are very real. The fears are very real, but things, things change.
Things change. You know, as Donna Michi once said in the only David Mamet movie,
nobody's ever seen things change. Donna Michi playing an off the boat Italian man.
I've seen it. It's a terrible movie. I think it's supposed to be charming. And you're like,
Donna Michi's Italian guy is not, it's not very good. It's like,
this was a, this was a weird window where they thought a Michi was going to be Fox office.
He was in everything because they were like, well, he's going to die in three to four years.
So let's really load them up with projects. And then like, like, like a year after that,
he guest starred on a golden girl. Like it was, I mean, we're talking like it's the wild west now.
It was the wild west then too, because it was like, well, if you were an 80 year old actor,
yeah, it's always going to be the wild west. There aren't a bunch of them. Yeah.
How are you doing, Pat? I puked out all my stuff. How are you?
Well, I'm all right too. You know, I'm, I'm fully back in therapy. Uh, our buddy, uh,
no, I shouldn't, but I've been looking at, um, AA not in a, I've bottomed out, actually haven't
had a drink in a bit, but just, uh, I've had a few friends had a great deal of success,
kind of making sense of their life. And it's like, when will this anger and this bitterness
and this resentment all go away? And it's like, that's part of AA too. It's not just about like,
I'm drinking 20 drinks a day. So I'm looking at that. I'm reading materials. I'm doing all
these things that you, that a man might start to consider at this time of life, but I'm, I'm,
I'm totally with you. And for me, I have my dad sitting there as a permanent reminder of what a
life of solitude can lead you to, which is basically insanity.
Now, but folks, just if I could interject what Pat means by that is his dad is sitting
right behind him right now. I had him stuffed as a reminder. He's, uh, just, I propped him up here
at the table. Speaking of TikToks, I watched another, it's a reason I used to watch, uh,
intervention and stuff as well or orders because it's an immediate boost to your own self -esteem.
Yeah. But I saw this TikTok of a woman who had four cats and as you watch it and she talks about
her cat, she keeps talking about her, uh, her spirit cat or her heart cat. Like the, the cat
met that she knew was like her partner in life. And little by little, as you watch the video,
you realize she's had this thing stuffed and she's dancing around the house with it in front of her
living cats, uh, who have just gotta be like, listen, bitch, we're still here. The favorite
is the dead one. Like, give me a fucking break. Yeah. Um, but, but speaking to what you were
saying about the AA thing, uh, I can relate to that in the sense that, uh, I sometimes will do
this. I am not a religious man. Uh, I have a, I would, I would say a fair resentment towards the
in some areas towards the religious upbringing I had. Godless is how I often hear you described.
Yes. We were members of the church of Satan and sure, sure. And if I had to kiss that statues
rump one more time, folks, uh, no, I, I, I get the hole, son, get the hole.
I have some, some compassion and, and fondness for the religious upbringing. And then I have
some resentments. It's like anything else, but I am not religious is the greater point,
but I will sometimes, especially in New York, cause the churches are so beautiful.
I will sometimes go sit in a church, not pray during the day, not during a mass,
just go sit in a church, admire the architecture for a bit, and then just take in the solace of it
and just be like, this is a, this is a calm place. Like there's, there's, there's a soothing
something in here. Uh, and I think there are, there is great value in utilizing an institution
like church or AA or whatever. Yeah. Sometimes in, in, in an unorthodox, uh, way that, that it
wasn't necessarily intended for, but, but, but you can kind of hit it from another angle and still
get great value out of it. Yeah. Um, my therapist was like, I shouldn't make it into a sex thing,
but she's like, it tends to be extremely helpful for men. And you'll find a lot of men in there
saying like, I really tried to avoid this cause my dad did it. Um, and people just start talking
about their families and how growing up around somebody who's very volatile and sometimes drunk
and sometimes not, whether you know it or not, has a massive effect on your psyche and your
relationship with drugs and alcohol and et cetera. So, you know, I got the book, you know, the
original, my name is Bill AA book, which you can buy for like five bucks and it's supposed to be
like a great read. I also got, who's that guy that teaches you how to quit drinking? I actually,
your old pal, Nikki Glaser, I saw, uh, some brush and she was Alan Carr,
Alan Carr. Yeah. She said she read this book and she was like, I just stopped drinking. I was like,
oh, okay. And then I talked to a few other people who had the same thing. Maybe is that Pete's
deal to that book? Excuse me. Uh, no, I don't, I don't think so. I think Pete
probably got some God shit in his something like that. But, but I might be wrong. I'm sure
Pete is very familiar with that book. I read the smoking one. Yeah. And it did help. Yeah. Uh,
I still smoke occasionally. Uh, but, uh, you know, I was also never, you know, look, the problem I
always have with this stuff, you know, I was talking to Dan, uh, Soder the other night,
very, if you don't know him, very funny comic. Um, did he quit drinking? Is he, he's been off
beer and on to Soder, but he, yeah. Uh, but he, uh, he, um, uh, uh, he's been, we were talking
about cigarettes. He's been off cigarettes for years and years. Yeah. And I said, yeah, man,
I was off for, uh, two years and then I started smoking again, kind of like an idiot.
Yeah. But I said, you know, I don't know, man. Yeah. He was like, you know, I've been really
itching lately and I know I can't do it. And I said, yeah. I said, well, I'm just kind of like,
you know, I'm just kind of like, I, you know, I, I'm just, I don't know. I've kind of resigned
to the fact to that. And it's just like, okay, I'm going to have a night here and there. Maybe
it's even once a week where I have some drinks and I have some cigarettes. I'm not smoking every day.
I know it's still not good for you. Whatever. I just, I don't know. I just don't worry about
it as much as I maybe should. And he said, he said, um, he goes, I wish I could do that.
He goes, the second I smoke, I will be smoking like a pack a day. Like I'll be fully in and
whatever. And that's always been my issue with this stuff is I abuse things without question,
but then I talked to like, you know, a definitive person that has an addiction issue and they're
like, no, no, no, no, no. You don't understand. Like this is my intake and there is no compromise.
And I was like, you know, I'm, so it's, I'm not making an excuse. It just always makes it tough
for me to fully go, I'm done. You know, uh, because I hear you. I don't know. It just
complicates it. That's all. I had been off drinking for several weeks and not having any
sort of issues, no cravings, no nothing. And had one really irritating experience in my life.
And I was immediately back to the level, you know, like just hard. That's my issue is like,
I need some other, I know people discuss meditation or something, getting you the,
you know, it can actually get you to the same place as being drunk after a while. It's like,
no, it can't. That's really a stupid thing to say, but yeah, you'd, you'd take, you know,
you drink a whiskey, a tequila, whatever it may be. I do immediately feel better. That's the allure
of drinking or you get high, you immediately feel better. A meditation, you feel sort of a queasy,
half -assed version of better. You're proud of yourself maybe for not taking the easy way out,
but it takes longer. It's harder. It's not as satisfying. Um, it's just not it, you know,
unfortunately, unfortunately, but I, like a lot of people, if I take a long time off,
I find I return to the same level I dropped off at. Oh yeah. I don't, I don't return with like
a Corona and go, all right, I haven't had a drink in a month. I'll have one Corona light
and call it a night. I go, I'm back bitch. Yeah. That's my, that's my thing is what I'll do is
I'll go off for a while and then I'll have one drink the first night and be like,
eh, I don't know. And then the second night you're like, well of a couple.
Yeah. And then the third night you're back. Yeah. Um, well when you eliminate hangovers,
which is pretty easy to do if you just sort of drink a few nights a week and
it's like staying in shape, but the opposite of it, keeping your drinking in shape,
you don't get these hangovers when you don't drink for a while. And then you have three,
especially at our age, you wake up feeling like dog shit. Yeah. And then you realize that the
hangover is there to keep the average person from doing, from making this a daily hobby.
But as soon as it becomes that hobby, it's like, well shit, it's almost like having no consequences
until you wake up at 43 and you're like, oh, now I just sort of feel vaguely depressed all the time.
I wonder if that was all the drinking I've done over the course of my life.
Yeah. I think about that a lot. Yeah. About that a lot too, Joe, but the, with my shit,
I bet if I'd never had a drink, I would not be fucking on top of the world right now. You know,
you can play what if forever, but I could have never had a drink. And then that means I didn't
go to a bar two weeks ago. And then that night I would have got hit by a bus. You know, you can
live your life like that if you want, but it's stupid. I always had terrible depression. I was
at anxiety. I always said, you know, a certain, certain amount of confidence, you know, I always
had ideas and things, but I was never, as a, as a, as a kid, I was, I was fucking hated everything.
Like I, this, this version of me now where people are like, you know, you're a curmudgeon,
you know, I'd like to, I'd like to think that it's more lovably grumpy most of the time. I know
sometimes it gets into a dark place, but, but who knows? But anyway, I was always like that. You
know, my friend Andrew said to me once we were, we were 20, we were like 20. Yeah. I was working
in a record store called Rainbow Records. And I, and I said to Andrew, I was like, everything on
the new release rec sucks. I hate it. Yeah. Why does all this new shit suck? And I was like,
I go, are we already at that age? Do we already hit the age of these kids today? I mean, we're
only 20, 21 years old. And he was like, no, we thought that stuff sucked when we were 14 too.
And I was like, you're right. Like some people are just wired like that where like you look at
what people are into, you look at what's going on and you're just like,
God damn it. It, it bothers me for better or for worse. It bothers me. So I was always wired
like this. I think, I think it truly is for better or for worse. It's for better in that you don't
just blindly accept crap from the masses, but worse in that you just miss out on a lot of enjoyment
of life. And, uh, you know, I found myself when I was 25 or something, I'd be like, ah, that
fucking sucks. Whatever, man. People would be like, why you didn't like that? And then you have a
fun conversation. And now if you're the guy at the party being like, ah, it sucked and everybody's
talking about it and laughing and loving it, you just seem awful. Like they just, nobody wants to
hear your size. Well, we all enjoyed it. So go be negative somewhere else. Yeah. Um, but I don't,
I don't like a lot of stuff. You don't want to be the guy who hates everything new, but then I'm
like, no, things are worse now, but every one of us guys has said that down through the ages.
Yeah. Things just get worse over time. I don't know.
Yeah. Well, speaking of that. Yeah. I got a news psycho. We're off to a hot start today.
Yes. Um, Matt McCarthy sent this to me, our dear friend, Matt McCarthy. Yes. Uh,
sent me a thing from variety. Uh, and I actually, I actually, I, I went, uh, back and forth a little
bit with Matt yesterday about this story, cause I wasn't sure how I felt about it. But then I thought
he, he sent it saying this could be a good news psycho. And I, and I went back and forth on it.
And then I realized because I was questioning it, it would, I think it would be a good, a good news
psycho. Uh, anyway, it's from variety headline reads the Blair witch project cast, meaning the
original cast. I read that. Yeah. Uh, asks lions gate for retroactive residuals and meaningful
consultation on future projects. The directors and producers of the groundbreaking 1999 horror film
release a separate statement in support. We believe the actors deserve to be celebrated for
their enduring association with the franchise. Now I won't read the whole thing, but the short
of it is a Blumhouse. Oh boy. No wonder Joe spired up. My faves, uh, announced that they plan to
revive the franchise with a new movie that would provide in the words of lions gate motion picture
group chair, Adam Fogelson, new vision for Blair, which that will reintroduce this horror classic
for a new generation. There is no new, let me just, I'm going to sidestep a lot in this.
There is no new vision. Okay. The new vision is you show an old movie to a fucking young person.
Do you understand this people? Do you understand you can revisit things? Yeah. Fucking sick,
sick, fucking capitalistic swine that have to rent wrench every fucking dollar out of something.
These people are sick anyway. By the way, let's reboot the thing. People are so stupid and so
uneducated on their film past. They could rerelease the Blair Witch project with the same ad campaign
of we found this footage in the woods. Uh, it was shot in the mid nineties. That explains why it
looks so shitty, but we really think this is legit. I mean, you have the internet of course,
but you could rerelease pretty much the same exact movie with the same campaign.
Yeah. And, and, uh, you know, dude, oh my God, it's just, it's just wild. And by the way, by the way,
I agreed with the actors in that article and I thought it was going to be, let me read,
let me read what their thing was first. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But, but, but I want to hear,
I want to hear what you say, but, but let me, let me just, for those that don't know
the, so the property has been acquired by, it was acquired, uh, by lions gate in 2003. Yeah.
They did not produce or distribute the original film. Uh, now did they do book of shadows?
I think so. I think they did. Yeah. No, no, no, no. Book of shadows was pre 2003. Um, okay. So, uh,
you're right. I was in college. Uh, it's so the statement on behalf of the actors lions gate
Blumhouse announcement sparked a strongly worded response via social media from Leonard, who was
contacted him or his co -stars about this project in advance. At this point, it's 25 years of
disrespect from the folks who've pocketed the lion's share unintended of the profits from our
work. What feels both icky and classless. Uh, they shot and improvised the independent movie
over roughly a week on a shoestring budget. They each received $300 ,000 in a buyout,
but the movie went on to gross 248 million worldwide. Uh, in 2002, the actor sued
artisan entertainment for using their likeness and names in the 2000 sequel book of shadows.
In the most recent statement, uh, they are looking to get payments equivalent to the sum of what have
what have, what would have been allotted through SAG -AFTRA had we had prior, sorry, proper
union or legal representation when the film was made. Okay. So that's the gist of it. Go ahead
and say what you're going to say now. Well, no, there's a few things. A, those three actors
getting a $300 ,000 buyout for a movie that came out in if memory serves 1999 is actually pretty
good. I don't know what they got in terms of residuals, but like if you're acting in an indie
movie, specifically an indie movie, that indie 300 K for your performance is not a bad payout.
No, but you're getting into this thing of them improvising it and of the quality and believability
of these non -actors performances. Uh, that's what made the movie work. That's what made a skeptic
America go see this and fall for it and believe it because of the actress performances. And I,
if I was a juror, I would want to look at how much of the story was shaped by their improvising.
And was it a curb situation where we had the story laid out ahead of time and they improv
improvised in that framework or did they really make up plot points? You know, that,
that should all be looked at, but it does get into a weird thing where now 20 plus years later,
they're still making money off this shit. Should the original actors be compensated?
Will the actors from Blair Witch book of shadows suddenly put their cup out for some money? Where
does it end? So it is a juicy, interesting subject. And I don't really know where I fall.
How about you? I, I, I, excuse me, as much as I think these studios are disgusting, uh, barnyard
animals, uh, I actually don't overall side with the actors on this for one reason.
Show me the contract. The contract is what you signed. Now, now you could argue,
I didn't have proper counsel or representation. And had I had that, I wouldn't have signed this.
Okay. That's, that's fair. But if you signed a contract, you signed a contract. Look,
I was in grand theft auto five. I was paid $3 ,000 per day for two days, $6 ,000 total.
It might've even been less than that, but at the most it was $6 ,000 total for a character that
they, you know, like any actor, you're handed what the character is.
You bring your own stuff to it. You ad lib certain things. You don't, you stick to the
script on other things, whatever it is. Uh, that's what I was paid for. I signed the contract. The
game made $1 billion. Right. Uh, I can't go back now and say, where's mine? I signed a contract.
I could theoretically go back and say, there were not law rules and laws in place for people in my
position doing mocap for video games back then. There are now that needs to be retroactively
serviced. Maybe then that would be an argument. But what I'm not seeing in this art article,
and unfortunately, this is very indicative of things like this these days.
I was victimized. I wasn't given a fair, whatever. Okay. But what did you sign?
That part of it doesn't ever seem to be introduced into the story. There's no part of this that is
saying the contract stated they could not use our likeness. And they did because if they had that
bull in the, in the, in the chamber, I'm assuming you'd fire it. Yeah. What I'm assuming is, is they
signed a bad fucking contract and here you are like, okay, well guys, I, you know, it sucks.
But, you know, you, by the way, I've heard way worse stories. I mean, I would have thought,
I didn't, I didn't hear that $300 ,000 payout part. Like, like I'm saying, I would have thought they
made $30 ,000 to appear in this. Like they, they got a decent payout on the movie only cost 10 grand
to make. Right. Now, aren't they saying though, that they think they should be consulted going
forward on the projects? Yes. Which is a little weird too. I don't think they were writers on the
first one, but I don't know for sure. Well, the writing thing is again, this is ambiguous. It's
like guys, you know, I stopped going on commercial auditions, like TV commercials. I mean, why?
Number one, I don't really have an interest. Number two, nine times out of 10, they ask you
riff in the room and they take what the actors are riffing and they put it into the script
and somewhere in the fine print, they're getting away with it. I'm not partaking in that. I don't
want to do it. So I don't, again, I don't know what the deal and agreement was that said, you know,
is there something that said, you know, that where you, is there something stating that you
shouldn't have ad -libbed, but you did. And if you, and if it's proven that you ad -libbed,
you should be compensated on the writing or whatever, that's all contractual shit,
but it is not illegal or unethical to have actors ad -lib in a movie. Most of the Apatow stuff
that makes it to the screen is probably ad -libbed by the actors. It's not illegal to do that.
It's not illegal to have your actors riff. It comes down to legally what was agreed upon.
And I'm not seeing anything that they agree. I think it's batshit that this cast is saying
they should be fairly compensated as consultants on all future. That's like.
Yeah, it's weird.
Mark Hamill being like, you have to consult me on all Star Wars projects. Like what?
It's weird. That's what I was thinking along these same lines the other day is I was watching,
I married an axe murderer and the movie we've discussed it on this show before. It's funny.
It doesn't necessarily work as a movie, but if you look at a lot of these star driven comedies,
and I'd even go through the step brothers era, you know, I'm talking that whole run from like
Ace Ventura to step brothers and beyond. We often would not even have a playable script,
a workable script. So I married an axe murderer with Rob Morrow in the lead that came out in that
same year. Like the movie would have been unwatchable. So what's more interesting to me
is these actors like a Jim Carrey, like a Mike Myers, who are basically told to show up and make
the movie work as a comedy. Like those guys deserve those $20 million payouts, I'm realizing,
because they often made the movie. If it's like just the movie is Mike Myers being funny,
then he's providing the work of almost everybody. They're showing up and turning
the camera on and just he's got to make this work today. And I think we don't have those
movies anymore. And a lot of the reason comedy went away is we don't have those actors anymore
who you could rely on to show up and improvise something that's hilarious every day.
I don't think Drew or sorry, Jim Carrey. Yeah.
Jim Carrey said when he was doing Me, Myself and Irene, he was like, yes, he was like, guys,
there was like, there was giant chunks of the script that just said, Jim does something funny
here. And I had that just in the big Wayne's World oral history, which they did for premier
magazine or something. That was when I first started getting an inkling that Mike Myers might
not be such a charming guy to work with. But Dana Carvey was like, he got really pissed off because
he got the script and it was carefully scripted stuff for Mike to do. And Mike Myers had written
the script and then it would say Dana does something funny. So I do think, you know, we've
gotten away from that, which is a positive, but also I just don't think we have the comedic talent
to sustain it, which is a shame. It used to be as long as you had the framework, they could get you
there. But I mean, we barely have the framework anymore. Here's the thing too. This is going to
sound shitty. I realize it. I'm sorry. But well, two things, you know, James Earl Jones,
uh, you know, what was his payout for Star Wars? That's what I was getting at in multiple interviews.
People have been like, you must be just, that must've made your life. He's like, no, what do you mean?
He's like, it paid $5 ,000. That was it. That's the contract. What was his payout in the recent
thing they gave him? Do you know that? I don't know. But the point is, is like before the prequels,
before any of that stuff, he was like, no, I made five grams. Like, yeah, that's what it was. Eddie
Van Halen in an interview, uh, talks about how he played the solo on beat it and never got credited.
And they're like, what do you mean you never got credit? The records it's on thrill. Like this is
what he's like, man, we had a, we had a rule in Van Halen. You weren't allowed to do side projects.
He goes, Quincy Jones called me and said, come down and do a solo on this black kid's record.
I liked the song, so I did it. He goes, I kind of rewrote the song too. Uh, and he's like,
and Mike liked it. So, you know, that's what it was. Like, you know, like he's not sitting there
going, so it boils down to what kind of person you are. I mean, he, yeah, he, I don't even know
if he's a smart person for doing that, frankly. This is the, this is the part I'm getting at.
Yeah. And this is where I'm going to sound like an asshole. Uh, Heather Donahue or whatever name is
McDonald, Donahue, sorry, who has now changed her name to Rye Hance.
Okay. Uh, has 40 followers on Twitter, 810 followers on Instagram or no, 3 ,400 followers
on Instagram. Um, not a sign of your value, not a sign of your value, but, but an author and whatever
she's doing her thing. The other guy that led the charge, Leonard, whatever his name is, Michael
Leonard or whatever, you know, has like 11 ,000 whatever. Here's my point. Why does this thing
seldom come from somebody who has seen other success? Why is it always somebody who, where
it's like, Oh, I didn't know what you were doing. Yeah. Coming out of the shadows, no pun intended
and being like, I want more for the thing I didn't get. And it's like,
yeah, we all do. It sucks. It sucks. They have contracts that are meant to fuck us. It sucks.
But, uh, you know, I've been, I've been teetering on a month away from broken,
homeless from the bulk of my career. And even I had people in my life saying to me,
we know it's not likely, but just in case this thing goes on to make $300 million,
you have to put in language that protects you. Is it your fault that you didn't have people telling
you that? No, it's ignorance. It's youth. It's whatever, but it is what it is. If you didn't
have people telling you that and you don't have that contracted, then there's nothing you can do
guys. And if you have contracts that stayed otherwise, show them to us. But it doesn't seem
like that to me. It seems like a bunch of people who were in a thing, who were no longer happy with
the payout because the money has run out. And maybe the current thing, I'm not saying they're
failures or anything like that, but maybe just maybe the current thing isn't going quite as well
as they had hoped. We're all getting older. We're all having the crises that I was talking about
and you start scratching your head and going, wait a second. I don't know. I don't mean that
in a callous way. I don't mean to say that anytime somebody points a finger, it's just for monetary
gain or self -interest or whatever. I'm just saying in these, the one guy I've seen do this,
who's massively successful is Chappelle. And I'm friends with Dave. I'm not knocking him,
even though I don't agree with this. But when he was doing the thing about Comedy Central and my
name and all that stuff, I had the same response. It's like, dude, I want to support you here. But
if you signed a contract, you signed a contract. What are you going to do? But he's the only guy
I've ever seen, maybe not that I can remember at least where it's like, I don't know. Am I making
sense or did I just sound like a dildo? You're making sense. It's a complicated issue. I liked
that they asked Lionsgate to do this Blair Witch grant, which is $60 ,000 for unknown or aspiring
genre filmmakers. I think that they went out of their way to make sure it wasn't just them
trying to line their pockets. Well, let me just say this to that. It seems odd to me that the grant
is about the amount of money you would need to shoot a low -budget, 48 -minute stand -up comedy
special on video. Guys, 60 grand to an aspiring? 60 grand? Why isn't the ask for the grant a million
and maybe your ask is a little bit lower? It's all just kind of fishy to me. I don't know.
That said, I'm not taking up for fucking Lionsgate. They're going to make an 18th
movie next year, whatever the fuck they're doing. It's a thorny issue. I would just say,
don't skimp on your lawyer. If you go into the entertainment industry, they all take 5%,
so make sure you get a good one. Number two, watch any movie about a musician's rise to stardom.
That should be how you look at your contract. Every musician got screwed over
by somebody in the 50s or 60s or 70s. You got to read this shit because they are trying to
get you and they're trying to make it confusing. Also, something they do with my lawyer is when
my lawyer pushes back, they call me and cry and make it seem like my lawyer is being mean to them.
They do all these manipulative tactics and it's just shitty. Let's get to that corner.
Yep. One positive story is on opening night on Netflix, whenever it dropped,
I saw this thing called Baby Reindeer. I said, what a dumb title. What a terrible poster this
thing has. What is this? It was actually such a bad marketing campaign that I looked it up.
There was one review from Scotland and nothing else. Netflix did not even submit Baby Reindeer
to critics. It is amazing. I watched all seven parts of it in one night. It's seven and a half
hours. Some go a little longer. It starts out as a dark comedy about stalking. It's the guy's
real life story. He was a aspiring standup, a decent standup Scottish. Eventually, he took
his story to the Edinburgh Fest and it was a story of him being stalked that goes to very, very,
very dark places. At first, you're like, okay, dark comedy about a guy who has a stalker.
It's a heavyset odd woman that comes into his bar. He's a bartender and she's just fixated on him.
Over time, the story just gets more and more involved and deranged and the guy himself becomes
not as sympathetic a character as you are thinking. I'm fascinated with this dude. He
really turned the lens on himself and made himself just as dark and complex a character as the
stalker. It's not anything you want to read any spoilers about and it's something you don't want
to start at midnight because you're going to watch the whole show in one sitting. The good news is
I put it up on Letterboxd and I was like, this thing's fucking amazing. I hope it catches on
social media because Netflix is not doing it any favors. Sure enough, a week later, it's become
this huge phenomenon. Not a great thing that's happening is people are trying to find the real
villains of the piece. They're trying to track them down and expose them.
Can everybody shut the fuck up and sit down?
No, I know.
In addition to the stalker, and I'm not going to spoil it, but there's a really
disturbing twist that happened in the story but also in this man's actual life. He makes a real
point of not naming who this person is that did this thing to him. People are not just saying,
I think it could be this guy which destroys lives, but I found who the guy is who did this.
And the filmmaker, the writer is coming out and being like,
guys, you're not correct. You're accusing an innocent man of horrific crimes. Stop playing
detective on this fucking show. It's my life. If I wanted to say who did these things to me,
I'd say it. That's a weird dark thing that's happening with this show, but it's fascinating.
I mean, the reason that people are so hooked on this and busting out their little magnifying
glasses and so forth is because it is incredibly effective. I highly, highly recommend it.
And honestly, shame on fucking Netflix for not releasing something so unquestionably
well -written, well -performed, well -directed, just an A across the board piece of entertainment,
and they don't release it to critics. That's what I don't get. I get that this thing with no stars
is not going to catch the world on fire right off the bat, but send it to critics. Give it a
fucking chance. I don't understand the most wealthy corporation in all of entertainment
letting word of mouth do their advertising for them. It's really irritating. And if I made this
show, I would be furious. However, people are smart sometimes and good things do catch on. So
finally saw it. And with all the ways I actually watched it after I had a very long talk with our
friend David Krumholtz. I was having a heart to heart with him, much like we had at the top of
the show today. And one of the great pieces of advice that he gave me, and there were several,
was go watch the movie already. It's kind of about all this stuff you're talking about.
And I was excited because I didn't know it was streaming and I'd been looking forward to it
a while. So I watched it that day. I really loved it. I'm not being diplomatic because David's a
friend and a friend of the show. I truly, truly did love it. It was exactly what I had hoped it
would be, which was something to me that I've talked about a lot on the show. I said, paint
was like this and some other movies and recent viewing, but it was very much that vibe of
independent late nineties cinema. Like it just felt like one of those movies.
It dealt with real characters. There was a quirkiness to it, which I liked. It was almost
at times like watching a Napoleon dynamite that dealt with heavier issues because it never gets
too serious. It always remains funny. It always remains quirky, but it still addresses these
existential issues. And I just really loved it. And I find David to be truly a captivating
presence on screen. He's one of those guys when he's up there, I can't take my eyes off him.
He's so likeable that you immediately forget what a unlikable role it is.
Oh, I thought you were going to say in real life.
He is. I mean, yeah, of course he is, but I just mean like in this movie.
No, no, no. I meant you forget how unlikable he is in real life. I thought you were going to make
a joke. No, no, no. Well, here's the thing, though. I found the character to be flawed,
but not unlikable. And I found every character to be like that in the movie. Even the people
that are antagonizing him throughout the movie, they seem right at first, and then they cross
lines where you realize each of them is just as selfish and fucked up as he is.
And the only one to I feel like you get or at least that you get to see stumble into a moment
of enlightenment is him in his final moments where he real. Oh shit. Sorry, guys. I didn't
mean to spoil. Fuck. Spoiler. Sorry. Ah, shit. Well, anyway, I don't think the movie is
spoiler proof. There's nothing. There's no big twist to it. So, so just in case, spoiler,
if you don't want to, you know, but in his, it doesn't matter. I don't even need to say,
but my point is, is he has a last minute revelation that, that I think is very small
and very simple, but it's indicative of the character's arc and journey and,
and that he has learned something. Yeah. I really liked it quite a bit. I look forward
seeing it again. And, uh, I'll probably, I'll probably purchase it if it, if it gets a physical
release, I'd like to, it's one of those ones I'll throw on. Um, I just like movies like that. I
like that. We were talking about Mamet earlier. I like the Mamet movies. I like the Woody Allen
movies. I like, I like movies that are simple, few characters, life, blah, blah, blah, um,
dialogue driven. And this was, this was no exception. So it was great.
Uh, yeah, I liked it a lot myself. I watched drive away dolls, which is new on Peacock.
And I gotta say, I was very, very excited and interested to watch this movie. And what's
fascinating to me is people think they can decide which Cohen brother did what based on them each
making one movie a piece on their own. Read some of these theories. I'm like,
you have no fucking idea how these guys put together 25, 35 years worth of masterpieces.
You have no idea, but now here's what we have. Joel Cohen made Macbeth. It was in my opinion,
artsy fartsy to a stupid degree to the point where it sacrificed entertainment. I found it
visually striking, but very, very dull and up its own ass in a way that the Cohen brothers
usually are not, uh, drive away dolls. On the other hand is an Ethan Cohen solo joint.
Fascinatingly, I learned a lot about Ethan Cohen in research or looking up this movie.
Research is a little extreme for what you do, but, um, he's married to a woman
who is a lesbian or realized she was a lesbian after they got married.
And now they have an open marriage where he fucks other women and she fucks other women.
And now they're filmmaking partners. They co -wrote this movie together years ago.
So the Cohen brothers, you know, it's like the Wachowskis they've been going through some changes
and maybe not as big as the Wachowskis, but some changes and drive away dolls is 84 minutes long.
It is packed with like 70s style, uh, trippy, like, you know, women dancing in their underwear
transitions between scenes. Um, one of the women who is dancing you through these transitions is
Miley Cyrus, which is weird and never explained. Um, but the movie is, is a kind of standard Cohen
brothers crime caper where these two young girls rent a car and it's got a suitcase in the back
and what's in the suitcase. Uh, pretty standard, but the movie is insane. They are lesbians.
It's Margaret Qualley who I like a lot and Geraldine Viswanathan from blockers was very funny.
Uh, Beanie Feldstein from book smart. They basically play three young lesbians who get
caught up in this very Cohen's style of what's in the briefcase. People trying to kill them.
Uh, you got a Matt Damon cameo, a Pedro Pascal cameo. You have a movie that's all over the place,
but super funny and crazy. And I would say very dick obsessed in a weird way. Like, you know how
in burn after reading, they've got the, uh, always sunny stole it, the exercise bike with the dick
that comes up through the seat. Yeah. Okay. The dildo. Yeah. This movie has a thousand dildos in
it. Okay. You know that that's like what I would say to you. So I get why people think they know
who does what in the Cohen brothers now. My guess is you probably don't, but from looking at these
two movies, Joel is very much the artist and Ethan Cohen is very much the let's hit them with a bunch
of dick jokes. And I hope that this isn't a permanent split because it's obviously the
of those two things that makes the Cohen so magical to me. I think that said drive away
dolls is a lot of fun and very funny and just full of sex in a way that movies are not lately. So
I enjoyed that. You rarely see like a horny Cohen brothers movie, but if that's what Ethan's going
to start giving us, I'm all for it. I liked it. Uh, one other one, unless we're going to do it,
are we going to do the new Woody Allen or should I just do it now? Go for it. Um,
Coup de Chance, Woody Allen's new movie, uh, uh, beginning rave review, not, well, not rave,
but, but very strong reviews by critics currently holding an 85 % or something on rotten tomatoes.
I said to Pat before I watched it, I was like, this thing must be really good if it's actually
getting these good reviews. Yeah. Cause people will pounce on any reason to, to give him a bad
review. Um, and it's, this is getting strong reviews and, uh, watched it, loved it, uh,
back, back to basics for him, not a romantic comedy basics, but you know, he used to in the,
in the late, I guess it was the late eighties. He, he, he did a lot of movies like this where
it was very simple thing about a marriage and then some sort of chain of events sets off an
interest, a very interesting journey for the wife who's not being appreciated by her husband,
not, not necessarily abused, but, but mistreated, uh, kept, um, condescended to that, that sort of
thing. Um, and, and the, the, the, it starts to play out from there. There's always an adultery
line, of course. Um, and this one turns into a, a bit of a, of a murder caper. Um, it's very simple.
It's very straightforward, but it's very, very, very well acted. It's very well, it's,
it's pretty well written. There were, there were some sloppy moments where I was like, come on, man,
they're going to talk about this in the next room type stuff. But I'm also like, well,
it's a French caper. So maybe that's derivative of French cinema and I'm not aware of it, or
maybe it's just the results of a 90 year old man making a movie. Um, either way, the, the, the,
the slip ups weren't egregious enough to make, to hurt the overall experience to me. Um, and it was
surprisingly fun. I, I was not expecting it to be fun. Uh, I was not expecting it to be kind of funny
uh, it was much, you know, everybody keeps saying it's his best thing since Matchpoint.
Matchpoint is a very well -made movie, but my God, it is a dire experience. Like it, it, there's no
joy in Matchpoint. It's a very sad movie to watch. Um, and this didn't feel like that to me. This,
this had a lot of like interesting characters. Uh, spoiler alert, there's, there's a sequence
where the girls, the main character's mother kind of is the one that starts to get on the trail of,
of what she thinks is a, is a miss here. And that was fun to watch. Like the mom detective
trying to protect her daughter and whatever. Uh, the soundtrack was great. It's very upbeat
against, uh, let me guess jazz, sort of a jazz theme or it, it, yeah, but like,
you know what he, know what song he keeps playing in it? Do you remember that song by us three
cantaloupe that was like, yeah, he, he uses, yeah, he uses the song they sampled in that a lot that
that's like the main song in it. So like there's like murder happening, but like he keeps playing
that song and you're like, this is supposed to be kind of fun. Like it's not supposed to be like,
I'm so depressed or whatever. So, um, I liked it. I liked it. It felt a lot to me like Alice,
which is a great Woody Allen movie. Um, it, it felt like a lighter match point. It felt like
a lighter Cassandra's dream. It like, I, I enjoyed it very much. It is in French, all subtitles
though. So you gotta, I have, I have a hard time with subtitles, not cause I don't have the, the,
concentration ability. I just, I feel like I'm always looking at the bottom of the screen.
Um, so, but, but, you know, it was great. I recommend it. I'm excited to see it. Um,
let's get to the movie at hand. Cause I know Joe's fired up about this one. I rewatched it this
morning and my opinion took a big tumble from, I, I suspected it might. I saw a big crowded theater
showing. That was a lot of fun. And then at home, I was kind of like, huh, oh boy. Um, but it's been
pretty, pretty highly praised. It was a little controversial for using a couple AI images.
And I think that we're going in so hard on AI just to be like, we don't want this shit here.
Like, so even when you do something relatively minor, like this movie did, um, that became kind
of the source of all the news about the movie after it got released was, can you believe they
used AI? Uh, you know, I don't think it necessarily deserves that. It's a very low budget film.
And that's what I liked the most the first time was it's kind of shaggy dog charm. But of course
that sort of thing does not generally hold up on repeat viewings as, as maybe Blair Witch would not
hold up on repeat viewings once the gimmick is gone. You had mentioned that to me. I don't think
look, it's in my opinion, it's low budget by today's low budget standards, which means it
looks like a $5 million movie. I mean, it's just like, it's, it's, it's not that low budget,
like, like a painstaking period piece like this, uh, with a cast that's this big. And, um, there's
a lot of visual effects. Uh, it did not strike me as terribly low budget, maybe $3 million movie,
but, but at the, at the least in my opinion, but, uh, everybody's screaming about this thing.
Everybody's saying it's so great. Everybody's saying, um, late night with the devil. Your,
your plot is it's, it's real simple. Guy's got a late night TV show. The ratings are struggling.
He needs, he does a Halloween episode where he's going to interview a girl who claims to have been
possessed by the devil and things go awry on camera. That's all this movie needed to be.
Point A to point B. Instead, what you get is a movie with a terrible framing device that this
episode of this late night TV show has been unearthed and you are now going to see it for
the first time. And you are not only going to see this episode for the first time,
you are going to see never before seen backstage footage of events that transpire while they were
shooting the episode. What's my problem with never before seen backstage footage? Well,
because what they did in this is they just shot scenes that were taking place backstage
and put and turned them black and white. So, so there are people speaking in hushed
tones backstage. This is the captured footage that they don't know they're being videotaped.
They're being shot from multiple angles. Uh, there's cameras clearly in their faces. It's
like, guys, this is not, if you want me to believe and be swept away in this concept that I'm being
taken backstage and I'm not supposed to be seeing this, whatever, fucking take two seconds to shoot
that properly. Because when you don't, it, we're, we're out of the illusion of this. It's, this is,
you know, the, I don't know why it has that dumb fucking framing advice other than to convey
a bunch of information about the main character that you don't fucking need. You don't need.
And it's handled right up front. They do sort of this, uh, it's only 93 minutes. So maybe there
was some desire to get it to 90. I don't know. But in the beginning, they do this. Here's what
the seventies were like. Here's what late night television were like. They give you the backstory
you need on this guy and you don't question it. It's like, okay, got it. Now let's get onto the
found footage. It is super weird to do a found footage movie that just isn't found footage.
I don't even think they're, they're presenting that black and white stuff in the back as part
of the found footage. Maybe I'm wrong. No, they are. They say it in the top and they say,
we also caught stuff. Yeah, they say you're, you're also going to see never before seen
backstage footage or whatever. I forgot how they phrase it, but, but that's why I went.
So you're watching it and you're going, guys, just make a movie where it starts with the TV show.
And then you go backstage and do it like Larry Sanders, where you go, oh, this is shot a little
differently because they're backstage, but I, it's not a documentary. I know that I'm seeing
what's happening backstage right now. I got even, even clearer just off the top of my head would be
you're watching the footage and then there's a documentary team, you know, walking you back
through the present day studio, you know, or something like that. There's a couple of ways
to do it, but, but yeah, if that's presented as found footage, but it's, it's artsy and black and
doesn't look at all like what found footage, camera footage would have been from that time,
then I don't understand that at all. It just looks like edited modern day film.
By the way, the show footage doesn't look to be of that period either. It's not filtered in a way
where you're like, if you're telling me I'm watching old footage, you have to make it look
like old footage. It can't be in high definition. It didn't bug me. I've seen that done better,
even in like, you know, the fucking Weezer buddy Holly video. I mean, that technology in 1994 was
better, but what this did to, to kind of give you that effect, whenever they added stuff to give you
that effect, that's when it didn't work. Like when they have the film bend, Oh God, I'm like, well,
what is the, why was the film bending? Like what, what are we even watching here? Those little
details would have helped sell this thing a lot better, but I didn't think in terms of I'm watching
an actual seventies Johnny Carson type show, I thought it looked good enough for me personally.
It is. It also, by the way, as they tell you, you're watching found footage
goes into a dream sequence at the end of the movie that the main actor has that,
that you obviously would never see in found footage. I don't know if it's supposed to be
some play. There's a thing where the audience gets hypnotized at one point by this hypnotist
and they believe they all witnessed something together that they don't see. And I don't know
if that dream sequence at the end is supposed to be like, now you're seeing a thing that you
shouldn't be able to see. Well, they do make a point of doing it to the audience, the home viewer
as well. So probably that was the intent, but it doesn't come through. Yeah, it doesn't come
through. But these are just the beginnings of the problem of the movie people. Let me get into the
comedy writer's room as joking the joke. They take a concept and then they layer it with another
concept and then it makes the original concept convoluted and ineffective. So for instance,
they have, before the possessed girl comes out, they have a clairvoyant come out.
The clairvoyant is, everybody's skeptical that the clairvoyant is a fraud. He's got this thick
accent. He immediately turns out to not be a fraud because he is able to tell things about
somebody in the audience that it's real. Then he gets like this crazy, he talks about how he's
getting signals from the other side, that's how it works. And he gets this crazy signal that's like
brain surge and he's going to almost hemorrhage or whatever. And during that moment, he doesn't
have the accent anymore. So then you're like, so wait, he was a fraud, but he's not a fraud?
What the fuck is going on? It's just poorly fucking written. It's too many details.
There's this whole subplot where the host of the show, it's not just that he's desperate for
ratings. It's not just that he's desperate for fame. He's also been associated to be connected
to a cult in Hollywood that's doing these terrible things. And then also his wife died.
When that cult pops up, you're like, ooh, okay. But that is almost an afterthought. It's not even
really gone into in the film. It's gone in at the end when you realize, which we'll get to with the
devil girl, that he's encountered this demon before in his cult and whatever. So anyway,
so that happens. Then they bring out another fucking character who's like a hypnotist,
but also a skeptic. By the way, all of these characters, all of them, from the director
to the Hank Kingsley ripoff sidekick character they do, to the clairvoyant, to the hypnotist,
everybody except the main guy who's the host is a
terrible actor. It is like sitcom threes company acting. It's terrible. It's bad.
Honestly, that's why I assumed low budget. When I looked it up just now, they're not saying the
budget, which is always suspect, but they're saying that they had 150K budget for effects,
which is not obviously not huge. But my guess then is the movie was probably three, who knows.
But yeah, the acting is, and they are playing, you know, 70s magicians and stuff. So there's
license to go a little broad with it, but much more on this second viewing at home. I was like,
I'm not buying this. And maybe it was Joe talking so much shit. Joe's very persuasive, but yeah,
it should work better at home, you know, a movie that's creating this. Like when my sister was
like, should I go see it at the theater? I was like, it's fine at home, you know, that's what it is.
But at home with the distractions and everything, it kind of just falls apart to nothing.
And by the way, I have no tolerance for bad casting. I have none. There are so many amazing
actors out there. This is a movie front to back, except for the main guy who's sort of known at
this point. He played polka dot man or whatever. Everybody else is an unknown. I have no tolerance.
Find a guy that's a convincing hypnotist and a skeptic, period. Don't hire a guy based on
his looks and then go, he looks the part and can do it good enough. Like it's bad.
So, you know, and so anyway, finally the possessed girl comes out. And again, joking the joke,
it's not just this girl with her mother. You know how it is on every talk show when they do
something like this? The parents bring the kid out and go, my little boy died and met Jesus,
or whatever the fuck it is, right? Yeah. And now he's here to tell the tale. They bring out the
but the girl, guess what? She was part of a cult and that cult died in a suicide fire.
And now she's been rescued and now she lives with the doctor that it's like, what the fuck
is going on, guys? Like, why all these fucking details? So anyway, they bring her out. They do
against the doctor's better judgment, who is absolutely appalled by being roped into this
talk show, being put on the spot to bring the demon out inside the girl, all this shit.
She still agrees to do it. Again, details we don't need, none of this. Just make it somebody
who's exploiting the girl. Like it's so simple, guys. And then have that go fucking wrong.
Instead of trying to make it look like she's not okay with it, then she's okay with it,
then she does it, then she's mad that she did it. Then when she gets killed, you don't have
any sympathy for her because she did it. It's fucking ridiculous. The girl then finally is
possessed. And when I tell you, they hit every fucking, they tick every box of every possession
you've ever seen. The makeup is the exorcist. The voice is the stupid modulator effect that
they do in every possession movie now. Her levitating. Oh, she's going to say terrible
things about his dead wife, you know? Yeah. Ah, the whore you married is in hell taking
jizz up the ass. You're like, oh, for God's sakes, people, do something original.
I gotta say too, this wife dying of cancer, the bald woman in bed or whatever, when they're doing
that in a horror movie, I'm always like, maybe I'm an empath, whatever you want to call it,
but I'm always like, a lot of people's lives have been affected by watching someone they love slowly
die of cancer. Use it when it's, this is not the movie to use that, you know? I just felt,
that's when it felt really kind of gross to me is I was like, no, if you're taking everything
else seriously, then fine, but this movie was trying to juggle so much. I think also there was
a comedy attempt. Like I'm reading online that it was a comedy at times, which I didn't see,
but yeah, him holding, you know, his wife dying of cancer, I was like, you haven't treated this
story with enough respect to pull this on me at the end of the line, you know? Also too,
there's a reveal at the end that her cancer was the result of his making like a pact. Right. With
the demon. A deal with the devil for ratings, yeah. Yeah, with the same demon that possesses the girl.
By the way, devil's not even part of this. She's not possessed by the devil. She's possessed by
some fucking demon. Anyway, they, yeah, and it's like, guys, why is it, just make it that
his wife died in an accident and then you find out that it was a sacrifice if you're going to do
that. Like again, it's the joking, the joking, the joking, the jo - it's so many needless fucking
layers to complicate things to get - I should not have to go on Wikipedia and reread the plot of
Late Night with the Devil because there's so much going on that I can't, I'm like, wait, wait, what?
I do it so much and it makes me feel stupid. The Civil War, the 824 movie, I did not have to and
on that one I was like, that's because there was nothing done to make this a compelling story.
This is an example of doing way too much and I feel like that's generally what the notes process
does. I don't know if that was the case here, but usually when something is getting way too
convoluted, it's because people at the top are asking for things to be clarified that don't need
to be clarified. Here's what I liked. You know, the charm, the low budget charm, even if it was
below five million, I liked that it seemed like a handmade affair. I think it's a very clever idea,
a late night show that devolves into horror. I think the execution was lacking in spots.
I think the effects were either embarrassingly bad or oddly effective. Like when the worms come out
of the guy's stomach, I was like, that was good. But when the girl's head separates and she's doing
the demon thing, that looked bad. That looked real bad. Also the worms thing would have been good if
a good actor was doing it. Yeah. But the guy going like, oh, oh, oh, what's happening to me? I was
like, Oh God guys. Yeah, I don't know. I liked it more than Joe. And I want to say that it made me
think about the exorcist believer and go, okay, that movie costs, or that at least the franchise
cost $400 million and we got an F. This movie cost much, much less and was let's say equally
as effective. I can, I can appreciate it for that, but yeah, a bit of a letdown. I'd rather
see this same premise attempted again, because this, this attempt seems not great to me on a,
on a second. The thing that bothered me most at the end of the day. Yes. And then we can put this
film to bed where I'm watching it and I'm going, you know, this pisses me off. These fucking young
filmmakers, they don't do their homework. They're doing shit that's been done a million times
watch the exorcist and learn what's been done already, whatever. I looked at these film makers,
they're like two guys in their fifties. Oh, really? Yeah. And I'm like, oh fuck, now really fuck off.
Now really fuck off guys. Um, uh, and David Duchovny, what's his name? Uh, Dalmasian. He was,
he was good. Everybody's like the brilliance emanating from, I'm like, guys, would you fucking
relax? He was good. He was good. I'll say this. He was fine. Do you think that that, what we watched
would, it would have been a successful late night show to rival Johnny Carson? Like absolutely not.
It doesn't even really work in that world. He's not that charming and he's certainly not funny.
We see his monologue play. You're like, nope. It never had to get into any of that. It just had to
be a late night show. Sure. But like, again, I'm like, no, this guy should be a lot funnier,
more charming, more everything. If this story is even going to work. Sure. I get you on that. But,
and that's the thing. Well, well, well, maybe that was the point was he's not very likable,
which is why he estimates boost from the devil. Yeah. But all this had to be Pat was for Christ
sakes guys, if it started just with the beginning of the show. Yeah. And then at some point he goes,
you just go, oh, in this universe, he's Johnny Carson. Right. You know? And then at some point
in the, in the show, he says, my late wonderful wife, I miss her dearly and the audience
applauds. And then somebody comes out and makes a comment about like, yeah, well, yeah, sure.
Yeah. You, you, you had nothing to do with that or whatever the fuck. And you're like, oh, wait a
do this. That would have had you in the moment for the entire time.
We never had to get into mass hypnosis of the audience.
We never had to get into a clairvoyant puking black sludge all over. Again, another trope. Oh,
and guys puking black stuff. Like Jesus Christ, guys. Let me tell you this. If I'm producing that
movie and they tell me I got $150 ,000 for special effects for the puking black bile scene,
I ask the actor to put a bunch of black shit in his mouth and spit it out
for $0 or maybe $5 for the black shit budget. Then I devote a hundred and forty nine thousand
nine hundred and ninety five dollars to the demon head exploding. That looks like it was made on a
Nintendo, the original Nintendo. Like we didn't need terrible looking CGI for the black bile.
That should have been cut. That was an embarrassing effect. And, and also to way more effective.
If the guy just spits it out all over the late night hosts desk. Yeah. And it's this,
it's this embarrassing thing of like, wow, this actually could be something otherworldly.
Yeah. Or maybe he's this guy is like sick from something. Right. And we don't know either way.
This is awkward. It's embarrassing. They escort him off set and that's the end of it. Instead,
they go so over the fucking top with it that you're like anybody who is a disbeliever
immediately would be like this got something's wrong here. And but no, they still have the
fucking like, you know, the, you know, the guy who should have played the restaurant manager on
it's a living sitting in the corner going, please. Yeah. It's like half pole. Yeah. Yeah. Please a
little fake puke. I know how to do that. Swallow a few blood capsule. Like you're like, oh,
they did all but have him dip his pointer finger into it and then lick it off, you know, and be
blackberry jam, you know, one of those things. Anyway, folks, my hog is my hog ain't been this
down since midsummer, which I texted that about. That's when you were taking Lexapro. I believe so
this midsummer. No, I, I liked it more than Joe. As I said, if you had caught me coming out of the
theater, I would have been a lot more positive, but yeah, it doesn't hold to a second viewing.
Not every movie needs to, but I think we both just wish there had been a little more
attention and care paid to the script because I like the premise. I like the vibes. It just
didn't hit me like I wanted it to. We will be back to discuss the prequel to the omen, the first omen.
Uh, I am on Instagram at the Patrick Walsh. We are on Instagram at see you in hell pod.
We also have merch on the Etsy store and a Facebook page. Uh, I got some dates coming up people.
Hamden, Connecticut, May 3rd, which is right around the corner. If you're in that area,
come on out and see me. May 25th, Newport, Rhode Island. Um, both shows are the final two shows
of I never promised you a rose garden. Uh, why is that? Well, because we will be shooting it
finally in September. Uh, I'm not touring it over the summer. I'll do a small handful of warm up
shows before we tape in mid September, but this is it. So come on out and I will be announcing
the actual special taping very soon. Um, and then just for regular fun stand up stuff, I'll be on
Bert Kreischer fully loaded tour in June. Uh, I'll be at Skank Fest in Vegas in late September.
Come on out. Have a good time. Jotaroza .com for all tickets and show and venue info. Uh, and if
you're in New York, come by Joey roses seven days a week, uh, opening every morning at 1130 am. Uh,
we'll see you next time. We'll see you in hell.