Welcome to We'll See You at Hell. It's the show about movies, folks, and I'm JoJo Movie
Us. Yes, it's the show about movies. The only one out there. Joe is here. I am here. Pat Walsh.
How are you, everybody? Walsh, how are you? Good. Really just an all across the across the board
terrible intro for both of us. But I feel like that means a good show is is in store. You know,
a bad dress rehearsal means that opening night will be great. As they say, you don't want to
peek during rehearsal. That's true. I just moved the tables and others wobbly noises. Good. If you
could also sort of position your knee underneath it so that it's constantly keeping it wobbly and
noisy. That was my dick. Okay, that was my huge dick. Folks, we're talking today about a picture
called malignant. James Wan film. Got to tell you malignant, not what you want to hear at the
doctor's office. But it is what you want to hear at the box office, baby. How long were you sitting
on that? Honestly, just made it up. I was delighted with how it turned out. What are you doing? It's
the new Coke Zero, which is unbelievably close to real Coke.
I can't get over how real it is. It's crazy. It has like no diet flavor to it.
What is it was a new formula. All Coke Zero is that or it's Coke Zero two. Now they just redid
Coke Zero again. And they're like now more delicious closer even closer to the real thing.
But they still make diet Coke, which still tastes exactly like you're chewing on tin foil.
Because people like the flavor. People have like a diet Coke thing, man.
So no, anyone who came up with it, a lot of like moms in the 80s, etc. really are addicted to diet
Coke. To me, I tried Coke Zero. I never look back. It's infinitely better. And if you're telling me
there's a better model, I'm on board. Yeah, all the Coke Zero has been revamped. You'll notice
the label is slightly different now. The Coca Cola is in black and their label is red.
But also, too, they redid Cherry Coke Zero. So that tastes like real cherry Coke. But what's great
is I used to drink diet Coke for years. And then I would get a Coke Zero and I kind of go back and
forth and couldn't really tell a great difference. And then when this came out and I tried to go back
to diet Coke, I was like, yeah, you know, like, just it would taste vile to me again. And I was
like, Oh, wow, this must really taste like Coke. I think the old formula was like a lot of chemicals,
but people got addicted to the chemical taste. And I'm sure Coke Zero is just as chemically,
but it somehow tastes more pure or something, even though I'm sure it just nausea. I mean,
you've seen those videos where like they sit or a cow heart in a vat of Coke and it disintegrates
in like 24 hours. It's not the best thing for you. Yeah. Yeah. But I drink a lot of it.
I've never known you to drink soda. I don't know that I've ever seen you drink a soda.
Once I discovered the powers of Coke Zero and got used to diet Coke, I started doing a lot of it.
Now I don't like, as I said, don't like diet Coke anymore. But I drink, I've really implemented a
lot of Coke Zero into my life. It's one of the few releases you can get through the day. You know,
you're trying to get shit done and you just have a refreshing soda and you go, you know what,
there's no sugar in this. It'll God knows what it's doing to my insides. But in the meantime,
yeah, I'm, I have a great taste guilt -free. Why not a seltzer or something that does no harm?
Please piss on a seltzer. A soda water. I mean, I don't know. I'm not talking LaCroix. There's
better brands out there than LaCroix. Man, do I hate LaCroix. LaCroix, you're tasting 90 % can.
It just tastes like you're, it tastes like the can has already started melting into what you're
drinking and you're tasting it. It's disgusting. Every writer's room is like, we gotta have a
hundred kinds of LaCroix because we're writers talking about right up there with the red vines
in every writer's room. Yeah. Nobody's favorite licorice. Nobody's favorite candy licorice,
let alone candy. You like a Twizzler or no, you don't like, as you said, infinitely better. No,
I love cherry licorice. I love strawberry licorice. I'm like a red vinyl past the time,
but it's, it's a wax treat. I mean, it's, it tastes like, it tastes like wax with a little
fruit flavor in it. Let me ask you this. You ever bitten off either end of a piece of licorice,
preferably a Twizzler and put it into your Diet Coke as a straw, a cherry? I put it into my cherry
Coke. Okay. It might be too much cherry for some. Please. Just warning. This is warning any listeners
who might be looking to try it. Your version is like the, like a diner version of the drink.
Mine's like the Ben and Jerry's, you know, where it's like cherry and we shove cherries inside
other cherry. There's a core in the middle of the can made of cherry. That's what my, my dad gets
is the bet. He does this joke every time, uh, which is, uh, what are you up to tonight? Oh,
I'm just hanging with my two best friends, Ben and Jerry. And then, uh, he likes to get the kind
with the core, meaning the center, like three inches of the, of the container is solid cookie
dough. And so like there's ice cream around it, but there's a center deposit, if you will,
of cookie dough. And what's he do with that? He eats one a night of these things. One a night.
And I would love to eat one of those. And I, I, I got, I have lactose issues. The older I get,
the less tolerant I am with lactose, but the, uh, I've got no patience for lactose and I won't stand
for it. Well, I'm the greatest Seinfeld jokes ever. Uh, but, uh, you like, so I got the, uh,
Ben and Jerry's, they have like a dairy free now. And I thought like foolishly, I was like,
this will be like healthier. It's still like 1200 calories. If you eat the whole thing,
which I guess is not that bad. If you're thinking about eating a pint of ice cream, but I mean,
I just, it's reasonable. I felt guilty. I didn't eat the whole thing. I couldn't do it. I, I felt
too guilty. Folks. Welcome back to sweet treats. Coke talk. Uh, I pitched a pod. I pitched a web
series called Coke talk. Like people like drunk history, but with cocaine. It wasn't drunk history.
It was just a, it was a scripted web series that I pitched to comedy central about a podcast where
guys were the two hosts were clearly like just jacked. Yeah. And like it was never, you never
saw them do the Coke, but it was just like tons of fast edits and lots of cutaways. They're just
barreling through the subjects to not people actually on Coke. It's scripted. Yeah. It's
scripted though. The guy I was going to say the last thing somebody who's not on Coke wants to do
is listen to two people who are on Coke. Yeah. Like, you know, and then like the joke, you know,
one of the jokes would be like, you know, there's this talk. It was a talk radio show. So like,
yeah, they'd call in and be like, what are your thoughts on this latest primary? Like, what,
you know, what are your thoughts, man, on the primary? I wouldn't, I'd love to know what you,
you know, it's like real Koki killed in the room and they waited two months and passed.
Sure. That's what they do. We should open a concert venue.
That's what I talked about when I was on Coke the one time we should open a concert venue.
I think the pilot episode was titled the Phantom Menace was, was pretty good.
Oh, they were really fucked up. Yeah. So it was, um, yeah, I thought, I thought that was
money in the bank, but no, no, it didn't happen. I got to tell you, Joe, right before logging on
here, I always complained to you about the Amazon customers that, that reach out one lady. I mean,
the people from the Amazon because you're racist and you don't like that. That's correct. Yeah.
One lady I got in a huge argument with, and I didn't talk about this on air, but basically she
was like, um, get an email from her and she's like, since obviously you're not going to send
the DVD I ordered, I'll take a refund please. She had ordered it three days prior.
And I said, I'm, I'm sending it. Uh, it's, it's in the mail. So I said, I'm going to give you
your money back just so I don't have to talk to you again. And then she was like, you might want
to think about the way you speak to customer, you know, one of these back and forth. So basically
she didn't report it because she was getting her thing for free, which let's face it is what she
f*****g wanted anyway. Right. So today people, people do anything now to get something free.
Just make up stories. This guy writes me. I got a text that my package delivered,
but it's nowhere to be found. And of them end of communication,
which is Amazon's problem. Didn't sign it. It's your mail carrier's f*****g
or your mail. That's what I meant. Yeah. We're in, we're across the country. You f*****g idiot.
Yeah. How is that my fault? It's nowhere to be found. God damn it. And you know,
you know how this is going to resolve Amazon telling me I have to fully refund his order.
What was it? It was an album. Was it pricey? Are you losing a lot of money? I mean,
that's 30 clamps. Oh God. Yeah, that sucks, man. The, I, I, I don't know how you deal with it.
I could never deal with it. I just, I can't do it. I can't. I couldn't. I had an incident.
Their new policy is the buyer is 100 % right at all times is the new Amazon policy, which is not
great because when, when something is their fault, they don't care at all. They send me the wrong
item now 25 % of the time when I order something. And then what do you have to do? Package it and
take it to a UPS store during a pandemic. Great idea, Amazon. That'll make it right. They're like,
how can we make it right? I'm like, well, you could send me the right item. And they go, great,
just take this to UPS, mail it to us. When we get it, we'll send you the proper item. Yeah, thanks.
That's making it right. Sending me what I wanted 10 days late and, and making me go to the fucking
UPS store and wait in the line with animals. Yeah. That should always be keep that one and
we'll send a new one. Always, always. They don't do that anymore because I guess they're probably
hurting for money. They just bought like the moon. They own like a large portion of real estate on
boom. The public is, uh, is problematic. I, I, I will say this. I had an incident this week. I, I,
we did, uh, weed versus alcohol and the latest taste buds. Yeah. And I really went in hard on
like weed culture because I think it's painfully dumb. Let me be clear. If you smoke weed, that's
fine. I don't care. I smoke weed sometimes. If you're a weed enthusiast, that's when I think
it starts to become dumb. Sure. Um, does my whole argument was I was making fun of it and I was like,
please stop telling, you know, this, this concept that, that weed, you can just smoke and drive and
it's fine. Like if I did that with booze, one hit of weed gets me way more fucked up than two shots
of alcohol ever does. Okay. And you know, but, uh,
people, so, so, so a lot of comp, not all the comments were negative, but all the feedback on
YouTube was negative and it was all from the weed circuit. People just screaming at me, uh,
or through these comments, you don't know what the fuck you're talking about. Okay. Boomer. Uh,
I don't think I can listen to this show anymore. Uh -huh. Your, your stated an opinion on an opinion
show. Yeah. Your stance on weed is so uneducated. You sound like an old man. Uh, uh, sorry that
you're such a pussy. You can't handle your weed. You're clearly an alcoholic. You know,
you can do two shots and not feel it, but that's not the average person. Cause you're an alcoholic
weed people. You sound like a bunch of fucking alcoholics.
This is what alcoholics sound like. Like it's like, yeah, you're taller. It's called a tolerance.
It's higher for you because you smoke it every day. Right. Um, I just can't. So I went on
Instagram and made a video where I said, and this is true. I said, I've pissed off a lot of people
in my time, but when you piss off a bunch of weed, weed head fucking burnouts to the point
where they're yelling at you, you really have a gift to get these unmotivated people to react
this strongly. It's a gift. And I do feel strongly about that. Get them up and off the beanbag chair
and into your mentions. Stop staring at the lava lamp. Yeah. You know, I was making jokes like this
and they're like, you don't know weed culture. You sound like the eighties. I'm like, it's a
that much. It's just more and more in the open and people screaming at me because I said,
try listening to Pink Floyd when you're not high. It's just a slog.
Put metal on the next time. Anyway. Um, and then all the comments on the, on the Instagram video
I made, we're very, we're like, this is hilarious. I love that you doubled down. So only the people
on YouTube for some reason, we're mad. I don't know why, but, um, but the thing is, is here's
the weed thing. I can't stand. I'm tired of the argument of it's natural. So is booze. Yeah.
Booze comes from potatoes and rice and grapes. I mean, look, booze isn't natural. It's a poison,
but I love both. Don't get grapes. You put them in a barrel. Yeah. And they ferment
and that's what booze is. Right. Weed. People act like you can just pluck it off the tree or the
bush and smoke it. No, you can't. It's too wet. It's too sticky. You have to dry it out. It has to,
it has some sort of processing. It has to go through. Okay. Cocaine I could argue is natural.
It comes from the cocoa plant. Folks, I wish I could convey how insane Joe looked when he said
that just now. Nobody's ever died from weed. Okay. So you're right. So it's better than Tylenol
because you could die from Tylenol. You're right. Only, only get my kicks naturally by which I mean,
I keep a toad in my home that I lick and I ration out the licks to see how high I want to be. That's
folks. I wish I had your, your ability for references. That would have been a great punchline
to a joke. I could do about how it makes me mad about weed people. I never would have thought
of that punchline in a million years. Licking a toad. Yeah. I would have thought of what I just
said, which is why my call, my comedy sounds like a insane man screaming through that, that tiny
window of bars, but people like it. People like it, Joe, because they can't scream like, and then
you are their scream. I, before we get to the corner, I want to, to read this because I read
it, I sent it to you, but I didn't read it over the line. Here's what she said. Hold Susan. Oh,
I didn't mean to cut your arms. No, no, no, no, no. I just now looked it up while you were talking.
The movie, by the way, was a DVD copy of the dream team with Michael Keaton. Jesus Christ.
She goes after three days, since you obviously aren't going to send me the DVD I ordered,
then just give me a refund and I'll order it from somewhere else.
I wrote, Hi, Susan. What a strange and rude way to approach this issue. I know the item was shipped
to you because I carefully packaged the DVD and brought it to the post office myself. I'm sorry
you didn't receive it though. It was no fault of mine. Why lead with some weird accusation?
I'm obviously not going to send you the DVD you ordered. Do you think I'm holding a $5 item
hostage to make you mad? Your item was shipped on time. I'm genuinely sorry I didn't reach you.
You should try approaching people from a place of understanding. Try something like, hello,
I never received my DVD. You know, talk to me like I'm a human being. I'm happy to refund your order
in full if it means you won't order from me ever again. Thank you, Patrick. She wrote back,
you're welcome and I won't order from you ever again. FYI, try some anger management therapy.
Good luck. This is what I mean with Pete. It's like this is exactly what I'm talking about.
I tweeted the other day on this, but this is exactly your thing too. It's just a different
subject. I tweeted yesterday. If you defend booze, you're in denial. If you defend weed,
you're enlightened. It's the same thing with this lady. I can attack you irrationally with anger,
but the second you display any of that back to me, you have the problem. It's like, no,
you're displaying the behavior you're condemning right now. Also, the customer is always right.
That whole thing is like, it has made every exchange between two people. I'm going like
now with fucking 21 year old hostess girls at restaurants getting attacked. It's like the
customer is always right to the point now where if you tell me, hey, I need you to put a mask on
whatever, it leads to a physical altercation because people can't handle somebody telling
them, no, you have to do something. It's both ways too. Then there are the staffers that say
the customer is never right and fuck you. Why should I do my job properly? That's happening
a lot now. We're finished. It's over. Nobody has the time or patience for human decency.
We were always walking on a line. It's again, Costanza, the great, you know, we're living in a
society and the guy won't tell them what time it is. We've always walked that line and there's
always people who stepped out of the lines of society, but now everyone is realizing how
fucked it is and how little they care about their fellow man and everyone's attitude is
gimme, gimme, gimme, fuck you if you disagree. And boy, it's going to make for an interesting
next couple of years. These are dark times. By which I mean, until the world ends.
Yeah, this is a rough, we're in a rough patch. Speaking of which,
this is a new psycho. It's a double line. This is a double new psycho. Rest in peace to the mighty
Norm MacDonald. Yeah, this happened while we were recording last time or we would have,
of course, discussed it. Yeah, I mean, there's just nobody that made me laugh
harder in the history of time. I don't think, you know, he's at least in the top five. I went
when I have my YouTube runs, it's two things. It's Jiminy Glick and it's Norm MacDonald on
shows or stand up or whatever it may be. One of the all time greats, a delivery all his own,
a fearless man. He made it about 24 hours of his death announcement before people started to
take shots at him. Yeah, for different things that he may or may not have done.
Um, nobody is saying justice should go on, you know, should go unseen or, or incorrect action
should go on, but nobody's saying anything like that. It just seems a little weird when you jump
in within 24 hours of the death announcement, when publicity for that person's name is at its height.
That seems a little strange to me. I don't understand why I don't understand why that
happens. And also without any frame of reference to specifics to what you're talking about or
specifics to what the situation was, or he allegedly did or whatever, it makes it even
harder when you start throwing out these broad strokes of he was known to sexually harass or
this or that, you know what I mean? It's like, it's getting, it makes it even broader and broader.
So I don't know if any of it's true. I hope it's not. If it is, I'm not saying anybody should go
unscathed, but for God sakes, I mean, it's like, it just feels like people are waiting to go for
you to go, I love this guy. And by the way, were people not, he was in trouble two years ago for
saying, uh, on Stern would, you know, what are you down syndrome or whatever? He said, I forget.
I was just listening to the thing. He was talking about, uh, you know, how people,
like in Louis CK's case, in the case of these abusers, their life and career is ruined
immediately. And that doesn't happen to the women. It's not fair that it happens to the men,
which is obviously a, or just a wrongheaded thing to say. And Howard was basically correcting him
and saying, look, man, I have, I've known women who have, who have been sexually assaulted in my
life. Believe me, it affects them. It affects them greatly. And for their whole life. I love that
Stern is now the mouthpiece for this. I know, I know, I know, I know. Jesus Christ. All right.
But Norm goes, uh, Howard, I hear you. And it's one of the few times I've heard him be sincere.
Uh, but he was like, I hear you. I mean, you'd have to have down syndrome to not know that, uh,
that the, these women also experienced some consequences and said it very seriously. And
then they cut to him on the view the next day going like, yeah, so, you know, you fucked up
when you got to apologize for your apology. Right, right. Right. I think what people couldn't
quite connect with him is that he was your, he was the funniest, smartest version of your,
like 70 year old kind of daughter and grandfather with sort of similar outlooks on life. And he
never really updated them, but his old school way of talking was kind of his charm. I just don't
think he, he bothered to update that when it came to matters of sexuality, talking to women,
et cetera. And when I, when I'm reading posts, like the complicated legacy of Norm McDonald
and all this stuff, I'm like, all right. All I had ever heard of him was that he was, he was,
um, asexual practically like that. El MacPherson really wanted to hook up with them after one of
the SNLs and he had no interest and like took a cab home and he was like, yeah, he speaks greatly
against sex in his stand. Yeah. He seems to just have no, no interest in sex at all. Now that
doesn't mean what you talk about in your standup is necessarily your life, but I know that's true.
Uh, but also too, like it's all I'm saying is this, I would never, um, discredit or dismiss
anybody with any sort of, uh, claim about anything that could have been detrimental to them
in any degree. It just, it just has gotten so convoluted that I don't even know anymore
that it's like, if did he make an inappropriate sexual joke? Right. And then that's considered
harassment. I think we've kind of lost the defining lines here a little bit.
Yeah. And the way in which it is, it is, uh, handled, unfortunately makes it even more
confusing. And, uh, you know, I think that's the reality of the whole thing. You know, that said,
yeah, well, this thing was using, it was using an interview with him to say, um, and look,
it sucks that we're now spending more time talking about this than we are about how funny the man
was. But yeah, should we, should we just go back to talking about how funny he is?
We totally can, but in the article, you know, they were interviewing norm and he was saying, uh,
look, you know, he's like, I've never drank in my, in my life. I don't drink. People always
think I'm drunk. And he goes, but sometimes, you know, I'll come up to a woman and
you know, just pretend to be drunk. Cause then for some reason, if you go up to a lady and you say,
Hey, you got a nice can, she'll slap you in the face. But if you're drunk, then she's kind of like,
Oh, you're crazy. So, but Norm's whole thing was talking in like three or four levels of sarcasm.
So I don't know if you read the really embarrassing New Yorker, one of those things,
the profile on him that was using his very sarcastic standup as proof that he was super
right -wing because of things he would say about like, it was, it's just absurd. Like there's no,
there's no looking at someone's work, someone's tone, someone's point of view anymore, uh,
to see like really clearly jokey interview clips from Norm MacDonald posted as fact after his death
to me is what's getting us into a bad area as well. And the headlines that you click on,
cause you're like, Oh my God, he said this. And you read the article and you're like, wait,
no, he didn't. But most people just read the headlines. It's fucked up in a way.
It is wild too. And even in this discussion, I don't think either of us has said anything wrong.
The fact that I am so hesitant in like even explaining like that I'm confused by the way
allegations. There's no room for confusion anymore. There's no space for it. It's so wild,
you know? But, uh, but anyway, onto the positive, uh, I love Norm MacDonald. I,
I met him. He was on my very first podcast ever. Uh, he was hilarious. He was extremely
genuine and, um, endearing with me. Uh, one of the greatest compliments I ever received was he said,
I would love when I was saying goodbye, he said, I would love to come see your stand -up if I can.
You're so smart and so funny. I mean, that's a huge, huge compliment to get from somebody
you admire that much. He was hilarious. He said many, many funny things to me and Sean O 'Connor
that day. Cause Sean was the guest and he was, and Norm was like, Sean was opening for Norm on the
road in Atlanta and Sean and Norm was like, you can come and do it in my room if you want, man.
Like, can we record it into the living room of his suite? And he was like in his bedroom
and then would like just come out and jump in and then walk back into the bedroom and come out,
jump in. It was an amazing experience. Um, and one I talked about for years, uh, and cherished for
years. Um, that all said, uh, that was the only time I ever met him, uh, or interacted with him.
Um, and he was great. And, uh, I hear stories like that about him a lot from people. Um,
and I've listened now to his audio book several times since he's, I think I've listened to it
two full times through since he died, uh, cause it's that weird, you know, you can't get enough
once the person's gone. Um, right. And I'm bummed because I always had a little quiet
dream in the back of my head that someday that would get turned into
a movie because it would be such a funny movie. Um, it would only work with him, but yeah,
yeah, exactly. So, uh, you know, and Artie Lang has been a very good friend of mine for many years.
And I know Artie and him were close and Artie. I think it's a pretty good judge of character.
If you're tight with Artie, like Artie is a good guy. Um, and, uh, yeah, it's a bummer, man. It's
losing irreverent comedians. We're losing them. Like they're just, they're dwindling away. And I
know a lot of people out there will think, well, that's good. Cause the times are changing. Um,
I don't think it's good. I think, you know, w what are we going to do? Just have South Park
and that's it. You know, like what the fuck else is left? Um, you know, you need guys like this,
you need the Carlins and the, and the McDonald's and the, uh, you know, to, to go on in the
chapelles to go on TV shows and, and, and panel and say some wild shit sometimes, you know?
Yeah, he was the best. I mean, even when his standup would just be no, no politics,
no sex, not just clean. I mean, there's just, there were a few people funnier. I saw him,
I mean, of course he's known for saying shocking things, but I mean, just
his, his material about, uh, finding a dead body or like things as he got kind of older, he got
wiser and deeper as well. And there was a lot of material about death,
which clearly he knew was, was, was coming for him as it comes for us all. But, uh, his,
his stuff in the last five years or so, about even up to his last set, which I saw about COVID
right before everybody got locked down was some of the best stuff about COVID that I saw,
certainly comedy wise, but he was awesome. My wife took me down to Anaheim to see him
because she knew how much I loved them. And I laughed so hard that I wanted to leave.
I was embarrassed and I couldn't stop laughing, but he's one of the few guys who could do that
to me every single time. Dirty work saw it repeatedly. I have two have listened to this
audio book twice. I think I've ever read a book twice in my life. Uh, he just was on another level
for sure. An original really influenced by anybody except like vaudeville comics or something,
you know, like, uh, that Bob Saget roast was, uh, I think rightly the thing I saw circulated
the most, but I mean, I can't even, can't even convey to somebody who wasn't watching that when
it aired the first time, like what a shocking, amazing piece of comedy that was my favorite
of him ever is the, when he's on Conan promoting the book and he starts talking about his wife,
first he says he's deeply closeted, gay. Yes. And then, um, and, uh, Conan's,
which I often wondered about, by the way, no, I know, cause that's never known. He's told the
truth. And then he's like, you know, and then Conan's like, so you're gay. And he's like,
what are you talking about? I'm not gay. I said, I'm deeply closeted.
Wait, did he do that on Larry King and Conan? Yeah.
Okay. Yeah. And, uh, deeply closeted meaning I'll never admit to it. So no, I'm not gay.
Yeah. It's just weird. Like, there we go. There's the knee.
Yeah. Just a weird prep. It's just such an odd premise, but my favorite part in that interview,
and it's my favorite thing I've ever seen him do probably is when he's doing the, uh,
the old battle acts jokes about his fake wife. Yeah. And he goes, uh, he goes, I'm looking in
the mirror the other day. I says, honey, I says, I'm fat, I'm bald and I'm old. I need you to give
me a compliment. And my wife says, you got perfect eyesight. I said, you're a dirty dog.
Yeah. The dirty dog is what brings it home.
Yeah. And then of course, Conan then has to go, what is this? What is the, is this a 1920s radio
show? Ha ha. What'd you say norm? What'd you say? Shut the fuck up, Conan. Jesus Christ.
Stop. I love Conan. Oh, shut up. I'll not have you bad mouth Conan.
I like Conan, but let the man do his bit. Why do you have to jump in?
Part of the bit is the mock outrage. I mean, that's, that was part of the bit for
it's not Mac outright. He starts riffing and talking into the mic and a 20s voice.
What'd you say? We got fair, fair field cigarettes. Say it's shut up. Conan,
let the genius work. I would argue going is also a genius. Carson never did that. Carson laid back
in the cut, babe. Carson was nowhere near as funny as Conan. Are you insane? Carson
was an outstanding host, a great late night figure, a reassuring grandfather type. He was
nowhere near as sharp and funny off the cuff as Conan. I think Conan is off the cuff. Very funny.
Yep. Carson also didn't have a desperate need for attention at all. That's true. That's true.
But I, you know, I've met him. He's always been nice to me. That desperate need for attention. I
Conan with your foul and you like, you like those guys or would you rather,
would you rather let's, let's, let's pray. I have lost all respect for the art form of late night
talk show host. I haven't seen one in a long time that I actually enjoy. Let's put it that way.
It's pretty much done. I think Kimmel is the last of the ones I've, I kind of like, I'm like, okay,
like that's, there's like an old school quality there. I kind of enjoy it. I don't love the show
because the format is the format, no matter what, how you slice it, but I do like him.
Fallon. I don't mind. Do I think he's great? No.
Fallon is a nightmare. What are you talking about? I mean, his personality, I don't mind the show.
No, I will never watch it. I wouldn't watch it with a gun to my head. Fallon is like hanging
out with a guy on heavy cocaine who's G rated. It's like the worst combination. It's like a
coked out muppet, but not one of the good muppets. I say all this and I'll do any of these shows if
they come, come calling, but yeah, I'm thinking Conan's got the number five podcast in the country
right now. Might want to get on that at some point. Yeah. But I'm a thick of the night man,
Alan picks late night, uh, offering. I was always a Snyder man myself. I love Tom Snyder
and I love, I think Letterman was the last of the Mohicans in my opinion. Um, I mean, you're,
you're leaving a lot of great comedy on the floor with Conan. I get that Letterman was your guy.
Conan is very funny. I don't, it's Jim Carrey ish at times. It's too much. You're like, dude,
take a pill. Just relax. Okay. Like, like I don't need the it's not the show is your show.
The show's not about you. So I don't need you jumping in every five minutes or every five
seconds with, with, with a riff. It becomes too much. I'm not saying he always did that.
I'm just saying he did. He had a tenant. We all know he had a tendency to do that. You know,
like so, so few funny people in the world, Joe, so few funny people. You're going to sit here and
you're going to put Conan's name in your mouth. I, I think he's very funny.
Let's go to the movie corn. I think he's very fun. All right. We're going to the,
uh, I saw a picture called the eyes of Tammy Faye. Oh, how was it? The reviews were lukewarm.
I completely loved it. I, when I saw a show, Walter was directing it. I of course love
show Walters, uh, comedy. I've liked his movies, but I think for the most part, all of them,
I just was kind of like, how is a guy with his sense of humor going to handle this material
when he's got, you know, Jessica Chastain basically in clumps makeup. And the, the answer is he
handles it beautifully. It's a very, very difficult tone because these guys are at their core kind of
SNL characters. They were always larger than life, ridiculous people, but, uh, the tone, my guess of
the tone that he tried to emulate is itonia. And that winds up being the perfect choice for this
material because it's sensational material with outrageous characters, but played relatively
straight, uh, and just kind of letting the costumes, the makeup, the outrageous behavior
speak for itself. But Jessica Chastain is incredible in it. She's an actress. I sort of indifferent to,
I guess I've never hated her or anything, but she's awesome in it. Uh, she kind of blows
Andrew Garfield out of the water, but Andrew Garfield is also very good as Jim Baker,
Cherry Jones and Vincent D 'Onofrio as Jerry Falwell. Excellent supporting performances.
I thought it was great. It's funny. Uh, it's nuts. It's, uh, I was talking to the guy when I bought
my soda before the show, who was like 20, he had no idea who these people are. So, uh, it's a great
way to be introduced to them. If you were not alive in the eighties and watching the insane shit,
these two did, but check it out. Very relevant to today's times and very, very relevant to what's
going on with Trump, Fox news, et cetera. Hmm. Okay. Very interesting. Thank you.
I watched in the tall grass in the tall, tall, uh, it is an adaptation of a Stephen King and
Joe Hill novella. By the way, how many books has Joe Hill written a thousand
books? Has he written a thousand books? A lot. Everything on everything on shutter,
Netflix, Joe Hill. Yeah, this is a book King and Hill co -wrote together a novella. Excuse me.
It's about a cornfield that a pregnant woman and her brother come across.
I'm sorry, a grass field, tall grass, not corn. Um, they hear a little boy calling from the outside
that he's lost in there and he needs their help. They go in to help the kid
and suddenly they realize something's wrong. They can't get out of the grass.
So something evil is afoot. What is it? It's a big mystery. Um, I'm not going to try to get into
describing the ins and outs of the plot. It's a little bit confusing, but kind of cool. Um, very
mysterious. Patrick Wilson plays a very interesting character in it. Um, it's the
best I've seen him in a long time in something. Uh, he's probably the most famous name in this
thing. You know what I'd like to see Patrick Wilson in? My asshole. Folks. Um, but as far as
Stephen King and Joe Hill adaptations go, this one was, was well done. It was very poorly reviewed,
which I don't understand. I think Netflix, one of the things they've done very well are these
King adaptations. I like Gerald's game. I like 1922. I like this. Okay. Um, it was the best of
the Joe Hill adaptations I've seen. I never watched lock and key, but Nasferatu or however
you're supposed to pronounce it. I thought was painfully boring. I think both episodes that
they've adapted now from him, three now they've adapted from him on creep show, which includes
the new, uh, episode first story in the newest season. Um, I find them very forgettable if not
bad. Um, but this was intriguing and I liked it quite a bit. I'm not saying he's a bad writer.
I'm just saying, you know, I was not a big fan of his tales from the dark side graphic novel
adaptation of the stories he prepped for the reboot that never happened, but this I enjoyed
and it's got that old school Stephen King flavor to it. It's spooky. It's weird. There's a field,
something sinister as a foot, something supernatural is happening. It's all the stuff
you want from a King book in the classic sense versus what he does now, where it'll be a story
about a detective hunting for an Institute where they train children that have special powers or
whatever the fuck, which for some reason is 2 ,400 pages long. It has several Trump commentary
chapters in it. Yeah. Yeah. It's just like, all right, I, I got his new one on audible.
And then I read somebody's comment on Twitter who said like, he does one of those things where he's
like, uh, and the, the kid who had just come from town where he saw the new, uh, the new movie,
it chapter two. And then in parentheses, like he didn't like it that much or something like
he's referencing his own work in his books. It's like, Jesus Christ that I just made that up,
but it was something similar to that. Uh, I saw the voyeurs and the reason I want to mention this
because I have long bemoaned on this podcast, the, the vanishing of sexuality in the cinema
and that new nun lesbian flick. No, but I'll be seeing that too. Yeah. This, uh, you know,
Joe's always like, you got porn. What do you, what do you, why are you so horny? Why do you
need to see naked gals? I don't understand it, but I do. It's, uh, it was a big part of, of me growing
up. My, my constant desire to see movies with naked women in them, uh, or men or men. And the
voyeurs is, is exactly that it is a modern day, erotic thriller. Uh, I'm watching this thing,
thinking, are they going to go for the nudity or is it going to be one of those erotic thrillers
where it's like a girl on top of a guy with her bra on and he's got the sheets pulled up over her
like how no one has ever had sex before. Um, it's chock full of nudity. It's Sydney Sweeney
from, uh, euphoria. She is outrageously attractive. Uh, you know, she was in once
upon a time in Hollywood under the silver lake. She's in a lot of pictures, but she is
right in the movie. It's a, it's a couple. She's part of the kind of tame couple. And then they
across the street, much like in rear window, this couple who appears to be having a lots of hot,
hot sex, but when the women woman leaves for work, the boyfriend is just fucking anybody who comes
by, he's fucking all kinds of people. And she starts watching and then she starts kind of
cracking it while she's watching. And then she's like behind her boyfriend, jacking him off while
they're watching the other couple have sex. And you're like, this is what I wanted. Then of course
it turns to murder and intrigue and twists and turns. But if you're looking for a modern day
erotic thriller, it doesn't hit the heights of basic instinct or something, but it's still
very good. Something you would have found at blockbuster and kind of slipped it in with a
couple of more mainstream titles. The voyeurs is for you. It's on Amazon prime. And when you say
turns to murder, you mean the guy's murder in that ass, right? He's murdering that ass, but there's
also intrigue in the movie. I mean, it goes to lots of sinister places. I thought the story was
good. The twist, the turns worked, but also great crank material, great crank material.
Oh boy. Jesus Christ. Anyway, I watched the craft legacy, the sequel to the 90s hit the craft.
I watched the craft legacy, which was Emeril's take on the witches about the magic of cooking.
Bam. Yeah. A lot of that catchphrase. Bam. Yeah. Yeah. And then Bam Margera's catchphrase was
Emeril. Yep. Folks. Um, I, this is a movie we could have done on this podcast, Pat, but I would not
ask you to sit through this thing. I didn't have the interest. Yeah, it is. I was excited to see
it because I liked the original craft. We reviewed it on here. Yeah. I heard pray tell that Feroza bulk
makes an appearance in this thing. So it is, it was a sequel, not a reboot. Um,
I was excited to watch it. I really was. I got a little hesitant when I saw it was Blumhouse
and that it was PG 13, but I thought, let me put those prejudices aside and, and, and enjoy this
thing. And for the first 35 to 40 minutes or so, I did. There's a scene right at the beginning
where the daughter and her mother are moving to live with her new stepfather played by David
Covey. And on their way to the house, Alanis Morissette comes on the radio, um, that song.
Uh, isn't it ironic? No, not that one. Uh, you ought to know. Not that one. Thank you, India.
Thank you. Disillusionment. Not that one. One hand in my pocket. Yeah, that one, that one.
Okay. All right. And they start singing it at the top of their lungs together. I'm looking at this
like, who has a relationship like this? What they're going to be mortified.
My mom and my sister's Alanis Morissette experience was my sister bought it at Target,
the cassette tape, put it in. My mom heard the line. Would he go down on you in a theater?
Would she go down on you in a theater? Ejected the tape and threw it out the window.
My mom did that with my ghetto boys. We can't be stopped CD. Yeah, she really did. Um, anyway,
I guess they could be stopped by an angry mother. Yeah. It starts fine enough. You're
watching this thing. You're like, okay, it's, of course it's Blumhouse. So every single male,
particularly the white ones in the movie is a paper thin piece of garbage. They're like bullies.
It's just like so absurd after a while, like just the way that they're bullies. It's, it's just like,
guys, go to a school and research bullies and see what they're like now. Do you know what I mean?
See how they operate now. They're not still walking up to kids in letterman jet, wearing
letterman jackets, you know, shoving them into lockers or whatever, but whatever. I'm looking
past all that. They create alt accounts on social media to drive you to eating disorders
and suicide. Yeah, it's like, yeah. So anyway, um, but you know, um, there's, there's a funny
twist early on where they use, the girls use their magic to make the biggest asshole in school,
like super woke. Okay. So that's kind of funny because he's like this piece of shit misogynist.
Yeah. And then all of a sudden, like they're in class and he's like, I'm sorry, what you're
saying right now is very triggering. And if you can't understand that, you need to excuse
yourself. Like, so there's like some fun they have with that. And then the movie just goes bad
shit. You see the twist coming a mile away that David Duchovny is about to become, he seems like
a great guy in the beginning. I mean, this is why Blumhouse stinks. The first scene you meet
Duchovny, he's like the nicest guy in the world, more charming than you can imagine. Yeah. In the
second scene, he's like to his stepdaughter, like we don't lie in this house and you've disappointed
me young lady, like just an asshole. And it's like, where, where the mom is like, Hey, I think we
need to slow down. And he goes, no, we don't need to slow down. I have a no tolerance policy for,
you know, like, can you evolve the character sort of for Christ sakes, it's like literally like
Harvey Dent two -face. Like it's that split of personality. So you're like, okay, let me guess
he turns out to be an asshole. And then you're going, you know what, actually it'd be kind of
cool if they were misdirecting you and you thought he's supposed, you're supposed to think he's an
asshole. Then he actually turns out to save the day. No, he turns out to be a shape shifting wizard
at the end of the movie. All right. Who wants the female's power. Are you getting the metaphor?
He says, was it better or worse than the Blumhouse black Christmas?
It was, and I believe I texted you about this. It was about a rung or two above black Christmas.
Okay. Which is not saying much. Not saying much. That Christmas was disastrous. Yeah. This was like,
it at least kept you for a little while. And then you were like, what the fuck? Right.
Um, it's crazy. It's like, it's, it's, it's, he does this whole speech at the end where he's like,
men need the power. That is how it works. Do not upset the bad. It's terrible. Yeah. I've
burned a lot of bridges in this, in this podcast. I've said, I've attacked Conan. I've attacked
Blumhouse yet again. I've attacked David Duchovny star of California cation. Um,
then you find out just before that happens, that she's the main character is adopted.
And she was never told she was adopted by her mom because the woman she was adopted from at the
institution made her swear. She'd never speak of her daughter or tell her about her mother. So what
does the mother do? Of course she comes clean with it all eventually. And then the end of this movie,
again, you see this coming a mile away, is the adoptive mother taking the daughter to meet her
biological mother, which the biological mother made her promise she would never do. And they
don't explain that part. They're, they're playing like, they're playing like, uh, uh, um, uh,
Gilmore girls music in the background as they go to meet the mother in the institution. You're
like, what are you doing? You're not supposed to be doing this. That was the deal. And then of
course, the mother is for ruse a bulk, which makes you wonder then you're like, how the fuck
does she have a baby? She's been in prison since the, since the first movie. Yeah.
It just sucked. It just sucked. It was just a terrible movie. What is it? The craft origins
or something or legacy? Oh, yeah. Yeah. Okay. Okay. Uh, I saw, I'll do a quick one here. I
rewatched Oscar from my, uh, from my youth, sly Stallone's God. Why Oscar? You know, I remembered
it being kind of the end of the road for Landis. And I was like, I didn't like this movie when I
was a kid. I like John, John Landis's movies through the eighties. Let's check this kind
of last one out and see if I missed a, a hidden classic. I didn't, uh, Stallone plays snaps
provolone. He makes his Angelo snaps provolone. Uh, he makes his dad, Kirk Douglas, uh, a promise
on his death bed. A lot of this was a time in the early nineties when every movie started with a
promise to a parent on the death bed. Honeymoon in Vegas. Uh, maybe I can only think of two, this
and Honeymoon in Vegas, but, uh, Kirk Douglas is like, you gotta go straight son. So Stallone tries
to go straight. It's a stacked cast. It's a very, very young Marissa Tomei who's funny. Uh, Tim
Curry is funny. You got Peter Rieger, Chaz Palminteri, Harris, Harry Shearer, Joey Travolta.
Uh, you know, you recognize everybody in it. Richard Romanis, Romanis, whatever,
a terrible performance from an actress named Jocelyn O 'Brien, who I've never seen before or
since. Um, but they're trying to do a screwball comedy where everybody's talking real fast and
the dialogue's real funny. The problem is the dialogue isn't funny and Stallone can't talk fast.
So it never really takes off. And I read an interview with Landis who's like,
Pacino was going to do it. We had gotten together $2 million for Al Pacino to play snaps provolone.
And he called me the night before and was like, they offered me 3 million for Dick Tracy.
Can you match it? I said, no, but you know, went and did Dick Tracy and got nominated for an Oscar
and got nominated for a crazy performance. But I was imagining with Pacino, it certainly would
have been a better movie, a funnier movie, but just at its core, nothing about it really works.
It's a, it's a, it's a relationship based comedy where you don't care about any of the relationships
or what happens to any of them. So it doesn't work, but I can't say I hated it. I don't think
it's deserving of like being one of these legendary bombs. It's just, it's that period
where Stallone was trying to do comedy and everybody was like, we don't want this slide.
We don't want it. Yeah. And I still don't want it. Sorry.
I saw, I can't decide which one I should do last year.
I'll go with communion.
Walkin? Yeah. Never saw it.
Don't. Okay. Never watch it. Yeah. Not worth your time.
Real slow burn.
Um, it's about a man that gets abducted by aliens. It's based on the autobiographical
account, uh, written by, I forget the act, the author's name, but quick walk and plays that guy
in the movie. Uh, a guy that by the way has been, you know, uh, there's a lot of holes
in his story at this point. Um, he, you know, what can I say about the film? It's very dry.
It has its moments of suspense that are interesting. Walkin gives a pretty solid
performance in it. Opposite walk in is, um, Mammot's, uh, what's her name? Mammot's first wife,
Rebecca Pidge. No, that's she's a second wife. Uh, Lindsay Krauss. Yeah. Lindsay Krauss,
gives a very good performance in it. Um, you know, the alien sequences are sort of haunting
there. They don't hold a candle to like fire in the sky. Right. Um, and you know, there's plenty
of room here for walking to do his walk and thing because he's playing a guy that's like
desperately trying to hold onto his sanity. And there's a lot of really weird sequences where
you don't know if he's dreaming or if he's having visions. There's a whole subplot where he goes to
a therapist who, who does hypnotherapy. So she hypnotizes him and he goes back to the scene of
the spaceship and kind of lives out different experiences in real time while he's hip, while
he's hypnotized. And those are really weird and off beat. Um, but at the end of the entire run,
you just don't care. You're just like, yeah, he got abducted. I guess early on when this came out,
it was pretty, it was still pretty new. That whole like alien abduction thing or,
or the idea that there were real accounts coming out about it. Yeah. Uh, and I think that raised a
lot of interest in the film, but at the end of the day, uh, it just didn't really, it was not that
interesting. I always wanted to see it. I'm glad I saw it. It was directed by,
let's see, communion 1989. What's this guy's name? It's based on the book by Whitley Stryber
was the author's name. Uh, and it was directed by
Philip Mora, who also made, uh, burning, not burning. This is just deadly air, Joe.
You got, you got the, the constant bumping of the table. You're, you're, you're fumbling through an
IMDb page. I mean, it's just, just death to listen to. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Howling to
I only saw howling one, but you also made the beast within, which is, is an okay horror flick.
Isn't the howling to called like my mother is a werewolf or sister is a werewolf. Oh wow. Pretty
close. Yeah. But it's pretty bad when you've got multiple movies on your resume and you're looking
and talking about one of them and you're going, the howling to was better than this.
Yeah. Uh, I won't say it. I mean, you've, you've checked a box for me. I don't need to see communion.
I like checking box. Gross. Uh, folks, we're going to talk about what weirdly has become
at one of the biggest horror pictures of the year. Uh, malignant. I have seen so many people
raving about this. I have seen a lot of people who hate it. It's oddly, uh, controversial, like on
letterbox, you know, people have really strong opinions on it. I've seen people call it a
masterpiece, which seems extreme. I've seen people say it sucks, which seems extreme,
basically malignant, which I have now watched twice. Uh, I really liked a lot the first time.
I liked less the second time. I think it is a movie that was done kind of on the cheap over
COVID. There's some element of homage to like Giallo films or like, uh, Argento films, you know,
it's very violent. It's heightened. There's a Stuart Gordon feel to it. Like, you know, like
a lot of like the nurse will look in the camera and be like, bring him to me and like bite her
kind of stuff. Like that's a little over the top. The Giallo to the look of the killer is,
is very Giallo as well. Yeah. Some just, you know, extreme angles and whips and pans and stuff,
some really awesome shots that I have, I've seen before, but like, uh, you know, like following her
around the house from above and you go from room to room really, I think what they were doing there
is saying, I mean, it looked to me like a movie that was shot entirely on sound stages. And I think
they were like, let's just build the set for real and then shoot over it and do this really cool
kind of mouse in a, in a trap kind of shot. So that to me is, is the fun part of the first hour
is kind of that it's in this little state of like being a little over the top and heightened.
But then the third act with the final reveal, which is spoiler that this woman has a twin,
an evil twin that was absorbed into her brain. The doctors tried to cut it out, but couldn't
because they would remove her brain. It's the, it's the ed ed. What's the famous story? Like the,
the, the curious case of Edgar, whatever about the guy that had the face in the back of his neck
that was supposed to be a twin brother would say terrible things to him. And that was a real thing.
Supposedly. I mean, the guy did exist whether or not that, that I think they depicted on American
horror story at one point, but it's one of those things where it's like they were supposed to be
twins, but the twin for the most part was absorbed into her body except for its face and mouth. I
guess, I don't know. Like this is where it starts to get a little kooky. The rules are kooky. The,
the it's an imaginary friend, but then you learned it was real and a twin. And that,
that to me was all really fun. And the way they reveal it is great. They're cutting back and forth
between people watching the old video of the surgery and the present day reveal of this twin
popping out of her head and kicking ass in a jail cell, which is an awesome and crazy and violent
and fun scene in watching it at home. I realized that really fun third act amounts to about 10
minutes of screen time. And the rest kind of drags a little bit in a second viewing for the most part,
James Wan is a guy who directs, I think, really fun horror without ever quite putting the stamp
on it that you want. It's like he makes movies that are a little more interesting than your
average horror movie, but I just wish he had a little more of a personal style to him, I guess.
However, this movie was really fun. The score uses a lot of where is my mind by the pixies
mixed with a score. I don't know if you caught that Joe, but they're kind of like sampling it
for the score. Yeah, I like that. I mean, whereas my mind has been used a lot at this point, but
when the thing starts kicking ass, the movie is pretty awesome. The kills are great. And I like
that aspect of it. I didn't recognize any of these actors. I didn't think anyone was really
excellent in the film, but for like low budget horror with some really cool kills and fun,
I had a good time. It's kind of the modern day drag me to hell, but not as good,
in my opinion, tonally, which I knew we had a problem when you said, when you text me and said,
it's like drag me to hell, but not as good drag. Hell is no masterpiece, but it's enjoyable.
Look, everything you just described is accurate and insane. If you never saw this movie and
listening to you describe that it's confusing and it's crazy and it's wild. And you're like,
I guess I think I get what you mean. Now put on top of that, all the unnecessary elements that
this movie has that for some reason, her body was able to fully absorb the twin to where it,
you couldn't see it anymore. Right. Until it re -emerges years later. Why does it re -emerge?
Because her abusive boyfriend slams her into a wall and she cuts her head open. And for some
reason that awakens the twin and it crawls back out of not out, it's just to the backside of her
backside, whatever the fuck. You think of this time was like the devil as they refer to it as
the devil at certain points in the movie. You'd think it'd be able to bust out of a half inch of
skull tissue without needing this. There's that, especially when it's not dormant the entire time,
talking to her through her childhood, you just, it's just not physically,
it's not visible anymore. Yeah. Then they add this element that for some reason the twin is
superhuman. So not only was it a horribly, horribly, horribly malformed and crippled
unable body of sorts that was just kind of hanging mutated into the back of her head and back and
whatever. Now when it re -emerges, it's superhuman. And when it takes her body over, it's able to do
kill 20 people in a room and do acrobats and scale walls and crawl around everywhere and
whatever. Okay, fine. Then they add another element that it's able to talk to others through
electricity, which what the, which the only connection to that that I could make was that
the way they shocked, the way they got rid of this twin to begin with when she was a little girl is
they shock it out of her or they shock it dead with like the fribulators or whatever.
Yeah. And then like, so I guess that gives it electronic power. I don't know, man. I mean,
the electricity angle was super unnecessary to me and didn't make sense. But it's a movie where
you're, you're sustaining disbelief from, from the jump, but the electricity seems like a bridge
too far to make for sure. And then, and then not to mention that every time it takes her body over,
it like breaks her limbs and flips them to work in the other direction.
And then that's just never addressed. Like it's never like, man, my arm hurts.
You know, so it is way, way, way over detailed, way too many layers going on here.
Is it a fun movie? It is at times the third act plays a lot like a horror based John Wick.
I ain't mad at it. There is a lot of what seems to be tongue in cheek or self -effacing humor
in the film, a lot of what seems to be purposeful, bad acting. I did not catch that when I was
watching it. I texted Pat about halfway through and said, dude, what the fuck is with this movie,
man? Like this is really bad. And Pat wrote back and you said, this is, this isn't, I think it's
supposed to be tongue in cheek. Once you said that, I was like, oh, like, okay, I guess I could
see that. But as my friend pointed out, the problem is it's, it's attempting to do low budget,
almost drive in or grind house horror on a clearly gigantic budget. So it doesn't play.
It doesn't play you. The, the average moviegoer that this movie is being marketed to is not a
hardcore underground horror movie. This is a Cineplex movie. This is, this is middle America
Cineplex, you know, and I'm not saying horror fans don't exist out there, but you know what I mean.
It's a popcorn movie. I find it hard to believe that the average person is going into this movie
with the knowledge of horror history to, to know that this is supposed to be some deconstructionist
approach to horror or whatever. Maybe I'm wrong. I don't know. That's hard. I'm hard pressed to
believe that. Well, and I, you know, we don't know necessarily that that's what was intended.
That's not really ever been James Wan style before even something like dead silence about the killer
dummy. He wasn't really approaching it tongue in cheek. And I think that movie would have
benefited from maybe being a little more tongue in cheek. So it's hard. It's hard to say what the
tone they're going for is. They don't quite go far enough for it to be parody, but it's also never
quite serious enough to be like a terrifying horror movie. I was saying to my friend, Chrissy.
Yes. If you want this to be, cause she was like, I loved it. I thought it was kind of wild and
goofy and whatever. And I said, look, I understand. I get that element of it.
I said, but if you want to make a movie, that's as wild as reanimator. Yeah. You've got to make
a movie as wild as reanimator. The opening credit sequence should not play like the beginning of
which the opening credits in this do the opening credits. See, see it should be melodramatic
strings and crazy music. Oh, we're going on a ride here. This is why it should be Hitchcockian
reanimator. Part one features a scene where a decapitated body takes its decapitated head and
forces oral sex on a woman, Barbara Crampton, reanimator too. They put bat wings on the head
and it flies around haunting people. You've got to have elements like that in there. If you want
this to be zany, like, but there's nothing like that in this there's over the top violence.
That's disturbing. There's a killer that is supposed to be scary. There's nothing funny
about the killer. Um, no, there was, there was no laughing in a, in a pretty crowded theater.
So I think people were taking it seriously. It's, it's, it's confusing to me as to whether or not
James Wan was intentionally making a tongue in cheek, as you said, but let's talk James
Wan for a minute here. I thought he did solidify himself with an original voice with the conjuring.
I saw scares in the original conjuring. I'd never seen before in a movie. I thought it was
really interesting. Loved it. I thought saw was when I saw it in the theater, forgettable.
I'm still not a huge saw fan. We've talked about it. Um, but it's a passable serial killer movie.
Like, you know, it's not bad. Obviously some people think it's great. Dead silence is a bad movie.
It's a very bad movie. Conjuring is, is a really solid movie. Conjuring two, in my opinion is the
same exact movie, but like a better, like heightened, more heightened, more intense version.
And now you got this. So an Aquaman, I thought was not good. We're in it. Say it.
And Aquaman was another one where people were like, I can't tell if this is supposed to be serious
or not. Right. Like, so one of my favorite tones is slightly heightened horror. And I love that.
And he's, he doesn't quite push it enough or something. It's just, uh, it's hard to put a
on the tone of this movie because the, what I think a lot of reviews are reviewing what
this should have been by, by just pushing it a little click to the right. Um, I think I agree
with Joe. It's, it's, uh, it's fun, but it's a little too reserved. It's, it's even more reserved
than drag me to hell. You know, that, that movie had more fun with its premise. I thought that said
a lot of shitty horror out there. I think malignant is pretty well done. And I do think that the,
back half hour or so is really fun and really cool and a lot of good kills. Uh, and the concept,
I've never seen the thing off the back of the head. I thought it was pretty cool and pretty
well handled. And you know, showing the really pretty graphic surgery footage helped a lot
because even though you know, it's not real, uh, it helps sort of grounded in reality. They show
you it done. And you're like, all right, I buy it. There were some, excuse me, there were some
twists. I thought the reveal was cool. Yeah. I guessed almost immediately that they were
Siamese twins of some kind or something along those lines. I mean, they kind of hit you over
the head with it. She was a doctor who specialized in reconstructive surgery of children. You're like,
okay, you know, in the opening sequence, you said you've been a very bad boy and now we're
focused on a woman. There's clearly there's a sibling relationship going on here. Some
something, something weird, or I thought maybe, maybe she was a boy and now she's a girl,
you know, or, you know, but, but, um, anyway, I thought, uh, there were some cool twists.
Even though I kind of saw it coming, I thought the reveal of the second kid was cool. I thought the
reveal of when, when the, when the, when her biological mother escapes the imprisonment of
the killer and falls through the floor and then lands in her house. And you realize the killer's
in her attic the whole time. I thought that was really cool. Um, and I thought the John Wicks
sequences were really cool too. Um, you know, this all said, I thought that there were some
borderline, uh, bad writing, um, and some bad, I couldn't stand at the very end when like,
she traps him in a prison in her mind and you see him in the prison and like, this is stupid, man.
Um, but all in all, not a bad effort. I blame the studio probably more than I blame James Wan.
This felt to me like it could have been crazier, but the studio stepped in and marketed it
incorrectly and maybe didn't let him go as zaniest. He maybe wanted to, you know, but like drag me to
you got an eyeball flying into her mouth from across the room. You got an old, I think vomiting
on her at one point. Like, you know, you gotta have a little, a few things like that in there
to make, you know, this is supposed to be crazy. It was kind of lacking those moments, except when
we first see the thing with its hands coming out of the back on the video, which kind of reminded
me of like basket case or one of those, you know, or old eighties horror movies that that was kind
of fun and funny. I mean, uh, yeah, I think Joe and I both liked it, but, but would have liked it
pushed in a little more extreme direction. My hog is slightly up my hog straight out on this one.
Yeah. All right. We'll be back next time with a very special episode where we're reviewing a movie
that is not horror, but is horrifying in some ways. Norbit. Thanks folks. Thank you very much.
We'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.