I've seen you when I was in love, I see you when I saw you.
When the day come I feel like carrying and I'm a dreamer.
I've seen you when I was in love, I see you when I was in love, I see you when I was in
love.
Welcome to We'll see you in hell everybody.
It's the podcast where we talk about the flicks, the dicks, and the chicks.
Today's episode is the watcher for some reason I was trying to sing.
I'll be watching you by the police, but started singing the puffed antifersion, which is great too.
I was just to find that song very moving. That was an honor of big if I'm not mistaken.
It was.
Um, the boy for a lot.
I hate, I hated, I hated when puffy started doing that.
When he was a bad boy for a lot of songs.
And no, when he was bad boy for like the 80s, I didn't like that.
But anyway, the watcher, not to be confused with the docuseries about Pat down at the men's locker room, folks.
Look, that's all I do is watch.
That's not a crime.
And sometimes I'll be like, Hey, you dropped your towel there.
And then I'll kind of look over the nose of my sunglasses as they bend over, but that's also not a crime.
Do you ever hear a standing on the corner, the, the old standard song?
I've heard standing on the corner with phone booth in my hand.
Remember that one?
And how to be.
Ever since the day we met?
It was, it was sampling some old blues.
It was sampling BB King and it was called like radio primitive Gods or something?
It was a massive hit in the late 90s.
I'm gonna bring it up.
Joe you must have heard this song.
Well, we look for that standing on the corner.
I think I'm right.
Primitive radio Gods.
Uh, the first first question that comes up.
What happened to primitive radio Gods?
What song is sampled in standing outside a broken phone booth with money in my hand,
which is the name of the song. And the sample is a BB King song called How Blue Can You Get?
That's all. Okay. You never heard you heard that song, yeah. I mean, I don't remember.
I'm sure I have. I just don't remember. It was good. I liked it. Standing on the corner,
the standard popularized by Dean Martin, who's one of Dean Martin's big hits contains the lyric,
you know, you can't go to jail for what you're thinking. And the quarter is standing. The
course is standing on the corner, watching all the girls go by. A brother, you can't go to jail for
what you're thinking. That's great. That's disturbing. I love when the oldies are like sort of
accidentally disturbing. My favorite is one that, of course, are my boy Phil Spector produced.
And nobody knew for some reason, even though he wrote this song. But it's called He Hit Me,
parentheses. It felt like a kiss. Jesus Christ. And the song literally is a very, very catchy song.
But it was done by the crystals who did, who did like that, those Scorsese songs, you know,
like the big ones. Then he kissed me to do Ron Ron, etc. And the lyrics are basically, he hit me,
but it felt like a kiss because it was him showing me that he loved me. That's what the song is.
That is fucking heavy. Yeah. It really is. It's like, I knew that when he was willing to go to these
depths that it meant he really, truly loved me. Which is probably what Phil Spector told the women that
he would beat throughout the many years day. He did that. That's intense. That's intense.
Latch, intense. What were we talking about? What's going on in the world of entertainment?
It's we're heading into Oscar season. I'm here in a little, I want to see the Fableman's,
the new Spielberg joint about his life. I've been waiting for him to do something personal for
since Schindler's left really. I'm excited. I'm not mad at it. I can't say I'm excited.
Yeah. I will look. I don't get excited anymore. But I will watch it. Let's put it that way.
There. So K, K, Hugh Kwan, who played short -round in that picture of him with Harrison Ford recently.
Yeah. That was really sweet. And then he was in everything everywhere all at once.
Yeah. He was great in it. Yeah. Yeah. I'm making this big comeback. It's really cool.
You know, he's back on the scene. But, you know, I saw an interview with him the other day
where it was like, do you find the temple of doom racist towards your character? And he's like, no,
Spielberg put one of the first -ever Asian people front and center in an action movie that wasn't
being done at the time. Yeah. We had the best time ever on the movie. No. I don't think it was racist,
a racist portrayal. It's like, can the guy enjoy himself for five minutes? Seriously.
Seriously. Now he has to become the spokesman for something. Jesus Christ, man. He has to feel now.
He's been given a second shot at a career. And maybe he's been happy and didn't dwell on it, but
but he's an actor. So my guess is probably not. He's probably been very bitter for 30 years.
And he gets this amazing comeback that everybody loves and loves him in. And now he has to go into
every interview with a not in this stomach because these are the questions he gets asked. It's really
irritating to me. And then the people who deserve questions like, what the fuck is wrong with you,
you animal? They never get asked these questions. Right. Yeah. It just go on. It's like these politicians.
You're like, no matter who's interviewing them, the only time you get a genuine question that everyone
is thinking is when some psychopath screams at them at an event. Yeah. No, but you should all be
asking that question. I know that person is getting beaten in a back room right now, but these are the
questions you should be asking because you're a journalist. I almost brought this up on the last
episode. I took a pause for a second because I wasn't sure how I wanted to, what I wanted to say about
it, but I know what I want to say now and it's not for you, Joe. Usually you just barrel through.
My stance is not aftermath later. My stance is not controversial in this. I had to give it some
thought. But Jerry Seinfeld made a comment on Dave Chappelle's SNL monologue that he said he thought it was
poorly executed. I'm paraphrasing. So it was poorly executed. Said something along the lines that
made him feel uncomfortable and that a bigger conversation he thinks is is called for that wasn't
appropriate to have in the interview that he was having at the time. I sure. Okay, fine. We yes,
the bigger conversation is always a good idea. You know what? Whether you thought the monologue was okay
or whether you thought it was offensive, that's your business. I have no opinion on either side of
that. I don't want to hear it from Seinfeld. I'm getting a little tired of Jerry Seinfeld, who I'm a
huge fan of, fitting into whatever comedy mold he needs to fit into in the moment to be the most
popular he can be. He chastised dirty comedy for years when he got saw as or when he was seen as sort
of fading out or a yesteryear type of comic, he started running around with Louis CK and Chris Rock
and Ricky Gervais. And those guys were big guys in the edgy comedy. Then all of a sudden he was Mr.
edgy comedy's fine, dirty comedy's fine. He starts hanging out with Sebastian, all of a sudden he's
on stage doing angry comedy. You know, now he's going to be like, well, I thought what Dave did wasn't
well executed in this and that. It's like, Jerry, pick a fucking lane with this man. Like stop saying
you're the proponent of stand up. You're the guy that said when Kathy Griffin held up a bloody
decapitated Donald Trump head and everybody freaked out. I don't get what the big deal is it's a joke.
You can't play both sides of this all the time. Well, here's what's going on. A, and of course, you
know, Jerry Seinfeld is to me, what Woody Allen is to you. I hear bad things and they bounce right off
me. I just doesn't doesn't affect me because of how important Seinfeld was to my life. He's hugely
important. Yes. Yeah. But I think that they they put him on this pedestal and they make him the
elder statesman of comedy, because they go to him for all the big comedy questions. I don't think
he's necessarily saying, hey, as the lord of comedy, here are my thoughts. I think they just go to him
and whatever he says gets publicized. That said, it is a little shitty to like pick your issues
and when that when the issue is anti -semitism in your Jewish, then suddenly, you know, because Jerry
Seinfeld then can't go to temple on Sunday and face it if he's like, I don't care what Kanye says
about the Jews, because these are his people. And he was a lifelong Jewish man. So it wasn't, but it
wasn't a care when it's you, Jerry. Sure. It's sure. But it was also it wasn't a reaction to Kanye. It
was a reaction to Dave Chappelle's jokes about. Okay. Yes. That's that's so my point is and I'm sorry
that the criticism was that that Chappelle's comments were minimizing what Kanye said. Correct. What
did it do? It was vague. It was vague enough, but but judgmental. Look, the part that bothered me
was him saying, I thought Dave's thing was poorly executed. It's like, yeah, Jerry.
Okay. That's fine. You can think that. But this is Jerry Seinfeld from the 90s again. And for the
last 20 years, you've been trying to show us you're not Jerry Seinfeld from the 90s. Now when it's
convenient for you, because you don't want to take heat, you're going to now go back to that Jerry
Seinfeld. I just think it's I just I'm tired of him flip -flopping all the time. I'm just I'm just over
it. You know, it's just, you know, he also was a guy that talks about how important comedians are and
how hard it is was what we do in this and that. And then you see him in another documentary and he's
like, stop saying what we do is important. It doesn't matter. It's like that's true. That's true.
They would ever pops into your head in the moment to go against what the room thinks you should be saying
or whatever. Like, yeah, I'm not saying he should be saying, yay, Dave Chappelle. I'm just saying,
I'm just getting tired of it. It feels a little condescending at this point.
I do feel like the dam is breaking a little bit in terms of people being able to put up with the
PC and this of everything. I think that is breaking across the board. Yeah, I think so. I mean,
and I hear it quietly, but like my agents will say things to me like, you know, they're starting to
look for like a edgy comedy at HBO. It's like a secret. Like, okay. You know, and when I started
in this business, every comedy was a balls in your face literally, balls in your face edgy comedy.
And, you know, I don't think it's right at that time that every movie felt like a frat house movie.
Even adult entertainment, you know, it's things started getting gross. Don't get me wrong. And
when you watch some of these late 90s movies now, you're like, Jesus Christ.
But I do think there's a marketplace for them. You know, like, we're going to be,
we're going to create the most puritanical generation of all time and a generation that is
completely uncomfortable with sex. Like because we're so prudent now, they're not seeing sex,
they're not seeing sex joked about only knowledge I got about human sexuality was from
sleuthing out what movies we're talking about about it. You know, so kids now are getting no,
I mean, I guess it's better to get it from your parents anyway. But it's like, you also want to know
what, what people laugh about during sex, what the real sex issues are. That stuff used to come
from the movies and TV. And now it doesn't. So I don't, I don't know. I think we're just going to have
kids who are all diagnosed with severe anxiety disorders by age 12. I mean, where we have a
generation that is going to be completely fucked up. Here's the problem. And I'm not the,
not those of you with kids, not your kids. I'm talking about everyone else's kids. Your kids
are going to be great. Here's part of the problem. I'm scrolling through screen rant as we're in the
news cycle. Vert segment. Yeah. Just seeing if there's anything I missed. I didn't see this before.
John Lenguizamo, Lil' Mufana is publicly slamming the new
Super Mario Brothers movie. Here we go. For its non -inclusive casting. It's a guy.
John, we weren't Italian and either with Bob Hoskins. We're looking to the Super Mario Brothers movie
to lead us. What's the hell are we talking about at this point? What he's really saying is why
didn't I get a check? That's, that's nuts to me. It's, it's just guys. What are we, who are we,
and I go like I get it, we don't have leadership from anywhere else. So I guess we're going to try
to get it from Hollywood, but it's just funny. It's just funny to think that. Yeah. Anyway,
Johnny Lenguizamo, Johnny Lenguizamo, it's a wild time. But I do think people are about at capacity with
how much of this we'll put up with of everything. You know, Chappelle saying it shouldn't be scary.
It shouldn't be this scary to talk. Correct. You know, I think, I think, and arguably,
correct. And then there's always people who are like, well, if you, if you had a good heart,
you wouldn't be scared to talk, whatever else. It's like, no. That's bullshit. Difficult conversations is
how people get smarter, people get better. The, the times that I have made personal growth
breakthroughs in my life are when I said something and somebody pulled me aside and said, what the fuck?
Don't say, you know, I go, oh, right. I didn't know that was fucked up. Thank you. If we're not,
I get to say the thing is hiding sex from people. It's like the real world is going on,
but we're creating a generation that won't know how to deal with any of this.
Let's, should we go to the movie corners? It's too early. I don't think it's too early.
I got three for today. So I'm excited. Beautiful. Are they on a theme? I like it when they're on a theme.
I, uh, two of them are, I really just three episodes of, uh, of New Heart this week, or I tried
to stick to this damn autommnal movies thing. It was real hard. There's not a lot to choose from,
but you let me know when you get to autumn in New York. I got, I got two autumn horror movies that
one of them showed up on some best movies to watch in November. Yeah. Uh,
brand Stoker's Dracula. I was surprised to see it on the lists, but, but it is, it does feel sort
of like a fall type of movie. You know, I just got it in the 4K. Love it. I just bought the god,
this is one of these movies. I just bought the god damn thing on Blu -ray because I had the fucking DVD
forever. And then the 4K comes out. And I'm now I'm standing at Best Buy the other day. And I'm like,
that the Untouchables and Flash Gordon. And I'm like, do I got to buy these again? Like,
God damn it. I got to tell you, Joe, I've heard the Arrow Flash Gordon is one of the best looking 4K
discs available. But it's only a 4K transfer. No, I got a 4K, I have a 4K version of Flash
Gordon, it's available. Did you watch it? I haven't because I didn't have a 4K TV, but now I do.
I just got it set up. I'm very excited, folks. I got a real nice 4K television and player.
So I'm going to be watching like the stars do. I think I have a 4K TV. I've thought I had it
this whole time. And now I'm starting to doubt that I have it. I don't know. You might not. I'm
in Best Buy the other day. And I start looking at it. It's going to be Black Friday. I could use a bigger
TV. Yeah. Let me look. I go over to the TV section. They got 8K TVs now. It never ends.
No, it never ends. They got an 8K TV out now. It's never going to stop. I'm stopping with 4K. I
said it with Blu -ray. You're not. You're not stopping. You're not. You're not going to stop.
None of us. I mean, look, I do really notice the difference. But, you know, VHS to Blu -ray was the
biggest jump we've ever made. I think everything else was just kind of playing catch up to that.
But 4K, I see a difference. And I'm not rebying my whole library, just movies that I think need the
4K. Good Lord will tell you. My regular, my regular old Blu -ray of Flash Gordon looks impeccable.
I'm sure it does. But it's a, this is how these, these businesses work. They'll keep us doing this
until we die chasing some, some quote better thing. But we're told each time that it'll never get
better. But I think it's better. In any case, yes. Bram Stoker's Dracula, Bram Stoker's,
however the hell you say it. I love this movie. It's one of my favorite from Coppola. It's one of my
favorite from Oldman. It's one of my favorite from Winona Ryder. It's one of my favorites from Hopkins.
It's one of my least favorite. Terrible performance from Keanu. Oh, yeah, yeah. And it is my hands down
favorite Tom Wade's acting performance ever. It's just a great movie. It's a great telling of
the story. The only, it sticks pretty close to the book. Coppola said the one element they added
that made it theirs or whatever was Dracula being in love with Harker's wife reminding Dracula
of his previous wife and falling in love with her. But that was about, that was kind of it. Like the
rest of it was, you know, sticks pretty close to the script. And it's deemed more or less next to
the, the hammer. I guess it's House of Dracula. It was the first one with Christopher Lee. That's
considered, you know, by and by to be the greatest adaptation of the book, the closest to the source
material. And this is, this is way up there as well. It's awesome. It's romantic. It's epic. It's
really creepy and scary. It's fun. It's gothic. And Coppola interestingly enough talks about on the
blu -ray. He shot, he wanted to shoot the whole thing on a sound stage because he had this idea of
making these like epic set, these, these, these, these, excuse me, these like perpetual sets, whatever
you want to call them, where there would be like a set piece in the foreground where the actors
be acting. And then behind them, it was seemed to go into like this infinite darkness. And once he
said that, you realize, like, oh, yeah, they do do that a lot in the movie. Right. But he wanted to
do that. And he said he leaned into his reputation when he pitched it. And he was like, you know,
you could send me off to Transylvania. And we could actually shoot this on location. And you know,
he started going on and on. Yeah. Knowing he goes, because I knew he goes, we don't want to send this
guy or it's going to be a disaster. Like it's going to be a apocalypse now over again. And he goes,
or I could just shoot it all on the sound stages, I guess. And he was like, and they were like, yes,
do that. Do that. Yeah. So I like stories like that where they sort of play, play the suits against
themselves. Sure. But it feels very story bookish. It's just, it's just a great movie. It's,
I hate, I'm not trying to pick on piano. He's, he's not good at it. But he's passive. He's
passable enough. He's not going to ruin the movie for you. But the main reason you win L .O .L every
time I watch that movie is when Gary Alman walks in with the, the buns on his head and everything.
And then counter turns to him and goes, Oh, it always makes me laugh out loud at how just he does
nothing to act like he's in the right time period, the right, I mean, just pathetic.
And then he doubles down on, on accents and how bad they can be in devil's advocate.
But he's doing some sort of Boston Southern mix that just doesn't work at all. Yeah, it doesn't,
it really doesn't. All right, Dracula. I'll tell you this, even at the time, even when even when
Reeves was kind of a laughing stock, I'd always take a Reeves over a Chris O'Donnell.
I never minded Chris O'Donnell. I thought I'm a little boring, but I thought he was a good
aero. I mean, the guy makes Matt Damon look like Mickey Rork. Don't you talk about the
Damon, Damon like that. I love Damon. I'm saying it's a little white bread. Yes, yes. It's a,
oh, you know what? I do have more of a theme here than I thought I did.
Well, it's my turn. I know. Folks, I'd like to recommend the one good thing that is new to Netflix
that I watched while I had the the app. Traveling band, Colin, credence clear water revival
at the Royal Albert Hall. This is a great, very short documentary. It's like 80 minutes long.
It is narrated by the great Jeff Bridges, who of course sounds awesome.
Everybody loved credence. That kind of vibe the whole time. That's more of a dignity, perhaps.
But he does a great job narrating it. It's footage of credence kind of hanging around and touring
and like going around London. And I realize I've never seen any footage of credence clear water
revival ever in my life. They're a band that's just one of the biggest rock bands in America. Everybody can
sing every word to like ten of their songs. And yet I've never seen them perform. I've never seen them
like ever ever. Like you've seen the Rolling Stones a million times. You've seen the Beatles a million
times in all kinds of locations. So it's just kind of cool to hang out with them and learn like it's
very weird. John Fogarty the lead. He seems like a crazed stoner half the time. And then he seems
like a real like square weirdo half the time. And I don't know what he was really. You don't learn much
and it's such a short documentary. Really the reason to watch it is the footage. There's a full hour
long concert of credence clear water revival in their prime going through their hits playing most
of the songs in like double speed. And you realize like how amazing they were for their time. They
sound amazing live. It's a great recording. And for me a great opportunity to see a band I've
always loved but had never seen perform. Check it out. All right. I guess my theme here is rewatch. Okay.
Not much of the theme but okay. I know. But there was there was well there was almost a religious theme
because Dracula gets gets religious. Which I like in a horror movie. But I am going to say that
this is also a religious film. I rewatch dogma. What is a religious film? I'm not just going to say it is.
Yeah. I rewatch dogma. Kevin Smith's dogma. Kevin, if you're listening, I know you're not.
Please, please stop smoking weed. This is an excellently written film. It's got a plot. It's got
it moves. It's got characters that are well rounded. It's got fantastic joke after fantastic
joke throughout this entire thing. Yeah. I remember loving that. None of it is inside baseball at all.
Like it's got a stellar cast. It's great. It's fucking great. And it's like, dude, what is happening
man? What has happened to you? It just bums me out. Somebody told me to watch
the clerks three was good. And I said, I can't. I haven't heard that. I said, I look, I want to see
it. I really do. But I just can't imagine that I'm going to enjoy it. And I said to the person,
did you like Jay and Silent Bob? And they were like, oh, yeah, I loved it. And I was like, I go, I
can't tell you how much I hated it. And she was like, you're going to hate clerks three.
Like you're going to hate it. Yeah. Yeah. Because it's all just become this big nod. And I look,
that's the world we live in. He's a guy that made his comeback on podcasting. His podcast studios
is now becoming a movie thing. And that's great. Like I admire the guy and his entrepreneurialism
and what he's done and what he's built. But, you know, he's taken that podcast approach and
everything is just for his fans now, which, which, hey, God bless. You know, it feels like
stone or not. It feels like this is a man who was shooting first drafts. Like he is not
polishing a joke. He's not, when he's done writing it, it feels like that's just it because these are not,
these are not something that the guy who wrote those first four or five movies or whatever
would put his stamp on. You know, he was never, he was never an amazing filmmaker or anything,
don't get me wrong. But he had a real voice. And I think made really great movies that were
important to a lot of people. And that does not sync up with what we're seeing now. He's not trying
at all. Well, there are a lot of filmmakers who are stoneers or alcoholics or whatever else. But
it enhances their vision. You know, they can do better with it or something. He clearly has had
such a quality drop off that it's like, I think it goes beyond the drugs fucking his brain up.
I think that it is like, it has made him not care about quality. And that's not a great
aspect for a filmmaker to have. Well, also, too, like, you know, I've heard this about him. And I
don't know if it's true. But I've heard that he really has a problem with booze. Really?
No, that he's really like somebody that like looks down on drinking. And like, I know for a
minute, I thought you made me have a drinking problem. No, no, no, no, he looks down on it. Like he's
judgy of drinkers. Okay. And no, maybe that's not true. But if it is, and look, who am I to talk?
I'm a big drinking proponent. And I look down on it's in session marijuana use. So I guess I'm a
hypocrite here. But it's just weird to me. It's weird to me that he like is I don't know. He said in
the past like, I made myself a deal. If I write, I can smoke weed. And I want to get high. So I write
yeah. And it's like, yeah, I guess, I guess that's a thing like I don't know. It's just, I mean,
Chris, when you're looking back at Jersey girl and going, that was a more coherent and well put
together movie than what you're doing now. You're in a bad fucking way, man. Yeah. Like he did
a great job. I was Zach and Mary sort of proved that he could bridge the gap. He could do one that
would sort of work for both his people and other people. And Zach and Mary solid, you know,
and then he made red state. Red state is a solid horror movie. He's good at it. And then he just
he drifted back and I don't know, it just became like I'm just going to do. I guess that heart attack
was like, it's just everything is a love letter now. It's just like, oh, snooze, oh, snooze, a
fucking rama man. Yeah. Yeah. Anyway, dogma is great. You should, you should rewatch it. Pat, it's become
pitch black. I know, but I don't want to get up and turn the light on. So it's daunting.
We turn around. I will. And I also like how it looks like I'm waiting for you to come home from work
and I'm smoking a cigarette in the dark. Can I tell a story about when I stayed for me with you during
the divorce? Yes. Well, it depends. I'll cut it out if you want me to. All right, I won't tell it
never mind. I mean, yeah, I don't know. It's not much of a story. It's that I came home and
felt you sitting in a house that dark at one point. I was like, why don't you come out and sit with me
and maybe we get out of the house for a few minutes. Yeah. Yeah, no. Yeah, those days are over. Yeah,
no, I know. But yeah, it's pitch black. It does look like you're waiting for me to come. It looks
like you're going to, it's like the end of wrath of man. We're staying. I'm just waiting to kill that
last guy. Well, I still laugh about how when you stayed out here, you used like some ancient pillow
that was in the other room. And I had a closet brimming over with pillows and just never told me,
I guess you thought I was going through too much or something, but you know, you were, you were dealing
with a lot. No, the last thing you needed was me and like, but Joe, I had a hundred pillows. You
know, maybe you lost them in the split pillows. Well, the first thing to go anywhere. No count.
Folks, I would like to tell you a little story. I have seen every time I log into who, so basically,
I, I forget some of the services when you cancel them, they pay, they reimburse you for the lost time.
Some of the services just give you till the end of your pay period. So I cancel Hulu. I'm like,
I'm not watching anything on here. And they go, you have 21 days to watch it or something. So
I'm flipping around. I'm like, I don't want to watch any of this shit. And then I asked my friends about
the patient with Steve Carell and Dom and Hall Gleason. I'm like, I like these actors that it was a
show on FX. I'm like, is anybody seen it? Nobody's watched it. I'm like, all right. Then I realized the
first episode, this is the 10 episode series, a drama is 20 minutes long. Ooh, there we're talking.
I'm like, all right. Now I'm into it. So I watch it and the premise is this. It's a great premise. I see
why the show got set up. A serial killer or a guy who has a desire to kill played by Dom Hall Gleason.
Um, kidnaps, a therapist played by Steve Carell and basically is like, I'm going to keep you
down here till you fix me. But he wants to kill the whole time. And then of course, as the show progresses,
he like goes out and kills. And Steve Carell can't stop it, etc. So I like that premise. Obviously
that sets up, to me, it sets up a great two hour thriller. I don't know why they made it into a
series. And that's still my question after having watched it. But Carell's good, you know, in a
serious role as the therapist. And it's kind of just a therapy show. It's like that in treatment where
you're watching almost a full therapy session with this tension hanging over. Is this serial killer
going to go out and kill again? Um, I'm watching it. Each episode gets like five minutes longer.
And I'm realizing I'm not caring about it at all. They start these subplots that aren't working at all.
Then I start texting a few of my other friends and they're like, oh, yeah, that show's awful.
I hated that show. Don't watch it. Don't watch it. And I'm like, no, keep, I'm going to press on. I'm
going to finish it tonight and keep watching and keep watching. It's starting to really lose me. Then
in episode seven, they introduced this new plot point that I hated so much. And it is that Steve Carell
who is having a psychotic break from being locked up in this guy's basement starts imagining a therapy
session in his mind with his dead therapist. And basically, Pat, as a joke, I was going to say that
an imaginary dog or something appears. No, yeah, it's not that far off. It's not that far off.
All right. So he starts imagining this. And it's so obvious that this was a show that maybe tried
to be a 10 hour long show. And something went wrong. Something got cut out. But something went wrong
in the show because how was your first episode, 20 minutes, and your seventh episode an hour? It
doesn't make me sense. So it's not working. He's going to have this therapy session in his mind with
his dead therapist. And it just feels like added. It has nothing to do with the story. Then they reveal
who's playing his mind therapist. David Allen Greer.
And like a scene from this fucking show, my hand started shaking. I'm not kidding. My hand started
shaking. I reached up for the remote, bobbled it and dropped it on my glass coffee table. It didn't
break. But I dropped the remote and I'm fumbling standing there with my hands raised like over
my head, trembling, trying to get the TV to turn off because I couldn't see him. That's how
fucked up I am with this man. So now I'm seven and a half episodes in and I'm never going to finish
the patient. I don't even care how it ends. But I was like, good Lord, I guess I got to start doing
two a days with this fucking therapy. Just seeing this man made me have a goddamn freak out.
But the show is not good. And the show gets worse as it goes. And then at some point you're going to
have to deal with that. I cannot recommend the patient on FX and Hulu. All right. That might be
a knee problem. I don't know. I'll start my third turn a damn light. I'm turning a light on
disturbing. But look how pretty it is now with the sun going down. It's not pretty. It looks
psychotic over here. It's freaking me out. It looks finch arrest. I rewatched this is a tremendous
probably the best of any fall centric horror movie I could recommend. And it's a rewatch. We
reviewed it on the show when it first came out. But scary stories to tell. Scary stories to tell
the dark. I got the Blu -ray a while back. I was a big fan of the movie when I saw it in the theater.
I'm a big fan of the book with me with pet. But scary stories is a perfect, perfect fall movie. It's
it takes place on Halloween. The movie itself does. The entire thing is leaves changing color and corn
fields and scarecrow and it's just great. It's just a great movie to watch this time of year. It's a
perfect Halloween movie. But I would say it also is pretty good leaning into the November time
and Thanksgiving time from a visual standpoint. And you know, I don't have much to say. I still
like the movie. I think it's one of the most solid horror, you know, in that in that vein of horror
movies that we don't get often, you know, a family, a weirdly family friendly horror movie that
still has edge that still has scares. You know, like in the family of the poltergeists or that type of
thing, it's very well done. And it's it's one of the better ones that's come out in a long time.
And it's still really good. It doesn't diminish. It's a very, very well done horror movie.
The sequel is supposedly still coming. I believe it when I see it, but I hope that that happens.
I really do. Scary stories to tell in the dark. Worth a watch if you like anthology horror, which I do.
Very well. What's that all else? Are we done? What's my last third? Yeah, you have a third, I think,
don't you? I don't know, but I will do Pink Floyd colon the wall, which I had never seen,
despite having been a Pink Floyd fan. Really, it upsets me greatly. It makes me really depressed.
It upsets me. I don't. It can't. It's really depressing. It's I it shows here in LA pretty often,
like at midnight screenings, and I've just never seen it, but it's for some reason impossible to find.
It's not streaming anywhere, not even to be, not even Roku. It's not available. And there's no
blu -ray ever made of it. So it must be some sort of rights issue. No blu -ray made of it. No blu -ray made of
it. So I located some sort of random, I guess, import DVD, which was great. And it's available on Amazon
and not that expensive. But I had always wanted to see it. I love the album. But yeah, it's a dreary
affair. It was directed by Alan Parker, who I love. He did like the commitments, which I think is
one of the great rock music, rock music movies. I highly recommend it by the Irish rock soul band.
I love that movie. And he's made a lot of great shit. This was, you know, visually spectacular.
It was the early days of MTV. So I'm sure blue some people's minds. I see why it might be awesome
stoned in a theater late at night. You know, I think it got a big midnight movie following.
But yeah, it's depressing. It's just kind of dreary and gray. And it's a lot of black and white
footage of people being drugged into the street and beaten, you know, over like really depressing
string sections and stuff. It's not a fun movie. And Pink Floyd are about the least fun rock band
there is. So it makes sense that it would be very overly solemn and serious. They're a real drag,
those guys. They are. And I got to be in the mood for some of their shit. And I do definitely
don't go any beyond the wall in terms of their music. But what's after the wall? What comes next?
Is division bell the next record for Christ sake? I think there had to have been stuff in between,
but I might be wrong. I don't know. I like their early stuff to some extent. Some of it's a little
stupid for me. And then dark side of the moon is great once a year, whatever. Yeah, the sweet spot with
them is, God, they're still considered together too, even though that was supposed to be the end with
that last album of instrumentals that they put out. Yeah, it was terrible. Not terrible. It was
just boring. I had this buddy in high school who was like such a Pink Floyd fan. And he like
insists every time we be in his car, he'd be playing some like experimental B side flute, Pink Floyd.
Like knock it off. Like we don't have this love where we're going to go this bar down the Pink Floyd
rabbit hole. My other buddy was the same way with Pearl Jam. And honestly, it made me never like
them as much as a Neuron or a sound garden because I had to listen to it too much in my friend's car.
And you know what you want. So here, I'm looking up Pink Floyd's discography after the wall,
they did the final cut, which was made primarily was material that didn't make it to the wall.
It was like leftovers. Right. After that, a lot of the wall. Yeah. And then after that, they put out
and this is what this is when I got introduced to them just by seeing the records in the store,
a momentary lapse of reason, uh -huh, where it's all the beds on the cover. Yeah. Here's the first line
on the Wikipedia page. This is the 13th album by the English Progressive Rock Band Pink Floyd.
It was recorded primarily on guitarist David Gilmore's Converted Houseboat
a story. Oh boy. Oh boy. And it's the first without waters. He's gone at this point. Yeah.
A story is a grand houseboat built it. Go fuck yourselves. And then after this, yeah,
is the one with all the light, the guy with all the light bulbs. This is one of all their
album covers was like a thing. A lot of the same thing in a field. Yeah. Yeah.
It just, yeah, I went to some Pink Floyd exhibit here last year with a buddy John Gabress.
I told you to watch his show in HBO Max and I hope you did. Very funny. I watched a bit of it.
It was funny. I didn't enjoy it because I was trying not to drink and the whole show is them going
around getting completely fucked up. Yeah. They drink more and more as it goes. But um,
Gabress and I went to this Pink Floyd exhibit here and it wound up being super low rent.
And at the end, you just like sat in this room and watched some of their music videos.
And God, they sucked. Yeah. Just one after the other. Just fucking sucked.
And there are these acclaimed visual artists. Meanwhile, I went to see Roger Waters. I was
stoned out of my mind, of course, ran into my former boss, Glenn Howardton. I could barely stand
up. But I'm sure he understood. I went up. Well, sorry, it's drop the name. Let me just pick that
up off the floor. I go up. I was with Vince. Another name drop. And we go get our seats. And I'm looking
around and I'm like, you know, it's the flying pig, the flying inflatable pig. There's like four of those.
He's been doing the same shit now for 40 years. Wait, this is Waters is doing the flying
waters was doing a lot of the. Yeah, this is yeah, this is when he was going around saying like,
I'm not going to perform in Israel or whatever, but then perform in the United. It's a shut up,
David, Roger, whatever, whoever the hell you are. It was a good show. I'm just like when I would see
footage of Pink Floyd on MTV when I was like a kid, they had the exact same setup, the stupid inflatable
pigs flying around. It's like, let's try something else. I had heard, I had never heard one
measure of a Pink Floyd song. And when I worked at Rainbow Records when I was 16 into my 17th year of
life, it was the best coolest job I ever had. That was when Pulse was released. It was the double live
album that had the red light in it that flickered on the cut, you know, like built into the packaging.
Yeah, I didn't know what they sounded like, or but I just remember being like, flock this band,
whoever this is. And then my friend Jerry McGlennigan, who's great. I remember him telling me,
I got to, he worked there too. I remember him saying to me, I got to get a copy of this for my dad,
I was like, yes, this is like dad music, right? Yeah, Pink Floyd. Very much so. You know,
yeah, in many ways it is. What was the year like, it was one of the weakest Pink Floyd albums,
beat out like some of the great alternative albums of all time at the Grammys?
It's got to be Division Bell. It's got to be that year. Well, you keep talking. I'll find it. I'll find it.
Unless you have anything else to say. I just, I'm not a fan of, I'm not a fan of that later,
Pink Floyd stuff obviously. I saw the wall when I was heavily getting into marijuana use.
In my freshman year in college, I had never seen it. Yeah. And these girls that we were friends with,
that all lived in a house. It was called the glass house. That was the name of it on campus. Yeah.
They were like, they were like, did with God. I watch the wall. You've never seen it. It's amazing.
It's about a guy that is a wall emotionally. I don't fucking know whatever they said. I was like, all right,
let's watch it. We got super high and watched it. And I was, it harshed my vibe as they say. I was
like, guys, this is fucking freaking me out. I'm really bummed out right now. I am not enjoying
this at all. Yeah. But I do like the album. The album. I was wrong with Pink Floyd. It was
stealing Dan that I was thinking of. They're like, come back album, which I never like stealing Dan.
You know, I can do a song every six months maybe or something of stealing Dan. But really Dan's rough
stuff, man. They're like very late period, very bad album. For album of the year in 2001, it beat out
the Marshall Mathers LP, which was like just the biggest thing, you know, like clearly demonstrably
the biggest thing, critically acclaimed audiences acclaimed, etc. Radiohead's Kid A widely considered
one of the best rock albums ever made, not even my favorite radiohead, but still I give it its props.
Back's Midnight Vultures, which is maybe my favorite back album. You know, it's absurd what they
award these things. And people still give a shit. I think they're starting not to. I think
I heard the Oscar moving to streaming. So like clearly, you know, like they've given up. Nobody
cares anymore. Nobody wants to see rich people award rich people. They might have gotten five more
years out of the Will Smith slap. It let you know, though, too, that, you know, when when when stealing Dan
wins best album of the year against everything else you just mentioned, you're like, oh yeah,
this like clearly isn't just voted for. Right. There's no way this got all the votes. There's
just no way. Or all the voters were very old people. I mean, that's changed too. That's an extremely
positive change along with a lot of other things that have gone on in the entertainment industry
is that the entire voting academy they used to say for the Oscars anyway. And I think the Grammys as
well, imagine your grandparents are voting because that's who everybody in the academy is. So that's why
Steely Dan wins. These old people look at a ballot and they're like, you know, the one name they've heard
is often how things win. And it's also why these love letters to Hollywood always win like the artist
because it's talking about how Hollywood was so great back then and all the voters were these
ancient people who work used to work in the entertainment industry and think the greatest days
were behind them. So it's very biased. They're all biased. And it never matches like you never look back
at the previous year's best picture winner. And it's had any impact on society at all anymore.
You know, they used to. Let's move to the to the to the thing at hand. The thing I hesitate to
even call the show. The watcher which I watched a while ago. And I when I was honestly getting ready
to talk about it, I was like, well, I could do the setup, but I don't even remember how it ends. And I
just watched it. Now I know they picked it up for a second season. Somehow I will not be there for
that. But there's never enough with this shit. Like you just said about the damn the damn
patient thing. Yeah. And like we said in the last episode, what John Stewart was saying, it's like,
why can't you just do a two hour thing? Why can't you just do a limited run series about an incident
that actually happened that there was a big New York Times article about that's really interesting.
No, we got to milk it for more. We've got to go more out of this. So now we're going to go a second
season with a TV show starring a well -paid actor, Bobby Cannevelli and Naomi Watts, who's been nominated
for Oscars for Christ's sake. These people are not coming cheap. Yeah. They got me a farrow out of
retirement for this fucking thing. You know what I mean? Like it's like, you know, and well,
it was a massive. It's a killer cast. It's a great cast. You got richer kind. It's a great fucking cast.
The show starts now. Yeah. It was a it was a massive hit. I think only Dahmer beat it,
bullfrog and Murphy productions. And the watcher also barely sputters to a seven episode run.
At a time when everything is pretty much 10 episodes. So it's like, probably they cut three
episodes of unusable footage out of it. I was listening to people complain today while I was out
about American Horror Story apparently was really good this season. But then in the end,
the final two episodes were one extended dream sequence that had nothing to do with the show.
And everybody's like, you finally had a good story. What did you do? So Ryan Murphy is either too busy
or too many things going on or something. But these projects always start out kind of compelling.
Like I remember reading about the watcher because honestly, I read about it because I was concerned
it was going to impact the screen plan trying to sell about my neighbor. But the story was really
cool and creepy and interesting. And I was like, oh, that'd be a good movie someday.
Problem is you tried to make it into a series. Now it's going to be a two season series.
And you don't have enough story. Like the pilot of this to me worked, setting up the world worked.
I'm like, okay, I'm interested in not to keep going. I was really into it for the first,
yeah, what happened? You know, I was really into it for the first couple of episodes. And then I
started to be like, wait a minute, let's just jerk me around. What's going on here? Yeah.
They set up a million loose ends that they never follow through on, which to me is not done on purpose.
It is not done in a way to create mystery to me. It's done in a way where they go, let's just do
this and we'll figure it out later. That's what it's like. And the motivations of the characters make no
sense. There is no set. The basic plot is these people, the suburban family who become strangely obsessed
with a house that they must have, figure out a way to buy it, even though it's out of their price
range and all that stuff. They buy the house, they live in it and immediately begin getting letters
from a guy named the watcher who's saying all this creepy shit and the letters like the house has
new blood and it needs to feed and all this crazy shit. And then the mystery begins of them trying
to solve the crime. What's going on here? The writing from the jump makes no sense. So immediately in the
first episode, Jennifer Coolidge is the realtor repping the house. She's they reveal immediately that
she's old friends with Naomi Watts. And you think when they go, we can't really afford this house
right there. You go, well, the realtor is going to help them get it because she's going to finish
their offer through. And that would create some weird suspense later when weird shit starts
happening. They don't do that at all. It's just a pointless relationship that that later becomes by
the way that they later be falls out and they later begin to think that Jennifer Coolidge is a suspect.
So the college character has no impact on the show like she's she comes in literally like
Kramer into the series drama. She comes in like the wacky neighbor in every episode and you're like
what's going on? Yeah. She's in a different series. I mean, she's in a different world.
And you've got a detective being played by the guy by a happy Gilmore. What's the guy saying?
Chris McDonnell always good to see Chris McDonnell. Yeah. He's in a different. He's playing like a
almost like a funny cop like it's bad. Yeah. And again, they want you to think he's in on it.
And then he's not though. And then you're like, well, if he's not in on it, then why did he
treat it so hastily in the beginning? Like, it's just bad writing. They set up all this stuff to make
you think one thing. But then they never followed through as to why that thing that that that they made
you think was invalidated. Yeah. You know, a good thing, a good mystery. I'll make you go, well, I
thought it was him. But it turns out it wasn't because what he was actually up to was this. They don't
do any of that. They set up the people acting weird. The handicap gardener or whatever. That whole
subplot. So then, so then what was going on with the gardener guys? What he just like to write
up and down in their dumb waiter and enter the house in his own will. Yeah. He's allowed. He is allowed
to enter the house. Willie nilly. But that has nothing to do with the house mystery. Then there's this
couple who's clearly obsessed with the house and everything else. But they also have nothing to do with
it. You just kind of like, what am I watching? You're inventing things just to like build time.
They've got to see where Bobby can of alley meets this weird couple for the first time played by Richard
Kind. And what's the woman's aim? I'm a big fargo Martin now. She's great. Yes, she is. They're both
great in this. But they they they this interaction. They are so fucking rude to him. Yeah. It's
your only response to this would be, if I ever catch you on my property again, I'll fucking murder
you. How about that? That's it. Like, it's like, but it's like, he just kind of lets it slide. And then
he's like, well, neighbors are kind of jerks. It's so weird. They say to him, we're going to come
on to your property and do what we want. Right. And then and then me and arrows in his yard like,
let my handicap son, Roger, don't wait. Why is that so hot? It's like, no, get out of here. That's
the response. Yeah. And then then they show like a flashback to the previous tenants with the neighbors
and how these same neighbors interacted with him. And they were lovely. Yeah. So again, you got a chance
here to do something cool and you blow it. Speaking of me, a Pharaoh, do the rosemary's baby thing.
Make the neighbors really neighborly, but they're weird. And then it starts to get sinister. That's
interesting. It doesn't make any sense that these people are assholes right off the bat. Yeah. There's no
tension built at all. He sees the neighbors. He's like, hey, how are you? And they're like, you don't
fucking talk to me, motherfucker. What? Where's the tension in that? You got Richard Kine saying,
fuck, which I found out. And a parapleeded khaki shorts yelling, fuck, I didn't like hearing him
curse at all. But in this shirt and a shirtless dick kind of memory serves at one, I think he is
sure. And then then they start to do the same type of thing with the family itself.
For like the daughter starts being like, what is up with dad? He's being an asshole. And it's like
he he he was concerned that you're like skirt was too short. So you know what I mean? It was like
the most passive like a dad being a dad thing. Yeah. And they make it sound like he's
I think they insinuated one point that he's got a sexual obsession with his daughters. And you're
the the dog. I'd say I'd say they keep hinting at it but never go anywhere with it. And again,
it's like, don't raise that issue if you're not going to explore it as a story point. It doesn't
make any sense because he is weirdly protective of his daughter. But it's like it's the same basic
setup as like she's out of control with Tony Danza. And who was the Bobby Canavale of his day by the
way, Tony Danza. Yeah. But it is weird. Canavale is obsessed with what his daughter is wearing and
how she looks. Then there's this really bizarre subplot where they keep saying this African -American boy
who's like their security guard, you know, security setup guy is fucking the daughter. And his race
is brought up a lot. But then they don't do anything with that. It's like they do this stuff up and
then not doing anything with it. It's weird. All they do with it is the daughter gets
spitefully mad at the dad for no apparent reason. And then decides to send a video out somehow
to his entire work network on their computers. Like like like a gag in like a long came poly or
something like that. You know, where they all see this video of the daughter saying, my dad won't
let me date the guy I'm in love with because he's a racist. When you know, damn well, she knows
that she's too young. She says to the guy when they meet, I'm jailbait. All this shit.
This is a thing that would divide a family permanently. Bobby Canavale, when he realizes she does
this, takes her phone from her. He's furious and smashes the phone on the countertop. And the way they
play it is Naomi Watts going to him. What is wrong with you? Do you realize your daughter just
dismantled this family's ability to make any money? Yeah. Do you understand what this hit? Like
it's terrible. It's just so poorly. And then by the way, two scenes after that, he's back in the house
and the daughter just goes, I'm glad you're home, dad. It's nice having you around again. And you
just smiles. And then I'm pretty sure two scenes after that. There's a fairly graphic scene of him
laying her down on the bed in a pair of panties. What? That might not be the same episode. But there
is like a sex scene with him and Watts at one point. Oh, no, him and Watts. Yeah. But he's the daughter.
Yeah. Yeah. He forgives the daughter immediately. There's no weird, there's never the part where she
goes, Hey, I fucked up. I'm real sorry. Yeah. It's like they did the work of setting up a lot of
interesting plots. They just didn't do the work of following them anywhere.
And then in the most bizarre turn to me of the entire show, when the family comes back together and
they decide how to work together to discover who the watcher is, right? How is the family against
the world? It turns into this, there, there becomes this like Han Solo Princess Leia report with
Cannivali and Noah Watts, where she starts to get like feisty and bossy. Like we're going to go down
there. We're going to tell what it is. And she walks out of the room like, like to take
char. You know what I mean? Let's go and she charged out the room. And then the camera hangs on
Cannivali and he'll have a line like, ooh, I like it. Mama. Yeah. Yeah. What the fuck is going on?
Yeah. It's insane. Meanwhile, their children are at home possibly being murdered. Like it's insane.
It's this show sucks. It's a really bad program. And I had not seen anything of Ryan Murphy's in
ages. I didn't watch Glee. Although I do love his, like I said, the impeachment and the OJ show and
all that stuff, which he produces too. But this was the first one where I was like, this reminds me why
I got out of American history. I'm sorry, American horror story after season two or whatever.
It's like, no, he can set up a great world. You just can't follow through. Can't do it.
You can't produce this many shows at once because I've seen, I've seen what this looks like.
And you've seen what this looks like when you work with people that are on multiple projects.
The room is at work, you know, doing the thing. The person comes in and they do the whole like, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay. Good. I got to go, got to run across town, got a meeting
with so and so. Yeah. I got a cantaloupe lunch with so and so so we can take notes on this.
You know, it's like, you can't do it. That happens a lot now because they only trust
ten or so people to run most of these shows. But it's clear because like the pilot, which he like
directed, there's a, there's a quality to it. It sort of works, but then just it falls apart.
Dahmer was the same way. The pilot's really compelling and then it just kind of keeps losing you
as it goes. And then when it ends, you're like, why did I waste ten hours? I do think Dahmer is the
better of the two. But you're talking about a hog down for sure. Well, don't let's not leave out that
this ends with zero closure. Yeah, zero. Maybe they knew there was a season two. I don't know.
It just ends with everybody is a suspect now, including now Bobby kind of Ellie. It's like,
now he's where they move out of the house and now he's weirdly obsessed with the house. Yeah,
as a person that used to live there, which makes no sense to me. And by the way, they have a
character in here who's, they have a woman who's a, she's a private investigator. And in every episode
after she comes into the show, there's a sequence where she goes, I have found your watcher. And she
breaks down who it is exactly why it's this person. She's a hundred percent sure. And then she's
wrong, right? And that happens like four episodes in a row. Yeah, they keep going back to her and
treating her words with respect. I'm like, she's wrong, guys. You'd fire this woman. You'd move on
to a different psychic. Yeah. It's, yeah, hogs down on the watcher. It's, it almost hit it
and then it just doesn't. And it's just bad. It's a bad show. Yeah, good pilot bad show.
Waste of a solid cast hog way down. We'll be back folks in December with, I would go as,
I think we would probably do this. I don't think I'm putting you on the spot by saying this. I
know we've already done playing strings and automobiles. But I'm assuming that in December after we
both have had a chance to watch this new 4K release with an hour's worth of unseen footage. We might
do an episode about that. Sure. That's worth revisiting. And I'm sure we'll do something. You know what?
I just bought the 4K if it's a wonderful life. We should do it's a wonderful life for Christmas.
That'd be fun. All time favorites. There's also all five of the Silent Night Deadly Nights are now
on shutter. I've only seen one in two. We reviewed five for this. The Mickey Rooney one. Oh yeah.
One and two for this. Remember the rape in that movie by the 10 soldier. Yeah. It's in tents.
But I would do three or four for this. We haven't done or we could also do the Silent Night which is
the remake of Silent Night Deadly Nights. We'll discuss folks and I'm sure there'll be new releases
coming out as well that we're missing them. Anyway folks thanks for listening. We'll see you next time
and we'll see you and how