Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal, durable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamber.
Howdy folks, welcome to a new episode of we'll see when hell the podcast it's part
of the Fangoria podcast network for more information about this network including other programs
how to follow our show or how to find episodes of any show please visit
fangoria .com and now on with the show Pat Walsh hey guys in full deluxe
stereo new format new format in case you missed it we are kind of keeping it
as it was a free -flowing conversation but we're not tying it to a film and each
week, the loose theme of the episode will be a sin. We're starting with the big
sev, the deadlies. Today's going to be wrath, which we just had to look up. I
thought wrath might be murdering someone. Turns out wrath is just anger, which is a
sin that everyone has. And I have every second of every day. And I think Joe has it
more than I do. I got it bad, baby. Yeah. And that ain't good. No, it helps me. It
fuels my writings, my comedies. I feel like it makes me a more interesting person perhaps.
But it is a sin, you know. Your comedies? Is that what you just said? My comedy, my writing.
Oh, I thought you said your comedies, like you were like a Greek playwright.
It helps both my comedies and my tragedies. I'm currently wearing a black shirt and I have the two
with the drama and tragedy masks and glitter on them.
I teach a class over at the learning annex.
I'll tell you, I'm annoyed with you already
because I'm looking at your value versus mine.
I mean, why are you so much lower than me?
Am I that much lower than you?
And look at the wave forms.
Look at, look at mine.
It looks like a cardiac arrest has happened.
Should we restart?
Now I'll just adjust it all in post.
How do we restart?
We don't have anything good here.
No, the people, the, the, the,
We don't need to restart the people afterwards won't know. Just hold the goddamn mic up a little close.
I'm holding it. There you go. Maybe I'm just too loud. Look, the people are sitting at home going,
what are you talking about? It sounds fine because I'll mix master this at the end.
All right. See, I'm not getting raffle. I'm getting angry at the whole affair.
I know what anger's you. What's angering you right now?
Yeah, I think let's let's start off big picture.
Country is in serious danger.
I don't pay attention to politics,
my anything I do politically does not matter
and will not change the world in any way.
Sorry, that's how I feel.
Right.
You're looking at these candidates.
I mean, obviously Trump's a goddamn monster.
Right.
Clinton, and this has zero to do with her being a woman,
you can think somebody's not going to do a great job.
job, even though they're a woman, she has a way of just, you know, sniping at sanders
and just like this, like one liners thing to them all the time, and well you did this,
you said this, you did this, I don't want that as my president.
Bernie Sanders is better about it, but he's an old cook, and he can't deliver on these promises.
There are no good options, and it's going to be one of those three people.
There are no good options.
There are no great options.
Let's see.
There have never been great options.
I feel like Bill Clinton at his time was a great option.
Barack Obama was a very important president for this country to have.
I think it was nice that we had Obama in there.
I'm sorry, I just called him Barack Obama.
Like I don't know how to speak.
I think it was nice that we had Obama in there.
But I mean, here's the thing.
Everybody goes, it's a mark of progress.
And it's not really because all that happens is is the people like us that
Try to think progressively at least say well, that's good that that happened
But we would have thought that anyway and the people that didn't want that to happen just became more racist and angry about it
So nobody changes which pushes people more towards a trump type
Nobody changes nothing can get fixed nothing will ever change
Don't vote. It's a waste of time. It is and I will still vote. I won't but
You know, and I, this is something I said at the last election was like,
if you don't clap at a concert, you're an asshole.
It makes no difference if you clap at a concert,
but if you don't do it, you're an asshole.
It's my opinion. And that's what I feel about voting.
It makes no difference. You should do it.
People have fought for your right to do it.
You should do it. When did they fight for our right?
How long do I have to be indebted to that for my right?
right. I mean, I'm not a historian. I mean, 100 years ago, or something, somebody did
something. I got to still fucking play. That's like, that's like somebody tell me my
great, great grandfather came over here. I don't fucking know that guy in a different world.
Other countries don't have that right now. It sucks for them. That's shitty. Shit way
to live. You know, but I couldn't agree more. But these people, you know, I'm watching the
season of House of Cards and obviously Kevin Spacey on that show is you know
just a complete monster they got this new guy coming up in the ranks he's like
40 young you know families good looking guys got big ideas and they reveal him
to you know have some scummy ties as well my point is where are these people where
the good like 40 -year -old men and women with like bright ideas were
excited and can't wait until they turn 40s. They can run for the presidency.
You're talking about a fantasy show. I am talking about a fantasy show.
You're talking about a baby child TV show. And that person would of course not be as great as you
want him to be. Barack Obama was in a way that person. But where are they? How are these
ghouls when the best America has to offer? Because when you have one, people start to refer to him as
they refer to Bernie Sanders as this guy's a cook and an idealist and none of this can ever happen.
Because deep down everybody knows change will never happen. Yeah, that's true. And if Trump is our president
I don't think that changes America in a big way either. It sadly probably won't. It'll change it. It'll slightly swing the pendulum
To the advantage of like the maniacs that like that guy for eight years. Yeah, and then or four or four
But there are no people in place
Brogobona can't get done when he wants to get done and neither will Trump. That's what I'm saying.
There are enough people in place who are going to be like, no, can't do that.
By the way, there are also plenty, plenty, plenty of people that are saying they know Trump personally
that this is all just stage antics so we can win. He's fully aware of what he's unable to do.
It's all just bullshit. It's bullshit. For four to eight years, if he wins, the people
in his camp will have it slightly better and then it'll change again and another guy
will come in from the other side or woman and and then it'll be able to it'll be that
thing again.
Throw a can of soda at an Asian if you want to look I mean I think the man's a god damn
nightmare patient idiot.
I just don't see any one president change in this country and I think that's what really
bomb people out and makes them full of wrath bring it right back home when you talk when
you talk to the average political enthusiast yeah I find it very similar to talking to a religious
enthusiast when you really hammer logic at them over and over they are reduced to the defense of
well you got to do something yeah and that's the religious defense well you got to believe in
something. Well, okay, well, then here we are now at the truth or the heart of the matter.
You don't believe in something because you believe in it. You just feel better believing
in it. And to me, that's the same thing with politics. You just feel better believing
in something. Right. Because at the end of the day, you know, you have no real way of changing
anything. No. And people get into these like these impotent rages where because they can't
do anything, they get more angry. And my dad, and I think a lot of people, my dad's age,
get in these holes where they can't stop watching Fox News because they start feeding off the rage that it gives them
Yeah, and then you know my dad you'll if somebody says like
George Bush in his presence
You're getting yelled at for eight hours
Like it's over. Stop it. Yeah, and you look on Twitter funny people people I respect spend their entire day
Responding to trolls. Yeah, who probably don't even feel the way they're expressing. Yeah, and they're like but Trump's Hitler
Trump's Hitler, Trump, write a joke or get off of Twitter.
This is the thing.
It's, you're driving yourself crazy.
I have, I have a bit about this in my act right now about
like how much I hate social media and the one thing I hate
about it is that it's given us Twitter activists
who do nothing more for the fight than tweet
what they think.
Right.
And you know, it's a one -sided conversation
if they want it to be.
It's like the weakest form of activism.
You could you could the most non -committal form of
We talked about that on here, and but I have a bit about it and basically the crux of the bit is like
This is why like true social change will never happen again like there are no more radicals like we had in the 60s
There there are no there is
You don't have Malcolm X staring out the window with the machine gun. You don't have Jimmy Hoffa fistfighting cops
You don't have Martin Luther King marching on cities like Birmingham. You don't have radicals. You have these privilege
privileged pampered, upper class cushy fucking pussies that have time to just kind of sit
around and pontificate and read the New Yorker and have discussions to whatever elaborations
they want and coffee houses and stuff.
Those aren't activists.
Those aren't people that are going to get anything done.
Nothing will get done.
Change is not brought by discussion.
It just isn't.
Now, change is brought by overthrowing horrific, horrific people.
And that's the only way change has ever been brought ever, ever, ever, ever.
It's a sad, terrible truth, but it's true.
And that's going to tweet hashtag feel the burn and then go to your yoga class.
What are you changing?
What are you helping?
You're wanting people to know that you like Bernie Sanders, so that maybe people who like
Bernie Sanders like you, you're not trying to change anyone's mind.
Who's mind has been changed by this?
Well, you say, you know, I've made this argument before to people and they'll go,
we'll look at the change that social media made in Egypt.
They were uprisings. It's like, yeah, they were violent uprisings.
Yeah, this isn't, these weren't discussed.
You can't do anything with this.
Like, and I'm not saying she'll go out and be violent because that,
first of all, I don't, I'm not suggesting that.
And second of all, that's also not an option here because they could induct
Marshall Law here in two fucking seconds so you could never sure you could never
take to the streets the way people used to it's all bullshit this is it
just fucking you're in for the ride and you're fucked and nothing will help you
yeah so just try to get along with your neighbors and just and even that can
hardly be done I just I went over I bought Joe and I a couple beers to enjoy for
the podcast at a liquor store. And I pulled into this parking spot, you know, there's
a giant dumpster that rolls off its wood block that was keeping it propped up. And this
thing swings into my car real hard. Right. Just like crashes into it. No one around. I
was saying I'm not going to sue the liquor store or something. But I'm like, what the hell?
I look at it. There's this old Asian guy there. And he comes over and looks at me. He keeps
shaken his head and he goes, the problem is there's no
accountability. Yeah. Nobody cares. You go in now, you, you
say to them, Hey, my car, it got hit by your dumpster, they're
not going to care. The person who messed the dumpster up is not
going to care. Then he's getting really angry. He starts going on.
He goes, apparently, the other day, somebody walks by with a light
Scottish accent. Well, I was, I was so worried about doing an
an offensive Asian accent that I opted on the side of scottish right here so uh he goes
walk I'll tell you this patty I'm Asian no but he went on and on we had a nice conversation but he
was getting matter and matter and something had happened to him recently you could tell but he
was just was like these kids walk by they knock over my trash can the trash spills out they walk off
laughing. They don't even know that I saw them. Why would they do this? Why are they doing this?
I'm like, I don't know. It's just a horrible time to be alive.
Yeah, everybody is just like, this is the best we can do. And it is, I think.
Yeah, look, man, it's sad. It's, I'm heavy on this stuff right now. I'm real heavy on this stuff right
What makes you what makes you angry on it on a day -to -day basis break it down to a small
I'll tell you what makes me angry as soon a day -to -day basis the fact that
The few fleeting moments of happiness. I have each week or found somewhere in a bottle
And then I and then I carry all this guilt about that like I like sure I should feel bad because everybody around me is some kind of
Fucking asshole that runs through runny and canyon and eats fucking quinoa three times a day
And you know, it's just I just got nowhere to fit in those people are miserable, too
It's what they're doing their own stupid thing. I mean Christ almighty. Where where's the
Where's the action anymore man nobody takes any risks. There's a fun. It's all fucking stupid
I you know the the outrage that people have
of particularly on social media,
which we've talked about in here too,
about this offends me, that offends me.
I think everyone is just so angry,
and they don't know where to put it,
and they feel like online is a safe space
to kind of bitch about things that are definitely
not upsetting them, definitely not bothering them.
Sure.
And it really drives me insane.
There's a bigger shit to worry about.
Well, I'll tell you this too,
So, you know, I was knocking the social media activist earlier, but I'll tell you, part
of me does empathize with them or sympathize with them because, I mean, that's the other
side of it is we live in this fucking freak show where if you do try to stand up against
somebody on the right, they will fire shots at you or, you know, come back with you with
some sort of racial onslaught or something just horrible.
Sure.
If you stand up to people on the left,
they'll try to have your job,
they'll try to take your money away from you.
And I mean, it's, you got bullies on both sides.
Nobody feels safe just speaking their mind anymore.
So then it gets reduced to these bullshit platforms
where nobody gets heard, but then nobody gets hurt.
And yeah, I mean, Jesus Christ.
I'm a good person, you know?
I don't have a hateful bone in my body
for a racist bone, or a sexist bone, or anything like that, and I feel terrified to just calmly speak freely anyway.
And I know that I wouldn't be saying anything that would piss people off, but you don't know it will piss people off anymore.
I can't even deal with it.
I don't know what to do. I don't feel... I find myself staying home more because of it.
that's very frustrating yeah it's it's the anger of just you know this
might bleed more into envy but when you see what is being released to the
goddamn movie theater every week when you see what's coming out on TV every week
when you look for the past 18 Fridays I've looked at Spotify new music
Friday by the way when did they change release date from Tuesday to Friday when
it that happened like six months ago that happened it everywhere yeah the music
now comes out on Friday not Tuesday somebody just decided that I don't like
that I don't like it either I like a Tuesday breaks up your week yes I'm gonna
look forward to I go to Best Buy and a Tuesday when I was a kid yeah I don't
need all the fun stuff happening on Friday this is not because I am old I believe
me I log in there every week and I'm like there's 40 albums here that I would
would rather filet my dick than listen to.
Yeah, everything is homogenized now to a point where, I mean, you really have to dig to
find the good stuff.
Yeah.
But, I mean, the good stuff's out there.
Let's give a little shout out to a band called The Shrine that I was introduced to this
week.
See, now, I think you tweeted about them and I looked to their Twitter page and they had 300
followers.
It's not a lot of followers.
Yeah.
Yeah, but they they're constantly touring Europe doing huge festivals over there and stuff which made me happy that they didn't have a lot of followers
I was like that here's some guys doing it and fuck all the bullshit. They're doing it still listen
They don't need a hundred fifty thousand Twitter followers. They're doing it, right
But I mean I found them because I went into old vacation records on sunset boulevard stop in there if you ever have time
That's not a that's not a plug with their day don't sponsor us, but I'm just a fan of the store and I said
I love Fou Manchu
Yeah, deep purple. Yeah, I'm looking for some good old stoner rock. What can you suggest?
They said you might like these guys. I brought the album
brought it home. I fucking love it and
But you know that you're not gonna find that on the front page of iTunes or Spotify. I mean you're just not well
Well, I mean, Spotify goes pretty deep, you know, and I go all the way to the bottom
and I don't see anything.
Fumantue, for example, I just bought some of their old vinyl records.
I saw them and they were amazing on a tour, but they were playing one of their best albums
in its entirety, one of those deals.
Yeah.
And I love when that happens, I was listening to the lead singer of Monster Magnet, Dave
Windorf.
Yeah.
He's on the best show with Tom Sharplin, which is my favorite weekly podcast, Little Plug.
And he was talking about how he'll say, hey, we've got some really awesome new music.
We're really excited about it.
Can we book a date at your theater, your small theater in Oregon or whatever?
I go, no, but you know, I'm looking here, you're about to hit the 15th anniversary of your
big hit album.
Maybe if you played that, we could book it.
And he's like, if we want to make any money, we just have to keep churning out the same
stuff we've already done that we know people on.
Oh, the monster rating guy is saying, this is a hypothetical example of a word.
No, he's saying that's the only way he can make money is he's like,
I got to go out and tour an album that's not in my heart right now.
The album that I love and want to play, no one will book me even though Monster Mac,
you know, they're not huge, but they got a fan base.
That's pretty good fan base.
And they're a good band.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, it's, uh, it's just a dark time.
And then people say, well, look at all these Netflix shows or look at it.
Look at that. Well, the truth is there. The people get in these shows have huge
followings. The seasons are, it's not some upshoed. You know, yeah. Maybe that
show the characters is cool. That's a cool idea. Giving 10, uh, 10 little
comedians are up, not little, that's so insulting. I love three of them. I don't
know the other ones. Um, their own shot. That's a very cool idea. And what
is it? I'm at lesser known, not little. It's called the characters. It gives each one
of these different comedians, they're shot.
I've never heard of that.
What shows that?
It's called the characters.
I have said it's pretty cool.
What's it on?
It's on Netflix.
Don't turn it on me.
I've never heard of the show.
You know, there is cooler kind of niche stuff happening,
but as a rule, it's happening with huge people attached to it,
which is no different than anything else.
I don't know.
Yeah, just sort of that vibe
like the 90s when it was like oh the undergrounds taking over but all the bands
that were coming from the underground were still like you still had to be on
Subpop or something like that. That's exactly right. We're like Geffen and Subpop
for an indie back then was as close as you could get to a major for an
and I'm a fan of the label. I'm not that's not a knock. I'm just saying that was a
huge independent label. Epitaph records. Blood, honey, melvans, all those bands. None of
them fucking got rich. It's the bands that used their sound and took it to a bigger level.
Well, and it was all the bands that went to, there was a Geffen Sampler called DGC Rarity's
Volume One. And it was like obsessed with them. Yeah, it was obsessed with them. It was
like every popular band from that movement. Yeah, it was like Nirvana and Crosber on that.
Yeah, with a great song. I'm sat on the beach. Yeah, yeah. Jinks, buy me another 24 ounce
Yeah, you know, I'm getting off a little bit here on a tangent and the truth is shit does
get made not much gets made without a do -ploss endorsement, an aptal endorsement, you know,
but those people are helping, you know, people with creative original visions that might
not make it to the screen in a big way.
Sure.
This isn't anything I'm feeling a great deal of wrath about.
I'm just mad that every time I go to the movies I'm like
Well, you loved we saw 10 Cloverfield Lane the other night you were on you were floating after that
I think 10 Cloverfield Lane the best movie in about six months. I
liked it. I didn't love it as much as you did
I loved Goodman's performance. I loved Mary Elizabeth Winstead. Yes, you want to hear one of the saddest things you'll over here
Loved her so much in it Google there to see if she was married
because I thought
But what are the, the chances aren't slim that we might cross pass in this cookie town
we live in?
The chances are slim that she would want to spend more time with you.
Right.
Well, of course.
Yeah.
She looks like a regular gal though.
She does.
She's been around a while.
She was in Scott Pilgrim and shit.
Yeah, but then you look at her red carpet pictures and you realize she's like the hottest
woman ever.
In movies, you're like, oh, that's like a normal, pretty girl.
Then you look at like the red carpet stuff.
You're like, oh no, she's ridiculously hot for sure
But I you know she's somebody I'd like to marry in theory
This is just where I'm at these days. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Uh, I but I liked the movie. I didn't love it
and I told you primarily because you know I'm a big fan of anthology horror and
sci -fi and the premise of the guy in the bunker is he crazy is he not is
something really happening outside has been done many times on many classic
anthology TV shows so it wasn't my first rodeo with that premise but they did a
good job with it. I just can't imagine they would have been done that well. I thought
And honestly, nowadays, even though I think it's way better than a competent movie, the movie is competent, I'm thrilled.
It was done very, very well.
But there are sort of plot devices that kind of go along with that story.
So that's where some of the surprise got taken away from me, because I was already thinking,
like they're probably going to do this thing because that's kind of how this goes
usually. Yes. Whereas you were massively ignorant to this to the existence of
this type of story. I've seen plenty of Twilight zones. I know that type of
story exists. I thought it was extremely well done. It was. Every movie you go to see
has been done a billion times for the most part. It was well done. But I thought
John Goodman deserves to win best actor and what is his best stock acting role ever, which
is a hard thing to say because he's always very good.
Never less than great.
And it's like John Goodman not nominated for supporting actor for the Big Lebowski.
You know, I don't know how it's possible.
Jeff Bridges not nominated for the Big Lebowski.
I don't know how it's possible.
I think one nomination is for flight.
Probably the movie he was his worst in.
flight where he plays Denzo Washington's drug dealer.
Yeah, but like he was, he went over the top.
He was, he was over the top.
He was good in it.
I liked him.
He was nominated for that though.
I believe so.
It is a very good movie.
It's a movie that I think a lot of people would write it off and think of, you know,
oh, that's a mainstream, whatever.
But I, I thought that movie was surprisingly edgy and.
I dug flight.
I liked it a lot.
Great nudity at the beginning when I wasn't expecting.
Huh?
Great nudity at the beginning. I wasn't expecting well that shot of him just staring into her coach as she bends over as a
Was mildly disturbing. I I still I'll tell you what took flight was my penis, right? I bet that day you had a bone in your body
the
No, the I I love Denzel Washington in a way that I still get upset when he plays anybody sort of skewie or bad
sure it still upsets me I still feel like I'm seeing my dad or my uncle play like
I do something mean sure so but he's great he's great in it I preferred we
talked about this the other night and you scoffed at me but I preferred the
witch to ten clover field lane and I don't understand why you don't get the
which but you don't I don't think that's completely absurd I thought the
which was massively dull.
It had a nice tone and it was shot in kind of a cool way as well.
Maybe if I watched it again with subtitles, it would help
because I had no idea what anyone was saying.
And I didn't care, frankly, that's a shame.
And the 10th time they did a slow zoom on a rabbit's nose
twitching, I said, yeah, I'm not scared right now.
And my buddy I saw it with hated it more than I did.
He said he would have walked out if I wasn't there with him.
I love the movie, I love the movie, I think it's idiotic what you're saying right now.
That's fine.
I think you sound like a stupid asshole.
It had a couple scary moments, it was trying to go for a David Lynch thing, it was nowhere
near.
I didn't get David Lynch from it at all, I got just that feeling of dread.
I got William Peter Blattie, I got William Friedkin, I got Kubrick, that's what I
got out of that movie. I mean, that's just crazy. It was very much like the
shining. The shining is an extremely slow film. And an hour longer than the
which I might add. I had way more echoes of the shining in clover time clover
online. You fucking asshole. Which also reminded me of movies like
Misery Die Hard. I thought it had a lot of homage. Misery and Die Hard, he says.
Yeah. Now, please. Well, she crawls around on the vents. I don't want to
To remind you of die hard it's essentially the plot of misery a woman wakes up tied chain to a bed
There were little nods to it throughout nobody is nobody's taking issue with the misery comparison
You said die hard and then you also an event forever and you all like this remind I think the director
And the writers and the producers nobody in that J .J. Abrams camp are always trying to create the feeling of those movies from their youth
80s and 90s movies 70s probably for them Spielberg as well and
And Kubrick I think this is as good a job as they've done with it. I have a lot better than super eight
Which you claim to like I love super eight. They wanted to make a goonies and they made a goonies
They could have called that goonies, too, and I would have been like yeah, this is the goonies goonies as well
Well, yeah, look I like the goonies, but I just want to down about I want something on the record
Your honor if this could please be marked in the record
highlighted with stars and asterisks next to it. For anytime we have a discussion
or a difference about movies on this podcast. I want our listeners to remember the
time you said, 10 Cloverfield Lane reminded me more of the shining because I
got echoes of misery and die hard from it. Not because I just want everybody to
remember that. That was your argument that it was more like the shining and in
and the next breath you mentioned die hard.
You're telling them what I didn't say
because of is not what I said.
I'm saying it had nods, I think, stylistic nods
that the director might even admit to
to a lot of those 80s.
You know who else crawls around in a vent?
Harry Krump.
You're goddamn right.
Did you get Harry Krump out of clover feeling?
No, but I did definitely get died.
Anytime anybody goes up in a shaft,
I think of die hard.
Well then you think of Harry Krump.
But I did not think of Harry.
Did you get Bert Wunderstone when the knife was coming through the walls and almost hitting her in the fucking face?
No, I don't remember Bert Wunderstone. It was by Don Scardina, who's a great man. I love Don. He is a great man.
You know Don Scardina? I do not. I do know Don. We had a meeting many years ago. He's very nice to me.
Okay, yeah, he's great. Here's the thing.
And this disappointed me slightly. I did read an article on movie web today about 10 Cloverfield Lane
and what the original ending was supposed to be.
Probably shouldn't say it.
It's too no.
It's, I'm not gonna say it, all right.
But in discussing what the original ending was supposed to be,
they were describing the current ending
and some other things about the current.
Croning, you know, it wasn't great for me.
But the, the, the, I don't know who the interview is
with the writer, whoever, it wasn't with,
I don't think it was with JJ Abrams,
but the guy's just literally going,
yeah, so this happens in the movie
which we ripped from Battle Los Angeles
And then this happens which we took from this he's just like sighting like yeah
We just took this from this other movie. Yeah, I found that a little disappointing which again back to my
Battle Los Angeles
It says it in the article but brings me back to my original premise or point it was a good movie
But there were many things in it where I was like I've seen this already so I'm not that excited about it sure
Where's the which I've never seen anything like that in my life?
Have you I've seen it done better a billion. Oh, please
What the village I am yeah, oh fuck you Pat. Honestly. Yeah, that's idiotic. Yeah, I prefer the village of the witch
Okay, everybody please fangory fans remember the time Pat was said I prefer the village to the which strongly
That's acidine
That's an acidine thing to say if I go to a movie with a completely open mind expecting to enjoy it
and I'm bored, not scared, don't like it, don't understand a word that's being said,
I'm not gonna apologize and say I did like it, and my buddy hated it more than I did.
Your buddy, you know, I don't know who your buddy is, who's your buddy.
I'm talking to numerous people who despised it, and then a couple who really loved it, and that's
fine. Everybody I know liked it because they were able to keep up with it.
No, I understood the plot. I'm saying the way they were speaking I was like I don't know what's
I got used to it, but that's just me, you know, I adapt to an experience. I thought that the girl was a good actor
I thought there were a few effective moments
But at the end of it, I was like
Like they every actor was unbelievable in it. They had those six -year -old kids speaking like that old English
It was crazy
It was crazy. The shit they were pulling off that fucking the little boy
When he's doing that monologue about Jesus. It was like it was one of the best act
It's the only movies I've ever been in was one of the best acting things I've ever seen in my life
I mean, we're just coming out of from a different place. Yeah, Christ go watch
Die harder. You know what you're hearing folks is rap
Well, you brought it out of me today, babe. I mean, but like
Like see you you still do that when I was like 20
And earlier
Maybe maybe even longer than that my friends would say oh, I hated this movie that I loved and I would wind up screaming
right or vice versa. I love this movie that I hate. You still do it at age 56. You still get this
upset. And I respect it. I love the passion. But now if somebody hates something I love, I'm like
fine. I'll watch it again. You know what you want. Don't get me wrong. If we were at a cocktail party
and you were a lady in a skirt, I wouldn't be yelling like this. I've seen but we're doing a podcast.
We're doing a podcast at 4 p .m. No, you have absolutely have not seen that. We're doing a podcast at 4 o 'clock in the afternoon with two beyond tall boys. I don't know what you call the 24 ounce cans. Well, it is 630. You haven't set your clock forward yet.
Uh, and I refuse to. I'm not playing ball with this daylight savings anymore.
It's gonna be an hour late. I just don't care.
All right. Now, I'll be on time, but I'm just gonna in my head.
I'm gonna say I'm on derosa central time. All right.
Well, for six months of the year, you won't be rebelling at all. It'll just be.
That's fine. Normal. And then I'll look at that as they finally adapted to me.
Yeah. But every time I get an email on the West Coast, they say,
house 3 p .m. and I'm going to say 3 p .m. PST 2 p .m. MST, which is my standard time. So they
know because this is what I'm doing from now on because fuck these people. It is really
stupid. I guess it's it's a farming thing apparently. Something like that. I don't know. We did
a monologue about it on the Pete home show years ago and got a lot of hate mail on the behalf
of farmers and it was we were joking obviously they'd be in bed at 12 30 in the morning and wake up at
330 to harvest the grain thought we were safe we thought it was like making fun of the amish
but apparently no now you I've heard you speak very
angrily about certain movies you you've yelled at me at a
restaurant about enjoying aliens which I thought was a
universally beloved movie by everyone in the world
but you screamed at me as though I had the craziest opinion by enjoying a
And acknowledged classic. I never screened you about aliens. I said you you said it was superior to the first movie
And that's what I yelled at you about. Yeah, and then I said I enjoyed Terminator two when you were upset about that shit pile that movie
Watch it again most people don't think that
Most people are idiots. We just talked about that for the first 30 minutes of the podcast
Most people I know who are not idiots and beyond got news for you. I've been to your parties folks
Um. Good. Is Juliet Lewis an idiot, Joe?
She was the famous person at the last one.
Uh, Johnny Galecki, man. Johnny Galecki had his had two parties.
He'd homes. So I've had both kids from Christmas vacation at my house.
Yeah. Juliet Lewis came to the first one.
These, this is very true. She came to the first one.
I missed her. I missed the second party where I could have gotten some Johnny Galecki.
Yeah. I got that.
Uh, who do you think is going to show up at the third one?
Can I throw some, I hope that really is Angela when we keep riding,
round and out those Griswolds. That'd be great. Yeah. Richard Kahn possibly or Richard Kahn or
Richard Kahn. Dickie Kahn. I don't think Rathus. Yeah. Now my birthday party. Yeah.
Belving showed up. Oh, now Belving is a big alleged co -cat on the hall.
And I used to go after tape nights over to this place. Dimples Karaoke and he would be there.
a grass -ively alleged leave and I saw it
groping the waitresses and I'd be like is he in here every night doing this?
And they're like yeah, it's a real problem but he tips well. So to dark
town we go to the bathroom for five minutes, come out like eyes bulging, start
grabbing waitresses asses. Mr. Belding. Oh boy. Dennis Haskins y 'all. And everyone
was like I wonder if he hangs out here across from NBC in the hopes that
somebody strolls in, has a few too many and offers him like a Mr. Belding
spin -off. Oh boy. Well he showed up at my birthday. Apparently he walked in, looked around,
walked out. But you know who did hang out for a little while was uh ex -Mr. Simpson, uh, Nick, uh...
That's right? Yeah, Nick Lachey rolled in for quite some time. Where was your party?
I was at that bar remember? Oh yeah, I remember, I saw Nick Lachey there. Tiny man. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I always thought he would be like a big like kind of like South Philly type and he's not. He's like
I got a little guy, Jessica Simpson went public saying that he had a very small penis and
couldn't pleasure him.
She did?
Which, yeah, I thought was a little shocking, but yeah.
I mean, she just says a giant ass and pussy.
We know that that's possible.
It's anything's possible.
Well, look, he's a tiny man, usually tiny men have big hogs, but I wouldn't be surprised
if he's told me he had a, he only had a little button on him, because he was so small.
Usually tiny men have big hogs, is that what you're saying?
That's usually the way, you know, nature kind of does it, you know, that you're a short
guy that give you something to throw around.
I'm a tall guy.
I have very average penis.
Now when I was building two, before we get into your smut, any deeper, was that something
that seems to upset you and a lot of people that never bothers me.
I was talking to a woman at work today.
She's great.
I have no issue with her at all.
But she was talking about 10 clover fuel and she was like, I loved it so much and me and my daughter on the edge of our
See and I had the best time and she's like, but that ending just ruined the whole thing for me
That is not an outlook. I've ever had my life. If a movie keeps me under a spell for 90 minutes and in the last 10
They do something stupid. It never pisses me off. You seem to get pissed off by a bad ending and things are hard
I get that you can be let down by it, but I don't forget the 90 minutes that came before that I loved
If it gets away from itself anywhere in the third act amount and that's a lot of fucking movies
I'm out and I will tell you I wasn't crazy about the end of 10 Cloverfield Lane
It seemed a little too was crazy about it convenient. I agree
That's what I you know when I read the it about I said goodman was perfect the movie was almost when I read the original original
Original ending. I was like oh this is much better. Yeah
But yeah, I didn't I didn't fully care for
For the ending it was did they say the studio said do a different ending or who made that I didn't read that part
I just read what it was originally in the script
But I mean there's a great twilight zone with Joe Montana. It's from the 80s twilight zone
Where he builds a bunker?
There's a guy his neighbors in the bunker with him
He
Same kind of thing. He's like kind of psychotic. He won't let anybody in he won't let anybody out
I didn't seem like a good role for Joe Montenia to me.
Uh, he's good at it.
All right.
He's good at it.
Did you mean Joe Montana?
No.
Okay.
But I'm glad you resurfaced a joke from Joe Montenia's SNL monologue in 87.
I swear to God, that's a joke they do.
All right.
Well, a little kid wants to leave and they dad goes, I'm sorry.
My son thought Joe Montenia was hosting and he's like, can I talk to you kid?
Yeah.
And that's like sure.
He pulls the kid backstage and he's like, I play a lot of bad men in movies.
It's not an act. Uh -huh. I suggest you stay and watch the show. It's really funny.
That's good.
Anyway, uh, the, uh, anyway, same type of thing. You know, and then the guy, there's even the part where the guy's like, I hear people out there.
We got to go. We got to get saved.
Joe Montana's like, you can't go out there.
The guy runs out, Joe Montana is like,
you're out, fuck you, you're dead, whatever.
This dome was built.
And then in the end, in the outside world,
the buildings and the people that were here
before the bomb hit.
The dome itself is containing
the remaining nuclear fallout or whatever.
So you realize, Montana, when he heard the people upstairs,
it was them building.
He could have escaped.
He doesn't and now he's sealed into this thing forever and his meters all say it's dangerous outside because it's all been sealed
To me that was such like a great twist on the ending. Yeah, and it's more of a TV or ending than a movie ending
I realize but yeah
I have a feeling with this with this 10 chlorophyll lane. There were like we've spent three million dollars on this blockbuster movie like that movie cost nothing until the end
you know like again I don't want to spoil anything but like they probably I
guarantee the studio was like you can't call this Cloverfield get people's
expectations up for action and then deliver this like very tense little three
character chamberpiece with no big stars because you know it's not an indie
movie. Well I think the movie still could have ended similarly to the way it
ended. I just thought they could have it could have had a little more depth. Yeah no
I'd read the ending like I said wasn't my favorite, but what do you know Pat?
What can you do? What else is pissing you off because we're gonna wrap this up in a few because we had to do two today guys
And we know there were some complaints about the length of the last one
You miss these two -hour marathon fucking talk sessions. And then somebody today was like
Hey, I thought if you guys were only doing it for an hour at least we could get it once a week or something
It's like hey, just be happy you're getting it at all baby
Listen, I'm very flattered. Thank you so much for all of your comments. It's very nice. That never makes me mad. No
But these are gonna probably be around 50 minutes today because we have to do two because I'm going on tour for three weeks
Yeah, we're trying to bang them out, which I should plug I guess, right? Yeah, maybe when we're done
Hey, nothing else really pissing me off, Joe
Well, we talked about how much I hate social media. We talked about how much I hate your opinion on many movies
So I think it was just the which talked about how much I hate politics and
the people that believe in it talked about how the arts seem to be at a real
low point talked about the lack of accountability out there I mean these are my
big ones yeah this is this is I mean I have huge bits about this in my act right
now so I mean speaking of accountability Joe had a dog walk at the other
night and the dog got out lost my dog you know the dog is back now and we're all
You can't trust anyone to do a good job with anything, you know.
It was a very traumatic experience and the reason was he left the front door open in
the dog right now.
I was like, well, what did you do that for?
The answer was, I don't know.
Yeah.
I mean, there's nothing you can do.
It's like dealing with, this is the problem these days.
It's like, you know, I hate to reference Cosby, given the current climate of things with
the man.
But he has that thing on Bill Cosby himself where he talks about kids and he's like, they
just say I don't know everything. Yeah. And it's like that's and how infuriating that is and
that's what adults do. And so the part part is is we're living in this time where nobody has
to be accountable and everybody can just be like I'm sorry I didn't know any better when you know
they did. Yet it's also the time where if you hit somebody you're more I mean the lawsuits are
going to fly it faster than anything. So there's no more like let's just go Duke this out please
because you're really fucked up and then there's also no more just admitting
to stuff. People have found the life loophole where they're able to just go oh
you can't do anything to me and I can just say I don't know and that's it.
And the internet is fostering it. Everybody says glaringly obvious, soothing, everyone
agrees with your opinion things all day. Then you get back all the speed back of
People going I agree with your very obvious boring opinion that everybody thinks right and then you're like
Yes, we all agree everybody. Everything's cool. Then when one person attempts to say something different original
I disagree whatever else
People can't handle it and almost force them off the internet now granted if that something is hate speech
that's not good but people having a different opinion than yours is not
fucking hate speech and it's often regarded that way. You don't feel like me
and all of my friends who share my exact same opinions feel about this topic and
therefore you're a monster. We got to all slam this but it's not the case. And
that's my point about the pendulum swinging. When Bush was in office the big joke
was that all of his supporters and everybody that was on his side and the
the criticism of them and the joke about them was that
these fucking people all hang out with each other.
They have the same opinion,
they don't want any outside views coming in.
If they do your trade or your treasonous,
you're against America.
Those people that were all complaining about that
are now the people saying,
if you don't agree with us then you're a sexist
or you're a racist or you're either so that.
You can't win on either side, no.
You can't call the assholes, assholes.
You can't call the dickheads dickheads, you're just,
No, you're just, you can't talk to anybody about anything anymore. There's no gray area. No. And then you and I, dear friends, our friendship has with stained many arguments, some small, some minor so many. I think there's been one or two.
But I'm saying us arguing about the which is an argument. That's what I'm saying.
I wouldn't very excited to see the which I didn't feel the same you and I butt heads on it
You think I'm an idiot you y 'all fuck you at me
But I know that
You that we're fine and that sort of
discourse
Should be happening a lot more and it doesn't if I if I was talking to people and I'm like, oh fuck you
Then chlorophyll lane was awesome, you know people get shaken up by it because everyone has become
massive massive buses. Oh yeah and actually you telling me you speaking this
passionately about the witch we usually agree on a lot of things. It makes me
feel to myself okay maybe when the witch comes on cable I'll check it out again.
Maybe I was wrong maybe I should watch it with subtitles. These arguments can
lead to maybe changing your opinion maybe helping you see things in a
different way. You don't have to be the end of the world. Joe loved the witch I
didn't like the witch. Were we still friends? Yes and I have frightened a few people
with my yeah no your opinions yeah sure I'm a rough around the edges you know I'm old school but
that's fine it's what I love I was gonna say one other thing about the shit about the people
the people I don't know anymore I don't know anymore it's an upsetting time now Wrath in the movie
7 was when he killed John Dell that's why I made the confusion when he kills Kevin Spacey John
Yeah. Yeah. Yes. That's it completes the cycle. So that was just it like that. They're they're filing him murdering a man as anger. Yeah. Okay. Cool. What a well, but I mean it is and it literally is the the truest definition of rap. It's feel my rap. See, that's, I guess that's what I was saying for a movie man. Yeah, for to be a mainstream blockbuster movie. That's a pretty hardcore ending. I watched seven. Once a year. My thinking is okay.
That was one of the first R -rated movies I saw I couldn't watch until late. I was probably 14 or something and I'm always like
Our movies not much worse now and the answer just simply is yes
It's not because we were kids and movies seem better, right? And there was shit coming out of that time, too
I think the same week seven was out Congo wasn't
But with the fucking Tim Curry and the apes, right, but
But it's just seems like a really bad time in 7 in terms of a screenplay as such a fascinating
and dark and perfect screenplay and there's a movie where the ending you're like holy
lord a that was completely unexpected and be the absolute perfect ending for this movie.
And that sort of thing just doesn't happen anymore.
No it doesn't it doesn't and as much as I can say chlorophyll lands affair movie in a few
months I really really loved it and I really did and was scared the whole time. When it ends I'm
kind of like all right it ended bad and I figured it would and what are you gonna do because that's
what everyone's doing they're like one of you gonna say it is what I can tell you I found the original
ending to be it's not as dark talk about that at seven but it was a little more along those
emotionally satisfactory missed had a dark as shit fucking ending and you know the crazy trivia
about that. That is not the end of the story. Yeah, no, no, the story they just drive into
the mist and you don't know what happens. Yeah, they were like, let's put an ending on
this thing. And I stick with people. I saw some interview with Darebot and he was like, you
know, it was Iraq and Bush and the world was so dark. I just wanted to dive right into
how bad I was feeling at the time and things have gotten significantly worse. And that's
We don't really reflect them.
Yeah, show everybody.
There you go.
Follow me, Joe DeRosa Comedy on Twitter.
Follow Pat at D Patrick Walsh on Twitter.
I'm coming your way possibly.
I'm barking on a three week tour,
starting Wednesday, March 16th.
This might or may not be out by then, I don't know.
But if it is, look here are the dates.
The 18th of 19th, I'll be in Wilmington, North Carolina.
I believe the 22nd, I'm in Greenville, South Carolina, I think that's a Tuesday, that Thursday
I'm in Hattiesburg, Mississippi, the next night I'm in Lafayette, Louisiana, that Saturday
night I'm in New Orleans, Louisiana, and then the following Tuesday through Saturday I'm
at Acme Comedy Club in Minneapolis, Minnesota.
So come on out, doing the new hour, ramping up to something special with this one, so come
check it out. I will be performing with the Thunder from Down Under, all -male
nude review at the Mirage Hotel and Casino from June 12th to June 19th. The 19th
is a very special night because I'm going full dick. Yeah, so please come out
show your support. When I take that dick out I'd love to have a lot of fans showing
at the respective deserves. Go see it. It is a sight to see. You've been listening to We'll
see you in hell. It's a presentation of the Fangoria podcast network produced by Thomas DeFail,
executive produced by Ken Hanley, a Fangoria entertainment, for press opportunities, advertising inquiries,
and information about We'll see you in hell. Contact Ken at Fangoria .com. See you later. Bye guys.
You