I'll see you on hell understand, I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell
Yeah, your favorite podcast covering higher, sci -fi action and genre movies.
I went into a little of a little small guy from Twin Peaks there.
Yeah, higher, is how you started.
Right.
It was just a mispronounce, an honest mispronunciation, but then I tried to lean into it.
They tell you to use what comes out in acting.
Is that right?
No, I made it up.
My parents used to tell me to use what comes out in the bathroom.
And that's when you got into your fecal modeling.
Right.
Yep.
Remember that?
Folks, we've been gone a long time.
We thank you for your patience.
We thank you for your impatience.
I like the people who are angry that we are gone because it makes you feel loved and appreciate.
And that's the only way that I can ever understand love is to rage.
Same here.
Going back to my fecal modeling.
The last time we talked, not me and you, but everybody was, we did two live shows in Shaitown,
Chicago, the windy city, the big blue baby, the bitch of the Midwest, the Dolly Madison,
the big blue baby is a term for Chicago.
I don't think so now.
Oh, okay.
Uh, the ringly city, okay, um, Crinkle town, Crinkle town, Catherine Zeta Jonesville.
She was in that picture, but very fun shows.
I can say for me, that was sort of a lifelong bottom for me, that trip.
Uh, and I, I'm sure I hit it well.
We had a lot of fun, but man, I was just down.
I've turned things around, uh, I'm lexaprown it up.
I've essentially stopped drinking, although I will dabble and, uh, things are good.
I'm working on new shit, put an old shit behind and, uh, how are you, Joe?
I'm fine, uh, I don't agree with anything you just said.
What do you mean?
I don't think you're in a better place.
I think you're, I believe drinking constantly, believe it or not, I am in a better place.
I know I'm kidding.
I'm teasing.
It's not a great place, but it's a better place to Patrick daddy's teasing.
All right.
Uh, I'm fine.
I'm, I'm actually hitting a low.
So, uh, I, well, I've been actually a lot of change in my life too.
I'm hitting a high and a low at the same time.
I've been living, uh, back in New York, uh, a lot of the time, again, which is also what
has led to the big apple, this hiatus and this change in, uh, distribution and all these things
with our podcast here, right.
Uh, so that has made me quite happy.
I, I kind of realized finally after six years that I just wasn't a good fit for Los Angeles
in a full time sense, made some friends, had some fun, uh, but, you know, being here all
the time constantly with no other option has not been good for me.
So, uh, per this recording, I'm, I'm living in both places and, um, I like that, but I got
to say the time that I'm here, I'm quite sad, uh, because it is just, don't I help?
You're not around.
You're married man.
I'm here.
Yeah.
For work.
We hung out this weekend.
Yeah.
You know, you, of course, yeah, the, the, the spurts of friendship that you get in this city
do help, right.
But all of my friends are married and in relationships and, and it's, you know, it's, it's, it's, it's
not like you can, when you, when you don't see your friends here, you don't see people.
I mean, you're, you're in, dude.
Sure.
Have you thought about joining a committed thrupple?
Uh, I talked to your wife about that.
She was into it.
You were not.
That's right.
You said, she said, she said, Pat put the kibosh on this kiboshi.
I was threatened.
Uh, so you figure, I'm bisexual.
I'm bipolar.
I might as well be bicoastal.
I'm Amy Poler.
Which is my bisexual name.
Your polar express, one of the most disturbing films ever made.
Which is my favorite bi club that I go to.
Have you seen the polar express?
No.
Why would I see?
Oh, came out when we were 26.
It's like, I mean, it's a mechus, of course, a genius.
But it is, they're, they're, we're not ready to do it.
Like the, the technology wasn't there.
So you've got this like cheerful Christmas movie, but everybody looks like a possessed demon.
And with dead eyes.
And it's like the early days of motion capture, it looks really unsettling.
Yeah, it's almost worth watching as a horror experiment.
But go on.
I remember when it came out being so mad at Tom Hanks, like this fucking guy won't do like splash
too.
I know.
But he's doing this goddamn thing.
And it was right.
And it's hell been on being taken seriously.
Like he just wouldn't, there's a five minute song and it devoted to how delicious hot chocolate
is.
Oh, hot chocolate.
It warms up your mouth and they're all dancing and drinking it.
Terrible.
Um, excuse me, so anyway, back to, back to my life, yeah.
Being back here is, it's, I'm not going to lie.
It's been a little tough.
I'm not a fan of the city as this business listeners of this podcast are well aware.
I have things in this city that I like, such as Mr. Patrick Walsh, this podcast.
But the city as a whole and being a man in the position I'm in and life right now and
what I can just be more proactive in New York, I can do stand up every night.
You know, when you want to get out of the house and go right, you can go to a place where
human beings actually make connections with one another and look each other in the face.
Uh, everybody isn't buried in a script somewhere, every bartender actually serves the
drinks properly because they don't secretly think they're supposed to be the next cluny.
Sure.
But now it's just a better overall experience for me.
Don't you think there's a little grass is always greener here?
Sure.
And I know that I know that once, uh, if I, if I were to switch over to New York full
time, yeah, I would need to get out of there.
Sure.
Sometimes as well.
Maybe you got to do the work on the man and not the location.
The work's been done on the man for years.
Yeah, it's, it's, it's, it's the, it's, I'm blaming full cities at this point.
Um, but here's the thing.
I would need to get away.
I just think the place to get away too is not Los Angeles.
That's where my thoughts are right now.
You know, but I'll have to come back even if I do do go through it.
I'll have to come back here for work and, and when I do do that, we'll bang out some
parties and, uh, and by parties, I mean, we'll go to the toilet together.
I didn't like banging out some parties.
I will say that.
Uh, anyway, now, Joe, could I, could I tell you some death cab for cutie lyrics that might
help?
Uh, okay.
I think that it's brainless to assume that making changes to your Windows view will give
a new perspective from a, a really good song called lacking out the friction.
Set up.
No.
I know the song.
I, I like death cab because you pulled it out of your phone.
You read it.
I just looked at the lyrics to make sure I had it right.
Uh, I had a feeling that not only would you not fully approve of my potential transition,
I also knew you wouldn't be able to express it as a normal person, which supports my argument
about Los Angeles.
What song lyrics are we have to read it through?
Well, Christ, that's like, that's like worse than giving somebody a hallmark card.
Uh, no, I think that, that's true.
You know, like if you're depressed, changing your, your city ain't going to help.
Uh, I'm not, I'm not depressed.
I'm not happy in Los Angeles.
Sure.
I don't like, I don't like being this far away from my family.
Yes.
Uh, that's fair.
I'm one of the, that's where we differ.
Well, yeah, me and everybody else in this city, everybody that prosperous out here hates
their family.
I don't know.
I'm not saying you hate that.
You know what I mean though?
They don't, but they, they have absolutely no problem not seeing them.
Let's put it that way.
Sure.
I don't like being this far for my family.
I don't like being this, uh, limited with standup.
Uh, I think you're doing a lot of standup, I'm, dude, I'm doing three shows a night back
there.
Okay.
A night.
It's like Glen Gary Glen Ross level shit like I got to go across the street.
Mitch and Murray aren't taking care of me here.
Sure.
Uh, I do a decent amount here.
Are you pounding the pavement?
What else is there to pound?
Bringing bells.
I'm bringing bells.
A ring ding dong ding, ding, ding, ding, ding, their heads ringing.
Uh, I can just do a lot more there.
The energy of the city suits me a bit better.
I'm closer to my family.
Um, and also to just.
Two other things and then I'll stop.
Number one, I don't need to see the fucking billboards anymore.
Sure.
I'm tired of it.
I don't need to see the fucking billboards anymore.
A lot of new shows coming to the epic network.
I'll tell you that much.
God almighty.
God bless you networks.
God bless all of you.
Yeah.
I don't need to see the billboards every three feet anymore.
Uh, and then also I, uh, this is three things.
There should be two.
It's three things.
Number two, I don't want to compete for stage time against Jeremy Pithin.
Sure.
Have you ever competed for stage time against Jeremy?
Guy gets more sets at clubs on past that than, than, than I do.
So that's to me that's competing.
And number three.
Did you do six seasons of entourage?
I did seven.
Oh.
On a little show called Elantiragio, which was the Spanish speaking version of a show.
And it did not many people here know this.
The biggest hit that they had seen in that country since Chico and the man.
And you played a euhenio, entourage, the longest name.
And I think that's why the show didn't take off.
Yes.
You can't put that on a t -shirt.
Yeah.
No.
It's, uh, yeah.
I was the main character.
Uh, anyway.
So then I, so, but then on the third thing is to, and look, this is not to pick on any one
of our friends.
Uh -oh.
No.
It's just a thing about L .A.
It's all.
But let me tell you this.
All of my shim, Donnecke, almost all of my friends out here do this, almost all my
friends out.
And again, it's not to take shots or to pick on anybody.
It's just a different way of life out here.
You know, I'll make a plan with somebody.
I'll be told, you know, I'll let you know what's up at whatever time.
And then you just never hear from the people.
Now is it devastating?
It's not devastating.
Right.
Is it, is it, am I scorned?
No.
But it's just like, I, it's just a different way of setting a plan.
Not only do you mean the people who are like, we gotta hang out sometime and then never
happen.
I mean, like, kind of setting like one of those like, you know, like, like, like, let's put
this way in New York if you say, Hey, man, so what do you think you want to try to do this
later?
Uh, yeah.
Let me see what's up.
But let's try to make it work.
Okay.
There's the, there's the understanding of, there will be a check in and we will follow up
on this.
Sure.
Here.
And again, I'm not, this is just a way of the, of it being, it's just the way it is here.
Yeah.
Most people I know that does, that just means you may or may not speak to me.
Right.
And I just, it's just not my thing.
It's not my rhythm.
I agree.
I just don't care for it.
So when you're married or in a relationship, uh, out here or have a kid or whatever it is,
that sort of stuff is not quite as, you're not as reliant on that hang to make a connection.
When you don't have that, it's, it's painfully isolating a touch out here.
Nobody else's fault, but it's just not, it's just not agreeing with me.
Well, I'm going to, here's a quick anecdote in the column of, I completely understand why
you want to leave Los Angeles.
Thank you.
You got more lyrics for me?
No.
Joe, Joe, you're, you may be right.
I may be crazy.
I happen to be listening to that song.
It's a very good song, uh, cab for cutie.
I, I liked the early stuff.
I'm sorry.
I never heard one of their songs ever.
I think they made some great music.
They could at least up through trans -lanticism, and I might go a little further.
That's what I heard.
They were part of that whole, though, like late 90s alt thing where, like, everybody was,
you know, all the wrong people were telling me that they were the greatest band.
And I was like, get out of my, it was like when Interpol and, you know, I fucking love Interpol.
I'm not knocking the bands.
I'm not saying they suck.
I'm just saying at the times that they were really big, all the wrong people were telling
me to listen.
I hear that.
Uh, so I got to go to the post office.
Here's how I start my day, Ashina.
I had all these Blu -rays and DVDs.
Joe just did a massive dump of shit up at a Miba music with a, a large chest, a wooden
chest full of DVDs and albums.
By the way, I slipped a couple out that I didn't mean to.
What do you mean?
I, somewhere in that pile that I wanted to keep.
Oh, you lost your mom from the train.
Well, you can always rebuy throw mom for, for 28 cents.
Um, yeah, so I had taken a lot of old stuff up to, uh, a Miba and didn't get a real
good price for them.
Some of them, Criterions, things I hadn't even unwrapped yet, et cetera.
I sell on eBay or Amazon, you know, and make a decent profit.
So I had sold on eBay a copy of Persona, Ingmar Bergman's Persona on Blu -ray because I got
the Ingmar Bergman box set.
I had all these moves.
As did I.
So I'm like, well, shit, I can make more money than I spent.
So I put it online.
This woman on eBay makes me an offer.
She goes, would you take 12 for it?
I'm asking 20.
Like, I really don't want to, don't put something on eBay to like get into a negotiation
with somebody.
That's how eBay works.
I realize that now.
But I go, yeah, 12 is fine.
Is it in mint condition?
I said, it's new.
It's brand new.
It's wrapped.
I've never opened it.
Can I see pictures?
Oh my God.
I go, honestly, no.
Do you want it or not?
I can put it in the mail.
I'm not going to go take pictures.
Otherwise, somebody else will buy it.
Right.
She's like, I'll take it.
I accept the sale.
She goes, now I should tell you I'm in Germany.
So you'll have to send it to this, like, the whole endeavour costs me more than what she
was paying for it, basically.
I'm sending it to some, you know, like, camp somewhere that, from there they send it
on to Germany.
Oh, I thought you were making some kind of Nazi.
No.
I'll leave that out.
Digs.
All right.
But I get, finally I get like a week into it like it's arrived at the camp and now it's going
on to her location.
I'm like, I need to change my settings clearly so that I'm not doing international sales
anymore.
So I wake up to three emails from this woman.
She goes, hi, the DVD arrived severely damaged.
I need to return it.
By the way, when Amazon sends me a record, if I buy a record, it's always got giant dense
in it.
And they're just trusting that you're not going to go, because you have to pay for it.
You just go.
I'll keep it.
Amazon will go, if you call up and go, it's damn it, they'll go, well, we'll give, here's
your money back.
Yeah, sometimes otherwise you got to drive it up to UPS and all this.
So she goes, it's damaged and she goes and the reason it's damaged, I believe, is that
you packaged it so carelessly.
No bubble wrap.
I asked you repeatedly to wrap it nicely, whatever, after this podcast, so I'm not digging
through my phone on the air, I will show you, he couldn't take her ass to the store for
an extra eight dollars and buy the fucking thing.
I will show you the photos.
I'm not going to, if I look it up now, I'll get too angry.
There is nothing wrong.
There's not even a slightest dent in the box.
It's in mint condition, perfectly sealed.
So I have a perfect rating on eBay.
Somehow she does too.
I go look, lady, you are going to return it to me because I'll sell it again in five minutes.
I'll refund your money, but if I were to send this to eBay and ask them to judge it, no
one in their right mind would say that that is a damaged product.
She doesn't even acknowledge that I've said that.
She just moves past it.
She's showing me pictures of a perfect DVD box as if it's proof that it's been damaged.
But I have learned sometimes people are fucking nuts and there's no sense engaging.
I would have been emailing her for days.
So I'm going to take it, I go up to the post office, she's going to mail it back to me and
I got to, I got to ship something else.
I bring it with me up to the post office.
These are two different incidents.
I'm already a little hot.
I walk in for once in my 10 year history in Los Angeles, there's nobody at the post office.
I'm excited.
I walk up.
There are four grown men, 50 years old plus standing and having a conversation behind the
counter.
I'm waiting.
Finally I stroll about halfway over to them, but not even up to one of their stands.
And I said, hey, are, are, when are you guys open super politely?
They all look up at me, they don't say anything.
The guy goes, yeah, I can take you.
Is this one we went together?
No.
Different.
I walk.
Oh, you're saying post office.
Post office.
Oh, I thought you meant amoeba's.
Oh, we can talk about that too.
Sorry, I got confused.
Sorry.
Talk about that too.
But he goes, no, we can take you.
There's a lot of attitude coming off him.
So I walk over.
I hand him the thing and I'm just looking to mail this, you know, cheapest way possible.
He goes, uh -huh, picks it up, he's looking at it, and he looks up at me and goes, so, um,
I guess you just didn't see the sign then, huh?
I said, I'm sorry.
He was the sign.
What are you talking about?
Did you want to step back?
Step back.
I look over.
I said, I actually, I didn't see a sign and I still don't, to be honest, I don't know
what you're talking about.
He goes, the sign that says, wait until you are called to get in line.
Wow.
So I said, sir, I don't see it right now.
And by the way, I left the post office not seeing this sign.
I don't think it was there, but even if it was, it's like, I'm walking in.
Like, this, you're a business.
He go, I go, I didn't see it.
He goes, yeah.
All right.
Is that's, uh, ah, shakes his head, starts doing the paperwork.
Then he goes, mutters to himself without looking up, just seems, uh, kind of convenient.
Jesus Christ.
I said, you know what, give it, give it back to me, I'm going to use the, uh, this, this
self -check out.
He goes, okay, stops in the middle of the transaction and hands it to me, looks up at me
with a smile on his face.
And I walked over to the self, check out.
He resumed his conversation and I checked it out by myself.
Jesus Christ.
I could have burned the place to the ground, right?
Take it easy.
It's a government facility.
I didn't.
Don't get, don't, don't even say that you want to though.
We all learned from Kathy Griffin, didn't we?
I just, I couldn't believe it, you know, like, what are you doing?
Um, when I was a grocery cashier, I didn't like bringing people up, but I'd be like,
hey, bananas, 401, I tried to dazzle them with my knowledge of produce codes.
You make it fun.
Uh, I'll tell you this, nine, four, one, one, I'll tell you this, uh, it's, it's, it's,
it's a, it's, look, it's going back to my hatred of Los Angeles.
Customers service is not great everywhere, but it is particularly bad here.
It's bad.
I'll grant you.
Everybody's mad that they're not, you know, I thought I was going to be the next faunsy.
Yeah.
Now I'm working at the, the, the fruit stand.
It's like, yeah, you weren't that good.
I'm sorry.
Right.
Or, or, or just didn't work out.
Leave this awful place.
Yeah.
Don't wait for the opportunities to pop up till you're 68.
Leave.
Go live a life.
Are you this vain?
It's this important to you.
Agreed.
Um, but yeah, that, that should happen to me, but the other day when we went in and we,
we were doing trades and, uh, you know, look, out of all the, out of all the businesses
in Los Angeles, I have, by hands down, spent the most amount of money at amoeba records.
Same here.
I have spent, uh, easily upwards of $10 ,000 in that store, which is a lot to spend in
a retail store.
And that's just on anime pornography, folks.
And that was just in the bathroom, uh, you know, over six years time, that's a lot of
fucking money to spend in a place that, where the average product costs 10 to 22 dollars.
Right.
Uh, you know, I have spent a shit load of money in that store and I've, and I've traded
it a lot of stuff and, you know, blah, blah, blah, uh, quite frankly out of loyalty to
the store, you know, like there, you know, if I, if I really wanted to take my time and drive
down to the valley or whatever, I could probably find some places where I could get a little more
bang for my buck when I'm doing a trade, but I like amoeba.
It served me well.
It's, it's, I'm a very loyal customer, uh, so I'll take the hit sometimes on the trade
and values, whatever.
But the people at this trade and desk get amoeba records for Christ's sakes, guys.
One guy is great.
Everybody else is not.
And there's a woman who's great too.
Yeah.
There's a woman who is so nice.
I can't remember.
I don't know anybody's name in there.
Maybe that's the problem.
Maybe I need to be asking people's names.
But, uh, I mean, we go in the other day, Pat and I with these trades, the one guy literally
looks at me and shakes his head like, oh, Christ, and it's like, are you kidding me right
now?
Did you just do that?
Are you kidding me right now?
Yeah.
Uh, and then the guy I get is like, yeah, next I go up and I go, how are you doing today?
And he goes, what do we got?
I go, uh, yeah, they don't, they don't do any pleasantries.
That's not something that can happen there.
Yeah.
It's like literally like when Darth Vader shows up at the half -constructed Death Star return
of the Jedi.
Like all angry.
You know, I'm like, and I go, I got some DVDs, some tapes, some CDs, some records, some
video games.
You know, what everybody brings here all day at your job.
And he goes, I'm going to tell you right now, it's probably going to mostly have to be trade
credit.
It's like, yeah, I'm not a fucking crackhead.
I'm not coming in here to get money.
Who is coming in and selling the stuff for the actual cash?
Right.
And not just going, if I wanted to sell the stuff for money, I'd go to a fucking pawn shop
or something.
I also love, I'm going to tell you right now, it's like that already sets things into such
an antagonistic vibe.
It doesn't need to be there.
The two things you do are sell DVDs and buy DVDs.
Man, I was hot, dude.
We walked out of there.
Remember, we were going over that coffee place.
I was fucking screaming.
I got a $6 coffee.
In the street, I think that lady in front of us thought I was talking about like my wife.
It's not like I was going to like murder my wife.
No, it was so bad.
I was like, that's fucking ass.
Oh, bitch.
It was rough.
Uh, but yeah, now the, uh, Jesus Christ, man, it's like, dude, I'm sorry your band didn't
make it.
Yeah.
What do you want from me, man?
It's not my fault.
You work here.
Yeah.
And you know what?
You do.
It's a pretty sweet fucking job as far as I can tell.
Absolutely.
Fantastic.
I think I would love working.
In terms of retail, you listen to great music all day, whatever you want to listen to.
You're hanging out with people like minded people with similar interests.
And by the way, let me swing it into the compliment direction because that's the thing I'm trying
to do now.
I'm trying to stay positive stuff too, Pat.
It does help me with my overall perspective each day.
Is that coming from this book on your, your table, the four agreements?
Four agreements is a wonderful book.
Somebody told me I have to read it and sitting on my shelf for upwards of 10 years.
You can read it in literally 22 minutes.
It looks like you could read it on the toilet and I've never read it.
Yeah.
Even though many people have told me it will change my life, but to be honest, it reads like
it was written on the toilet, but it will change your life.
It's so simple.
All right.
The first agreement is being peckable with your word.
Okay.
When you, when you, when you'd say negative stuff to people about people, you're spreading
poisonous energy.
It's not healthy.
It's sure.
So anyway, you know, to speak generally about amoeba records does, I don't think counts.
Maybe it does, but, but so I want to say a positive thing now, and this is what I love
about amoeba.
I go upstairs with my credits lit.
Yeah.
I got a cool 250 bucks credit.
I go upstairs to the DVD and Blu -ray section because I want to buy some, some, you know, special
edition things and whatever, that I didn't want to spend money on before.
Night and day.
I'm up there.
I go up to the one of the guys I go, hey man, I'm looking for a movie called Target starring
Boris Carlaw.
He goes, oh yeah.
Bogged out of it.
Yeah.
Bogged out of it just first.
And I go, yeah, I think so, right?
And he goes, yeah, you know, I'm always on the lookout for that.
That's a tough one.
All right.
Hold on.
Let's, let's go look around.
Uh huh.
Takes me to four different sections.
He's underneath.
He's like, we don't have it.
It's tough.
I go, I'm looking for this edition of Metropolis.
Uh huh.
He's like, he's like, there's a new one and I go, yeah, there's one called the complete
and he goes, oh yeah.
It just came out and I go, yeah, and he goes, I go, it's got like 25 minutes of extra footage
and he goes, he goes, they just keep finding more Metropolis.
And I was like, yeah, I guess so.
Yeah.
And he's like, all right.
Let's check silent.
And let's check directors.
Then let's check Colt.
Then let's check.
I was fucking incredible.
I've never had an issue with the sales people, the checkout people.
It's those desk return desk.
It's the only, it's only them.
There they are.
The people who are lovely, there's always that man and woman that waited that, that work,
their whole job in there is to work that like, can you look this up for me, desk?
Right.
Downstairs.
Every time.
All smiles.
Yeah.
They're telling you if it's even in print anymore.
My cash here the other day, I'm buying the 2k transfer to the thing.
He's telling me.
Crazy fucking stories about inside of the story, wouldn't that be of interest on a horror
podcast?
I almost don't want to spread the story because Carpenter was so mad at the cinematographer
for spreading it.
Okay.
That I did.
You know what guys?
Well, we're going to do an episode about the thing from another world because we saw that
along with House on Haunted Hill.
So in that episode, I'll talk about it.
I better watch it again while awake.
We're going to do it as an episode.
But we're going to talk about those seeing those marathon movies is one of the things.
So on that episode, I'm going to talk about the 2k transfer of the thing.
And then I'll tell that story and then I'm also going to talk about rewatching the prequel
the thing recently.
Yeah.
I why I went through all of them and not a minute was lost or wasted, I should say.
So, but anyway, the rest of the experience was wonderful.
But those trade in it's like member and Jackie Brownie goes, he goes, I don't know, I don't
know what they deal with with that, something about that job just makes them fucking miserable
down there.
What are you talking about the customs people?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Speaking of Mr. Quentin Tarantino today's film is once upon a time dot, dot, dot for some
reason in Hollywood.
I think that's him saying there have been a lot of once upon a time, sure movies, this is
one of those.
We will be discussing it everywhere I go people are talking about it.
I'm back doing the personal training.
My trainer was like, anybody see this movie, all four people in there working out said, yes,
we all had a great conversation about it.
It's a good conversation movie and we need more of those.
But first, let me take you down because I'm going to Pat's movie corner.
And folks, I have watched a whole lot of movies.
I have been trying to challenge myself to enjoy the time off and relax and not be antsy and
panicked as I always am whenever I get two days off of work.
And I have really been doing it.
I've been watching a ton of movies.
I'm on the letter box app.
If you want to follow in real time, I review the movies as I watch them and I think letter
box is a really fun way to connect with people.
It's what social media used to be.
You sort of see what your friends are watching.
You comment, you write a little review if you want and not enough people do it.
I think it's really fun.
Any whoot here is what I, Pat Walsh, have seen.
I'm going to start with, do you think there's any chance we do killing of a sacred deer on
here?
We could, because there's a couple that I've seen and a couple that you've seen that
the other hasn't seen that we said we would do.
Sure.
So if you watch Breitburn and the Clint's, I will watch killing of a sacred deer.
All right.
And we can do it.
Well, here's what I will start.
You know what I'm going to start with?
Corke or Romano.
All right.
Folks, I listened to, I can't get enough, especially on audio books, of a celebrity, whether
I care about them or not, reading their life story.
And for some reason, I was fascinated to hear Chris Catan's autobiography entitled Baby
Don't Hurt Me, the story of Chris Catan.
That's a great title.
It's a shame.
It is.
Chris Catan.
I have never seen a man play such a victim in all my life.
Oh, that's right.
It's the song.
Baby, we don't know.
That's right.
He, it's so fascinating.
It's not a good book by any means, but he is describing these situations where he is
clearly at fault and painting them as if he is the world's greatest victim.
He'll do things like say every time I'd appear in TMZ, they would accuse me of being a drug
addict.
I, little did they know I was just in pain.
I had broken my neck, blah, blah, blah.
And then one paragraph later, he's doing cocaine.
It's like he doesn't have the awareness to even make that connection that like you were
on drugs, though, Chris Catan.
Yeah.
It's like maybe have the, have the insight to go, now look, I dabbled like anybody did.
Of course.
Say something.
He talks about with, and it's the same, you know, like Moby was to like talk about how
he dated Natalie Portman and then she was like, what?
Hey, I was a child.
You were a creep and fuck you hold on that home, she wasn't a child.
She was a legal age, she was a legal age, but it's, it sounded like they had very different
opinions.
Don't get me wrong.
Anybody smashing Boby, I'm on board.
I fucking, I didn't realize I'm podcasting with Alan Dershowitz, but yeah, he talks about
how he dated Zoe Deschanel when he was in his mid 30s and she was 19.
Why Zoe Deschanel is dating Chris Catan?
I don't know.
Then he talks about how Will Ferrell, who, who might have met and is nicer than you might
even expect he would be, the sweetest man in Hollywood.
And at some point, he told Catan, look man, we've been friends a long time.
I can't do it with you anymore.
And Catan tries to paint Ferrell as the asshole, but you're like, if Will Ferrell is cutting
off your friendship, you're to blame Chris.
And that's what makes the book fascinating to me.
It's not well written.
He tells stories about his childhood as if you care.
He talks about like a Mr. Peeper's sketch.
You get behind the scenes of every mango sketch, every Mr. Peeper's sketch as if they are
Shakespearean texts, but any who.
My favorite section of the book was talking about the film Corky Romano, which I had never
seen.
He claims that the film was co -written by him, Richard Lagrovinez, who wrote Bridges of
Madison County and many other great films, and Paul Thomas Anderson.
Now none of those three men are credited on the screenplay, but he claims that those three
rewrote it and made it what it was.
Then he claims that they shot the movie, hold on, what was it?
When it made it, no, no, no, made it what it was.
Nobody remembers this fucking movie, but no, so he's claiming the script was amazing.
Him, Paul Thomas Anderson, and Richard Lagrovinez, they do the film, they shoot it in its entirety.
Everyone who sees it thinks it's a new comedy classic and loves it.
Sure.
Then a Disney executive comes in to watch a cut.
He accuses a Disney executive of being drunk, coming from lunch, even though he has nothing
to back that up.
He falls asleep during the screening of the movie and everyone starts to panic.
If the executive doesn't like it, we should reshoot it.
Then he claims that while they were shooting the end of the movie, they also were reshooting
every scene that had already been shot and telling Catan to mug shamelessly and to smile
big in every scene as if Catan is a subtle performer.
Like you know me, Chris Catan, I'm usually under playing things.
He claims they made him act as over the top as he did in the film and then the movie was
ruined.
But then still, after shooting on the movie, he claims that it came out and the only reason
nobody saw it is because 9 -11 was going on and everyone was scared to leave their homes.
These are the amount of times he doubles down on this thing.
So then he says, now the movie made $25 million on a $5 million budget.
When Billy Madison did that, they claimed it was a smash hit.
When I did it, they claimed it was a bomb.
It's like, dude, go to therapy.
Go to therapy.
This movie came out 25 years ago.
Anywho I said, look, I got to see if Paul Thomas Anderson's got his fingers on this movie.
Am I going to recognize his work?
Korki Romano is not good.
As you can imagine, no.
Everybody remembers that scene of Chris Catan and a girl scout uniform going, would you
like some cookies?
That was the trailer.
My friends used to do it all the time.
I don't remember that, but sure.
There is one genuinely laugh out loud scene where Catan has a bunch of cocaine thrown into
his face and he goes to talk to a group of people and he's coked out and it is really, really
great.
It functions as like a sketch basically.
There's a little bit of physical comedy here and there that's all right and then the villains
of his family and the piece, the mob guys, are played by Peter Fock, Peter Berg and Chris
Penn.
So there's some comedy there of them being like, God, this fucking loser.
It's not a wash out, but I can't recommend the film as you might understand.
Sure.
I understand.
I can recommend Baby Don't Hurt Me if you just want to watch a man just really kind of
lose his mind on record.
All right.
We got the rave going on downstairs again.
Yeah, I know.
I know.
You had another reason why I'm not thrilled living here, but what are you going to do?
Have you seen anything or you want me to go?
Well, we're running a little long here.
We're at 36 minutes so you can cover movie corner today because I don't have a ton.
All right.
And I'll save mine.
I highly recommend Blind Spotting.
It is a film starring the dude from Hamilton.
So I was not particularly psyched because I didn't love Hamilton, but David Diggs and this guy
Raphael Cassal, their friends, they wrote it together.
It's set in Oakland where I am going this weekend.
What are you going to Oakland for again?
My buddies do this baseball trip every year.
They go to a different baseball stadium, multiple school friends.
It's always a good time.
It is a movie.
There is a choice late in the film that I think is going to rub people the wrong way.
I went with it.
It is basically a comedy set in Oakland with some really serious undertones about racism,
about gentrification, about how the city has changed, etc.
It's comparable and I mean this as a very positive comparison to the film Friday.
The two leads are clearly best friends in real life too.
They have an amazing chemistry.
I couldn't recommend it more highly.
I was blown away by it.
I absolutely loved it.
Check it out.
Okay.
And I saw, well yesterday I watched another 48 hours.
Terrible.
I've never even seen another 40.
Nolty and Murphy.
Murphy three times does the joke.
It was in the trailer, but he does it three different times in the movie.
I've had a bad day.
I was on a bus that flipped over.
I got shot in the leg.
You know, in every 80s movie they list what they've been through.
They do it three times.
They both look tired.
Nolty looks like he just woke up.
Can't recommend it at all.
All right.
All right, great.
Is that what you need?
That's good for me.
Okay.
Is that good for you?
It's good for me.
I can do a scary stuff.
Please do.
By the way, the original 48 hours.
Fantastic.
I'm knee deep in the audible books right now.
Sure.
Maybe don't hurt me?
No.
I'll recommend one that will suit sort of the theme of this podcast a bit.
It's so loud.
Yeah.
This is louder than it used to be.
No, it's not.
This is always how it is.
And no matter how many times I say to him, it's too loud.
He does it again the next day.
It's moving the floor.
Yeah.
All right.
Life is horrible.
It's fucking ridiculous.
Uh -huh.
I literally stood downstairs once in the vestibule and recorded on my phone.
Just like did a video recording.
And you could hear it on the phone audio.
I mean, it's fucking absurd.
Yeah.
It's fucking absurd.
And then also too, his girlfriend who doesn't live here is just now permanently parked in
our back.
We have this tiny back lot where everybody gets one space.
He's now allowed his girlfriend to permanently park in the ex the excess space of his space.
I love that.
So now like getting into my space is extremely tight and you know, because her car is just
always there.
And she has said to me before, I don't know how to drive so I don't park well over here.
So it's just like, okay.
So it's just another obstacle to fucking deal with.
And then the other day I hit my landlord's car pulling in like I wasn't hard.
I scrape it.
You tell them?
Yeah.
I go over.
It's my landlord's roommate.
I go over and I'm like, hey man, I'm sorry, like I scraped your, but I get the landlord.
I say to her, I go, I'm really sorry, I scraped your roommate's car.
I mean, it's not terrible damage, but it's just that parking lot is so tight.
Like I thought I had more space to get in.
I didn't.
And she's like, oh, is so -and -so's car here?
And I go, you mean are not the downstairs neighbor or the other neighbor?
You mean the, her over there?
Yeah.
You know what she doesn't say is so -and -so's girlfriends?
It's like, why are you asking me if a residence car is here?
Uh -huh.
Why are you just letting a stranger have her car here 24 hours a day?
Right.
Meanwhile, when I go away and I have a dog sitter in here, she's like, dog sitter can't be
parked there during the day.
It's too many cars.
It's like, oh, I'm sorry, so I guess it's just, I can't wait to get out of this fucking
place.
Anyway, it's literally more peaceful living with two other people in New York.
All right.
I'm not, that's not me overselling.
I'm just saying like, I hear less shit.
Sure.
Anyway.
Okay.
Sorry.
Scary stuff.
And there goes the techno music again on cue.
It's not even like current techno music.
No, like, it's trash fucking idiot fucking dumb.
It's like, it's like, its like, C .C. peniston, like in late 90 or early 90s house music that
like -
Sorority garbage would listen to and that would be dancing too.
Yeah, exactly.
You exactly coked out trash like Chris get tan. Yeah would dance to this music. Uh, anyway.
Audible book I can't recommend highly enough. I've been listening to it every night to go to sleep.
And it's not even Christmas time. But Audible has, and I believe it's an Audible exclusive,
they have Tim Curry reading a Christmas carol. Oh nice.
Full, he's the full book. It's not, you know, sometimes they have like a cast of people. He does
the entire thing. It's fucking incredible voices of everybody. Yeah, he's doing all the characters.
It's Tim Curry. It is absolute best. Uh, and as I said, I've been, I've been going to sleep to
it every night. It's not even Christmas time. But I'm a big, big fan of the of a Christmas carol.
As a story as a book, particularly though, as an audible, an audio book. I really, really enjoy
listening to audio versions of that book. Yeah. Um, it's, and I don't mean audio plays of it.
I mean, like somebody actually reading the book is quite enjoyable because the, the, the, you know,
the pros of Dickens and the, the wit and everything and the narration is very funny and it's just a very
enjoyable listen. And the Tim Curry, you can't beat it. I mean, it's, it's awesome. It's well worth
the credit on audible. I love almost every version of it. Yeah. Scrooge. I love, uh, you know,
Muppets. I love married with children's version. I love it all. Now we're children didn't do a
version. They did it. It's a wonderful life. No, that's right. But that's okay. You know what I mean?
I know every TV show at some point has done something along the lines of a Christmas. You love every
TV show ever is what you're getting here. I love the, I love a Christmas episode of a show. Yeah,
me too. Uh, let's move to our picture of the week. Certainly the talk of the town. I guess
that's because we live in Hollywood. But uh, once upon a time in Hollywood, the new picture, the
ninth picture from Quentin Tarantino, will this be his last? He's supposed to do one more. Will
that be Star Trek? I can't believe the man would go out on something he didn't write. But I'm curious
to see. I also think he'll keep making movies. The young man. But I assume you're not being on
Twitter. You've not seen the amount of, uh, let's cancel Tarantino articles that are coming out
because of the Sharon Tate subject matter. Sharon Tate treating the death of Brad Pitt's wife as a
joke in the movie, which got a massive laugh when I saw it. Yeah, it was hilarious. Uh, but like,
oh, is that funny to you? Then I love that everyone accuses him of being some sicko because he likes
women's feet. So he puts a hundred close -ups of women's feet in this movie, including like pressed
up against glass at one point. So I think there's some element of fuck you to this movie of like,
yeah, I like women's feet. Sorry. In this world, that's all you can, you know, well, look, for a man,
for a director as deliberate as Quentin Tarantino is. Yeah. For you to hone on, hone in on the feet
as if it's the only thing he is overly exploring in this movie. Right. The minutia is so delved into,
you know, at one point I'm watching this thing, you know, I love the movie overall. Just spoiler alert.
Oh, we should give probably a little bit of a synopsis, too, but go ahead. But, but, you know,
so the movie is about two, well, I'll, we'll do, let me say this and then I'll do some. There's,
there were points in this movie where they're going into aspects of DiCaprio's career like flashbacks
and I was going, why are they showing this right now? This is, I don't need to know this. Yeah.
So the point is, is the guy gets into detail so minutely. I wouldn't be surprised if there were some
weird, see the feet symbolize this and, you know, whatever the fuck kind of thing. I don't know.
Maybe there is, maybe there isn't. As far as the Brad Pitt's wife thing goes and there's going to be a
lot of spoilers in this review. Halfway through this theater. Halfway through this picture, I was,
I was like, wow, he's really not painting except for Sharon Tate, the female characters in a great
light in this movie. They're, they're not that likable. But he painted the, the, the ones that
needed to be likable, likable, meaning, Sharon Tate, the little girl who co -stars with DiCaprio's
life for you. Kurt Russell's the stunt woman wife is great. Very funny. You know, so that's all great.
And by the end of the movie, you realize, oh, he painted these other women in a, women in a poor light.
So when the climax, climax scene happens, you're not completely disturbed by what goes on.
So it all ends up making sense. But, well, and let's, let's discuss the ending separately. Yeah, so
synopsis of the film, synopsis of the film. I mean, look, everyone agrees that you could take
minimum a half hour out of this movie. And yet, I, I never felt bored. I never wanted stuff out of it.
There is at least a half hour that just shows Margot Robbie as Sharon Tate walking through Westwood
watching her movie. When they cut back to her watching her acting in a movie, the second time,
I was like, Quentin, come on, buddy. Like, that was a little much. But basically, the movie is this.
Leonardo DiCaprio was a sort of star on the rise. Now his star is on the fall. He was supposed to be
another Steve McQueen. Right. He missed it. Like a lot of actors. He never quite got his big break.
Now he works. So the film opens with him working the trade in desk at Amoeba.
Now, he is a, he is a drunk. He is sort of circling the drain of Hollywood. Al Pacino is a big time
producer who wants him to start doing spaghetti westerns. He feels that sort of selling out, but
eventually agrees to do it. Brad Pitt is his long time stand in slash best friend.
Stunt man. I'm sorry. Stunt. Well, same thing. Well, no, because the stunt man plays a key.
Yes, that plays a key role in all this. Ultimately, I think he is his stunt man slash best friend slash
essentially. I was a little confusing to me. He lives elsewhere, but also seems to kind of live with
Brad Pitt. Like when he's walking his dog at the Capriose House, I was like, what's going on?
He's, yeah, he's, he's, he's stunt man that the Capro keeps on as basically an assistant during
the downtime and his career. And I think that's pretty much based on Bert Reynolds had how
need him live with him forever. And then eventually would do movies to him as favors. Yeah. But
and Bert Reynolds, fun fact, was supposed to play the Kurt Russell part, but sadly passed away.
Right. That's what I heard. Another fun fact I learned Margaret Qualie who plays the pussy cat
character is the daughter of Andy McDowell. Who's the pussy? Oh, the one that gets the that hitches
the ride with the one who, yeah, is clearly very into Brad Pitt, asked to suck his dick. The,
I mean, the, the issue, Tarantino, I was surprised in that scene that Pitt says, no, because I thought
back then it was kind of like an anything goes. I thought back then you could get a blow job.
Like it didn't like people weren't, he probably would have been fine. You read these stories about
like these guys fucking 15 year olds and shit back then. Nobody seems to care. They do though,
because one of them is Roman Polanski who's featured in the movie and is now not allowed in America.
Yeah. Yeah. But I mean, you read like Mick Jagger fucking Mackenzie Phil's when she's 16. Sure.
That girl is clearly 17 or 18 in that movie. Yes. And in real life, I think 24 or something.
So I was surprised when when not, not saying he should have done it. I was just surprised that
they went that route with him being like, no, I'm good. You're too young. An interesting choice in
this day and age two, for example, to set the camera up basically inside her butthole for that scene
where she is leaning into Brad Pitt's car to proposition him. The camera for five minutes is like
looking into her ass. Well, but I'll tell you, listen, people can and people will complain, complain
about that all you want. That is the brilliance of a good director. He shows you the temptation of it.
Yeah. This girl is fucking beautiful. She's got her ass hanging out of her cut -offs.
She gets into the car. She's clearly into Brad Pitt. She offers the suck as Dick no strings attached
and then what a fucking great moment for that character when he goes, miss, I'm going to need to see
some ID. That's the first time you go, oh shit. I think this guy's actually like a good dude.
Yeah, aside from killing his wife. But even that, like when she's like, and even with the killing
his wife thing, they insinuate that it very much could have been an accident. It's very much a play on the
Robert Christopher Walker, which is face thing. So it's a very funny scene and also with all these
you know, uproar articles about it. Treating a woman's death as a joke. It's like
it's a character flaw. People are allowed to have flaws. They're fucking characters.
Also, the end of the movie. That's a big flaw, of course, but what are you talking about?
I think the end of the movie insinuates that he did not murder his wife, that it was an accident.
Because the end of the movie, when the big showdown happens, he is very, very cool even with a head
full of acid until somebody attacks him. And then it is just like, you know, he gets very
Bruce Lee in that moment. You know what I mean? Right. Well, that's the other issue. The only person
of color in the movie, Bruce Lee, I'm just addressing the controversy's first. And I think we should
treat the ending as basically a separate movie, which it is. But Bruce Lee, the only person
of color in the movie, an icon of Asian cinema being treated as a joke to make our white hero look
better and stronger. I would say did that scene even happen? It seems like it might be a fantasy
in his mind. I think it's all fantasy. I literally think that scene was just, I think that scene was
Tarantino going, who was the baddest dude on earth in Hollywood back then? Bruce Lee. You know Tarantino
fucking loves Bruce Lee. Yeah. He's not mocking him. How do we prove that Brad Pitt is the baddest
dude on earth in this final scene? Oh, we'll have him beat up Bruce Lee. Right. It's people,
it's not to all be taken so fucking seriously. Like it's just come on, man. Like it's how I took it
is that he didn't get the job. And he's imagining while he's doing like fixing the Capra's antenna,
what might have happened. I don't think he actually beat the shit out of Bruce Lee. No, I think he
does because when it cuts back to him, he goes, he goes, so it's a scene where Kurt Russell says,
I can't work with Brad Pitt anymore. Yes. This guy's a problem. I can't work with him.
And then Brad Pitt thinks back to why he can't work with him. He thinks he reminisces about the
last time he worked with Kurt Russell's character. Oh, so that was a different occasion. Yeah. Yeah.
All right. I miss him. And then he beats up Bruce Lee on set. He gets fired. What the fuck is wrong
with you? Throws him into her car. Yeah. It's funny. Dense the head stunt woman's car.
Right. She's like, get out of here. You're we hate you. Whatever. Then it cuts back to Brad Pitt.
As you see, he's reminiscing about this. And he goes, fair enough.
Again, that's correct. Yes. Another great little peak into why this guy is a good dude.
Like he can admit when he's wrong. He's like, I fucked up. I didn't deserve that job.
When Brad Pitt took his shirt off, there were audible gasps in the theater that I did not appreciate.
The man, it's I felt uncomfortable with how attracted I felt to him. I feel the same way. And he's
like 55. Brad Pitt, this is my favorite. I have ever seen him ever in a movie ever.
And that beats burn after reading, which is saying a lot because God damn, do I love him and burn after reading.
He, he'd never make my top hundred actors, Brad Pitt. I've always thought he was good.
I liked him in a lot of things. Moneyball seven, fight club, etc. But this is the first time where I was like,
damn, like the it was as if it was written for him. I love to caprio just as much.
But we've seen the caprio, you know, excel in a lot of different kinds of roles.
The scene where the caprio is beating himself up for missing the line, that really hit home for
me. I was like, that is how badly I treat myself. Masterful. He's talking in the mirror out of that.
He was incredible. Talking in the mirror, you're done. And it's, and it's such a minor thing.
He's killing the scene. He's just doing great. And then he drops like one line. Yeah. And then you
see the testament to what a brilliant actor Caprio is. He drops the one line. And then for the rest
of the scene, his acting is all thrown on. Right. He's all like wide eyed and like, yeah.
He's so good. But yeah, when he goes in the trailer and he's reflecting and he's yelling in the mirror,
you had to drink eight whiskers hours because you're fucking drunk. You put that four.
He's like, you're done drinking. You're done drinking. Then it has a drink.
He was just awesome in it. And you know, he's, he's one of the greats. And then when he goes back
after a lunch in that scene, we'll have to do the rest of the scene. And he screams in the mirror,
you better get your shit together into himself into the mirror. You better get your shit together,
man, the mirror where I'm going to paint the fucking patio with your brains tonight. Yes.
Threatens himself goes in. They do the second half of the scene. And it is some of the best acting
I've ever seen to Caprio do. And it's to Caprio as Rick Dalton as this character. Right.
It's interesting because he is so like if somebody were that good in this Western TV show,
it would be jarring and throw off the whole tone of it. And that's kind of what he's doing.
It's he's talking about how like when Bruce Dern who's in the movie or Christopher Walken would be in
gun smoke and you'd be like, holy shit, like who is this guy? And that was a cool touch.
So however, you watch the 30 minute scene take place in a two and a half hour movie and it's kind of
like, why am I watching this? But it's fascinating in a way. Like so when people say it's too long sure,
there's nothing I would have wanted edited out really. I think this film was very clearly an homage
to Tarantino's love of a specific era of Hollywood. For sure. And the unsung heroes of Hollywood.
I felt like him showing you these 30 -minute stretches of decaprio acting was his way of saying,
just like with Travolta, I was right. There were people that were really overlooked,
that were really good, that deserved better. I mean, you watch Clugman in the old Twilight Zones.
And not the Clugman's career is anything to shake a stick at. But you watch this guy and you go,
the most he got was the odd couple. Are you fucking kidding me? This guy is blowing the fucking
roof off of these things. Look, how did he not star in movies? So it's a very interesting
homage to clearly his love of a certain period of Hollywood. I don't hate the guy
for basically writing that love letter to who his favorite characters were from that period.
Which were these old sort of western actor, shit kicker type guys, these drinking men's men.
That's okay. You're still out to like that stuff. Not everything has to be in recognition of
everything else that we're discussing right now. You're allowed to like something. So I don't have a
problem with that. I think we're also really a piss because Uma Thurman said that he choked her,
Diane Krueger said that he choked her in glorious bastards. In both cases, the women were like, yeah,
that would help me get into the scene better and it was approved by them. And at the same time,
Uma Thurman's daughter is in once upon a time in Hollywood, the same girl from Stranger Things. So clearly,
Uma Thurman feels that it's a safe set. Right. If her daughter is there, people sometimes are
getting outraged when even the people involved aren't outraged. I know. It's matter with you. It's
crazy. Do you have this daughter? Also, Harley Quinn Smith popping up as one of the Manson girls.
Really? I enjoyed seeing her in there. And also this criticism of Margot Roby and the use of
Margot Roby. He wrote a story that involved Sharon Tate as a character. And Quentin Tarantino is
such a hot director. He can get an A -list actor like Margot Roby to play the small role. There's a
fucking difference. Stop making it sound like because you're just supposed to add, you write the
story first, you write the script first. You don't add things because of who's playing the part.
By the way, Margot Roby is thrilled with the film. Let her enjoy this. If it wasn't Margot Roby,
or somebody that just fucking glowing and delightful, you don't fall in love with Sharon Tate.
You don't feel for her. You don't care as much. Margot Roby was great. It didn't ask a lot of her
perhaps, but it's not nothing to fall in love with somebody who has no dialogue in a movie.
That's awesome. It's also for somebody to walk around with almost no dialogue and exude
that much charisma. It's what Sharon Tate was. Sharon Tate was a model that turned into an actor.
She was somebody that just had charisma wafting off of her and people were in love with her from a
distance. Margot Roby somehow magically captures that. I don't know how you fucking put me in that
role. You'd be like, why is this guy just walking around? I'm going to kill this guy.
Also, people with just as big a role in the story, Roman Polanski and the other guy who she was
married to have way less to do than Margot Roby. Roman Polanski doesn't even have a line right
for sure, the pedophile fuck. Now, Emil Hirsch, a lot of people had issues with his casting because
three years ago, he choked out a female publicist at the Sundance Film Festival in front of a lot of
people. He did? Choked her and dragged her across the floor. Over what? He was super drunk.
Okay. And he thought she said something about him or something, but oh jeez. So people were certainly
like, why is he, like, you know, Heather was like, where's he been? And I told her that story. She was
like, oh, well, then I didn't know about that. Yeah, I mean, to hear Terence, you know, kind of,
yeah, kind of cast some people with that people have issues with and blah, blah, blah. If you ignore
if it was some up -and -comer with this script, would this movie ever get made? No, I don't think so either.
No, this movie, and it would have also gotten panned. I mean, there is something about having a
biological knowledge of Quentin Tarantino that lets you appreciate what's going on in this film.
Right. It does fit into the lexicon of his movies. Had this been his first movie out, you'd be like,
what is this guy doing? Yeah. You know, but, but so there is something to all that. Also,
there's undoubtedly elements of fuck you, Hollywood, in this picture, for sure. When DiCaprio was saying,
you know, I'm kind of, you know, a man just gets more and more worthless every day or whatever,
you can't help but sort of feel Terence, you know, talking about himself. He was the talk of the town
and now he's - Yeah, there's there's some of that. There's, I mean, look, he's definitely a
fuck you. But look, here's the thing, and this is what drives me nuts about the criticism. The people
screaming at Tarantino right now and saying he's an asshole are the same people that were applauding
him when he took the stance during the Django on chain promotion against or was it the hatefully
promotion against the cops? Right. He took the fucking stand against the cops at that rally and got
tons of shit from cops. Tons, cops were going to boycott him and everything. Everybody applauded
his bravery. Now he gives a little criticism in another direction or whatever or a little
flippancy in another direction and it's, well, fuck you, you're no good, you canceled. And it's like,
I just don't get it, man. I don't get it. Like, that's where we're at. That's where we're at.
Anyway, the movie itself, in the end, really a sweet story about a friendship between two guys,
the pit and the Caprio thing. I thought was really sweet. Also a love letter to Sharon Tate
ultimately that she lives at the end in this revisionist thing. It's wonderful that you don't see the
title of this movie till the end of it. When Sharon Tate is alive, where things look up for Rick
Dalton, they all go in to have a drink and then it finally says once upon a time in Hollywood,
when you go, oh, this literally is a fairy tale. It was interesting that he doesn't go in and
check on his wife who has just been through this incredibly traumatic thing. He just goes next
door to have a drink with Sharon Tate. You feel like that marriage probably isn't going to go
the distance. No. Well, I think I felt like that was, I felt like the purpose of that was so that you
would feel like he and pit aren't done here. Yes, for sure. Like when he said, because he says to pit,
I'm going to have to let you go. I can't keep you on with my what being married now. And when he tries
to go to the hospital with pit over going to stay with his wife, I felt like that was the way of saying
these guys are going to be together for a long time. For sure. And then he doesn't go check on his wife,
which I thought was kind of funny too. But the ending of this movie is, you know, open to a lot
of discussion, of course, but basically people were complaining that they didn't know about Sharon Tate
and Polansky, and then they couldn't enjoy the movie. They're like, we didn't know what was happening.
Kids for the most part. But it's like, if you don't know about one of the most notorious crimes
of the last century, then it's your own fault. But basically, what this is is a, in a way that's
pretty similar, I think, to and glorious bastards, a revisionist history of a super notorious
event. I mean, in that case, it was the killing of Hitler and a bunch of Nazis. In this case,
you know, Charles Manson's cronies basically killed Sharon Tate, who was Roman Plansky's very pregnant
wife. It sent him on this downward spiral. In this movie, they go next door by mistake.
And they attempt to kill DeCaprio and Brad Pitt, but they fight back in a very shocking and
completely unexpected way spoilers to come. But my God, the last half hour of the movie is some of
the best shit Tarantino's ever done in my opinion. And Brad Pitt, I mean, when he is bashing that woman's
face into every surface of the house while high on acid. I mean, I was laughing, but just also
kind of blown away by it. And it's Tarantino. He does violence. Great. But it was so violent.
And then when Tarantino comes out, I mean, sorry, when DeCaprio comes out with that flamethrower,
the place just exploded. It's, it was me too. At midnight showing, it's now 245 in the
morning, the place is cheering. I, what's so brilliant about this scene is, so it's a set the
stage. The Manson trio come in. It's, it's one of the male henchmen and two of the female henchmen.
And whom a thermos daughter who abandons them, because she has second thoughts. Yeah, they come
into, also, and stranger things, but to murder them, Brad Pitt is not in that, or is just getting
back to the house when it happens after having smoked an LSD cigarette, right? After walking his
dog, he's tripping. He does a great job of capturing what it's like when you're tripping.
An awesome job. Uh, he's not easy to do. The people come into the house with a gun. They're
going to kill him. Uh, and DeCaprio's wife is in there as well. They're going to kill both of them.
DeCaprio are, uh, Pitt, the scene starts with Pitt saying, are you guys really here? Which is hilarious.
Right. He's tripping and then he realizes, oh, shit, this is really happening. Doesn't panic.
And then it all jumps off when he has a signal for his pit bull, like a, like whatever.
All the pit bull stuff was amazing. Yeah. And this pit bull attacks the guy, grab nuts first.
He's got the gun. And then Pitt is holding the can of dog food in the whole time.
You're just dying for him to hit somebody with the can of dog food. But when he does, it like
essentially takes the woman's face off and the place went nuts again. It was amazing. Uh,
and also right before this, I'm going to interject, you get a great quick scene of the Manson
kids in the car. And you see them for the hipster, self -absorbed pieces of shit that they were.
Yeah. Which I thought was great too. Everybody knows the Nazis are evil.
People just think of these guys as faceless murderers. But Tarantino takes the time
to give you a scene of them just being complete fucking losers before they are humiliated and annihilated
by Pitt and this stupid fucking movie that about to come out where it tries to show that the Manson
women were victims that murdered, you know, it's giving me a fucking break. Anyway.
So anyway, he attacks. Yeah. Meanwhile, the whole time de caprio is out in the pool in the
float, wishing to music doesn't know any of this is what you sort of forget about anyway. So
now what is so one of the things that is so brilliant about this scene is this whole movie that
keeps slowly showing you that Brad Pitt is a not somebody to be fucked with. Be capable of
killing in some way. Sure. And see a hero like a great dude. Right. And here it is his stuntman
who de caprio has just let go because he can't afford to keep money more literally being de caprio
stuntman in real life. Right. He's in the house with his wife doing all the bad shit that de caprio could
not do. Yeah. And it ends with the final living Manson person woman running out of the house screaming
because her face has been busted open from the dog screaming and firing gun into the air.
She jumps in the she bust through the window. De caprio in a great almost spit take.
Yeah. Holy fucking shit. Yeah. She jumps into the pool. De caprio jumps out of the pool runs into
the shed comes out with the flame thrower as you said. And here's why they show the moment of him
learning how to use the flame flora because this is the one stunt he's ever actually done in his career
is shoot this fucking flame thrower. Right. And he shoots it at her with all the fucking authority
and he knows how to use this thing. And when they set that up and here's a great tip if you are
an aspiring screenwriter it's something I try to do as well. If you're going to set something up
like that to not shine a light on it and make the audience go well obviously that's coming back later
make it a joke. So when de caprio is learning how to use the flamb thrower he's like could we maybe turn
the heat down on that yeah the guys like well no it's a flame throw gets a big laugh and it doesn't
make you think okay that's coming back later right so when he walks out with the flamb thrower a
of course you remember that funny joke earlier but you're not sitting there going all right here he comes
and because that was truly surprising and amazing and just the extent to which he blows this
woman away is amazing. Yeah. And then there's the great interaction with him and Emil Hirsch when he's
burnt with last one with a fucking flame throw yeah from 14 fists of whatever he's like yeah I
still got the goddamn thing and my shit still works yeah yeah you know fantastic movie eight two hugs
up from these guys absolutely I mean I'll be seeing it again I want to see it in 35 or 70 millimeter
I know there's a few screenings like that around town in LA maybe there's one near you but I think
everyone should just be happy any film fan should be happy we're getting movies like this
and I read a I wish I could I could give credit to the guy who said it but he was like you know people
have issues with Tarantino like showing pretty real aspects of his personality in this movie like
all the foot fetish stuff and etc and that's what people seem to be bothered by he's like what they
should be doing is being excited that a filmmaker is putting any personality into his movie and I
thought that was the greatest way to put it is like yeah this guy is making movies with flavor with
with a personality behind them that aren't assembled in a chop shop and I just thought it was fun as
shit you know if we're gonna talk about where does it rank in the terms of Tarantino I don't like how
that's always the first question you know oh I saw the new Tarantino where do you rank it amongst
you know pulp fiction well pulp fiction is one of the best movies ever made so why can't we just talk
about it but I think you're talking about a movie that's probably in the second half of his films if
we have to answer that question but it's one that I know for a fact will grow on me over time much
like a Jackie Brown where it's just something you can watch again and again and again I'm not sure
yeah I had to think about that but the more I think about it I think there's a chance it could
supersede Jackie Brown for me my top two are always gonna be fiction and dogs obviously I go
fiction but at this point I would put this probably above kill bill it's certainly a deeper movie
than either of those behind hateful eight but above maybe neck and neck with Django definitely
above glorious bastards I thought was a great movie but it's it's I'm not a big war movie guys so
it was one of my lesser favorites to watch I liked it more than hateful eight probably a little more
than Django but I got to reevaluate it's one I want to see again and again I liked it more than
the grindhouse segment oh yeah definitely it's it's it's an absolute blast it's the best movie that's
in theaters right now I would I would strongly recommend all right we'll be back next week with or next
time next time with another picture that's causing a lot of discussion mid -summer yes and let's
I'm gonna skip the Joe De Rosa comedy on Instagram that's all I got and I am the Patrick Walsh very
rarely on Twitter or Instagram but that's where I'm at now let's get on with the show and on with
a Joe we'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell