Summer is here and Bet MGM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer or check out
our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bet MGM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Waiter, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia only, games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal -durable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided in applicable terms.
Reward subject to expiry, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamber.
The football season is full of guarantees.
And here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning, or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
winning hits different here must be 21 plus gambling problem called winning
100 gambler offer not available in all states terms apply see
fanatic sportsbook app.
Hey everyone, welcome to the Will see you in a hell podcast.
Now a part of the Fangoria podcast network for more information about the network including other programs how to follow the show and find past episodes of we'll see you and help.
Please visit Fangoria .com. Now on with the show and on with the Joe.
You said that last time too, right? I think this is my third.
Oh, okay. It's our new opening, frankly.
I like that you're good. I got to think of something that rhymes with Pat. I received a single tweet where someone said they they really loved on with the Joe. So I'm doubling down. All right.
Triple and down.
Thrice. Thrice, you've said it apparently. How are you doing, Pat?
I'm doing good. I mean, good and bad. I'm waiting to hear on my my pilot, been working on it forever. It's been a
Maddening experience, but it is into the CBS network. We'll see where that goes. Right. I
Got it till you hear Joe. I'm not gonna say who said it. I'm not gonna throw anyone out of the bus
But this network note process everyone knows it's difficult. You've you've been around when I've been on some phone calls
Everyone has has their say and I had to go through a production company
then Warner Brothers, then CBS for every step.
So every step you're getting three sets of notes
from three different places.
Each place has three people representing them.
So it's about nine people.
And this is tough stuff because for those of you
that don't aren't familiar with the TV writing process,
one note from one person could mean rewriting the script
from page one, so you're getting that many notes
for that many people. God knows the chances of, I mean, it's just got to be an immense amount of
rewriting. Yeah, I mean, when the notes are like, hey, you know, I just had a thought like could
you maybe swap this or whatever? And then what they either don't realize or don't care is that when
you change that little thing that they think will take you five minutes, the entire script can fall
apart. Like because now you're later on you're referencing that moment. Right. And it's not there
anymore. And you have to be so vigilant about this and go through it again and again and again.
this is why it's almost never good when you're sitting in a movie and the
credits are rolling the opening credits are rolling and you see that it's been
written by four to six people yeah and then you you're sitting there going this
doesn't make sense and it's because right this is why right and I you know we're
working on this for a long time and I feel really good about it but it made it all
the way up the chain to the head of CBS he had a couple thoughts I'm sure he did
They're always going to have thoughts.
They're never going to say like we're making it.
But when he says I have a couple thoughts,
then now everyone is giving you notes
and it goes back to one again.
So you have to go to production company,
you go back and forth till they like it enough
to pass it on to the studio.
But then you got to give it to the production company first
before it goes to the studio.
Right.
So they give you, they're like maybe this, this, this.
When it finally gets up to the studio
or like finally I can relax,
then the studio has their thoughts.
Then before they'll pass it to CBS,
Yes, you got to send it back to the production company then the studio then the network again
It just keeps going and going and going and everyone has their thoughts and the thoughts conflict each other
Sometimes what one person will say? I hate this the other person will say what happened to that? That was my favorite thing and
I've really reached something of a breaking point and I'm going to tell you want just one note I got which I already told you Joseph
We'll tell our fine audience and folks I just want you to know in case you're
ever thinking about getting into television. This was a note that I received. So
imagine like you're sitting and you finish typing something and you're like
it's like personal and meaningful and funny and you're like yes send. Finally
thank God and then 45 minutes later there's an email in your inbox and it says
notes and they're just like hey this thing that you like read 80 times before
turning in to perfect it. And here's what we thought was wrong with it. And then you open the
document and they're just doing their job. I get it. But you open the document. The first note
I saw folks and I was like on no sleep and kind of in a terrible mood. I also have to work full
time in addition to doing this. Right. And I open it and the first note says, here you have Leslie
saying to chip, have a good day, but chips only going to the mall and to church. Have a
good day seems like something you would say only to somebody who was going to work.
Please consider rephrasing or cutting the line.
And I just picked up the phone and I was like,
guys, this is not going to, this is not going to work. This is not, this is not a note you
can send to me after we've been back and forth on this 500 times. Oh, you can't say I'm not
okay. I'm sorry. But I was just like, this is, this is, you know, completely unfair. This
is, this is not cool. What are you doing? And I say, you know, unless Heather, my girlfriend,
who I live with unless she's going out to like get the mail and she's wearing slippers right every
time she leaves the house I say buy I love you have a good day what these are the most normal
things in the world so to pick on that I mean some of these notes will be like you have them saying hi
could he say hello and I tell you yeah you lose your mind and you want to scream at them like
but did you did you like it did you know all the work I put into this is it funny right right
So now it's finally into the head of the head again and now I basically have, they're all kind of like it'll probably Monday before you hear.
So now I just am on the edge of my nerves and my sanity for the next four to five days, which could even go longer if they take longer to decide.
I have noticed, yeah, there's been, there's probably been about five different times you've said to me finally turned into the pilot.
Yeah, and each time was true.
Yeah, and then like it seemed like you were in it to celebrate and then like the next day you were like I can't do anything for the next five days because I got a
I got to rewrite all the stuff again, and it's it's not an easy task
I admire that you're that you have the wherewithal to do it. I couldn't do it. Yeah, I couldn't do it
I I went to Nordstrom Rack today
So
You know, I was I was talking to my my friend Morgan who you also know about this
She had a pilot in the mix as well. And she was like, look, it's in, you know, I'll know what I know, but she said
Honestly, if anybody asked me to read the pilot right now, I would show them the first draft I turned in and not the one
That has gone through this quote perfection process
Well, sure, and that's how I felt about almost everything
I'll say in some areas, you know
Certainly some of these notes were helpful and here's something to think about and here's this and that
But I don't think great stuff comes from committee. I really do not know. I had a I had a I had a job where I did that where I kept I kept like my second or third revision of the script. Yeah, and said this is the one I will send to people as a sample. Yeah, not the one that actually goes on TV. Yeah, it's yeah, it's you get paid either way. It's how I look at it. I got paid paid nicely, but then like the real kicker and I've been in this position before I
is you do all this work and you're exhausted and you're like,
I can't do anymore, this is it,
this is everything I want it to be, here we go.
And they can read it on the toilet with their kids screaming
and then you get a call like, yeah, it's a no.
Hang up and then that's it.
Yeah, that can happen.
Yeah, no, I mean often more often than not does happen.
It's a, it's a real disgusting business we've chosen.
We work, I think we've probably said this before in the show.
We work in the most disgusting business in the most disgusting city.
Yeah, absolutely.
And that's not a knock on L .A., L .A. is a wonderful city.
It's the environment, it's the people, you know, but it's it's it's a tough scene, man.
Well, look, Patty, let your old friend Joe take some of your cares away tonight, plerate.
Please do.
It's about five of 12 midnight, meaning 12, we're in my my lavish apartment here.
having whiskey. It's a Wednesday evening. We don't know when you're going to hear
this, but we're here and we're feeling good and I'm glad to see you Pat. I did
WTF today. Oh, nice. I did. Mark, Mary and Pat, it was a wonderful time. I only
did it once before and it was a live show with a bunch of different comics
together, paneling, and Mark was gracious enough to have me on to help promote
my upcoming special, February 3rd, you let me down on Comedy Central Midnight, February
3rd, February 7th is the Street Date, where you can download it. February 5th is the
replay at 1am. But anyway, he had me on. It was wonderful. I think we were meant for each
other in many ways. Do you go childhood up? Talk about the childhood abandonment, intimacy
issues rage the whole thing I mean we were pretty much on the same page
throughout it which I don't know if that's a good sign or a bad sign I mean
it's good that you found a friend did the podcast get a mention no no no no
wait no it did get a mention it did we'll see you in hell yeah we talked about it
because I mentioned both podcasts but the main focus both well I have another
other podcasts now that's coming out on Farrell very soon.
Haven't even started. That's good in a minute.
We recorded several episodes. It's about to launch.
Who was it with?
Emotional Hangs with Kurt Braunhuller and myself.
You already did this.
Well, it's officially launching on Farrell now.
It hasn't launched yet, but it's about this.
Is it fine? How do you do?
Well, sorry that my hour special that I've worked my whole career for
took precedence over the podcast plug one time.
And Kurt Bronnellar's podcast.
No, no, no, I mentioned ours.
Don't, you're going to start now.
I let you into my home.
Man, we're a year in and that's getting an equal footing on one of the biggest podcasts
in America.
I let you into my home.
I give you my booze, I break bread with you and you spit in my face.
You come in, you take your dick out, you stand up on my dining room table and you piss on
me.
You don't have a dining room table.
Yeah, I'm speaking figuratively. Pat, maybe this is the problem with your script.
I don't have a dick.
This is the problem with your script.
You don't understand figuratively versus literally.
That's the idea that's definitely the problem with my script.
I did a podcast tonight and you got this podcast got to mention.
And in the process, I promoted your special, which I have no part of or ties to it all.
Well, thank you for doing that.
Just so you know what I do for you.
And then, you know, you we all hear how that gets repaid.
Well, you think you'd want to promote this podcast.
It's a big thing you got going.
I mean, you want to talk.
You want to talk, feel like seconds.
I sat here all night tonight.
Didn't do a damn thing, waiting for Patrick.
I'm going to record.
Well, I didn't.
It shows up at 11 .45.
Now, look, I'm as mad as you are about this.
And I didn't.
I'm not mad.
I'm just saying, let's not talk second.
I'm not your consolation price pet. Now we were supposed to do this podcast on Monday when I had no plans
That this always gets left out that what brings us to these points
He said how's Wednesday? I said great, but I am doing another podcast after work. I can come over after that
Joe said fun
I did warn him the podcast can sometimes go long
I had no idea how long now. This is a huge podcast as well. It's not it's not WTF
But it's a massive podcast called the Gilmore guys
It's my buddies to me Kevin Porter
They're funny dudes. I love them. I've known them forever. I used to do the Gilmore guys podcast all the time, and it was an hour and
I hate the Gilmore girls, but I would watch the episode we'd go in talk shit about the Gilmore girls riff
Tell jokes and go four hours. I go over there tonight at seven o 'clock for this podcast and as I'm pulling in I noticed that
They've switched the format. It's now on to bun heads. I knew that going in
So it's almost like kind of a joke.
Now that they made a joke during the Gilmore guys,
what are you gonna do when this is over?
Cause they make a lot of money off it.
And they're like, I guess we'll go into the lady
who created its next show, Bunheads.
We'll do Bunhead Bros as a joke.
Nobody remembers Bunhead.
It's a bad show that was on ABC Family.
So they go, we'll do the Bunhead Bros podcast as a joke.
So they go, do you wanna come in
and do the second episode of Bunhead Bros?
I was like, all right, where do I watch Bunheads?
I watched it on the ABC Family. It's a bad show and I'm driving in and I see that Ben Schwartz
Did the first episode of Bunhead Bros and it lasted three and a half hours and I couldn't believe what I was seeing
So I walked in and I'm like guys. This doesn't go three and a half hours
I mean, you don't talk about Bunheads for three and a half hours
They were like I mean they've started to get longer recently doesn't have to go that long whatever I would I would have canceled
This thing was a firm four hours and the podcast will be up and
We talked about this episode of bunheads and finally I blew up. I was like guys. There's no urgency
There's no that like we need to end this. There's no we should wrap this up. Who's running the show here? What's going on?
Pat, it sounds to me like the inmates are running the asylum. You're not wrong
And I'm not criticizing these guys because I love them and I think they're funny
But I started to feel like a goddamn prisoner and I I left and they don't edit it
They put up these raw for our podcast and people listen to the whole fucking thing some of these podcasts fans are sick
They're sick in their damn heads what I don't want to listen to this for four hours
I told I said I said this is a family guy cut away where Peter would be like
I got to go do my buddies four hour bun heads podcast and you cut to it and he tries to get up and the doors are locked
And they kind of laugh, but I'm like, I'm not kidding.
Yeah, I'm trapped here.
You're real wound up tonight.
I'm just looking at our waveforms up on the computer screen
there.
Oh my.
Look at, look at that.
Look at yours versus mine.
Well, I got a lot going on.
You're a, you're a chatty patty tonight.
Look, I'm just upset that you let them keep you there
and you didn't, you didn't stand up for me.
You didn't get up from that.
I try, you'll hear me on air, try to leave.
Like they don't let you leave.
Well, thank you for plugging this special.
I appreciate that.
I do appreciate that.
And I did mention our podcast today.
Yeah, and Kurtz.
Well, I have things happening in my life.
Have you told the people you're writing this fancy script
for about your podcast?
No, I think they all know about it.
I wish I hadn't now that I've just revealed this note
that they gave me, but oh boy.
Boy, would I love that?
Boy, would that make me happy?
Well, the pilot doesn't go because of this punk if it all hinged on that after all this work
I doubt they listened to it, which is fine. I doubt it too. Let's let's look
Let's get into the meat of this thing. All right, please. I mean to me Joe
It's always the meat. I don't think peat when the few punk as I do listen to when I check in and out of I
Always prefer the downtime to the meat if I'm being honest
Well, the the shit in around, you know, look, we shit around the whole time. I mean, we, you know, it's it's like this this
Poe podcast is a D D infuse. We can't stay on anything for more than it's true
And I don't think there's anything wrong with us moving the thing along because otherwise you wind up talking about bunheads before
Well, that's what I'm saying you're complaining about nobody steering the ship over at this other fucking thing and now
I'm here trying to steer the fucking ship and you're giving me a fucking mouth about it
I'm not giving a fucking mouth. I was trying to say I enjoy talking to you. I like talking to you, too
Everything is an attack. I just wish it didn't always have to be during work times. I miss quality time with you
That's all I'm mad because I look we can go out of one in the morning if you want after this is over
Are you teasing me right now? I'll have a nightcap with you baby. I'm in all right great. Oh shit
All right, well, look at this you want to two boys are back at it again
So I great -tweet the other day and I wish I could give credit to the person
It said don't assume my gender just because I'm back in town
That's very good. I loved it. I think you know who it was is my friend Everett Byron who goes by rad milk on Twitter
I'm gonna promote him for some reason. I'm feeling generous y 'all
Our dear friend Karen kill Garif
from the My Favorite Murder Podcast and many other things.
The doll.
The coworker.
We have been occasionally texting back and forth
our favorite George Wallace tweets.
My favorite Twitter.
Yeah, he's amazing.
So the one I sent her the other day was
when I'm not busy backstroke and through the damn Everglades,
I'm performing at this venue in Florida,
it. Which was an amazing, amazing tweet. Yeah, maybe, maybe better than, uh, even the,
the edgeiest alt comedians who still every time tweet Philadelphia, I'll be in you on Friday.
Yeah. Yeah. I know. Guys, just, just don't make the joke. I know. Just just say you're,
you're doing a show. I know. Or else you, you go big and you go, I'm, I'm going through the damn
Everglades. I George Wong. The reason I bring it up is because my favorite wireless tweet of all time
is I was there, I was there, and everybody didn't win
Chung that night.
Yeah, that's great.
That's a masterpiece.
Wallace has retweeted me a couple times, not to brag,
once, recently, once years ago, and the time he did it years
ago was the only time my life where I've ever, like,
DM somebody.
And I was like, you're the funniest man on Earth.
I love your Twitter.
I'm gonna be in Vegas and I'm seeing your show at the Mirage or whatever he's got.
Yes, I believe you've told this tale in the pocket.
I don't say that you don't tell it again.
I believe you have.
I'm not saying it so you don't tell it again.
I think I did.
I mean, I'm saying tell it again.
I spent a lot of time together.
It might have just been off air.
But if I'm gonna tell it quickly, if not...
I'm saying tell it again.
I'm not saying don't tell it again.
I'm gonna be there.
I can't wait to see you.
And my intent wasn't even to ask for something.
He goes, I'm gonna get you in a booth up front.
He goes you want to bring some ladies or what are you going to do? I'm like, no, I'm not going to bring a lady
But I had a whole booth right in front of the stage to myself afterwards. He kind of put it does his autographs
Then he's like, let's talk we talk about comedy
He's like, you know, he's I'll sign some of you one or we can just talk. I'm like, let's talk most delightful man
I've ever met did you make love to him that night? I didn't make love to him
And I didn't get anything signed because it felt cheap to me because he was just a great great man
That sounds great. That's a nice story. Yeah, I love him George. Well, he's a I'm gonna
We're promoting him follow him on Twitter. Follow him on Twitter. Mr. George Wallace
That's like the time moon units appa said hello to me on Twitter. Okay, and you know what is appa fan?
I am I've got the tattoo of my arm. I never met the lady in my life
Says hello to me out of the blue one day made my year couldn't be the less of a fan of zapal
See now I didn't I didn't shoot on your story. Why do you get a shit on my story?
Just just just just say that's good for you, Joe. It doesn't matter if you're a fan. I think it's great for you
I just don't like that. Oh my god. All right. Let's let's do the movie
Yeah, well, you know what? Hold on
Even though I'm trying to steer this ship. Yeah, try to move us along here. We have to mention
That Pat and I and our dear friends, Ian and Jesse. Oh Christ. How do we miss this?
one night our friend Jesse Pop who's a very funny comic every Monday night he
has an event at his apartment aptly titled Monday Night Beers you go over you
watch a lot of shark tank and you drink bar rescue a lot of bar rescue to and
you drink so one Monday I don't know roughly two months ago we were all over
there and we were we were pretty knee deep in it. And I said guys Bert Young who played
Paulie and Rocky is performing in a play in two months here in in L .A. He's 87 years
old or something. Does anybody want to go because I want to go? Yeah. For our people hands
just shot up. We're all in. Let's do it. I need to say in my anti defense, I had not
had a sip of alcohol.
Don't I that's that's the crazy part to me and that's what keeps me up at night.
I didn't have beer one and I was like sure now I was I was good in the bag.
I had drank about a bottle of Merlot at this point what I suggested it and then
just to put things in perspective the next day when I sobered up I did nothing
from that point on except try to get out of going to see this play.
Yeah, Pat would would almost shame me that I was I would suggest why are we going to this let's not go to this
So we went we went we went to a Mexican restaurant to get dinner before the play because it was right next to the theater
We walk into the Mexican restaurant Bert Young is sitting in the restaurant eating like
Chimichangas before he's gonna go on stage in 30 minutes 30 minutes before a huge Mexican meal, which should have been a tip off
So
The place called the last big and again Bert Young is a joke kind of rushed through it
He played Paulie the fat alcoholic in Rocky and he played the
the, uh, the old timer with the inhaler who does one last hit on the
sopranos. You know him if you saw him. Gary Anjo. Who the hell
does know who Paulie and Rocky is? I feel like you might confuse him
with Mickey. People don't know Rocky. Paulie. Paulie. Paulie. Everybody's
favorite character. Very young hip crowd. Yeah. So, so we're sitting
there. We're in a booth. It's Jesse, Pat, me, and Ian. We're in a
booth. We, we, we, we've had quite a few margaritas at this point.
Uh, and then we did a shot of, I said, let's get a shot at tequila for the road and some guy next to it.
We ordered, oh, yeah, Don Hulio or some shit and the guy next to us goes, you're not going to get the house to
Kila. Yeah, you got to get Antonio, Stakela. So we get, get it. It was like, it was like a prairie fire going
down your throat. It was just paint thinner. It was not even a color that tequila has ever been. It was sort
of a maroon. Yes. So we're like, all right, let's do this thing. I'm still thinking
of how do we get out of this up until the last minute. We go in. I'd tell you, I've never
sobered up so fast as five minutes into this fucking play when I realized that I was trapped.
We grab, we were on the way in. We say, is there a bar to the person who sells the tickets
with his will call? We go, is there a bar? He goes, well, I can sell you beer. That's never
a good sign when the will call booth is where they you buy the alcohol. So we buy we had
to walk across the stage to get to our seats, which means that if you want to leave, you
have to walk across the stage. You have to walk in front of the actors as they're performing
with about six inches between you. In other words, you can't leave unless you're just a
complete animal. Now here's the thing. Yeah. In a situation as you may suspect, uh, listener,
dear listener, the play's not going to be good. But I'll tell you what, you don't suspect
how not good. Yeah, but, but you, as you ordered any of us, here's the thing. We're this
two have been a good play. That would have been magical. We would have been like, you had
to walk across the city. It was so intimate. There could have been more than 50 seats in
this thing. So we're sitting there. There's a little anticipation. Is this going to be
good? This is pretty cool. I'll tell you the minute I knew we were in trouble. Bites go
down. Lights come up. First character comes on stage. He's out there for about two minutes
before Bert Young's entrance. Bert Young walks in zero applause. Nothing. I couldn't believe
that. Nothing. And we didn't discuss it after the show. I couldn't believe a 50 person theater.
Bert Young, the only reason anybody's there comes out and nobody clapped. Nobody clapped.
Nobody clapped. Nobody clapped. Nobody does anything. The first character that comes out by the way is
like a Malibu's most wanted style Jamie Kennedy white rapper in like kind of a big costume.
Yes.
And it's like.
Uh oh.
I believe it was the Malibu's most wanted costume.
It was some sort of a do rag and like, yeah, which at one point, one of the, it's a play
about all Italian mobsters and at one point, one of the 70 year old mobsters goes to about
This kid he goes to kid in the do rag. Yeah, it's like that guy wouldn't know what a do rag his well
I made a bet with Joe when I read the synopsis and it said
Paul you know Bert Young plays this old mobster and
His sidekick is a hip -hop loving what whatever the hell and I'm saying
Guys, what do we think the odds are that Bert Young calls this guy the end word and it came out and it was a white man
So it didn't matter. It didn't happen. He didn't even and my bet was he wouldn't say it to the kid
He'd refer to the music in some derogatory. Yeah, and that never happened either. No
There was no music. I don't mean to say it like I'm disappointed. I was just surprised believe us
We we weren't angling for the N word. I just was like something about this feels like it's gonna get weird
so
So Bert Young comes out to zero pause pause sits down at a desk
where his character conducts his daily business and proceeds to not just read every line that he has to deliver in the play from various pieces of hidden paper on the desk.
Hidden?
Because on several occasions he lifted the paper up to his eyes to see it.
You could he didn't see the paper that he never he did never he he would bend up half the paper and you saw him reading off the paper
Okay, but he he wasn't holding it into the air wasn't holding up the light now
And not only is he reading the lines literally reading them because he doesn't know them now grand look
There's a preview. Maybe it was whatever he's mumbling it and whispering you couldn't hear what he was saying the other actors couldn't hear what he was saying
Uh, and then, uh, the highlight for me was, uh, at one point,
Bert Young goes, ah, fun ghoul, which for those of you that don't know,
that means fucking Italian.
And why does he say this?
Well, it's an ad lib because the earpiece that they're clearly feeding him
his dialogue through has fallen out of his ear and he has to pick it up,
put it back into his ear.
A bright orange earpiece falls out of his ear to the ground.
He picks it up, places it back in so you know that it's not set right.
And no, he's not hearing things anymore. And then the paper really starts taking center stage.
I sent Joe today a review of the play and they pointed out something that I kind of suspected but didn't know well enough
Is that the other actors are referring to lines that Bert Young did not say. Yeah. Wait, wait, you're Jesse sent us the review. I sent the review.
Jesse, I thought you Jesse sent it. I sent it to you. I thought Jesse sent it.
I sent it all right. Okay, listen, I'm not nobody sent it to take your credit away from you. I didn't felt that way
But I felt a little bit like you were stealing it from Jesse
I got to be honest and I felt like I had to say some no, I looked up reviews. There was one review
And they were like and it was a rough one's bad
It was a rough review and honestly not rough enough and I'll tell you when I tapped out of the play and this and this is
Nobody could nobody
Nobody in the group that we went with could understand why.
If you're Italian or if you're raised Italian like I was, you know that it's not spaghetti
sauce.
It's called gravy.
It's Sunday gravy.
It is a tradition.
It is an event there.
It is such a thing.
It is such a staple thing.
There's a line in this play where you know what if you watched a mob movie ever, if you
goes I'd stop by because I was at home making my sauce and I was furious you
would never call it sauce in fact not only would you not call it sauce you'd
be offended if somebody called it sauce then he goes should we also say he was
in a target track suit yeah he was in a target track suit then he goes he goes but
and it's noon and he pours himself like a tall scotch every character because
there's only a bar and a desk on the entire stage. Every character, even though it's established
that it's midday, pours themselves a tall drink while they're doing their lines because it's
the only thing they have to do. Yeah, because they're waiting for Bert Yang to be said dialogue from
various sources. By the way, a lot of his dialogue is asking if he can get a lot of soup to bring
home to his wife because she has the gout in her leg.
Yeah. So he's in the back of a Chinese restaurant. He keeps asking this Chinese guy, you know,
but I really want a lot of soup, a lot of soup to bring home to my wife. And he's like,
I'll get you some soup. No, but the way that the Chinese guy who owns the restaurant,
yeah, who comes in and does in a row, several shots of tequila. Yeah. And then it doesn't register
on him at all that he's done all this to kill him. He's doing shot him to kill him.
Going back out and running his restaurant. Yeah. And Bert Young's like, I need this soup
for my wife. And the wife calls in and they got this recording of a woman being like, baby,
my leg. Hey, it's, can you bring me home some of that soup from the Chinese restaurant?
And then Bert Young's like, yeah, baby, I'll bring you home the soup. She's like, I know,
but I want a lot of soup.
Baby, I promise you I'll bring you on the soup.
Don't you know I love you?
This goes on for 10 minutes.
Yeah, the gout.
He hangs up on her and then he tells the Chinese man,
hey, I want a lot of soup for my wife's leg.
She's got the gout.
We hear it all again.
Yeah, yeah.
Something's telling me it wasn't supposed to be like.
I think you're right.
And then my favorite one, the whole thing
was when the guy that said he was making the sauce,
The reason he was out of the house when he was making his sauce, which he gets in the zone
when he makes, he says, I get in the zone when I make my sauce.
Is because he said he didn't have any garlic and he goes, you know me, I could have skipped
that step, but I just can't skip a step.
The first step in making the gravy.
This wasn't, I didn't have any basil, garlic, yeah, garlic.
which you need to put into the meatballs and you need to saute for the show.
Now he was basically also indicating that garlic is his special ingredient.
That like his kind of secret recipe that nobody knows about in Italian cooking was garlic.
It was written by an Italian man.
It's yeah, it was literally been like a Mexican person being like,
you know how I like to put in a little cumin right?
Yeah.
Yeah. So we are sitting there and the play is supposed to be 90 minutes. So I'm like, well,
we can make 45. But as the reviewer of this play pointed out, it's built as a 90 minute
play and it lasts a very long feeling two hours because Bert Young is just kind of winging
it. And the other actors are like, okay, by the way, the guy who played the white rapper was
kind of good. I thought he was good. I thought the guy that played the Chinese guy was good.
That Chinese restaurant owner was good.
I thought the lady on the phone was good.
Yeah.
The problem was really burnt young and he also showed nothing on his face
that indicated I'm in over my head here.
I don't think he knew.
I think he's old.
Might be a little seen.
And I think they hired.
I got.
Forgive me for saying this.
Yeah.
I think they.
I think they hired him and he showed up and they were like.
Uh oh.
But what's his rating?
And this is what this is what happens in Hollywood and to bring it full circle.
this is why this is the the shittiest fucking town in the world is that I
guarantee that this playwright is telling everyone after the show well I wrote
this brilliant script and Bert Young ruined it that's what's happening and the
script was not the matter is this is one of the worst scripts that's ever been
written like I when I would take screenwriting in college or even high school nobody
had anything this bad and the plot as it were is that a hundred thousand
dollars of casino chips were lost by a bookie out on the town and they're trying to get
them back.
So we left at intermission and just we're right towards the end of that one which I didn't
know was towards the end.
Yeah.
I mean, the thing is falling apart of the seams.
I text Pat, he's three seats over for me.
I just write, this is a real scene, man.
He writes back, we are gone in intermission.
The lights go up, go down and back up again at intermission.
and we are darting across the stage.
We get to the door, we can't leave
because the cast has to go out through the main entrance.
A woman was guiding Bert Young back
to the Mexican restaurant, presumably to have another meal.
But so the lights dimmed and then came back up
and in between that time where the lights dimmed
and came up, I was out the door.
So scared was I that I would be trapped
for another hour of this.
And then in the review, apparently, the key dilemma of the casino chips is never resolved.
So either the play didn't resolve it or more likely, Bert Young was kind of like, I guess
we're done here and just ended the play.
Now we made a pact.
We made a pact that night that we would go back on closing night to see if there was any
improvement.
I'm not doing that.
I don't want to do it.
But I think we need to do it.
I'd have to be a lot more drunk than I was or high or something.
Well, let's get fucking wasted and go.
What do we do?
If we can maybe do like an edible and take an Uber over there,
but then we're going to be cackling at this shit.
We eat the fish.
You can smoke weed in public now in Los Angeles.
It's officially illegal.
I heard you can smoke it outside now.
Well, I tell you, the people outside your apartment sure were.
Hey, folks, we eat some animals.
We go over there.
We get drunk at that Mexican joint.
We have those delicious Mexican ribs again, but Joe, we spent $20 because this was a preview night.
If we go back, the tickets are $40.
Pat, that's a risk I'm willing to take.
It's not a risk. Like, what is the risk that maybe it'll be a great play?
And that it may be worth the extra 20 bucks.
These people had booked this venue for a month. This thing goes to like February 12th.
It's a real bummer man because I'm a big Bert young fan not just from Rocky
I like I like Amityville part two quite a bit and I enjoy him in that film and he's in an episode of this
Prano's that is one of the best standalone episodes of a show I've ever seen in my life, you know an amazing episode
Pope a Greenwich village. Yeah, he's a great actor. He's not any more folks. Listen
speaking of
Well, not even what a shitty transition. Sorry
We have to get to the movie. I feel like this episode needs to be titled The Last Vig and
there which and people will figure out why it's titled that after they've heard this. But
we're almost 40 minutes in and we have not gotten to the movie at hand for our horror movie
centric podcast. That's true. I think we can go ahead and skip the the movie
corner recap. That's fine. I feel like that kind of was that for this the last
big was that for this. It is but real quick because I saw one brand new movie and
we like this podcast to be fairly current. I saw our Patriots day. The new Peter
bird movie about the Boston Marathon bombing starring Marky Mark and I gotta
tell you it's really an a solid and pretty exciting movie and it felt almost
80's style and that the portrayal of the villains was you know bordered on a
little bit racist and weird right you know it boarded on like you know I hate
Muslims kind of a kind of a vibe, but you know, they did blow up a fucking marathon. So yeah, I got
It was solid marquee mark was pretty good. There were some really tense really well -done action sequences
And I'm starting to really like Peter Berg as a director of very effective true stories
Told in like a you are there kind of feeling going back to Friday night lights. Yeah deep water horizon, et cetera
And Patriots say it was even better than Deepwater Horizon, uh, Deepwater Horizon.
That came out.
Yeah.
That's not a movie.
That was with Marky Mark.
Yeah.
You're thinking of Deep Horizon, which is a horror movie.
I remember Deep Horizon, but I'm talking about Deepwater Horizon.
I don't think it's called Deepwater Horizon.
Now you've fucked up so many titles of so many things.
I don't fuck up titles.
The latest of which was when you called the show, the show house, Dr. House M .D.
Dr. House M .D.
Look I'm looking I'm pretty sure it's called the border horizon and I'll prove that in one second
But folks
Here's why here's where this movie lives is
JK Simmons is fucking awesome in it. I love this actor. I always have you love him too. I love him
He's got a scene where he's like walking into a firefight like a big like shoot out and when I look this up
I couldn't believe this this was a true thing all these cops are trying to catch this one
College -aged terrorist on a on a residential street and it goes completely awry
It's the best scene in the movie JK Simmons is so fucking good in this and
John Goodman's in there Kevin Bacon's in there. It's a great cast the bank haven't seen the bacon in a minute
Yeah, he's great. He plays the FBI guy who comes in.
He's always good in a role like that.
Look, it's a B, but you know, for an HBO on demand, like, you'd have a great day watching
that movie. And by the way, I was right. Deep water horizon. Deep water horizon.
It's about the, uh, the offshore drilling rig that exploded and created the worst oil spill in
USA makes me think it come on up for the horizon. Come on up. Uh, I saw the buy by man.
Joe, why didn't we go sit by a man for the podcast?
I saw it with a friend of mine.
Kurt Bronnellar?
No, I saw it with a lady friend of mine.
Oh, yeah, romantic.
Look, that's none of your business.
Should I go see it and we do it up for the podcast?
I hear it's one of the worst movies I've ever met.
I would love you to see it.
It is a pile of stinking dog shit.
I am furious at it.
You know what, I actually thought?
I don't want to blow it by shitting on it right now.
I want you to see it and I want to do an episode about it. All right, we'll do it because it is a disgrace
To film making that's all I've ever heard and I thought to myself if they're ballsy enough in this Twitter age
To call this movie the buy -by -man. I bet it's gonna be great
Because they have the conviction to call it this terrible lame cheesy title and apparently it's not it is
It is a fucking
pile of shit that's what it starts like okay I'm not gonna get into it I want
you to see it and I want it I really really really really want to trash it I
mean it's it is it is a it is a fucking disaster I'm in all right all right
well folks look finally we get to it we're here to talk about Blair Witch now
Pat if you take the helm I'm gonna grab us two brusquies I'll do it I'm gonna
to take the helm. We're going to talk about the new Blair Witch and I told Joe I want
to be a little cautious here because the writer of Blair Witch, Simon Barrett, follows me
on Twitter. I think he's incredibly funny and a very gifted screenwriter who did the
guest and your next both of which were directed by Adam Wingard who also directed Blair Witch.
And I think that Blair Witch is not a particularly good movie.
So I told Joe, I felt a little weird about it, not that we're friends, but you know when
you're Twitter pals with somebody you feel a little conflicted.
I don't think he's going to listen to this, but I'm just saying.
I think that the guest is fucking fantastic.
I think Adam Wingard is a very great, exciting new horror director who's clearly modeling
himself after like a John Carpenter.
and I love what they do. This Blair witch just kind of wasn't for me. It was very loud and I felt
exhausted by it. Well, I, I, um, I'll shoot you straight, folks, because I'm not like Mr.
Hollywood over here. Look, keeping tabs on who's following me on Twitter can say this, can not say
that. I'm not one of these guys. Look, I'm just trying to keep my, uh, my outie in the shop. I
I loved Blair Witch, hated your next, I almost offended by it, hated it, did you like
the guest?
Never saw the guest.
The guest is great, we could do the guest on here.
I'm not against it, the guest to me looked like the, look like another like Pacific Heights
kind of thing, or what's the one with Leota and Madeline Stowe, Unlawful Entry, I love both
those movies.
I don't dislike them, it just, it just seemed like another one of those kinds of movies,
What's the one with Sam Jackson and Patrick Wilson?
Lakeview Terrace.
Yeah.
Those are some of them.
That's one of my favorite genres
and they don't really make them anymore.
They're good movies.
Yeah.
They're just not...
They're not a type of film that I'm anxious to see.
All right.
So I didn't see the guest,
but I did see you're next in the theater.
I thought it was terrible.
Okay.
I thought there were so many logic holes in the film.
I get very angry when I'm watching a movie and I'm watching people make decisions where
I'm going, God damn it, just if why is nobody saying to just do this?
And I felt like there was a lot of that in your next.
And I wasn't buying the plot twist, either.
The plot twists were a little too crazy and felt a little too contrived for me where it was
like, look what we just did, you didn't see that come and dig in.
And it's like, well, no, I didn't because it doesn't make any sense for me just because
that movie introduced me to the song, looking for the magic by the Dwight Twilly band to
70's song.
They're kind of a Tom Petty -ish outfit.
It was my most played song of last year.
It came out like 1976.
That to me was enough to sell me on the movie, honestly.
Well, the one thing I did like about your next is it had the guy from Kingpin in it.
It's the only other movie I've ever seen him in.
The guy with the, where eyeliner throughout Kingpin?
Yes, yeah, the guy, the entertainment tonight.
The guy that for some reason is a bowling alley
in his basement.
I just read it like an oral history of Kingpin
that I should have sent to you and I will send to you
where they talked about all the casting
and everything that went into it.
And they were like, because of Raleota
and something wild war, the whole time they watched
something wild, they were like, is he wearing eyeliner?
And there were that's how little that's how why I love those really fairly
Bros. movies is because they were so dense with jokes, but they would also do
stuff that it's like almost dangerous. It's so stupid. And they were like
yeah, our villain's gonna wear very obvious eyeliner in every scene. And he does.
They were like yeah, we just said you do it too. Yes, it's it's an odd. It's a character.
it's great though. Yeah. So Blair Witch, now I really liked Blair Witch quite a bit and I hate
the original Blair Witch. Okay so let's go starting with the original and walk our way up. So the
original Blair Witch project I saw at the same year as the sixth sense and the sixth sense I saw with
a 105 degree fever and I almost had a heart attack when Misha Barton comes out and pukes. As we've
Discuss I've left up into my sheet when I saw that in the theater. I mean I that I knew I that I was sick
And that was the scene that made me realize that I honestly was close to death. I really was
And that same it's almost seems like the same that would have been where you died during that movie then no
Haley Jolasner would have to help you help you out. Yeah, he would have been able to see me
That's it feels like that same summer. Maybe I'm remembering it wrong
But I think there are both 99. I saw the Blair Witch project around there and I got to tell you there are moments
I haven't seen it in honestly almost 20 years, but
There are moments where you're kind of bored moments where you're kind of frustrated
But it was I saw it early enough where I thought it could be real even though I knew it wasn't I was in high school
But at the end that that final 15 minutes where they go in there and like are standing in that barn
I remember my heart going so fast and it was very similar to the sixth sense experience where I've never had anything like it since except when you and I saw it follows
Yeah, I love it follows which there were a couple moments on that that really really got to me
But just where you feel your heart going a mile a minute that never happens for me anymore because my heart is so dead
But that original Blair which did it for me and to that I tip my hat
I don't think it's a it's a classic, but it was really effective in its day. Why didn't you like it, Joe?
I thought it started great. I was very and because I knew it was fake going into right. I was very impressed at
knowing it was a contrived film
seeing how well or how convincingly they made it seem like an actual documentary. Yeah, an actual found footage
because at that point found footage hadn't been done to death and so so I
appreciate that you got to give it some props. I appreciate it in the way that
you know that I appreciate the Beatles. I don't like the Beatles. I don't enjoy
their music. I've tried and tried and tried. I don't like it. I don't care for the
music, I get annoyed that everybody tells me it's so brilliant all the time. I want to go on record
as loving the Beatles. That's fine. But I appreciate them, yeah, for what they did. So I appreciate
the Blair Witch film that it broke some new ground and it pulled off an amazing feat of shooting a
movie for five grand or whatever it was and making a gazillion dollars. Yeah. That being said,
at the end of the day I was like I'm watching people find piles of rocks like
I'm not scared I'm not freaked out yeah and there to me there was no real pay
off other than I mean the the kid the guy in the corner at the end that was
kind of cool I don't even remember specifics I just remember being so fucking
freaked out by the last ten or so minutes I need a little more I need to see
something I don't have to see a lot I need to see something which is why I like
this new one. No wait no let's go to skip over book or shadows as tempting as it is to do so.
Now book or shadows. I mean if it were if I if there I have a copy of it right here if I
had a copy I'd spit on it right now. I saw I saw book or shadows opening night with some friends of mine
and I don't remember anything about it except I I'm gonna be real honest with you folks.
Early high school. I was very into the bear naked ladies. Oh Jesus. Fuck this was before one week hit
And they oh she you were into the good stuff the good stuff. Yeah, the early. Okay. I'm not proud of this
But I I do think they have some great songs. I have listened to them in 20 years god damn it Pat look
I'm not proud of this. You sound like a god damn
See person. I'm not proud of this, but then I sound like a man that lives in it in a dinner
I'm trying to open up like like a man that lives in on a dock. I'm trying to open up to our listeners under a boardwalk
Or trying to open up to our listeners and say that I might have had a both a t -shirt and a bumper sticker that said B &L
Oh my you know bumper sticker. This was early high school. You're a pig person. We're talking 14 years old. I don't give a shit
If you've heard their life
I'm not gonna stand up for the bank ladies, but their live album. You're like, okay, these guys are pretty good
No, and I'm a guy who even in high school when all my friends were obsessed with it
I didn't like Dave Matthews or any of this shit. I like it very negative ladies. I'll just make up for it
I'm just telling it doesn't make up for it. I know it doesn't I'm not proud of it
But but at some point I like a lot of people around that age
I started turning more to your nirvana and honestly for me it was bands like the totes and things that might not be
Super cool now. These are great. Yeah, great. I love the totes and getting into cooler and close ship
And I saw Mississippi Nights, which is a tiny, tiny venue where I saw many, many great bands of the day.
I went and saw, and you will know us by the trail of our dead, who was at least their first album. It's fucking amazing.
And the openers were Queens of the Stone Age in a tiny theater. And to this day, they're one of my favorite bands, Queens of the Stone Age.
And they played and it was so loud that people were throwing glasses of beer at the stage.
Hard core rock dudes like turn this down, we're damaging our ears.
We don't like this.
Well, you sure they just weren't saying we don't like what you're doing.
We hate you.
No, it was, it was a loudness thing.
Okay.
And a couple of years later, I saw them open for the food fighters and they were so loud
that I wanted to kill myself.
Okay.
They've stopped doing that.
I'm a huge fan of that band.
But they come out and it was like they do
Nicotine Valium like it in marijuana you see an alcohol all of which are drugs that I had not done at that time
And many of them I still have not done, but I was like whatever this is and I didn't drink until I was 23
And I was probably 17. I was like I love this shit
Yeah, I'm into this I love his guy and Book of Shadows opens with that song
And I hadn't heard it since that live show and I was like, okay, this is gonna be like some
dark fucking shit. I'm ready for this. It's the guys that made the paradise
lost movies, which are some of the best documentaries ever made. Those are the
guy's some kind of monster. Those are the guys that made they were
better. They were going from these like amazing documentaries. This was their
chance at doing a narrative film. And I don't remember a single thing about
book of shadows. I just remember all of us being like this is one of the worst
was I've ever seen in my entire it's a pile of dog shit once again. Yeah. The every character in
the movie looks like remember that conveyor belt scene at the Austin powers after they thaw them out.
Yeah. It looks like they took every character to the movie and did that through a hot topic.
Yeah. And they just went in like like in like a Scooby Doo kind of thing. They just on a conveyor
about went in one side naked and came out the other side of the hot topic like in in costume for the
movie but it's no found footage right it's all it's just a standard it's a full
scripted whatever I can't remember if you see anything is it a world like a
couple years after the events of the Blair Witch Project it's a it's a it's a
scripted and scripted film in the narrative is that these characters saw the Blair
which project and now are going to see if it's real, which is basically the plot of
every player which movie. We want to go see if this is real. They go up to the woods,
they all end up dying by the hands of the witches, magic or whatever. And then at the end
of the movie, the way the witch, this is the one thing I really remember and it is my,
And I've mentioned it before in this podcast, it is my cardinal, cardinal sin of a horror movie
above all other pet peeves I have about horror movie tropes. At the end of the movie,
the way the Blair Witch covers her tracks, so nobody believes in her or whatever, is they, all
these files appear at the scene of the crime on the different people.
They'll envelope files. Yeah, okay, that incriminate them to it looks like they all killed one another or one of them killed
Everybody or something like that. So so basically the Blair Witch went
Shopping at that went to staples and bought supplies and just in case I need these yeah, I'll put these files together
That's my biggest peppy. Have ever were they labeled to choose the label there's like there's like their names are on them and stuff and there's like photos and paper clips and it's all very
Toma first very neatly done the Blair which is very very neat. He's detailed oriented, but that's why I hired her to work at my
Tempe agency. Yeah, yeah. So my friend Jim Pinkstone, your friend too. Love Jim. Who we always talk about on here.
You know, he always bitched about in the in the house on Haunted Hill remake. The way they get everybody to the house is that they're they're invited by an email.
So he's like so he was always like so so the the house the evil house opened a hot mail account
It started emailing people. It's why I always had a problem with the ring. It's like evil house at MSN dot com. Yeah
So it's it's now the ring to me is one of the best horror movies in the last 20 years
I think it's a decent mystery movie, but here's what I always say if a horror movie is scary
It's a good horror movie regardless of the things that might bother a
You ring is not a bad movie, but my one problem was always that the fact that the ghost had to be sitting there going
They seem to be into this video tape medium. Let me get into that which in this new one now
It's gonna clearly have to be a YouTube video, so I guess somebody uploaded it
Did you watch on friends that like I told you to? I still haven't seen it now
Unfriended folks, and I'll recommend it again
If you want to talk about that Blair witch spirit of like a $5 ,000 movie being like super effective
Unfriended is great. It's not a classic
but like it's it's it made you kick yourself because you're like I could have
done this for five grand with my friends and made you know 80 million dollars.
Yeah, or just had a movie that you made spent five grand with that nobody saw.
Even that is cool. Yeah, I made a movie, you know, that's it.
So Blair Witch 2, we both agreed, dog shit, Blair Witch 1.
I remember nothing except feel good head of the summer by Queens this time.
Blair Witch Project, the original we agree, was groundbreaking, you know,
You liked it more than I did. I wasn't a fan. Let's get on to the newest one Blair Witch now
And there we know what cracks me up is that I had the VHS of Blair Witch project because eventually blockbuster ordered so many copies
And I worked at blockbuster that it was selling for 99 cents. Yeah, so I owned it of course and
Then eventually a target or something someday. I saw the DVD for like 299 and I bought it
But I was like, I don't know why I'm even doing this. I've never watched it
But what cracks me up a little bit is that the Blair Witch Project is available for purchase on Blu -ray.
The movie looks like security footage.
Well, that's, you know, we were talking about that before.
Like, I love the work that Scream Factory is doing.
But I'm not that crazy that it's all on Blu -ray.
I don't necessarily want...
certain horror movies where I would like this sort of high res, remastered 1080p 4k,
whatever like 2k, whatever the fuck you are, or the thing.
Yeah, but like, you know certain horror movies, you know, I just, I got Pinkstone again,
gave me Creepshow on VHS for Christmas, I want that on VHS, I already had it on DVD,
but I want that on VHS, I don't want that on Blu -ray, you know, I got Creepshow 2,
the new collector's edition on Blu -ray for Christmas, mostly because I wanted to see what the special features were like and everything.
But, you know, I'm a little less inclined to watch the 2K restoration than I am to watch the sort of grainy transfer on the DVD.
Now Blair Witch is basically the same story as the original.
their base they were trying to find the Blair witch information on yeah I know on his sister who
died and by the way if you're unfamiliar with this film for for any reason the Blair witch is
it's basically the Blair from fax of life became a witch yeah I'd by the way now look I already
confessed to bear naked ladies I'm really opening up tonight I did it was with seven other
people we got assigned to do video projects in film school and it was seven
people and we did a short film that I think I still own and it was called the
Nair meaning like the hair removal the Nair bitch project okay what happened
I want to be very clear that this was not my idea and this is why I hate working
in groups to this day. But uh, folks, I mean, we're now starting to realize where you're
getting all these notes. Folks, it wasn't funny. This wasn't my product. Anyway, uh,
what was the plot of the Nair bitch project? I think you could figure it out. No, I can't.
That's what I'm asking. I actually, I don't get what the joke would. I think this was, it was
something a very, very hot girl in my class pitch. And I was like, good idea because I wanted
to have sex with her spoiler alert. It's a ghost that uses name or something. Yeah. I
think in the in the end it was revealed that the wish had like super hairy legs.
Jesus Christ. I know and I didn't have I didn't even so much as touch this
girl folks. I don't feel good about it. The new Blair Witch here was I just
watched it on bluer. Here's my issue for an hour. I wasn't scared and also it was
was so fucking loud and just constantly loud.
It's real loud.
There was no quiet.
There was no like quiet is scary.
Loud is not scary.
And these, it was just hammering me over the head
and everyone who was in it was screaming the entire time.
So they're doing it found footage style,
but everyone holding the camera
or having the camera pointed at them is going screaming.
And I keep turning the volume down and down and down and I'm getting annoyed.
Now the last half hour of this thing had some great scares. It was still loud.
But I'm trying to be some old man here either.
But there was no variance in the tone of it. It was just like an endless assault to me.
However, when she finds the like the tapeworm thing in her leg and pulls it out,
that was really, really fucking effective and scary.
Particularly, although this is not the hardest thing to do to make people scared, when that girl is trying to crawl out of that ever tightening tunnel, that really fucking freak me out, probably because I'm closed for a little bit, obviously.
But I was like, okay, this is great. It didn't to me make up for the previous hour of just generic loud nothing.
I thought I thought that this film was what I wanted the original film to be all right
It was found footage which I'm not a big fan of but it was found footage done very well
It was
Suspenseful and then there was some payoff. I liked it. There was a payoff
I thought the scariest part was the the when the fucking tents started flying up in the air
Yeah, that like really freaked me out for some reason
So I liked that it had pay off
I liked I also liked that it had purpose and it wasn't just hey we're just going to go up into the woods to see if this
Which thing is real it was it was the plot if you haven't seen it is
The brother of Heather is that the girl in the first one?
He think it's her brother and he thinks that he
He sees a video online. He thinks that he has found her and he's going up to the woods to see because he thinks she's still out there
somewhere. So, I liked that it had a little more of the personal purpose to it. It wasn't just
aimless wandering. I thought I liked that they used all the major scare tactics from the first film,
it's just sort of the, you know, initial appetizers into the real scares of this film. And I also liked,
Oh no, actually, I also did, and I didn't, but I didn't like, and all -found footage movies
do this.
And guys, stop doing this with every found footage, just hear me for a second.
Every shot doesn't have to start with the camera turning on.
This one, too, it's credit, tried to differentiate it by putting on, like, my glasses have a camera
in them or whatever.
But still every single shot is like it's like they're it's it's that wild like
tilt up like the camera just turned on and I'm getting my perspective yeah
if this was truly found footage people would edit it in a way where they
would cut that stuff out number one number two they would put like title cards
and things into the footage.
They would build it into a documentary.
No documentary that was constructed from found footage
would literally just be the found footage.
Yeah, which is, that's my biggest gripe
with the, that's my only gripe with the movie.
It could have been presented in a way
with interstitial interviews and things like that.
Well, I'll say that's not gonna be scary though to me.
Like if it's some guy like talking about it who survived,
that's not scary to me.
I don't need a guy talking about it who survived
But yeah, you put in it's like that I love the movie Bernie. Oh sure good Jack black. Yeah, that's
Sort of a mockumentary. It's it's a hybrid, but like
When it when it's cutting away to all the townspeople throughout the movie, you know
Husbands and wives by Woody Allen does it too. We're just cutting to the to the to the interviews with the different
Couples and stuff they do that salad. Yeah, I think that's an effective thing and it and it sells the believability
If anybody was building a document, because the Blair Witch movies are presented as documentaries.
If you were a filmmaker, you wouldn't just splice together all the found footage.
You would splice it together with some sort of narrative around it.
That's true.
I think there have been movies that have done that, but I can't think of any offhand.
Very few.
What does your...
I've heard the Bay is kind of interesting, which is like, I think it's Barry Levinson.
the Bay the Bay is a found footage or movie that I've heard is pretty good. I've never been heard of it
But do you have like a favorite found footage movie? I don't know that I do I thought Chronicle was pretty cool when I saw
Chronicle was cool. I look to be honest
I'm not a found footage fan. I would say that this was probably the best one I'd ever seen
Yeah, I mean I think I thought I thought it had a very strong last half hour
But to me, it needed some sort of tonal. I didn't give a shit about anyone in it, which is always a big sticking point for me.
I mean, if you're strictly saying, here's six people, they're kind of unlikable, and we're gonna follow them into the woods.
I gotta say I need a little more romance than that. I mean, I don't care about them.
I was pretty invested in the brother of Heather. I was interested in that. And I was pretty invested in that weird couple that like takes them in.
the they were interesting yeah and I they were like we've been gone for five days
that was kind of cool and it kept me guessing like but I'm trying to think of
other found footage movies
well what other you know yeah Chronicle was fine yeah I mean project X I thought
really sucked just because that guy was the monkey movie with Matthew
broader. Oh the time travel one or whatever? No. Project X is just your standard teen party movie,
but found footage style. Is it a comedy? Yeah. Okay. I mean, I guess I can't think of many
found footage movies either that I found there was the the galos. Didn't see the galos. There was
you know open water. Oh yeah, that wasn't good. Which I found painfully boring. Yeah, it's a hard
John were to make really I thought they did it well with this I thought it was I
thought it was your typical hour build up of of sort of building building building
the suspense and then they delivered with a half hour of really crazy shit
which I don't think most on footage movies do did you see I really I really like
Adam Wingard and I think he's from the same school as like it follows where
they're trying to they're really trying to do a John Carpenter style of filmmaking
Why do you what but what makes you say that why do you keep saying John Carpenter?
I mean even the credits of like the guest it is like John Carpenter's
Okay, like it's an almost an homage to it. They feel very 80s. Okay, and he makes you know almost like a movie a couple movies a year
It seems like easy. All right. I think they're trying to he's trying to emulate them. I like Wingard a lot
But he did the pilot for outcast, which is the cinamax horror show if you see that about the rap group
No, no, I would like to see Outcast folks, you know, we're about to wrap this up.
If you've seen Outcast, let me know if it's worth my time.
Quarry on Cinemax is one of my favorite shows and I haven't met a single soul who has seen
that show.
But Outcast is a horror series, so it might be good to talk about on this show.
All right.
Talking about future episodes, I'm going to try to see the buy by man, the fact, like thinking
about having to pay $15 for it here in L .A.
It's disturbing to me, but I'll do it.
And go to a matinee, pay eight.
That's true.
But man, who would have smoke and pile of shit it is?
But people, you know, a lot of people have asked,
is your next one gonna be prisoners?
And we've talked about it a lot.
I asked Joe over this week to watch prisoners.
He couldn't do it, but I would say a pretty safe bet
is that our next two will be prisoners.
and the buy by man if I see it I can watch prisoners on my own I just couldn't
come over to watch it that one night that's fine I mean to me prisoners the
fucking masterpiece I'm tipping my hat on that but if you haven't seen it
watch it then you can really enjoy that episode when it comes out on a week or
two well also let us know too if you have any interest in this because I truly
want to do silent night deadly nights part parts two three oh I'd love it four and
five. So as viewers, let us know if you'd have any of these fucking things get so crazy.
I mean, the first one is nuts. The second one is even crazier than you watch to.
Oh, yeah. Then I'll borrow two from you tonight. I'll watch two is a two is a fucking romp. Yeah,
I'll watch that one. Yeah. So and plugs. My special comes out February 3rd Comedy Central at midnight.
Not the TV show. I mean, it premieres at midnight. You let me down. Replace February 5th when I am.
and it's the internet for download also the album version February 7th I will be
on the Gilmore guys podcast next week it is four hours of us discussing an
episode of bunheads which no one has seen I will say that there's a lot of
really funny shit in there but you can check that out that's all I really got
Oh and I'll be at the Oklahoma something casino I don't have it in front of me
February 4th I'll be at a casino in Oklahoma yeah you can find it you just
Google me you'll find it alright folks as always we love your your tweets and
your feedback if we don't respond to everyone we are seeing them and take them
in a consideration. When we slap a like on it, it means a that we're seeing it, b that
we're liking it, and c that we're like talking about it as something we're going to incorporate
into this show. There are big things coming for this show in the very near future that
we're excited to share with you. You can find me at the Patrick Walsh on Twitter and Instagram.
You can find Joe at Joe DeRosa Comedy on Twitter and Instagram. You've been listening to
I will see you in hell.
It's a presentation of the Fangoria Podcast Network.
It's produced by Thomas DeFaio, an executive produced
by the great Ken Hanley of Fangoria Entertainment.
For press opportunities, advertising inquiries,
and information about we'll see you in hell.
Contact Ken at Fangoria .com.
Folks, thank you very much.
Keep those five star ratings coming.
We love you.
Talk soon.
You