I'll see you in the next video.
Welcome to will see you in H .E. double hockey sticks.
I sit here, Joe DeRosa, face -to -face, dick -to -dick, with my boy, as he would put it, Patrick
Walch.
We're in the same room, baby, as he would put it.
How's it going, everybody?
We're sitting at my kitchen table, almost Batman -style lavish luxury of my home.
Joe's out here for a week, we've been having fun, we've been helping each other get through
the day.
Fun is extreme, but we're having a nice time.
I do wonder, I've been here since Sunday, it's now Wednesday.
Yeah, I'm feeling it today, I'm feeling how long you've been here today.
Are you?
No, come on.
I think almost that we should live together.
It's worked out pretty well.
I feel, I say it all the time, as we all grow age in this crumbling republic that we live in,
and inflation continues on, and prospects for the future just evaporate.
I think it's all going to be golden -girl style old age, and I love us.
You're nothing wrong with you and me living here together in harmony, not sin.
Yes.
Tap and some ass here and there.
Drinking, recording a pod, our only source of income, eventually.
I love it, and also you don't have a legal right to clean out my bank account, which will
be a nice change in roommates.
Yeah.
Yeah, no, it has been very smooth.
I haven't been with a roommate for a while.
My best roommate ship was my old buddy, Jerry, who lived together for a long time, and it was
just because you got to live with somebody like you.
You and I know that if the other person goes down to the basement for an hour and a half,
leave them alone.
Yeah.
They don't want to talk in that period of time.
What the hell is happening outside?
Chain sawing?
It sounds like a chain sawing.
It sounds like a truck went by.
No.
Yeah, no, I agree, and then there's also a good level of courtesy so far.
You know, hey, man, is it okay that I'm in the room?
Is the phone call okay?
Yes.
You got to take this call.
You know, it's just, it's you get to an age, you say, get the hell out of my way, leave
me alone.
Yes.
If we want to watch a movie, we'll watch one.
We watched Honeymoon in Vegas last night, which will be, I assume, our first movie quarter,
a mutual quarter pick.
First movie we watched together in upwards of a year, I would say.
Yeah.
I love the film.
I really do.
There's something about it.
It meanders a little, especially for like a 90 minute movie, but Cage is awesome.
Parker, when I look at like, we should do sometime like top 10, Dave, top 10 best people,
humans have ever looked on film.
Maybe we do girls and guys, so it's not sure.
I'll do Paul Newman in hood.
I'll throw him out first.
That's how comfortable I am with my eyes actually.
I'm fine with that.
I'll toss one out.
Y 'all give you a will Smith and I am legend, sure, right baby.
It's right slapping those aliens across the face.
You keep the end of the world out your mouth.
That is slogan and I get it mixed up real life in the movies.
But I have to update my list because Sarah Jessica Parker and no offense to her, I couldn't
be less attracted to a human being now.
But my lord, was she amazing looking in this film?
I still find her very, I'm very attracted to Sarah Jessica Parker.
Okay.
I think now it's her personality that bothers me.
That's what I like as a human.
Well, I'm attracted to Carrie Bradshaw.
Okay.
The character every I watched and so it goes with the fuck was it called and just like that.
And just like that.
I fell in love with her all over again.
Okay.
She's that character is the quintessential New York free spirit true.
I love her.
And I'm watching that thing and at the end of it, I'm going to spoil the end of the season.
It's fine.
She makes out it ends with her suddenly making out with a smokingly hot man 20 years easily
her junior and it's completely believable.
I'm like, I buy this 100 % as much as I bought Khan.
Yeah.
Fallen for Khan in honeymoon and then I thought you make your dog.
I was like, okay, yeah, you buy you buy Khan 100 % Joe and I were commenting.
It was sort of a tribute to Jim, but Jim doesn't have a lot of comedy in the film.
He's sort of the villain.
He's great in it.
And the hair in this movie, they would never allow they really would never allow a leading
man to have Nicholas Cage's hair in this film.
He's he's balding, thinning, but it's before he fixed it, I would argue now he looks even crazier,
but the hair, it's just standard.
It's your friend who's hair is thinning, but to see it in a romantic lead is very odd.
And then Khan's hair has sort of a like a Larry fine, yeah, probably too.
And it looks absurd.
Also, it's almost like a lufa like a shower lufa, but it's orange.
And there's a coral reef element to it as well.
Yeah, just these two bizarre looking balding men,
lusting after one of the hottest women of all time, it's crazy.
Yeah, she's in her everything about her in that movie is magical.
And then you got Khan, his side man, who's almost steals the show, I would say,
very funny.
He's the guy from Goodfellas, I just realized that.
Well, I read last night the Cadillac, yes, they call him, I forget his first name,
but they call him, I looked up the IMDB trivia on it last night,
and they call him like Bobby Sandwich in the film.
Okay.
And the year before he was in Goodfellas,
where his name was Bobby Rose Beath.
So it was a tribute.
Okay.
And he's what a lucky actor gets shoved around by De Niro and Goodfellas,
gets shoved around by Khan.
Yes, I mean, he's two of the great.
Yeah, guys, every actor that's ever played a sewer technician
or a, a mob shlub is in this movie.
A lot of great character actors.
A lot of, I love Cage doesn't get to do it enough, but his slow burn is fantastic.
Now, there does come a point in the movie where he just starts every line in a whisper
and ends it in a scream, but it's funny 95 % of the time.
And I think he's doing it because he's like, no, this is funny.
It is funny.
It is, but I'm saying I think that's why he's doing it.
I don't think it's like, a lot of people think Cage doesn't have a grasp on reality or something.
Right.
I'm like, no, he's like, no, it'll be funny to see me like freak out like this.
Yes, yeah.
And I think these were Coke days for Cage and in certain scenes.
Probably for Khan.
Yeah, probably.
There are scenes in this where he looks so ghost white and hung over in addition to the hair.
It's a terrible looking transfer.
Don't upgrade your blu -ray if you have a DVD.
It might look worse than the DVD, but I've always loved the film.
It's a great screwball comedy.
I'm going to venture you're the only person in America that owns Honeymoon and Vegas.
You're probably right, but I've loved the movies since I was a kid.
There's something about it.
I was an Elvis fan and a Cage fan.
I guess that's what brought me to it.
And if I'm being real, there are several very vivid pauses that I can remember
cracking it to in that film.
Thank you.
I saw him last night and I was like, do I need to step out?
Oh, boy.
It was much more gag heavy than I thought.
Yeah, there were almost naked gun style gags in it, which will lead us to our second
shared movie quarter.
But naked gun, I mean, but like that thing where it's the runner of the different Elvis's.
Yeah.
And it's like the Asian Elvis, then the black Elvis, then the child,
which is named child Elvis is played by a young Bruno Mars.
It's just so fucking funny, man.
Like the idea that everybody in Vegas wants to do an Elvis impression.
Yeah, which makes the climax of it so wonderful.
And they all jump out of the thing.
But I was, I pointed out the gel last night.
This is Andrew Bergman who co -wrote Blazing Saddles.
And then he had an amazing career doing it.
He did the in -laws, the original.
And he did the freshman.
All kinds of great comedy classics.
And he wrote the song, We Were Only Freshman.
Yes, by the Virpipe.
He was in the Virpipe.
But I pointed out the Joe.
I stopped it at the 15 -minute mark.
And I was like, we know everything we need to know about our three main
characters.
The story is completely set up.
We feel we're in the hands of a confident film here.
And it's a rare feeling these days, which is very sad.
You feel like some idiot is running the camera at the time.
We don't know how it's going to end or what's going on.
Or any idiot running the camera.
Idiot right in the script.
Yes, idiot running the studio.
Yes, idiot's abound.
Then we watched mutually this morning.
An episode of Police Squad.
Yes.
And I found that to be a joyful way to wake up with you this morning.
We were in bed together.
As he toes, he's Joe brought me down a little,
sort of like a riding desk with a half a grapefruit.
Some oat bran.
I'm having trouble shitting, you know.
So not kidding.
Toast slightly burnt just the way you like it.
Yes.
Bergman by the way, I suddenly dropped all my knowledge of this man.
He also wrote, Oh God, you devil.
Joe last night asked me one of the most pathetic questions I've ever heard.
Is it worth owning the Oh God trilogy on Blu -ray?
I'm still contemplating it.
No.
He also contemplated it.
He wrote the original Fletch.
Wow.
Strong.
Very strong.
And, you know, I'm sure Joe and I will be watching the new
John Ham Fletch.
Trying to be optimistic.
He confessed Fletch.
It couldn't have a worst title.
It's a reboot.
Just call it Fletch.
Confess Fletch.
When I saw the title, I'm like, wait a minute, is this a sequel?
That's cool.
Is he playing like the original character in the 80s?
It's like, no, it's a full reboot.
So call it Fletch.
Yeah.
Fletch something else, not confess Fletch.
Sorry.
It gets worse.
Bergman also did soap dish, which is a very funny soap opera deal.
I've tried with soap dish.
I can't, I can't get into it.
I don't know who it is.
I like it.
And he did it.
It could happen to you with Cage.
Cage clearly loved him.
He's a good man.
I like his work.
Strip T is killed his career.
Um, Demi Moore at her hottest.
I was, I was, uh, all of my time in 1996 because I was not 17 yet,
was spent trying to get to see Strip T's.
And Showgirls, which came out the same year.
When she in the trailer, the TV trailer,
ripped that shirt off and started strutting down the thing.
Yeah.
Me and my buddy Mike Bello were like, dear God,
like, what are you doing to me?
I'm 17.
I can't figure out how to talk to a woman.
Don't wave this around in my face.
Yeah.
I remember, uh, seeing, I think she was on.
I want to say 2020 or some shit.
And I was sitting in the living room doing my homework or something.
And they showed that very scene where she burst her shirt open.
And I remember my dad, my dad who would just sit all day
and night watching TV within the recliner with the recliner up on his, uh,
barca lounge or whatever.
Just went push the thing down and went to a full upright,
leaning forward sit, which rarely happened,
unless there was like 9, 11 going on.
But it was like, you have my full attention.
I remember being at my friend's, uh,
house where we were kids and his dad would
same thing barca lounge with beer.
Yeah.
Dad drank beer throughout the day.
I didn't realize it was alcoholism at the time.
Yeah.
Just thought he liked beer.
I remember one time was we was watching something on HBO.
This is back when HBO would chill like nudity like at 3 p .m.
Yeah.
And, uh, this girl took her top off and full tits out.
And it's just dad just goes, holy shit.
Sometimes the reaction just comes out of me.
You know, um, um, yeah.
So anyway, we watched a police squad and that was enjoyable.
Was it that?
It was.
I had seen them when I was a kid.
I bought the blu -ray.
Another blu -ray.
You don't need folks.
The police squad.
But, um, and now after realizing, okay,
you didn't need to upgrade your entire collection.
I'm starting to dip my toe into 4k and I already regret it.
But I don't even have a 4k television.
Told you.
I told you not to do that.
You don't listen.
No, because I'm my next TV will be 4k and blah, blah.
I want to have the top of the line.
We watched episode called the butler did it.
And as I said to Pat, I mean, if you went classic police squad,
naked gun, Leslie Nielsen.
There's a scene in this where he has to interrogate a murder suspect
while the murder suspect is playing street basketball.
And Leslie Nielsen starts fully playing street ball while interrogating him.
Getting three pointers, blowing on his fingers.
It's really funny.
It's a really great classic like Zucker Brothers, Abrams, you know,
it's I wish they would have recreated it in one of the movies to be honest
because they do recreate a lot of the gags for the movies.
Well, the good thing is they learned when they went to movies that you don't need like
the opening fourth of your episode to be like a serious crime drama.
The movie just immediately is like, all right, we're just doing jokes.
They try to give you a little bit of a plot here.
And I think there's probably the network like just make it like a colombo
and then it can get weirder over time.
But those the early scenes are slow to say the least.
But then it gets so funny.
But yeah, it's only a scene or two and yeah, gets rolling.
It's great.
Nordberg is played by a white man, not OJ.
Who is that guy?
Never seen him.
And Ed is played by a different character actor.
But I've seen the guy that plays Ed and stuff.
Me too.
I think he usually plays kind of a dick.
Alan North.
What were you known for?
Sino evil here.
No evil.
He's got a really funny face.
Zarpakko.
Long kiss.
Good night.
That's a picture.
Lean on me.
Glory.
That's a picture.
I mean, so why why maybe he didn't want to do the movies?
I mean, Kennedy wasn't a bigger name than him.
Wouldn't think so.
No.
Kennedy for sure is much funnier.
I don't know if I agree.
I think they're both great.
Okay.
I think they gave Kennedy way less funny stuff to do.
Yes.
Like, I'm trying to think of another scene I think of all the time.
One of the few things I can eat on Keto as a snack is pistachios.
Right.
I always think about that scene in the original
where they're on stakeout and his lips are red, which I never got.
Because he's in the red pistachios.
Okay.
I haven't had a dead red pistachios.
And you get red all over your fingers.
And you can get it on your mouth.
They exaggerate it.
With the giant, he's got the shells piled up.
Yeah.
So he can't open the car door or whatever.
I found him very funny in those pictures.
I did.
The guy in this.
Who?
Kennedy, yeah.
No, but everything you just said was a Nielsen gag.
The pistachios?
Yeah, that's all.
No, no, no.
No, they're both doing it.
They're both doing it.
Nielsen has got the red all over his face and then can't open the door.
That's Nielsen.
No, I think it's Kennedy.
I'm almost positive.
I'm telling you.
Well, you want about $5 ,000?
Sure.
Okay.
So why would they give Kennedy the big gag?
They give him, they got to give him gags.
The only Kennedy gag I remember is when he's foaming at the mouth.
Right.
It's just a sight gag of when Nielsen, again,
and all they want is sex.
It's a 21 -year -old, you know, that's the only,
that's the only Kennedy.
Oh, more, more.
Yeah.
And then I remember Kennedy going a Petomanian ship, but that's not a joke.
The guy Peter Lupus is the guy who portrayed Nordberg in the show.
He's still alive at 90, and he was a bodybuilder.
He's very funny.
He's funnier than in the show.
He's funnier than Sipson in the show.
It's where they targeted like losers, you know, like people who
Ricardo Montalban and Robert Dulay at this time, Wayne Newton, you know,
like that must have been part of their aesthetic.
Like let's go after people who are just beyond washed up for still a presence.
Even Nielsen at this time.
You think so?
I mean, sure, Kennedy was 20 years past airport,
which was his big hit, right?
Two years past now.
Well, the idea was we're going to get all these guys that are known for these hard -boiled
right dramas, yeah.
And then they clearly had a thing, well, no, Wayne Newton's not in it.
Wayne Newton's in a Ford Fairly.
And he's in one of the Nielsen spy artists.
But, but Dulay, I was going to say there's a pattern with like singers,
but there's not Montalban.
Yes.
Who's the bad guy in the third one?
They go young in the third one with what's his name?
I don't recall.
Well, Wayne Newton is a naked gun two and a half.
Yeah, it's your boy Fred Ward, right?
Whatever his name is, yeah.
Wayne Newton is a naked gun two and a half.
Wayne Newton plays an oil executive.
No, Dulay is naked gun two and a half.
He's the villain, but Wayne Newton is in two and a half.
What?
Frank suspects a wealthy influential man an oil executive here played by Wayne Newton
is behind a secret.
Oh no, this article has it wrong.
Yeah, that's Dulay.
Newton's in Ford Fairly.
Love the internet.
You can...
Oh no, let's write here on the internet.
You realize as you're reading it, the article is incorrect.
As they say, that's your own damn fault.
But I don't know.
I remember seeing Wayne Newton in one of them.
You didn't.
He's in Ford Fairly.
Which is a similar style of movie.
You can be in both.
And I'd be in the naked gun.
It seems like he should be.
I understand.
Yes.
I got confused for a second.
He's in.
I was thinking of the HBO Max drama Hacks,
which Wayne Newton is in for some reason.
And he looks absolutely insane.
Uh, yeah.
Absolutely insane.
He said so many facelifts.
Yeah.
Yes.
Wayne Newton was in Vegas vacation.
He was in perfect strangers.
I tried to watch.
I tried to get washed with Vegas vacation.
It's terrible.
Never loved it.
You do like it.
You've said I like Vegas vacation.
Well, yeah, I saw it theatrically.
I remember it being a letdown.
And yet I had some laughs.
I remember my biggest laugh was that
they were playing the war in the casino.
And now when you go to Vegas,
they play war in the car.
But, uh, yeah, the quaid stuff in that sucks.
I like the stuff with the kid actually.
Ethan Emory, the pop anopolis.
It's kind of funny.
Yeah, I mean,
I used to just really hate European.
And I used to say to do a Joderosa style
antagonize people that Vegas was better than European.
It's not.
But European sucks.
I don't think it's, I'm surprised you think it sucks.
It's got some great
stuff in it.
I like European vacation.
I think it's a hope that's solid.
I don't think it's as funny as the first one.
And then it's hard Christmas.
It's hard to beat.
I mean, Christmas, it's a Christmas movie.
I mean, it's, it's almost
playing with all wild cards.
Once you make it a Christmas movie,
it's at a different level.
It is.
I just really admire that the plot of
Christmas vacation is the family comes over to the house.
Like, that's only something you can do
if you got John Hughes or somebody at the helm.
Sure. That's not a movie you can pitch.
The family comes over.
What's the story?
He wants to make it the best Christmas ever.
Okay.
What's, what else is going on?
There's nothing going on.
Right.
The bonus drama, I guess,
whether he gets his Christmas bonus.
But it's a classic.
They learn nothing from the classic.
The classics are always simple for the most part.
And I got this pitch now.
My favorite thing I ever read,
wrote the script out because my agents were like,
you can't pitch this.
It's about a dysfunctional family.
It's very much based on my family.
And my agents were like,
you're going to have to make them be vampires
at the act two sprake or something.
I haven't read it yet.
They were just like,
you need, if you, if you
want to pitch this,
you can't go in and pitch a dysfunctional family.
There needs to be some other element.
That's why that's what has stopped me
from the last five years of writing.
The movie I wanted to write about my family.
So I'm like, I'll never sell it in a million fucking years.
The way you would sell it is if you lean into
being adopted.
If you lean into being Egyptian and Italian family
or something, you got to put some sort of
yeah, but then it's like this fake like,
I don't to fit in.
It's like, that's not what it is.
You got to do my big,
fat Greek wedding with Italians.
You know, uh, but yeah.
So I don't know.
But anyway, what else we got?
What else have you seen?
Well, I mean, we're we're in a loose movie corner over here.
I feel like we are in a loose movie corner.
I'd like to shout out the new FX on Hulu.
Is that the channel now?
Original drama comedy series chef.
You mean the bear?
I mean the bear.
Oh, uh, always shit.
The bear.
I haven't had breakfast and I'm going through a lot.
The bear is excellent.
Uh, I always get my guard up when everyone is telling you that
something is great.
But I watched it and it's fucking great.
It is eight half hours.
The best episode is the seventh episode,
which is like 17 minutes long and it's one take.
And is it is the best episode of TV this year by 5 million percent.
Love the lead kid in it.
The kid from shameless.
I think he's great.
It's a lot going on in this show.
It's about depression, grief, loss, family, etc.
Uh, it's marketed as a comedy.
I did not smile once.
That might be again.
What's going on in my life.
But I did not find it to be very funny.
I found it to be a really great and well -written drama series.
A lot of Chicago, uh, local flavor to it.
And any issue you have with the show, like at the beginning, I was like,
so it's about a chef who works at the French laundry,
the best restaurant in America.
It's Santa Barbara or it's up north somewhere, California.
And loses job and he takes over his, uh,
fathers or his brothers,
beef place in Chicago.
And he decides he's going to use his top shelf chef strategy here at this kind of low -down beef
restaurant.
As it started, I said, I have no interest in this.
I don't like shows about cooking.
I didn't watch the fucking Bradley Cooper chef movie where he,
I remember in the trailer said, we're serving up culinary orgasms people.
Who said this?
Bradley Cooper in the film Burnt.
Another one of those bad boy chef movies.
That thing came and went, I didn't even, I was like, what is this?
This is fake movie poster.
What it seemed to be, yes.
But, you know, I've never liked anything about a chef ever.
Ratatouille, I suppose, but that was a rat chef.
Uh, I dug it big time and it's a one -day watch.
Uh, they got picked up for a CZ2.
Great, great.
So easy to, uh, check it out.
It's a really good show.
Joe Bob says, check her out.
It's got like an uncut Jim's vibe.
You know, it's just, it's relentless.
It's very intense.
It has the most lame white dude soundtrack I've ever heard.
It's like Wilco, John Mayer, Van Morrison, all these people.
But it all works.
I don't know what to tell you.
It all works.
Every clip, every clip I've seen is hilarious, by the way.
I don't understand.
I'm, I'm really flummoxed by this.
I can think of a few scenes that we've ever been.
I know that scene is, that's just very funny.
I'll probably, I'll probably watch it again, but it's very intense.
The scene I saw, it's not funny to me.
The scene I saw, it was very funny.
I have a friend, I know a guy, I don't know, I wouldn't say a friend,
but I know a guy that has a restaurant who has an employee who did this.
But when there's a scene where there's a woman addressing the crew
and she says something to a woman and the woman goes,
no English.
And she goes, no, no, you speak English.
I actually just heard you speaking English, which is really funny.
I have a friend, or I know a guy who has a restaurant who said,
I have an employee that when he doesn't want to do something,
he pretends that his English isn't good.
Really?
And he goes, how the hell do you address that?
You can.
And I always thought, what a funny thing that is.
How could you ever do it?
And they did it on the, and I was like, well,
the good for them that they did it.
Like that is the thing that some people will do.
Right.
So I was like, this is ballsy, this looks funny.
I got to watch it.
I'll keep it simple.
Stupid.
What was that? A series of books?
I was just thinking that myself.
I kind of play piano.
K -I -S -S, keep it simple, stupid.
But there was a whole series of books like
Kiss Piano, Kiss Fanta, like chicken soup for the soul.
Right. Exactly.
I rewatched the watch.
Man, you love that watch.
Well, I hadn't seen it in a while, and I was in a mood to be sort of just
frivolous and laugh and didn't want to think about anything.
Yes.
As I usually do.
And I threw it on.
And it's not as good as I remembered.
It's way more dick and sex jokes than I remember.
I got about a 13 % on Rotten Tomatoes when it was released.
But I got to tell you, people,
nine times better than any comedy movie that's been released since it came out.
Well,
in that type of comedy.
Okay. Fair.
What, tell me the comp.
I mean, the watch was 15 years old, wasn't it?
Okay.
So I'm making it younger, which is why I'm saying
what, since it came out.
Yes.
In the last eight years.
Okay.
Well, you're not going to get much argument here.
I don't know when I think bridesmaids was 2010.
It's so funny when you talk about what has happened to comedy.
Everyone says bridesmaids.
Everyone.
And then you go, that was 12 years ago.
Yeah.
So, so that's what I'm talking.
I'm talking the last five years, whatever it is.
A grouper.
You know, there's movies with big laughs.
My grouper, the movie is, that's 2011.
Yeah.
No, you're right.
You're right.
There's nothing.
Yeah.
And I'm watching this thing and I'm like, you got, you got Vaughn.
You got Stiller.
You got Jonah Hill.
And you got Richard.
I can't say his last thing from the IT crowd.
I -O -A -D.
Yeah.
They're all areas.
They all have perfect comedy timing.
By the way, they're all completely their own personalities.
Yes.
Like Stiller is doing Stiller and he's doing it great.
Yeah.
Vaughn is doing Vaughn and he's doing it great.
Hill is doing Hill.
Richard's doing it.
They're doing the thing that, what the fuck is this?
What?
It's saying the zoom went in 10 minutes.
What, what?
That's for Christ's sakes.
Don't you - I thought you had an account.
I do.
It's - it's - it's everything not working again.
Jesus Christ, whatever.
Well, stop and start and off to edit it all together.
Let's leave this in so they know what we do to suffer for our art form.
I'm not - I'm not editing it now.
Nine and a half minutes till the fucking zoom ends.
Anyway, you ever see nine and a half weeks speaking of Bonham?
Yeah.
Anyway, it's pretty hard.
They're all - they all have perfect comedic timing.
They all have terrific comedic instincts.
And they're all funny in their own ways.
Is the script - the structure of the script is perfect.
Yeah.
It's got too many dick and sex jokes in it.
It relies too heavily on that.
But - but those jokes are very funny at times.
And then the jokes that aren't that are very funny.
Maybe I'll give it another view, you know?
I mean, it's just - it's just - it's just a shame.
You want - I mean, maybe it got such bad reviews because it was so bad putting it up against
because everything else was so good.
Yeah, yeah.
But I mean, you put this thing against - I'm telling you,
any theatrical comedy release the last five to eight years,
you're going to be like, this is 90 times better.
Just from - even from a production standpoint.
Right.
It feels like a movie.
Remember when things felt like a movie?
I'm watching the trailer - I've never seen it, but -
I'm watching the trailer for Eddie Murphy Metro on YouTube.
Christ, did that suck, you know?
Yeah.
And it's not very well -reviewed.
Yes.
Ebert really liked it.
But I'm watching, like, scenes from it because the guy that's in dope is in that -
Uh -huh.
Say it was like in an article, like, one of his - his 10 best villain performances,
and one of them was Metro.
Wait, who are you talking about?
The white guy in dope.
In the trailer, the guy that they, like, hired to help them surveil the UFOs.
That don't even know who you're talking about.
Have you seen the second trailer?
I guess not.
Uh, anyway.
But I'm watching scenes with him and Eddie Murphy,
and I'm watching the trailer, and I'm like,
God damn it, it looks like a real movie.
Yes.
It's a real - it feels like a real movie.
Now whether it was good or not, fine.
You know, but like -
I missed that, man.
Like, nothing feels real anymore.
Nothing feels invested.
Oh, Christ, did you watch the Halloween kill?
I'm all the way all over the map.
Uh, how do we end trailers now?
Well, let me watch it before we'll do it on the next one.
All right.
I love - we need to do that.
Sit down and watch all the trailers.
I - because that's what I could do it now.
I used to get so excited to go to the theater,
and now I want to watch them at home and it's sad.
What, uh, I guess what, you do one more?
We got six and a half minutes before this thing comes off.
I'll do one more.
Uh, I gotta mention,
I - my, uh, you know, attention span is completely gone.
And I - I'm always looking for something that I can watch quickly
that isn't like a TikTok or something.
And I got very hooked on something
that numerous people have told me that I would love.
And of course, I did.
It is called on cinema.
Uh, with Tim Heidecker.
Oh, yeah.
And the guy who does, uh, Neil Hamburger.
Yeah, yeah.
What's his real name?
I forget.
Norm Crosby.
That's not his real name.
Um, um, and - and - and - and - and - and - and - great literature.
Continue, yeah.
So, uh, they have an amazing chemistry that basically all it is,
you can watch the first 15 hours of the show
and one continuous YouTube.
I would watch it hit by bit.
Um, um, each episode is roughly 5 -10 minutes,
but it's essentially a parody of like what Joe and I do,
of - of a two guy discussing movies show.
It's - they're doing Cisco and Ebert.
The - bit - and it's a bit that you would think
would get run to the ground watching it for 15 hours,
but it doesn't.
It's just that Tim Heidecker is dumb.
He doesn't know much about movies.
You know, the thing Tim Heidecker does all the time,
but he's really good at it.
And I - I've - I've had it with Tim Heidecker.
I'll get into it.
I've got - I've had it.
All right.
Guys on fucking Twitter all day long preaching it everybody
on how to be a better human.
You - I don't see that.
On adult swim for five years, that's true.
Shut the fuck up.
That's true.
Oh, look, I'm doing a fake stand -up.
Oh, because you can't do real stand -up, Tim.
Fuck you.
I think it's a valid artistic pursuit to do a stand -up spoof.
It was very funny.
It is, but everything he does is a deconstruction.
It gets old after a while.
True.
Look, look, this guy talks funny, but he's a detective.
Oh, okay, Tim.
Thank you.
This is for you.
Would you say that about Andy Kaufman?
Joe, the great Andy Kaufman.
No, because Andy Kaufman had - had colors.
I think Tim Heidecker is very talented.
I - the high horse is - it's killing me.
I - I hear you.
I don't follow him so I don't know.
I don't know about him.
I had done follow.
I'm like, I can't do this anymore.
Anyway, go ahead.
The show is - Turkenteng knows every single thing about movies.
He's got this giant BHS collection
and he's kind of a success nerd.
Yes.
And Heidecker brings him on as like a guest
and quickly realizes that he needs him
because he knows nothing about movies.
It's really the only plot.
But these two have such a simmering hatred,
such a tension between them that goes on.
It often feels real.
Heidecker has an Asian wife that he keeps crying
about throughout the episodes.
That's kind of a running gag that goes on
and she's way too young for him.
He'll just start sobbing in the middle of an episode.
But I watch all 15 hours.
Next up, I'm going to do their Oscar special.
They do a long special every year with the Oscars.
I dug it.
You know, I think it's really creative and funny
and it's a testament to what you can do with $4,
which is a lot of his career.
I like The Tim Heidecker cooking show a lot
because I did think the movie show was funny
but I thought the cooking show took the movie show concept
and boiled it down to what you wanted
which was -
I haven't seen four minute episodes.
Right.
And it's him -
Shocking.
He can't cook.
But he thinks he can cook.
But it's funny.
Yeah.
It's funny.
I'm a fan.
I dug it.
It gave me so much needed to laugh.
I'm a fan too.
I just, you know, it's a little much sometimes.
That's all I'm saying.
I'll do one more and then we'll cut the edit.
I'll be fast.
Stranger Things finale slash Obi -Wan finale.
Can you not spell spoil stranger?
Oh, you're going to watch it.
I'm done one and a half.
And I don't know what hour of left of my life.
I tell you what, finish it and we'll just do the whole season.
All right.
As an episode.
Because I've spent 15 goddamn hours in my life watching it.
Yeah.
I'd like to get something out of it.
I'll just quickly do the Obi -Wan finale
and feel free to spoil.
I have not seen Obi -Wan and will not be watching.
You know what?
I'm not going to do the Obi -Wan finale
because I'm depressed about it.
Oh.
And Kathleen Kennedy and Disney are ruining...
I don't know if it's Kathleen Kennedy.
Disney's ruining Star Wars.
And it's just...
They're so lit.
It's just making me very sad at this point.
And there's moments of greatness and all of it.
But they're just making decisions that I don't understand with the plots.
They're making things more complicated than they need to be.
It's not rocket science guys.
There's blue prints out there.
It doesn't matter.
I'm going to get upset.
At the end of the day,
I ended up liking the Riva character.
I know when I first started talking about it.
I wasn't like a huge fan of the character.
I ended up liking her character at the end of the series,
which I predicted might happen.
I really enjoyed the Vader stuff with Hayden Christensen.
I really enjoyed the Obi -Wan stuff.
There just wasn't enough of it in a series called Obi -Wan,
which is crazy.
The final fight between Vader and Obi -Wan was pretty cool.
There were some great moments.
But again, they just dropped the ball in areas that it shouldn't have.
And...
I was going to just say what I'm completely perplexed by.
Oh, damn it.
It's just...
I don't know.
I can't help you.
I didn't say it.
It's fine.
Well, one thing they did that doesn't make any sense,
they do a flashback with like from the prequels,
but it's them now.
Like with the authors, it takes place in that time period.
And they do a flashback to the second prequel.
It's like, guys, they're older.
Like, do a flashback to like the Revenja, the Sith timeline.
Right.
So maybe it looks a little more...
And they don't de -ange them.
They believe creating...
So everything in the show is a special effect,
except the one thing they needed today.
Following a series, Boba Fett,
where they recreated a 20 -year -old Mark Hamill.
And I'm like, why aren't you just...
It's decisions like that.
I just don't understand.
Yeah, yeah.
I don't get it.
It doesn't make me excited for a second season.
Maybe they'll do the second season better than the first,
but the problem with Star Wars is this.
I said I wasn't going to root better.
Anyway, this would be my last one.
My problem with Star Wars is this.
And it's everybody.
That's why I didn't say Kathleen Kennedy.
It's a JJA.
I mean, it's a Disney.
Because JJ Abrams fell victim to it in the end.
Kathleen Kennedy is doing it.
Even Philone and Favaro, to an extent, are doing it.
It's either...
They're resting.
Everything was in the battle.
And everything knew.
They're building around the nostalgia.
Sucks.
And you don't need to do that.
You've got a literally universe of characters,
and stories, and planets, and environments.
With this fascinating mythology,
and the magic, and the force, and everything.
And they just keep trying to shove
new, not that interesting stuff into it.
And then they do nothing with the new,
not interesting stuff.
And it's pointless.
So for instance,
I didn't end up liking this Reba character.
But in the end, she turns good.
You're like, make her awesome.
Make just make her a villain that goes down with the ship.
But they're like, no, we can't kill her.
Because we might need her in the next season.
Every fucking thing.
It's a commiser,
like it's like a scrooge thing where he won't let go of any penny.
You know what I mean?
Because I, you know, I account for every penny.
I might need everything.
It's all mine.
It's like, let go of some shit.
You killed Han, fucking solo.
And you won't kill some of these secondary characters.
Because you're afraid you might need it's ridiculous, man.
It's fucking, it just sucks.
It's just sucks.
I did hear almost nothing positive about Obi -Wan.
And they keep, they've got this affinity for comedians.
Stop putting Bill Burr and Camille Nanjiani
and Horatio Sands and Amy Sideris into God dare Star Wars.
It's, they stick out like sore fucking thumbs.
Who is Amy Sideris blind?
You know, a fucking junk dealer that fixes ships or stuff like that.
Is he voicing it or just her?
No, it's her.
That's very strange.
And then because they clearly think
because, and how fucking sad is this one?
How sad is this?
Because they know that this disgusting,
fucking rotting American population we live amongst.
Can't watch a God damn TV show without looking at another device.
Yeah, right?
So they've done away with all of the alien language in Star Wars.
It's gone.
It used to be, and it was so fucking cool.
Like when I saw Return of the Jedi as a kid,
and Job of the Hut is speaking this is hot tease it's gone.
This language and there's subtitling it.
It's, it's awesome.
It's like this is a real guy.
Like this is happening.
They got rid of all that.
Why?
Because nobody can read while they watch the movie.
They have to look at their phone.
So now everybody in Star Wars just speaks perfect English.
And because everybody speaks perfect English,
and they're like, well, everybody can have an English accent,
which is what they've used to do that made it cool.
Right.
They're using like Boston accents and Southern accents in Star Wars.
So you'll see an alien with four heads be like,
y 'all get away from my ship now.
And you're like, what the fuck is this?
What the Jesus cock Christ is going on right now?
It's just terrible.
Fuck you, Disney.
Fuck off.
They got shut down that hotel they opened.
That's like three grand tonight.
The Star Wars hotel they just opened.
Why are they going to shut it down?
Where is it?
I think it's in Disneyland.
Oh, okay.
It was washed.
It sucks so bad.
And it's such a fucking joke.
And videos are getting out of the internet.
If people like going to the store going to be like,
look at this.
What is it?
It's a Star Wars experience hotel.
And it costs like three grand for two nights.
Okay.
And you stay in a room, a room, a space room,
the size of your fucking half bath room.
Uh -huh.
And you go and eat in a restaurant
that looks like you're in some time share presentation.
Except there's an alien bringing your dinner.
It's terrible.
They have to shut it down and bring consultants in.
Yeah.
Because they're like,
how did we botch this, this badly?
It's crazy.
Disney fucking sucks.
And for some reason,
they're nailing Marvel stuff from our,
I don't like it anymore.
Right.
Thank God, by the way,
all those reviews of Thor made me happy.
Yeah.
When people started being finally these critics are like,
between all the goddamn gags,
I can't take any of this seriously.
It's like, welcome to the fucking club.
My question would be why were you taking it seriously before?
If I may, you got to have stakes in a movie.
There has to be stakes.
And you can't have stakes when you're doing a fucking Chevy chase gag every three seconds.
The original Thor, I mean, that was almost like a slapstick romp from what I recall.
Not Thor, the, uh, the,
the last Thor, the last Tiger, what, yeah, that was ludicrous.
They said they up the comedy of this one.
Yeah, yeah.
That was a, that was a tough one.
I mean, the gags and that were like ancient.
They got Zeus being funny in this.
Russell Crowe as Zeus.
I saw some clip where he was like, uh, not so much or something like that.
I was like, why is he, what?
I'm not so much.
Even Paul Reiser doesn't do not so much anymore.
To see the, uh,
to see the George Carlin Mickey Mouse bit.
No, that's how I feel now about Disney.
George Carlin had a Mickey Mouse bit where he's like,
he's like complaining that they announced his birthday on the radio.
Uh -huh.
And then he's like, you know, no wonder this country's in the shitter.
We, we waste valuable airtime celebrating the birthday.
But imaginary wrote it.
And he, and he, at the time, this was like so bluntly,
I was like, you know, it's,
fuck Mickey Mouse.
Fuck him and his ass with a broken dildo.
I hope he dies.
I hope he goddamn dies with his hand in goofy's pants.
I'm a baseboard in a soiled bathroom in a poor neighborhood.
That's how I feel about Disney now.
I hate Mickey Mouse has always been the most boring cartoon character alive,
except for maybe Betty Boop, who at least was attractive.
Um, I hate Mickey.
I gotta tell you.
That whole crew, yeah, I could give a shit about any of them.
Totally agree.
Tell me you're going to watch a Donald Duck short against a Daffy Duck?
What are you nuts?
Daffy Duck is one billion times funnier.
And Bugs is five good,
Jillian times funnier than fucking Mickey.
Everyone's counterpart is way better in Looney Tunes.
Daffy Duck.
Daffy.
And you know, Sam, many say I'm in my opinion.
Yeah.
The funniest cartoon characters of all time.
Borgone Leghorn is good.
Borgone Leg?
They're all, they're all great.
I'm saying my two funniest of all times.
Yeah.
Tweety Silvestre.
I'm going to give Daffy the crown.
I'm going to give him the goat.
Yeah.
I mean, on his best day,
goofy couldn't hold a candle.
This guy, look, look, look.
That's his whole thing.
There's a, there's a one year range of people.
And that range is like people who were 10 when I was 15.
All those people love a goofy movie.
Just one shot up.
You highly a generation of people.
Many generation loves the goofy.
You also have follow that bird.
Oh, I love Philistine.
I saw Father Berwin.
I was five and I did love it.
John Candy's in it.
John Candy.
Chevy Chase.
Yeah.
It's the whole STB crew.
That's my old boss.
Yeah, it's the whole STB crew.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I just rewatched the trailer.
It's an entertainer.
Because I was like, I just remembered it from out of the blue.
And I was like, what's that movie about?
Yeah.
Definitely my first three movies.
And I'm not quite sure on the order.
We're American Tale, follow that bird.
And the re -release of ET all in 1985,
when I would have been four.
I can't believe they didn't make a portal
called an American Tale.
I'm sure they did.
We're a guy dressed as a rat.
Fucked women.
I'm sure they've done it.
Was an American tale.
Was the tale a play on the fact that he had a tale?
Or was it just straight up and down tail?
Oh, it's actually spelled T -A -I -L in the title.
Oh, it is.
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
Were you the one who was looking at that blu -ray over there?
I came home and it was facing out.
I wouldn't lay a finger on it.
I guess somebody else did.
Not for me.
Fible?
Fible goes west.
Fible goes west is great.
Jimmy Stewart's last role.
Look, I'm sure they're wholesome and strong animated films.
They might not hold up.
Who knows?
Let's get to our picture of the day,
which we haven't even mentioned yet.
The black phone.
You were singing a black phone song earlier,
because I had one in my head and you sang a different one.
Off my, I believe.
What was I singing?
Oh, you were singing Jenna Jackson's black phone,
baby, come back, number, black phone, baby, you want to die.
My head, in my head, before you started singing that,
I was going, black phone in it.
Solar sound.
You'd also do black phone in that little boy smile.
Oh, that's a good one.
I think we're going to disagree on this.
Oh, black phone, black, black, black, black,
black phone, black, black, I'll be going.
I think we're going to disagree on this.
Solar silent.
I think we've talked Solar silent.
Oh yeah, yeah.
I briefly liked them.
You know, I think I've said on this podcast,
one of the great shows of my teenage years
was Solar Silent and Jen Blossoms at Rib Fest.
St. Louis's Rib Fest.
A festival -sellering spare ribs?
Yeah, rib.
You can either buy them a la carte
or you can do what me and my buddies did,
which was by a $25 -all -day -all rib pass.
Well, what's hilarious is you and I at Rib Fest
for different different reasons.
You're there for the blossoms.
I'm there for the ribs.
We ate plenty of ribs.
We can have a good time.
Solar Silent, everybody says their pre -MTV success days were great
and they had kind of a replacement vibe going on.
Clearly they're influenced by them.
I like a couple of their albums.
I'm not going to lie.
I don't know them that well.
But let's talk about the black phone.
Based on a story by Joe Hill, who's a guy,
I just can't point to many really strong pieces of work
the man has his name on.
I'm sorry.
Well, but you're talking only adaptations.
Right, I haven't read any of his books.
I haven't read any of his books either.
I have one of his books.
Yeah.
Excuse me.
I have to point this out.
I just typed in black phone to bring up the Wikipedia.
And the very first question and people always also ask
is black phone a true story?
Oh my god.
Holy shit.
Well, if you haven't seen it and you only saw the trailer,
I could get that because it's a period piece.
It does look eerily.
It almost looks like the trailer makes it almost look like the lovely bones
or one of those kind of things.
That's correct.
Yes.
But it's a movie.
Not a good movie.
Takes place in the 70s.
Well, well, executed in that sense.
It does feel like the 70s.
Ethan Hawke plays a kidnapper named the grabber.
Several kids have disappeared.
Is he a pedophile or not?
Oh, I think that that's very much insinuated.
Why would they just not do it?
Because the studio probably said you can't do it.
But our rated film.
The studio.
I'm not saying like show the scenes.
I'm saying you sound aggravated.
You didn't get to see any action.
I'm just I was in an our rated like
and everyone's talking about how intense and scary this movie is.
I'm like, we don't even know what the guy's fucking motivation is in this thing.
Yeah, it's definitely insinuated in these pedophile at one point that
well, let's get let's let's back up.
Ethan Hawke is a kidnapper.
His they call him the grabber.
Yeah.
Kids are disappearing.
Our main character gets abducted.
We also learn that his sister has psychic dreams
and the kid that's abducted before the main character,
the little girl sister has had a dream about that.
That actually does have evidence in the dream that only the cops know.
This gets revealed to the cops somehow and the cops actually start to go to the sister
to get help in finding her own brother.
That is obstructed by the fact that their father is an alcoholic.
You find out that the mother had these visions too and I think killed herself.
So the father is in the depths of alcoholism and is abusive to the kids physically.
Not sexually, but you know hits them.
Because he doesn't he can't handle everything going on and he takes it out in a terrible way on
the kids and he forbades this girl from having these dreams or exploring them.
So she has to sort of secretly figure this out.
The mystery on her own and meanwhile that's cross -cut with the experience of her brother
in the grasp of Ethan Hawke who wears a terrifying mask.
Good math.
That looks almost like a v for vendetta, but scary.
And a little Donnie Darko in there.
And he starts hat there's a phone that's not hooked up in the room he's being kept in.
That rings and when it rings and he answers it the previous kids who have been abducted and killed
by Ethan Hawke give him clues on how to escape and he has to so everybody's kind of building their
own case on how to solve the crime here and get you know get this kid to freedom and that's basically
the plot of the movie.
You know that's it.
Yeah I mean really as soon as I realized this was a ghost story I checked out.
Why though?
I kind of liked that I excited me.
I just wasn't that cool.
We get so few of these kind of thrillers and look a big part of my issue with it might be that I
was expecting a great prisoner's style thriller not that I was expecting anything on that level.
I knew what I was getting but I just the my biggest issue really is just that it felt so soft.
You know and it wasn't scary to me and I didn't like the story and I didn't like the ghost stuff.
I can't say I was bored really I can't say I was like was dying for at the end or that I hated it.
I just called an average horror film and that's about as far as I can go with it.
It didn't do much for me and I don't know why I didn't think it was a grand slam.
I thought it was a very solid piece of work.
I thought it wasn't I thought it was intriguing.
Yes.
I was rooting for the kid.
I was scared for his safety throughout the movie.
I thought Ethan Hawk was fantastic.
Always like a hawk.
I liked the plot device that Ethan Hawk's brother was living with him temporarily
and was actually on the his was like a conspiracy theory guy that was trying to solve the case
and to realize it was happening underneath his feet.
Yeah and that guy was good.
James Ransom I like that guy.
He's a little big I would say but he was good.
He's always big.
He's like he's doing they did sinister together.
He's good seeing them together.
Oh well he played that role almost like a cartoon if I remember correct.
Yeah so I liked it.
I thought it was well plotted.
I thought it was well executed.
Um and you know there's there's not a ton to say about the movie.
It's I understand where you're coming from.
If I went into this thinking I was going to get a prisoner's type of film.
I would have been very disappointed.
I went into it thinking I was going to get a blown house well film
and was like that was good.
I think it is blown house.
It is yeah well they co -produced which probably means it was over five million so they couldn't do it.
So it did have it had teeth.
Uh you know especially in this day and age to do a movie about kids that got abducted
and killed you know it had teeth which is why again I think they they probably reeled back
on the pedophilia stuff and it's situated it because they were like guys it's it's really sensitive territory already.
I guess in room was he fucking the kids mom in room?
I guess all room.
Room is oh boy especially the first half hour room is so fucking good.
But um I don't remember I don't remember who was fucking the mom or not.
He wasn't fucking the kid.
But I'll say this.
Uh can you know like like you know like number in Elm Street for instance.
Yeah.
The original.
The pedophilia is only implied in that.
So it didn't you know I was like I get it yeah.
And they they implied it that that scene it got an audible crowd grown in the theater.
When uh when he goes what when he wakes up and you and you and you're
regret or sorry Ethan Hawke is sitting there like squatting staring at him.
Uh huh.
He's like what are you doing down here and he's like I'm just looking at you.
Right.
The whole theater was like oh god yeah um this was also the first time I'd seen a movie in a
full this was the experience I had when I said I go to the movies excited in 15 minutes and I'm
furious uh huh.
I will say this the audience as the movie went when I saw it it was pretty full.
Slowly turned and put their attention on the movie which gave me hope for people.
Yeah uh and by the end of it it's like it's become like concerts now.
Movies have to win over people.
Yeah yeah or they'll just start talking.
Yeah by the end of it people were like sort of cheering and like you know
there was one thing that really made me laugh there was there was two black guys in front of me
and when the kid goes do not go up the stairs it's a trap uh huh because he wants to play this game
called bad boy or bad daddy whatever the fuck it was called.
Right and then the kid goes up the stairs this black guy goes
typical white people shit
and he wasn't trying to make his friend laugh he was he was a hundred percent
earnest.
Yeah so like I had not a movie experience like that in a while where like people were like
actually getting into it and uh and like I said roading cheering so that was fun that was
fun uh and again I really like when when the kid escapes and like almost makes it and then like
Ethan hot catches him again I was like god damn like yeah you know I my I was invested I was
invested and I was I thought it was beautiful at the end when the dad literally kneels before
the two kids and he's so happy that his son is found and he's like I'm so sorry
yeah crying you know it it you know look if we talk of course we're not going to love it as much as
poltergeist that's a classic for our child but I would say if you put this up against a poltergeist
just from unseen to either to see both of us kind of I see structurally an integrity wise these
are pretty even films you know that's it's insane wow I would call poltergeist my favorite horror
movie of all time so I completely disagree but you're but you're but you're that's I think that's
an insane state I watch it every year and I my my love doesn't diminish that's fine but I love that
that it ends and then has a second it better ending I love everything about my listen poltergeist is
good would but you got to take out of it your personal love for it for a second what I'm saying is
I'll never agree with you but you can say what you think I'm not going to agree with it what I'm
saying is yes the first of all there's it's hard to find a similar movie mm -hmm
they're cut from similar cloth in the sense of there's actual threat there's kids it's not all bubble
gum and whatever right it's a ghost story but it's a family story it's this is hard this is a
hard subgenre to figure out here come to find a lot of candidates for I would say what at its
core poltergeist is a haunted house move say good and its core poltergeist is a haunted house move and it's
core that's what this kind of is right to go story kids we're seeing this differently
my kids in a basement and there's a phone where dead children talk to him right my point is
the black phone in the basement like why wouldn't Ethan Hawk remove that phone why is there a phone
a pay phone I believe if you're going to lock a child in your basement would you leave a phone in
the room it's not connected oh it's a dead phone yeah he says that is he this is what concerns me when
you have an opinion like this on the movie I feel you miss this is one tiny detail one tiny that's
a huge that's a huge detail in the movie Ethan Hawk says to him the phone rings but don't answer it
because it's ringing because of static energy down here it's not connected to anything and he picked
and then Ethan Hawk catches him on it and screams him and then later the kid goes he can hear the
phone and he knows we can talk to you that's a huge why are you not removing the phone why do you
leave the phone you know I that's my question I feel like this was well written enough that if I
went back and watched it again I would go oh because that's there with there's a reason for it but
my point is I didn't see this on a very tense date yeah but I it wasn't it wasn't it wasn't
but I didn't wind up missing anything well I'm according to your date who was sitting there
watching it who was tense and god only knows but I I texted you what's happening I'm going to the
bathroom thinking I'd miss something but I came in before the credits were done I didn't miss anything
yeah that's not possible but but because I sat and watched the beginning of the movie
went to the bathroom when the credits started and made it back in time okay I swear there was nothing
missed okay so anyway anyway I put it back to my poltergeist point yes there are very few horror
movies that you could say it's sort of family appropriate there are ghosts there's an emotional
dynamic there's a lot they they I would say these sort of fall into a similar subgenre of horror
and I would say if I saw both for the first time ever I like poltergeist more but I'd say quality
wise this is not like this is not like oh my god well it's terrible it's it's a solid movie it's a
solid movie whether it's for you or not I think is where the I don't disagree that it's solid I don't
follow the poltergeist comparison and I think poltergeist is a million times better what reminded me of
a little was stir of echoes which is the dead person trying to help except this was good case stir of
echoes ten times better you're nuts Pat I've seen stir of echoes 15 times there's something wrong it's
it's no joke it's a difference of opinion how do you not get this at this point I love stir of
echo I thought this movie was as you said solid that we're talking about poltergeists is nonsense to
me no it's a different opinion how do you not get this at this point but tell me compare it takes
stir of echoes and poltergeists off the table all right tell me another movie that focuses on
kids you know what scary stories tell the dark yeah I'd say this is about comparable to that movie I
thought that was better than this but you're all over the place I'm not I like this a lot so then you
think scary stories tell the dark is comparable to poltergeist and an equal entertainment I don't think
poltergeist is anywhere near as good as you do I think that there's a huge nostalgia factor with it
I do not watch it once a year I think it's a I think it's a good movie and I enjoy it and I consider it
one of the classics but if you gave me a you got to pick 20 and that's all you get for the rest of your
life and and you said it's all got to be hard poltergeist probably wouldn't even hit the 20 and that's
my number one so I you know obviously I'm not hearing this argument but that you like it look
you've got more of a Spielberg e thing to you than I do I think not in the last 25 years but you know
what I mean my date also said that her favorite horror movie of all time she's a big horror buff
oh yeah lovely bones and I just I honestly didn't say a big horror buff yeah what else is she
she didn't say anything stranger things this is the woman that was filling you in on what you didn't miss
Joe she and I had our issues but when you ask somebody did I miss anything and she says no and then
the directed by credit comes up I figure I didn't miss anything all right
Sarah Christ Sarah what what's the matter what's the matter now it's it's praying it's uh oh
what oh stomach thing there for a second okay um I I would give a hog up to the black phone
yeah my hug is straight out it feels and not it not erect it's uh it's resting atop the balls but it's not
like crawling into itself or something so um why didn't this school and eva right movies in this way
maybe they would have had worse if you remember you were very against it oh against what you didn't know
the hog when I started saying the hog thing when I started saying welcome to the hog house you were
like right I don't want to do this the hog bit how hard a movie makes you dick I like that no I do I don't
like when you used to go the how long has oh my oh my oh that made me sick you like the hog bit now you
did not like it as the boner bit maybe somebody can go back and tell me but I think the only time I had
an issue was when Joe had a southern accent and would Emily Florence is the reason
and she got behind the hog house bit and then fans started going forward and saying I like the hog house
yes yeah but anyway I'm gonna bring that back I forgot about that
that's fine how to do it welcome to the hog house oh my god listen I'm gonna show it to Sui in there
I don't Sui and like kind of a motel hell vibe Sui always strikes me as what a guy would say before he
fucks a pig sure sure but that's not what it's meant for I don't know why Sui calls pigs but I can
Google it if you want to really bring this thing to a strange close Sui definition a dish prepared
oh that's not it a dish Sui pig definition god damn it Sui is a pig call in northeast England
as is guess guess all right fine
so I mean one of us needs to talk here to end the show Joe I just want to I just want to point out
that I just got the thing the meeting ends in 10 minutes again which reminds me
there's going to point out that Pat legitimately asked the question when we were restarting
your zoom wouldn't be acting differently because you're in LA right
what was that a dumb question yeah I said it's an insane question I said your internet it's an app
I said your zoom wouldn't be doing that because you're in LA right because what other explanation
could there be oh several several several darling several that's that's nowhere near use we use a
zoom every week when we record yes and now it doesn't work when you're here what's the very
important L .A. Pat your app does an app doesn't act differently because you're in LA that's that was
my point it wouldn't happen because you're in LA right it wasn't a question it was no there surely
this couldn't be it so what is it no it isn't well it's a quite it's that wouldn't even enter
my that that would be like that would be like I like I wouldn't say it couldn't be the chain saw
interference right I wouldn't even say it because it's there's no way come on it's funny I'm breaking
your stones a little bit right I said I was going to bring it onto this show and you laughed and now
you're getting I thought you were going to bring on how annoyed you were with zoom I thought we
are on the same team we are we are I am annoyed with zoom you heard me curse zoom it was funny come
on it's funny because the gag is you have tech issues yeah by the way I feel like Jordan peel will
have a movie called zoom in the next two or three years doesn't seem like he's heading towards something
called zoom by the way how many reviews have you seen yep it's a yep for peels no I'll throw this
mug at you right now and it's not your fault uh we are by the way going to see nope if not tomorrow
we'll be doing it on the pod shortly so go out and check it out next for your local cinema episode
coming up definitely is a very special episode with Dana Gould as our guest we're going to have a
talk around with Dana for a for an hour or so and uh and that'll be coming up next so we'll see you
then thanks for listening everybody joey roses NYC dot com for all the joey roses info joderosa info
dot com for all my ticket sales and show information come out and see me come out and see us at the bar
either way uh and then joderosa comedy instagram and twitter the padrock wash instagram and twitter
you can hear me on lizard gooperman's in your hands podcast with my old friend caraclanque
you can watch the miss patch show when it premieres on beets he plus on august 11th the
Emmy nominated miss patch show for best comedy direction which is very exciting and that's about all I
got i uh love you all we will see you next time and we will see you in hell