Folks, we'll see you in hell back again to talk about
a movie called Talk to Me. We couldn't figure out if this was from New Zealand
or Australia, and I gotta tell you, do we even need to? I'm a little tired of the
Australia, New Zealand, who cares? Same place. Talk to me is from Australia.
Okay. Can we just put that to bed? Yeah. To me, it's like saying, like, is it from
the States or Canada? Like, who cares? Right. Um, for a screen man, and I just saw between
between recordings here. Jada Pinkett Smith says she and Will have been separated for seven years.
She thought the Oscar slap was a skit. Okay, Jada. She's the worst person on Earth.
They've been separated for seven years. And they're like, why wouldn't you divorce? She's like,
I made a promise to him and I just can't see myself going back on. What? You've got a man
throwing away his career as one of the biggest stars in Hollywood to defend your name
and your haven't been together in seven years because you made a promise? She sucks.
By the way, Will's no walk in the park. Uh, yeah, but I mean, I'm taking her over. I'm taking
nuts. Also, there's an article here that says cheers to Roz Doyle, one of the most progressive
women to ever grace a sitcom. Does everything have to be this, you know, does everything have
to be there? Um, Joe, what's going on? You're settling into the new house. What are you going
to be by coastal? If you consider, uh, the Hudson river, one of the coasts to paraphrase, waiting
basically that kind of thing. Uh, I'm not, uh, I'm having a dishwasher problem. Uh,
this is my first issue in the house. I've been here for about a week. It's been smooth sailing
so far, but today was the first day I used the dishwasher. Cause I finally got like my utensils
and glasses and stuff in the mail. And I've run it twice now and twice. Now the pod is not
dispensing or dissolving properly. Um, and I don't know what the hell is going on. Something's
wrong and I got to figure it out and I'm sure it will be fine, but I am an anxious mess over
it now. I'm already a disastrous mess. Well, first, let me just say how much I appreciate
hearing the story about how the dishwasher doesn't work twice in five minutes. Cause it
is a really good one. I heard it pre -taping. I'm hearing it post. Um, no, the previous owners of
the house will definitely probably leave you with a couple of little surprises, things that don't
work that they didn't tell you about. It's a little annoying part of buying a home. Um, and if your
pretty minor in the grand scheme of things, it's a new appliance. So something's not right. They
put in brand new appliances, uh, which is very nice, but, and they also, they've been, they were
very adamant about it being a smooth transition. There was a hiccup with the furnace and they just
replaced the furnace as at no cost to me. They were like, we just want this. So everything has
I peeled, I peeled like the plastic thing off the dishwasher control panel today. It's a,
clearly a new device. It's just, something's not right. Like the temp isn't getting hot enough or
I don't know what the hell is going on. Also, when you set it to normal, it says that the cycle is
two hours and 40 minutes. Like something's not right. No, I, I, I do some tweaks. So I don't know.
I'm sure it'll be, like I said, I'm sure it'll be fine. And you bought the, uh, the Amityville
horror house, correct? Uh, yes. Yes. You just thought you'd roll the dice on it? Which is weird
cause it's in Pennsylvania. Somehow they moved it here. Uh huh. My mom today goes, where is
Amityville? New York? Yeah, New York. Oh, okay. Sorry. I thought my mom today goes, uh, she's,
she's standing over my sink and she looks at the dishwashing soap I have and she goes, get rid of
this is crap. Get good dishwashing soap. And I go, that's the soap that you gave me. She goes, oh,
of course doesn't address it or take any responsibility for any of it. Just brushes
it off and moves on to her next offense. Anyway, uh, just like Will Smith said before that famous
slap, you know, parents just don't understand. Um, let's go to that, let's go to that MC. Um,
oh, already. All right, let's do it. You know, I would love to talk about, uh, a really
good, interesting, low budget indie that just came out on Netflix called Fair Play. Um,
this could be in the Oscar consideration. My guess is that it's a little too below the radar
too, but it's a really, really well acted, um, movie that, you know, this would have been
Michael Douglas and, you know, Sharon Stone in 1999. But now it is that guy that, that was in,
um, solo Alden Ehrenreich, the guy that played young Han Solo from hail Caesar and then Phoebe
Denevor from game of Thrones, who I was not particularly familiar with or Bridgerton. She's
not even on game of Thrones. I thought every young British actress was on game of thrones,
but she was actually on Bridgerton. Uh, and then Eddie Mars on who was just kind of a good British
character actor, but it feels a lot like, um, it was written and directed by Chloe Domont,
but it's got a feeling of those movies like a disclosure or just where it creates a really
interesting interpersonal dilemma, a sexual kind of dilemma and explores it like a thriller. And
is basically a young, hot couple at a, um, you know, a New York kind of wall street type firm.
The guy thinks he's about to get promoted, but instead they promote the gal and he starts to
unravel. He can't handle it. He can't handle his woman being more powerful than him and being his
boss. And he starts acting out. He stops being able to perform sexually. It starts getting into
his head and, um, it's really dark, interesting stuff. And then it becomes darker and darker
as it goes a lot of twists, a lot of turns. If I had a grievance about it is that I think it
goes a little too far, a little off the rails in the end. And I think it tries to, it tries to have
too many twists at the expense of what its characters might really do. That said, it's very,
well -written and very well acted. I love this Alden, her Jesus Christ, Aaron Reich guy.
And, um, I'm glad he's hanging in there. Cause after a couple of bombs that he had in a row,
usually they'll just kind of send you back home, but he's a really good actor. And I had never seen
Phoebe Denevor, but she's great too. I really recommend it. Fair play Joe.
Oh, you can, excuse me. You can do three in a row. Cause I'm going to actually read.
I'm going to read a read. All right. I'm going to read a read. I just realized it's the same.
Oh, a Rex read. Okay. I got you. I got a, I got a review here from this, from this guy that, that
the title alone, I don't even know the movie. Yeah. Title of this thing alone. I'm like,
Holy Jesus Christ. All right. I'm intrigued. Um, I saw,
you know what I rewatched? Joe was a movie you and me saw a movie that we did not like.
And I wanted to give it another chance because so many people in the last 10 ish years have
told me what I'm I've heard the word masterpiece used about the movie spy starring Melissa McCarthy.
Oh, for God's sakes. Um, and I'm, look, I'm a huge McCarthy fan. I'm a huge bridesmaid fan.
I like the people in the movie. I like the supporting cast. And I saw it sitting there on
Amazon prime or something. I was like, you know what? I'm going to give it another shot.
And I felt exactly how I felt about it. The first time the amount of you look like X,
you smell like X, you, the, the amount of those jokes that are in this movie is, is appalling.
It's like they kept in every single alt that was pitched on set and it just gets to be a tonnage
of this stuff. You know, I can't laugh at you smell like a fish who raped, uh, uh, you know,
whatever. It's like, all right guys, like how many obscure new combinations of words can we come up
with, um, to avoid the fact that this is not a very entertaining story. Uh, I didn't hate it.
Melissa McCarthy is very charming. I like some jokes in the movie are funny. The fact that she
keeps her, all of her aliases and disguises are increasingly like dowdy, um, kind of cat lady type
women is funny. There's funny bits in it. I think Paul Feig is a guy who knows comedy and has done
great things. I just, to me, this was, uh, kind of a dud even on a second viewing. I gotta say,
I don't get the love for spy. Uh, it's cause it's not good. It might because it's not good.
Um, and then I would love to shout out, um, a pretty entertaining three -part documentary
that's on HBO Max called telemarketers. Um, it is produced by the uncut gems guy,
the Safdie brothers, and I had heard it compared to American movie, which is kind of one of the
great documentaries, um, about these two kind of misfit guys who try to make an independent film.
I highly recommend it if you haven't seen it. So, and a horror movie too. Have you seen the movie,
Joe? American movie? Yeah. Great. Yeah. It's great. Um, what happened to those guys?
I think they made another movie and, um, you know, people made fun of it and, and that's it,
but, you know, I don't think they like took Hollywood by storm or anything. Um, telemarketers
is about the eighties, the early days of telemarketing at a city, New Jersey call center.
Um, and they have just all kinds of footage early cam quarter, like your dad would take
at a birthday party footage of almost like a Wolf of wall street type world of just debauchery
and insanity in the telemarketing world of the eighties in New Jersey. Um, and these people were
absolute scumbags. They were lying to innocent people and widows and et cetera, and telling them
that their donations, you know, 95 % of your donation will go to the retired police officers
fund and then just pocketing all of the money. So it was a very long -term grift.
The most fascinating aspect of this movie is they interview probably 50 people, mostly men
living in New Jersey now who spent their eighties and nineties doing this and ripping people off
and every single interview. They must have, once they realized this was happening,
they must've known they had gold. Every single interview, the subject is drinking a giant amount
of alcohol and it is so troubling because you know that they have to live with it. And you know,
a lot of them at the time were like, you know, I had to make money and they make excuses for it
and so forth. And you don't hate these people, you know, people got to make money. And I think
they turned their heads a lot of time and some people genuinely didn't know, but it's pretty
fucked up what happened and the people are not doing well coping with it. So these two guys want
a real pill head who's like sober now and his friend set out with Michael Moore as their cited
inspiration and go to like expose this world of telemarketers that used to be their employers.
So I'm probably making it sound a little more fascinating than it is. I think this would have
been much better as a traditional two hour documentary, which is the case for most of these
multi -part documentary series these days, but it's really interesting and a lot of great
characters. If you like a documentary about like weird people doing weird shit and scandal and so
I recommend it. All right. Yes.
So Rex Reed has reviewed this film called foe starring.
F -A -U -X?
No, F -O -E. Starring however the hell you say her first name, Ronan Ladybird,
Swashwas, Swastika Ronan. How do you say it?
Shorsha Ronan. I actually love her. I really love Brooklyn. I love that movie.
She's a great actor.
Here's the lead. This is the headline. Ready?
Foe is a one -star deadly boar rambling heap of junk.
My God, Rex. Come on buddy, lube it up a little bit.
He starts with one door opens, another door closes or strike that reverse it. No sooner did I sign
off on the unexpected cornucopia of riches that compromised two weeks of the Toronto
International Film Festival when two weeks of the smaller elitist New York Film Festival began in
far fewer films of any real interest are ever shown at this rarefied event.
So he didn't get an invite translation.
And they mostly interest only the people who financed them in the first place.
This year they surprised me with only one genuine masterpiece maestro Bradley
Cooper's rich luxurious and breathtaking biopic about Leonard Bernstein.
I hear it's great.
The spectacular star turned by Carey Mulligan as the bisexual genius conductor,
composer's tortured wife, Felicia.
But several worthy and rewarding supplements worth noting, highly recommended.
He starts this thing by pointing out the movies that he thought were good.
This is the beginning of his review of another movie.
Okay.
He goes on and on about the movies he liked.
Paragraph break.
On the dark side of the coin, there was unfortunately a hateful and pretentious
load of pornography called Poor Things that trashes the career of Emma Stone
and a deadly bore called Foe about a disintegrating marriage in some bizarre futuristic world
in the year 2065, plagued by catastrophic droughts, AI and bad acting.
It just opened commercially to a firing squad of bad reviews.
So here goes.
Wow.
Gives us one out of four stars.
He's now trashed two movies, which he's not reviewing here.
Now here's what's wild to me.
I'll read more of the review, but I looked up this movie
because I'd never heard of it, but he's talking about how it's playing at this
earnest little festival that nobody goes to except the people that funded the movies.
I'm on the Wikipedia page for Foe.
Under the release section, Amazon Studios entered negotiations for
distribution rights in July of 2021.
This is where we're at with independent cinema.
Amazon.
This is where we're at.
This is indie cinema.
Okay.
Anyway, here's his review.
A married couple named Hen and Junior live in a 200 -year -old farmhouse in a once productive
Midwest farming community now ravaged by scorched land, depleted crops, and people
replaced with robots created by artificial intelligence.
Junior works in an industrial chicken plant.
I kid you not.
He writes.
Hen works in a...
That's weird.
Her name's Hen.
Works in a diner, but mostly she just sits around moping
and stands naked in the shower crying her eyes out.
They are played by Irish hunk, Paul Mescal, and the charming resourceful
S. Ronan.
I still can't remember how to say it.
And whoever convinced them to appear in this paralyzing fiasco
should be placed under house arrest.
Water is a valuable commodity and it must be conserved in the limited
amount of time left before the planet ceases to exist.
Nobody has any water to drink, but Hen and Junior are always
quirking an endless supply of Cabernet Sauvignon.
He goes on and on about the plot.
They endlessly debate the fate of the world.
The talk is dull and repetitive, but in the hope of keeping the audience
from snoring, there is plenty of nudity.
After a year painfully passes, the stranger returns.
All right.
Care something about a spaceship.
Here we go.
The movie does sound insane.
I'll grant you that.
He writes, there is no ending, but before it fades to black,
Junior is cloned and now there are two of him,
but you never know which one is the original Junior and which is the robot.
While Hen opens another Cabernet, the two Juniors sink into an
inconclusive bout of head -scratching yammering.
Eventually it left turns into a new romance between Hen, Junior, and the Replicant.
So they're having a three -way with the clone.
Okay.
By this time, I could no longer keep my eyes open,
so I haven't had a clue about what happens next,
but I do not intend to see it again to find out.
This is a paid critic.
Faux is sitting on a pretty low, it's got a 19%.
I hate Rotten Tomatoes, but it's got a low, low, low rating.
The title of Faux makes no sense and neither does anything else in this rambling heap of junk.
The actors deserve a medal for babbling so much convoluted clap track with a straight face.
It is a colossal nightmare.
Oh my God.
I mean, it's like he's being tortured sometimes.
I love this, man.
God, I want to meet Rex Reed.
Jesus.
You're in the same city, make it happen.
I bet flattery has got to be the key.
You got to tell him you're his biggest fan.
You want to interview him or something.
I don't think there's a doubt that in the world that I am the biggest Rex Reed fan alive.
He might be.
I have both books that he wrote, courtesy of Matt McCarthy.
Are they all this bitchy or did he become that way over time?
No, they're more celebratory.
They're books.
He wrote them in like the 60s or 70s, but no, they're not like that.
I don't think he was this and I don't remember him being this
embittered when I was a kid in the 80s.
I remember him being like sassy, but like I don't remember him being like,
I mean, he's not wrong.
The movies he shits on, he's usually pretty right.
Like they suck.
Seemed to be this violent back in the day.
This angry for sure.
Anyway, Talk To Me is an Australian horror movie directed by Danny and Michael
Philippu.
It is about a group of teenagers who come into possession of a dismembered hand.
And this hand, when you shake it and say, talk to me,
you basically invite a spirit from the afterlife into this world.
Once you say then your second sentence, which is, what is it, Joe?
Come on in.
I let you in.
Yeah.
Come on.
Doors open, you know, something like that.
But that is the general premise.
Despite it being Australian, it felt to me almost like that great run of dimension horror
in and around the scream era, where it's basically, aside from the occasional parent
character, it's basically just a horror movie populated entirely by teenagers.
And, you know, the movie's got a really young spirit.
You know, it's like young and fun and creative and exciting.
And everything that the other movie we talked about this week is not the exorcist believer.
This movie cost almost nothing.
It uses almost entirely practical effects and makeup, really, really excellent makeup,
especially for a low budget movie.
And it just, with so much less in terms of resources, it does so much more in terms of
being scary, in terms of being compelling, in terms of creating characters we care about.
Um, in terms of, you know, we talked about in this exorcist episode, how that movie Joe said
had no rules.
You know, Gremlins is the perfect example of a movie that establishes its, its rules
and follows them.
Exorcist did not do that.
Talk to me, does a beautiful job of that and not making it feel like you're being hit over
the head.
They're like, it's that great, you know, it's like an urban legend.
They're like, Hey, we found this hand.
We bought it off some guy.
Here's what he told us about it.
Here's what we know.
Here are the rules.
The spirit can only stay in our realm for 90 seconds.
Anytime past that, they fully come into our world and that can be dangerous and scary.
So you've got to get them back before that time happens.
And it's always clear.
The only thing that wasn't clear.
I watched the movie once in the theater and then again at home with subtitles.
The only thing that wasn't clear to me was the accents.
So I would recommend subtitles on it.
But, um, beyond that, you know, it's not perfect, but I think this is just a really
great little horror movie and whatever these guys do next, whether they do the next evil
dead or whatever it may be, I'm sure they're, they're in talks right now.
I know they're doing a sequel to this movie, but I'm sure they'll do so.
They are.
I didn't know that.
I'm sure they'll do some big horror franchise next and, um, they deserve it.
You know, so often these people get bumped up and you're like, what the fuck?
But I mean, these guys made a really great, uh, low budget horror movie that scared me
worked, worked like a charm.
I thought it was great.
The, uh, so yes, they do do a very good job of establishing the rules.
I want to speak to that first because, uh, I'm gonna stick with for it.
The only thing I didn't catch and I had to read on Wikipedia is, was the time limit rule.
So if you say, let me in, or I let you in, the demon possesses you, right?
But if it goes, if the possession goes past 90 seconds, it's, uh, bad, you know, bad things
can happen and sort of ambiguous.
And I didn't quite catch that, but that is the case.
And the reason it goes bad for our main character is because she lets a demon, or not a demon,
but the ghost of a dead person.
It's always the ghost of somebody who horrifically murdered with her stay in her body for too long.
Um, and because she does that, I guess the door to the other side is sort of open
and it eventually leads to her seeing the spirit of her dead mother, uh, who was sort
of guiding her and giving her messages from the other side.
Now in another comparison to The Exorcist, this is yet another thing that this movie does
outstandingly that The Exorcist completely fails at, which is establishing the relationship
between a daughter and her deceased mother and why you should give a shit.
And for all The Exorcist does in actually showing you the mother before she dies and
showing you how she dies and then creating a fairly absurd scenario where the father
has to choose between saving the mother and the baby.
I didn't, I don't even know if that's a thing that can, maybe it is, I don't know.
But anyway, um, this movie, you never meet the mother until you meet her ghost and you
know from the jump, just through the writing and the directing and the acting, how much
this girl's mother means to her and how hard the loss of the mother has been for her and
the strain that that loss has put on her family or on her relationship with her and her father.
Anyway, and taking that two minutes, uh, makes all the difference in how much you care and
to everything that happens in a movie. And it's that two minutes or five minutes or 15 minutes
that is just glossed over more and more, uh, in the interest of let's get to a big scare
immediately. Let's get, you know, this movie does, you know, wisely kick off with a big crazy, um,
scare or shock, um, before, before settling in a little bit and telling you about its characters.
I'm not saying you can't do that, but you gotta spend that time getting to know people before
you start picking them off. You know, other, it's the difference between an okay movie and a great
movie every time. I was worried at the beginning of this, um, party scene. Yeah. It's so the movie
opens with a big party, kids, the high school party, but I think, uh, because the kid's mom is there
like cutting vegetable vegetables to serve the kids. It's odd detail, but,
uh, a kid shows up to a party. The mom of the, of the kid who, whose house it is, is like,
says to this other kid who showed up, your brother is, get your brother out of the bedroom. He's
being weird or whatever. The kid goes in to see what's going on with his brother. His brother's
acting really odd. His brother then stabs his own brother in the stomach and then kills himself.
And then it cuts to the title screen. Now, admittedly, when I saw this cold open, I was like,
Oh Christ, here we go. All right. Oh, it's the thing that gets in your body and makes you kill
people. And then you kill yourself. This is a smile. It's going to be whatever it's another one
of these. And it, and it wasn't, um, it wasn't at all. Um, it wasn't, that's not like a routine
thing that the demon does. The demon does when it gets in you or one of these spirits gets in you.
You find out later in the movie, they're basically tortured souls. And I don't really remember why
or fully even understand why they want to get in living people and, and cause those living people
to hurt themselves, but they do for whatever reason. Um, and I think, I think your classic,
they're mad about being dead, you know, something like that, right? They're malevolent spirits.
Yeah. So there's a kid brother of the main. So there's the main character and then there's
her best friend and the best friend is a kid brother. The kid brother wants to try the hand
thing. Uh, his sister says no, and she storms out of the room. The kid then begs the friend
to let her do it. She says, okay. And lo and behold, the kid does it and he gets possessed
by who? The spirit of her dead mother. And she lets it go on for too long, the possession,
cause she's so obsessed with talking to her mother and the kid goes way over time and starts to
violently harm himself in a very interesting way where he's slamming his head into the,
it's kind of like the thing in hereditary, but it's more graphic. He's just slamming his head
like the desk and cuts it. He like squishes his own eye or something. Uh, anyway, he ends up
in like critical condition in the hospital and he still has this thing inside of him.
And the plot of the movie becomes about the main girl trying to redeem herself with the guilt she
has for letting this kid get, get into this place through her own selfishness to talk to her mother.
She has to save him or figure out a way to save him. Meanwhile, because she also left the door
open for too long to the other side, as I said, her mother's spirit is now appearing to her and
kind of guiding her on how to save this kid. Um, and you know, spoiler alert, uh, when,
when you get to the climactic moment of the movie where the mother is telling this girl,
you have to kill him. That's the only way to free him. You realize in the very last moment
that the mother is not in fact, the mother, she's a malevolent spirit who is deceiving this girl.
And the girl then, instead of throwing this kid into traffic to kill and save him,
throws herself into traffic and, uh, she wakes up, she's in the hospital. It's a very dreamlike
sequence. And all of a sudden the lights go out. She approaches a table, uh, a candle is lit because
they always light a candle in the ceremony. And you see a kid you've never seen before sitting at
the table. And he says to the girl, I let you in. And you realize, Oh my God, she's dead. And now
she's appearing in the game to somebody else. It's a really real, I think, I think I explained that
properly, but it's an awesome ending that for once in one of these fucking movies, they earned,
you know, everything that leads up to it makes sense. So it's very, very satisfying. Like she's,
uh, going through all this stuff in the end of the movie. And at first, like with fair play,
I was kind of like, Oh shit, I think this is going to try to do too much. It's going to try to have
too many twists and in the process stop being effective. But because everything is explained
beautifully, you follow it and it makes sense. So all these twists and turns that take place,
you're there with them. You're following them. You're feeling them on an emotional level. That's
where this movie succeeds while so many others do not, especially modern horror movies.
Now, what do you think the, I'm surprised to hear of a sequel. I mean, it was a big,
this was a big success. And by the way, so, so I'm not surprised in the sense that this movie was
successful. So usually they try to make a sequel. I'm curious what a sequel would be though. Yeah,
I don't know. Outside of more of the same, unless, you know, I don't know, maybe it's this girl now
trying to help other people from the other side. And my assumption is it would drop the girl and
new people find the hand, but I, but I don't know. Um, her trying to get back would be cool though.
So that was kind of the vibe of, of one of the Poltergeist sequels, I think. Uh, well they show
at one point, like she's able to see like temporarily she's when she's still alive,
she's able to go into the other side and see like what's happening to a human who's still alive,
who's being tortured by these souls. And it's really fucking creepy. There's that old man.
Yeah. Remember the old man like who, who's like rotting and he's like on the bed cackling and
shit. Like that guy was really scary, man. Yeah. That stuff, you know, it reminded me of kind of
it follows, um, which was one of the, you know, Hereditary did it too. It's a use of like naked
old people to kind of shock you. But, um, yeah, that scene, it almost, it reminded me of society
too with the big like pile of bodies, like, like pinning him down, like the kid. And because he's
a kid, much like that scene in Dr. Sleep, which I am very excited to watch after Joe and I finish
recording tonight. I really want to watch the new director's cut of it. Oh, there's a new,
when did that come out? It came out when it came out on Blu -ray, but it's a full like hour
longer. So I'm going to watch that tonight. I have, I have the Blu -ray. I didn't realize
there was a director's cut on it. Yeah. I'm excited to see it. It's supposed to be great.
Even better. But I wish I had that here. Um, yeah, you know, that scene in Dr. Sleep where
they're there, Jacob Tremblay is being tortured and me and Joe were like, you know, it was one
of the most disturbing recent horror scenes. Um, it's similar. It's, it's a quick flash.
And especially at the theater, like there's so much detail into that scene of just like
this kid being tormented in the demon realm. But, um, man, it's so effective. It really is
because then you, they, they make sure every step of the way you get what the stakes are,
you get how dangerous this is, how scary this is. Um, it was just great. You know, it's just,
it's great to see people giving a shit and trying, you know, um, I, I, I enjoyed the movie
thoroughly. Got to say, um, I got to say too, it restored my faith in, um, a 24 because a 24 had,
you know, in my opinion had stored it, sorry, had sort of slipped into this, you know, they,
were doing this fucking thing, man, where it was like, you know, the, the, you'd see a trailer for
something and you'd be like, oh shit, this is like a horror movie. This is going to be scary.
And then you'd watch it and you'd be like, this wasn't even a harm. Like what the fuck was this?
Like nothing happened to it. And then what people forget is that they're, they're, they do develop
projects, but they're also, they get at least half their business from being distributors.
So they'll, they'll buy movies like Miramax used to, um, promote them and, and sell them,
but it doesn't mean that they developed them and made the movie, uh, at least half the time,
they've just bought a movie and they're releasing it. And that, that I'm pretty
sure was the case with this one. The, uh, okay. Well then that does make sense. You know, I,
I just, you know, a 24 for a while, they had really, they had really, really gotten up on
their high horse. Yeah. And they, they, you know, they were just in a place where they're just
stroking themselves. So fucking hard, man. You know, like, come on guys, Jesus Christ with this
shit. Um, and, uh, you know, this, this excited me, this was like, oh, this is like what I used
to like about a 24. Like this is the kind of cool shit they used to do. And this feels,
you know, it's a very high quality film, um, without question. And you know, it's, they,
they had a budget here, but 4 .5 million and it's made about 90 million. Say again. It cost $4 .5
million and it made about 90. It's, it's made 90. That's amazing. Yeah. I mean, this, this just
like one of those classic, this just feels like classic. It's funny to call 4 .5 million indie
cinema, but that's what it felt like nowadays for sure. Yeah. That's what it felt like to me. Um,
the actors, I looked up the main, uh, girl, you know, I, the only thing I don't know for her from
anything, uh, she was in like some fantasy movies. Yeah. I didn't recognize anybody in the movie.
She's in this thing called the portable door. She's in a lot of stuff. They got a streaming
service down there called, uh, oh, come on. Where is it? It's, uh, it's, it's the Stan, S T A N.
Okay. Which is weird. I didn't, it's just weird to know like, oh, Australia's got their own
streaming thing that we don't have here. Um, but anyway, you know, I'm just surprised that
it's, it's interesting to see something with Australian actors and you're like, no,
they're actually just Australian actors. Like they're, they're, you know, you, you usually go,
oh, that's the person from this. Oh, I didn't realize she was Australian, whatever. Like this
truly was like a made in and for Australia thing. So it's cool that it's gotten all this like great
global attention. It's doing so well. Um, I, yeah, it, it, I really hope, you know, and I do think
that real horror fans, you know, love obviously practical effects, old school effects. Um, I just
hope there's more and more of these movies with lower budgets where it's like, and I'd, I'd love
to see a labyrinth type movie with a lower budget, you know, just like some sort of return to that,
because I think people prove time and time again that it looks both, it's both cheaper and looks
better. Yes. Just plain and simple. This Netflix show I was going to write for the finale of the
show, there's a scene where he throws a match at a, at a, um, escalate and the car blows up.
And it was the worst effects I've ever seen in my life. And like all Netflix shows, it looks like
it costs like a hundred million dollars an episode, but they, they just, something about
the CGI effects these days are just not hitting it. And I really hope that there's some sort of
bigger return to more traditional means of special effects because it's always more effective in my
opinion, always. Tell me the name of the show again that you almost wrote for. Yeah, I guess it
unstable. Uh, the Rob Lowe and his son show and about the horses. Yeah, exactly. But yeah, got,
you know, got called in amazing meeting. And then they were like, we're actually not hiring anybody.
That kind of stuff happens more than you would believe. It's like, oh yeah, sorry, sorry. We
interviewed you. And it's like, yeah, crazy me for getting my hopes up after I came in for a job
and told me I had it. Did you meet Rob Lowe? I did not. I briefly met his son. Um, yeah.
Gorgeous kid. I assume. Yeah. He doesn't really look like Rob Lowe actually, but, um,
it's just some good stock. You're coming from there. That's for sure. Yeah. He still looks great.
The hair, you know, man, if I ever, it ever, ever starts to go, I would reach out to Rob Lowe and
I'm sure he'd take the call. Yeah, he might. He might. My, uh, my buddy told me Rob Lowe has
this book. I got it on audible and I haven't listened to it yet, but he said every chapter
ends with like, and this snot nosed kid came up to me on the set of the outsiders and he
knocked my baseball cap off my head. And I just thought this kid is such a prick. I'd never
like every chapter ends with the reveal that he's talking about somebody who went on to great fame.
I thought you were going to say it ends with him being like, and I then, and then I fucked another
11. Uh, no, I don't think he probably wants to go too much into his fucking days due to the
controversy behind it. He'd rather you forget, but the, um, but I, by the way, Joe, why did you
say the man's politics offend me? Yeah, I love, I love that that suddenly he's become a right -wing
hero where they're like, they're trying to silence Russell Brand because he's the only person
speaking the truth. That's how far we've come from God's light, you know, just insanity.
I don't care about his politics at all. Uh, he, he, I do think it's done. I'll tell you the thing
I'm most disappointed. Well, if the allegations are true, that would be the most disappointing
thing, obviously, but it's disappointing to me that his YouTube about two years ago, I got turned
onto it and it really was like this very interesting kind of, Hey man, like I'm just asking questions
and I'm kind of going up the middle and I'm questioning all sides kind of thing. I was like,
this is really cool. And it's really turned into just this click baity. Yeah. Like every video
now is like a picture of Biden and then a picture of like a mushroom cloud and then a picture of
Russell Brand looking surprised. And it'll be like, he's done it this time. And you're like,
what, what is this? And it's, it's all bullshit. Yeah. And he started doing that right around that
time. Remember there was that aliens thing and like, it was right before we found out aliens are
real. Uh, when they had the congressional hearing, what was it an Arizona or whatever, like there,
that police footage got released of the kid being like, look, man, there were like seven foot tall
things in my backyard or whatever. Right. Russell Brand put out a video and I was trying to find
more information about that on YouTube about the alien thing. And I saw Russell Brand's video and
thumbnail was like a picture of like flying saucers and like the headline of like aliens in,
in Arizona or whatever. And then like, it had like red circles drawn around like the flying
saucers in the, in the, in the like grainy shot and the thumb. And I was like, holy shit. Yeah.
What is this? And then I watched the whole video and I was like, wait a minute, Russell Brand just
click baited me. There was nothing in the video. Like what the fuck? And ever since then I've
noticed that's what he does now. It's a real bummer. Yeah. Yeah. It's a real bummer. Um,
I've never watched. I've seen, I've seen. I'm not watching club random Bill Maher's, uh,
you know, video podcast of him being casual smoking dupes with his buddies, but, um, the site
of him and what he thinks is casual wear is my favorite part of the show. It's always like a
Hawaiian shirt and jeans, like he's Billy Crystal and running scared or something. You know,
it's the ones I've seen it's fully slicked back hair. Yeah. Yeah. Swimming goggle, sunglasses.
Yeah. T -shirt tucked into jeans, blazer on top of it, smoking like cannon joints to the head.
Yeah. Yeah. And in joints. The state one is very funny though. The David. I've only seen it. The
only really lengthy clip I've seen is when Richard Dreyfuss was on there, like, am I really never
going to get the chance to play a black man? Really? Like he gets, he gets these people
fucked up and they say horrible things and it's only going to lead to terror. But, uh,
I'd do the show in two seconds if he asked me. I'd be down at club random in a heartbeat.
I actually went, my, my buddy and I used to watch during the pandemic. We would watch real time
with Bill Maher to make fun of it because we find Bill Maher very funny, not in a genuine level,
but in a he's ridiculous level. And it was a good kind of bonding for us. We would text and watch
it. So we, he got, got me, um, he had a buddy who wrote for it and they got us in to a taping of
the front row and we were kind of going as like an ironic joke. And my God, did we regret it. It
was one of the most depressing days of my life. It was a horrible time. The show was laughless.
And then, and then, uh, you know, Maher between takes, like he just has such contempt for his
audience as you can imagine, you know, like there's no, he's trying to be like cool in his
monologue. And then like, there's just no engagement and nobody seemed to be having fun and
anyway. Oh, you hate, you hate to hear it. You hate to hear it.
The, uh, I've never been to any taping like that. I saw, um,
before I worked Conan, I went to many Conan tapings and there's, they were the most fun by far.
So much fun. I saw some Conan tapings by like, you know, proxy. Yeah. Like I'd have to go over
and talk to JP Buck about something when I was writing for, for Pete, uh, on the Pete
Holmes show. And, you know, I, I'd like get to talk to Conan for 10 seconds backstage before
he went on and I'd watch some of the warmup or whatever. And then that was it. Uh, but I did
go to the Colbert report back when Stephen Colbert was still funny and, uh, like, uh, um, I, but I
was very funny. He's so funny. I wish he would just be funny again. He was. Yeah. God. Like these
guys get so on their thing and then they just don't stop. And it's like, all right. You know,
when I first, when I first moved to New York, I saw, I went to Letterman and the guests were like,
I think Ben Stiller, I just always got great guests. Um, I went to, I waited overnight and
into SNL. I saw SNL many times before I worked there. Uh, Conan, many times I had to work
Carson daily many times, which I would do. It was fun when they were great bands. He was
sometimes have great bands, indie bands, but usually he was a drip and not entertaining to watch.
Um, I did his show. I performed on his show twice. It was very stand up. He's a nice guy. And like,
what was great about it was what was great about Conan in the early days,
bands that wouldn't play anywhere else would play his show, comics wouldn't play anywhere
else would play his show, et cetera. He, uh, the second, the first time I did it,
it went very well. The second time I did it, I didn't do too well. And the reason was
I got there and they go, we're doing a double episode with Fiona Apple.
She's emerged from her latest depression to discuss her new record, the first in four years
or whatever. Uh, and, uh, we're going to do a double length interview with her in front of
all of her fans. And then you come out and do stand up for six minutes. I was like, yeah,
great guys. You guys share a lot of overlap. That's for sure. Oh my God. It was brutal.
Yeah. Um, yeah, but, but, uh, they were nice people over there. Anyway, folks, um,
everyone episode. Yeah. What's, what's so, so next episodes, we, we still have to finish the
other half of the Q and a, we're not forgetting. We will do it at some either this month or next
month, probably. Uh, but are we doing our directors episode? Joe and I have both seen the new insidious,
which we are going to do at some point. If I can remember watching it. Um, but yeah,
you know, we, you know, we'll release this live episode, but that's not going to come out in
October. Um, so, you know, we'll figure all this out, but, uh, we got more coming. Obviously
we love you guys. We appreciate you guys. Thank all of you for all your support.
We'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.