I'll see you in hell.
Welcome to We'll see you in hell, it's a podcast that talks about movies and you tune in
to listen to the talk about movies. My name is Joe Erosa. I had gang, my name is Patrick
Walsh and on today's show we're going to be talking about Gretel and Hanzel, an adult
fairy tale, not an adult fairy tale. It's not like that Alison Wonderland porno that came
out in the 70s. What was that? I think like if you watch it now, it's just kind of a hard
art, but at the time there was some sort of porno version of Alison Wonderland, 1971 I want
to say. I got you played the drive -in circuit. A lot of play on words of big and small, eat,
eat me. I'm sure there was tons of that. Yeah. Yeah. All right. The Cheshire pushy babe.
Yeah. As they say it writes itself, it does. A lot of movies did in those days, they were
written with the aid of cocaine, but mostly on your own. I think that's where we're headed
back to, basically. I mean, people are going to have to do drugs just to get through the
goddamn day when they return to life. I don't know how these people are going into set. You
going over to craft services with an iron man mask on? I'm ready to just, I'm ready to
go full non -mask or wrestle the guy at the target entrance. I'm just ready to do it anymore.
I got to tell you it's, I told you about this, Joe, but it's been nagging at me. I wrote
an email back to my father that I did not send, which is a helpful way of managing your anger.
I agree. But he sent me, I would have normally sent it in the past, and then regretted it the
second I hit said. But my dad sends me and my sister. He's like, you will have a funeral
for me. He's not ill. He just sends us this thing. You're going to have a funeral for me. It's
going to be at this church. You're going to play these four songs to the parishioners.
You're going to hand out lyric sheets. Come on, Eileen was in portais. Why come Eileen? I like
Dexy, and her midnight runners, but not at a funeral. Then he's like, you'll have a reception
where people have cake, no alcohol in all caps. It's like, no, people are going to have a drink
if they want. Then we're all supposed to just do this indoors. I'm sure half of his friends
are anti -maskers. I was going to send a big nasty email, and then I just was going to send
a collection of articles about how weddings and funerals are super spreader events and how
they kill off dozens of people. But instead, I just ignored it until today I got the text,
hey, did you receive my letters? Because there were two 10 page letters that arrived. I'm going to
have hard copy letters. Hard copy, not unlike the journals kept by the John Doe, Kevin Spacey
character in the movie seven. Yeah, legal pads, yellow paper. Now, are you going to do an
aptile style documentary about your dad when he passes like the Gary Shaneling thing, where you
read all of his private letters on HBO? No. No. I mean, I think I'd go read the letters at a pitch
and they'd be like, so this is true crime. This is going inside the mind of a completely insane person.
But the other letter was way crazier and I'm not going to share that one with you, but it just
goes on and on and on and it's like it's just the ramblings of a man who doesn't care if I'm sure
even if half the people there died, he wouldn't care. He's dead. He wants us all to celebrate his memory.
You think he has anti -masker friends? Your dad's a pretty staunch liberal. I would think that that
would be a big deal breaker for him. But for some reason, he doesn't seem to care much about this. He
says he stays in his house. He only wears his mask and then he said to incidents where he had to go
get tested because he spent the whole day maskless with somebody who had COVID. So I don't know. You never
know with your parents, but God, it's just imagine you don't speak to your dad for like a year on the phone.
Maybe some of you have that. I don't know, but then all of a sudden you just get a 10 page letter
about his funeral. So these were instructions. These were instructions where he to die during COVID,
specifically. Yeah, but it also doesn't really leave open the door to the possibility that he will survive
COVID. And then he's saying, well, all of his friends who have died from COVID, which I think there
are quite a few, their families didn't have funerals for them. And that will not be acceptable
to him. We will have to have the funeral. He has quite a few friends that have died from COVID.
That's intense, man. Didn't Missouri. They just walk around down there. Wow. Wow.
I want to start, I want to change what I said earlier. What I want to do is become somebody who gets
caught on iPhone video, wrestling a Walmart greeter, but with my mask on it.
So what is the argument? No idea. Just really, let's throw more curveballs into this whole thing,
really confused people. Yeah. I can't believe we haven't seen that yet. Honestly, you know,
would be a funny kind of like Borat, Jamie Kennedy type thing to do. I'm sure there's more recent
examples than Jamie Kennedy, but you walk in to a grocery store wearing two masks and you start
screaming at everyone for only wearing one. Right. Right. Yeah. And then they'd try to be mad at you,
but you're actually more safe than that. You're like, I care about your safety. I guess you don't
care about mine with your fucking one mask. Right. And then how do you reveal the prank? You say,
you got exed. Isn't that what Jamie Kennedy used to say? I think on my new show, I'm going to go,
you got pissed on and then I take my dick out and I piss on them. So it's like they're so mad
about the pissing they forget the prank. And then I just run out the door. Okay. I like that. I like
I think you got a good idea on your hands here. And I'd watch it. Thank you. Sure. I'll watch
anything with piss. That's just how I was raised. Sure. Sure. Yeah. I think we're going to get that
piss tape that that Trump piss tape. I don't think it exists. It might not. Tom Arnold said it
exists. Oh, well, then I mean, this is where we're at as a country. I mean, look, I'm no fan of Trump,
but for Christ sake, so I'm not listening to Tom Arnold. Yeah. It's this writer, John Levinstein on
Twitter. He written for Crowell show and arrested development and much stuff. He's a very funny,
cranky guy. But he wrote this post when Tom Arnold was like, I've got the news that's going to
bring down Trump. I've got the news. And I wish I had the exact wording, but his tweet was like,
he's been a sitcom writer forever. And he goes, I have the same fragile hope that Tom Arnold will pull
through as I did when he guest starred on an episode of Tom, I wrote in 1991. It's very funny.
That's very funny. He truly is the polar opposite of Rose Am. It is the two ends of the crazy
spectrum. Yeah. I mean, he's as far as I can tell now, he's a relatively normal guy,
except he's claiming that he has hard evidence, hard evidence that the government officials
don't have. What is he talking about? But he hangs in those circles. I mean, that's his kind of like
what circles are these? He would have been at a party in 99 where Trump said the end word or
something. That's where that's exactly where he would have been. I guess so. I guess I'm doing
fucking rails in the, in the, you know, pool house. I sort of believed him, but he, he never really
came forward with it. Well, that's the other thing too. It's like, where, okay, you have it. Where is it?
And then I'm getting a little tired of that. That's every news thing now. There's evidence that says,
okay, what show it to me? Until then, fuck off. I don't care. When you have the thing and you want
to show it, I want to see it. Well, you know, many sources are saying, that should be enough for you.
No, it's not, it's not, it's never been enough for a real patriot like myself.
Do you, could you ever imagine saying, like you wanted specific things for your funeral? Have you
even given any thought to that at all? Would you care? I'm just hoping somebody finds my body at this
point. I mean, I'm, I'm probably going to be dead in this apartment for weeks before anybody's
even aware of it. So true. You know, what's your frequency talking to the parents? Will they know
if you've died? I called them today. We talked about twice a week, I'd say. So it's pretty frequent.
We're at a point now where I call them. They call me. How are you doing? Awful. How are you?
Awful. Sure. You know, everybody's depressed. Yeah. It's, it's awful. But we are in contact. So they do,
they, they will know, I mean, my mom panics, if I don't call her when I get back from like the
supermarket, you know, right? So her insane worry will, will see to it that my body is found.
Now, here's the problem. If she doesn't hear from me, she knows nobody that I know.
Right. I don't know who she would call. She's got no numbers. You know, right. Nobody knows
anybody's numbers anymore. Yeah. She'd have to call the cops and then they'd have to come break my
door down. You know, I know my number and I could get my wife's and three tries. Beyond that,
I don't know anyone's phone number. I don't know. I mean, but I'm saying my mom doesn't have any
saved on her. It's not like she's got friends of mine. Their numbers saved, you know. Right. And you
don't have con to like be eating you anymore and dragging parts of you into the hall. So people
get suspicious. I have, and let me be clear. Absolutely nothing.
It's a dark, dark, dark apartment. I'm in these days.
Well, you know, it used to be like at least a quarter of my friends were not depressed and
they were very cheerful people at upbeat. And then those would kind of balance you out. And then
sometimes you're the upbeat guy for them. It's just rare in my case. But now everyone's just depressed.
You reach out to text an old friend. They're like, I don't know, man. I just kind of don't want to
be alive anymore. So you're never getting anything that's lifting you up in any way. Entertainment,
it used to do it. That's not doing it anymore, either. No, rolling up that spot. In fact,
you know what? I'll save it for the movie corner. A movie I just rewatched.
And it made me so depressed because of how good it was and how we could never get a movie like
this ever again. And it's from like 10 years ago. This is the problem with the with the odds.
Yeah. Yeah. And now the 2010s, the problem is things haven't changed enough since the year 2000 to
now for it to seem like it was a different time in the year 2000. You know, like from the year 2000
to the year 1980, you're talking insanity leaps and bounds with technology, with style, with the way
cars looked everything. You see cars now from 2001, 2002. They look like they probably just came out.
The clothing thing hasn't changed that drastically. You know, like MP3 players and all that stuff
were pretty early on after 2000. You know, I know smartphones were obviously a huge, huge thing. But
cell phones were plenty full existing before smartphones and everybody had a cell phone and Nokia
would ever in the year 2000. So you see these things from that time period. And you say,
and it and you miss it and you go, I wish stuff was still like that. That seemed like a simpler time
to me. And then you realize, but it wasn't last year. It just feels like it was last year. It was
20 years ago. Yeah. And you know, you have to accept the change is going to happen over the course
of 20 years, two decades, but I find it very hard to do lately because because you see these things
that are literally 20, some of them 25 years old and it feels like literally yesterday. And I don't
mean just for people my age, for everybody. Nobody looks back at 2001 is like way back in the day.
You know, unless maybe you're like an 18 year old and you were, you know, one, but like,
I just did the math wrong, but you know what I mean, you're I might be missing your overall point.
My point is is it was easier to accept change in the year 2000. Yeah. Because 20 years ago,
look like 20 years ago, then you're saying there's there hasn't been as many differences in this
past. There hasn't except just the except just the content and entertainment differences that
happen over the course of 20 years, right? So the Charlie's Angels of 2000 was women in tiny
bikinis, jiggling and jumping. And the Charlie's Angels of 2019 is three very angry looking women
wearing full pants suits. Right. It's shoulder pads. Charlie's Angels is different. That's the one
thing I can think of that I can point to the difference. But you'll watch like you do know what I
mean? Like you'll watch like a sitcom from 2001 and be like, man, those were great edgy jokes you
could do on sitcoms back then. And it makes you feel sad because you feel like, oh, that was just
yesterday. What happened? Then you go, wait a minute, it wasn't just yesterday. It was 20 years ago.
The problem is 20 years ago, looks like just yesterday. So it's very hard to adapt to the difference,
you know? It's very, very hard. Yes. I do think also that people watching that run of like
American pie and then the next 10 years of sex comedies will be every bit as shocked as
they are when like people watched Mickey Rooney and breakfast at Tiffany's with the, you know,
the fake buck teeth and the, you know, he's playing a Chinese man. Like it's shocking to what,
how do they think that was okay? But social moors more is whatever you call it have changed so much
in this 20 years. I think I'm American pie in those movies will be just a shocking to a teenager.
Are they shocking? Are they that they're shocking kids of today who are, who are, who only know,
you know, the most proper respectful ways of interacting, you know, I wonder because
because they're watching the four in exchange student strip on a webcam and everyone in school
watching it and pointing and laughing, people will be like, so this is a serious drama. Like we have
to, how do we protect this girl? Well, it's interesting because there's there's two sides that
there's the side of the, you know, the the the the the gen, you know, what we call the Gen Z,
or ZEDs, or whatever, in the land of ZEDs, I've heard it. Trust me. It's out there. You just
got to look for it. All right. But I mean, it's interesting. There's the one school thought that
is, you know, kids are, they've been raised in an extremely sterile environment and anything,
even marginally offensive, let alone greatly offensive wherever you put American pie
in the category of would they would find completely shocking to the same degree. But
there's another school of thought that says like, actually, kids today fuck way earlier and
they're having tons of sex and and maybe they'd watch that and be like, oh, this is tame man,
like, we're doing fucking angel, do kids even do angel dust anymore? Whatever the kids do these days.
Well, yeah, they wouldn't be traumatized by the pie fucking. I think they would be traumatized by
the the way guys speak about girls the way, especially the way the the exchange student has treated
in the film. Or maybe they just laugh. I don't know, but it's things have gone through a great big change.
When I'm looking back at 2000, I'm thinking, I mean, I was pretty disgusted with the culture then too.
You know, those were the the limb biscuit days. Yeah, it was bad, but I definitely
I look around now and I don't see much that's anymore inspiring than limb biscuit.
You know, well, I mean, look, that was around the time too that that third
woodstock happened. Yeah, no, there was like the fires and the rapes and the sexual assaults and it
was just a shit show was disgusting. And I was completely disgusted by it as most people were.
I wasn't a big fan of the original woodstock, but I could at least get behind what it sort of stood for.
But I remember when that happened, and I remember being so grossed out by it and hating not that the
bands were responsible for it, but just hating the bands that were there even more because their fans
were doing shit like this. Right. But what I didn't ever think was necessary was for instance,
to ban woodstock because it went horribly wrong or something. And that's kind of the part of that
time period that I really miss, which was like we you could hate something and just say I'm not
going to go to that because I think it's gross and stupid or offensive or or appalling or whatever
word you want to put on it. But you know, it can exist over there, I guess. Hopefully they learn
from their mistakes and do better next time. But I'm certainly not going to support them. And that's
gone away. That's the thing that's gone away. And then like in an entertainment sense,
and again, I'll elaborate on this in the movie corner, this sense of irony, which we've discussed
on here before, irony is just gone. It's like, yeah. You know, when I crazy, when I see people
online and it's, you know, obviously the Republicans are deserving of all they get and more,
especially at this moment in time. But it's like they'll, somebody I know is funny, will intentionally
misconstrue a clear joke and start shooting on it. It's like you're smart enough to know that's a joke.
The person who made the joke knows it's a joke. So why are we pretending? And I think now they do it
as a way to get back. If you're going to misconstrue everything, our guy says I'm going to misconstrue
everything. Your guy says what it amounts up amounts up. What an amounts to is just everyone being
angry, everyone pretending they don't get what the other person's saying. And I hate it. I hate every
interaction that I see or that I'm a part. I think I, you know, my, in my opinion, both parties have
been reduced to simply one party once you literally did. And the other party once you, you know,
ostracized and socially dead, you know, one party doesn't care if you're safe with COVID because
they're wearing a mask or whatever. The other party doesn't care if you're cast out into the street
because you lost your job because they blew up a joke you made on Twitter or whatever it is.
It's a sad time. It's a sad time. And I'll tell you this in the house for 12 months is not helping.
No, it's, you know, the, the little arguments that people get it, you know, like if you and I
went up to, to a bar for a day, you and I would probably have two or three little arguments that not
having those in your day to day life just makes you always tense and angry and on the lookout for an
argument. And when everyone is in that mode and everyone is in the red, then that's how you get to
like people screaming at each other at Trader Joe's or whatever else. Oh boy, I was at Trader Joe's
today. Yeah. And I like Trader Joe's. I'm a fan of the store. Sure.
You didn't mind. They are, they are ridiculous with the COVID stuff. I'm a safe COVID guy. I put my
mask on, you know, I play by the rules. They're doing this thing. They've got full plexiglass like cubicles
around the cash registers, right? Yeah. That's yours, whatever.
So if you're standing directly in front of the cashier, there's a piece of plexiglass between the two
of you. Plus you're both masked. Okay, fine, right? Yeah. However, if you stand there as they're
ringing you up every time the cashier, because I always forget they go, could you please stand over here
on the number? Because you're technically closer. And it's like, dude, standing over here on the number
is in theory more dangerous. Look how much farther away from the glass I am, I could expel
something into the air over here. There it's safe. It's like guys, for Christ's sakes, like let's not
get insane here, but you know, but whatever. They're always very polite. Our Trader Joe's does not
have that. They do have like I walked up and the guy was like, do you need a sanitized basket?
And I said, oh no, I brought my own bags. Which Trader Joe's used to insist that you bring your own
bags. And I'm like, no, I'm doing the right thing. I've got my own me bags. Oh no, you can't use
those, sir. You can't put something into the bag and then give it to the cashier. So now now I can't
do the thing that I was forced to do or else I had to pay for the bag a year ago. Yeah, and that's
stuff like that is what that happened to me at Trader Joe's as well. And stuff like that drives me nuts
because over and over they've said like surfaces are not the problem guys. We've got to focus on more
important ways of stopping the spread. But yet, just like anything else in this country, we can't
get past. Yeah, I get I get being paranoid. I mean, I used to sanitize the groceries when I
when I brought them home at the beginning of this. Yeah, at the beginning. And then they see you don't have
to and you stop. Yeah. But who knows? Let us take you over to the movie corner before we just completely
spiral here. I mean, it wasn't too dark was it? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, you got to address it.
I mean, you can't pretend it's not happening. You got to smack it up, flip it and rub it down. Oh no,
if I may start us off, please just to get this movie, I'm talking about it out of the way. I rewatched
thank you for smoking. Yep. The Aaron Eckhart vehicle. And I believe the last time Katie Homes
appeared in anything. I mean, she been in anything since then? Yeah, she was in somewhere thing where
she looked like Jackie O. I don't remember what it was called, but this is and I don't mean to be
you. Anyway, thank you for smoking. If you haven't seen it, it is a satire about a big tobacco
rep played by Aaron Eckhart, who is a lobbyist on behalf of Big Tobacco. And it's his job to kind of
go around the country and take the bullet in the public forum on behalf of Big Tobacco. And then
convince people that tobacco isn't bad for you. That's essentially a gist of it. Obviously, you get why
that's a problematic field for him to be in and what the challenges of that are. And this is
what I mean about what we've lost in entertainment. It is such a funny movie. And I remember seeing
this in the theater and loving it. And Keckner, David Keckner plays a gun rep, Maria Bello plays an
alcohol rep. And there was an irony in all of this. There was an irony and a humor and again, a satire
in watching a character, not a real person, a character who represents something that I think 99
percent of the public would deem as bad for you. Almost duplicitously go around saying to people
it wasn't bad for you. And being able to laugh at that and still somehow like the character,
that's what comedy was at one point. You could do that. You could watch, I always use Anchorman as the
example, but like you could watch Anchorman and go, Ron Burgundy is a jackass, but that's why he's
funny. That's what I like about him. And interesting thing about the movie, I never noticed this before.
I've seen it a few times, not one person smokes in the entire movie, not once. So here's a picture
that was made at a time in Hollywood. Now that could have been an artistic choice, I don't know, but
I think it's also probably very likely that this was made at a time in Hollywood when Hollywood would not
show people smoking on camera or wouldn't want to. And they incorporated that standard into an interesting
challenge for the script and the director. And they pull it off to the extent that it's not even
noticeable. It's not even noticeable that you don't ever see somebody smoking a cigarette and a movie
about a cigarette lobbyist. So it just really, really made me miss right off the bat. He's on a talk
show and there's a kid with cancer. And like they're calling him cancer boy behind the scenes. And they're
making jokes about it. And then the bad guy in quotes in the movie is William H. Macy who plays a
Democrat from Wisconsin. And he's the one behind the scenes being like, when you get a sick kid, he's
got to look hopeless. Where the hell did you find this kid? He looks too good. Like it was really,
really funny man. It was, it's a really funny movie. But here's the, here's the part that floored me.
At the end of the film, and this is a big joke where you're supposed to laugh and be like, what a
jackass this guy is. They're interviewing William H. Macy's character and he's talking about how he's
going back through old movies and super imposing other objects over cigarettes. And the person
interviewing him on the like entertainment tonight style show goes, don't, don't you think you're
changing history? And he goes, no, no, we're not changing it. We're improving history. And when that
movie came out, your reaction to that was supposed to be what an asshole. Right. And here we are
some 15 years later. And literally exactly that is happening. The erasure of history
because we find certain behaviors that were documented at a time when things were quite different
as offensive. Not saying we shouldn't find them offensive. And you're seeing these things be
edited out. And it's just shocking to me that in a short 15 years, it might even be less than that.
We have gone, we have swung so far in the other direction of this that that's very, very shocking to
me. Yeah, it's like when you watch broadcast news now, the, the bar has slipped so low that nothing
in that movie would be shocking. The big turning point of broadcast news is this guy that she's
falling in love with William Hurt. Holly Hunter learns that he edited in a faked reaction of himself
crying to a woman's confession that she was raped. So he doesn't have the tears there. So later on,
they shoot an insert of him fake crying that they can use for it. And she's so disgusted by this
that she, you know, breaks up with him. She's yelling at him in the street. She's, she can't believe
his morals, whatever. And that now, I mean, good Lord, like that would be a blip in the radar of
what happens on news these days. So that's how these movies are going to wind up dated is that the
things that seem shocking will be nothing. It's like you watch Nixon, like I was talking about on
here the other day. And it's like, boy, this is small potatoes, you know, this was the biggest political
scandal in a hundred years. But it's nothing now. Yeah. Crazy. I watched this performed live.
Jason Wrightman at Lackman, the art museum here did a live reading of it with Courtney Bevance
in the what's the air in our cart roll? Josh Gad was there. You know, great. But yeah, it was kind
of fun to see like a live reading. I would see only one way I went to when did Josh, Josh Gad
become the ambassador of my childhood? Why am I seeing all these projects where it's like Josh
Gad says to get this, you know, to get this Disney live action hunchback of Notre Dame project off
the ground. He's really had to what the fuck is going on? Why do they need Josh Gad to spearhead these
things? He is the classic case of the guy that Hollywood thinks is, you know, worth every penny,
who's like going to bring in audiences from all four quadrants. And the truth is nobody likes Josh
Gad. I don't know one person who goes on a big dad fan. I liked him in like Book of Mormon,
which is the first thing I saw him in when it was, you know, on Broadway. But yeah, he's got four
five projects in the works at any given time. And no one likes him. It's very impressive. And he does
these things. Like I think he did something with plans trying to automobiles the other day, but I can't
sit and watch Gad. He fucking is starring. Okay. So he's starring in the Honey I Shrunk the Kids reboot
series. Okay. Right. They're doing a TV show of it. Okay. What D plus? Yeah, Disney plus. Yeah.
And he stars it. Not so I read this thing the other day. Not only is he starring in it, it's his
project, right? So he went to Disney and was like, I want to do this. This is a dream project.
I want to do this. I want to make it happen. So they green light it, right? Yeah. I want to start it.
They green like that. He goes. The only way we're doing this is if Moranis comes out of retirement
to do it with us. He gets work. This Moranis is coming out of retirement to do this. Yeah. He scoffed
it. Ghostbusters 3. Clearly the man is is finally in need of money because he's doing commercials
and shit and blah, blah, blah. So I just don't understand what this sway is that Josh Gad has over.
No clue. How is going on here? No clue, but he can get things green lit immediately.
I'm going to do three for your consideration movies that I've watched. So you can see if you want
to watch these before the Oscars. What are the Oscars this year? December? I don't even know what
month it is right now. So I'm honestly, I'm hazy myself. I don't know day to day what day it is
and without my calendar, I would just miss every meeting I have. Okay. I saw Palmer. Palmer is about
to drop on Apple TV. It is a film about Justin Timberlake who's getting out after 12 years in prison.
A lot of hard and criminals look like Justin Timberlake. He returns to his home to put his life back
together and forms an unlikely bond with Sam, an outcast boy from a troubled home.
Weirdly in this synopsis, they're not mentioning that Sam is, I want to be very careful with how I
say it, but certainly wants to be a woman, dresses as a woman, acts like a young girl. So that's a part
of its way to check every box, to warm every heart. And because of that, it comes off just gross.
I couldn't stand the movie. It's begging you to like it. It feels like it was a hallmark,
hall of fame production, same level of story, acting, etc. It was directed by Fisher Stevens,
the actor from Short Circuit, who portrayed Indian man in the film Short Circuit in brown face,
if you'll recall. He's now become a director. And I just can't recommend it. It's going to flop
on Apple TV this week and you'll see it and go, I guess I'll watch that. And you're going to be
disappointed, but don't say I didn't warn you. I watched Drunk Stone Brilliant Dead, which is the
National Lampoon's doc. Boy do they love each other over at the National Lampoon. They really do.
They really do. A bunch of fucking rich kids sucking each other off. I will say this though,
it sticks on my theme of the good old days. I mean, here's a magazine that is, or was not really
anymore, but at one point was considered the greatest comedy magazine that has ever existed. Okay.
Helped Spawn Saturday Night Live. Well, actually, Lauren Michaels seems to have stolen
that's a knell from the live, as from the live National Lampoon shows. But anyway,
this is a thing. Again, you're just kind of in awe when you're watching it because you're sitting
there going, you know, it tried to be offensive. It's whole thing was nothing is sacred. You know,
nothing is sacred. And they said that now it's been sort of reduced to just like, you know,
a tit mag basically, you know, it's like, it's like, frat boy stuff.
I mean, they also did a full -length parody of Lord of the Rings called Bored of the Rings.
Yeah, they were breaking big ground. It's not the same owners or operators, obviously, but
look, I don't even think what they were doing was that funny. Bored of the rings was in their
prime. That's disgusting. That movie. What's that movie? Wait, oh, you're talking about, you're
talking about like back, they didn't do that as a movie though. They did it as a book. Yeah,
like the first National Lampoon. Okay. I thought you were saying it was a new movie. Sorry. No.
The movie was called a stupid and futile gesture. Yeah. Yeah. So I, my pal David Wayne directed it,
but I wasn't a fan. And not because of anything wrong with the script or the direction
or the acting, I just didn't like this. I didn't like how celebratory it was. It's rich kids.
I mean, these are Harvard kids. I mean, you know, come on. You know, like, of course,
when you got daddy's money behind you, you can, you know, it's a lot easier to take chances.
So that part, I was like kind of like, yeah, whatever. But that said in watching the documentary,
I just again was long for time where if you made, for instance, a rape joke,
the assumption and knowledge was you were joking because they do on this. There's a sketch they play
where it's, you know, and, you know, I'm just using that as an example. I'm not saying, you know,
but my point is it's just, I just missed the time when people gave other people the benefit of
the doubt that what their intention was was pure. Even if it didn't land or even if it didn't work,
or even if it didn't, whatever, that the intention was pure and that we've lost all ability to be
discerning in our judgment. And I worry about it because, you know, look, this show started as a
first show. And it's my ultimate goal in life to get these horror projects of my own made.
You know, it's not going to be long before they come for that genre too. And, you know, I mean,
right now we're lucky that we fly under the radar with horror and it's not a contender for
the Oscars and these awards show things, but neither is comedy. And they've, they've blown comedy
to pieces at this point. You cannot be funny anymore. I mean, just watch one of the latest network
sitcoms that it's, they're, they're, it's a, they're abominations. I mean, it's not, it's not
even like is this your cup of tea or not. These are terrible, terrible, benign, safe, boring,
fucking painfully boring shows. You see it now has also infiltrated stand up. Stand up is no longer
daring or interesting. And it's going to happen with horror where they're going to start to say,
you know, we don't, we don't want to see horror where people get murdered.
Murder's a sensitive subject and it's triggering whatever. And, you know, so I don't, I just don't
understand what's going on. But anyway, things go on cycles. I mean, I hope so. I don't think anyone
alive thinks anything genuinely funny has been made in the last five years that things will change,
but yeah, it's rough stuff. One of the big Oscar controversies this year is how to
rank the movies that Steve McQueen made these five short films. They run in length from two hours
down to like barely an hour. And they're called small acts. They're on Amazon. They eventually decided
to put them into the Emmy category as a mini series, even though the stories aren't connected in
any way. It just seems completely wrong. They have a similar setting, you know, they're all in the same
basic time period, which is the early 70s in London. And it's, they're all dealing with the black
experience. But beyond that, you know, they're five different movies and you should watch them as such.
Uh, but yeah, just real quick to run through them. The best of the first two mangrove is the first one,
which is a the best courtroom drama in at least five years. It's a great, great movie.
You'll, if they had just simply released it as a movie, it would definitely be in the Oscar talk.
It's so much better than the Aaron Sorkin thing, the trial of the Chicago seven, but it's got a similar
feel to it. Did you watch that? I did. It's awful. I mean, it looked unbearable. It's like a
bad school play and the acting, particularly by Baron Cohen and the guy from succession, Jeremy
Strong or they would have been too big for him up at movie. These performances. They're insane.
Unbearable. I am so tired of the Abby Hoffman thing. Who cares? Who cares about Abby Hoffman? Not
to mention, he, there's documentation that the man was a child bluster. I've seen three movies in my
lifetime making this man a hero. Anyway, mangrove is the best of the bunch with a close second being
Lovers Rock, which is part two. Lovers Rock is much closer to like a short film or an episode of TV.
It's a one hour party, but it's a party like in the prime location and time of great reggae music. So
especially when I'm getting a little high ladies and gentlemen, you know, and Lovers Rock is great.
It felt like being at like a crowded house party without the negative aspects of that and I really,
you know, you miss that. It's a very sweaty, dancing, fun vibe. I loved it. I listened to the soundtrack
all the time. Now Spotify has a great small acts playlist. The third one, Red, White, and Blue is
your kind of your standard serpico type drama about racism and the police force. And this one was
very good too, with John Boyega from your Star Wars films. I would highly recommend all three of those,
kind of in that order. And then the last two were lesser. One is called Alex Whedall, which is
like a brief biopic about this artist. And I thought was pretty average. The other one is called
Education. And I did like it, but it is about how the school system was racist back then. And of
course, all these things correlate to today, a problem of today. So they each kind of have their own
little theme, their own little mission statement. They're all well worth watching. I would recommend
the first two. Small acts on Amazon Prime, Steve McQueen, a great filmmaker. You can get five
as movies free. Why don't you go watch them. All right. Last in my people and from a greater time
reviews for today, I watched Pretend It's a City 7 episode, DocuSeries series. Excuse me about
Friend Leibowitz directed by Martin Scorsese. I watched it kind of reluctantly. I didn't really have
any initial interest in it. I didn't understand why it was seven episodes. And I found Friend
Leibowitz interesting, but I didn't know that I wanted to necessarily sit and watch a seven episode
docuSeries on her. And boy was I 100 % wrong. I went into this thing with an open mind and within 15
minutes was completely hooked. And left after seven episodes being a huge Friend Leibowitz fan.
And having such great admiration for her, I knew very little about her aside from the fact that she
was a writer. And a commentator of sorts. And I have immense admiration for her, which she did.
The journey she's taken as a not just a woman, but a gay woman in the arts, in literature,
in a completely unapologetic stance for her beliefs. She's somebody that speaks her mind. She's very
candid yet respectful. She's one of the funniest people and fastest, sharpest people I've ever watched
in anything. I mean, she's just everything that comes out of her mouth sounds like it's been scripted.
She's brilliant. She hasn't written in a long time. She's got a famous case of writer's block that's
lasted. I think since the 80s. But just seems more like a lazyness, I will say. I feel like she just
doesn't like writing, which is I understand completely. Right. So just watching her go through this
seven part series that plays very much like a love letter to New York and made me feel
some brightness in these dark times here when you're kind of going, why do I live here right now?
It's just so sad and whatever. But you keep going. Her attitude of, you know, you live in, you don't live
in New York because it's easy. You know, you live here because you can't and somehow you make it
work and you do it. I just really loved all that stuff. I loved her very balanced takes on social
issues. I love that she has strong stances, which which are morally founded and very justified morally
yet she is able to rationally discuss things and hear other perspectives. And I kind of honestly
was refreshing to hear her stance on art where she talked about artists and said like, now would I,
you know, certain authors, whatever she would, would I hang out with this guy? No, right. No, he's a bad
guy. But does that mean he's not a great writer? No, he's still a great writer. I just really liked
I liked all of those elements of this thing. She was a real voice from a different time. And she's got
incredibly knowledgeable and sharp commentary on the current times that never to me came off as
sobby or pitiful or woe is me or anything like that. It just came off as I know what the score is.
And this is what it used to be. And this is what it is now. And hey, fuck it. Time goes on.
And she never curses either. I think she curses once in the entire thing. It's pretty impressive.
So I don't think so. Anyway, it's worth checking out. And it's really fun watching
Scorsesey with her on camera because he is elated. He's a good laugher. He laughs too much, frankly.
Sometimes she's getting into the setup and he's like holding his sides laughing. But no, I'm glad
you recommended to me. I watched all seven parts as well. I see why you like her. You remind me a
bit of a friendly, but what's Jim mostly in looks. I would say we look similar. And I saw a lot
of myself in the woman. Yeah. Actually, the walking through traffic and like yelling at cars and stuff.
Right. I get it, babe. Yeah, it is a love letter to New York. Weirdly, it's the first time in ages.
I've watched something like that and not had any desire to go back to New York. I know in my
heart, I'm done with the city. But I had my time there. I loved it as well. It's very funny.
I had zero interest in watching it. No interest in friendly, but it's but came away a big fan.
It also really shows the different interview styles. Like Scorsesey,
interviewer and just listens and laughs. Spike Lee really challenges her. And they like keep fighting
over little details and getting into funny arguments. Yeah, I like Baldwin talks over and interrupts her
every time she speaks. Yeah. And it goes to show you like how much late night TV, like talk show,
those aren't interviews. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. No, every aspect of entertainment is worse. For sure.
When I was while I watched Jimmy found interview, somebody on fucking zoom last night night. Man,
I just wanted to die. I saw news of the world, which is another for my consideration.
Direct screener today. Yeah. It's done by Paul Greengrass, who I love. He did the born movies and
the United 93, which I probably will never watch again, but I thought was about as good a
dramatization of that fateful 911 flight as you could ever make. I think he's great. He brings a lot
of realism to stuff. He shoots his action in a very exciting way. Except here, news of the world is a
Western. And just nothing feels right about it. Basically, it's Tom Hanks. He's traveling through
the West, bringing news to townspeople. But, you know, of course, there's some shots taken at fake news
and et cetera, and how you get your news. You know, it's all, you know, like unforgiven had a whole
lot to say about violence. But it concerns itself with the story. It's telling first and whatever you
take out of it. Great. This movie set out to have a lot to say about news and news in America and
Fox news. And then it's a Western. And that's why it's unsatisfying in just about every way.
Tom Hanks is not along in the Old West. You know, he's one of these actors where you see him in a
period movie and you're like, no, not buying it. Sorry. Jeff Bridges, when he did true grit, he walks
into frame in the booths and everything and you're like, yep, I buy it. And now let's proceed.
Hanks, he walks in and just never feels right for the entire time. He's too modern a man, something
about it. I don't know what else to say. The girl they cast in this, I also didn't like, frankly,
hell in a zangle. I wouldn't say it to her face. She's 10 years old. But she spends the first half
of the movie just being very annoying. He's supposed to kind of, while he's bringing his news to the people,
he's supposed to transport this like almost feral young girl. And believe it or not, folks, they
find a begrudging respect and love between them. It's not a bad movie. You see where it's going a million
miles away. I'm just saying between Paul Greengrass is very modern shooting of action. And Tom Hanks,
being the star, it doesn't feel right. Nothing works in it. I love a Western. I love getting swept
up into that other other world, you know, this does not sweep. It doesn't feel right. And I didn't
care for the movie. I don't plan on watching it. I put the DVD screener aside and I was like, I
don't think I'm ever going to watch this. Yeah, it's, you'd have to be in a bind. It's average,
you know, Hanks is Hanks. I like him, of course, but it just, it didn't click for me.
Yeah, I'll go ahead. You're bringing us to our feature. Yeah, were you going to say something
else? No, I was going to say this exact same thing. I was probably going to say it better, but
today's film for review is Gretel and Hansel. Retelling, if you will, of the classic fairy tale,
Hansel and Gretel. It came out in 2020, actually, Jesus, I can't believe it's that new.
Beginning of the year, yeah. Good God. Oh, my God. Anyway, Hansel and Gretel, the famous
brother's grim fairy tale, this was directed by Oz Perkins, who was Tony Perkins, Anthony Perkins's
kid. He also did the black coat's daughter. And I am the pretty thing that lives in the house.
I have not seen either of those. I have seen both and came to this as a big fan of Oz Perkins. I
feel like he's done a lot of great sort of more vibe type horror. You know what I mean? Like,
basically I mean a 24 type horror. Like where the vibe is very creepy as opposed to horrifying
scares. The vibe is like perfect cinematography over necessarily shocks and things of that nature.
So they're really trying to create a mood with these Oz Perkins movies him and his team. And I
code's daughter is probably going to be too slow for some. It moves at a very slow pace. I
thought it was fucking awesome. Got the girl from Mad Men and the Young Girl. Some big twists and
turns to it takes big chances. I liked it a lot. I am the pretty thing that lives in the house.
Very generic haunted house horror. It'll even attempts only a couple of scares at all. I was less
sold on that one. But I like Oz Perkins. I like how he makes a movie look. And this one is no exception.
It's a beautiful movie first and foremost. Yes, beautifully shot,
extremely well acted by everybody in the film. It's stars. What's her name from it?
Sophia Lilis. Yes, she's great. She really carries the film. Also, the star of Uncle Jack,
which I recently talked about on here. When I first saw the trailer for this film, I was intrigued
because my favorite fairy tale of all time is Hansel and Gretel. I was intrigued, but I admittedly
was rolling my eyes a little bit because I was like, here we go. There's one of those things where
they're changing it now to Gretel and Hansel just to be like just to do a gender swap thing,
like, which I think I've complained about it before. I think it's kind of a lazy, insulting thing
to do to the group of people you're trying to celebrate is just doing some swap thing.
But it was interesting when I want, but I still wanted to say it. And when I watched this,
I realized I was very wrong. This is a story that makes perfect sense being called Gretel and Hansel.
Gretel is the older one in the story. She is the one that saves her brother at the end, like she is,
she is the one in charge. And I guess I just never realized that. So I thought this made perfect
sense with the, quote, row reversal. And Sophia does a really wonderful job. She's great in it.
There's some more adult themes here. There's a scene at the very beginning where she goes to
get a housekeeping job and like this, almost like Marquis de Saad type of guy is asking her if she's
still pure, if she's still a virgin, you know. So ever seen the whole movie, it was that that guy was
straight out of Twin Peaks, you know, he was so good and creepy. Yeah, so it gets into. Are you intact?
Yeah, that's what it was. So it gets into, you know, some of the trials of women during that time period.
And the story, more or less, plays out, you know, the same as the original fairy tale. They make
a few changes to streamline things a bit. There's no father in this one. And the mother that wants to get
rid of them is just their only guardian. Makes it a little less convoluted. And, you know, when they
leave and end up in the woods, they find the witch's house. It is not made out of food this time. But
when they go inside, the witches serving them tons of food. And things kind of unfold from there. You
know, what is the food they're eating? Where is it coming from? Have other children been here before?
Why is this woman being so nice to them? She seems to know magic. What's going on? And at the end
of the day, it ends up pretty much telling the story of Hansel and Gretel, as you know it, as I know it,
with just a bit more of a, you know, moody, moody vibe to it, I guess I'd say, right? You know,
yeah, for sure. I was sort of surprised by how basically faithful it was. All those grims,
fairy tales could easily be horror movies with slight changes made to them. A lot of them are
scary. And they've done it. They've, I think, didn't Sigourney Weaver do a Hansel and Gretel,
where she was the witch? No, she did. No white. No white. Yeah. A dark fairy. It was called like an
adult fairy. It was, it was along the lines of what you said earlier, the judge. But I actually had that
on a VHS tape at one point. It's not good. Sam Nees, isn't it? It's not a very good movie.
I, I, I would like to see more of that. I'd certainly prefer these to, you know, by which I mean dark,
low -budget versions of Grims, fairy tales. You know, knock off five of them. Do them instead of
the constant Disney reboots were subjected to, because these stories have proven they stand the
test of time. They've been around for hundreds and hundreds and hundreds of years. You're going to
have to get Josh Gad on this. Gad will play a troll or a dwarf or something. Yes. But, um,
yeah, I came away from this thinking, okay, if this had been an A24 movie, it would have been as
talked about as something like the witch. I do think it was made with the same level of care
as the witch. And it looks beautiful. It was also sort of easier to understand, although that guys
movies play much better with subtitles on, including the lighthouse. But I liked it. I will say,
at about a halfway point, I'm like, okay, each new shot is something beautiful. I could pause it. I
love looking at it. But around the halfway mark, you're kind of like, I'm not caught up in this story
much. And they don't release, you know, fix it by the end. It kind of meanders from the halfway
point to the end. For me, I wasn't really caught up in the story much. I just, I liked it as a vibe
piece of, uh, I liked it as an acting piece, a cinematography piece, et cetera. And I think fans of
those, uh, type of like slow burn, beautiful looking horror movies, which is really becoming its own
sub genre. Um, this one should be ranked among the top. It looks great. It's a great looking movie.
I love Oz Perkins. And I think really we're just waiting for him to get that budget to make that
big movie that's going to put him into the, the league of the, of great new horror directors. I
think he's got the chops for sure. Yeah, I liked it. I liked spoiler alert. I liked at the end that
Gretel ends up taking up the mantle of the witch. And, you know, with the idea alluded to that, you
after she destroys the original witch, uh, I thought it was a cool, I thought they did a very good
job with making this a commentary on gender in its own way. Um, I enjoyed it. I agree with everything
you said. Uh, I was, I was roped in until the end. I, I'm a sucker for a witch as they dealt as they
sort of divvied out little, uh, uh, clues about the witch's heritage and her power and what she was up
to. I, I maintained interest. Uh, I liked watching that mystery unravel. Um, I, I really enjoyed the film.
I really, really enjoyed the film quite a bit. And it was a tight, I mean, it's like a tight 90 minutes
man. You're in, you're out. Right to the point. None of it's, and it's nice to see a movie this
pretty that's not masturbatory. There was never a part where I felt like Perkins was being indulgent
or showing off or anything. It was just very well done. He had all the elements. I love one of these
old fairy tale movies starts with the old lady voiceover like once upon a time that was an evil child.
You know, it just gets you swept up into the moment. It took me back to feeling like a kid hearing
the fairy tale again. Uh, and I really, really enjoyed it. I would highly recommend it. And I think that
there should be some more of these types of films being made. These are public domain. This is,
anybody can adapt these things. Right now. It's kind of like the Lovecraft stuff. And, um,
you know, some of the Dickens works. It's like, these are, these are public domain. It's like
adapt them, you know, instead of spending $40 million to make a new version of my blue heaven.
I'd watch it with Josh Gaden Kevin Hart. Anyway, my hog is up. My hog is up as well.
I would also recommend the other Perkins films, particularly the Black Codes daughter, which I think
is, is really solid. And that's it for us folks. I will say I'm going to push for Joe and I in
coming weeks to do the little things, which is the new Denzel Jared Lito, Rami Malak serial killer
thriller. I have seen it. And I think that we could have a real good time discussing that one, Joe.
Okay. So it's come at age beyond max. Check that one out. I think it's coming on the 29th. Did you
already talk about promising young woman on here? I didn't, but I've seen it. And I'm that's
part of the point we should probably do. Yeah. Down for it. Yeah. That's, that's right in the
show. Jotaro's a comedy on Instagram and Twitter. Jotaro's a comedian on Facebook. Check out taste buds,
podcasts for self volcano. And I debate food each week drops every Monday on YouTube on the no
pressure network channel at 11 a .m. I'm no longer with without a country. So you can keep listening if
you like, but I'm not there. So that's up to you. Whatever you want to do. I'm not here to judge.
And the Joey Rose is sandwich. I pop up still going at the stand in New York City every week Wednesday
through Sunday. The Patrick Walsh Twitter and Instagram. I will also be doing of course my monthly solo
movie corner. That should be posting between now and the end of the month. We will be back with our
second episode shortly. And that one will be the new shutter film anything for Jackson.
We will see you next time and we will see you in hell.