I'm here for Bet Rivers Online Casino and Sportsbook with poker icon Phil Helmuth.
And now thanks to the excitement of Bet Rivers, I'm also a slots icon.
That's great. And a same game, Parley icon.
Cool, cool. A Blackjack icon, a Moneyline icon.
A roulette. Take it from Phil Helmuth.
If you love games, Bet Rivers is the place to play in Bet.
Bet Rivers.
Games on.
Must be 21 plus in present at West Virginia.
Void were prohibited. Terms in conditions apply.
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gambling.
The football season is full of guarantees.
And here's another.
No weather sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October.
If your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 plus.
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gambling.
Offer not available in those days.
Terms apply.
See Fanatic Sportsbook app.
It's a good show.
Happy 2019.
And welcome to We'll See You In Hell.
This is your podcast for horror movie, sci -fi movie, fantasy movie, action movie,
and sometimes comedy and drama movie information.
We do the reviews.
We do the commentaries.
We do all that good shit that you like.
Good to be back.
And this is your episode for January 14th, 2019, in this glorious New Year of God.
Oh.
Yeah.
We haven't done one of these in ages.
We pre -recorded a bunch before the break.
But wasn't it nice, folks, to get a new web on Christmas day and new web on New Year's Eve?
We kept them coming.
Yeah, we took about two weeks off here.
It's important to us that you're happy.
Yeah.
Yeah, we took about two weeks off because we had to go see our families and things.
Yeah, it was fine.
But I'm happy to be back with you, Pat, because I consider you family.
Oh, well, you often refer to me as fan.
I do call you a fan or daddy.
I'll call you daddy I prefer.
Yeah, we had breakfast this morning, Joe and I.
Can you make this thing stop jumping on the screen?
It's going to drive me insane.
I can't.
I've tried.
I can't get it to stop.
I can't figure out how to uninstall it.
Yeah, I know.
It's annoying.
But you can deal with it.
It's a little icon.
I've had it with Apple products.
I mean, every apple besides sucks.
My computer is constantly like having trouble with the internet.
My iPad is always losing the signal.
It's because they want you to buy a new one.
My phone asks me 10 times in a row to sign into the cloud.
And I'm like, there's no option to say I'm not doing the fucking cloud.
You have to every time I turn on my phone, say no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
And that's that's a product I paid $800 for.
It's wrong.
Yeah, I'm done.
Next computer, next computer for me is going to be, I'm going to get one of those like
a micro soft, whatever to fuck it in the zoom.
Oh, why a zoom?
What's a zoom?
Zoom was the Portman's iPod.
Oh, yeah, I remember those.
I had one of those.
And then Neil Young came out with the ponio.
It was like a $1 ,000 iPod that he said sounded incredible.
But it was the exact same sound as everything else.
Yeah.
Well, you had another thing that Neil Young put out that I had zero interest in.
No, I'm going to get one of those, one of those Windows tablet things
with the keyboard.
And that's it.
I'm done.
I've done playing these fucking games.
Apple stock has dropped.
I think that's it.
I think they're, you know, I think they've overstayed their welcome at this point.
I agree.
They're not going away, but I agree.
Well, who knows?
Maybe they are going away.
I have a SEP IRA that I used to, like as an insurance,
or not insurance, what do you call it?
You know, you put a little money into it every year,
sort of like a 401k type deal.
So my accountant has me do it.
I always put in the max you can put in.
It's untouched.
And they tell you where it goes each month.
You get a statement.
It's like your investment has gone up.
X amount of dollars are down.
X amount of dollars.
I get it this month and I was like,
well, I've been reading a lot about how the stock market is collapsing.
I wonder if that affects my thing at all.
Oh boy.
A massive drop of money.
It's fluctuating.
It's not fluctuating, my.
It is.
Well, it jumped over Christmas.
It jumped 950 points.
That's the biggest jump it's literally ever had.
All right, well, that's good.
So it's fluctuating.
It's not because I have a similar thing.
And let me tell you, Pat, the hundreds of dollars I have in there.
I would talk about Trump, but I got,
isn't one of our people that contribute Jackson's Starship?
Is that a name that you say when you're doing the thanks?
I don't know.
I don't think so.
Because this guy does not follow me.
I've not tweeted about Trump in a year.
I get a message.
Patrick, is it just impossible for you to not make some
whiny Trump comment?
Jesus Christ, man.
And I start to respond.
And I'm like, you don't know who this is.
But it made me so angry.
And if you're listening, I don't want you to be able to listen.
And I hope that I'm going to look through our donors.
And even if you are donating money,
I'm going to block you and make sure you can't listen to the show.
I don't know if we're able to do any of those things.
But the message has been set.
He had one follower.
Everything he tweets is like some white power
shit or man power shit.
Oh, well then, yeah.
What do you?
But I still let it upset me to the point that I'm thinking about it weeks later.
I think this show often teeters on an almost pro Trump.
Oh, it does not.
But you know what I mean, though.
I certainly don't think we're bastions of the current
liberal sensibility or something.
You rarely discuss him.
I don't know where it's coming from.
Yeah.
So whatever, whatever.
Times are, oh, it's tough out there right now.
It's not a fun time.
Oh, the times they are a dog shit.
Yeah, it's not a fun time.
On all sides, all sides.
It's just not a fun time.
No, it's, it's real bad.
It's, I don't want to, I've been, as you saw when you walked in,
Frazier was playing.
I'm rewatching Frazier again,
because when the world makes no sense, I just, I, this is what I do.
I don't want anything new.
I go back to like old things that are comforting.
You're rewatching it an additional time since the last time you rewatched it.
Yep.
Oh, wow.
All right.
I just go back to things where I'm like,
it was an easier time.
You could make jokes.
People weren't trying to cut each other's throats at all.
You know, like, yeah, people were getting along.
You could have different ideologies and it was okay.
Sure.
I'm talking about Frazier and Niles.
Yeah, of course.
Yeah, I don't want it that different.
Right.
You know, let's, let's, let's all sort of stay on the same page here.
It's just, you know, it's just, it's not a fun time.
But anyway, you, you all know that.
That's why you tune into this show, right?
For a little escape to lift your spirits.
Joe's in a new apartment.
I got to admit, I feel off my game.
Why?
It's just, it's, I got to get adjusted to the new setting.
I don't think you like the seating arrangement.
Or sitting next to each other on a love seat.
Yeah, thigh to thigh.
So it's, you know, a little out of my comfort zone.
Yeah, and I, I could have gotten dressed to be honest.
You could have, yeah, worn underwear at least.
Just a dick hanging out.
But you're always complaining about how we're seating.
You know, you're, you're, you're across from me.
You're complaining that you can see my balls.
Like come in today, Joe's like, you want to take that chair over there.
The chair appears to be made of cast iron.
It's a comfortable chair.
It's not.
I said it.
It is a comfortable chair.
You're all wound up today.
Where'd you get it?
A target.
I almost guessed target.
It's a nice little mid -century sort of metal chair.
I have one in my office and I work from it.
And I am, I have no problems with that chair.
We had my big chair, my big blue chair,
which could theoretically go there instead of that metal chair.
That's in there now for my gaming purposes.
Right.
Maybe I should put it over there.
I think so.
Why?
So I can sit in it.
I don't know.
You sit on the damn love seat.
We have moths at my house.
That's nice.
Not food moths, but clothes moths.
And I get to,
I don't, yeah.
It's a nice thing is food moths.
Food moths, you just throw out all your food and then you're fine.
Clothes moths are like in the walls.
So I come home to Heather having a complete nervous breakdown.
She's washed everything we own,
sent all this shit to the dry cleaners,
which I'm sure cost a tremendous amount of money.
We got rugs rolled up
and I have yet to see them off.
So she may be losing her mind.
But she won't stop and we just keep spiraling out of control.
We're getting screens.
That's the problem.
The lady that lived there before was kind of this hippie -ish lady.
She was delightful.
But she was like the great thing about this place.
You just leave the doors open.
You don't have screens or anything.
But then you get moths.
Right.
So now we're getting screens put in the house where
everything's a fucking project.
There's big every, every morning I'm like,
where are my, we,
Heather and I saw each other for like 30 seconds on Friday and I was like,
where the fuck are my socks?
And she's like, they're in that,
they're in one of these plastic bags.
An entire room full of plastic bags.
Which one?
Right.
I'm just going to work wearing no socks like, you know,
some sort of Robert Evans.
How do you know there's no moths in the bags?
Those clothes are all thoroughly washed or dry cleaned,
but then she doesn't want to open the bags.
So we're having an exterminator finally come and look,
but I was like, why didn't you do the exterminator before
doing everything on your own?
How big are these moths that she supposedly thinks are there?
I mean, that's how you're going to know if she's gone baddy.
I mean, they're not house size.
You know, she starts talking about seeing red eyes in the dark.
You know, you know that she's losing her shit a little bit.
Well, I think it might be payback for having written
the sci -fi original film, Mothman,
and painting them in a negative light.
It's a karma payback or her or your wife's
discussed that you could have been involved with such a project.
Karma pay, karma pay, okay.
But they do, I mean, it's a shitty situation.
And then we pulled all the rugs up in my house.
So then like, for whatever reason,
the floor that was underneath the rug,
since it's never been exposed is super slippery.
So I'll come walking into each new room,
slip and fall on the floor.
I mean, we're falling apart.
We're falling apart.
It sounds terrible.
It's awful.
And I wish I cared more.
Yeah, yeah.
I don't give a shit about anything you just said.
I don't know why.
I don't mean that in a standoffish way.
I just...
You don't live there and you've never come over to my house.
Don't invite me over.
I've invited.
You always invite me the last minute.
You always do this thing of like,
well, you know, I mean, but we really want to
two guys sitting at a house.
Oh, I never say that.
You invite me at the last minute.
You go, I'm watching a movie if you want to come on.
I'm like, I can't.
You invited me to that.
That's how things work.
Make a plan.
Have a good day.
So things work.
Get home at seven.
Hey, you want to come watch a movie in an hour?
What, why is that prayer?
You never take me up on plans anymore.
I invite you to all kinds of stuff.
When?
Oh, constantly.
I had a fun show tonight when you come with me.
Oh, I'm not going to go to your shows.
Which, which, don't think I haven't noticed, by the way.
I go to, then I stand there with comedians
who don't know me.
For 10 minutes while I'm on stage,
then we hang out.
It's uncomfortable.
Oh, stop it.
You go to other people's shows all the time.
Very rarely.
Oh, shut it.
I've been to your shows.
Once.
No, many times.
Actually, I will say every time you come to my show,
it's never good.
I think you're some kind of fucking goochers or something.
I mean,
I've been many shows.
But I got those shows in March in Vegas.
I know you'll be at those.
You fucking addict.
I saw you in Vegas.
No, but these are my own shows in Vegas.
Great example.
Yeah.
But you'll come out to those, I assume.
Sure.
Let's have some Vegas fun, me and you.
It sounds great.
Were you yet the, like, a Reno hotel this time again?
All I know is I'm playing a place called bonkers.
Bonkers.
Is there an exclamation point or no?
I don't know, but I imagine there's some sort of coconut
instead of the oh and the logo.
Right, right.
I could only imagine, right?
What else could be?
Oh, here's a game I've been wanting to play with you.
Ready?
Yes.
I give you an occupation, okay?
Yeah.
Then you got to take that occupation and come up with an expression
that means this guy is crazy, okay?
That applies to the occupation.
So the classic example is the crazy car dealer.
This guy's not playing with a full deck.
Car dealer.
Yeah.
I think it's a car dealer, okay, guy.
You know, so what I thought of was an account
like a crazy, John Bobbot.
This guy's not playing with a full dick.
There you go.
Right.
I thought of one for an accountant.
You know, I don't think this guy's ledger is balanced
if you know what I'm saying.
Okay, all right, give me one.
Uh, priest.
Which you could also use the full dick one.
Priest, uh,
uh,
all right, DJ.
I wasn't done with priest.
It was taken.
Didn't sound like it was going to go anywhere.
DJ, let's just say all this guy's records ain't spinning.
And I mean, I don't know.
I think this guy's record skips.
Yeah, something like that, you know.
Priest, uh, let's just say,
thanks be to God, I'm not in that fucker's head.
Right.
What?
No, it'd be like, this guy's preaching to a half empty chapel.
You know what I'm saying?
You know, it's like one of those things.
I got a confession to make.
This guy's cuckoo.
No, no, that's too elaborate.
Hey guys, uh, I don't think he's,
I don't think this guy's all the way in the confessional
if you know what I'm saying.
That's not, it doesn't work at all.
I know, but I'm saying it's like one, like something like that.
Like give me, give me an occupation.
You're like, no, not like that.
How about like something worse and farther away?
From these very shaky rules that you laid out.
Give me one and I'll do it.
Give me an occupation.
Uh, grocery store cashier.
Uh, hey guys, I don't think this,
I don't think this guy's got any change in his register.
You know what I mean?
You know, like that kind of thing.
Yeah, all right.
Give me another say this guy's putting the gallon of milk on top of the eggs.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey guys, I don't know about you,
but I think his scanner's broken.
You know, it's something like that.
Uh, how about a dentist?
Antist, uh, guys, I think this guy's drill goes the wrong way.
I don't think this guy's playing with a full mouth.
That's, that doesn't make that just literally no sense.
Open your mouth and say looney tunes, right?
Uh, folks, let's get on.
One, if I may, with the show and at the same time on with the Joe,
it's a new year.
I am brain dead.
Even though I did have a $3 .25 cup of coffee this morning, I still feel asleep.
Outrageous.
$3 .25 for a single cup.
$6 for bottomless coffee.
Outrageous.
I've never been serving breakfast should offer you bottomless coffee.
And it should be at most $3.
I was on my way to me pad at the diner for breakfast,
and I was late because I found a man face down in the street.
I thought he was dead.
I pushed him with my foot a little bit and he was real stiff.
Yeah.
And I was like, hey, buddy,
is it a bad sign that I was jealous of this man
when I heard he might be dead?
I'll tell you, he looked, he just looked at, he did have a bottle of booze in his back pocket.
So I couldn't tell if he just face planted drunk or he looked dead, though.
Yeah.
And the stiffness of his arm maybe feel that I called 911.
They said in a cool 12 minutes later, they called me back and they were like, so we're leaving soon.
Where is he again?
Like it's like, forget it.
If you're in the process of going down, you're done.
You're done.
How was the gentleman dressed?
Sweat shirt, jeans that both looked, you know, not new, but clean.
And then loafers with no socks.
The way you'd think a drunk would dress like, you know, that had a house,
but just was like, I'm fucking done with this bullshit.
Right.
I, most disturbing thing, one of the most disturbing things I ever saw in New York was a guy in a
full suit, more like rush hour in the morning, laying face down, seemingly dead outside of a
subway station.
And, and moss, hundreds of people just walking around his body.
Yeah, got to get to work.
No, I'm like, it's not like I would have been less concerned if it was a homeless guy,
but like something about a guy in a suit, lying there dead, you're like, what happened here?
And why does no one care?
Well, did you do anything?
I didn't know.
So you're just like the, I was late for work.
You're part of the problem, Pat, you know, it's this rat race.
I've always said, and this is my own phrase I made this up many years ago.
If you're not part of the, if you're not part of the solution, you're part of the problem.
Yeah.
I'm very proud of the coining that phrase and I made a phrase.
If you got time to lean, you got time to clean.
That was me, right?
Now, Joe, why did you tell our Kelly to do what he did?
For a period of 20 plus years.
Listen, man, you know, you, you would know had you been at the taping of my one hour special,
which was special to me.
And my many of my close friends were there.
You thought you needed to go see a Rod Stewart concert and it wasn't Rod Stewart,
but it was an anniversary gift for my wife's parents that was set in stone long before your show.
You would know that I took shots, hard shots at our Kelly in that special.
I can't believe this man is still working.
This is outrageous.
It's been completely, it's been insane since the Chappelle days.
I remember seeing that's the P on your sketch and I was like,
what's funny about this though?
The situation like why is this a joke?
The sketch was very funny.
It was, but the situation itself was, was dire.
I watch all six parts of surviving our Kelly.
Took a lifetime documentary.
What the fuck is going on anymore?
Turned down by HBO, turned down by Netflix.
Netflix has 14 million shows and they were like, no, not for us.
Lifetime had to bring you the news.
I've never been one for Frontier Justice as you know.
I've always sort of criticized that sort of Twitter lynching thing that everybody does now.
I do believe in due process, but for Christ's sakes, guys.
If we need, maybe that is the only way.
If we need lifetime to be the ones that bring fucking justice to the Arkelli victim.
Well, the fucker police or anybody doing anything about this.
And by the way, it seems to be where they're still not.
The only celebrity who would appear and it was John Legend,
who's a guy I've never liked much.
I think a singing voice sounds like the cowardly lion,
but many, many people would not speak out against Arkelli.
It's like, why?
The guy doesn't have power anymore.
He's just a creepy old perv.
And then what's interesting to me is everybody knows about pissing on the young girls,
the 14 year old girls, etc.
Everyone knows that.
But there's talk to these survivors,
like they go back into the room where Arkelli kept them for years.
And they'll look at the room and be like,
this is where some of the most depraved things you could ever imagine took place and start crying.
And you're like, what are we talking about beyond peeing on children?
That's what they never get into specifics, thankfully.
Right. But you're just like, how far did this go?
Everyone who goes into a room where they used to be with Arkelli starts sobbing.
Right.
And the suggestion is that we're through the looking glass
in terms of what these people went through.
Yeah. Well, it's a dark scene.
It's a dark scene.
It's real bad.
Guys got some hang -ups, clearly.
And all these celebrities are like,
sorry, I shouldn't have made a song with them.
And then like, when did you make a song with them?
2017.
It's like, oh, so you knew.
Oh no, that's what my whole thing was always.
Like, it was like,
it's funny because now I think we need a little more understanding about
the separation of artists and the art.
But back then, we had zero on.
We had zero ability to not separate it.
It was like, everybody was like,
people would be doing songs with a guy.
I'd be like, yeah, he's skinned a three -year -old alive last week.
Geez.
But that's not, you know,
there's a difference between his art and the artist.
I can separate it.
It was so out of control back then,
people doing shit with Arkelli,
you know, Lady Gaga did something two, three years ago and then
she's releasing all these big statements about how she's ashamed of it.
And I was like, what is that?
And then I'm like, oh, right.
She's trying to win an Oscar.
Everyone's got their own fucking motive.
She doesn't feel ashamed.
What she do.
She probably made five million dollars off that song.
She's not donated a dime to anyone.
Well, what did she do?
A song with Arkelli?
Three years ago.
Did a song with Arkelli.
And then there was a very graphically sexual song.
She's just full of fucking shit.
The song's called, like,
fuck me in the butt.
It's like the name of the song.
Hey, appropriate name, because who the hell wants to look at that face?
All right.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Bradley Cooper did, I'll tell you that.
This is what you tune into.
You seen that star as born yet?
No.
Why the fuck would I want to watch that fucking movie?
You'd probably like it.
You know, two of the supporting roles as I've told you.
Sam Elliott and Andy Dice Client.
I know. I want to see Andrew Dice clean it.
But I know he's never once going to say in the movie,
a brown star is born.
So now I don't want to see it.
He's gotten zero.
I thought he'd get all the awards talk.
He hasn't even been mentioned.
He's great in the movie.
He's always great.
He's a great actor.
He's great at playing like the lovable lug.
He's very good at it.
Not to say he's not probably great at other things,
but I just enjoy him in that type of role.
What the hell are we talking about on today's show?
Oh, bird box.
Bird box.
Which is a euphemism for a Pelican's vagina.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Oh, folks.
Folks.
One of the stupidest titles of a movie ever, bird box.
Bird box.
But we know we're going to do the movie corner
and stuff before we get into it.
But I will say this is a teaser.
About 25 minutes into this movie, I texted Pat
and I said, bird box, more like dog shit.
It's not a good movie, but we'll get back to that.
We'll get back to it.
I'll see you when I can help you the mother.
Let's take this.
Why don't you take us down to the corner?
Let's go over to the old corner store.
Before we do though, I'd like to send out
a real true RIP to Mr.
Marty Funkhouse or himself.
Oh, yeah.
So sad.
I'm so sad about that.
Truly one of the funniest men that ever walked the earth.
We're not going to see him in the new curb season,
which sucks because he's become the highlight of the show.
I heard he shopped two episodes.
That's just not true.
That might be true, I don't know.
I'm very sad.
And as it should be, the clip making heavy circulation right now
is him telling the joke to Seinfeld
on curb, which is his greatest scene ever.
And also a superb performance by David and Seinfeld in that scene.
Right. David screaming at him.
Can you just finish the fucking joke?
Yeah.
And then Seinfeld doubled over at the,
your cut is in the sink punch line.
Sure.
Going, I didn't know it was going to be that disgusting.
Yeah.
Well, it's a really, really funny scene.
I'm very sad about the Funk man.
Apparently was recently diagnosed with cancer.
I guess it was very aggressive.
I didn't know he had it.
Wait, two other people died too.
It was Funk Halzer.
It was three in one day.
And they were all 76, seriously, but they were all the same age too.
I don't remember who the other ones were.
That one affected me the most.
Was that, that was 2019, right?
Yeah.
Well, I'm going to write 2019.
Somebody's really a clubbing in your apartment complex.
I hear that club music every so often.
I can only assume it's my downstairs neighbor.
I usually can't hear it if I'm like listening to the TV club.
I don't have a problem with club music,
but it's one o 'clock on a Sunday.
What are you doing?
All right, so how weird is this?
I don't know.
It's, it's, it's odd.
Captain and Taneel was one of the other ones.
Yeah.
Also, six.
That affected me a little less.
I must say the captain died.
We're captain died, not Taneel, sorry.
Also, 65.
How weird is this?
Steve Buscemi's wife died one day ago.
65.
Everybody died.
I think she was 64.
No, 65.
Okay.
Is it right there?
And then the third person that died was 65.
Who the hell?
Oh yeah, mean Jean.
Mean Jean, right?
God, that's weird.
Four people at the age of 65.
That's odd.
And it was on January 65.
That's what I found particularly odd.
I, are we gonna, we're gonna do the Spidey verse?
You're gonna see this shit?
Should I save it for an episode?
I can save it just in case.
I don't give a shit.
You can, well, now fucking save it.
I don't want to see it.
I don't care.
I'd like to do Aquaman.
We can, we'll come over to the house.
Let me give you three months notice.
All right.
And we'll watch Aquaman in late April.
We're going to the movie corner?
We're going to the movie corner.
I am gonna save Spidey verse.
Maybe you check it out.
All right.
I've got a lot to say about that picture.
Let's go with one of my favorite shows of the year.
It was a limited series.
Whatever you want to call it.
Showtimes Escape from Danimora.
I heard this is great.
Sure.
Basically, they're running from this serial killer named Dan Amora.
Okay, folks.
Directed by Ben Stiller,
who I think much like Danny DeVito will be a guy that just
never gets the respect he deserves for being a really gifted director
because Zack and career were so successful.
But he's a really good director cast in this thing,
especially for Showtime.
Patricia Arquette, Paul Dano, or Dana,
and the great Benicio del Toro,
giving one of his best performances.
It's the story,
news story a few years back about a woman who
snuck two convicts out of prison.
She was banging them both, trying to pit them against each other, etc.
And it's a seven -part, I think,
so seven -hour movie.
It's very funny.
It's very exciting.
Del Toro is incredible about it.
It's funny.
Stealing the show is this guy, Eric Lang,
who plays Patricia Arquette's very dumb husband.
He provides most of the comic relief.
He is extremely funny this, dude,
and really good at playing an idiot.
Supporting cast has got Bonnie Hunt,
who I've loved since I was a little kid.
David Morse, who's always great.
I love David Morse.
Just a super entertaining movie.
The one question I had is that like
the big part of every article about this case
was talking about how the Benicio del Toro character had a giant dick.
And it was like a legendary dick.
And in a seven -hour movie,
they never mentioned the man's dick.
I found that out.
I got to be honest with you.
In a 90 -minute movie,
if I don't hear a mention of a dick,
I don't even want to say it.
I don't want to hear talking about the dicks.
That's an excuse, inexcusable for step.
Seven hours, no dick.
Give me a fucking break.
It's really good.
And one of the, my favorite TV moment of the year
is the end of maybe episode four or something.
And Patty Arquette is like,
you know, they're kind of talking and figuring it out.
And Del Toro gets in their face and goes,
his eyes get real wide.
He's been talking normally for the entire run of the show.
And he goes,
don't tell anybody in a monster voice.
And it's insane.
It's like a Nicholas Cage move.
And it's how that episode ends.
Clearly, Del Toro was like,
I'm going to try something on this next day.
And it reminds me of how much I love those little moments like that,
where people just do something insane.
Because in real life, people do insane shit all the time.
So many movies and TV shows are boring as fuck.
I admire that they went with it and that still are left it in the cut
and ended the episode on it.
I fucking loved it.
Check it out.
All right.
I watched the documentary after porn ends three.
Which is the word installment in the after the porn, after porn and series.
Yeah, it was fine.
I mean, you know, the first one I thought was really good.
I thought the stories were a bit more diverse.
And there was a little more left to the sort of
to your own interpretation about moments that sort of seemed maybe darker than they were being conveyed
or more hopeful or whatever it was that you took away from it.
I felt like it left the viewer with a little room to kind of draw their own conclusions about
is porn, bad or good or whatever.
This one was a little more on the nose.
It was kind of like there were happy stories and then there were sad stories.
And there was kind of not a lot of in between or gray area.
But I watched it mainly because I was always a big
Christy Canyon fan since I was a kid and she's in it.
And I wanted to see what she was like.
And she's awesome.
I don't have one fucking regret.
I had a blast.
You know, she's like, I do radio now.
It was awesome.
I fucked everybody.
I loved it.
Like she, it's like the most,
it's like the greatest example of like sexual positivity and ownership and whatever.
And then I also wanted to watch it because Bonnie Rotten,
who somebody I have done a few podcasts with,
I met her through my friend Eddie Ifte.
And I know she left the business and I just want to
curious like I wonder how she's doing and she's doing very well.
She's got a daughter and she's married and she's got a very nice life.
And she seems to have no regrets, which is great.
So, you know, it was an interesting watch, you know, but
do they show you any hardcore porn and the
they show like little clips and you certainly see some like boobs and stuff in it.
But it's you're not seeing like insertion and gizz and stuff like that.
Sure.
You know, it's an R -rated documentary.
It's not.
Right.
I wouldn't watch it with my mom.
It's with that way.
In a similar vein, I listen to the audio book if I may recommend an audio book
by John Ronson, who's a really great author who did the
the book about like 10 people whose lives were ruined by Twitter.
Okay.
Take this. I gotta pee.
All right.
His book, that's a fantastic book.
Like the lady who tweeted the joke about, I'm going to Africa.
I hope I don't get AIDS.
Then she got on a plane and by the time the plane ended her life and career were over.
It's a fascinating book called, if you'll wait, please.
So, you've been publicly shamed and I recommend it highly.
He's written many great books.
But John Ronson did a podcast.
I guess about a year ago, that was about porn.
And this new audio book, which is only like three hours, focuses in on
one specific porn star in her kind of tragic end to her life.
So, the butterfly effect was his first porn and it was like how porn affects everybody
from the top on down. Great audio book that I listened to.
And this new one is called The Last Days of August.
The Last Days of August aims, who is a porn star that I have long loved, sort of a more recent one.
She hung herself in a park.
So, they talked to her husband and you don't really get a lot of answers.
It raises a lot of questions.
But it was fascinating. It was muddy.
You talk to all sorts of like, I mean, the porn world has amazing characters in it.
I recommend it. I think I got the audio book for like three bucks, so check it out.
My next picture, I'm going to go into, is called Den of Thieves,
starring Ice Cube, Sun, Gerard Butler.
Den of Thieves, I've heard from all kinds of people. They're like, it's actually pretty
fucking good. That's the review I always hear. And it was. It was kind of a really poor man's
heat. I mean, obviously we're talking about Gerard Butler in 50 Cent and not near on Pacino here.
But Den of Thieves is a very entertaining action movie. It's like two and a half hours
for no reason at all. It's got incredible shootouts and action in it. Gerard Butler is great
as like an alcoholic burnout. He looks terrible. It's perfect for the role.
Somebody pointed out to me that in the best shootout in the movie, there are no extras in any
of the cars. It's supposed to be a traffic jam. I wish nobody had told me that because it really
ruined my enjoyment of it. But the movie is new to streaming and I think it's on showtime.
And I gotta tell you, it's an entertaining picture. It's stupid as hell. But if you like cops
and robbershit, it's a really good example of like a second tier gym. All right.
Okay. Your second choice. I watched a documentary called Score
which was about film composers. And it was great. They just kind of go through the history of
music composition for film like why it started with silent movies, obviously. And the reason they
started to add music live music to its showings of silent movies was to drown out the sound of the
film real going. Right. And yeah. And then it became part of film in a staple. And they kind of
take it from there. They interview all their great composers of our time. You hit the middle
of this thing. They give you like a 20 minute chunk on John Williams. Yeah. Which is awesome.
Everybody's like every single person in the thing from like Hans Zimmer to Danny Elfman is like
he's God. Right. You know, like, you know, so I'm on the airplane watching this thing. They're
showing the finale, the climactic scene of ET. I'm crying my eyes out.
For just getting the chills and how you know, just getting so swept away by the these movie moments.
They do a big thing on Elfman too. How Elfman kind of was like the, you know, kind of took up the
mantle of John, you know, it was sort of the second coming of a John Williams type. Right.
And how the Batman theme was what defined him like he had done this thing that nobody had ever done
before. With a piece of Batman theme. Well, he was, they were saying like nobody had made
nobody had kind of done the John Williams thing except with that type of tone before.
Okay. You know, like, it was something along those lines. And he was saying like, yeah,
there was no real prototype for a movie theme like that. So I don't know, you know, there's more
to it than I understood, but it's as far as music theory goes, but it was a great documentary.
It was a nice little watch and it was fun getting this here from the composer's Hans Zimmer and you
know, and all the others I mentioned and many, many, you know, Hans Zimmer played Coachella like two
years ago. I didn't know that played like his biggest themes. And like apparently it was a highlight
of the fest. What do you see it on the airplane? That's where I said I was on the plane. Where,
where, Joe, it doesn't mean I can go take a flight so I can watch it. Well, why not?
Live a little. Is it on a streaming service or a new idea? All right. I didn't seek it out
after I got off the plane. I just, I saw it. It was overplayed. Fair enough. I'm sure you can rent it
on iTunes or something. From my last picture, I would love to discuss a movie called Arizona
that I watched. Apparently it was supposed to be the directorial debut of Danny McBride and
star Seth Rogan. Instead, it starred Danny McBride and had a tiny role for Seth Rogan.
Caitlin Olson has a tiny role in it. David Allen Greer has a tiny role in it.
It's a comedy. It's a, like a super dark comedy, but it's, it's set in Arizona. Believe it or not.
Danny McBride is like a guy who's pissed because he bought a house from some realtor and it did not,
you know, it was a, a bum deal basically. He goes in, he's yelling at Seth Rogan like you fucked
me over and he accidentally kills him. The star of the movie, Rosemary DeWitt, who's a great actress,
very likable. The best part of this movie I would say. Witnesses it and then for the rest of the movie,
basically, is being stalked by Danny McBride who kills 15 people. And really, at some point,
about halfway through, I was like, oh, so this is just like a Friday the 13th movie with Danny McBride.
It's kind of like horror. He just keeps killing people. Why does he kill 5th? Why? It's one of those
things where he keeps trying to get out of his initial situation and he keeps having to kill everyone
that comes by. I thought the movie was a complete drag. It's, you know, I already have very low
thoughts of humanity. So I don't necessarily need to see a movie about how bad humanity is.
But not a laugh to be had. I thought it was just a real dreary drag. So all I can really say about it,
it wasn't really funny or exciting or scary or suspenseful. And after the first person dies and
the second person dies, you're kind of like, oh boy, this is going to be like a Cohen Brothers type
thing or like a simple plan where, you know, things go from bad to worse. But the difference is
you felt each death in those movies. You were like, oh, God, these are good people. Yeah, you know,
who made a mistake. Danny McBride is a piece of shit who continues being a piece of shit for two
hours. So every person he kills, you get to meet them for one minute, you know, nothing about them.
And then Danny McBride kills them. And he feels nothing about it. You don't care about the people
because they haven't been set up well in any way. So you're just kind of watching people die. It had
the exact same emotional impact of a Friday the 13th movie, which is to say none. I can't recommend
the movie. That was harsh. You would hit on that one. I'm sorry. It's a well made movie. I'll say
one positive thing about it. I like, I like, I like your style. I will end with a re watch. I tried
to do again, horror fans. Tell me what I'm missing. Tell me what I'm missing. Night breed. Never
saying it on it on the director's cut. Never watched it. Just go trade it into me, but it's fucking
worthless. It's a terrible movie. I've tried over and over again since it came out on video when
I was like 13. Clive Barker. And yeah, it was the follow up to Hellraiser. I couldn't wait to see
this thing. I thought Clive Barker's doing a movie about monsters. And there's all kinds of crazy
monsters in it. And this is going to be amazing. This movie fucking sucks. It plays like a sort of
monster. It's it's fucking terrible. Do you watch the director's cut? I tried watching the director's
cut. All I got out of that was it's longer, right? Which is not what you usually want in a movie
that sucks. People think that it's a divisive film, but there are people out there that think this
thing is a classic. I want to hear from those people. Tell me what I am missing in this thing. Yeah,
fucking sucks. And I can't stand a movie where there are monsters that talk like contemporary human
beings. Sure. You know, it's I'm sorry. It's dumb when a monster says fuck. It's just stupid. It's
stupid. Unless it's ready. Yeah. We were like, yeah, this was like a creep that died and came back.
So it kind of makes sense. You don't want to see a Frankenstein being like son of a bitch. Yeah,
so yeah, fire, this fucking fire. Yeah. I hate the movie. I don't think Clive Barker has made a
good film since Hellraiser. I think Lord of Illusions is it flirts with being good in moments
backula. That's backula and the guy that plays the the the Kroger boss from a
Seinfeld is in it. Okay, I had seen it. You know, like I said, it flirts with being pretty cool,
but it just never grabs you fully. You know, I can't remember other movies Clive Barker directed
right now after Hellraiser. I know he isn't directed much, but I know midnight meat train was
based on one of his. Again, I think that movie is very whatever. He didn't direct it, but
anyway, let me know what I don't get and we can go ahead and slide on into our review of the day.
And that review is about Sandy Bullock as Bird Box. That's her character's name.
Her name is Jenny Bird Box. Blindfolded Utah teen crashes car while doing the Bird Box challenge,
which just came up when I googled it, people you're stupid. It's, well, this is what happens
when you when you when you live your entire life online. Now people are seeing movies and thinking
that what they need to do is take things from movies and put them into real life in some way,
shape, or form, usually under the guise of these stupid fucking challenges. Yeah. It's like
asshole. Do you not understand how a movie works? Do you not understand that it's impossible
because it's a movie? You stupid fucking idiot. Yeah. Jesus Christ man. Like it's fucking crazy.
But I guess that's always happened. You know, people have always seen stuff in movies and thought like,
well, I guess I could try to fly if Superman did. You know what? It's you know what? Keep doing it.
It's it's natural selection. If you're so fucking stupid that you're going to put on a blindfold
and drive your car, go ahead. Get out of here. We don't need you. You're not contributing.
I thought I could have sex after I saw a pornographic film and I learned that I can't.
I knew going in. That wasn't happening to me. Yeah. Bird Box is a post -pop
elliptic movie that follows a woman with a pair of children dubbed boy and girl
who must make it through a forest and a river blindfolded to avoid supernatural entities,
which caused people who see them to die by suicide or force others to look.
The cast is stacked. It's got John Malkovich. It's got Lil Rail. It's got Sarah Paulson,
Sandy Bulls, BD Wong, Jackie Weaver, machine gun Kelly, who everyone is trying to make into an actor.
Rebecca Pigeon in a very brief role. Yeah. She's in it.
I don't know if it was made for Netflix or if it was one of these they bought up.
Like apparently Netflix passed on homes in Watson and Netflix doesn't pass on.
Shit. Yeah. Netflix is adhering to a strict, we'll produce fucking anything policy.
Right. I couldn't believe Kevin Smith just said they turned down Malkrats too.
Who's making his call in the shot? I don't know. But Bird Box, it definitely doesn't feel,
it feels like a movie that was probably made for Netflix. It doesn't feel like the kind of movie
that they wouldn't release because it wasn't up to snuff because people fucking love this movie.
It's a terrible movie. They absolutely love it. I have heard nothing but raves.
It's the poor man's quiet place and quiet place does not hold up to second viewings.
It's a ludicrous movie that really worked. It was super effective in terms of a first viewing
and not beyond that. Somebody recently pointed out yet another criticism of quiet place to me.
Yeah. That I thought was really great. I wish I could remember who says maybe they go,
so let me get this straight. Your kids 11 years old and you just now are taking them to the waterfall
where you're able to talk. What? Like you've just kept this from the whole time.
There are a million plot holes in that movie. There are in Bird Box as well. I found this thing
passable at best. At a certain point it turns into the river wild. I always enjoy things on the river
but it wasn't even as cool as the river wild. Let's start with the notion that a blind folded woman
could somehow row a boat down a river for 48 hours. Let me tell you that. It's so crazy.
Folks, it is hard to paddle a boat with no blindfold. When I go on these river rafting trips,
I used to go on a Missouri or whatever, invariably within 10 minutes a group of smart people would wind
up hung up in some little side patch of grass and people getting thorns in their hair and stuff.
It's simply not feasible but fine. It's just to me, even if you're willing to look past the logic
problems of the movie, for example, them driving a car with unable to look out the windows or anything.
Well, they drive. I thought it was a cool little device that they drive. They black out the windows
of the car because they can't look at anything because they don't go crazy. Then they drive the car
using the GPS with the screen and they basically do it like a video game, which I thought was super
cool. Then they get to the supermarket they're driving you to get supplies and somehow without knowing
what part of the supermarket they've crashed into or where in the parking lot they've landed with
this car, they somehow know exactly how to get into the supermarket without looking. You've got
it should just be 10 paces up. What world was he living in before this apocalyptic thing happened?
I'm saying. It's so nuts. Before we get off the subject, a little real friend of mine. I've
known for years. I think he's a great actor. I think he's a fucking hilarious comedian.
They gave him the role that you've heard me complain about on this show many times. They may
can be the black guy who has the answer. The mystical, he comes in and he goes, it's the end of days.
In Morocco, they refer to it as days, Moritees, whatever the fuck. He starts rattling off all these
around the world cultures and customs about what this means. Then it's because he's writing a novel
that he carries on him about the end of the world. It's so ridiculous. And he gives this
dissertation on the end of days, by the way, five minutes into the fucking movie. As soon as they
get trapped in the house, he's like, you know what's going on here? It's this. If anyone could say
to have stolen the picture, it'd be Malkovich. He does a good job as a guy who hates the world.
When you agree, though, at this point, Malkovich is another one just mailing in at this point.
He's mailing it. Just showing up and being the guy being like, I said, you are a fucking idiot.
That's all he does anymore. And that's who he is in this. What the fuck are you doing? Don't put the
birds in the oven. That's all it is. That's just, you know, it's like, all right. He brings things
to life a little bit. He has a weird take on things that I enjoy. Looking just
crazier and crazier to the older he gets. It says here, Netflix report of the bird box had the
biggest seven day viewership for any of its original films to date with over 45 million accounts
viewing it. This claim has been met with skepticism from analysts who cited a complete lack of
independent verification. And this is what Netflix does. They feel like they don't have to,
they won't release their ratings. No. They won't tell you who's watching anything.
Just once in a while, they'll be like, you know, this was kind of the biggest movie of all time.
And then you're like, but wait a minute. What? Yeah. Yeah. I find them shady at best. Netflix is
basically, it's, it's, you're talking to Kenny Powers. Yes. You know, it's like, all right,
I guess if you say so. You know, yeah, we, we accounted for 99 % of all TV viewership this year.
And you're like, what? Have you been to a meeting in Netflix? I've pitched there. Yeah.
I wanted to, it was like a Tuesday 1 p .m. meeting. This place, you would have thought you were at a
fucking Los Angeles nightclub. There's, there's serving drinks. There's a coffee bar. There's
200 people in the lobby of this place. Yeah, it's nuts. They have to go up. They got like 18
assistants coming down. Like, are you here to see so -and -so? You're here to see so -and -so? Yeah, it's a scene
over there, man. I was like, wow, that's, I mean, I get that it's supposed to be dazzling me
or whatever. Then I get brought up for my meeting. I'm in like some abandoned conference room. And I's
like, oh, so you put all your money in the lobby. Yeah, yeah. So everyone thinks that I go to the lobby.
They get that food bar down there. Yeah. Unless that's that's the level I'm at is that they brought
me to an abandoned conference. No, that's sort of the where I was in a sort of darkened corner room
pitching. Yeah. Uh, you know, it's uh, Sandy Bullock delivers a nice performance in this thing.
She's always great. She's, I never realized what a crush I have on Sandra Bullock, by the way.
Jesus, she's in still an incredibly intriguing woman. The what? I, I don't like her as serious
role time stamp on. I don't mean like that. I mean, like, after all these years, I still look at her
in a very swept away. I think her appeal is in romantic comedies. Um, her screaming like my kids
and all that. I don't find her to be particularly great in those roles. She's got kind of the Julia
Roberts thing where it's like, yeah, we know you're acting. But uh, this is the first time I've ever seen
Bullock succumbed to the, uh, the pressures of, uh, surgery. She looked like Michael Jackson to me
in this. But she had plastic surgery. I never thought so. Or she'd done a very good job. And
this movie to me, I could not shake how much she looked like Michael Jackson. I didn't think she
looked like she had surgery in this. Okay. Maybe I don't think so. I don't know. Maybe I got to watch
it again. Or maybe she, she didn't. And she just grew up to look like Michael Jackson. It looks like
old MJ. Um, I find her, uh, striking, uh, and I did injury. Well, you're attracted to Michael Jackson.
Yeah. I want to fuck Michael Jackson. Yeah. And I have to old. And I got zero. A lot out of it.
Yeah. You know, uh, you know, I only wanted to get was a ride on that Ferris wheel. I got nothing.
Sure. Uh, the, uh, I liked Bullock's performance in this. And I, um, I liked, she was about one of
the only people I liked in the whole movie. Um, the, the, they never show the monster. I mean, of course
there were little screaming in for you in the middle of the movie review. Um, they didn't show the
monster because they designed a monster. These creatures that you see that make you see your greatest
fears or whatever that it is. Right. They designed one of these things and it was so ridiculous looking
that Sandra Bullock was lack, couldn't stop laughing in between the tapes about them. Uh, and then they
released pictures of it. And it looked, it did look ridiculous. Yeah. Uh, except for movie web .com
who said that it looked chilling. I, I don't know. I'm addicted to movie web. I can't stop going to
it. Very few websites make me as angry as they do anymore. Well, I've never, I've never been.
It's a lot of clickbait anymore on there. But, uh, but, um, and I don't know what they're watching,
but they're watching something that I'm not. Yeah. Uh, but anyway, um, I, uh, I just thought the movie
sucked. And, you know, it's, it's, you know, the, the, there were some decent sequences that were
sort of suspenseful, quite frankly too. There's this fear throughout the film as the world starts to deteriorate
of, you know, there are these people out there that have seen these creatures and haven't killed
themselves and want you to look at them now. And I'm like, okay, so then what's the problem? Right.
So then look at it and become one of these other people. Well, they don't seem happy.
They didn't seem unhappy. They seem like they were driving around having a good time. That's true.
Uh, you know, there was, there was also this thing where they let the one guy into the house, but his
eyes didn't look crazy. Yeah. And then he turned out to be under the influence of the creatures,
which I was like, okay, I guess that's something that's evolving. Like your eyes don't change when
you look at these things. But then at the end, when she goes into the blind refuge, the first
thing they do is check their eyes and then they go, oh, they're okay. It's like, well, are they?
Because you check the other, you check the, the English guy's eyes and he wasn't okay. So what?
Yeah. They did a little, you know, these movies live and die on establishing the rules and sticking
to them. And this movie seemed to just play real fast and lose with those rules.
Some cool little elements, Rebecca Pigeon killing herself by sitting down in fire and just being
engulfed in flames. I thought was really cool. I thought the whole hell -breaking loose scene was
great at the beginning. Yeah. I think it's a good scene. And I think the driving scene, even though
it was stupid, was cool. There were highlights to it. I didn't think it was a waste of my time,
but it's, I didn't like it. And I will continue to bitch about the dissolving middle class in this
country and the best example of it being entertainment. As we watched George Clooney sell fucking,
you know, carried coffee machines on. Yeah. And commercials that used to go to college kids
that were struggling to fight acting jobs. The fact that they got Sarah Paulson in this thing
in a six -minute role. You know, I'm sorry. It offends me. It offends me. She doesn't need that part.
That part, give that part to somebody that fucking needs it. Yeah. You're getting no,
and if you're a Sarah Paulson fan and you're excited that you see her name on this fucking thing,
which they do sell it with her name, I'd be pissed off turning it on. I'd be like, wait,
she's dead in the first five minutes. Right. I'd be pissed. It's, you know, that that really bothers me,
man. That really bothers me. How do you feel about every voiceover commercial going to John Hamm or
Jeff Bridger? It's crazy. It's crazy. It's like, it's like these, these were jobs for people that
were trying to work their way up or people that couldn't make it in the, in the character or leading
man side of, or woman side of things. So then they would get jobs in advertising. And that's where they
made their bread and butter. And it's, they're taking it away from people. I think it's fucking insane.
All voice roles and animation are played by celebrities. Oh, it's ridiculous. It makes no sense.
Like John Hamm doing a car commercial or doing every car commercial as he does now. You're like, no,
you're an amazing looking man. Go do work in movies and make all that money and let the people who
don't look like you record it because at best, you're like, who's this? Oh, right. This, John Hamm.
This is not going to make you buy a car. It's ridiculous. It's ridiculous. I'm offended by it.
And I'm also offended too by, by transparent casting. Okay. When, when everybody gets into
the house in this movie, they've literally got one of every type of person in this house. And it's
like, you know what guys? Here's why bothers me. Diversity does not bother me. Other ethnicities on
screen that aren't white people that does not bother me. I am in full support of both of those things.
How fucking stupid do you think I am that I'm supposed to believe that somehow you got a perfect
array of people in this house because God forbid. And here's what this is what gets me people.
God forbid these people casting these things who are trying so desperately to show you they're not racist.
God forbid they actually act in a not racist way and just put four black people in it instead.
Instead, they want to insult your intelligence and go, look, there's a black person and an Asian
person. And it's like when they did the fucking live Christmas story that takes place in the 40s.
And the couple was an interracial cut. You're like, I'm sorry. You expect me to believe that in
the 40s, there's this interracial cup that there was a movie about this far from heaven. We know how
this was treated back then. You expect and you're going to tell me I'm racist because I'm finding
this odd that you're not calling any attention to it in the 40 because God forbid they just do a
Christmas story with a black family. They won't do that because they're fucking racist. Instead,
they want to make you feel guilty about it. This movie was straight up college brochure style. It was
Hispanic, Asian, black, white. They had they did have one of each and it was glaringly obvious.
They had the girl from one of my favorite movies last year, Patty Kakes about the the young kind of
heavy set white rapper. Oh, was that her? Was that the Patty Kakes? I fucking love Patty Kakes. She
was in this, you know, but really, they just kind of had one character too many. And then the
Beatty Wong thing where they're like, see if you die, if you watch this live, I'm like, that's what
you're giving Beatty Wong to do. Like, how about instead of risking, it's not like he's, it's not like,
hey, go out and fight the monster and see if it works. It's let's do something that might not
even help us too much and it'll probably kill you. It is true. And then it does. It is true. It's
like, so why? So what if he does see it on the TV screen and doesn't go crazy? Then what? Yeah,
then you, then you can watch it. Stupid. Uh, uh, big, big hug down from, from me on this one.
Hug down for me as well. And speaking of Sarah Paulson, I find her to be an okay actor. I liked her
most as Marsha Clark and the OJ think, but she's fine. She, she, she works in my building at work.
And I see her there all the time. And I'm like, well, what is she here for? And it was American horror
story before Christmas, but now she's there again. And I was like, oh, I thought American horror story
wrapped. What's going on? And I look, and I realize that she's there doing another Ryan Murphy show.
She does three Ryan Murphy shows a year. Right. And this one is called ratchet. So I'm like, oh,
I guess it's about a woman who's like a mess or whatever, ratchet. And I find out it's a prequel to
one floor over the kook who's nest where she plays young nurse ratchet. And clearly just because
ratchet now means like a hot mess, somebody thought that was a cute idea. But it's like, who gives a
shit about a ratchet prequel story? Young nurse ratchet. And then it's pulsing again. It's like,
she can't do everything. She can't be in lead in five shows a year. That's what's, that's what's
bothersome. It's, it's, it's, dude, it's the rich get richer. It's, it's, it's nothing more elegant
than that. It's just like we've complained about where they give the same five comedy parts,
the same five people. Yeah. It's every, every cool Hollywood comedy is, is Franco and, and
that whole crew. It's, it's, I'm tired of it, man. I'm tired of it. All the same people get to do
all the same shit. And you never see like a surprise, surprise person in a movie that you don't expect.
There are fucking actors out there that I'm just like, like I'm watching, like I rewatch witches
of Eastwick. Yeah. On the airplane. Tremendous fucking movie. Just a tremendous movie. I'm actually
going to read the book. I really, really love that movie. And it never disappoints every time I rewatch.
I wrote her name. I was a kid and I watched it. I watched it on CBS. You got Veronica Cartwright in this
thing. Uh -huh. Just tour to force performance. Give her some fucking parts in something. She's
incredible in this movie. She's incredible in everything she's ever in. Nobody knows who she is. Yeah.
It's like Jesus. Veronica Cartwright could walk down the sunset boulevard and asshole naked.
Right. And it wouldn't even make the news. We just had on the show Joanna Cassidy, who played
Eddie Valien's fiancee in Roger Rabbit. Yes. Another real sassy, brassy, broader. Yeah. And uh, she comes
in. She was funny as shit. It was a good role, but she brought like a really interesting energy
to it. And you know, they kept pushing Mary Lou Henner. I'm like, I don't need to see Mary Lou Henner do
this part. It doesn't make it. She's not right for it. You're just trying to cast a name. So Cassidy,
look, I'd be happy to see Mary Lou Henner in something at this point. I just don't think she's a
strong actress. But Cassidy comes in. Uh, she was fucking delightful. And I go up to her. She's in
Blade Runner as well, Joanna Cassidy, which I did not bring up. But I said, I gotta tell you,
I was like, you're so great in this. I remember you when I was a kid from Roger Rabbit. And uh,
I said, you know, the movie was very overwhelming because I had a crush on both you and Jessica Rabbit,
animated character. And she was just really funny and down to earth. And she's like, you know,
for the longest time, every part I went up for went to Kathleen Turner. And then it, you know, well,
I don't want to be too awful. But Kathleen Turner now looks very different than she did.
Right. And she's like, this woman still is like a knockout. She's 72 and she's beautiful. And she's
like, yeah, I just sort of thought like, all right, I'll stay in the game or whatever, but the parts
don't come. And it was a real bummer. She's great. And that's kind of the, as I've said before, the
good part of this job is you can cast anyone because all these old actors are waiting by the phone.
And they don't get the parts. And it really sucks. They're all just as good as they always were.
I don't know. It's a sad business. I'm sick of seeing the same five people. Yeah, I'm done.
I can't do it anymore. Anyway, like midnight run. Imagine, this is one that popped into my head.
Imagine a comedy coming out now. Start, you know, at that time, Robert DeNiro and Charles
Groden, those are not the people you would have thought would have appeared in that movie. No.
You never would have dreamed that those people would be in that movie. No.
And you'd never get a buddy movie with people like that now. No. Whereas you'd have so much fun.
I'm going to talk. Go ahead. Imagine if it's Nick Cage now, they finally put him in a big
budget movie. And it's this fucking Spideyverse movie because it's just his voice because they think
people hate him. They're dead wrong. People love Nicholas Cage. He's doing these five dollar direct
to DVD things because he made some stupid financial choices. But put him back in the movies. People
love Nicholas Cage. Right. Second of it. Well, speaking of midnight run too, you got what's his name
in there? The guy that was in Beverly Hills Cop one and two. Yeah, I thought Koto. No, no, no. Well,
I love Yafat. There's another guy you never hear from and didn't get enough work. No, the guy that
plays the other bounty hunter. Oh, yeah. I know who you're talking about. I don't know his name.
I think his name is Walsh in the movie. I already said no dick breath. That guy. Yeah.
He's like Ray. John Ashton. John Ashton. He does radio in like the Midwest now. It's like
the guy's one of the funniest fucking actors I've ever seen in anything. Yeah. Looks like a
looks like a Dennis Farina type. Yeah. Or Dennis Frans. Wait, which one is it? Frans.
Frans. Although Farina's in midnight run too. And you don't see him in things anymore just because
he's dead. And I don't think that's fair. Farina's another guy that I thought should have been in
more shit. Yeah. Right. That's our show people. Listen, if you're in Austin, Texas or near Austin,
Texas this week, this week starting Wednesday night. That's two days from now. I'll be a Cap City
comedy club through Saturday night. Bunch of shows. It's always fun there. Gonna have a good time
down in big old Texas as usual. Come on out to a show in March. I will be in Vegas. As I said,
bonkers comedy club. I think that's only two shows. And I got some other stuff coming up,
but we can save it for next time. Oh, January, February issue. It's a six six issues per year now.
But the so the Jan Feb issue of Penthouse. My I have a copy of it. It was very exciting to see.
My first ever fiction story has been officially published. It's not the first one I ever wrote,
but it's the first time I've been officially published as a fiction writer. It's called Wallace
and his checkerboard. I hope you enjoy it. It was a real thrill for me. It is absolutely a dream come
true. That's right. Very cool. In the print Penthouse. Yes. So I could buy it and have a valid reason
to have a Penthouse in my home. Yes. And what I would what I would really like is if you did buy it,
then I found it. And the only pages stuck together were my story pages. I would enjoy that.
And they're not erotic in any way. Your your tales? Zero eroticism. All right. I'll try it. I'll try it
anyway. I am Twitter and Instagram the Patrick Walsh cool kids Friday nights on Fox. They have us
on two weeks and then off for five weeks, because these people really know what they're doing. But
you can catch the reruns. You can catch us on Hulu. We're off for the next three weeks, but
check it out. We're doing well still. And I hope we get a season two. Next week on the show, Joe,
we are doing. Oh, we are. Phantasm. So if you've never seen it, check it out. Phantasm one. All right,
talk to yourself.