It's the bonus app. It's the bonus app. It's the bonus app. It's the bonus app. It's the bonus app.
Per March.
Pat, hello.
Hello, everybody. Joe and I,
even after pledging, we would see the film us together did not see the film together.
Joe has pledged to me that we will see Pat's cemetery together.
We'll see if he holds that promise or not.
But we saw it. We saw it separately. We have a lot to say.
We'll get to it.
In the meantime, what's going on? Joe, you're eating some comedy club pizza.
I mean, a little piece of pizza because I'm very hungry.
How is it, Dave, too?
Holden up.
It's delicious, surprisingly.
Okay.
Surprisingly delicious.
All right.
From flappers in Burbank.
Yeah.
Who would have knew? I never went a million years ago to order the pizza.
It came out during the show. I was like,
it smells awesome.
That looks like really good.
Their food is good.
But I was like, you know, you don't expect the pizza to be great, you know.
Right.
It's really good. It tastes like good pizza rea pizza.
All right.
You know, what are you drinking there, buddy?
This is a Topo Chico mineral water.
It's Mexican mineral water.
Mm -hmm.
Just doing a little hydrating.
Joe and I are going out tonight, painting the town.
Painting the town red.
Gonna see Cypress Hill.
Yeah.
It's Cypress Hill.
The first opener is Exhibit.
Now, what's Exhibit's big song?
I never liked Exhibit, if I'm being honest.
I like Exhibit.
What's his big song?
I know he's pimped my ride.
I mean, I don't know that he hit, but X was one of his single.
I think he'll give it to you.
No, he had a song called X that, like, Dr. Dre.
He had it, I'm called Restless, the Dr. Dre produced and so well.
I bet I'd know a couple of his songs, but never a fan.
And then after it, it's like the Hollywood Undead Academy is playing.
Now, what the hell is that?
But I am excited to see Sweet Sweet Cypress Hill.
I keep confusing the Hollywood Undead with the Hollywood Vampires.
Hollywood Vampires is like Johnny Depp, Keith Richards, Ed McMahon, David Spade, Corey Feldman, Bob Sagitt,
The Ghost of Sam Kenneson, Tom Arnold, and Susie Esman.
Susie Esman.
It's a good lineup.
Lisa Lamponelli.
Folks, how are you most importantly?
Are you taking care of yourself?
It's March.
The Iads of March.
It's coming in like a lion.
It's going out like a lion.
I got a little something to give the listeners that we haven't heard this in a while.
On the show.
Hold on.
Oh, crack that beer.
I'm just drinking a little Topo Chico.
I know, we talked about it.
You seem even higher than on last episode.
No, I know that I said Topo Chico, but that's all I'm drinking now, or I'd give you the crack.
No, no, no, I'm saying you seem, I'm saying you seem as if you've gotten even higher.
Like it's settling in.
It's quite possible.
Yeah.
I didn't say you were sneaking it.
Folks, I deserve to relax when the weekend rolls around because everybody's working for the weekend.
Everybody wants a little romance, and I'm no different.
I wish you guys could have seen literally what he just did with his head.
Pat's head just fell backwards like in the JFK final speech when he's playing the footage over and over.
Involuntarily.
It went back.
I know what I'm doing left.
What did you do all week, man?
Well, I had a week up in like Arrowhead, as you know, I came back.
You know, getting back into the groove.
There's a lot going on in town.
There's rumbles that the writer's guild is going to ask everyone to leave their agencies.
And basically the gist of it is agencies are now packaging things.
So they'll say we'll set this up for you.
But only if you use one of our actors and one of our directors and make a big UTA package or a big CAA package.
And people feel that's unethical.
You're supposed to just be working for your client because you take 10 % of their income.
That should be enough.
That should be why you're working hard for them because you benefit too.
And that's really the crux of the argument.
Neither side is really budging at all.
And also agencies are starting to get into producing.
So like your agency will be one of the producers on a show that you sell.
And that I think almost inarguably is a conflict of interest.
So I've been talking to some guild people.
They're doing amazing work.
We'll see what happens.
But it looks like we might be heading towards another sort of strike situation where writers are asked to leave their agencies.
I can't leave my agent.
My agent just doesn't represent me for writing.
I know.
And the problem is all these people who have worked and worked to get agents now worried because that's kind of like the big first target you got to hit.
If you want to become a successful writer is to get an agent.
People can't read your stuff without it.
So now all these people are very concerned.
And I get it.
It's a very complicated issue.
Why don't they just make it illegal for the agents to package things?
Why don't they just do that?
That's what they're trying to do.
Yeah.
That doesn't mean you have to leave your agent.
Well, the agencies won't negotiate that though.
They won't engage that point.
So here we are.
Which means they must be making a shit ton of money at it.
Of course.
That's why you want to be with a big agency.
Right.
This business sucks.
It does.
What do you think you do if you believe right now?
What would I do?
Yeah.
I'd get...
I'd sell my house.
I'd take my little nest egg.
And I'd buy a cool ranch.
I want to always buy a cool ranch where we...
Doritos.
Manufacture cool ranch Doritos.
But also I got a couple horses and I can ride around and...
You know, till the land a little bit.
I think I'd be a good like western style dad.
Pop some kids into the wife.
It's a nice way to put it.
And just live out there unforgiven style until finally you roll up
on a horse.
Get me drinking again.
And then we go and kill a lot of people.
I tell you that it's your services are needed.
Right.
My favorite scene in the history of movies is...
Clint Eastwood who has given up alcohol because of all the dark secrets tied to it in his past.
And he hears that Morgan Freeman has been killed his dear friend.
Yeah.
And propped up in front of a bar on display for all to see in the coffin.
Clint Eastwood without saying a word with no close up.
Grab the bottle of whiskey takes a giant swig.
Yeah.
One of the best scenes in all of movies.
Yeah, it's great.
It's great.
And this becomes a complete badass.
And the moral really is.
Always drink.
If you want to be awesome.
That's what the moral of that movie is.
It says a few other things.
It's like the scene at the world's end when they realize like what they're dealing with.
And finally.
Nick Frost.
Just takes the entire tray of shots after he's preaching so variety.
And he does it.
Each one he does he goes.
As he downs, he goes.
I should try that again.
I remember being very let down, but I've heard people love it and I should try it again.
It's fun.
You know, it's.
It's.
I like it.
I like those three.
It's like a nice little trilogy of films they may.
Sure.
Yeah.
Um, we don't do movie quarter on this, right?
No.
And the fact that you still have to ask.
I mean, I'd like to just talk about movies I saw, but then I would feel too much like path movie corners.
You don't do segments on the bonus app.
All right.
No plugs.
No segments.
It's just me and you.
All right.
We'll strike up a conversation.
Dazzle me.
Um, you want to see my dick?
No.
Uh, how far are you in the Pat Cemetery audio?
I'm about a third of the way through.
I keep falling asleep listening to it.
Michael C. Hall does an awesome job.
His voice is very soothing.
He's great at it.
And it might.
It might.
It might speak a lot to my general demeanor that I'm going to sleep to these types of books.
Right.
Um,
But I think I'm where he's very engaged right now.
Spoiler alert.
I think I'm where he's very engaged.
I seem to keep missing.
These elder sequence in the book.
I want to know what it's in there.
No, I know it's in there.
I just keep missing it.
I want to know what it's like in the book.
Like if it's scary and scary.
Yeah.
Uh, I'm excited to see the new one.
I hear it's very fucked up.
But, you know, I believe it when I say it.
Uh, I'm excited.
Yeah.
Here's blood drenched.
And I heard that what I've been reading is that everything that you see in the trailer that is basically
stuff that takes place in the original story is the stuff leading up to like when the movie then changes
and goes off in its own direction.
So.
You know, man, I look forward to it.
Uh, I think it's.
I don't know why you need to put a whole new spin on one of the greatest novel ever.
But okay.
Well, I read a really great review from.
I think it was trace thermon from bloody disgusting said basically he was like this.
Excuse me.
This is its own thing.
Uh -huh.
And it can exist in this universe.
It can exist alongside the Stephen King movie version and the classic book.
That book is pretty amazing.
I mean, they were like he describes their marriage in like two paragraphs.
It's the clearest portrayal of a marriage I've ever heard.
I was like, I get completely who these people are.
That's nothing to do with horror.
The man is just a great writer.
He paints these details great.
Movies always get them wrong.
Focus on the big moments.
They lose the small moments except for something like misery, which realized that's really a character movie at the end of the day.
Almost a comedy drama, but it's a character movie.
Well, I was instead of a horror movie.
I said you got to realize about the show.
I was surprised that his own adaptation of his own book with pet cemetery.
Yeah.
Left out.
The marital issues that they were having.
Unless they got cut out of the film, but they're so well written in the book.
Right at the top of the book, he's like, he says like the dad is tempted to just drive.
Yeah.
And ditch the family.
Right.
And, you know, when I watched that documentary about the making of pet cemetery,
they talked a lot about those themes in the book and like basically, you know,
and that this book, and that's why I dealt with sort of alcoholism and all these things,
this book was supposed to be about the sins of the father, like it's a story of the mistakes
that men make in trying to keep their family together and the things they hide from their family
and then how that comes back to ruin them, which I thought was interesting, especially when you consider
he's not happy with his family in the beginning of the book.
And the movie, they seem happy.
They just seem like they have normal movie kind of speed through that shit.
I hope this, you know, the original movie is probably 95 minutes, 97 minutes.
I hope this one takes its time.
I hope they try to do the book justice.
I hope it's not just like somebody who didn't read the book, but saw the other movie.
I hope it doesn't go the it route.
I hope a lot of things.
I don't know why Lithga is not doing the fucking main accent.
If fathers make Michael C Hall does an amazing one in the book adaptation.
You telling me Michael C Hall is a better actor than you John Lithga.
You acted circles around him on the Dexter show fourth season.
You were a great villain.
You blew him right off the screen.
I mean, Lithga is doing less of a voice than he did in third rock from the sun.
Yeah.
Yeah, usually not the most subtle performer, John.
Lithga.
I love the man.
But come on, man.
Turn it up.
Give us what we want to hear.
There's a movie coming out about the three women that murdered on behalf of Charles Manson.
It's written and directed by the woman who did American Psycho.
Mary Herron.
Yes.
She also did pet cemetery.
No, no.
It's two different people.
Mary Lambert.
Mary Lambert, you're right.
Did pet cemetery.
That's how few women directors there are.
I combine the two.
I like Mary Herron's work.
This fucking movie.
I was tearing my fucking hair out, dude.
The thing is, there's three women that murdered in Manson's cult in prison.
It's based on a true story.
And then a reporter goes into like get to know them and figure out what they were doing.
And like where their head was at.
There's a scene in this fucking trailer where the reporter goes.
Perhaps the only victims weren't the ones outside of this jet.
And I'm like, are you really trying to victimize the women that murdered on behalf of Manson right now?
Let's pump the brakes a little bit here, people.
Let's pump the sympathy brakes a little bit here, guys.
This is a little fucking nuts.
It's a little fucking nuts.
Come on.
All right.
That's all I'm saying.
That's all that's it.
That's it.
All right.
You know, that's all I got to say.
Let's get into us, dude.
I feel like I got a lot, a lot to say.
Let's talk about us.
I mean, first, let's talk about what's not fair about this.
Of course, you're going to compare it to get out with get out, which came out, I guess, about two years ago at this point.
Jordan Peele, it seemed like a movie that he had been honing and perfecting for a very long period of time.
It seemed like a movie where every step was thought out.
It seemed like a movie which had a lot in its mind.
And very smart and a lot to say, but never felt preachy.
It was also scary.
It was also very funny.
Everything worked.
One of certainly one of horror's best -ever debut films.
Those are unreasonable expectations to bring into his follow -up film.
But they're there.
And I think, first and foremost, what has to be said, and what I think anyone will say is it's no get out.
And the movie is certainly no get out.
That's what I'll say to start, Joe.
Lower your expectations.
I had really high expectations, and I think they kind of bit me in the ass.
I, um, I think, well, yeah, I agree with everything you said.
Yes.
It is no get out.
Um, I think the films.
Look, this is my opinion.
I don't know if I'm right or wrong.
I think when you do something as popular as get out.
And it's in it and it receives the critical acclaim that it does.
And it gets the accolades that it does.
And it's also as socially relevant as it was.
I don't think you're going to have a lot of people around you telling you what not to do.
Right.
At that point.
And this movie to me feels like a first draft of an interesting idea that should have been
rewritten a few times.
Uh, and should have been reigned in quite a bit.
It is a very, very big concept.
It is a very complicated concept, which becomes quite convoluted by the end of the film.
I would argue that it's a big conflict and not landed really well at all.
Like you don't, it's not a satisfying reveal when you find out what is going on.
But no, it's almost hokey.
It, it almost, yeah, it leaves you with a feeling of like really, you know.
And the audience, you could tell kind of wanted to be cool, but I also.
I remember walking out of get out and people were like fucking high -fiving each other.
Yeah.
Walking out of the empire strikes back.
This there was just kind of a quiet.
It felt like disappointment to me.
Jordan Peel is a great director.
There's great visual stuff in here.
He can direct the shit out of a horror movie.
I just felt like this would have been a great like premiere episode to the Twilight Zone.
It felt like a smaller Twilight Zone story.
It's not really landed very well as a feature film.
But it does make me excited to see his Twilight Zone.
Well, let's.
It made it did the opposite for me.
It's made me less excited.
And I hate saying that.
I hate saying that I met Jordan.
He's a very nice dude.
He's always been very nice when I've spoken to him.
I think he's very talented.
This made me less excited to see the Twilight Zone.
And as I pointed out to Pat yesterday, when I kind of step back and sort of thinking about this Twilight Zone reboot,
I was like, well, why was I excited?
All star cast Oscar winner at the helm.
CBS behind it.
They were behind the original.
Great.
Well, 2001, we saw a Twilight Zone reboot that CBS was behind with an all star cast that an Oscar winner was at the helm at.
And that that time was far as Whitaker.
I am concerned that this Twilight Zone is going to be a sort of retread or not a retread, but reminiscent of that 2001 Twilight Zone where the ideas are there.
The execution is not.
You just be excited to have a horror anthology on the air.
There's a million horror.
There's a million.
Look, there's a new creep show coming out.
I'm excited about all of it, but we're not talking about excited about anthologies.
We're talking about what did this movie do to my opinion about it.
And I will tell you, this movie to me at times felt a lot like that 2001 Twilight Zone where it was like this is an interesting idea.
But there is a lot of shit that needs to be cut out of this and a lot of screws that need it to be tightened that just weren't.
Let's start with the directing.
I think Peele is a great director and I think he's got a great eye and I think he does some really wonderful visual stuff.
But the aesthetic, there is no aesthetic consistency in this film.
It starts out with these gorgeous moving sweeping shots, slow moving cameras and it's gorgeous at the top of this thing.
And by halfway through, it's paint by numbers.
All of that goes away, all of it.
All of that great imagery and great framework and everything.
All of it goes away by halfway through the film.
So that's the first issue that I had with it was this is a disjointed piece of work.
This is something that starts with a very much a, you know, almost an, you know, an Argento kind of vibe to it or something like that.
And ends up feeling like a saw or something like that.
Do you think there was a stylistic choice or ran out of money choice and accidents?
No, I think it was, I didn't really notice the change in style.
I think it was a really big idea that didn't land and it was overly complicated.
I think one of the things that is taken away and so I think that with the themes in this film and the sequences being disjointed, so was the directing style.
Because there wasn't the basic core of a good script was not there.
It wasn't there.
It's a convoluted bulky script.
There's too much shit going on in it.
So now you're watching this movie.
And by the way, a mile of fucking minute, you're getting symbolism thrown at you.
And you're trying to fucking remember everything to see how it will be significant to this plot line.
That just becomes confusing after a while.
Because here's the thing, this isn't a fever dream movie.
This isn't an Argento movie.
This isn't a string of a bunch of sequences strung together to sort of give you a certain feeling or a certain mood or whatever.
It's not that.
This is a movie with a very fucking linear plot to it where everything gets explained.
So if you're going to make a movie like you got to pick, you can't do both because you're layering one thing on top of the other.
And you're trying to invest yourself in this linear story that moves and you're trying to relate to it.
And then all this other shit is getting tossed at you on top of it.
And you're trying to recognize why it's important and why it's there.
And then when you can't figure it out all at once, it just comes off as confusing.
It doesn't land.
And Tim Heideker and Terrible Casting, Elizabeth Moss as the couple.
They're clearly going for bigger comedy than the rest of the film was.
But it was also kind of like to what end?
I'm usually, I'm not a fucking genius on things, but I usually follow what the symbolism is, follow what the satire targets are.
I was just kind of like what is being satirized here?
I'm having a hard time following it.
I could see if they were right wingers because a lot of the theme of the movie was,
we're worried about the outsiders when the real problem is us Americans.
I think that's supposed to be a theme that's coming through in this movie.
I'll say it's not coming through super clearly.
But also, just like everything else, it wasn't quite landed right.
Whereas get out at the moment each of its targets hit, you'd feel this big collective knowing laugh from the audience of like,
oh, that feels that feels true.
That feels like an encounter I've had in my life.
And this all just felt very conjured up.
You know, it didn't feel real.
I saw this movie in a more or less pack theater.
For the first half of the film, people were laughing hysterically at the jokes.
They were gasping and squirming at the scares.
Good first half.
And then from the middle of the movie on through the end, it was dead silent.
The jokes were not hitting.
The scares were not landing.
People you could tell were confused.
It was, it's just, look, I describe this to my friend as I go,
it's like listening to a Steve Vy record.
It's like an art thing that's just not hitting.
It's just too showy.
It's too much.
And in my opinion, now there's going to be a lot of spoilers in this review.
In my opinion, this movie could have been a simple story about a doppelganger family trying
to get into the house to harm the main family.
It never had to leave that house.
It never had to be explained.
And all of these little commentaries could have still fucking been in there.
All of them.
And it would have been a streamlined, great, scary, fun experience.
And instead what you get is a movie that starts out and, first of all,
confusingly with facts, the top of the movie they give you facts about tunnels.
Yeah, that right off the bat, I thought, no, I never liked this.
You're catching me up on something that happened before the movie.
Before the movie starts, I just don't like it.
I know Star Wars does that, of course, but it's like, I don't know.
Something throws me off about it.
I was a little hopeful because unbreakable did that.
Yeah.
And I was like, what is comic books going to have to do with any of this?
And then it actually did pay off.
So I was like, oh, okay, cool.
So it starts there.
So right off the bat, you're thinking, what are tunnels going to have to do with any of this?
A lot of rabbit imagery.
A lot of rabbit.
A lot of rabbit material in the movie.
Yeah, it's, again, that's just another thing where it's just like,
it opens with the shot of these, we're not opens, but the credit sequence takes place.
Pretty much.
They really put a lot of focus on rabbits.
And really all you learn is that the people eat rabbits, the clones eat rabbits.
Yeah.
And the rabbits don't seem to be clones because they don't all look the same.
Right.
Which is just another confusing thing.
You know, and then so from that point, then it turns just into a straight up,
like, fucking, like, John Cainting movie.
That's like, this family's with a fat dad is going up to this cabin.
He's heavy.
You know, but you know what I mean?
Like, it's, you know.
It's a heavy set.
And, uh, and you're like, okay, this is fun.
And then they, and then Tim Heidecker comes into this thing.
And you're like, well, Tim's great as the,
sort of schmucky, you know, rich white guy character.
But then halfway through this thing,
Heidecker has to turn evil because his doppelganger.
And it's like, I'm supposed to take Tim Heidecker seriously in a monster.
I'm not buying it.
Sorry.
I thought he played that stuff pretty well.
He didn't play poorly.
He didn't play poorly, but it's distracting.
It's fucking Tim Heidecker.
It's distracting.
It's not good casting.
And they're, I'll say, you know, like if you're watching,
let's say, Boogie Knights, you know, like,
there's 100 movie cues in that,
our music cues in that movie that should all feel kind of two on the nose
or like two show offy.
But they all just kind of happen organically.
And you believe them as the song,
the people would be listening to and everything else.
This movie,
when a scary scene is starting,
they kind of accidentally turn on good vibrations by the beach boys
to get that kind of creepy sound effect.
And it felt super forced to me.
And I'm a man who really loves music moments and movies.
A bunch of my favorite moments, especially from 80s movies,
are when movies use music really well.
And I just thought it was clunky and not well done.
The juice wasn't worth the squeeze on a lot of those gigs.
Like the Alexa playing fuck the police instead of calling the police
is like kind of funny.
But then the kids are coming into the house to fight these doppelgangers
who could be lurking around any corner.
And like ice cube is blaring.
And you're like,
dude, this is hurting the tension.
This is hurting the tension, which let's get to the next thing.
And I said this to you on the phone after I saw it.
You want to talk about characters doing stupid shit.
I mean, there's a million moments in this movie where a character purposefully
goes upstairs after one of these things.
You're like, why would you do that?
Why would you ever do that?
Right.
It makes no sense.
At the end of the movie when they're fleeing,
she gets out of the fucking car and goes up to the guy.
Now, I guess given the ultimate twist,
that makes a little more sense.
Right.
But the kids going upstairs,
and then also to like, you know,
you've got two children who end up having to literally murder people.
Yeah.
And then at the end of the movie,
the kids got like PTSD because he got put into a locker.
What the fuck are you?
This is, this is bad.
And then you're supposed to be like,
oh yeah, at the beginning he was scared when he was locked in the closet.
See, I saw this kid murder a woman with a rock.
What are you talking about?
It should be said.
Lupita Niongo A is one of the most beautiful women in all of movies.
I'm sorry to take it there first.
It's not her must -of -fine and characteristic.
But what a lovely woman.
Yeah.
And a very good actress.
She does a lot with this movie.
She walks away with this movie.
She's playing a dual role.
She's playing her and her clone basically.
Spoiler alert.
But you know that.
You're listening to a podcast about something you may not have seen.
She's great in both roles.
She's really creepy in the bad role.
A little goofy in spots.
But I thought I thought by and large performance worked.
And she's good as the mom.
And really she's the one that when you think back on the movie,
all of her choices make sense and line up.
Some of the other stuff in the movie doesn't.
It definitely doesn't give you that feeling of like,
oh yeah, oh cool.
You just kind of like, oh.
And that's a shitty feeling to have on a movie like this
where the whole time you're just waiting for some final reveal.
The reveal is not great.
I'll say that.
Well, we can talk about the reveal.
There's a couple.
Your first reveal is these doppelgangers,
the tethered were created by, I guess, the government.
They just kind of say they created us.
And put into guess what an underground tunnel.
Where they also in the reason they were put down there was
because this was supposed to be a cloning experiment where
they cloned human beings.
But be up in cloning human beings they realized.
Because the reason they were cloning them was for puppetry.
They wanted to be able to control the people in society
with like doppelgangers of them behind closed doors.
The experiment went wrong because they found out
they could clone the body but not the soul.
And so they abandoned these clones in this subway tunnel.
I guess it was with a working escalator in it, by the way,
and full electricity.
That's never explained.
And spicken span, by the way.
Just one of the clean, this is an underground hallway
where lunatics have been living since the 70s.
And clean as a whistle, full working electricity,
everybody's healthy, aside from their mental state,
they seem to just be eating fine down there.
They're somehow getting an endless supply of rabbits.
And yet none of them are taking this escalator up to the ground level
that just works.
None of them are accidentally wandering on to this escalator
at any point.
Even because, by the way, if your clone walked in that direction,
you would walk up the escalator.
Right.
The who you're tethered to.
So that's never...
And again, this is the kind of thing.
I can show off a lot of questions when I'm watching comedy
or a horror movie.
I didn't even ask myself these questions.
I just knew I was not interested in what was going on.
I was not invested in what was going on.
It's a terrible reveal.
It's just...
And I've seen some YouTube commentaries on it
where they say, like, look, or explanations
whether they say, you know, this is a movie about the lower class.
These people are literally the lower class.
They're underground.
I'm like, look, that's all very interesting.
But it doesn't mean it's entertaining or fun to watch.
Again, Steve, I can play a guitar like nobody.
If Frank Zappa is not there being like, Steve, play this.
It sucks.
So I'm not saying this sucks, but, you know,
it's just a swing and a miss.
So anyway, that's the first big reveal at the end.
Is that these two...
What is her name again?
I never remember how to say it.
She is the...
Her twin that she was tethered to her doppelganger
were special because they had independent thought
and abilities from one another,
whereas everybody else did,
and everybody else was just kind of stuck together.
And therefore, her doppelganger needed to find her,
needed to kill her, and then make a statement.
The statement is...
Oh boy.
Hands across America.
Yeah.
Terrible.
Again, I get it.
It's about...
That was about feeding the poor and helping the lower clown.
And I get all that.
And right off the bat, they're showing you the clips
and they got the VHS cases on either side of the TV.
I love that nostalgia.
I love the vibe it was giving me.
Climax starts in the exact same way,
like on an old -fashioned TVVCR combo.
But just again, didn't really pay off.
Didn't really work.
Well, you got these...
This is the mission, the doppelganger, she says it.
Evil and Poia, I say right.
Lupita Nihanga.
Lupita?
Nihanga.
Lupita, okay.
All right.
Don't you want to get mad at me?
I'm not getting mad.
I'm mad at names.
Lupita.
Evil Lupita says...
She goes, she goes, we wanted to make a statement
because now it's our time.
Right.
And it wasn't enough for me to just kill you.
We need to make a statement.
So the statement is going to be hands across America
except it's all doppelgangers.
Now, here's the part they never explain.
She could have killed her easily.
At the beginning of the fucking movie,
she's got her chain to a goddamn table.
Right.
And she's going, I want to take my time with you.
Why?
Yeah.
The longer she's alive, the more of a threat she is
to you getting your job done.
You wouldn't do that.
You wouldn't play a fun game where somebody could
conceivably go get the cops
because you didn't execute your plan quickly enough.
Right.
You would kill these people immediately
and get them the fuck out of the way.
It really felt like the difference between, you know,
like, it's like the strokes, you know?
The first strokes album comes out.
They've been playing those songs for five years.
You're like, holy shit.
This album's amazing.
The second one comes out.
They just do the same thing again,
but it's still great and really entertaining.
So actually, it's a bad comparison.
It's terrible.
That's really worse.
Get out is like the first strokes album.
Perfect.
Come out of the gate swinging.
The second one is not like the second strokes album
which is awesome and which I highly recommend.
This is like this movie is like the fifth strokes album.
It's like the fifth stroke album where you're like,
I got it guys.
I'm not super into anything that happened here.
I never once felt scared.
It creates good atmosphere in fleeting moments.
But, you know, it represents a step back.
And I think what I'm trying to say with my strokes thing
that fell apart very quickly is that you put five, ten years
in your brain and you're always thinking about your next project.
And then you finally get the chance to do it.
And you come out swinging.
And it's all you thought about for years.
And this is what happens on a lot of people's second movie,
second album where you don't have five, ten years to think about it.
You got six months because they want to make some money out of you
while you're a hit.
And this felt sort of like that.
A lot of stuff felt half baked.
A lot of stuff felt like a little more time.
A few more revisions.
This premise could have been executed beautifully.
But as is, it's like a promising failure.
The setup is great.
And it's not landed well.
Let's get, let's talk about humor.
You're well into three, three forces away through this movie.
You've got characters who've now been,
who've had to take to viciously murdering people.
Right.
To defend themselves.
And yet they're all still just making like jokes.
Right.
Terrible.
It's bad writing.
You know, there's a scene where, and this,
this joke really bound to the theater,
but there's a scene where the dad finally sees the doppelganger
is doing the hands across America thing.
And he goes, looks like some kind of fucked up performance art.
That's supposed to be like a funny joke.
And it just bombed.
Yeah.
There were a few hard whiffs.
So, so that happens.
Also,
I mean, you think back on get out,
the security guard was really with the comedic relief.
And then like, you know,
kind of laughing at the dread or the horror of the situation.
But the security guard played by a little rel.
Every line, every time he stepped into the plate,
was a huge laugh.
And this just felt like everything was coming up short.
Well, you make a, you make a good point.
Rel was relief.
Right.
It was comic relief.
And by the way,
rel didn't do jokes.
Yeah.
He just was a, he was a refreshing character to come in
and make you feel better.
Like when he goes, see, I know a man at TSA shit,
it'd be tingling.
Right.
That's not a joke.
It's just a funny thing to say.
Right.
This is like trying to insert like Iron Man style punch lines
into this thing.
And they don't work.
Also, too, the commentary on
the mother, you know,
gleefully killing the statement rather
of the mother gleefully killing her
tethered at the end of the film
where it is sort of that moment of,
what does this say about us?
Well, nothing.
Because the entire family had to do that at that point.
And then the little kid looking at his mom
with like cross, not, not cross eyes,
but a crossed expression on his face.
At the end, like he's, he's freaked out by her suddenly
because she killed this woman.
It's like, he killed somebody.
They've all, everybody killed somebody.
Yeah.
There's a joke.
There's a gag in the movie where they brag about
who has the highest body count in the family.
That takes away from the statement.
That takes away from what it's all supposed to mean.
So, which brings us to the final twist of the film.
You find out the very end that in fact,
surface mom is the clone
and the evil mom is the surface mom.
Meaning when she's a little girl,
she runs into her doppelganger.
Her doppelganger grabs her.
And this is revealed to the very end.
grabs her, chokes her,
which explains why she's speaking in that goofy voice
through without the movie.
And then she switches places with her.
Now why?
She's the only one that figured out how to fucking do this.
I have no idea.
That's never really explained.
And then the last shot is the kid staring at the mom.
I don't trust you, suddenly.
And it's like,
yeah, but dude, she's still your mom.
Your mom didn't switch places just now.
Your mom switched places before she was your mom.
So she's still your mom.
Right.
It's just, it's just not well executed, man.
It's just not well executed.
It's upsetting me getting upset.
It's a tough and unfair comparison,
but get out just had it was a movie where every question
that you had was answered.
Every plot point was accounted for and addressed.
And this just feels like a sloppier thing.
Will I see the next thing Jordan Peele does?
Absolutely.
Of course.
Excited about the Twilight Zone.
Enough to maybe even get CBS all access.
Look, I look forward to watching the Twilight Zone.
I will watch it.
And I hope that it's great.
But I will say this.
This kind of shook me up a little bit, dude.
This shook me up a little bit.
Because this played exactly as you said a minute ago,
or not a minute ago, 20, 30 minutes ago,
like a bad Twilight Zone.
Yeah.
You know, it's, it could have been a good Twilight Zone.
Had it been simplified.
Now look, here's my take on it.
And we talked about this a bit on about the hereditary guy.
Another name I can't remember already.
I asked her.
Are you asked her?
Um, there was, in my opinion,
there was no need for this movie to come out this quickly.
Right.
Us.
There was no need.
Jordan Peele,
what an Oscar.
He, it was, it was a landmark moment in Hollywood.
He had a really like a masterpiece on his hands.
The following year.
The movie.
He produced with Spike Lee wins the best screenplay Oscar
The guy is on fucking fire
This Twilight Zone thing is all over the all over the
Entertainment News and everything this movie did not need to come out this quickly this movie could have sat for another year
And been refined and been turned into something really great
But for some reason it was
It was just it was like almost rushed out like I don't I don't get it
And you know, and it's by the way it's Blumhouse strikes again once again Blumhouse
Being the the only new movie studio in history that apparently gives zero notes to anybody and
It's obvious that they don't know how to like Blumhouse you you they're they put out what they get
That's it. That's why everything so goddamn disjointed every fucking thing they do you're like
This totally doesn't even match what you guys do half the time, you know
So they're not gonna tell you don't do this don't do that
Which look is nice in theory for an artist, but it's nice to have another voice. They're going you know
I don't know if this works and you know, maybe this you know something I
Think nobody's gonna give the guy post get out a note. I think maybe this time that was a mistake
I think next time he's gonna come back to the plate and I've seen a ton of people rave about this movie and love it
I it is when I may revisit I feel like maybe there's something I missed but
You know, I think what we're saying is
It's a noble failure a disappointing
Second chapter in the dude's story, but we're all looking forward to the third basically. I want to read
Let's pull up our favorite guy here see what he had to say about it
Who old Peter Travers? Oh, well, I'm sure it's got a lot of exclamation points
I just want to see what he says because I feel like it could lead to something interesting
Us talks about it who we are now
It does have a 94 %
Well, that's critics consensus audience scores down to 69 % yeah, I mean that I feel like that's about right
It's just kind of goes from spot to spot
Okay, here we go
tap critics give it to me, baby. All right
Katie Walsh, I didn't know there was a reporter named Katie Walsh not to have Travers I'm pissed past him
No, you know, yeah, I said where you have Travis there he is
Neongo delivers one of the great performances in horror movie history
That's an overstatement as Jordan Pills is raining it
But yeah like every time you're like even when I agree with you Travers you go too far. Yeah, she's very good in it
It's not one of the greatest performances in horror movie. It's not I'm sorry. It's like she's very good
I think the voice she does as the evil doppelganger is is almost laughable
Sure, you know, but she's creepy. She's great when she's doing all that like when she's the tethered person she's going
Like doing all like the weird like signaling and shit and she's great as the mom, but I mean
Come on, dude as Jordan Pills shows us the world a world tragically untethered to its own humanity
It's empathy. It's soul
If that's not a scare fest for its time. I don't know what is four out of five start
What is he even talking about right there? I don't think he knows if you ask him
What world is he talking about? I'll say again. I saw this man fall asleep at a premiere of memoirs of a gaysha and then write a glowing review
Oh god Richard Roper says this is an unforgettable dance with the devil
No, it's not no, it's not
It's not an unforgettable dance with the devil
Leah Greenblatt from entertainment week. He go see us on its own terms two hours of bloodspraying body snatching
I I agree with that far more than I do with Roper Peter Travers. Yeah, you'd have a good time
If you shut off the party or movie party or brain that wants to really analyze shit. Yeah
I will say, you know, I was there to like party and I was let down. Sorry
This is interesting. Now this guy get this counts as a fresh from time out Joshua Roth
comp
Only a three out of five. I think this is a fair review
Us is too confidently made to expert in its scene to scene command to call it an example of sophomore slump still
You feel a slight letdown. Agreed. That's that's a spot on fucking review. Great spot on fucking review
um
We don't have to read these people's reviews. Well, I was enjoying reading some of them
What the people under your heart?
San Diego reader. This is the last one I'll read because this is a bad review
Give it a one out of five Matthew Lakona the result is a bloody but weirdly bloodless a sort of thinky exercise in horror filmmaking
There's more juice in the laughs here than the scares. That's
Also very accurate right, but for me it made the cardinal sin of these kind of movies in that it was not funny enough
To be a comedy not scary enough to be a horror movie and that leaves you in a really kind of bummer place
I think mixing comedy with anything is very tricky. I am not in any way saying that that is an easy task. It is very very hard
But that's where the director's job truly comes in and the director has to know
Hey, man, this is not working in the grand scheme like this tonally doesn't work right here
We need to change this or we need to at least shoot an alt for it in case this joke doesn't seem to be landing
So then we have a way to fix it
So, you know
Anyway
That's us. Well, you know the best horror comedy in my opinion is not a joke driven thing
You know, it's something like misery very character -based
Um, you know those movies can be really funny
This one
The the jokes by the end of this thing weren't they were not character -based jokes
They were just gagged like the dad going it looks like a fucked -up
Performance Rp. It's like this is the same guy at the beginning of the film is yelling at the kids to stop cursing
Yeah, that's just to me just it's just not good character. It's not character -consistent
There's some cool stuff as you see in the trailer. They're going to make I got five on it the song of the summer
I've already heard it out of god of a lot of cars in LA
They use it very in a very cool way in the score
They use that hook kind of in the score as a repeated motif. I dug that
Didn't feel like it was a waste of my time
but
You know it leaves you wanting more it leaves you looking on to the next
Project from our old boy Jordan peel now if you'll excuse us
Joe and I are about to go see Cypress Hill
Do you have any closing thoughts Joseph?
I just remembered we forgot to do shout -outs
For Mondays episode so I have to record them right after we do this. Okay. That's my
You don't seem excited about that. I just hate when I forget to do it
Because now I got a fucking send we got to say in the email don't attach the shout -outs
It's all right. Let me find you all right anyway
That's it for me. I look forward to see what Jordan does next not a waste of time
But this isn't going to change your life
But you know you see it and let us know what you think we'd love to hear your thoughts on the film
Thank you everybody. We'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell
You