Summer is here and Bet MGM Casino is coming in hot with casino thrills!
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and the Wizard of Oz, only available at Bet MGM Casino.
Spent on spectacular slot favorites like Cash Eruption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp,
Rakin' Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones and Squid Game from Anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of BetMGM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the BetMGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
BetMGM and Game Sense remind you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate choices.
BetMGM .com for T's and C's, 21 plus to wager.
Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as non -withdrawable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
gambling problem, call 1 -800 -GAMBLER.
Firestone Complete Auto Care's epic savings event is the sign you need to stop putting off your car's maintenance.
And you can save up to $100 on tires and services while you're at it.
Don't wait, call Firestone Complete Auto Care for an appointment.
Hello everybody welcome to we'll see you in hell oh the tales from the dark side
episode you know that you read it before you downloaded it am I wrong Pat you're
not wrong Joe this is Jodorosa on one side of your head and Pat Walsh on the
other that's right we're on either side of your head so you can watch the movie up the
middle if you choose to do so that we'll see you and how podcast is now part of the fangoria
podcast network for more info about the network including other programs how to follow this
show how to follow those shows or to find episodes of any show please visit fangoria .com let's
get on with it I'm excited about watching this tonight by the way people at home start
are queuing up your Netflix. You want to tell them about how we're going to be at the mile
high horror festival. Yeah. Yeah. Well we'll tell them about that while
they you find tells the dark side hit play pause it on as soon as it starts so we can
all start together in a few moments here. Yes. You want to tell him Pat.
Okay. I I'm just a little concerned I'll get the date wrong but we're going to be
in Denver Colorado doing the podcast live. We're not 100 percent sure we're allowed
to tell you what the movie is so we're not going to we will closer to the date and that
date is October 3rd which is a Saturday and we will be if I'm not mistaken 8 20 in the
morning I think we can tell them now because
this is going to come out the week of the fest okay then let's do it it's we're doing
maniac cop to maniac cop to which I have never seen I'm going to watch it ahead of
time. Yeah I'm looking forward to it. You haven't seen it either. I have. I have not seen it
and I'm embarrassed to say that. I've seen maniac. I've seen cop and a half. I've seen
stopper. My mom will shoot. I've read maniac McGee. I've seen Mr. Magoo. I never knew never
maniac up to. I always thought maniac cop was. I didn't. I didn't know it was like so
lauded as a as a series but I wouldn't have even thought horror necessarily I thought
I would have thought maniac cop was like a extra violent dirty hairy kind of thing.
Well yeah they told us that what we were doing is maniac cop to be loved and we're gonna seem
like buffoons because it's apparently very beloved in the horror community.
Well here's the thing we're not gonna seem like buffoons number one have a little hate
than that. We're going to do just fine. Okay. There's nothing wrong with vulnerability.
That's what I've learned in this business. Sure. Is is you got to have a little vulnerability.
The only comedians I like are vulnerable and let you in. Who wants a conceded comedian.
Yeah exactly. You got to go out there. You got to say hey folks I'm not perfect. I'm
sorry I've never seen this before. I just watched it last week and I loved it. Right.
you come out and you're like hey I had a threesome last night then everybody's like oh yeah
come out and you're like hey I don't know how to talk to a Goyle then everybody loves you
exactly that's my advice for upcoming comedians and I would also say Goyle I agree with that
let's start this movie right and we can you know oh and that was the one other thing I
to say was when I when February it's almost 8 30 in the 20 in the morning I was like what
who the hell was going to come to a live podcast and their response was people will always come
for maniac to yeah that's when I or maniac cop to excuse me I love it when I knew we
had a goodie on our hands yeah I can't wait to watch it I'll be drinking at 8 20 in the
morning that day you know you think well it's insane how could I possibly drink
at 8 .20 in the morning and then you remember old friend Bloody Mary.
Well I go for screwdriver.
That's fine too.
There's a whole line of breakfast drinks that you forget about to help the alcoholic who
might enjoy a brunch.
They should have an aisle for the supermarket.
market. All right. You should be all queued up by now
and paused on the first you know frame or so of the movie.
We'll say one two three. The star is starting to come into the
Paramount logo which is my favorite logo volt. We'll say one two three play and we all
hit play on play here we go one two three play and we're rolling the stars are swirling their
way around the mountain alright this is tales from the dark side the movie came out in nineteen
ninety turned a nice little profit for paramount pictures I thought I had never seen it but
as I watched it earlier tonight I started watching them ahead of time because otherwise I focus
on the plot and I don't talk as much I realized I had seen the opening which we're about
to see where Deborah Harry has a young Joey Lawrence it's not Joey Lawrence Daniel Lawrence
yeah the kid from actually playing trans I don't know my favorite movies they are brothers
they look exactly alike yeah and he's locked up in the kitchen and I remember being horrified
by it I watched it now it's it plays as a comedy if anything yeah it's it's like the light -hearted
wrap around story even though the premises that she's going to eat him right but I like
a movie with a good reach around story. Folks. Start the jokes. But yeah. I saw this in the
theater on opening weekend. I couldn't wait because I was such a tells from the dark side
TV show fan and I was mesmerized to the entire thing. See now you one part of it scared me.
I loved every minute. Okay. Yeah. See you said one of your favorites of all time in the
horror genre I'm I'm nowhere near that and I think it probably has to do with when you
saw it. For example I showed you tremors which I would consider one of my favorites of all
time and you're you know you enjoyed it but we're fairly indifferent to I and I was I
wasn't indifferent I enjoyed tremors but to me tremors is more of a of an action comedy
with horror elements in it. It's fair. It's more of a canine if you will. Or a turner
in my hooch. Tremors was with my style of scary when I was that age where I could handle
literally not scary. There's literally nothing scary at it. There's a lot of monster attacks.
I'm saying I couldn't handle much and it was right up my alley. No one would say like oh
tremors was fucking sick bro. I also like a monster with a hell of a lot of fun. I like
a monster with some personality. I'm not a fan of just a big you know lumbering worm.
I think doesn't really you mean a grab would yeah grab wait sorry no you're gonna see that
the new tremors when it comes out I or I think it just did or it's about to they're up to
like five and I've been talking about it for years and they actually just discussed it
on key and peel that I went with the series for about three until they had them up and
walking around like dogs which is the whole hook is that hey we got a movie about giant
underground worms and they just make them walk around like little dogs right well make
koojoo again if you're going to do that tremors people I don't have a beef with a worm dog
no it's one of the animals I'd like to see if I think was definitely definitely had the
most effective worm dog yeah I'd like there's a twilight zone where the kid imagines the
monsters yeah yeah and and like he always imagines them like with like eight eyes
and stuff right hopefully imagine a dog with like eight eyes it's called it's a good
life and then the kid will be like the kid will be like that dog was funny I made it at
eight eyes but I got bored with it so I made him go dead so my point is if I was the kid
that could do that I didn't vent the worm dog and then I'd make it go dead well I didn't
really follow that Joe but I hope you enjoyed yourself I did the first and last there's
three segments on this wrap around deal my favorite type of horror anthology horror I love it
yeah I know you love it I I like it kind of like it's fun I wish this movie had three different
directors like a twilight zone the movie it felt very stylistically similar to me well
it's it's but it's it's what now here let me tell you why I love the movie my favorite
franchise and horror is creep show creep show one two to me or masterful films this is arguably
maybe the best of the three it's not called creep show but it's the same group of people
it's Tom Savini George a Romero and Stephen King were behind this one of the stories in
this cat from hell was supposed to be in creep show two but they I guess because of budgetary
reasons they cut two stories out. So it did make it into that of the money to have a cat
chase around a guy in a damn wheelchair. Well that's a little more to the story than that.
But I guess there is one special effects in the most part it's a guy in a wheelchair
yelling Tom Tom Savini has gone on record of saying this is unofficially creep show
three. There is a movie called creep show three but none of the original creep show
people have anything to do with it. It's an abomination. So how do they get the
writes them. I think they probably the rights to the name were just probably up and it's
not like they recreated any characters you know. So but in my opinion creep show one creep
show two in Tales of the Darks of the movie it's a it's a virtually flawless horror trilogy
which is very hard to come by as even the most astute horror fan would agree. I think
I think I find them pleasant diversions. What is that? You know like they're they're kind
of middle of the road. Cool little scary stories to me but I don't think of them as being great
horror films. You mean the anthology stories. The whole shebang yeah. I well look I will
say anthology is not for everybody. Certain people get annoyed because it's too they
feel like they can't settle into it. Yeah it's a little too short to get your to
invest in anything and then right up my alley it's right up my short attention span alley
well for this MTV generation Joe and you know you're about thirty forty years younger than
me so give me give me a hot twelve to eighteen minute tail any day of the week I mean I love
it Twilight Zone.
How about a hot twelve to eighteen year old tail I'm not into that but neither I'm
I'm glad you squeezed in another pedophilia. I certainly did. Yeah. There you go. I held
back a terrible joke just there that I guess I'll share with you. Let's just say it involved
the phrase squeezed it in. I imagine I imagine this much folks. Tales from the dark side
the movie stars Steve Buscemi and Julianne Moore and maybe if not their first film an
early one for both of them. Well that was kind of cool for me. If you're watching along
with us the first story is starting now called lot two forty nine right based on Arthur Conan
Doyle tale. So I'm Bushemi it starts Bushemi Christian Slater and Julianne Moore talk
about a different time Slater's the big name in this slaters the big name this came
out Slater was the guy the other two it was like who cares hot off pump up the volume yeah
which is still a great movie still a big Slater fan I get I like that Mr. Robot show that
he's in I always get excited when I haven't seen it but I may check it out it doesn't
it's not jumping off the shelf at me but I've heard a couple recommendation it's pretty
great it's pretty great but that's for another podcast all right you want Mr. Robot talk
go listen to the Mr. Robot podcast.
All right, fine.
You fucks.
What would the name of that podcast be?
The Mr. Robot podcast.
I don't know what else.
You're a classic riff, myster Joe.
Look at these sweaters.
Actual sweaters of the time or are these guys just being painted as douchebags?
Well, they aren't.
They're douchebags.
I mean, this is very on the nose.
I think this is how douchebags dressed in 87.
It did they?
And this is 1990 or were they just going off other movies of the 80s?
is this 90 yeah well this is how douchebags dress back then they it was a lot of sleeveless
v -necks it was a lot of tennis rackets all right douchebags in school used to play tennis
that was what the bullies used to do I'm sure they still do now bullies now are real bullies
they'll beat the shit out of you the douchebags at my school high school all played golf you
know for the for your like more fratty type douchebag guy and then the football players
We're all just wild degenerates, like horrifying people
to be around.
Yeah, I mean, it's bit sunflower seeds into your face,
you know, that kind of thing.
Yeah, certainly the frightening people at my schools
that I attended were not tennis players.
Right.
You know?
Look, these guys are, this is how it goes in an Ivy League.
Sure.
That's how it is.
Buscemi, by the way, this was my introduction to him
as a kid.
I had no idea who he was.
And I remember seeing, when I first saw Reservoir Dogs
about three years after this being like oh my god that's that's the guy from tales from
the dark side yeah so weird for me to see him in another role because I only knew him from
this pretty much always been one of my favorite actors really now is he had a tee like has
he had his teeth done because his teeth look particularly big and crooked in this and
I don't remember them looking like that reason oh no I if anything they look worse if you
could say if you could look at a picture of Buscemi from today and say that you think
think he said his teeth done. I'd left you out of the goddamn room. What are they so
they still he's still got those same teeth. Yeah like open a tin can. You know like not
think anything of it kind of teeth. Oh hey God bless him. Yeah those teeth bought him
a career like chopping him or those old like cylinders of high C like with one big triangle
on one side and one small triangle on the other like he just sort of chop in and down
it in one disgusting goal. This would be this would be my response if I would I'm Steve Buscemi
criticize my teeth. Yeah. Okay. Hey. Yeah. Big old teeth. These teeth
bought me a Ferrari. That's what I would say to people. He definitely drives a Ferrari.
He seems like that guy for sure. Favorite. I'm going to go with a fairly obvious choice
and say Fargo. I don't know how way to possibly do better than that. You're nuts. All right.
what do you got? You put Fargo over Reservoir Dogs. You put Fargo over Reservoir Dogs. Yeah,
I put Fargo over Reservoir Dogs by about 5 ,000 percent. It's insane. What are my least favorite
Coen Brothers movies, by the way? Oh, God. How do you live with yourself? There's no,
there's no one at home being like, yeah, he's right. Fargo sucked. There's no one at home
doing that right now. No one. I didn't say Fargo sucked. I just said it's, I like Reservoir
Dogs better and it's not one of my favorite Coen Brothers movies. All right. It's a good
movie were you a lady killer's man. Intolerable cruelty. Number one lady
killers later has some laughs and so does the top. I'm joking. My number one obviously is
Big Lebowski. Yeah that's fair. I would follow it with possibly maybe a Miller's crossing.
Crossing is great. Raising Arizona might be my favorite. But I love the shimmy and Fargo
Which was the question because I said performance now, mr. Pink
I don't understand the hell you're saying
It's fine. You know, you're not a very tolerant man. I'm very tolerant
Which is a lot of sorry
I don't have the patience of a guy that watches the same movie back -to -back in one night
I mean, I don't know what kind of psychopath you are. Well, I'm not watching it all right now
I'm talking and I had never seen it. So I would have been like what's going on. What's going?
Why did they just do a terrible 80s wife the fact that you're able to just sit in or in
front of it twice in a row is nuts to me you're a sin of well I'm talking to you you're a
sin of file I mean an insult if I if it had been a movie I'd seen a hundred times I wouldn't
have to do it but it's not an insult I just said it's nuts to me look at this refrigerator
they're supposed to be really wealthy and they got that 50s Donna Reed fridge in the kitchen
Maybe it's a classic what happened to this guy. I like this guy that plays Julianne Moore's
boyfriend who's like who's like the definition of a white guy. I feel like he might still
he looks like a character actor who's in movies now but it's not him for sure. Yeah he's probably
by this point either strolled into the porn waters or you know he runs a tire shop in
the valley or something like that. He's got a good porn look I like it. Yeah I think
I think even now 25 years later he'd be one of those kind of 55ers hanging in there.
Yeah.
Coming by you know playing the neighbor who's visiting the babysitter or whatever it is.
I don't know.
Oh my sweet boy.
You think they still have storylines in porn.
They still do and everything I watch I'm usually fast forwarding it but.
The hell are you seeing that as a storyline in it outside of like bang brothers where
they put a girl in like a bus or something you know maybe I kind of seek them out but
I tend to go for something a little longer. I like to treat myself like a lady and those always have story in them
I never like a clip that like opens on a gaping butthole or something. I don't need that in my life
Like I like to be romanced a little bit. You'll still watch a thing where it's like, you know
Let's turn this into a porno
The guy goes I inherited a mummy and then he opens the coffin. He's like, oh, I mean a mommy
me and a hot milk gets out like you. This is a real milk. A mummy I'd like to fuck.
Should we write this you would you would you would watch that kind of porn. Oh no I'm not
talking about if the story is just ludicrous I just mean if it's a simple. Hey you know
your dad's out. I'm your new step mom. Your home visiting for the weekend. That's a little
a little back and forth zone. A lot of the clips. You know what I'm going to say something
kind of profound. I like a little back and forth before the in and out. And that goes
for life and in the erotic cinema. All right. That's that's I get the stories
you're talking about. All right. I thought you were saying like old school like everybody
works at a hospital. You know. No I'm not doing that but I miss that. You know nurse
There's time to make the incision right here. You know what I mean? Yeah. Yeah. He sticks
his penis in her vagina. Right. You get it. I got it. Looks like you need a shot. Nurse
you head off down the hall. I think Mr. Herman needed a sponge bath. I like my incision bit
a little bit better. I wouldn't know. I was fucking competing with you Joe. You weren't
but I didn't just I didn't lift mine from Seinfeld. That's all. You're gonna lift the Seinfeld
bit from the famous episode of Seinfeld. I don't know how you live with yourself. Do you do this
at work? Well, I didn't know Seinfeld was a hardcore porno film. What's that? I'm saying
you know how they get the side nurses and doctors off down the hall on their own stories
sort of like a Pulp Fiction. It also featured Steve Bushin, which was an anthology film.
Well, sure. Yes, it is three stories. Yes. Anything with three stories. I wouldn't
says I like you shimmy and pulp fiction more than I like him in Fargo. I don't I don't know
what I'm joking. Did you also love William H. Macy and Fargo. I loved him in it. Yeah
he was incredible. He's great. And so was McDormand. She's wonderful in it. And so is
that Austrian guy whose name I can never remember that played Peter Storm. Also in
Seinfeld. We're bringing it back. He played the guy who got the Frogger thing across
across the street his name was slippery Pete folks. Peter Sturmer. A bit of a resemblance
to our to our leading jock man in this short story. I wouldn't argue that you know your
opinion of Julianne Moore as an actress. She's wonderful. I thought she was and then
I hit a point where I never wanted to see her again and I've been there for 510 years.
I think she's fantastic in almost everything she does. I mean she's unbeatable and boogie
nights that that that was 20 years ago that you're talking right into what I'm saying I'll
name a recent one that David Cronenberg movie she was in about Hollywood maps to the stars
with one of the most upsetting films I've ever seen in my life she's fantastic in that
she was I just you really see her acting these days she was terrible on 30 rocks she
did a Boston accent that just really you know sent me into my room for a couple days
is I couldn't quite deal with it and then you know she's just a little hammy even in
that still Alice I didn't like her I didn't see that she was great in Don John yeah I
did like Don John I like Don John a lot I'm a great movie still Alice is the amnesia
movie or not amnesia Jesus Christ Alzheimer's the subject of Alzheimer's in it yeah it's
the subject I want to see the least I have I really hate anything to discuss with
Alzheimer's yeah it's a terrifying home movie I think I talked with us on
Pete's podcast was Alec Baldwin going but Alice your your glasses are on your
forehead Alice Alice the cars parked right down here Alice
Alec Baldwin talks in that English accent yeah you know when Alec Baldwin's in
like a drama where he's not supposed to be like a tough yeah he defaults to like
almost like a 1930s sure accent now it so the story of still Alice is she's a
younger woman that gets early on set Alzheimer's. Yeah it's so depressing and then you know
Baldwin kind of I don't know he just keeps he tries to hang in and then he winds up leaving
her spoiler alert because the movie wasn't depressing enough. Jesus Christ I used to
work with people that at Alzheimer's and there was a woman who was in her late fifties
that had she was she was gone she was off the map and it was very sad to see somebody
that young I mean it was sad to see anybody with it but somebody that young with it
It's my biggest fear.
And now we're really into a horror podcast.
Yeah.
What are your fears now?
That's why a horror movie about Alzheimer's,
I might not see that.
I don't like anything to do with Alzheimer's.
We've established that.
Let's lighten up.
I donate money to them.
Let's lighten it up.
You should too.
I'm just picturing people sitting in their cubicles
right now wanting to slit their throats.
All right, well let's talk about Christian Slater
and a blue tank top.
Our turtle neck.
Did you wear turtle necks?
Yes. Now my posture was always too bad for a turtleneck. I look weird in one. I no one
looks cool in them except maybe like Bruce Wayne. Bruce Wayne looks fantastic in one.
But I always wore turtlenecks under a sweater. It was kind of my signature look. Oh God. I
look real real nerdy for many years. You look like one of these jocks at the Ivy
League school. But in a nerdy body. You carry a tennis racket around with you. Imagine
the the jock wardrobe but with a real dorky face and body if I may say so Pat and I had
a put ourselves a drink before this podcast I'm about halfway down my whiskey I'm so tired
from working all week that I'm I feel completely drunk right now already all right we'll keep
it together it's together I just feel I mean I could I could go to sleep in your arms
at this moment and not feel strange about that at all I would feel very strange about
I don't blame you.
I'm just trying to tell you where I'm at right now.
I think our listeners might enjoy a solo pod for me or it might be like when Wayne left
and Garth had to take over Wayne's world.
Now I don't look at it that way.
I look at it as the is like when Joe Perry did the solo album with her for marriage.
I look at it as a positive.
All right.
The fans are going to like it.
They're going to support it.
What was it?
What was Joe Perry's solo?
Can't remember.
it was the first thing I could access in my head one of my friends out here is his son
delightful guy he's at my house for the party I am friends with my friends with a step son
my friend Aaron is a step son my buddy Anthony I'll just shout him out Anthony Perry Junior
it was Anthony and one of the kids in the band the three brothers band yes tab the band
yeah me and Burr used to hang out with those guys nice guys I missed him at your party
unless he was there we just didn't recognize each other he was there he was there I love
those guys yeah they're great guys look at us name dropping again folks if it's your first
listen themes that reoccur on this podcast pedophilia name dropping yeah both despicable
who knows which is worse but we're not dropping like fucking huge names we're saying I my
buddy is the son of Joe Perry you were going on and on about about that's a great shot
by the way when the camera goes past the mummy. It's a great shot but you think that mummy
might be a guy with a mummy helmet on like could there be and I guess mum is a real it's
a real mummy that they brought to life. Just mummies to me it's always like mummies
and I'm like even in the mummy I was just kind of like just push him over it's a mummy.
They're not scary. We did a we did a monologue when Pete Holmes
still had his talk show and it was about the what monster is the scariest monster. Uh -huh.
And I wrote a lot of the monologue and I remember the section on zombies and mummies is it zombies
aren't scary because they just they just wander around slowly right they all look like
your grandfather got loose from his bed at the home sure you know you just want to see
if he needs if he needs somebody to if he knows where he is and if he needs somebody to escort
him back to his room right you know that's how I feel about mommy did you not think that
joke was funny no I'm with you what did you why did you laugh at all that joke it's a
funny joke it's like your grandfather got loose from his bed at the home yeah I mean
And we just get off Alzheimer's and now we're talking about a grandpa not knowing where
he is.
All right.
Well, you know, these people got to get through this brains in the fruit bowl.
Mummy pulled out the jock guy's brains and put the brains in the fruit bowl and the
silver spoon.
Mummy in the light of the moon.
Julie and more is hamming it up.
Now she seems kind of natural here and she did to me up until like Magnolia.
Yes she's way way way over the top but she's playing like a real coked out drugged out
lady.
I've never seen her be hammy.
You said you thought it's a newer development for her.
We saw black mass the other day and and I thought Peter Sarsgar was was phenomenal
in it and you said he thought he was a little hammy and I didn't I thought he played it
like a guy that was on a lot of coke.
I liked him I wanted more of him in the movie but he just was in kind of a different
thing.
And it gave the movie some energy which I felt it really needed because I thought
Black Maps is surprisingly very slow. I got to tell you I rewatched the documentary tonight
about Whitey Bulger and it reframed the movie for me and it made me appreciate the movie
more. Okay.
And I also think that Bulger wasn't an informant and I actually believe his story over the
FBI story that he was. I mean everybody was lying so it's really anybody's guess.
Yeah. I don't know. I just for some reason I believed his story a little bit more. Okay.
Uh you got Julianne Moore sitting in front of a bloody fridge your boyfriend's been murdered
Chris Slater looking like a young John Travolta always doing a Nicholson impression in these
early days especially they couldn't cliche this up more they're now at the funeral
of the dead boyfriend and Chris Slater and his rich sister are drinking brandy out of
snifters sure would have killed you to throw me a snifter tonight by the way I don't even
an owner's chair. It's a terrible chair. I'm trash. I don't own
a snifter. Who does this. It's like an episode of Frazier.
Yeah. It's ridiculous. We had the guy on our show this week.
Gil remember Gil from Frazier. Well you just watched the entire
series for some reason. I remember Gil. Who the hell
plays. Who's the hell is Gil. He's like the chef. I'll do my
impression of you and you'll know who he is. So I go yeah the
food radio guy. Yeah I go where do I know you from man like
You know he's 70 years old now or something like where do I know you from he goes well
I did only live in seasons of Frazier. He talks. How we do. Yeah, really he was also well
No, I don't want to say anything. He was a little I kind of stayed in character like it came out
He was like where's the bathroom my friend goes. Oh, it's right over here. He goes. I know
We're like, what was that? I don't get it. What's that? It wasn't a joke
I think he was just kind of like don't tell me where I'm going
thing but why did he ask then Joe that's the point of the story we were all kind of like
what's this guy's deal I don't know but what was his character was it a man that would
ask questions he was a snooty butler you know a very annoying butler he's seventy oh at
least yeah really yeah he's very funny on Frazier he was great yeah he's got a very
distinctive voice I love the I love the show so much I am rewatching many episodes of it
Well, outside of Seinfeld and Curb your enthusiasm, Seinfeld, Curb your enthusiasm.
The Golden Girls, the Honeymooners, Mr. Belvedere, Frazier, those are my five where it's like
Mrs. Belvedere.
I'll rewatch him.
I don't care.
I love it.
Elvedere, vodka.
All right.
We all heard the Belvedere.
I haven't seen Frazier in at least 15 years, but I used to like it.
I would go as far as to say there are moments that are hysterical.
Oh wow.
It's one of the most laugh.
They got a good farce thing going when they would hit it.
Yeah for sure.
And it's one of the most laugh out loud sitcoms to me.
Those five to me are like to me gutturally laugh out loud sitcoms for the most part.
If you were texting with Frazier you would text LOL.
I would text LOL.
All right.
I'd also text STFU shut the fuck up yes because he'd probably say a thing like do you want
to meet for a brandy and I'd say shut the fuck up but not telling him like shut the fuck
up like I hate you saying it like oh Frazier shut the fuck up I love yeah you know what
I mean I bet Frazier would have a lot to say about emojis what do you think you'd say
well now I'm just want to talk like Gil I got that in my head I don't I can't really
to do my Kelsey grammar on Twitter corrects people's grammar which I love when somebody
corrects my grammar I say thanks a lot Kelsey grammar and nobody laughs ever on the just like
how when I order a drink at a bar I go I think I'm going to have a little ditty about Jack
and diet never gonna laugh at any bar ever I do it at least once a year because I'm like
somebody will laugh even if I got a bartender I'm like this guy's got a good sense of
humor I'll do it they always get it it's not like they don't get it they just never
laugh and it hurts you want to hear my bar bit that nobody ever laughed at sure as you
try to do a guy that didn't know how to order drinks properly okay and I'd go give me a
white Russian no line please you know stuff like that three dad material do me a do me
a favor bloody Mary easy on the whiskey just a pinch of the Kahlua like I would just drink
order wrong nobody ever thought it was funny ever yeah I'm big I'm big on like at a party
party when you first get there. These are all very dead material. I love dead bits.
Sure. Me too. Any party like when you first get there and
they're like you want to drink. What can I get you. I'm like I'm going to do a white
wine and Red Bull please. And you always try to get just a funny a funny
blend. Right. But you'll never beat. Tanker and tonic
from Kington. Tangerine and no it's not. I'm sorry.
Tangerine and tap sweets coming real. I got a long drive ahead of me.
Well, we've talked about it previously on the on the podcast.
Kingpin has the two funniest drink orders of all time.
Tangerine Tab, as you just said.
And then later, when the dickhead boyfriend,
bowler guy, is sitting at the bar,
he goes, hey, sport, Coca -Cola.
Coca -Cola.
What an asshole.
That guy is only in Fairleigh Brothers movies.
And I think he was like an entertainment tonight
correspondent, who is not a great actor.
And throughout, Kingpin is wearing eyeliner.
Yes.
Yes which I find very bizarre and in a movie where everyone is insulting everyone's appearance
the entire time no one says a word to him about wearing out but I will tell you that his delivery
of Hay Sport Coca Cola like this guy this guy should have won an Oscar he was a very
effective use yeah yeah the now we're at the point in the movie now if you're watching
along with us Christian Slater is about to he's putting lighter fluid all over Steve
because you know Steve Buscemi has somehow gotten this mummy to kill his sister and his best friend.
And now he's going to try to have the mummy kill, well not.
He's going to just burn Steve Buscemi alive, excuse me.
Now Slater in this scene, even if you're not watching, I'd suggest you go watch it afterwards.
Because Slater is really Nicholson.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Nicholson ink up the entire scene.
I mean his most Nicholson he was probably heathers or maybe cuffs but he was just doing straight
impressions for like that 10 year period.
I find his pump up the volume to be incredible.
Oh super yeah this is all in that same two or three year period.
All the great themes have been turned into theme parks yeah I used to love that line it makes
no sense.
No it's completely untrue.
It's a very 80s 80s lawn where you're like that's deep man but it's not.
Yeah well he used to say that Nicholson was his idol.
Well, sure. And but here's the thing. He naturally sounds like Nicholson. Yeah. And
I mean a little bit has a look of a young dragon. Yeah. So you know it's not all you know it's
kind of like how it's kind of like how action Bronson sounds like Ghostface killer. Yeah
exactly who in a video said that action Bronson should be killed. I saw that I didn't really
approve Ghostface's response. I didn't either at the top. I understood why
I was a little upset but I didn't think you should all call for a man's death over it.
No I mean stealing somebody's flow that's been going on for centuries Patty I mean you
know sometimes I think people in this town are stealing my flow they're not jump they're
not this I thought was this supposed to be a little blow job bit because it sure felt
that way to me now like the director wasn't like hey we've kind of framed this so it
looks like that guy's really blowing Steve Buscemi I never once in my entire life
Ever thought that and I've seen this movie a hundred times. You're a pig with a filthy mind. That's where I went
Sorry, disgusting pig. I just want to see Steve Buscema get blown by maybe they let that pig talk fly at CVS on
Your foul mouth sitcom you work on but not on this podcast. Did you like?
The mummies and the scorpion kings and all that garbage
Sort of tipping my hand on how I feel about them. They're okay. I mean the first one's pretty good
You know, it's it's more of an Indiana Jones type of thing than a horror movie.
Man, I really hate it.
I went on a date with this girl once.
I would say six minutes, sorry to brag, six minutes into the meal, she goes, um, so like
you like movies.
So like what's like a movie you can just watch like whenever it's on, you just have to
finish it.
And I probably said Fargo, you know, or something like that, and she's like, for me, it's
the mummy.
funny. I will always watch the mummy when it's on and I was like okay but I was like losing
the interest rapidly but I'm gonna hang in here and then this girl talked about that mummy
a lot. It went on and on and she thinks Brendan Fraser is so cute. I think this is very endearing
but it wasn't funny. It was just like the girl seemed to have a real Jones for the
mummy I think it's I think it's endearing I don't I don't think it's
endearing because it sounds funny I think it's endearing a girl really loves the
movie the mummy all right it didn't didn't work for me somebody being
passionate about the mummy I don't have time in my life about I'm not being
passionate about it she was and you're a heartless bastard yeah exactly that
couldn't understand she's not into your indie house drama bullshit I like a
wide variety of movies. But speaking of a indie house drama bullshit I did just like
I saw a good night mommy dying to see it I might go tomorrow night. It is so scary you
should see it's going to leave the Los Feliz up here again tipping my hand as to where
me and Joe live. But it was really scary and really tense and I loved it. Good night
mommy it's a German horror movie basically only three characters. Some other people
would pop in but it's two twins they're like ten years old their mom comes back with her
face all wrapped up in gauze much like a mummy keeping it on story was she in an accident
or is it plastic surgery well I'm not going to answer any of those questions but she comes
back and the kids start to suspect that it's not their mom basically and it was that's
the premise and it's very very scary you should see it it's great okay very good
Now isn't this cab driver in this scene somebody famous is that Joe Pantolioni it wasn't right
no but I now you mentioned I think he might have was it I don't know just look like a
way buffer dude I think I feel like that cab driver somebody that I should wreck it by the
way that was another trope in 80s movies like the cab drivers were always like these SNM
leather there's chains all through the cab they do that in a plane trains and automobiles
Yeah, they should. Well, the guys got porno over his car. Yeah. Speaking of cab drivers,
the next story that's going to be on in a few moments. Captain Halistar's Buster Poindexter
played a cab driver and Scrooge. Yep. You know it. Yeah, with William Hickey. So he
was in Scrooge. No, he's in crystallization as you know, Uncle Lewis. Yeah. But what
we, you know, you're just saying they're both about one year prior. They were both
and some great classic Christmas movies and now they're in this together with a cat Scrooge
could be my favorite Christmas movie I wouldn't argue with that I love Scrooge I have my favorite
Chris movie I would say it's a wonderful life is one of my favorite movies home alone I love
home alone but I saw when I was 10 too but I mean for God's sakes it's your favorite
it. Yeah it's a favorite Christmas movie of mine. Christmas vacation is a favorite Christmas
movie. I love Christmas vacation. Gremlins is a favorite Christmas movie. I love Gremlins.
I'll tell you what my second to Scrooge is. Disgusting your voice when we slightly disagree
on something. Oh look and the cat from Hell Stories opens
with a cab. Yeah. I will tell you my second place to Scrooge. I can't wait to hear
it. Love actually. Yeah I love love actually. Makes me cry every time. I think though
that it's you know it doesn't feel at all Christmassy except for a few little sections
I disagree wholeheartedly I don't know I think they cover the Christmas bases nicely in that
film I think that movie would be a nice entertaining picture but I think that the Alan Rickman
Emma Thompson story takes it over the edge into something better it's a wonderful film
it's a wonderful live film cheers the Hugh Grant story it's it's touching my favorite
story though is Bill. Bill Nye. Is that his name? Definitely not. Bill Nye the science
guy. Who's the guy that plays the rock star in it that was in Sean the dead. Oh yeah. His
name is Bill Nike. Yeah. Very close. Yeah. Yeah. My that's my favorite story him and
his manager. It's it's it kills me at the end when he tells his manager like you're
my best friend. I love you. Yeah. It's a pretty great movie. Any time really anytime
in a movie someone is telling someone something they have wanted to say for decades. That
always put a little lump in my throat. I'm a sucker for it. I'm a sucker for it. Now William
Hickey. Yeah. The star of Bill Hickey. Bill Hickey. Well sometimes he went by William.
He always went by William but I called him Bill. My friend used to do that. Like he'd
like refer to stars like Bobby DeNiro movie stars like with familiarity Jimmy Kong. Yeah
he'd be like he'd be like that's the great thing about math out. I always wanted to
be like you're a you you you're you're a you're a social you're social studies major at a state
school but you don't know math out yeah I'm Walter math out you know a lot of things it
depends on the person but there's so many things people will do when talking about action
stuff that bother me so much but really like you know if you were to say to me oh you
know Pacino was so great that would but William Hickey I remember this when I I studied
that was a theater minor in college and when William Hickey died they had his obituary
up on like the bulletin board in the theater department so he must have gone there right.
Now it was just like they would post when famous actors or whatever passed I think though
I don't think he went there but anyway he was like when he died he was only like in
his sixties he had like some kind of yeah he had some kind of physical looks like a
God damn cool. I thought he was. He was so funny in
Chris's vacation. He's great. I thought he was like 95 years
old. He was he was actually young. He had like you know he had some kind of disorder
or something and he just he looked he was sickly you know I guess I like when his wife who
was the voice of Betty Boop by the way. That's who the place is wife. I never make
his tell you the original Betty Boop from the 30th and she was oh dear did I break
wind and he goes Jesus did the room clear out Bethany hell no she means presents then later
on she goes I hear something a weird squeaky sound and he goes you couldn't hear a dump
truck driving through a nitroglycerin plant yeah yeah he just makes kind of a lame old
wisecrack seem new. I like when he goes grace the blessing points to his mouth to his teeth.
Yeah. That's the mark of a good actor. Anybody can point to their mouth. He points to his
teeth. Isn't that the guy that plays like breaking bad. But doesn't he also play. Isn't he the
usual suspects. No. I'm thinking of the other guy. Oh yeah. Well that guy had a huge role
and breaking bad. He was the guy who winds up with the bomb thing on his wheelchair.
Yes. I like that guy. I also like the Kobayashi guy. He passed away recently.
Yes. People always die, unfortunately. Eventually we all die. Sometimes the hands
have an evil cat. Most of the time at the hands of an evil cat.
So this one was written by George Aromero based on a Stephen King.
Oh, yes. I'm sorry. Based on the Stephen King story. Yes. And the first and third were
written by Malcolm McDowell, who I always mistook with Michael McDowell from a Clockwork
Orange. Malcolm McDowell is from a Clockwork Orange.
And this is Michael McDowell. You're right. I actually was in the process of confusing
it while I talked about how I confuse. Yeah, not to be confused with Roddy McDowell.
No, or Andy McDowell. Yeah. Hey, I'm going to tell you my joke about Andy McDowell.
But you ready for this how many people have a joke about Andy McDowell. This is what keeps me big in the stand -up circuit
What do Andy McDowell and my uncle Gary have in common? What?
They both ruined four weddings in a funeral
You
That's a good joke
Want to hear a one -liner I wrote
For work the other day. Yeah, well, I'm not gonna laugh at it now after I get an oh god from you
is a good one liner I had to write a one liner for like a borscht belt kind of thing.
Okay.
I said either my cook is becoming one hell of a nag or my wife is becoming one hell of
a cook.
I mean maybe I had to be a part of the scene I don't I think that's a good one liner.
It's a it's like a Milton Burley kind of thing.
Look I'm still a little wounded from the treatment of my end of McDowell jump.
It wasn't a well -crafted joke. I'm sorry
Well, of course it was a huge hit on Twitter, and if you're gonna, right? That's all that really matters. Well,
congratulations
13 and a half you love to think you're funny our friend genius comedian Karen Kilgarov
She loved it Joe. I bet I could get a different take out of it on her. Well, go ahead and try
I'll call her tomorrow ask her
What you really think of that for weddings in the funeral tweet and then she like she'll be taking the phone away from her head
laughing Michael McDowell yes also wrote Beetlejuice a masterpiece it is with
somebody named Warren scarring so which I would have to assume with some sort of
pen name but I think the reason I was watching this is because I was trying
to seek out other movies the writer of Bealjuice had done but this doesn't
really have that feel to it Bealjuice like and the guy hadn't done a lot of
of other stuff, especially nothing in that tone.
Beetlejuice is a real special thing.
I think Burton must have had a lot to do with it too.
I love Beetlejuice.
I'm excited that they're doing a sequel.
Yeah, I just.
What, Pat, what?
I'm going to keep my hopes at a 60 % because why would I not?
Burton's directing it.
Keaton's in it.
Winona Ryder's in it.
What's not to like?
Well, they keep going back and forth on it.
They got the guy who wrote fucking Dark Shadows
to write it, which was a terrible movie.
It was better than I thought it was going to be.
You must have thought it was going to be real damn bad John.
I mean I don't know.
Hold on though.
I want to look up Beetlejuice and see.
Now why do you think the original writer isn't writing it?
Because he's dead.
He died at age forty nine.
From what?
I don't know.
I just looked it up and he was dead at forty nine.
I'm on the old iPad here and of course it's an iPad mini from however many years
ago.
It's the first iPad mini and as soon as iOS 9 came out the thing doesn't work properly
anymore.
of course. Unbelievable. Alright I'm looking up Bealjuice and Wikipedia. Glenn Shattuck's
also dead who played Otho. One of my favorite characters in the whole film.
I've probably I would say I've seen Bealjuice maybe more than any other movie other than
maybe Home Alone or Roger Rabbit. They were they hit me in that 10 year old I'll watch
something a million times wheelhouse. Warren Skerron died at 44 44 sorry not a screen
name that's his real name Warren scaring no no I was okay Warren scaring is dead but so
is 44 so is Michael McDowell at age 49 well that must movie was cursed Warren scaring what
to say here first success was getting the film the getaway shot in Texas driving force behind
the distribution of the Texas chainsaw massacre that's great notable writing works include
Beverly Hills cop to very funny Batman yeah he was in the Burton camp he also he had also
written unproduced sequels to the Jewel of the Nile now did he write the Beetlejuice
goes Hawaiian sequel that was bandied about or did that never actually go to script well
how about this he wrote a he wrote a Beetlejuice sequel that was never made called Beetlejuice
in love did you know that no but Beetlejuice goes Hawaiian I think was offered to Kevin
and Smith. Beetlejuice goes Hawaiian. Yeah it was a project that was like shopped around
for a while about 10 years ago and what the hell was it about.
Beelge's in Hawaii. One of the worst things I've ever heard
in my life. Yeah of course I have no I mean Burton can't make
a sea movie these days for my money. I heard big eyes was good.
It was fine. It was fine. Look you know I hate to say it.
I'm a fan of Burton's earlier work but for the most part Burton's stuff was a lot of
was a lot of look and not a lot of substance. Oh I completely disagree as always with you
Joe. McDowell died of AIDS. Michael McDowell. He died of AIDS Jesus Christ. He was diagnosed
with AIDS in 1994. Well AIDS Alzheimer's were hitting all the fun topics tonight folks.
It's a real pick me up of an episode tonight.
It's getting a little dark now but I mean I look I'm going to say I'm going to say this
right now and I don't care who I piss off you know I never thought Edward Scissorhands
was that great oh I don't know I don't know what to say to that you know I loved Edward
Scissorhands I love Pee Wee's big adventure I love Batman I love Batman Returns I know
you hate Batman Returns is not a good film. I think it's an A plus. Oh stop it. Idiotic
all those early burdens I think are just fucking classics but then again Batman Returns is
an A plus for me. Yeah. Get out of here. I don't believe you believe that. But I do
and I'm saying it and why would I not. So you you don't have a problem with penguins
with missiles on their backs. That's just fine. No again. That's the movie I saw when
I was 12 but when I watched now I still love it just as much. I saw it when I was 13
and I knew it sucked in. I was like this sucks. I saw it in the theater. You would have seen
it when you were 17 because you're older than I was not 17. So you didn't see it when you
were 12. It came out in 92. I was born in 81 and I saw it in the theater. Let's look that
up. I'm going to look that up. I'm sorry. I know that is true. I'm going to I'm going
to look it up. Hold on a second. I was so I was 11 and you would have been I'll
I was a very different age, but I don't know why you wouldn't love it because Batman Returns
was so fucking dark like way ahead of its time.
Well, first of all, it wasn't dark.
It was it was it was weirdly dark in certain places like psychosexual and weird and awesome.
It was weirdly dark in certain places and then it was oddly stupidly comedic in
other places.
It's dumb that people go to the Penguin speech and start throwing tomatoes at him.
where the gag is the penguin actually says what kind of people bring fruit and vegetables
to a press conference. It's like it's stupid. The gadgets are dumb like they're too ridiculous
the way they work. It's not believable. There's the thing where Batman pulls a chunk of concrete
out of a wall and it like you always get hung up on this shit. It's Batman. It's
even a character from the comics. Like why are they adding don't add a character.
Well see I never give a fuck about that shit. Batman Returns to me is so much better than
any comic book movie made in the last 20 years that everybody thinks is so genius. I think
it's great. It's in tone of what it should know when it's fun. It's fun night. You
can't say better than the certainly better than Batman begins. Both of Burton's Batman's
are better than Batman. You're just and the Dark Knight, it's an odd comparison, but I'd
say they're they're about on a par. The Dark Knight is probably a little better. But depending
on the day, I might like Batman Returns better than Batman one.
Pat, you're out of your, what are you talking about? Sorry, I know I'm not alone here either.
They made, they took so many liberties with it. The way Catwoman becomes Catwoman, it's
Ridiculous Liberty shit will never bother me
Look that I guess it's the rest of the world. This is what the difference is with for being logical nerds who are super into
Comic books isn't super which at this point is the world everyone is into comic books
I never have cared about them at all so when we go into a
Movie like this you guys are all going in like and what's gonna be different than my graphic novel
and I'm going in like a child ready to be entertained and I'm not entertained by these
I wasn't going into it like that but I was smart enough to know by the way I was 14 when
this film came out I was smart enough to know that when this came out catwoman becoming
catwoman because cats chew on her fingers makes no fucking sense now whether or not they're
making up their own origin story is a different argument well I would all bite her and she's
You know like what happens in the book is there like radioactive? No, she's just like a cat
She's a cat burger. She's like an anti -hero in the books and she has no cat power
Oh, what and even if she did why would cats chewing on your fingers give you cat powers?
They're like they there's a bunch of cats like attacking so stupid so you can either go okay
I'm in a ridiculous world and like this scene looks amazing that's that's the penguin the penguin one of the coolest like
sort of like John Gotti meets Donald Trump characters in comic books like this
super billionaire like pulling the strings puppeteer kind of crime boss
villain and they turn him into this like mutant like it's fucking all that dumb
Tim Burton shit like I want to find beauty in the obscure I want to find
beauty prettiness in the ugly have dreamed of a better
oh god it's terrible Burgess Meredith that's a penguin for you it's ridiculous
It's just and then they add this third villain and it's too much. It's like it with Christopher
Walker Max Shrek. Max Shrek barely makes an appearance.
Oh, so bad. You must like it more. It's not so bad. I can't even put up with this. The
guy playing his son. It's literally like daddy daddy. It's stupid. It's a it's not
a good movie. Do you prefer Batman and Robin? No. Those are
dog shit. Well, you're talking about Batman Returns as if it's dog shit to make your
point I will not dog I will put this is this is the height of Batman returns to me it's
Christmas time and I want to take a nap that's Batman returns to me it's Christmas I'll put
it on I'll fall asleep to it because I don't care enough to keep watching it but it's Christmasy
enough that I find it comforting that's it the first Batman I'll watch I watch the first
Batman I love them both dark night I love it after dark night I'll play that much
this world allows for all these things. It's a democracy. I can't believe it. I'm looking
it up now. It's got an 80 percent. What does that return return? People love Batman return.
People are stupid. Here's another thing. Let's have a whole new villain with the penguin.
Okay, cool. I'm into that. Let's make all the penguins henchmen exact ripoffs of the
Joker's henchmen. They're all clowns for some reason. It's stupid. It's it's
not creative it was like a paint by numbers movie it's a bad movie I think
it's a visually spectacular movie that gets into some really weird stuff but how
we all wear masks and relationships it's very sexual it's very exciting the
action sequences are great I love the winter vibe I love walking though his
part may be superfluous I really love Michelle fire for his catwoman nobody's
ever done that better she's sure she and I don't think anybody's done the
penguin better she plays a good pack cat woman but the the the the writing of the
cat woman the her words and everything to me is stupid well it's stupid by the
way Selena but it's all stupid Selena Kyle isn't a fucking raggedy beaten down
secretary I love that to her transformation and that I fucking loved it
and I think a lot of people do Selena Kyle is like is like it is like a
borderline like prostitute that's like like that lives in the slums made a
different choice which I think is a better choice seeing a prostitute then put
on a leather out that's not a transformation that's not an arc well
you're the one that likes all the weird sexual stuff you probably like a
couple hookers running around that film I don't have any opinion on how
hookers would have factored into that but return here while you expel all your
perverted fantasies through one of my childhood heroes Batman yes no room for
your filthy thoughts in my Batman mythology well I said I liked her being
a dowdy secretary and you said you wanted her to be a perved out prostitute
and now you're lecturing me on morals this looks terrible by the way this
whole thing with the purple fringe around the outside what's the cat's
perspective looking at. Yeah because all cats see things with a
purple ring around the lens. It's just a bizarre choice. Cats
have green eyes at least make it green. Black and white. It's
black and white with the faintest yellow. It's black and white
with the like tiniest hint of purple around the edge. It's
so it's like I never even noticed the purple till you just
said that. All right. Right Joe. But you know look you've
got a more stew to make this trip to Denver. I don't know at this point. I just have never
also by the way has screamed to me in a restaurant about aliens being a terrible movie. No I never
said that is a lie. Oh we can call alien three. No you Joe as God is my witness. You're
upset about aliens and you were very very upset about Terminator 2. Oh yeah I lost stand
by that. And these are just kind of movies that are just generally considered classics
But there's no like fun back and forth.
You're always just like so angry.
My argument with you about aliens was I said some people make the argument that it turned
the franchise for being a horror suspense sci -fi movie into an action movie and some people
don't like that about it.
That was my only argument.
They made an interesting choice and I went with them.
And if we were having a discussion about the big picture of James Cameron's work,
I probably said if aliens is the best.
I don't think we can survive that time.
right after that Batman Returns because we saw Ford Fairline and the writer of Ford Fairline
and Batman Returns was in attendance and we already had kind of an early version of this
argument. Now did and that guy said that guy said they said you wrote the adventures
of Hudson Hawk Batman Returns and they named one other one of his movies and he said yeah
That was my failing down period. He said that
That was my failing. I don't think that guy would think that that he's he said he said I'm one of the most hated men in comic books
He said that
Well, okay, I don't like comic books the writer said it. Jesus Christ. I don't like comic books, Joe
I'm saying a movie about you know Jesus where he's a pimp is good or something if I could watch the fucking Avengers or
Batman Returns 10 times I'd watch Batman Returns 10. Listen, I'm not saying you got to love
the Avengers. I'm just saying Batman. Everybody loves the Avengers. I don't love it. Everybody
loves Batman Returns, according to you. I love a movie that doesn't have to be three
hours long. Look, I'm not. Do you hear me? Do you hear me defending the Avengers? People
do love Batman. I like the Avengers and they really don't. Alright, buster point.
My friends love Batman returns. But I've met your friends. Yeah. No they're down. This
cat is killing Buster Point Dexter. This was pretty effective. I guess this is what they
couldn't afford in the original creep show. I don't think it was that they couldn't afford
one of the effects in the story. I think they didn't have enough money to make five stories
so they only made three and they cut to that's all. That's all. It's pretty gross.
Yeah it's great. I thought the cat would burst out the tum tum.
It's gross that it comes back out of his mouth. But I like the cat crawls into his stomach and
just kind of incubates in there for a little while. Is that the right term?
It works. Why not? I'm very excited for the next story
to come on. First we got to get through the end of this story.
story. Yeah, the last story was the best. I mean, it's fantastic. And it's got a real
dirty 80s New York feel to it. Yeah, it reminded me a little of After Hours, which is a great
Scorsese movie that it always underseen, I would say. It always makes me think of the
fly. Mm hmm. Similar to the Goldblum one. Yeah, like these people live in these big
lofts and they're all artists and creators. That's what After Hours was as well. And
they have no money or anything like that. I wonder like you think William Hickey's like
all right you got to spray him with blood fine. You have to do a couple takes whatever
or is he like just a miserable guy about it. What do you think I bet you I would be
willing to bet William Hickey was probably a joy. I would be I would think maybe I would
think he was probably a joy to be right. He's got a Burgess Meredith vibe. I bet
British Meredith was a joy. He was also William Hickey was in. Oh my blue heaven. Yep. As
the mob I had now and he was in. You're under arrest. Yeah. My blue heaven does not hold
up. How dare you. OK. Watch it. I own it. I do too. I watch it frequently. No it does
not a wonderful film Steve Martin Rick Moranis two of my all -time favorite Steve Martin is
so miscast in that part and he is so unrealistic and not even attempting to be realistic in that
part watching it as an adult I was like this is one of the few movies where I can just
say I was wrong as a child I disagree I say Steve Martin walks a fine line between cartoonishness
and realism. Oh, well then watch it again. I've watched it a few months. Realism, Joe.
I always watch it. Realism. He's ridiculous. It's a broader character than most of his
comedic characters like his non mafia character. I like the role. I think he makes it somehow
unbelievable. Oh, I buy it the whole time. Oh, because ship. The guy was a pastor. What
are what are what are some of the lies he's telling when he's like dribbling that basketball?
Why do we find all those stolen textbooks in your truck your car? Because I was delivering
them. This whole thing is that he's always lying out of stuff. I can't remember any
of it though. I forget. Well, it's a very forgettable movie. It's structured terribly.
There's like no story to it at all. That's stupid. You're stupid sometimes. I would
have loved it as a kid. It's a horribly structured and plotted and acted film. I love Jane Cousack
and the music is bad. Her name is Joan Cousack. I always love her. She's always a bright
spot but come on I love the soundtrack my blue heaven is a wonderful song yeah
well that's why you can like the song my blue heaven there's a wonderful version
of it in the film it's it's the version that's the version of it well there are
many versions of it Pat it's a standard what's the big one the biggest one for
sure you know Sinatra did a version of it many people I don't know if there's one
that you know you know what's that I know this might be the final episode this might just
be the final episode why are you getting a never like this guy stand up I'm just gonna
say that Robert Klein yeah every time you're they're interviewing any comedian over 50
it's like well obviously Robert Klein was a huge influence all right great but he's
not funny I think he was like the first of he was like sort of like they think the first
like alt comic like he was the first guy to kind of like yeah be casual and wear sweaters
and yeah I've never seen a full set or something even I just I never I own his box set I own
every one of his specials and it's you know it's not totally for me but I respect what
the man did okay you know sure can I tell you that sure and he plays a good agent in
this story kind of right looks like Neil Brennan a little bit to me he does and I can't
I remember what else I've seen him in.
Everyone bars like this existed.
Look at this bar they're in.
Well, they existed in these movies, for sure.
They also exist everywhere in St. Louis, Missouri,
if you want to come home with me this Christmas.
And get involved in a darts tournament or two.
I thought you'd never ask.
Hey, if you ever wanted to play a three -hour game of darts
while Papa Roach plays, head to St. Louis
and go to a bar.
But this is a great little dive bar.
Look at this.
This is what you call your local.
I love spots like this man.
This guy has been in a thousand movies.
James Remar.
He's in so many movies.
He's in Django and Shane.
He's always fine you know.
I love James Remar.
Yeah he gets the job done.
Plays it good when they put him up to it and he plays a dirt ball he's very good
at it.
Yeah.
And he's about to make love to Ray Don Chong who was a big 80s babe.
I think she might have a body double in this.
How happened to her she's a good looking woman still she fills out a sweater I'll tell you
that much I dated a girl briefly that looked like Ray Don Chung and it didn't work out
unfortunately she's Ray Don gone you know Jesus yes she is I'm looking her up right
now I tell you this Joe you say to me she's Ray Don gone I'd laugh and we'd have a nice
time. You're just in this mode where you've got a shit on everything I say. I don't think
the listeners want that teasing you a little bit for God's sakes. Don't get all sensitive
on right on gone. She's right on. She is. Maybe Pat. Do you ever think maybe it hurts
that she's gone. It was like a ready to joke about it. Sure. Have you ever thought about
that. No I didn't. I don't. Of course. Here at all. Didn't I. Did she die right on
Chong. I believe she did. Did she die. I thought she died. I might be. Okay. All
all right Joe I don't think so wonder why Ray Don left Jesus oh I'm all work every
sentence I say is squatted over now I'm worried that's down worry that she died give me a
second here no she's not dead how about Maria can she do Alonzo did she die another try
named 80s I believe that she did die yes how about Mary Elizabeth master Antonio from
the abyss no she's like abyss no fuck the abyss is such a great great movie we don't
like James Cameron I'm not a big fan of his work and I hate avatar I'll give you that
but I mean the abyss terminator two and aliens like what what more do you want terminator
two sucks all right well let's let's move back I can't do this tonight I can't listen
to me watched it I watched it a lot I mean you want to show on my blue heaven watch
turn your two it's just as ridiculous but it's a science fiction movie so my blue
heaven was the anchor man of its day was supposed to be Joe I will slap the drink
out of your hand my blue heaven should have starred and he was he was the
perfect age and everything he should have said should have starred Alec
Baldwin coming off a Beetlejuice and a Miami blues and he could have done it
all in that movie. There's your Ray Don. Yeah. She's beautiful.
She's hot. No comment on Alec Baldwin being the perfect
choice for my blue. You don't you never comment when you know
I'm right. Listen. I didn't say you were wrong. It's an
interesting premise. I haven't really thought about it. Yeah
sure. It'd be good. They're just I'm just kind of getting
sad now because I'm looking at Ray Don and thinking of that
girl I dated that looked like her. All right. It didn't work
out. Give her a call tonight. She'll appreciate there's
rate on naked for real. Okay. Then maybe they're they're the real deal.
She looked in this movie with I I paused it. I'll be honest with you. Also this is a great
monster for a three million dollar budget. That's her now though. Oh. All right. She's
an old you know I hate that I had that reaction. She's an older woman. Yeah. I'm sorry. So
she's probably in her 60s. None of us would want them 25 years later put up against a
bottle of them from back in the past she was born in 61 so what is she 56 yeah yeah so there
you go no 54 that this demon is really scary in this one yeah I just said it was a great
demon on a low budget no bullshit I also dated a girl mind I'm gonna go back to that girl's
bird beer you did a girl look at that demon kind of look like that demon in a weird way
like if there was like a pretty version of that demon that's what she looked like and
And once once now once I realized that I couldn't get past it I had to break up with her over it a
Lot of relationships. I've had or just something that I've been like
Mmm, and I get fixated on I
Think my a lot of that might be growing up with Seinfeld
I called my buddy out on it the other day that he finds something with every girl like date to and they're always ludicrous
And I think it's growing up with Seinfeld and these start to seem like normal reasons to end relationships
every week Jerry having like Matt she has got manhands she's got a high voice
got a low voice that whatever it is they start to seem like good reasons to end
relationships with beautiful intelligent women because of sign film well I
believe that those premises were written because they are good reasons to
break up with somebody and that's where those jokes came from and that's where
they're so relatable yeah I mean but in order to survive and be in a
relationship that goes anywhere you have to be willing to look past stuff that's a
lot smaller than Jerry and George threw away. Yeah it's it's it's the women that
George Costanza threw away looking like he did or just mind -boggling with no
money. He's worse in uh he's even worse in shallow howl where he dumps that like
really hot chick because she's got the weird long tail and then all along he's
hiding a tail. A tail? He has a tail. That's the final gag in the movie he
as a vestigial tail.
Is that a real thing that people get?
Maybe one or two, probably.
The hell is that?
What's a vestigial tail?
What is that?
You just, you don't remember this?
He shakes his tail.
You start talking about shallow how,
then I chime in with another fact about shallow how.
Just asking a question, Pat.
We can't go on like this.
I'm asking a question.
No, I don't know the Fairleigh Brothers process.
What does that mean?
What's a vestigial tail mean?
I don't know what this is.
What's the word vestigial mean?
Well, you're holding a little an iPad looking up pictures of a topless right on Chong. Why don't you Google vestigial you use the word you I
Think vestigial means like you have a little bit of a tail, but in the movie. He has an actual town
How long is it?
It's like a very small flaccid penis and he wags it at the end of the movie
I spelled vestigial wrong first. I wrote correct. I spelled it correct first try. Maybe it's a tail that falls off. Oh
Oh, that can't be a real photo.
No, of course not.
It's like an elongated spine sort of situation.
Here we go.
Human vestigiality.
It says that involves those traits occurring in humans
that have lost all or most of their original function
through evolution, although I don't fucking know.
All right.
They have already lost me with this description.
Speaking of shallow how I went the other night buddy of mine had floor
Tickets to see the Foo Fighters who I loved in high school and really haven't liked their music since
So yeah, I went to the Foo Fighters show I knew I didn't like their music anymore
But it didn't matter it played a lot of the old classics
politics. They were great and Jack Black came out and sang a full and pretty amazing version
of Russia's Tom Sawyer. Oh that's pretty cool. And it was great. And then Stevie Nicks came
out with Hyme and they did stop dragging my heart around and gold dust woman. And that
was really awesome. So Hyme is sort of our modern day Fleetwood Mac. It's three very
young girls and they make awesome pop dance kind of music and they're great. And the
Foo Fighters played the Times Square music and Jack Black sang it yeah and he was it was
spot on and Jack Black was looking heavier than I've ever seen him and he's a heavy guy
really I hope he's okay tell me give me the Foo Fighters set you know they played from
their entire career but like you know they definitely picked the songs from the later
albums that are pretty good like a best of you and you know Pretender and those songs
that I'm not interested in them anymore, but they kept the hits coming and they played
enough of the first three albums that I was interested. Look at that. That's that's that's
Ray. That's all Ray Don. That's Ray Don's Chong.
Making my Ray Don long. There you go. There you go. You think Ray Don Chong could get
a job on Ray Donovan? Ray Don. She's two thirds of the way there. Ray Donovan. John Ray
Donovan John. Is this something? Is this a hot sketch? We could pitch over at the UCB.
Now this is the 80s. And they just had sex after meeting 10 minutes ago. I didn't see
a rubber warehouse loft. If I lived in New York in the 80s, I wouldn't have sex with
anybody. It just felt like a like a living STD. Yeah, place. Yeah, you know, and it
was during the scare of everything. Oh, God, I would have been terrified.
right. I guess now I mean obviously it's still a big frightening thing but you never hear
anyone say like oh my buddy got AIDS. I'm going to talk in any STD but you heard it a lot
back then I would imagine from people I know who live there just like oh another friend
of mine another friend of mine. Hopefully we're kind of out of the what you hear about
this douchebag hedge fund guy who bought the rights to the AIDS pill jacked it from
$13 to $750 $750 wait what look up the story once we're done but it's this head funds dude
the picture they have of him is like with two thumbs pointed at his dick he's like the ultimate
like douchebag bro frack guy right he bought the rights to the AIDS pill that like takes
care of the most serious form of AIDS not ATZ but another you know very obviously it's
a very important pill to people with the AIDS bar. Sure. He bought it and he raised the
price from thirteen dollars and fifty cents to seven hundred and fifty dollars per pill.
And they confronted him about it. They were like you're a monster. What are you doing?
He's like you guys really shouldn't be mad at me about this. You guys should probably
calm down about that. Like just like these weird deferring methods. Right. But he's
just kind of destroying lives like he like he's like if you want these pills 750 bucks it's
a sick sick man and how many do you need he's the most hated guy in America if you get on
Twitter or whatever it's for a certain it's for a certain symptom of AIDS that like more
serious patients need I believe I want to look it up right now well I would look it
up after it's just it's an interesting fact all right I'll look it up after and by that
I mean sort of now there's interviews servicing with them and shit it's a big news story Jesus
I didn't hear about that yeah then again I'm terrible at reading news you know I often
go back and forth I anything related to the news the world whatever is so depressing that
I avoid it and I realize that makes me one of the head in the sand kind of people.
But also like what do I need to be more depressed about other things too.
Like I know everything sucks I don't need to read all about it.
It's I mean I look I listen to the news every morning and I try to read a bit too.
I know enough.
It's a lot of bad news you know it's all bad I mean that's the game they're in.
It's like I asked people to work. Hey, what's going on this weekend? Well, you know, it's
supposed to be 110 degrees out. Why are you looking up the weather? Just live your fucking
life. You're gonna on a Wednesday be dreading the weekend because it's going to be hot.
I got to admit, I'll often I'll often look up the weather early. I mean, people do on
vacation to go on vacation. It's like, oh, well, you know, it's going to be this
like, oh, man, it really sucks. YOLO. YOLO, baby.
maybe but the but you know the weather the weather can impact your weekend you wouldn't
you know you maybe say I want to go outside on Saturday and then you see it's gonna be
110 degrees yeah what are you doing this weekend we got a wedding what's that about buddy
Sean Clements who does a great podcast called Hollywood Handbook that I recommend I was
on it but they're all very funny that's it that's about all plans Saturday Saturday
at the National History Museum natural history in town here. Yeah. All right. Well, that's
I love an in town wedding. All my friends have weddings on Saturday. I don't the hell
am I going to do going to any of them sit around my dick in my hand on Saturday. Sounds
like a good Saturday to me. Hey, am I wrong? Hey, that's my reaction to that. Am I wrong?
I'm giving you the hay that I'm giving you hey that that was that was a that was an affirmative
response.
There's an element of right of a Walter sob check John Goodman and Lebowski to you to
me not certainly not in the weight but just in the hair trigger temper the anger about
a lot of things the argumentative nature who's got a heart listen when I first saw
the Big Lebowski I said I related to that character actually so I can't argue with you
totally it's a hilarious game I just read a great fuck I think it was on film drunk I
always hate this when I read a great article and I want to give the person credit but
I don't remember who was but it's about this big giant theory as a giant article
about how they thought that Big Lebowski was about how the real way to be is to just
be like a sponge and absorbing what people say and not engaging with their bullshit.
They're talking about how the dude is very just like anytime anybody's yelling at him
or whatever he's just walking away and he's like I don't need this or whatever.
And people talking too much is what drives him nuts and like what the downfall is
in the movie.
It was all about how the movie is about the needless talking that people do.
And whether it was what Cohen's intended or not, it's a fascinating article.
I urge you to look it up all right. I would like to I would like to read this article
I love that cash I think I talked about this podcast
I had a I did the first one I had a film professor who would find the gay agenda in any movie and
Even though you knew it wasn't intended most of the time. It was just fascinating shit
I like people's theories people's weird ideas on stuff
That's it nice. All right fair enough
If you're watching along with us
We're really like a goonie or Neil Brennan the guy does yeah, if you're watching along with us the weird -looking Neil Brennan
Guy is on screen again
And they're at James remars. I can't remember his character's name. They're at his art showing
he's he started drawing pictures of this demon right thing and
But not showing them anybody but the but the process of doing that and inspired him and invigorated him
and now his art is doing well again.
And he's with Ray Don Chong, who's super hot
and yet is sleeping with this man,
even though it looks like he fell into a vat of Crisco.
Earlier that day.
I mean, now, is Remor,
I mean, I'm not trying to shit on the guy.
Is he a good -looking guy by 80s standards?
He looks greasy.
Remor, I think, has given me a poor man's
Mickey Rourke 80s vibe, you know?
know right he's just kind of there nowadays he's much more of a character actor type dude
yeah but yeah I mean he's alright yeah I mean you're not bad looking but it's a it's definitely
a time where everyone could have fucked up teeth I mean RDC though it's like a 10 sure
but I buy these two as a couple and I like the casual interracial vibe of it without calling
attention to it if I can be honest with you. That's like you know it's something I always
admired about this film. My mom said that to me when she took me to see this. Did you
really? No. No. No Pat. I mean this was very unusual for the time period. It didn't strike
me as odd when I saw it. That's good you're a very enlightened kid. I was always very
open minded. I remember going to see the pelican brief at the dollar show with my
dad and that was kind of my first discussion of race with my dad because I was like so wait
like Denzel Washington and Julia Roberts for two and a half hours are like running around
together and in any other movie they would have been a couple they would have hooked
up at some point right why did that not happen and my dad was like well you know I think
I think it's just hard for a mainstream audience and I was like, oh, okay, all right, but your
dad was for it.
He seemed to be I mean any discussion of sexuality caused the car to become icily silent.
So we kind of stopped talking about it, but right, but you got that you got the idea
that he saw the flaw or fault in the pub.
Yeah, not not that he agreed with it.
Yeah, I mean it was a pretty shitty thing.
I mean like obviously any movie like that especially a big John Grisham kind of thriller the the
two incredibly attractive leads are gonna fuck and in this movie they were like pals Denzel
Washington Julia Roberts it was kind of fucked up now who does Tom Cruise bang in the firm
does he bang with a firm that's it I love the firm I just rewatched it and I was
being I was saying we're talking sex and it's called the firm yeah exactly what what
to see who does he bang in it. His wife is Gene Triple Horn who used to be Ben Stiller's
wife. Gene Triple Horn. I always think that's the lady from all in the family. No it's Gene
Stapleton. But no he cheats on his wife in like the Bahamas or something and it's one
of my favorite scenes ever in the movies. He's Wilford Brimley. That movie has the
best cast of character actors ever. Yeah. Holly Hunter's awesome and Gene Ackman.
and all these amazing people.
Tobin Bell, who played Jigsaw down the line
in the Saw movies, but Brimley has pictures
of Tom Cruise fucking this woman on the beach,
who they like set him up to fuck, to blackmail him.
And Brimley starts going through the photos
and he's like, you know, wives by nature
tend to be okay with the occasional slipup
early on in a marriage.
But these are the kind of intimate acts, oral and such, that a young wife won't forgive.
So if you can imagine a tight shot of Wilford Brimley saying oral and such, it's just such
a fantastic scene.
I was cackling when I watched it recently.
Oral and such.
You've got one of the best scenes on Seinfeld ever when he goes, you know, he goes, yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. I work for the post office and I also happen to be a general. Yeah.
He also wonder like did he know he was funny because he seems to be humorless. Him in in
and out the great Kevin Klein movie in and out. Yeah. Who does he play in that again?
He plays the Joan Cusack's father to bring it back to Cusack and best line of that.
Yeah so it's based on that Tom Hanks speech where he outered his high school drama teacher
when he won from Philadelphia but Kevin Klein's not ready to come out it's a very funny movie
if you haven't seen.
Yeah I love it and so they it's on the Oscars and he's like you know the reveal that Kevin
Klein is gay and they're all talking about how outraged they are they go around the
room with how outraged they are then Wilford Brimley goes he mowed my lawn once never
again.
like talking about like an Academy Award winning actor really cracked me up at the time.
He I that in and out was a was a special genre of comedy that came out in the late 90s.
It was a very specific type of comedy.
Saw it on a double feature with the game starring Michael Douglas loved it.
Those comedies in the late 90s, those mainstream comedies,
very, very glossy, shiny look to them.
Yeah.
Very whimsical, quirky soundtracks,
a lot of horns and things and people sneaking around and stuff.
Yeah.
Grumpy old men is one of those movies.
Sure.
Like, boom, boom, boom, boom.
Like, you know, like an orchestra.
I actually hate that style of music and comedies.
It bugs me.
Most comedy music bugs me.
I like a silent awkward comedy most of the time sure but yeah 80s and 90s were bad times
for scores and comedy. Plants are Zonobiles is pretty much my favorite comedy I would
say and the music in that is really fucking annoying. It's like this weird digital. At
one point they do a remix using Steve Martin's dialogue from the yeah I know like a rap song
I know so terrible and I just block it out and I love the movie when they turn that
digital music music sad it's it's I mean it's just it's horrible yeah it's it's
hardly is boom boom boom boom that's so sad god it's cuz it's so cold yeah
detached yeah I we talked I think on this podcast about how I sold this old
copy of Gator bait this like VHS movie like I used you know sell things once
they go out of print and I because I love the movie so much I had a copy of the
Soundtrack to planes trans automobiles a used copy soundtrack was terrible. Yeah, and I sold that for
wait for it
$500
Of a CD it had gone out of print. I found it in a used record store, and I was like $1. Yes
I love the movie. I'll buy the soundtrack and
Five years later. I'm like wonder what this is worth anything like that
I don't hear a lot of people talking about the planes trans automobiles soundtrack. It was on Amazon for $500. I
I put mine up for like, you know, $4 .99 and it sold the next day.
The next day?
The next day.
At a time when I really fucking needed money.
And that's something I'm going to recommend to all of you out there.
You got a big collection of anything.
Hop online and see if it's worth any money because that got me through some really rough
time.
This is a strong recommendation for the audience, Pat.
You heard it here first, guys.
Try to find things that are rare and out of print.
Settle them for near five years.
I'm saying you might have them that's what I'm saying and then sell them online to people
I guess that culture has become bigger now at the time I felt like I had really stumbled
upon something great because I that's the only way I made rent each month was doing
little scams like this.
Criterions are great to buy and hold on to they go out of print.
Now here's my question.
We're at the big twist to the final story here where James Reymar was attacked by
the demon that he meets Ray Dong Chong the demon makes him promise will never tell great
effects ten years later he's got a beautiful family he finally opens up to Ray Dong Chong
and says this is what attacked me the night I met you did you see this twist coming yeah
totally you did I did from the jump of it no not from the jump but I knew that once
he was like don't tell anyone that obviously he was going to tell someone but I mean did
you think he would tell her and she would be the demon. No I guess not. I thought the demon
would pop in through the window or something like. Hey guys. Right. Sure. Did I think the
demon would have that rack. No. Do I. Now if you now pretend you're a single man.
Yeah. Well actually we just do this with your current
girlfriend. Okay. Your girlfriend comes to you tomorrow. She says Pat. Here's the
deal. I'm actually this demon. Uh huh. But you love me. And as long as you never mentioned
it again we can just stay together and I'll always look like this to you. But just know
that deep down underneath on this demon and if you ever mentioned it'll it'll come out.
Do you do you do you go. Is she cool that if we break up or does that
trigger the demon. Yeah no you have the option of breaking
up. Do you break up or do you go. I can why put me in this position out of sight
out of mind. Why put me in a position that's going to like jeopardize my relationship.
It won't jeopardize your relationship. It's such a absurd thing. I'm truly curious because
I wonder how I would react. I don't want to be with a demon. You figure
she's got like contacts in hell. But there would be no party.
I also figure a demon's not going to be very trustworthy. There'd be no party that's
like out of sight out of mind. No not with a demon. Here's the sad news. You're saying
she's a demon with a heart of gold. No it's just she's like Ray Dawn. She's like a nice
girl unless you say something then she turns into a demon. It's real sad when the kids
turn into the fucking demons. That's rough. Isn't it? I think that's why they made
them cute so it would seem less rough. I guess they're kind of cute but then they all turned
a stone here at the end their gargoyles. Here's sad news for the guy that paid five hundred
dollars for your. Oh I bet it's worth nothing now. You can just download the soundtrack or
stream it for free on Amazon music. And which is the CD though. Well I'm only seeing
the cassette for forty five dollars still that's pretty good because that's just an example
of movie that was kind of like an okay thing and now it's become like a beloved Thanksgiving
classic yeah well like oh I'd love the soundtrack and then they'll go up and look online if
they got a lot of money they're like all right that's what it costs I'll pay it forty five
dollars for a cassette I mean you know God bless I mean the weird thing is only would
you put the iPad down Pat it's my job as it's not as trying to connect with you I'm connecting
with you I'm the information guy on the podcast I look things up Deborah Harry we didn't mention
his lead singer Blondie who didn't know that hopefully you would know she was so hot man
imagine a lot of people didn't know that Joe who are listening to the podcast not everyone
knows that the lead singer of Blondie is Debbie Harry. I think everybody knows that is this
law is one of the Lawrence's dead joke. We're talking we're probably talking to half the
people who don't even know what Blondie is with you with people dying tonight. You thought
Ray Don Chong was dead. She's 54 for Christ's sake. Well I know Jonathan Brandis killed
himself. Yes. I'm going to look up. I thought one of the Lawrence's was dead but I might
be wrong. And don't yell at me now. Why are the iPad? This is why you ask a question.
Lee is one of the Lawrence's dead. What are we gonna just let it hang out there? But when
I look over and you're perusing, you know, Etsy for a new blouse, nothing of the sort
is happening. A new blouse with a print of Ryan Gosling's face on it. Hold on a second.
it. Let's see here. Joey Lawrence. Whatever happened to him. Whoa.
Your Lawrence is alive and he's on the show Joey and Melissa or something on the kids
network. What is that like a like a Nickelodeon sitcom. Yeah it's like a you know what Disney
channel or one of those. He looks weird. Look at Joey Lawrence. He looks like he's made
of claymation yeah why why does he look like that I had filler plastic surgery is that what
that is it looks like filler to me which I learned about very recently what's filler
filler is similar to Botox but you're basically putting a skin like substance into the wrinkles
in your face and then you wind up looking very strange and a lot of people do filler it looks
so weird yeah the movie's over just ended because I'm looking up that I missed the
I'm looking up this goddamn Joey Lawrence question you had you don't have to I know Joey Lawrence
is alive I don't know about Matthew Lawrence now I know I know Joey's alive Matthew Lawrence
holding it together look at that kid looks sharp looking really good good for you Matthew
who's the other one Andrew Lawrence Matthew Lawrence is in Plants and his automobiles
he's Steve Martin's very cute son yeah and what Matthew Lawrence was also on Boy Meets
world was he not? No that was Fred Savage's brother Ben Savage. No but Matthew Lawrence
played his friend didn't he? No that was Ryder Strong which is a gay poor name if I ever
heard one. The other friend. Hold on I'm looking this up. I don't think so but maybe. Television
he was on give me a break. Okay that seems right. He was on blossom as young Joey. Okay
Drexel's class. I bet Joey went into the producers and he was like you gotta get my brother
to run the show I mean it's just like me boy meets world sixty eight episodes play Jack
Hunter you want to talk about another gay porn jack hunter and writer strong he also was on
Drexel's class to bring up our old boy Dabney Cole I used to watch Drexel's class it was
on at the same time as the Sinbad show I think I was watching the Sinbad show and during
a period when the Simpsons was on Thursday if I'm not mistaken, Patty, we got another
podcast center about here. We did. I hope you guys enjoyed it again. We're on itunes.
We're on all those little fringy side podcast places. We'd love a review. You click the
stars. You say Joe and Pat are great. We love the show. If you do, I need you to lie. If
you're listening to the fifth episode, you probably like us. We love to hear your suggestions
and we love your tweets. I'm at the Patrick Walsh. Joe is at Joe DeRosa comedy. And that
goes for all social media. And we'll be at the mile high comedy festival October
over third sat whatever the Saturday Saturday X over third and we're at eight twenty a .m.
Maniac cop to maniac cop to come on out drink with us we're going to drink all the basically
Padme's plan is we get up at seven a .m. to do an eight twenty a .m. podcast and then
we're just going to drink all day I'm going to say this convention I am at my funniest
with a drink or two under my belt and also at my funniest when I wake up way too early
And I'm in a bad mood. This could be a real funny combination. I think it's gonna be a great time
I'm probably gonna break Joe's balls a lot. I think we're gonna laugh and have a real nice time
I think it's gonna be great. I'm looking forward to it. I've done a lot of morning radio on my day
I'm good in the morning. Okay, especially if I'm drinking you like morning sex. No, no big fan
All right. Well, that's another time
Another discussion
save that for the Mr. Robot pot. You're fresh, you know, you feel fit because you just woke
up. It's not fresh. I feel like it's it's been sleeping
all night. Things are caking up and going stale. I'm a sexual being if that's a crime
let me out. You've been listening to ladies were coming
to your town Denver October 3rd. Yeah, and I would consider having sex with you even
even if you're secretly a demon. I do believe in the out of sight out of mind sure. This
has two stars on Netflix by the way. It's ridiculous. They're they're so harsh with
the Netflix ratings. It makes me furious. Everything is two stars. It's absurd. By my
returns doesn't you've been listening to we'll see you in hell presentation of the
Fangoria podcast network produced by Thomas DeFeo executive produced by our friend Ken
Hanley of Fangoria entertainment for press opportunities advertising inquiry inquiries
and information about we'll see you in hell contact Ken at Fangoria comm. Thanks guys