I'll see you in the show that talks about movies but today it's talking about TV
TV. That's Patrick Walsh over there. Hi everybody, we are going to be talking about a TV show. I think you should leave with Tim Robinson the third and probably final season of this sketch show. What is that the word on the street that it's over. I just feel like it barely hangs in every year and they get less episodes every time and, you know, actually, I guess it's had six every year. Okay, fair enough.
It always is six they get shorter though. Yeah.
The I went back to the original season, the were episodes of the season one rang in around like 18 minutes. This season they're coming in at like 11 and 20 seconds or something.
short. It's a brief. It's brief and funny. Two things. Very few comedy shows are these days. So we'll get there. We'll get there.
What's going on in your world, Joseph?
Chinks, I just came from picketing. Well, how did it go? Did it fix everything today?
Yeah, we were at Disney and the heads of Disney kind of came out on the roof like that final Beatles concert and we're just like, guys, we hear you. We're giving you everything you need and launches on the mouse house today.
And then they just had this spectacular spread of launch for everyone to enjoy.
No, none of that happened. Disney had actually wheeled out a giant sign that said, honking is illegal in this neighborhood.
Honking is illegal only in LA. Oh, dear. Well, it's not. It's a sign that Disney put out and then everyone that drove by honked in support of the science. It's like, nobody is on your fucking side. Okay.
Poor Disney. Poor Disney. All they wanted to do was be racist. Yeah. And the worst example of capitalistic. And then they got called out on it. Now they have to be woke. Oh, that hurts them. And now they have to be fair to the writers.
Poor Disney sucks. It just sucks for them. I was trying to piece together the latest scandal for Disney. So I haven't seen a little mermaid.
I think it looks horrible. I thought the Lion King live action thing was fucking horrible. But so Joe, as you pointed out on the show, Melissa McCarthy comes out and says my performance as Ursula was influenced by the drag movement.
Well, that she drew from her own drag experience. She's now saying that she spent time as a drag queen. I don't know what's going on anymore.
Okay. So I don't think you did. Melissa, but her makeup artist is somehow in the new. I've never in my life seen a makeup artist involved in like a discussion in terms of controversy.
People are saying that Melissa McCarthy, if she was truly going to be influenced by drag performance, should have gotten a gay makeup artist.
Now I've been working in this business 15 years. I have never met a makeup artist. A male makeup artist who was not gay. I just haven't. But apparently you remember.
You remember Hank, right? Old burly Hank. The old. Yeah. Let me just give you some more rouge before we go out this. We he was everybody.
Well, he has some of this bucket. Let me touch up your rouge. He worked more than anybody with all the makeup jobs.
He was the only guy that the straight male actors would let put makeup on their cock because they knew that he got nothing out of it.
You know, he just he was there for the work. Anyway, I still don't fully understand what's happening here. And I'm trying to explain it as best I can.
But people were saying if Melissa McCarthy is going to be influenced by drag culture, she should have had a gay makeup artist. For some reason, she had a straight makeup artist.
And then the quote I saw was the makeup artist was like, why can't I do makeup just as good as a gay makeup artist. And I was like, this poor bastard's going to get canceled. Now all he's doing is showing up for work.
And also you know how you know how traditionally because because it'll say it when you watch an interview with Melissa McCarthy, let's say on a DVD feature, you know, or or talk show or something that bottom key across the bottom of screen will say actress slash comedian slash staffing of makeup artist department.
Yeah, yeah, it's crazy. It's she doesn't hire the makeup artist.
I actually more often though, the lead with her probably most notable credit, which is former drag performer, Melissa McCarthy and then get to actress comedian.
I read an article about the little mermaid. I mean, this little mermaid is all anybody can talk about. I mean, it's getting more pressed and then Biden.
I read again. I saw and more disturbing than the fall is him walking back on to the White House lawn 78 feet from the press like just they won't let him get anywhere near the press.
Yeah, fear that he might talk. And they go, are you okay? And he goes, I got a bagged and then just keeps walking. And you're like, I literally saw that I go, what is happening?
What is happening? And then prop up that corpse again. Oh, yeah.
There was an article I read about the little mermaid. This actually came from a pro a pro diversity of diversity.
Diversity, uh, uh, enthusiast or, or, um, diversity lover, not diverse. What's the word I'm looking for?
Son of a bitch. Uh, when you're, when you're a promoter of something, uh, advocate, excuse me advocate, diversity advocate.
Yeah. Um, like that's their job, I mean, sure. Okay. They were, they were, uh, they were criticizing a little mermaid.
Because they said the fact that it ignored slavery was doing a disservice to history. I'm like, buddy.
I'm not looking to the little mermaid for a slavery plot wide. Now wait a minute. Why would and or should the little mermaid, which has to my knowledge, never dealt with the horrors of slavery.
Why should it deal with it now? Because he said that given, even though the time period is not specified, given the, uh, the garb and, uh, the ships and the look and everything of that time period.
He can tell that it's, it's such and such a time period and in the whatever region it takes place in. And that was a time of heavy slave trafficking.
And the fact that this movie depicts the people living in racial harmony is doing a disservice to history and teaching our children about what happened.
And just because adults don't feel comfortable talking about slavery and history doesn't mean that we are to deprive our children of, of learning about the horrors of it.
I, which, that point I agree with. Sure. But when he said, combine it with the little mermaid. That's what I was going to say. Doesn't have to be in the little mermaid.
This is up there with the, with the leg was, I'm, oh, I'm boycotting the Mario movie because it's not diverse enough.
Yeah. People are losing their shit, man. This poor, Halley chick. That's the star of the little mermaid. This poor woman. She's like, I just wanted to, I'm just trying to make a fucking look.
Can I just be in a fucking movie? Jesus Christ. Yeah. It's also like that poor girl has to answer for a million fucking things now.
Just simply being cat. There, there's no interview that isn't going to ask her about being the black little mermaid. And that fucking sucks. Yeah.
I sent Joe. We haven't been to keen on Taika white TT. But he gave a speech at a, at a diversity luncheon or something. And he's like, I'm so fucking sick of diversity. Can we stop with diversity?
He's like, we'd rather be making you great new stories than having to come to events like this. Like what are we doing?
Well, and he also said it was crazy. I was a president and make the news. I guess because he's, he is himself as diverse.
Well, I think his point was stop asking us, meaning the people that have been discriminated against or marginalized or whatever.
The diversity issue. He's like, you cause the problem. Fix it and like, shut the fuck up and leave us alone.
And I, at least that was my takeaway. And I thought he made a great point. Yeah.
Yeah. It's you guys did this. Why are you turning to the people that you've been exploiting for a hundred years to fix things? He's absolutely right.
It's wild. Yeah. Any hoot.
Yeah. But that's, that's kind of all I got. I mean, I, I feel like it's, it's, it's obviously a more positive upbeat time than the pandemic.
But it's like, yeah, another period of time where it's like, don't know how long I'm going to be out of work.
Don't know how long it's going to last. So there's not, I don't know. There's not much going on in my world.
I gotta tell you, and I gotta tell you, and this, this will presumably make certain people won't like this opinion.
But I gotta tell you, I don't know if it's a better time anymore than when the pandemic and lockdown was at least then we could kind of blame craziness on this terrible, weird, unique situation we were all strapped in.
Now I get even more depressed and dejected by it all because we have an opportunity to be out there being better and it doesn't seem to be happening.
Yeah. And it, it's just what a fucking train wreck, man. God almighty, this, this, this, oh yeah, this AI thing is really getting to me.
It's just so bad. And then this thing with the, with the, the economy, the debt ceiling and yeah, I started an article about that. And I was like, I'm just going to skip this one.
I'll think I need to learn about the debt ceiling because I don't need another thing to worry about.
And then, and then like whether you agree with AOC or not, whether you agree with Joe Biden or not, whether you agree with Ron DeSantis or not, whatever, whoever the politician is that you like or hate or whatever, the fact that none of these people can even go out to make a speech anymore.
Or that people, the audience being like, fuck you pig. You're like, this is insanity.
Like decorum is just gone. Like this is wild shit at this point.
I'm trying to watch the AOC thing about like about this, this, this, the national debt and everything. And I'm trying to determine if I agree or disagree with her and I can't even focus on it because people in the audience are literally screaming like,
you're a fucking pig. It's crazy. Yeah. Yeah. There you go. All right. Anyway, let's talk about the Barbie movie, little news psycho. What the hell is going on with this thing, man?
This, this seems like a national hypnosis or something going on with this Barbie movie. I haven't talked to a person who has the slightest whiff of interest in seeing this thing, male or female adult or child. It seems to exist, almost like the movie toys with Robin Williams.
In this area where you can't imagine anyone wanting to see it and enjoy it. It looks too adult for kids, but too kitty for adults.
It's a style of movie that's never been attempted by Greta Gerwig and Noah Bombak. So who knows if there'll be any good at it. Although I like their work.
I do too, but I got to say, and maybe I'm wrong. Just from the trailer alone, I'm like, that's very apparent. The fantastic sequences they show with like the manufactured supposed to look fake backgrounds.
Dude, it looks like it looks like SNL sketch quality at best. Yeah, they are not hitting the surreal note that they're trying to hit with those visuals at all.
I'm seeing more and more of that. I just watched the latest season of Dave on an FX. And there was stuff in the finale has Brad Pitt and Rachel McCatams in it.
Huge stars. It's a 45 minute episode. And basically, it's a stalker who works with Dave who shows up to bring him a script. And then, you know, it's your classic half hour comedy now, which is to say that it's a dark thriller with very few laughs.
It's just kind of played like Cape Fear or something, just some girl stalking him. Anyway, him and Brad Pitt are in this house, like fighting this girl. And it was a pretty decently done episode.
All the money they must have spent to pull this thing together. The final scene of the movie, he goes to Africa or the show. He goes to Africa to meet with Drake, the rapper.
Clearly, they are not in Africa. So they're superimposed. And it looks so unbelievably fake. Then you start to question whether Drake and Dave are even in the same place because they both look so fake. And then it's little by little, you're like, oh, wait a minute, they're not no wonder this looks so bad.
Drake couldn't even like be in the same room as him. So they had to shoot this on some green screen thing. Then for the final shot of the season, Drake puts his arm around Dave and they like walk off into the sunset. And it's the worst looking,
looking fake is looking shot I've ever seen. And it's like they'll pay to get Brad Pitt, Rachel McAdams, a multi location shoot. But now we're still doing this thing where we're, we've got worse looking special effects than we did in 1981.
Everything looks fake. And in a time where we're questioning everything with AI and, you know, deep fakes and all that, when it starts seeping into just a regular show, it takes me out of it in a huge way, like that's not a show that has special effects. Why does it look like I'm watching Tron when I'm watching two men have a conversation.
Yeah, it's it's troubling. It's troubling.
I, I think that well, I was heading to save at the Barbie movie, but, but well, I'll go back to Barbie.
A bit of good news for me. I don't know if you'll care or not, Pat, but Kim Ketrow confirmed. Oh, sure. Returning for just like that season two. It's just a cameo.
Where apparently they revealed the full details of the cameo. This is another thing they're doing now. I don't understand why the studios are just leaking the spoilers.
I guess it's a means to try to work the people that are going to leak it before them. But I watched I watched this day finale. The night it aired. And I knew that Brad Pitt was a huge and huge. I'm just spoiling it now too. I guess, but this huge surprise was spoiled a meal. I don't even on Twitter.
Yeah, let us enjoy something. It's all we have. So, so Kim Ketrow's confirmed she's going to come back in the finale of season two. It's it's apparently the scene as a phone call.
And the article I read went out of their way to point out she did not speak to any of her former cast members or Michael Patrick King in the shooting of this scene.
But hey, I'm glad she's back for a scene. I'm glad it all I aside from what they did with Miranda and what they did with Miranda's husband. I'm blanking on the character's name. I like to use Steve. I like Miranda.
I thought, Miranda, I thought you liked it. Nice cream with me. I wouldn't. It seems like you don't even want to talk to me anymore. I may be in there. Yeah. I was sad that big died until all the Chris no stuck him out. Then it was like, Ralph would all right. So I bet they were thrilled. They killed him off. They brought her high five and in the office. They pat. There is no way they didn't know. And they said, here's how this is going to go.
We're going to kill off the character. You're not going to say a word. And if it comes out, you're off the show anyway. Yeah. And we're doing you a favor right now. That's that's undoubtedly what happened. No, as we know, I know some key players here real well.
And that's all I'll say Kim control. I think she did a wonderful thing here. She knows everyone wants her back. She knows she's got him over a barrel. My guess is, she asked for a million dollars to do the phone call. And she said, I will not be in the same room as Sarah Jessica or Michael Patrick King, they can come to me.
And I bet they did it. And I just think that's awesome. I hope she got five million dollars for it.
But I just I love that she and I look, I'm not like I'm a huge Kim control fan. I just I love that she seems to be one of the few people in this business to say.
You are a monster who made me feel like shit. You need me more than I need you. And fuck off. Like I really respect that because I guarantee this guy that we're talking about who runs these shows was not nice to any of these women, but they're all.
They're all back. I hope I hope this stuff with SJP is more misunderstood than than not. I would like to think that she is more delightful than not delightful, but I don't know who knows you never know in this business. You see a lot of famous people out there that seem like real gems and you get to know some of them and you're like, holy shit. So it's not most might be harsh, but it's a lot.
Barbie, here's the thing that, you know, and they just I just watched a thing about this new Miller light campaign that Megan Kelly talked about it on her show. And I know she's very polarizing. I'm very aware, but she did make a point that I'm going to give her credit for is I don't want to regurgitate it. Like Miller light has this new campaign with a lot of glazer.
Where a lot of comes out and says Miller beer beer ad campaigns for beer are responsible for a lot of bad shit.
It's, you know, they they were womanizing and they were this and they were that blah, blah, blah, blah. Right. She goes, so we want and all of our Miller merch out there that exploited women and promoted all this bad shit. It's still out there.
People own it. People collected it. It shows and events and whatever. And you know, you all have our shit. So if you have a, if you have old Miller merch that that promotes these these outdated ideas send it to us.
So we're off the bat. I've got a problem with this. Now we have to work to help you do fit, you know, send it to us. And then we'll turn it into good shit. So my first problem is putting us to work to Kiki's point.
The second issue I have with it is once again, which is what the guy said about the little mermaid. Actually, let's erase history. Pretend it never happened. Destroy the evidence, which is stupid.
Third problem. And this is ties into the Barbie movie guys Miller just stop doing it. That was the point Megan Kelly made just stop doing it.
You don't have to lecture us. You don't have to make us feel bad that you did a thing. Yeah, you did a thing. You regret doing the thing. You want to be different.
Be different. Yeah, you know, and she called glaze or a library and she goes, you got to send this library and out to scold us.
Which did make me laugh, but, but, but I agree with the point. And it's, by the way, this, this high brow concept of turning. Oh, and the concept of the campaign is they'll take the old merch and turn it into fertilizer.
Into faux manure that they will then use to farm hops and whatever else, right.
How are you going to turn a t shirt into fertilizer? What the fuck you talking about?
There's a way to make faux fertilizer out of old. I don't know. It ends the campaign ad ends with a lot of who I'm friendly with. I'm not knocking her tasting the fertilizer and going, that's good.
Good shit. So you have a woman. It's a campaign to stop doing awful things to women in your campaign. And then you make the new weapon eat literally eat shit literally eat shit is the joke.
This is why where are these commercials airing? Why did why did they need to do that? And why am I agreeing with Megan Kelly on anything?
I bet they did it because like they're like, we better come out with it now before somebody looks into our dark past. It's like, no, we all remember beer commercials had women running around in slow motion. We remember it.
Things have changed. We forgive you. We still buy Miller Lite. We don't buy Bud Light because you had a trans activist drink it in an ad is the latest scandal.
It wasn't even an ad. It wasn't even an ad. They sent a trans woman can one six pack with pictures of her on it. And kid rock and Travis Trent had a fucking hissy fit. And now, but you know what? All that keeps Travis Trent in the news.
Also, also fuck you Bud Light in every part of that. Fuck you for making a financial play to look woke when it was paper fucking thin.
Fuck you for retracting it the second you got heat from your from your fucking redneck fanboy pseudo promoters and spokesman.
And fuck you for throwing the people who created the campaign under the bus. And I believe they got fired. This is the thing. Stop with the fake virtue. Everybody stop. I don't need to be taught how to be a better person by Walmart.
Okay, stop. Like just sell your fucking cakes and chemical candies and and shitty vitamins and and what and cheap clothing and blankets. And that's the end of it. That's all I need from you Budweiser. I need you to do one thing.
Sell beer. I don't need to hear your political stance in any fucking direction ever ever.
Well, they've never taken up political stance in anything. It's like, why start now? It doesn't it doesn't make any sense to me.
And regardless, let's go to this movie corner.
Oh, sorry, the last.
Oh, sorry, I'm going to say Barbie. Yes. And the reason the Miller Light thing ties in the Barbie thing is is the Barbie movie.
It's like, it's like, well, I could give two fucks about Barbie. I never played with Barbies. And I don't give a shit if you did. And I don't even only played with them to have my Ninja Turtles fuck.
And I don't disagree with the idea that it promotes a false a bad image of false unattainable image to young. I get it. I agree with all that.
But you make a goddamn Barbie movie. And the movie is here's the problem with Barbie. And it's like, even if you're a fan of Barbie, now you're going to sit through this thing with a certain level of guilt.
That's not a certain level. I mean, as far as I know, the entire movie is about that. So I just don't get like what we're doing.
Like, let the people that like it like it or take it off the fucking it's this cake and eat it to approach. If you think Barbie is so awful and you think the sins you've committed through the production of this doll or so awful, discontinue the fucking doll.
And leave that's it. Stop trying to figure out a new way to make money off of it without doing anything.
Fuck off. Like, oh, God, it's anyway. All right, I'm done.
I agree. Folks, I saw a picture.
I saw a clip of Trump. I think I might have been an old clip, but he was like, where do we go?
Why do we love saying it? Don't we? Where do we go? Don't we love that?
So the man make does make me laugh sometimes. I just get me to this. You're like, why are you saying Puerto Rico like that? It's hilarious to me.
I watched not much, but I did. I mentioned the Michael J. Fox documentary. I saw a personality crisis colon one night only, which I watched really only because it's directed by Martin Scorsese.
And I have seen every movie that Martin Scorsese has the buster point Dexter thing. Yeah, all right.
Look, Scorsese, I don't know how the man is 80 years old and he's directing four hour movies and also two and three documentaries for HBO every year. It seems unlikely.
Maybe he has this one has a co director David Tedesky. So maybe Scorsese walks in and gives notes. I'm not sure. I don't know how involved he is.
But basically this is a one night performance of David Johansson. David Johansson was the lead singer of the New York Dolls, which is a early punk band that I prefer to like the sex pistols. I think they made better songs.
But they're early in that punk movement. They're great. New York band.
So he's doing kind of like jazzy type covers of them. He's doing covers of his own songs that he did as buster point Dexter, which is kind of his the darkest point of his career, which is when he was like saying it hot, hot, hot, hot.
That was not when I loved David Johansson, but I liked him and scrooge and some of his acting work, you know, but it's the guy kind of singing his way through the career.
And it's entertaining. Then there's interviews with him and then more traditional documentary stuff where you learn about the history of the New York Dolls.
If you don't care about the band, if you don't care about the music, you would have zero interest in this. It'll be way less entertaining to you than like the friend Libba, what's thing.
Because it's it's truly just a documentary about this really obscure band with a hour long performance tied in entertaining didn't blow my mind. Joe.
I've got two. I watched well, I've got a confession to make. I started watching the smart list docu series. And after my tirade last week about celebrities doing podcasts, I turned this thing on out of spite.
I wanted to be mad at it. And boy did these three gents woo me and sweep me right off my feet. I loved.
I sent you a voice memo saying how disgusted I was by it in the first 10 minutes, like they're on the private jet. And I'm like, this is what I'm talking about. God damn it.
Yeah. And then once they get to the first hotel and start making fun of each other. Yeah.
And do the show and like talk about the podcast and the way we've all talked about our own podcasts. I just was like, I fucking love these guys. Like I was making me laugh really hard.
Sean Hayes could be the most wonderful person that's ever lived, I believe. I hope I meet him one day. I hope he has to care for me one day in some capacity.
It's unlikely, but sure. Yeah.
Bateman has a quiet darkness to him, but I enjoyed it very much.
Yeah.
And really the back and forth between our net is so funny. Like the back and forth between our net and Bateman made me laugh was like our net every five minutes just being like, oh, OK, professor.
You fucking tool. Thanks for the suggestion, you know, and then like him like wolfing down food and like Bateman being like swallow the first bite.
Yeah, it was really, really funny. And it led to me listening to the podcast. And I love the podcast. I appreciate that.
As you know, look, they're Hollywood celebrities. They're clearly of the liberal class of thinking, you know, they're not certainly not conservatives.
But it's rare that you find people in that mode that are willing to still make edgy jokes and take some chances with the humor and be as open as they are and be crash.
And I thought it was awesome. I just loved it. I really, really liked the show. And I liked the podcast quite a bit. The only thing I don't like about the podcast is I wish they didn't have a guest sometimes I like them more than hearing from the celebrity guest.
I like want to listen to the three of them talk, but, but, but it's a, it's a wonderful show. And I really actually, I think Sean Hayes on Broadway right now. I'm going to go see that show. He's in.
It's funny that we have not talked about this since you took, you were like shitting on the show because I had the exact same experience. I turned it on. I said, not only are we doing a documentary about a fucking podcast.
But it's in black and white. I was like, this is so fucking pretentious. And I was every bit as angry as Joe. I watched all six episodes in one city. I laughed throughout. I love these guys as well.
Annette, I've always liked, but he certainly wore out his welcome in film and TV. And you don't kind of seem as much anymore. But he is by far the funniest of these three.
Sean Hayes, the heart, as you're saying, exactly right. Like him laughing is just delightful to watch. And then Bateman reminded me of myself. He seems to carry around a tremendous amount of darkness. He seems to have a lot of food issues.
Them arguing about their food issues and what they're going to get for dinners and lunches and stuff is pretty much the entire show, but it's all very, very funny.
That scene where that scene where they're ordering the room service.
And Bateman's doing the ordering and he's he's going, yes. And the gentleman that wants the bacon double cheeseburger fries once a diet coke ironically with that.
Yeah, just just it's so fucking funny, man. It's so funny.
Yeah, they're really funny. They have a great chemistry together. I don't know how Sean Hayes entered the group, but you need him there. He's perfect with them.
They seem like true friends and like Joe saying, there are a lot of jokes where I was like, I was surprised they left that in.
I think it's just because these guys have a lot of good will. Everyone loves them. And everyone knows they're not out to hurt anybody's feelings.
So I really enjoyed it. I'd watch another season of the documentary. I'll probably give the podcast to listen.
I actually found the documentary whenever they'd be talking to one of the stars, like even Will Ferrell or somebody, I was always kind of like, let's go back to hanging out with the boys in the hotel room.
Is that really the best part of the show.
Yeah.
So that's my number two. And you did that was my number two. And I'm saying that's my number two.
Oh, oh, oh, okay. Okay. Wow. All right. Great. I only have one more arrested development. I, you know, I'd only ever seen. I'd seen parts of the original series. Yeah.
And I watched season four. And I know I watched season two do that. I don't know. I just did. Dude, there's a lot I missed in that period because that was the period that was out.
Well, the sopranos was that period.
Yes.
A rest of development was that same period. Deadwood, the wire, the wire rescue me.
These were all major shows from that time period. I missed almost all of them because when you're touring with Gloria Estefan.
Yes. Yeah. Well, they were in the Miami Sound Machine at that time.
I was playing the dual snare drums.
Behind Gloria. No, but I was I was starting in comedy. And I was out every single night. Ad nauseam doing free shows and open mics and whatever I missed a lot of TV.
So anyway, I, I, the only arrested development I'd seen front to back was I saw season four. And I knew that that I remember those a big TV event because
that was the, well, that was the first thing that Netflix. That was the first series Netflix made. Yeah. And it's so bad.
Well, here's the thing. Having not known the show. I enjoyed it very much because I was already a fan of all the people in it. I knew them from other things at that point.
And I just had never gone back and watched it. I don't know why I just didn't. I'd seen an episode here or there.
Anyway, I was like, well, I'm going to go back and watch a rest of the development from the beginning. I'm only partway through season one, but.
Wow, what a treat. What a great thing that I get to like go through for the first time.
Season one and particularly season two are so fucking funny. And three is great beyond that. I actually stopped watching. There are many episodes I haven't seen because it was just making me sad.
But one, two and three are good. Two is amazing. And two has a Martin short appearance that I'm not going to spoil for you, but I'll just.
Good Lord. That is a funny episode. So many funny episodes. There are maybe never been a better, deeper comedy cast ensemble than a rest of development. Why everyone became famous. Yeah.
And what let's like Seinfeld level, all right, ensemble. Like and like wild.
You know, talk about you're like you couldn't do it now. Like that, that three episode arc where Julie Louis Dreyfus is playing the blind woman.
Yeah, I'm like, Jesus Christ, man. Yeah, like the amount of times they do, like, like a Laurel and Hardy style, she's talking to a wall joke, like, and thinks it's a person or whatever.
Yeah, it's just nuts. But I'm. And then, and then I, I refell in love with Julie Louis Dreyfus and felt bad about all my yelling about her last week. So, so there you go.
That's good.
Um, where are you in the series? You're in season two, right? Isn't she? No, that's season one still. I like, I would put it on before bad. I would doze off. And then like, so then like I saw some later ones.
And then I was like, fucking, I had to go back and rewatch ones. I missed. But, um, I look forward to rewatching. I watched the original cut of season four, which was the linear like character focus episodes.
They re -cut it to play like the original show. So I'm glad I get to, when I get to it, I get to see a new version of it. And then I never seen season five, like, which was not very well reviewed. But, I don't know, some critics said it was better than four. So, I mean, it's, it's interesting to have somebody kind of start with the end because I, I found it unwatchable. But maybe if you watched it without seeing the other stuff, it would seem better.
I don't know. I don't know. He did enough of a recap in the beginning that they're like, here's kind of where we're all at. And, uh, and, you know, I just was, I think at that point, when it came out, I was there for Michael Sarah and Bateman. Yeah.
Yeah. You know, and that was enough, you know, and tambour to because I hadn't seen him in anything in a long time. So he's, uh, yeah, they're all, they're all, they're all amazing. I mean, it's, it's, it's David cross to it is, it's cross at his bat. Like, that's the, the character you always want to see David cross play like the idiot.
Like awkward, you know, he's got a couple of proud falls in that that I would put up with anything on earth. Nice, nice.
He has a fall once where he falls with his foot straight up in the air. So like he lands on his back, but one foot goes up that I, I might have to watch that after the staping actually.
My third one is called soft and quiet, uh, AKA Joe heaven sex.
Ladies and gentlemen, um, soft and quiet is on Netflix.
It is deeply disturbing. We briefly talked about doing it on this show. And then I think I texted Joe was like, hey man, you don't want to watch this if you're depressed.
Um, the just is, it is a elementary school teacher, a, you know, a lovely seeming blonde woman.
She organizes a mixer after class for like like minded women.
And the women get together and they're talking and this is basically the cold open of the thing. They're kind of catching up and talking about school and their kids and everything.
And just a big group of, of ladies, you're not sure what's going on. And then one of them brings in her covered dish.
And she's like, I brought pie and she takes the aluminum off the top of the pie. And there is a giant swastika carved into it.
And I'll tell you folks, that's one way to open a movie. It's going to give me the watch. I'll tell you an opening.
And from there, the women have like a half hour conversation that I really thought was excellently written and acted no matter how it was disturbing, of course, but it seemed like how these conversations would go in a really well written way where they're all talking about their lives, their struggles, you know, like catching up and learning about each other.
And then little by little people start dropping the real reason they're there, which of course is they hate the way society is going.
And you realize that these are, you know, beyond right wing. These are super racist, super hostile, super white power type women.
They do a great job of differentiating them. There's the real hard core one who's like, let's let's, let's fuck them up.
You know, there's a few who are curious about the lifestyle and so forth. And those dynamics all play out in a really interesting way.
Are they have a question are they literal Nazis or is the swastika like a joke because they kind of, you know what I mean, like wink, wink, we're not Nazis, but we are or is it literal like they're like clan people.
Yeah, they're, they're normal, but I think they recognize you can't walk around in a, in a robe and hood now.
So they're dressed in act like normal women, but behind closed doors. It's like, let's talk about what's really going on with the Jews and that kind of stuff.
So at about the halfway point, they all say, hey, let's go get some wine at the store that one of them owns in town.
They all go into the store, they're starting to drink, they're starting to get rowdy, they're starting to feel much more open about talking shit about minorities because they know they've got people who aren't going to judge them for their views here.
And as the store is closing to diverse young women enter the store, and they're looking to buy wine and they're like, get out of here, we're closed.
And the women kind of argue back, they're like, well, by the most expensive bottles, sorry, we just need a bottle, they fight.
And before you know it, things get really, really ugly and they take these women home, they do terrible things to them.
They feel like they need to make it look like a sexual assault so that nobody suspects them.
So they, luckily that is off camera, but you know, it's one of those that just keeps going and going to a place where you're like, alright, I wish I hadn't watched this thing.
It's like that from the jump, it's super disturbing to hear these women talk like you know people in America are talking behind closed doors, but then when it goes this other place of like we need to like damage this woman's vagina.
So people think that she was raped, you know, it's like, alright guys, it's not sure what point you're making now, you know, it's like they take it too far.
It winds up being a really strong and effective movie that I think just goes too far, but it's a movie about going too far.
I'm just saying it wasn't entertaining by any means after a certain point.
Got it.
They're right.
Alright.
Which brings us to the show again.
Yes, also on Netflix, I think you should leave with Tim Robinson.
I think we talked about both of the previous seasons on this show.
We definitely did season two.
I don't know if we reviewed one or not.
Yeah.
You know, I would probably rank them.
One, three, two.
I think three is very quick.
I definitely was left wanting more.
It's very, very funny.
They do a lot less of the really long sketches that I do not think is the strong suit of I think you should leave.
I prefer them when they're brief.
But look, it's the funniest thing in all of television.
There's nothing funnier airing right now.
And there's nothing even close in my opinion than I think you should leave.
And I love this new season.
It's just it's sketches.
The only other thing we got in terms of sketch comedy is SNL.
And I think you should leave is about five million times funnier.
So highly recommend it again.
We can go through the sketches.
But I love it.
I think I love Tim Robinson.
I think as far as a sketch show goes, it's probably the best thing around.
I would rank this season as the worst of the three.
I thought season two had much nothing in this.
There are a few sketches in this that made me laugh out loud.
Nothing in this though made me laugh as hard as like the closing sketch of the first episode of season two where he's in the haunted house and he's asking if the ghost jerk off on the walls or whatever.
Like nothing.
I like this season quite a bit.
There's some standout sketches we can talk about them.
But.
And I don't think this is an epic.
I think it's fair.
And I text you this.
It started.
It's doing too much of the thing I was afraid.
And I went back and rewatch season one and to kind of confirm it.
But like it's doing too much of the thing.
I was afraid it was going to start doing which is like there are just so fewer jokes.
And so much more of just.
I'm going to just say this line in a crazy voice, which is what Tim Highdecker started doing.
Like Tim and Eric was brilliant.
And then like Tim Highdecker did the like show where he was like the action hero guy.
Yeah.
And like there were no jokes.
The whole thing was just like it's funny because they say everything with the wrong inflection.
And it's like that's kind of funny.
But like after a while, I'm like, come on.
And there was a lot of sketches in the season where I was like.
Man, there's just like no ending.
Like I actually wanted a little more out of that.
Like it just it was kind of a bummer.
Like, but.
But.
That said, I think they were leaning into a certain thing.
I don't think they were incapable of doing what I'm saying I missed.
I think they're just embracing a certain quality of the show.
And very much saying like, I want it to be even more surreal and even weirder and even whatever, which is great.
Like good on them.
I think that's awesome.
But this happens with sketch shows like the later kids in the hall stuff to me.
In the original run was nowhere near as funny as the first few seasons.
You know, SNL obviously is not as funny as it once was.
Like, I think it's just the nature of sketch comedy.
Like you get to a point where I was also bummed to by the dearth.
And I'm sure it's not.
I don't think it would be Tim Robinson's fault.
But like the there's no Sam Richardson or Patty Harrison in this.
They're in one sketch each.
My.
Yeah, my assumption would be that those two are just very busy and hot comedy people off doing other stuff.
But yeah, but you know, the sunny guys are always really busy.
But they, you know, they're there when it's time to do the thing.
Like, like, isn't that hard to.
The SNL people are busy.
They do the season.
Like, so that hard to schedule it like where everybody could do it together.
Like again, maybe not.
I guess there were there weren't as many kind of big names in this one, which is fine by me.
I think big cameos is kind of the death of comedy or one of many bricks.
And the death of comedy.
But.
Yeah, Odin Kirk was a real highlight of season two.
He wasn't back either.
I don't know.
But the high -digger sketch was funny this time out.
The high -digger sketch was great.
He looks great by the way.
He lost a lot of weight.
I didn't recognize him at first.
He looked really good.
Um.
My favorite was arguably the Schwartzman sketch about don't talk about your kids at the party anymore.
Like they're very funny.
Yeah.
Really got me.
Really fucking funny.
I got a little list here.
I mean, we can go through.
There aren't that.
They don't want to be in that many sketches, but.
A TV pundit copes with conflict.
Not sure what that would be.
So this doesn't even tell what they all are.
But that's why I remember what that is.
That's the one.
That's the first sketch where he's like the pundit.
But he's like, I will.
Oh, yeah.
If I disagree with you, I will look at my phone.
And it was funny.
Yeah.
No, that is funny.
I mean, even when the sketch has lost me completely, there's something that pops up that makes me laugh.
And he'll make a face that'll make me laugh.
Yeah.
Um.
So that VR shopping spree where he starts like screaming as if he's in total recall when he's
supposed to be doing the shopping on the game show.
Yeah.
That was very funny.
Okay, if he gets out of breath in real life, he can't do it anymore.
Like, yeah, that was funny.
Will Forte getting his ponytail caught under that car and screaming.
That's a sketch that I could have gone for 15 more minutes of.
Forte screaming, I'll watch it forever.
And then when the other ponytail guy shows up, I love that.
I wanted more out of that sketch.
Maybe I got to rewatch it.
It didn't hit me in the way.
I got excited when I saw Forte.
Yeah.
I got I want to rewatch that one.
The next to the Swartzman sketch, the in my opinion, the arguably best sketch is the guy, the, the mime guy.
Where he's like, I'll pay you if I say something on stage.
And it's like the whole audience is the frat guys being like, what are you doing?
Trying to make him pay the money and he's going, why?
Love that.
But I preferred the guy who the old like Filipino man who came in and was trying to tell his dirty stories, but you can remember them.
Now, that's a great example.
That's one of the sketches where I was like, like, I feel like in season one.
Yeah.
The twist in that would have been he's like, I can't remember any of the songs.
Everybody at the party's mad about it.
This sucks.
Right.
And then there would be like this twist where the guy riffs the song.
And all of a sudden every, you know, the people that hated it are yelling like, let him finish it.
It's art.
It's beautiful.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
And it does this weird turning on its ear thing.
And instead in this, it kind of starts to move in that direction.
And then he just goes, now's where I turn my back and you all jack off.
And I'm like, all right, that's kind of funny.
But like, I don't know, like, I feel like there was more meat on the bone here.
Like, you know, there's definitely times where they're favoring the weird to like the, just the progression of the sketch.
And kids and all would do that as well.
It's like, yeah, you're just, you're bored with the format of sketch or something.
So you're just throwing out the craziest thing that could happen.
But that is a problem.
That bothered me a little bit with the Tim Meadows sketch because I was like, great.
We got Tim Meadows.
Yeah.
In a way we rarely see him, which is like explosively angry.
And he was hilarious doing it.
Yeah.
It's one of those photo booths where you take the props and he takes a feather immediately sticks it down his throat.
And you graphically all over the pool.
And then yells at the fact because the photographer they do a straight photo.
It's his daughter's wedding.
And they do the straight photo.
And then he goes, all right, everybody grabs something and do something zany.
One, two, three, he does the puke thing.
And then he gets furious.
And he's like, three seconds isn't long enough to think of something zany.
Which is not only hilarious, but relatable.
I have felt that pressure.
Totally agree.
Because you wind up like bringing your hand up to do something zany.
And you see the flash.
Well, shit.
Now I look stupid.
And I'm not being zany.
But the sketch for some reason last 40 seconds.
It's like it's starting to build.
And I'm like, oh, wow, Tim Meadows is destroying this.
And then it's over.
Yeah.
There are several moments like that where I'm like, all right, I didn't need that.
You know, you got to assume they shot more.
This happens.
This happens with what you said is very accurate and insightful.
Certain comedians get sick of the form.
And then they won't.
It's at the expense of the comedy.
This is the thing Woody Allen did in the, in some of the later movies that he still acted in.
He would have like perfectly written Woody Allen dialogue.
And it wouldn't be funny because he would be delivering his punchline be going.
And he would be stammering.
And you're like, he's doing this because he thinks that delivering the punchline sounds hacky.
Yeah.
And it's too punchy.
So, so now it's not a funny scene because he won't just land the fucking rhythm of this thing.
Yeah.
And kids in the hall are the best example of it where, you know, in the documentary, they talk about that.
We're Mark McKinney's like that fucking dress factory sketch.
God, dammit.
I fucking hated it.
Like, you know, they were doing like French surrealist cinema by the end of that fucking show.
And you're like, what the fuck are you guys doing?
Having done a full rewatch of kids in the hall over the pandemic in order.
Boy, do you start to feel it?
I mean, once one of those sketches kicks off, like when they'll cut to like a big brown ominous building and then go inside.
And there's like a long establishing shot of people trudging into work.
And it's like, guys, I'm glad they gave you a little extra money this year.
But nobody's laughing, you know, always, always in McCullough.
Yeah.
Or Thompson.
Those are always in McCullough or Thompson.
Yeah.
Come on, guys, please.
Like whatever you're satirizing, it might be spot on, but you've done nothing in terms of comedy here.
Anyway, why are we shooting on kids in the hall?
No, we're not.
We're not.
It's just, it's, it's, it's well done.
This, this season though, you know, dude, there was this season again.
It was very funny.
I'm not knocking it.
It had nothing as funny to me as guy in the suit.
I don't want to be here anymore.
You're right.
I don't want to be around any.
You know, like none of the sketches, not none, but very few of them took that crazy twist.
You know, the pants thing in the last season.
Everybody gives, man.
We're just keeps getting more and more ominous.
That this guy has that one wasn't for me.
I don't think they handle the long form stuff too well.
Where, like that one was 15 minutes long on its own.
It was too long.
But, you know, him and I watched the whole season three times, and I still laugh just as hard.
To my issue was long sketches that went nowhere.
But you're right.
The hits were funnier than in three.
So nothing will ever top in my opinion, hot dog car.
I mean, the hot dog car sketch is like, I was like, I'm gonna have a stroke.
I was like laughing so hard.
I really, in season one, love Heideker is that guy who knows more than the rest of the party.
Of the jazz expert.
I, I mean, had to look up which episode it was in so I could rewatch it the other day.
Yeah.
Like that was a jump right to it.
A real specific like just the whole vibe of that.
I was like, this is a accurate to a point of being horrifying and be unbelievably funny.
Yeah.
Colgate comedy.
Nothing.
Nobody.
That means they're all idiots because they don't know stuff.
Even though it's stuff from 50 years before his generation.
And he's 20 years older than all of them.
And the line where the ladies like he's, he forces her to mime the sax playing.
And he's like, whoo.
I wish I could hear what you are playing because you are off the back.
Like it, it is so.
He, it, like I, I know, I know it's perfect because I'm like, I've met this guy.
I wish I could remember the guy that it's so perfectly satirizing.
Yeah.
In my own life.
But I'm like, this is so perfect.
Like the, the fact that he wants to eat the walnuts.
Yeah.
Like everything about it is amazing.
But well, now have you seen Detroiters, Joe?
No, I never, I never caught it when it was odd and I don't think it streams anywhere.
So I've never seen it.
I bet it's on Paramount.
Plus.
I don't know.
But uh, Detroiters is maybe one or two seas.
It's two seasons, but not as funny as I think you should leave.
But the two of them together are amazing.
And the stuff that is funny is like holy shit.
I highly recommend Detroiters to anybody.
Um, is it?
Yeah.
I mean, I'm, I'm, I know it's a sitcom.
I'm assuming it doesn't have the, any of the absurdity.
No, it has a lot of the absurdity.
It's, it's a comedy central sitcom.
So it's, it's more surreal than like a broad city or something like that.
It's more like Stella if you remember Stella.
Okay.
All right.
Um, so they have stories kind of, but really it's just them being loud and obnoxious and weird.
And it's really, really funny.
Right characters.
Um, folks, we highly recommend.
Of course, I think you should leave with Tim Robinson.
We'll be back.
Hog way up.
Love it.
Hope they do more.
Me too.
We will return with a discussion of Mad Max Beyond Thunderdome in honor of the great.
Queen of Rock and Roll Tina Turner.
All right.
Yeah.
And I'm not sure what after that.
But that's what's up next is Thunderdome.
We got Flashman month.
Well, so we'll probably do that before the end of the month.
And I would assume.
And if you don't want to, I'm not putting you on the spot, but I'm assume we'll do Boogeyman.
The new Stephen King.
I'll see that Boogeyman.
Yeah.
I might go actually this weekend to see it.
So I would assume that those would be the next three.
And then we'll see you in Ohio and see it together.
Why are you going to Oh, you just mean midway.
Yeah.
I think we're going to Ohio.
You're the only thing that could get me to go to Ohio.
How about that?
Actually, I was just in Ohio.
They're very nice people.
I don't mean anything by that.
No, just not much to do.
I got to plug my new record coming out June 9th.
The penthouse papers collected readings.
Doing this one with a special thing records and very proud of this.
I had an op -ed column with penthouse for two years.
And we did a studio recording of me reading all the different entries of the columns.
It's funny, but if there's no audience that's stand up, but it is funny.
It's sort of like an audio book, I guess.
But check it out.
It'll be streaming everywhere.
Did all digital platforms on June 9th.
And come to Joey roses.
If you're in New York, Joey roses NYC dot com.
Check us out on Instagram at see you in hell pod.
We often forget to mention.
Thanks to Emily for all your help and hard work.
We also got a Facebook page that I assume is still thriving.
I haven't been on there in a while in a merch page at Etsy.
Folks, we love you.
Thank you for joining us on our Patreon journey.
We will see you next time.
And we will see you in hell.