I'm here for Bet Rivers online casino and sportsbook with poker icon Phil Helmuth.
And now thanks to the excitement of Bet Rivers, I'm also a slots icon.
That's great! And a same -game parlay icon. Cool, cool. A blackjack icon,
a money -line icon, a roulette. Take it from Phil Helmuth. If you love games,
Bet Rivers is the place to play in Bet. Bet Rivers. Games on.
Must be 21 plus in present in West Virginia. Void were prohibited. Terms in conditions apply.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another, no other sportsbook has
an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning, or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
winning hits different here must be 21 plus gambling problem called winning 100
gambler offer not available in all states terms apply see fanatic sports book
app. There's a new podcast app that delivers chilling true crime stories
straight to your mobile device every day they release a new episode that
investigate the gruesome true acts of America's worst serial killers and you
can explore into the minds of psychopaths and murderers to get started find and
download murder minute from the app store or visit murder minute dot com that's
M -U -R -D -E -R -M -I -N -U -T -E dot com to get your daily dose of true crime creepiness delivered
and straight to your mobile device.
It's a good show!
I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell I'll see you in hell I'll see you
and how your favorite podcasts about horror,
flicks and sci -fi, flicks and fantasy films.
Well, I'm Joe D 'Rosa.
That is Pat Walsh over here.
Patty, good to see you, buddy.
Good to see you, Joe.
It's a, what is this?
Tuesday.
It's a Tuesday evening.
The dread all blends together anymore.
Now, Joe, you were saying earlier you've got vagrants,
vandals, people shaking down your balcony.
Yeah, I got people coming onto my balcony, taking things while I sleep, not balcony,
patio, I live on the first floor.
So I called and complained to the building about it and how much you really leave an out there?
Not much.
It's not about the possession, it's about somebody potentially coming in here and murdering
me or something.
Sure.
Sure, sure.
It's the access that freaks me out.
And then, fleeing, making 700 trips with rap cassettes.
Yeah, I'm not worried about the theft
and we're worried about my safety.
I get that.
It's a little freaky.
You know, you got your blinds open
and you're like, is somebody like watching me in here?
Like what's...
Well, Joe, this is America.
Why don't you head over to the Walmart
and buy yourself a fucking shotgun.
gun. The thought did cross my mind. I'm not against it, but I'm not going to do it
just yet. I don't think we're there yet. I don't think so either. I don't think Joe
DeRosin needs a shotgun, but it could get there. Who knows? Yeah. Yeah. It'll be Grand
Torino up in this bitch. Do you see the trailer for the new Grand Torino 2, Grand 2 Reno?
No, the Mule his new movie. I did. It looked pretty cool. Yeah. Looks good. What is in the
92 he's sold still directing still acted. Yeah, yeah, who else is in it? I saw the true preview and look kind of cool
The longest I've seen a preview just let Ruff shoes and summers isn't it
The preview was like one long scene. I haven't seen that as a trailer in like 10 years Rob Reiner
Acoustic yeah, they're like buddy cops, right now robs his son. He's like, why do you insist on smuggling the drugs?
Right, and there's that scene of Rob Reiner running from a building that's exploding
Yeah, which looked pretty sweet. Yeah. Yeah. Well, I have a jaoli. He's a jaoli man, but
It was fun to watch him run in slow -mo. Look, it's two different people him him and Pacino are the ones where it's like
Rob Reiner now and Rob Reiner on in the 70s. It's two different human beings. Yeah, and same with Pacino. He's another one. I
liked
But when Eastwood goes, you're as stubborn as, and then turns and looks at the camera and
he goes, a mu, and then the title of the mu will fill the screen.
I thought that was pretty sweet.
Right.
My favorite part is when he accidentally shits all the drugs out of his ass in front of
the cops due to his irregularity, really more movie about adult diapers.
What? Well, it depends. What is the, um, there was a little bonus joke. What? Oh, it
depends. I didn't even get it. Sorry. I thought I felt I needed to explain it, but then hopefully
some of our listeners are brighter than Joe. Oh, he's, he doesn't realize he's a mule. No, he does.
The trailer starts. He opens his trunk and he's like, what's this cocaine doing in my trunk? No,
he's opening his trunk because the fucking cop is like, what do you got there? He looks baffled by
the cocaine. I was in it. No, I think he's looking at it like, I think some maybe he
think something spilled or okay, you know, one of those things. I was on the on the walk
in to the movie. So I it wasn't watching it very carefully. I was seeing a star is born
which I'm saving for the live show. Oh, okay. Fair enough. All right. I'm going to supporting
role. Who do you think plays Lady Gaga's dad? Do you know the answer? Dave Chappelle, isn't
it. You think Dave Chappelle plays Lady Gaga's dad? He's the only other person I know that's
in the movie. But you know, that would be possible. It's a it's a it's a old boy twist at the
end. Right. No. It's somebody important to your life. I'll give you three guesses. Jonathan
I'm distracted. Pat is, he came in with a diet raspberry snapple, mixed it into a glass
with iced tea, not a bit of ice, or it with vodka, I mean, but vodka and that in the
glass, not a bit of ice, just warm, then bites off two ends of a twizzler and starts using
that as a straw. And now he's dipping the twizzler and playing with it like a, I'm stirring
it like a southern judge who usually a definition. I mean, look, you should keep your
vodka in the freezer. It's where vodka goes. I didn't even know I'd vodka in there.
I got to be honest. And that was purchased. Apple is cold. So it balances out.
Who plays? The answer is Andrew Dysclay. Andrew Dysclay plays the dad plays Lady Gaga's father.
How was he important in my life? Excuse me? Because I'm a comic. You mean you talk
Talk all the time about Andrew Dysclin.
I'm a fan.
You seem to have been a key influence on your whole vibe.
I'm a fan, a relentless misogynist.
I'm a fan, I wouldn't say he's been important in my life.
All right.
You know, how is he?
He's a good actor.
Excellent.
And how does he play it?
Like what's the character?
We'll talk about it in the live show.
Oh, okay.
That's right.
I want to crack it up.
Well then stop bringing it up.
All right.
I have an announcement to make.
Yeah.
I mean, this decision today, I feel great about it.
I'm done with single cam sitcoms, I'm done.
I respect the hell out of that, they're not funny.
I'm done.
I can't take it anymore.
I tried to watch one today, it was my first dip back in the pool in a while, and it's
just these absurd characters that are just copied off of the last show's absurd characters.
Nobody is believable, they've become a parody of themselves, they're terrible.
What was the show?
I don't want to say.
Okay, because there are people that I really respect on the show, but it wasn't camping.
I watched the pilot of camping.
Holy Christ.
I don't know.
I don't know if we're counting that as a comedy.
There wasn't a joke to be had, but it was a wild time, man.
If that thing could get made, you know, good luck to everybody.
You can do it.
It's insane.
I just, Julia Lewis decides to go fully frontally nude for the first time in our entire career,
unless I'm mistaken, in camping, in front of a child.
Yeah, it's very bizarre scene.
The whole, the thing had no plot.
It is six people show up to go camping.
That's, and it goes on for a half hour.
Well, apparently something goes wrong,
which sounds like they're just ripping off a search party.
Shouldn't that something have gone wrong in the pilot?
Shouldn't there be an incident, some incident?
If you're gonna tell a story,
do people tell stories anymore? No, no. People think that, you know, look, there was one person,
not one, but there was one of a few people that was good at capturing real life situations on
camera. It was John Casavetes. Sure. And there's been many more. You're not John Casavetes. No,
stop it. You don't know how to make Peter Falk at a dining room table eating spaghetti interesting.
John Casavetti's did, these people all think they're Casavetti's.
It's annoying.
They got Jennifer Garner along with Ann Hathaway are two actresses who, the public, fairly
or unfairly, perceive as nags, you know, shrill annoying women.
I've always kind of liked them both had no real issue with them.
They're not my favorite actresses on the planet, but I think they get the job done.
they've got her playing like the extreme version of how everyone sees her as
this uptight anal fussy person and all she does throughout the entire pilot
is say like almost like Bob Sagitt used to do on full house like plan out well
know at eight ten we've got to make our other that's all she does the whole show
and they're on a camping trip so it's like no I've scheduled us in to swim
them tomorrow. Now it's not swimming time. Then they released this big statement. The
show's only getting bad reviews says the entire creative team of camping because they all
started it. Brett Gellman, but then if you click on the article, they all say the all the
critics are reviewing it negatively because they're misogynistic. And they said, how come
the sopranos can have an unlikeable lead character, but this show can't. These sopranos
is one of the most densely plotted beautifully written shows in the history of
American television. For my opinion the best. Here's the thing, you can't compare
camping to that. There are different people, the characters are nowhere near as
developed or layered and to throw out misogyny because they didn't like your show
is kind of nuts. Everybody loves fucking killing Eve. That was a very
unlikable woman. She was a fucking assassin. Everybody likes the one with Pam
What's your name from Louie? It's a great show better things. Yeah, everybody likes that show. Hey, I'll give you I'll give you a
feminist vehicle
Yeah, purposefully feminist vehicle with
Riddled with complicated women nine to five one of the great movies of all time. Sure. I love every minute of it
You know why cuz the
Mess messy women in that movie aren't fucking annoying number one. Yes, and number two. It's well written
There are, by the way, annoying men characters too.
Tony soprano was not annoying.
You are breaking bad, Walter White was not annoying.
He was a despicable character,
but it wasn't like somebody you couldn't spend time with each week
and there's a key difference there.
I'm not even saying you can't do a movie about annoying people
or a show about annoying people,
but let's not pretend it's misogyny
that your show, which has no story to tell yet,
let's say, although I can't do annoying characters.
I can't like I could never do those any Adam Sandler movie where he does a voice
I can't do you mean most of them like little Nicky and the water boy like those ones
I'm like I can't do this. It's it's driving me fucking crazy
If Seinfeld was just George, it would be a shitty show that's exactly right
And you could argue that curb your enthusiasm is sort of that but curb your enthusiasm is
It's fucking hilarious and it's got plot and it's got twist and turns and that's really just the difference
I mean there there's no comparison and I find it
It's just kind of shitty to throw out a term like misogynistic when you just it's just that people don't like your show
There's also several annoying male characters and female characters the Juliet Louis when my favorite actresses of all time
She's there for five seconds as the girlfriend of another guy on the camping trip. She strips to
You know full frontal nudity in front of a ten -year -old boy
But the extremely anal retentive mom doesn't cover his eyes
Right even though she's trying to micromanage this trip down to the wire
The kid holds a BB gun. She about has a heart attack
But there's a woman full -frontally naked two feet in front of him. There's no
Move to like shield him from it. I don't know what I'm watching. There's no consistency of the characters
beat to beat. It's a bad show. It just, it just drives me. I haven't seen the entire pilot,
but as I said on the last episode, I saw several long sequences from it on YouTube because they
kept playing them before every video. I saw enough to be like, I mean, if this is what you're trying
to get me on the hook with, yeah, I'm not going to like the show. I don't know, there's better shows.
everything sucks yeah let's before we shit on more things let's get on with the show and at the
same time on with the yeah yeah yeah hot a Joe right very good did you like you ought to know when
it came out no you can't admit to yourself that you liked it at least for a period of time I made
me liked it the first time I heard it. It's a killer song. It's, you know, it's, yeah,
it's a very well written, there's a lot of well written songs out there that I don't like.
It's not my style of song. We're in about Dave Collier.
So from four hours. My friend said he asked Dave Collier if that was the case and he said,
Dave Collier went, oh, come on, what the fuck, man? And walked away. Very angry.
Yeah, it's about him. Well, I also think he's just tired of being asked, is that about you?
I don't think your friend should have asked them that.
I'd pairing, Kool -A and Mourna, and then Ryan Reynolds after that.
I love Mourna said as a person, and some of her tunes I like, but you know, that one, that's okay.
I mean, I don't like the love better than the thank you, India.
Thank you, Terry.
She's one of those singers I don't hate any of the songs.
I don't love any of the songs.
I don't like any of her songs except you wouldn't.
If they come on, I'm not upset, but I never put it on.
I like many more Cheryl Crowe songs than I'd like to learn it's more so Christ anything but down
It's a great song. Crowe's got that first record and that's it for me
Once she lost the flannel shirts and the boozy broad vibe. I didn't care anymore. I didn't like how she came back on that second
I'm all dialed up. I like I didn't care for anything but down. I like her cover of first cut as the deepest and I like
Uh, leave in Las Vegas.
I like strong enough to be my man or whatever the hell that is.
Um, I'll tell you who I do.
Like, I like quite a few of us are like, should I have twain?
Got no beef with twain.
I always get excited at a wedding.
I always goose me up.
That won't.
Yeah.
Not my favorite.
I like her all right.
Um, how do we get on these people?
What the hell are you even talking about?
You sang.
Oh, a land of sports.
Yeah.
And not my, not my thing.
The Lil' affair scene, you know, Paul Nicole,
not really in for me.
Jewel, I liked a couple of cuts,
but you hear them now, they sound ridiculous.
You took your coat off and stood in the rain.
You're always crazy like that.
Really, really, Jewel?
That crazy?
That's the craziest thing you can think of as a songwriter.
She's another one I liked because she was like this
folksy mountain woman and then she came back
and she was all fucking plastered up with makeup
up and doing like dance music and shit and I was like what are you doing yeah into a
shun I was like what are you doing your intuition that song sucked and then remember when
uh Tegan and Sarah did that they well they didn't like they didn't doll it up but they
came back with a dance record. Tegan and Sarah you know the the con uh if it was you and
and then so jealous are three excellent albums.
They made three great, nearly perfect pop albums,
and then they just went to pop.
They lost kind of the kick to it.
Well, they were like a breeders kind of thing,
and then all of a sudden they were like a dance group
with no band and just, and I liked that dance music,
but it wasn't for me.
Either Tegan Orserra came to my birthday party once,
and I talked to her and she was very nice.
Maybe I believe the same party as Julia Lewis.
It was a kind of party where I really seemed like a mover and shaker even though I didn't know any of the celebrities that were at my house
Look, I've said it for years. You've always been a suck up in a kiss ass and a brown noser
And I'm not surprised for a minute that some
Famous people just happened to show up at your birthday party. Hey, sorry, or that you'd pretend that you didn't know they were coming
Or that you had paid them to be there
Small thing. I'm a Scientologist so they're all in my roll of decks
actually from the day Julia Lewis came to my house I started getting a lot of
Scientology literature I get one like every other day. She is Scientologist? Yeah
yeah we're all fuck her then. Oh hey hey what do you want me to fucking sugar
code it? It's a nice lady. Well I can't say fuck her because I still I still I
can't stop supporting Tom Cruise. I think I support Tom Cruise the actor I don't
even want to know what's going on with Tom Cruise the man. I feel like it's not
good. Tell me you wouldn't light up if he walked in this room right now. Oh, of course.
Hey guys, you want to get a beer? Yes. You know, whatever you'd say.
You're gonna try and drink beer because, you know, you only eat seeds or whatever you
It has to do for this fucking weird diet, but yeah.
I'm gonna start, by the way, today we're reviewing Apostle, which is new to Netflix.
Yeah, we've got much to say about it, but we'll get into it.
and I will be getting into a lengthy talk about the apostles and bringing in some Bible study,
another religious elements that I think this podcast is lacking. Great. But I'll wait until
we get to the Bible. Get to the movie for that. Excellent. I watched, you know what I had not seen
since I was maybe 15 years old. You're dick. Come on Joe. What? It's a movie that
As gotten this like cult status it played in the cemetery here in L .A. recently, which is usually like a pretty big movie
People talk about it non -stop. You see memes from it all the time the movie is called Empire Records
Oof
Now I worked in a record store when that came out. Yeah, which is why it was like doubly insulting right
I loved teen movies never more than when I was about 15 years old. I was like this is awesome. It's exciting. Let me check this thing out. I rents it and I was like, that fucking sucked. Talk about no story. I mean like and it's not like no story in a days to confuse way where like you like the people characters were all pretty repellent. There wasn't a laugh to be had. There wasn't any good romance or anything. I always saw Empire Record as the poor man's mystic pizza.
sure and I wish all mystic pizza is the poor man steel magnolias well
that's very true yeah you're twice removed by the time you get to empire
records yeah I thought maybe I was too young sometimes you rewatch something
and you're like oh I get all this now the movie fucking sucks it is a it was
critically panned but it's just gotten this new life where everyone loves it
maybe it was on HBO all the time back in the day or something I don't know how
it happened, but y 'all are out of your goddamn mind. The movie sucks. The only good thing about it
is it unleashed on the world a fiery hot single by the Jim Blossoms called Till I Hear It From You.
God damn it. Till I hear it from you. Why do you, why? Oh no. Great song. Yeah, it's like a kind of
Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang, Gang
It is. Anyway, it's like an episode of MTV's next, like the level of story and plot they're giving you.
Well, speaking of movies, we haven't seen this. We're 15. I rewatched Stephen King and George A.
Romero's The Dark Half. So I'm pretty recently. Sorry, Timothy Hutton.
As a kid, I didn't enjoy it much. On the rewatch, I loved it. It went right up there with some of my
more favorite Stephen King adaptations. I thought Hutton was awesome in it. I
loved him in the dual role. I thought Romero did a really nice job directing
it. It was right at the tail end of when movies still had that grainy texture
to them and and still had a natural darkness to them. I just really enjoyed the
movie. I really had a lot of fun watching it and it's one that I would
actually purchase for my collection. I tell you, I did purchase it as one of those Amazon
has a lot of get eight movies on one disc kind of deals, you know, and I have quite a few
of those kind of a bunch of old junky movies in one. I didn't do much for me, dark half
and I watched it pretty recently. I didn't think anything was scary about it. It was kind
of boring. I liked him with the Hutton as a rule. Well, mine was a second watch and that's
when I really liked it.
And I, the second, well, I was less familiar
with Stephen King at that age.
So on this second watch, I started to pick up more
on the Stephen King themes, like the Hutton character,
the dark side, I forget the character's name,
like the George Wood at Straight,
or whatever his name is, like the evil writer.
George Straight is a country singer.
I know, I was just, you know, doing my best.
But the, you know, he's kind of like my best.
Wasn't good enough.
He's kind of like the bad guy in the road virus
goes head north, which is one of my favorite
Stephen King stories, you know?
Stephen King always writes those sort of like
greaser, like evil, faunzy characters.
Right.
And I just really enjoyed it.
And then when I read about it online and read
that King wrote it about, it was basically an auto,
It was a it was a fictional take on an autobiographical thing that happened to him which is when he got found out to be Richard Bachman
Yeah, and then he wrote this story and then so then when you watch the movie and the wife is like
You're gonna start drinking you're gonna do you know, and he's like I'm not an alcoholic and then you read about Kings intervention
Right to read that story. No
He said you know the family and friends were all gathered and his wife came down with a shoe box of shit
She collected from his office
just, you know, because he was like, I'm not, I'm fine.
And dumped it on the floor in front of everybody.
And he said it was beer cans, joints at marijuana,
and assortment of pills.
He names all the pills.
Several glass vials of cocaine
and then coax boons caked in blood and snot.
And that's when he got sober.
Okay.
So when you know those things about King personally,
it puts a kind of new cool twist on the movie.
What was the Bachman story like how do you get well the Bachman books were I know what they were dinner right was one of them
The Bachman books were you know they were they were stories he wrote that were were more cynical and and darker
Then the average Stephen King stuff
Mm -hmm. So and then like he'll still once in a while put out like a Bachman book and say like you know
He writes like a fake thing where it's like this was a lost menu script after he died and oh he said got found out. I thought it was like some
Secret or something it was he was putting the books out under a pen name
I read the bottom and and and a kid in a bookstore figured it out in wrote to him
Yeah, and he was like yeah, dude expose it. I don't care
He's like the jigs up and then he said once it became known that it was him all the books like quadrupled and saved
How did the kid figure it out?
Something about or maybe it was the kid at the publishing something about like
Where they were coming from and something was I forget to be honest
I can't even remember, but he figured it out.
I gave a rewatch, I've been going through
the Eddie Murphy back catalog,
and some David Allen Greer catalog because I like the man.
Which led me to boomerang.
I had not seen boomerang in 20 years.
I consider it lesser Eddie Murphy,
and yet it's a very good romantic comedy.
It's not super funny.
But I think it is a good romantic comedy.
There are some scenes in it that are outrageously outdated,
that could not air today.
He keeps turning off the lights when he's trying to fuck the old lady,
Eartha Kit, who actually looks kind of hot, I think, in the movie.
But he's like, let's turn more lights off in here.
I always found those kind of jokes dark and gross,
where it's like how ugly a woman is.
They were doing them as recently as dumb in number two,
where there was like 800 jugs about how ugly Kathleen Turner was.
Yeah, I don't get that.
I never like it.
It doesn't feel good to me.
But on the whole, boomerang is good.
Some funny, you know, you can't get much better romantic comedy friends than David Alangrier
and Martin Lawrence.
They play off each other well.
Robin Givens, I was unaware.
Was that beautiful?
I am striking.
I mean, just unbelievable.
She's half naked, half the movie was incredible looking woman.
and Halle Berry as a like a 25 year old woman. A lot of entertainment. Soundtrack, of course,
includes End of the Road by Boys to Men. One of the greatest songs ever written.
And then the true laughs come from those scenes where he's doing the perfume commercials
that like old purve dude. Do you remember those? With Grace Jones? I saw the movie when it first
went to video and I didn't like it because I was too young to get it and I never really revisited it.
I bet you like it now he's kind of a playboy who can't be tied down and then a woman kind of gives him what he's been given women. It's kind of like the
What's that song get you by weezer? I just player gets played. I just remember being so painfully disappointed as an Eddie Murphy fan. Yeah
I get that that because that was I remember him going in our on our sitting on like denouncing
Everything he had done for the last like 15 years. Yeah
And like saying like raw like he was just an ego maniac and it's like okay, dude
Maybe you were but the come on dude. Yeah, it's fucking hilarious. Yeah, so I was just really bummed out with this like new Eddie Murphy
Yeah, well after boomerang he just made lots of shit for years. Not a professor was a rare
Blind bright spot
Grace Jones plays stron J like a model who walks around with her ass hanging out all the time
Strong J. Strong J. Yeah, that's that's rough. They had some real outrageous hit in this movie
There's this old bald like perv dude who is like his commercial director and so he'll show Eddie Murphy stuff
And there's like women deep -throating bananas and stuff and he's like just take out the banana man
You know that's too nasty. You know that's too nice. That's all that's all really funny
Then at the end he doesn't have the time to preview it and the guy shows it and it is strong J and
And she spreads her legs and basically gives birth to the giant bottle of perfume and pulls
it graphically out of her self.
And then the tagline says,
Strong J, it stinks so good.
And folks, this was a mainstream romantic comedy that made like a hundred million dollars.
I like that.
I almost fell out of my chair.
I couldn't.
Not from laughing.
I was just shocked.
That's a funny joke. The movie was nuts. I mean it the the swings in tone. It was kind of like coming to America
Where like the soul glow comes in and you're like well, I guess we're just doing like a sketch in the middle of the movie
Yeah, yeah, but these sketches were not a successful. They were certainly funny
I watched I did watch the blacksmith in the devil which I talked about last week. I think
Man
Well, maybe it's my fault. It's a movie from Spain. It's a very dark fairy tale,
essentially. It is an old fairy tale about a blacksmith who outwits the devil.
You're big into dark fairy tales lately. Yeah, I like that kind of stuff. And so,
this is a film version of it. It's a sort of a retelling of it, but it still takes
place in the sort of dark, not dark ages, but, you know, the 1600s, whatever it is. Sure.
And it's, it starts so cool and it's so well shot and it's so moody and atmospheric and you feel like you're watching this like almost like this, you know, children's movie like like the old dark Disney movies or something, you know.
And then it just gets cheesy, man, it gets really, really cheesy which might be my fault because I chose to watch it with the English dub.
instead of reading the subtitles.
Everything seems cheesy with Dubs.
Because that was the way they played the trailer on Netflix.
So I thought, well, usually they'll play it
with the subtitles, maybe this is the way to watch it.
So I watched it that way.
And some of the performances were just,
they just sounded crazy.
Like, how have they not gotten better
at dubbing techniques by now?
I don't care that it doesn't match the lips.
but how is somebody not able to direct this properly and be like this sounds
ridiculous when you put it to the to the picture tone your performance down
right so all in all I'd give it a see you could have switched at any point
to the subtown it was I was already in Clancy Brown does one of the voices and I
really love Clancy Brown I liked hearing his voice and I didn't want to stop
quite frankly. And yet you're highly critical of his performance. Not his. No, he was fine.
He was fine. It was mainly the guy that played the devil that that kind of ruined it. It was
so ridiculously over the top. I think Clancy Brown reads a couple audiobooks. Do you have Stephen
King's? Pretty sure he does. What's his name does? Like all of them. Will Patton. Yeah, he does one.
Will Patton. I mean, if you ever want to your audiobook to sound like a suicide note. I know.
Christ almighty. The guy is just doesn't bring a lot of heat. I think he's great at it, but he's just he sounds so sick. Yeah, he does.
I watched also is a four year consideration title this year. It's on Netflix now, but it's got enough theatrical release. It's called private life.
It's from Tamara Jenkins who directed slums of Beverly Hills, which I really enjoy always have.
of starring a young David Crumholz in his underwear.
I love slums at Beverly Hills.
And a gorgeous Marissa Tomay.
Then years later she directed Savages.
Great movie.
Which was a great movie with Laura Lennie
and Phil Seymour Hoffs.
Now this picture has Catherine Hahn
who I always love in Paul Giamati.
And what's it called?
Private life.
Oh, is this the one where they're trying to have the baby?
Yeah.
Oh, I want to watch this.
It's two hours plus of a couple of trying and failing to have a baby
You know it's in an age where like all HBO shows are this like kind of
Kind of well to do New York people having their little problems. It just didn't feel particularly novel to me. It felt very
Depressing a I mean any couple trying to have a baby for over years is going to be a depressing story regardless and
And it just kind of was and they're like,
where we ever gonna have sex again,
a lot of those conversations.
It felt very real and it was very well -acted.
I just kind of was like,
do I wanna watch a married couple suffer for two hours?
Again, like...
Well, and I'll say this,
the ghastly amount of money,
it cost a couple to go through fertility procedures
and all these things.
Yeah.
for them to not at that point adopt and instead be so fucking self -important that they think they
have to bore the baby themselves and not help out a baby that needs a fucking family. I just think
it is so self -important and self -centered and stupid and outdated. The option doesn't even come up in
the movie, but like, you know, each couple, to each couple their own, people have very
strong beliefs about childbirth and having a baby and I get that.
This movie, I don't, has brings up some of the debates, but you know, she's like, I don't
want to have a surrogate, I want to do it myself and all that.
And what's, what's important to you and what is your kid and what isn't your kid and all
the stuff is kind of baked into the movie, but I mean, I don't need a movie to be a fun
watch, but it was kind of not worth the depression. And it's, I think the third movie I've seen
where Katherine Han walks around wearing a t -shirt and no pants or underwear when he's a
pooh style, which makes me wonder if it's like in her contract. She did it in that really great
movie called Afternoon Delight, which I loved, and she did it on her show. I love Dick. You know,
It's a strange look.
I don't like it for a, it looks better on a woman than a man, but...
Fair enough.
Interesting.
Anyway, they basically, they asked their niece to, if she wants to do it for them, and
they bring in this kind of wacky niece character.
It's got kind of that Woody Allen thing of like every character talks in these hyperliterate
voices, and I tend to not like that, because it doesn't feel real to me.
It sounds like an abominable film, to be honest.
It's not abominable, it's better than I'm making it sound.
It's just kind of like, I don't know.
I felt as if I'd seen it before.
And it seemed like something where,
if a couple's actually going through that,
why do they want to watch it?
If you're not living this terrible life,
why would you want to watch it?
It's almost like a documentary.
And that's an adopted child.
Why would I want to watch it?
Yeah, sure.
Fuck everything.
I agree.
GMOD is great.
Han is great.
You know, it's certainly well done.
It's just not something you need to rush out and see all right close in this out here
Finally saw what we doing the shadows
Like I don't know why I took me forever to watch this movie
But I finally watched it. I loved it. I was scream laughing from front to back
Jermaine what's his face from part of the Concord delivers on on every front as usual
The writer director who also stars in the movie is the main vampire delivers on all fronts
Because everybody's great.
It's such a funny take on that sort of office docus style kind of thing.
They now every fun, scary cliche about vampires.
It's awesome.
I just loved it.
I thought it was great.
I should rewatch.
I remember being in a terrible mood when I saw it and thinking it was amusing but not seeing
what everybody else sees.
They're making it into a show now for FX.
Max, the great Matt Berry.
Yes, which I'm extremely excited about.
That's why I watched it finally.
Yeah.
That Berry's not in the movie, is it?
No, but I believe he's probably gonna play
the Jermaine Clement role.
Like I've done, imagine Matt Berry is playing
the guy with the long hair and the mustache.
I thought Clement was in it, but maybe he's not.
Is in the show?
Yeah.
I don't think he's in the show.
Okay.
I think it's a different cast.
Yeah, sure.
All right, I can't imagine Matt Berry's not playing
like the like womanizing.
Yeah.
Like that's the guy he always plays. I know
One of my comedy heroes Mr. Tom Sharpling is writing on the staff really that's very good
Yeah, and I think it's Paul Sims who does Atlanta, which is an exceptionally great
Show and I'm sure it'll be awesome. Maybe Clement is in it. I thought it was a new cast
But I look forward to seeing I even think he might be involved in the writing of it
I was I was floated that as like hey, would you be interested in this?
And I thought Clement was like in the room
Maybe he's just E .P .ing.
Yeah, maybe so.
Pat, do you got time for a little scary stuff
before we get into today's film?
I'd love it.
All right, folks, fans of...
Oh, you know what?
I'm going to save this.
Because I needed one more, I won't even say what it was
and why I want to save it.
But I'm going to save it for the live show.
Yeah, folks, the live shows have already taken place, and I'm sure there'll be a lot of discussion on them because we got a lot of a lot of heat coming.
You're going to want to get these live shows. If you can't be there, you're going to want to listen to them.
We've got some nice surprises for you.
I guess we can get into our movie for today. We're at 37 minutes. I mean, that's sure.
No, no, no screaming and news cycles.
I don't have one for today. Let me just quickly revisit
Bloody disgusting and see if anything interesting has popped up since I last checked
Read in some Halloween reviews that are comparing it unfavorably to H2O
Meaning H2O was better or meaning they're just like it's it's like wiping away all these movies including H2O
Like it's so much better than them, but it's giving you what H2O gave you better
it's doing a better version of H2O.
It's doing a worse version of H2O.
Is what I read today on like the onion.
I absolutely love H2O.
Yeah.
I think it's a tremendous horror movie.
And from trailer one of this thing,
I said, it's just H2O again.
Right.
It's Jamie Lee Curtis has to face off against Michael Myers.
Yeah.
Which is why they made H2O.
Right.
And then, you know, well, actually, yeah.
This is good for the news 24 -hour news psycho screaming in.
Joe and I are going to see it either Thursday night or Saturday day or Friday night
But I I'm certainly pumped to see it, but this review was not inspiring. I've seen some good some bad
Uh, I don't think I've mentioned this yet, but this is good for our new psycho today
Blum house, mm -hmm has already announced
That they're working on sequels
They're announcing this publicly. What is wrong with everybody? So now I'm gonna wait a week
It's not even out yet.
So now I'm going into this movie knowing number one,
Michael Myers definitely is not dead at the end
no matter what they show me,
which I understand that that's sort of an assumption,
but that's lame, especially when you're saying
we're trying to write the wrongs of the franchise.
I agree.
So that's number one, number two.
So now you're gonna make a bunch of sequels
to this sequel that was made to erase all the other sequels.
Right. It doesn't make any fucking sense. Right. They can't leave anything alone.
Just leave it alone. Move on to the next franchise.
God damn it. It drives me fucking crazy. Make the nightmare on Elm Street prequel if you're this
fucking franchise happy. Make another fucking Texas chainsaw massacre that's worth watching.
Make the fucking hell razor remake that everybody keeps talking about that's not getting made for
whatever reason. But for fuck's sake, man, how many fucking times are we going to go down
this Michael Myers road? See now you're bringing in a lot more negative energy into this
picture than I have realized. I hope that I hate this thing because I want to be on fire
on Saturday. I mean, I'm going to tell you one key word I've seen in every review. Humor
Pat?
No, not to say things like that when I have a glass in my hand.
But is an L .O. Cool J doing his erotic wraps, isn't that also in H2O?
No.
There are two scenes in H2O where L .O. Cool J is a security guard who wants to be a writer
an erotic writer.
Yeah.
And he's reading his erotic stories to his wife over the phone and she's yelling at him
that he's an idiot.
That's a shitty bit in that movie.
It's okay. It's it's it's it happens twice right and then
It's it's like a brief moment of comic relief, and it's the only comic relief in the fucking movie, right?
You know, it's what was a solid movie and I'm sorry. I
I like to age to all but yeah, we should wait. I'll save it for Saturday. Anyway, that's our news psycho
Today's movie is a possible pad. If you could, if you could give the folks at home a synopsis
while I refill my beverage. I'll vamp. Which, which is Halloween themed, by the way.
I mean, look, I'm bad when watching movies that knowing what time period it is. I'm bad
it knowing where they're at. So let me bring up the wiki here. Apostle, first off it's by the guy
who made the raid and the raid too. Joe has not seen these films. They're two of the best action
movies of recent years. They're absolutely incredible. And he brings some of that style to this like
period piece, which works awesomely. It works so much better than like Sherlock Holmes or something
like that. I really loved how they brought kind of modern fighting in without it
feeling like a fucking night's tale or something like some anachronistic type
deal. The the basic premise is it's 1905 this dude played by Dan Stevens who's
the guy from the guest which I loved travels to a remote island to rescue his
beloved sister who has been kidnapped by a mysterious cult that's demanding
ransom for her return. He learns basically that these people are very sinister. There's
an elements of torture. There's kind of a lead guy who becomes his kind of main adversary.
Subplot where he knows about a young couple who's had sex and maybe a baby on the way
that factors in pretty heavily. Which they're not supposed to be doing is they're breaking
all the cult breaking the cult codes. But essentially, you know, this is our second movie
in as many weeks about a man rescuing a beloved woman from a cult. Mandy was the wife.
This picture it's his sister, um, he might be banging. Man's got a strong love for his.
He's like, well, it was like, whenever there was a dark moment, you made it beautiful.
I don't know, talks to their sister like that.
It also seemed to me so much earlier than 1905, didn't it?
Or was that just like the village?
I agree.
I thought we were back in the fucking Christmas carol
or something at least.
I was shocked by 1905, I saw that just now.
But movies right around the corner for Christ's sake.
It looked like it was in like the Crucible days,
kind of like the 17th, but anyway, he goes in,
And he tries to infiltrate this cult.
There's all manner of spooky shit.
The big sort of centerpiece is this scene where the boy who's fucked the bad guy's daughter
is tortured and they drill into his head.
I wouldn't say that's the centerpiece of the movie.
Everything I read about it was like there's a torture scene that many will not be able to
take.
So I was waiting for that with Bated Breath.
It didn't gross me out as much as I expected it to.
It wasn't as bad as the bone tomahawk cut a man and crouched in half by his dick.
It certainly wasn't.
But it was, it was bad, but it was a great scene.
It was intense and then when they cut to the cave, didn't head, you know,
that's a pretty great shock shot.
Yeah, then they put the, they do it to enlighten him and in the giant hole in his skull,
the bloody hole, the guy puts like a piece of paper that represents enlightenment
right inside of his head. It's pretty dark stuff. I loved the way this movie was
shot. It felt both period and new, which is very tricky to do. Like I said, and
not make it feel like everyone loves a night's tale. I remember it being kind of
like fine, but I don't like when people in the old times are talking like the
present day and I hate that. This felt like a really good mix of modern filming
technology, but it didn't feel like the Sherlock Holmes or every punches and slow
all that shit, I despise both Sherlock Holmes movies.
Now they're making it third, by the way.
All right, of course they are.
This was an awesome start to finish.
When they break out the true fight scenes
like between Dan Stevens, our lead guy,
and the father, that fight scene was just fucking awesome.
When they were going at it.
Wait, which fight scene?
The dad, the guy who drills the head.
Right.
And our lead guy had this big like.
Oh, like at the climax of the movie?
Yeah, that's a great fight.
Just one of the best fight scenes I've seen between that guy and the kid who they drill into his head is great
Yes, for sure, you know the shot when they so they're putting his head in a vice and I was like all right
I know this isn't gonna be more traumatic than the casino scene where the guys eyeball pops out of his head right
But what they did was so awesome they give you the inside the kids head point of view and you see the blood shot
Fill up his eyeball that's great shot was awesome
And you also you're in the eyes and then you see the eyes blood shot.
I've never seen that shot before and I loved it.
And you also hear the audio muffled as the vice right clamps his ears shut.
Right. Pretty great.
They had done it.
That's seen, especially in a theater in Kaplan when they shoots the loan in the ear
and the sound mix goes all weird.
Great. I mean, I've seen I've seen a version of that and loved it.
But that eyeball thing, it's hard to do something new in an action movie or a horror movie.
and this movie was doing a lot of kind of cool fresh new shit without being super flashy about it.
The story was cool. There was nothing really corny about it. Dan Stevens maybe miscast. He
wasn't like awesome in it. He's the main guy. Yeah. I thought he was great. I liked him, but you know,
look, I bought him as a young Harrison Ford type. I bought him as a guy that like
like, was almost psychotically determined, had been through some shit and was, you know,
grizzled and was ready to go the full nine yards.
I, but I liked them in that.
I thought it was good.
And I really liked Martin Sheen or excuse me, Michael Sheen, as the, Michael Sheen was fucking
great.
Yeah.
As the sort of brother Malcolm the, the, the profit, uh, cult leader, super intense, super creepy.
Michael Sheen is always great.
I'm a big fan.
I met him once.
you know. Why is he still dating Sarah Solomon? That's when I met him. I did a show at Sarah
and he was there and I did it. It was it was the comedy jam and I covered Spirit of Radio by Rush.
Okay. And he came up to me afterwards and he was like, oh mate, I love Rush, a great job mate.
Oh man, I was telling Sarah you got to hear this reggae bit that's about to come up like he was very
excited about the rush cover. Very nice. Yeah, it was very cool. Nice man. It all feels sort of like,
Okay, this is a weird cult type stuff, but very grounded in reality until they bring up the witch
And when I saw the witch I realized and this is gonna be controversial this movie is what I
Was led to believe the witch would be which was exciting awesome interesting intense
It was it felt similar, but I loved it so much more than the witch. I know you loved the witch, but well, they're different types of movies. They are
the witch
in this movie is so disturbing when they are feeding
or the blood and she starts sucking on it like a baby on a nipple
or whatever like eating the body parts through a tube.
Yeah.
That was all really fucking weird and like cool everything
with the witch right up to the end when you realize
that like he is now one of these like grass people
and like he's got witch blood now and stuff.
Well such a cool tank on a witch by the way
because the actual Wicken religion,
you know, the real Wicken religion,
not the movie fairy tale version of it,
is all based on the appreciation and worship of nature.
It's, you know, so at the end of the witch,
they kind of did this too,
but I like that they actually created a witch
who was both scary and pure at the same time.
She wasn't evil.
She was scary because they were malnourishing her
and abusing her powers through her film
for the benefit of this cult.
So she looked frightening, but she wasn't evil
and the blood that she was feeding on it
was because her earth was alive, and she was part
of the island that they lived on.
So I thought that was a very, very clever take
that I'd never seen before.
It all, all that stuff.
Like when it took that turn, usually when a movie's
like normal, normal, normal for 90 minutes,
and then there's a supernatural thing,
they don't pull it off.
It sucks, it's stupid.
but this like took that turn
and I was like completely on board with it.
It was genuinely unsettling and creepy and weird.
And all the effects and everything in it
felt like new and cool to me.
I just think this guy is a great director.
If you haven't seen those red pictures, check them out.
It's just non -stop incredible action.
They're like when you were in like 16,
you saw the Jackie Chan movies,
which now would probably be very dated,
but they're like that level of inventive and they're both great.
That's funny because I just re -watched RoboCop and I watched the Director's Cut,
which is streaming on Amazon Prime, so it's got apparently no different than the one
that's been available on Blu -ray for years.
No, no, no, it's got, there's considerable, there are scenes that have considerable more
graphic violence in them.
But that's available on Blu -ray, they're trying to play it off as a new cut.
I have the cut.
Oh, no, they're not advertising it as a special cut on RoboCop.
I read on a website somewhere they were like, Hey, FYI, the version of RoboCop streaming
is like the uncut version.
You should watch it if you haven't seen it.
So, but anyway, I just watched RoboCop.
And I remember like it took me back to when I was a kid and I first saw that and
being so blown away by this move.
Like it was, I felt the same way when I saw Total Recall, both Paul,
You know, I felt the same way when I saw, you know, the last crusade and, you know, like
there were just, you know, die hard. I remember feeling like that. Like there was just a really,
really cool thing about being a teen or a tween and seeing an action movie that was good.
Yeah.
And we get so few good action movies.
They used to be weekly and it's not, oh, it used to be better when we were younger.
They really were.
If you look at every weekend in like the summer of 89 has a movie that is still revered
as a classic.
Predator.
Yeah.
It was another one.
But I agree.
Look, and you know this, it's been my gripe about the Marvel movies.
The Marvel movies have become what killed action movies.
Once every kill had a punchline and a pun and whatever we made fun of it
We thought it was stupid and cheesy everybody did right now. It's what Marvel is doing in every film when people are going
This is brilliant right and it's like what are you talking about these are bad jokes? Yeah, that are punctuating significant events in the movie
And it takes away all the significance of the event right so that's what killed the action movie
You know by the time I remember cliffhanger being like a sort of a comeback for Stallone cliffhanger is pretty dope
Yeah, it's not fair because they took it seriously. Yeah, but you know before that he's doing you know
But the time he was doing like cobra and shit like that people were like all right, dude Jesus Christ
You know how brooding and and and wise ask can you be at the same time? Yeah
Anyway, I guess that's our show
Sure
Yeah, look for both of those live shows on the patreon. We have already recorded them when you hear this
we are recording them in a few days as we record this.
Our next several, and we haven't quite figured it out yet,
but our next few will be Event Horizon.
They will be the people under the stairs, Wes Craven.
Based on fan requests.
Like you guys are requesting these movies a lot,
so we're gonna do them.
And I'm plenty happy to do them.
So the live shows are Halloween and Tales of Halloween.
and they'll be available for the October and November
Patreon bonus apps.
Correct.
My show is called The Cool Kids on Fox.
We're doing well.
Thank you for watching.
It's on Hulu as well.
It's on Friday nights.
I'm on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh.
And that's all I got.
Jotaro's a comedy on Instagram.
When you can catch me, catch me on there.
And visit the Hot House store.
on Etsy. Yeah, get yourself some on the Facebook page. Thank you to Emily and Ken for running that so well. Yes. Get yourself some hog merchandise.
Uh, and that's it folks. We'll see you next time. We'll see you on home.