I'll see you in hell.
Hey, when the shine of your screams
becomes a thing on my dreams,
you know I say, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to
talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I
'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk
about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm
not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about
this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not
going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this
I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to
talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I
'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk about this, I'm not going to talk
Yeah, that's really funny. Go ahead, were you going to say what it was? Sorry, I just
No, I was just I was waiting for waiting for your anecdote there. I um
The one that I can't shake, the one that I can't forget, because usually I see the same old man and this old man loved him some ass back in the prison days, because he's I mean he's told me hundreds of stories of asses he's climbed for his own
uh
But he tells the story about this young man
Who's like day two in prison and scared to death to go to the bathroom even like forget taking a shower
He's scared to just reveal any part of his lower body to anyone and uh
sure enough
He's looking all around. He goes to the bathroom. Some guy comes up behind him and goes stay right there
Don't even wipe
right
That that's it that I'll be I'll be on a walk, you know a
Sunset walk around my neighborhood, you know feeling good and that'll pop into my head
And make you feel better or worse much better much
Much better. Yeah, don't even wipe is a title for something. I mean that's something don't even wipe
my own
Jesus it gets heavy in prison man
It does I hope to not go personally. I hope to not go um
To speak speaking of prison, you know we got Shaw shank
We got uh, you know
I watched the trailer last night because Joe was talking about it with me via text for the new Stephen King adaptation
We're talking about a Stephen King adaptation next week on this show
They're coming as hard and fast as but sex in a minimum security prison
Um, but this new one is called what Joe the life of Pablo is that's the Kanye album. What is it?
Life of Chuck I believe but but I don't think it's an adaptation. I think he just wrote it
Maybe I'm wrong. I maybe I'm wrong. I was
Because it doesn't say in the trailer, you know from the story or book by Stephen King
It just says from Stephen King like he wrote the screenplay
So I thought it was like oh no, it's this here based on the 2020 novella by king. Oh, okay never mind
Uh, it's being touted by at least one critic as the best Stephen King movie ever
Yeah, that's nuts. I already know it isn't let's just kind of be real about it um
But yeah, they called it what did they say Joe in the trailer? I'm gonna bring up your text because you got the words exact it said from
So so it said um
Uh from the mind from mind of Stephen King
Who wrote it sounds good and then it's directed by Mike Flanagan and then it said and from the heart and soul of Mike Flanagan
And at that point I turned the trailer off this thing
This thing could have been an announcement that I had won the publisher's clearinghouse. I was stop listening after a statement like I mean I just this is
Get just fuck off guys fuck off
Enough enough. It's just the hyperbole anymore is just sickening
I like
The work of Mike Flanagan and obviously I like the work of Stephen King
But yeah when you go too early to that jump like when Lee Daniels did Lee Daniels is the butler
Or when you do from the twisted mind of Ryan Reynolds
You're gonna piss people off man. You're really gonna piss people off. Oh god
Yeah, we can't put Flanagan amongst the greats here guys
He's had some pretty good Stephen King adaptations movies and TV. He's talented do not get me wrong and he
And he will be
ranked amongst the greats
At the very least of this genre
Sure
In the end absolutely I tremendous respect for the guy what he does but like
Just fine
You just from the heart and soul come on with this shit man. You know stop it
I'm so insulted at this point
That anything that comes out of a Hollywood
Studio factory is trying to convince me it cares
Or is human in any way shape or form. It's just like guys
You're making widgets make the fucking widgets let me react to the widget how I want to
And get the fuck out of my face. Yeah, we can end it there
You can't call them widgets anymore Joe. It's uh, little people
Um folks the life of Chuck. So here I am. I thought this was a Truman Show type picture
um
And maybe it is I watched the full two-minute trailer. I have no idea what it's about. It's it's saying
From the you know from Shaw shank from Green Mile from doctor
You're like okay, but I have no idea what this thing is about
Um, and I'm looking on Wikipedia and it's not telling me what it's about
Is it a well, I guess you know, I look it looks like the kind of thing where a man is
Living his life, but maybe somebody's writing it like his life as a movie is my guess
I couldn't I could I'm not kidding. I did shut it off
Yeah, almost immediately after that that card came up
But yeah, from what I did see it's some sort of you know, hyper reality fantasy
Yeah, you know
Mr
I said talented mr. Ripley life and times of Walter Middie kind of thing sure the fuck that movie was called
sure
Um, weird cast also Tom Hiddleston
Jacob Tremblay
She would tell edu4
Karen Gillan mark hamill
Mia Sarah
Sloan Peterson from Ferris Bueller
Oh, I have not seen in a movie in literally 25 years
Um, Matthew Lillard. I'm always happy to see him even though I didn't love him the first time around
David Desmouchien who if there's a horror movie will be in it now. That's a rule
And then kind of cool Heather Langen camp. Oh, that's cool. Yeah, so I'm not a bad guy. I'm intrigued. I like when king goes
You know
non-horror which this appears to be
But yeah, it says sci-fi fantasy and I'm not maybe they're keeping it
Close to the bone a life-affirming gender bending story based on three chapters in the life of an ordinary man
gender bending
I'm sorry John Rebending. Oh
I'm so used to everything being gender bending
um
Well, and while we're on the topic of trailers
Yeah, we were gonna talk about this but also uh
New friend of the show
Joe Romano texted me and said I really hope you're gonna be discussing this on the next episode and I said
Romani sorry
I'm uh Ramoni excuse me. I grew up. I had it my dad's best not well one of my dad's best friends my whole life was named Joe Romano
I keep mixing their names up anyway
um
The uh he I said yeah, we're definitely gonna be talking about it
But I'm glad that you want us to talk about it or he too because we're going to but uh the naked gun trailer has finally dropped
Um, hadn't I had different takes on this now it came to us from
I think Matt McCarthy sent it to us
Or did you send it to me and met?
No, I think Matt sent it. I've had the script for about six months a friend sent it to me
And I I don't know if I told you Joe, but I told somebody
I started reading it
It's the bit where Liam Neeson is in a Girl Scout uniform and he beats up the guys. I think I was talking about this a couple weeks back and
I just said this is not my naked gun. I don't want this
And I stopped reading the script after the cold open the trailer pretty much is that cold open the trailer pretty much is Liam Neeson in the Girl Scout uniform kicking ass
Um, but I found no laughs Joe found some laughs. I like I did like the bit that
You know all cops are haunted by the memory of their father. That was a funny bit. Yes, and I like that
You know Paul Walker house or is the son of George Kennedy
Well, I like that stuff, but that's about it. Go ahead. Joe. Let me interject. I thought yeah
I thought that um
Uh that bit that that bit was not only funny with where it was
Them looking at the pictures of their dads. I was like yeah
This is this has never been done where every character is the son of the character from the last from the original movie
Yeah, that was funny. That was very funny, but it's funny
The OJ joke made me laugh out loud because it shows each one of them looking at their respective fathers from the previous thing
And then they show a guy and it's it's OJ Simpson as his dad and he looks at the camera and does the head shake like
Which is which is a direct?
They do that and naked gun two and a half when they're in the bar
And he says give me a black Russian and the waiter looks at camera and he he just shakes it said
Yes, that's easy
Yeah, that made me laugh really hard
the opening I
You know as you said is the Girl Scout thing. I didn't think that was that funny
But weirdly I was in um
I was in Key West when this came out
Yeah, and I was I was doing a festival called Q West the Q from impractical joker's produced and
I was I showed it to him. I showed it to a couple people because I was around some comedy friends and
That sequence in the opening got way more of a reaction out of people than I thought it would have
I didn't think it was that funny
But we were also in Key West
Shit house. So everybody's in good spirits. So he's a west more like
But um, but I I think um
Shoutouts by the way to Q and jiggy for having us down there the Q West festival was really a great time, but um
But but yeah, I don't know I don't know
The the beginning was a little
I don't know the second half felt like naked gun the first half felt like
You know spy hard where it's like look we're being zany, you know
Yeah, look any any joke attempt in a trailer in 2025 is appreciated
uh, I have
Probably too much. I mean the naked gun is my
Star Wars if star if star if Star Wars is Joe's Star Wars the naked gun is my Star Wars
And seeing this just bump me out. That's all I can say it was it was far from seeing the trailer for the force awakens
Let's put it that way
um
I think I don't think I'm talking out of school by sharing his opinion, but
Uh, I hope I'm not at least but Joe said in a text. I said I thought it was
Funnier than I thought it was gonna be and he said I think that Leslie Nielsen is two in on the joke at this point
To play it straight which yeah early amnesia excuse me and it which was a good. Oh, that's weird
Leslie you know sin Liam. I never realized it anyway
um
Which I didn't think of and I was like yeah, you're right. I guess he has done a lot of the like isn't it funny when I say
Weird shit with a straight face
I only go back to that life is short episode life's too short episode, but I think he's done it a lot more than that at this point
He did he did it in Ted he did it in Atlanta the show Atlanta, which was the weirdest of them all where he talked about his race has passed
Um
Yeah, I don't know I'll see it. I'm excited. I assume it's coming to a streamer. I'm not sure which one now
I'm probably it's going into theaters dude. All right. Great. Great. Yeah. I mean, you know who who who knows who knows
You know fingers crossed. I wonder if like Priscilla Presley will show up somewhere. I bet you she does I bet you she's got a cameo and it's somewhere
I think she's the know living the interviewed one of them at Abraham's or whatever whatever one of them who's alive
And he hated the trailer and was all pissed it was the classic guy who didn't get asked to the party so he's just gonna shit on it, you know
Um, those guys are old and have become a little crotchety. I saw them talk before a screening of airplane here in town
And they were still pretty funny, but you can tell they're a little myth like everybody in this business that you're not still
relevant at age 75, you know, it happens, but they were a myth
um
speaking of Joe Ramone I
Purchased the 4k the brand new 4k of Uncle Buck
And it looks fantastic. I would say
You know everybody was pissed about the plane's trains transfer in 4k
I was not I was happy to have a movie that looked better than it's ever looked before
Even if that look may not be perfect. I'll take it
Sam with Uncle Buck. I can't say that the transfer blew me away
But it's the best I've ever seen this movie look for sure and
The only special feature I had time to listen to was Ramone's excellent commentary on the movie
And as I was telling him
There's almost no information about Uncle Buck. There's tons of information about the making of plane strains
precious little about Uncle Buck
He did a fantastic job and there's a second commentary on the disc as well, but I only listened to Joe's
Most interesting uh tidbit for me even though I told him it kind of pissed me off to hear it
The entirety of the film was shot in a high school
So all these interior shots where bucks like dancing with Lori Metcalf or he's at home with the kids and all the
All the interiors were done at a high school same with home alone
Which is actually since those houses the Chicago houses were such a
A dream place to live for me as a kid it really kind of bummed me out
But um ex-teriors you know like the home alone house recently sold for five million dollars the exterior
They look at a big beautiful house
But as every time they go inside
They're like in the gym at a local high school, which is crazy to me. I mean how brilliant of
Uh John Hughes or if it was his idea, but it's like hey, we're gonna shoot in the summer
Yeah high school is gonna be empty. So let us know for nothing
And here um my buddy Jeremy Garillek who uh
He did the wedding ranger and he was one of the writers on the hangover and he does a bunch of common now
He has this company called American high
Uh, and they made the Pete David's movie big time adolescence. They made a few movies
But he did the same thing he bought a high school and uh he shoots like a movie or two there a year
It's so smart. He bought a high school
Yeah, yeah like it was just we're it was like we're not gonna use this anymore
Right. Yeah, he didn't like you know shove the kids out
I'll tell you what I'm gonna pay all these kids to wishes
We're gonna take over
Um also read about it. They haven't had a smash hit yet, but once they do I think it'll really pay off
It's it's a cool company. We should have plugged this much sooner and in mad I apologize, but but follow McCarthy
Matt McCarthy at McCarthy redhead follow him everywhere, but particularly follow him
Uh on tic-toc because his entire tic-toc is all
Uh, VHS
You know, he's a massive movie collector and uh and VHS collector and his whole tic-toc is is VHS reviews and
Him looking at blank tapes he bought in thrift stores and
Uh, he's got a lot of insight on here about VHS collecting and how to do it properly and
Uh and
All playing old commercials and weird shit he finds and whatever it's very cool. So follow that again. It's McCarthy redhead
Uh on tic-toc
Please do uh
Let us get to our own movie corner. Yes
By the way on today's episode we're talking about the rule of Jenny Penn. Yes
Uh starting Jeffrey rush and Johnny Liffke
I
Saw
Number one on the call sheet a new three-ish hour documentary on apple tv
Heart and the right place. It's one of those documentaries where the hearts in the right place
But everything about it just kind of rubs you the wrong way
It is about what it's divided into two
Uh, one is black leading men in film today
And the second part is of course black leading actresses in film today
The documentary is simply talking head interviews with the biggest
Uh black stars in film dent, you know, you're denzel your jimmy fox your angel of bassit your viola davis
They talk to everybody they get everybody
Do you get some kind of amusing stories? Yeah, but this is the most dry
Uh
Sort of not
entertaining at all documentary that I've seen in some time it was such a bummer to watch that it's the rock
You know and
Will Smith and Kevin Hart and so many I like all these people of course, but so many of these little like talking heads are about
What it means to be quote number one on the call sheet what this means is that they list the cast
And you're the first person
So on cheers
Ted danston would be number one on the call sheet on the office. It's Steve Carell number two would probably be krisinski three rain
Wilson you see what I'm saying
So this is about how exciting it is to be a black person who's finally number one on the call sheet
Okay, how is that a three-hour documentary?
Like well three hours might be a lot. I get yeah, I get the premise, but uh, it's
Well once it's once it's set once the premise is set that like okay
From Sydney poitier to today black people have made a
A huge
Gain they've covered a huge amount of ground huge amount. Yeah, great
But to have the rock be like you know when I was
You know on my first film and I saw you know Brendan Fraser up there at number one in the call sheet
I said that's going to be me
That'll be me someday, you know, and there's so many of these stories about people talking about the dream of being number one on the call sheet
And it's just I don't know why that started to bother me because it seems like somebody who's like
Following capitalism or something. It's like it's yeah, it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's a
achievement in the sense of
It's saying
Everybody should be able to do the same thing. So I get that yeah, but I hear you
It's it's kind of like when Spike Lee stopped out of the
Up to down the aisle the Oscars because he didn't win and it's like spike you
This rep this whole thing represents everything you rail against like you shouldn't be upset
Yeah, that this shitty group of people is not recognizing you. Yeah, it's like you it would be like you getting mad that
Trump is not recognizing you you don't like that. So why would you want that to you know what I mean? So
Yeah, I hear you. It's it's kind of a
This whole thing by the way can I just just to tag on to your
Your review here
I'll tell you what I've had enough of if I see one more fucking clip of Will Smith
explaining in an interview
What grace and mental stability looks like I mean what the fuck is going on guys this guy is off
The fucking reservation. Yeah, okay. I mean he's he went sideways on international television
Two years ago and now every clip is him being like what's important man in life as you need to your goals
It's like what the fuck is going on. I'm getting sick of it in general
I'm getting really sick of people with a
gazillion dollars in the bank on Instagram telling me what doesn't matter in life money
Possessions food what really matters and all that will bring you happen is look get the fuck out of my face dude
Oh god, it's just yeah, they're asking anymore with this shit
One of my favorite Elvis Costello lyrics of all time. I've said it on the show before
Wasn't it a millionaire who sang imagine no possessions?
Yes, it was yes, it was and fuck you John Lennon for a lot of what you did. Oh, yeah
I
The documentary was was just very very average and I was I was a little annoyed to see it was done by Reginald
Huddlin who is such a great black director and an energetic director of film and this was not just not that
I would so much have preferred a documentary about great
character actors, let's say or
you know some sort of talk about
Acting as opposed to what it means to be at the top
uh
I don't know for three three hours of that. I was like this is the wrong thing to be teaching young actors to strive for
In my opinion even though it is wonderful of course
That black people are are welcome to the table and and and equaling and in many many
times
surpassing their white counterparts. Of course, that's fantastic. I just don't think it's a three-hour documentary
um
Some interesting stuff though with Will Smith talking about like even Denzel's like
Oh, well once will started on men and black at Independence Day was like we all were like oh fuck like we're we're in now
They really look to the people they speak to really look to Will Smith as being the crossover guy more so
Than even Denzel even some people at the a etc because commercially he was so massive
um
I'll do two document I have documentaries
I watched old dirty bastard a tale of two dirties
Guess it was on Hulu
What a fucking great documentary this was it was just it was just about old dirty bastard. It was about his
RISE and subsequent
tragic fall
uh
It started with you know the formation of Wu Tang Klam and like what he represented he was sort of the the like key
member in the foundation of that group
And he really embodied and represented the true like rawness and spirit of what they were doing and a
originality and
Of course as fame came in troubles came into and they talk about how
You know
Unfortunately, it became as undoing
um, it's just a really nice documentary. It's an interesting story. It's it's warts and all they pull no punches. They don't sit and
Try to make all of his bad behavior seem eccentric or quirky. They they talk about his flaws very honestly
And they talk about the beauty of him very honestly
and it's just a nice
nice little piece if you if uh of
Television watching if you if you or Wu Tang even if you're not a Wu Tang fan. It's just an interesting story, but um
I mean, I never thought I'd see the day where ghost face killer made me cry
But to the Jesus Christ there's a part at the end where they're like what would you do if he was here?
What would you say what would you do right now?
And he was just like man I'd hug him and I'd kiss him all over his face
I'd fall asleep next to him. I love him so much man. I miss him. I'm a I started crying. I was like Jesus. It's very beautiful
But uh, it's a good doc man, and I enjoyed it really cool interviews with
Dante Ross and ghost face killer Rayquan
Uh stretch Armstrong some some true hip-hop icons in there which was very cool to me
Uh Mariah Carey they talked to a lot in it because he did her big single uh fantasy
Um, and that was kind of cool too to see Mariah Carey
talk in a normal and and sort of
Very stripped down sort of human way about somebody because you kind of only ever see her
Like on some like diva special or something you know what I mean like it was it was nice to see her
Just talk about how much she loves the music and telling the story of when they recorded the song in the studio
And how she was like during the whole session she wasn't physically there but she was on speaker phone just listening for hours
and um and
You know the story is very funny and uh she was funny and it was it was it was a it was a nice documentary
I again if you're a Wu-Teng fan especially it I would say it's essential watching and if you're not
Uh, I think it's still riveting
Uh, riveting watch uh, but old dirty bastard the tale of two a tale of two dirties
That's this is supposed to be their last tour correct coming up
Yeah, they just put out
It's not enough fit
So they put out a record on record store day. It's not enough so so there's two they do two kinds of releases
They do the Wu-Teng clan releases are the official albums. So that's like
36 chambers
um, you know
Uh, eight diagrams a better tomorrow Wu-Teng forever all those
Then they do these like in between albums or mix tapes. I don't know what you call them a lot of them and they're usually built just as Wu-Teng
Or Wu-Teng and mathematics so they just put one of those out
On record store day with 12 new songs. I've heard three of them. They're all very good
I've got a copy being held for me at my local record store forever changes
Uh, it's 72 dollars a little overpriced
But not because of the stooots Carelli gonna hold a poster well
Not because of the store it's some kind of
It's some kind of one of a kind never been done before vinyl release on record store day
I guess it's a very limited whatever and I guess they're not gonna release it digitally
Except for the single. I don't know. I'm gonna buy it. I have to but
But yeah, this is the last tour. It's called the final chamber I think and I think they're gonna
a purportedly put out one more
official Wu-Teng record
Wu-Teng clan record and then that's it. So I think I mean, you know everybody always says this is it
Actually at this point. I'm like no these guys are all probably in their mid fifties like this actually could be it like jazzy retired
eight times at like 34
Yeah, it's a kind of a different story when you're approaching 60 so
Um, I think we can all agree those last several jazzy albums were the cream of the crop
Him and Justin Timberlake doing duets about how gold their watches are yeah
Yeah, I love those
um, I went to Tarantino's new Beverly Chinne ma
And it's been so cool
Living within
Five minutes of the vista which now does you know movies from Tarantino's private collection every weekend
I they have great movies at 10 a.m. Every Saturday and Sunday in addition to their midnight screenings
So I've been going to those 10 a.m.s nice when I blast
New Beverly I went to see two great
comedy capers
But as is often the case with the new Beverly I didn't make the double feature the older I get I just watched one
I was on a date so that contributed as well
But it was a fish called Wanda and dirty rotten scoundrels and I just thought what a great
Match up both 1988 comedy classics. Yeah both movies. I loved as a kid
Both movies that combine like jewel heists with big laughs um
A fish called Wanda is so fucking funny. I wish we got a lot more non-monty python
Committees from the pythons. You know what I mean? This is pretty much the only classic
We got fierce creatures, which is sort of a spiritual sequel to this and I remember being very let down by it
Maybe it would hold up. I don't know
But this was written by John Cleese and considering Cleese wrote this and faulty towers
I'm prepared to declare this man the most talented of the fucking pythons
Eric Idol and these guys get a little too cutesy for me Terry Gilliam gets a little too weird for me
Cleese is the G
Cleese is the G. Yeah, I agree and
I love what this movie is doing it is combining
brilliantly the
snooty british
upper crust snob
You know farce
with the down and dirty slapstick sex
raunchy american farce and weirdly it works beautifully
It's directed by this real old man named Charles Criton who did dead of night the classic horror movie
The original one the original one. Yeah, he's his christ lavender hill mob
You know, he's an old guy by the time he does fish called wanda like you know easily in his 70s
I believe so the movie you know
It's a little I wish it had been directed by a younger man
But then fierce creatures was and it certainly wasn't any better than this so who knows but the movie is
Just nonstop laughs the Americans are Jamie Lee Curtis who is
Stunning in this as she was for
Most of her life and and remains. So, you know who would have thought she'd become a bigger star now
But um always a brilliant comedian she still doesn't get the the props for Kirk comedic skills. She's one of the great female comics
Curtis is awesome in this
Kevin Klein steals the movie. He won best supporting actor
As like your textbook
ugly American the stupid
Uh, they kind of stole the marty McFly don't call me stupid his was don't call me yellow but
Klein is so funny in this and basically Curtis and Klein are double crossing everybody including each other
um
It's great many dogs are killed
That kept building and building it was really fun to see all these big sight gags with an audience
Michael palin is super funny in it as the guy with the stutter the stuttering jokes, you know gasps from the audience like
It's just it's a style of comedy that we talk about all the time is missing um because this is like
It's it's it's making fun of people
But it's assholes doing it and we always used to get that
And now we don't get that for some reason
The the most evil horrible man in the movie is being an asshole and it's very funny
We know we're not supposed to think this guy is a hero, but at some point we lost that um
It's really funny and not enough people have seen it the girl I went with had no idea what it even was thought it was a kids movie
Um, if you've never seen a fish called want to check it out. It's very very funny very well written and very well acted by a killer cast Joseph
Um, you have discussed this already, but I finally watched it. This is the Tom Green documentary. Yes
uh
Tom Green uh, who was a pop culture comedy superstar
Uh in the I guess it was mid to into late 90s
Into the early aughts
Um
He had the time green show on MTV, which was a cultural phenomenon
um, and it was the precursor to jackass and anything you've ever seen
Eric Andre where where people do extreme things
For jokes for laughs on camera
um
Tom then went on to
Star in several movies
um
Uh and uh
Had a very public battle with cancer
um
And then kind of step back and and and went back into doing stand-up
And is still quite notable and quite known and uh and still has a following but um
But you know in comparison to where he was and in the in like 99
Certainly a guy leading a much simpler life at this point
So the documentary is about how he left LA bought a hundred acre farm in Canada
And lives a relatively quiet life up there while
Simultaneously touring and doing stand-up um
I've known Tom for years uh
I met him
14 years ago something like that 15 years ago
He's an extraordinarily good guy. He's very funny
He's got a good heart. He's a great dude and I loved the documentary because he truly seems happy and uh
I don't know it was just a guy
You know living this insane life with all these insane happenings and
You know, he's just got up he's got a purity to him that comes across on camera that
Sometimes people are able to fake but I can tell you with somebody that that's spent time with him
He he is that guy. He's a good dude. So it was nice to watch. It's nice to see he's still so close with his parents
Uh in his family
And uh it was just a really good watch man. I really enjoyed it um it was heartwarming and and you know
evoked a few tears
Uh, and then also very funny to just watch you know, so uh check it out if you want there's also a companion
mini docu-series called tom green country
That's just about his life in like learning how to run a farm basically
And then his comedy special also which I'm blanking on the name of dropped on prime as well
So it's kind of triple hit solid. I watched him. Yeah. He's solid. He's funny man. He's a good comic
He's he's he's he's he he wears his many hats well
Yeah, um, and I hope he does
I mean, he might have zero interest
But I would like to see him act again because I think he's a good actor now. So I think he's somebody like where it would be fun to see him
To play a more straight role
Uh, you know, maybe a supporting role in a drama or something and be I bet you he'd be fucking great at it. So
Um anyway, or maybe a dark character be cool to see him play like an unhinged like
socio path or something
Definitely see him as a stalker. Yeah. Yeah exactly. So anyway, check it out. This is the time green documentary
Uh, I went to a 10 a.m. Vista screening of 1941 Steven Spielberg's
much maligned uh film from 1979
I am a massive blues brothers fan. I know a lot of people don't get it
Don't like it. I can't help it. I watched it when I was five years old
I've always been obsessed with it. I love it. I think the musical numbers are some of the best in film
History. I just love it. Jesus
James Brown on the church and and Ritha Franklin singing think of the diner. You know, there's a there's a lot of classic stuff in there. This is in
1941 not in the blues. That's all blues brothers. Oh, you're talking of the blues brothers
Yeah, wait, you're just the way you just said that I got confused you said 1941 James Brown in the diner
No, wait, what do you say? I'm saying 1941 is basically
The blues brothers just not good without any of the musical numbers correct. Obviously. Yeah. Yeah. No
You know why it's not good because it's John Belushi
He sucks
He's not fun. I tried to say to somebody the other day. Well, the blues brothers is funny and they were like is it
Is it and I was like, you know what you're right? There's like too funny scenes you take the musical numbers out of that movie that movie sucks
Well animal house is funny if you've never seen old school
It's he's not funny ever. Okay, we've talked about blue share a lot of I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry
Um, I love the blues brothers. That's what I was saying. I do love. Okay. Are you out here? I do think it's funny
But I particularly love it for its music and its musical numbers and all these great performances from these soul R&B legends
um
And I'm shocked that the blues brothers. I love it so much that it is so beloved and that
1941 exists and is so hated and ever since I was a little kid
I thought I'm gonna try this one more time. We've all got those movies
Everything about this is screaming that I should like it. Oh, yeah
And you'll try a movie like that every three years until you die and you'll never like it
I have so many movies like this
1941 is a big one. I thought maybe since it's such a big expensive bloated blockbuster that it'll look great
On the big screen. It did look great, but this is not a good movie
1941 is so bad and for anyone who doesn't like blues brothers
I would urge you to check this out so you can at least change the bar a little bit
The movie is written by another group of people we discussed last couple episodes
Robert Zemakis and Bob Gale
So yeah Zemakis has made some bad shit in his day. Oh, I got a whole spiel ready for Zemakis on the next episode
so
Well, we talked about him on the here episode pretty pretty much. I got I dealt I went and delved back in
I'm got I got more to say about Zemakis. Okay. All right
but
1941 and it's weird because this week on the best show with Tom Sharple in their discussing is the blues brothers funny for almost the entire three hour show
um
It is to me 1941 has zero laughs
uh, it is so crazily broad and
It's just a lineup of hilarious people not being funny for two hours
It's Steven Spielberg thinking that blowing shit up will just be funny without having to add anything to it
Blues brothers eventually devolves into a huge car chase
But it's visually inventive and full of gags and and fun and exciting and everything else
This is just a big bloated mess. It's got a funny premise after the attack on Pearl Harbor
Panic grips california
So it's basically like a war movie on Hollywood Boulevard and that should work
But it doesn't so
It's Boulouchy and Acroid for some reason they almost never have the two men interact with each other
Blues brothers wisely realized that people like them together
uh, Ned Bady who I did enjoy
Christopher Lee Tim Matheson from Animal House
Tochiro Mifune from all of uh, Kurosawa's movies
Thankfully not as racist as these scenes could have been but not great
Robert Stack
I liked him in it treat Williams Nancy Allen John candy
Patty lapone you recognize everybody in the movie slim pickens
Joe Flaherty Michael McKean the list goes on and on and on nobody is doing anything funny
I saw Flaherty interviewed once and he said Steven Spielberg kept coming up to him
He's done jaws
He's the most successful director on earth and he kept coming over to Flaherty and being like is this funny
I
How do you make this funny? There's nothing funny about Steven Spielberg
No, he never should have been at the helm of a comedy obviously
You know is John Landis a better director than Spielberg? No, is he a better comedy director? You bet your ass
For people don't understand that for five years he was
Well, I'd say I'd put it more than five, but yes, well, what is it?
Well, ten years. I mean he's got ten tops. Yeah, yeah, yeah, okay
Fair enough you can go American where I will have to come into America and be good. Yeah, it's okay
Um
Or you know you can go animal house through come into America for sure so maybe a little more than ten animal house doesn't count for me, but go ahead
Balushi is a zero in this movie. This is Balushi's worst movie. This is worse than neighbors with Acroix
um
Spielberg does not know what to do with anybody. It just feels like
He saw that animal house was a phenomenon and said I want my animal house. Well, Steve you can't have it
Because you're not a funny person
Um, this is basically an action movie where everyone is acting insanely trying to get laughs
and it is also a
Comedy where you're like why is there so much action? Why don't they land one joke and they can't do it there's
20 minutes of this with Eddie Deason and a ventriloquist dummy stuck on a Ferris wheel
I don't know if you know Eddie Deason, but I believe it or not
I don't have the names that ringing your bell
Google him right now if you're listening and and if you're Joe if you recall the nerds from save by the bell
The nerds who were too nerdy for screech to hang out with with pocket protectors
This was the Eddie Deason character for like ten years in film. Oh, yeah
This guy yeah, he's so annoying and so big and so broad and every choice in this movie is wrong
And I'm sure in 1941 has some fans, but for me it's a piece of shit
It's been a piece of shit since the first time I saw it and each of the five times I've seen it between that and now
I'm going to stop watching it. I sold my unopened copy of it
1941 is bad
Uh, and finally
There's really nothing much here to say, but I watched the docu-series history of the sitcom
What can I say folks? It's the history of the sitcom. It's many episodes every episode is themed
You know, one'll deal with gender one'll deal with race one'll deal with just you know the family life whatever
Uh, they go pretty thoroughly through sitcoms
Uh, I almost tapped out after the first episode because I don't need a spotlight on Pamela Adland
Uh
Like she's a genius
What sitcom were they referring to? The fucking show she had on it effects whatever the one or things
Yeah, yeah, the one Louis gave her and then she immediately rolled over on him publicly
I've seen every episode of it and I like the show quite a bit. Why are we calling that a sitcom?
Oh pat because it's brave because she calls her daughter a cunt see she's a genius. There you go. She's a fucking genius
I
Mean a lot of people would say a sitcom is multi-cam, but well no sitcoms are single cam like modern families is sitcom
Okay, uh better than that's disturbing that you you should know that as a
Uh what I said what I said was some people would only call a true sitcom a multi-cam like James burrows
Yeah, no it's it's multi-n single cam so modern families and their curbs and their
Better things is in there a show that not a comedy. Yeah show that
18 critics deemed as brilliant and not one person I've ever met in real life has ever seen it um
Uh, so anyway look nothing against Pamela Adland, but it's just like
You know they they keep going back to her in this first episode like she's Norman Lear
Yeah, and she's got nothing to say
Yeah, she'll go like she'll go like oh my god. Yes
Too close for comfort oh
I loved Monroe that these are her insights, you know, and you're like thanks Pam. Okay. Thank you
But uh it picks up after that and uh it was good you know in fact Jim J. Bullock heavily featured
And talking about like him having to
His character was gay, but they could never say it and he was closeted
Because he was terrified he'd ruin his career and there's a lot of really interesting stuff in there
And it is fun and it is funny they don't lean so much into the personal struggle and and
Uh and all that that that that you don't enjoy the comedy part of it. So it's a lot of fun
um
And you know it was worth it was worth a watch
I think it's on paramount plus it might be on hulu. I can't remember anymore folks
Let's get to the movie of the day
Speaking of hilarity
John with gallon Jeffrey rush starring in the role of Jenny pen a movie Jeffrey rush
Wouldn't have made with a gun to his head
but given
Given a couple accusations. I think he's now stepping into the horror
John world
Yeah, it's hard to get a read on who Jeffrey rush the man is we've all seen John let's go interviewed at length
But I don't think I've ever seen
Jeffrey rush talk to for more than five seconds
He did have some kind of dodgy me two stuff which is why making him a judge in this
Who is ruling on sex crimes is a little weird
But um I did research it and rushes cry. I never want to be the guy who's like
But were they really that bad his stuff was sending suggestive texts to actresses
He worked with and so forth not right
Not great is one the follow-up allegations were like
Yeah, he like
Dance naked around me and his the second time something got brought up he was like look
It was one of those things where he's like look maybe my humor is not forever
Yeah, well the first one he had all sorts of proof and he not only did he get off
But the woman owed him like a couple million dollars. Yeah, and then they come then second one came out
I was like he shook his dick in my face outside of his dressing room of walking around naked and then his response to that one was yeah
Like hey, we all like to have fun on
So it's like Jeff
I think rush will be
Look he's he's 78 years old. So it's like you know
But I think he will be allowed to work. Yes, but
Uh, I do think that he probably wouldn't have done this kind of lift gal on the other hand
I feel like let's gal will jump at anything if it's an interesting thing for him
He doesn't give a shit how big or how small so they were like do you want to play a unhinged
Cockney lunatic and he was like yeah, fuck yeah, let's go like and yeah
That he's by him because he goes from like
The crown yeah to this he's what that's the kind of actor I love, you know who's just like
What is it?
Do I get a chance to do my thing? Yeah, I'm in that sounds great
um
And this feels like a modern
Whatever happened to baby Jane which is one of my favorite
Certainly one of my favorite old-time me horror movies with Betty Davis
And John Crawford as two old ladies kind of like terrorizing each other yeah
That's basically what this is this is John Liff Gow as an old creep in a retirement home
Jeffrey rush is kind of a snobby judge who gets taken down a peg by
God as we all will he has a stroke while uh, you know speaking on the stand
And winds up in this home while there
He discovers this really bizarre
Guy this bizarre situation which is John Liff Gow harassing his room harassing Jeffrey rushes roommate
And kind of harassing everybody in this home and at first it just seems like oh he's a bully
But it gets darker and weirder and stranger and Liff Gow goes more and more nuts
Um
He carries around a little puppet that he calls Jenny Penn who he wants everyone to bow down to
And even kiss the asshole of
That's kind of the first moment of this where you're like oh, I'm watching something a little insane here
He's asking people to kiss the asshole
He'll pop it he sneaks into their rooms at night because he has like all these
These are there's gonna be spoilers here just so you guys know, but he has access to the entire facility because as it is revealed
Halfway through he worked at the facility for like his whole that was his career
So he's got all these access cards and everything before he was a patient at this facility and
He sneaks into all their rooms at night
With the puppet and terrorizes them does things that are anywhere from
emotionally terrorizing to physically harmful to almost deadly to the to the patients
And yeah, he'll pull pull talk to the he puts the puppet over everybody said he goes who rules and they have to say Jenny
And then he turns the puppet around to show his wrist and then he says now lick her asshole
Yeah, and they have to lick his wrist and that's his way of just being like if you
You'll demean yourself and do that
I might just leave you alone
um
As pat already said it gets more intense more sinister throughout and what starts to happen is a real cat and mouse game between Jeffrey rush and John
Lithgow
With Jeffrey rush being
somewhat incapacitated from this stroke
and
Initially optimistic that he's gonna get out of this place
But then slowly starts to realize his because of his age his condition will probably worsen and he might never get it
So now he is forced with
having to
Deal with this psychopath the problem is is John Lithgow is sort of wily and has a way of getting away with this stuff
We're making it look like he's not the one doing it so other people get blamed
um
And uh Jeffrey rush has to very much take matters into his own hands that I thought the movie was very fun
I thought Lithgow was fucking wild in it in a great way
I was I was pretty hooked in my only
criticism was I
Did feel like I was kind of waiting for the moment where they revealed like not only did Lithgow work there
But he's also the his family owns it or something
Yeah to kind of justify
Why he was so repeatedly able to get away with stuff
I was like if everybody in this thing just came together and told the
The staff like look he's doing this. We're not all lying
Yeah, he'd that'd be the end of it
And I just was a little confused as to why everybody cow-towed him so much
Maybe there's something in there that I missed
That was my one sort of gripe or or also too they have these call buttons
For the nurses obviously because they're they could they could have a
Health issue at any moment any time of day
I never understood either why when he goes into the rooms and terrorizes them. They don't just start hitting the button
To call the nurse
You know that was confusing. I definitely get what you're saying and they could have addressed that better
I took it as
Prison style where you're not reporting him for fear that
He will retaliate on you tenfold
But it's hard to think that about everybody in this place that everybody would be so scared of him
I agree
Then again, he is scary they even gave him prosthetic little teeth
Yeah
And Lithgow is fucking awesome, you know my my thing with people in these types of movies and they make a lot of these types of movie
is
Why aren't you going for it?
You know like
It doesn't always have to be Hannibal Lecter with like oh hello
How are you, you know, it that that's an option and that's one of the greatest villains ever but
Where where are the Betty Davis in whatever happened to baby Jane villains today?
Everyone's so scared of going too big and too broad in comedies and horror and everything
But man when it happens, it's fucking fun to watch, you know just somebody chew in the goddamn scenery
Uh, I love Lithgow in this. I love Jeffrey rush in this
I haven't seen him in a long time and I thought he was great and very sympathetic in the part
I love the third guy the
Maori guy who is the roommate of Jeffrey rush
Yeah, yeah, he's great
My only real issue with the thing is that
It's good enough to make you wish it was a little better. It you know, it's like it's stuck in this high B or B plus
Territory and it's a B movie so great. It's on shutter way better than your usual shutter fair by the way. Yes, but
And a lot of that is the cast, you know, this was just too random old guys and your usual shutter budget
I don't know that we'd even be talking about it, but
It's really well done. It's well shot. I love how they were doing, you know, interesting angles
You know, they're always like just showing you the tops of people's heads or very very interesting angles
Keeps you on your toes
It's just never quite scary enough or a suspenseful enough and the twists and turns and mechanics of the script are never quite smart enough
And as Joe said you're waiting for some big third act twist that doesn't come so all it is is a really good B movie that for me
I spent the whole time going man. I wish they had spent another couple weeks on this to make it an A
That said
A B an entertaining B movie horror movie like this is a gift and I really enjoyed it. So my hog is up. I
agree I
I agree on all points. There's there's nothing I could say to ref I could not refute anything you said
And and I don't have much to add to it. It's a simple film. It's an entertaining film. It's a performance based film
Um, and it's the kind of movie I usually really enjoy. I like I like something that focuses in on a couple of characters
That are going to go head to head. I'm very excited about this new David mammoth movie coming out called
Howard
Something to rub I forget but anyway mammoth wrote and directed it was him play he wrote and he wrote and directed the movie
It's his first movie in years and years and years shy will buff stars at it
But it's two two convicts
That somehow get a gun smuggled into the prison
And do like but it's cl- it looks like classic mammoth
It's like three guys in a room dealing with a situation and I love stuff like that
And that's the kind of stuff that they bring to the table in this movie
great performances
Very well directed some nice suspense. It is scary
Uh, and uh at times quite stunning visually my hog is up
Not a not a masterpiece, but very strong fair the rule of Jenny pen on shutter check it out
Folks, I'm a joderosa comedy on Instagram and uh
Whatever the hell it is on tic-toc joderosa comedian
uh
Some plugs
I got shows people uh, I think this will come out before but I have chosen Connecticut april
God right now april 18th and 19th
At New York comedy club in Stanford Connecticut four shows tickets are available
Outside of that
I've got upcoming gigs in
Let's see here we've got
Well, we're doing the screening of my special on april 29th
One screening angelica film center in New York City april 29th 9 p.m
Come on out and see that
Uh, before it's available for public consumption. Please tickets are available south orange new jersey south orange performing arts center june 7th
Uh june 27th and 28th the lab at zanes
Comedy connection august 1st and 2nd uh and some other dates following throughout the fall
joderosa.com for those and then lastly
Uh, come to joey roses if you would
Uh, joey roses
Dot com uh, get yourself a drink in a sandwich
That's it for me
My name is patrick wash at the patrick wash on instagram for the time being
I
Discussed on the solo pod if you want to buy something from my amazon store. It's pta pat 05
Many of you have done that already. I'm happy to sign them dedicate them whatever you want
Um, somebody asked me about that around christmas time and I was just like hey if other people want to do that great
So look me up there
There's a very active community on patreon. We love you guys. We appreciate you. We have a facebook page
We have an instagram page at c u and hell pod
Um, we will be back with a review of oswald perkins the monkey
We'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell