I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, and when the sound of your screams becomes
a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say, I'll see you in hell, you know I will, I'll see
you in hell, you know I will.
Folks, it's We'll See You in Hell, the podcast where you talk about movies.
I am Joe DeRosa.
And I am Patrick Walsh.
This week we are discussing the Nicolas Cage, Nicolas Holt, Aquafina vehicle, Renfield,
the quote horror, quote comedy, Renfield.
We had a turn of events on the last episode, which I think was last month.
No, this is, we're still in, I don't know, we're on a little, we even done this in a
long time.
This is our third episode today that we're recording.
We usually do one and keep it moving, but Pat and I are on such a roll right now that
we decided to go not for just two, but for a third.
Spur of the moment.
Unplanned.
I've never felt more alive.
We were a bit polarized.
Which is sad.
We were polarized on the Pope's exodus, but then I changed my mind and I became convinced
that it was an enjoyable film.
Renfield, I don't think, well I'm curious to see where this goes, but this is a movie.
Let me take some suspense away for you.
If someone had a gun to my head and said, the only thing I need to do to keep from pulling
this trigger is for you to change your opinion convincingly on Renfield and come away from
saying that you liked it okay, I'd say pull the fucking trigger.
Pull the fucking trigger.
My opinion ain't changed.
Yeah, no, I don't think mine will either.
I have a lot to say about Renfield, but it can wait.
I have a lot to say about Renfield and interestingly, because we just spoke about the Pope's exorcist,
I have, I want to compare it to that film in particular.
Okay.
Because, you know, they were probably the same budget.
I talked a lot about Nick Cage and how he would have been different in the Pope's exorcist
and maybe it would have been great, maybe it wouldn't.
But yeah, Renfield, I got a lot to say and yet nothing really to say.
It's not worth much to say.
What did you do?
How are you, Joe?
I'm fine.
I was going to ask you what you did all weekend.
I've done nothing.
I on Friday night, I went out for some drinks.
I started at my bar, had a few things to take care of their business wise and had a drink
or two and then went with, I was with Janis Papas.
I did his podcast and we went and got, we went to Smith and Walensky's after we recorded
and got some burgers and a prime rib sandwich and shrimp cocktail and some drinks.
And then we went down to my bar and I took care of one or two things.
We had a drink or two there.
And then I went up to the stand with Paul, my partner who owns that place and had a few
drinks at the stand and then came home.
Very uneventful, but fun, enjoyable.
Yesterday I get up.
I go to the Apple store to take care of some business.
I come back.
I go to not one, but two grocery stores, two separate grocery store trips.
I look at my phone.
I'm 10 ,000 steps in.
I did it.
I sit on the couch.
I pop on the Pope's exorcist.
I follow it with a little bit of Owen Wilson's paint.
And the next thing I know, I'm waking up at 5 a .m. on my couch.
Once again, I have forgotten to brush my teeth.
You know, just my back hurts because I'm half on the couch, half on the ottoman.
And then Sunday hits.
And here we are today.
This has been the bulk of my day today.
Is the recording this with you?
How about you?
I spent the entirety of last week in Vegas.
As you know, they put me up there in a, you know, apartment sized room.
And I had a really nice time.
I took the focus off of gambling, which is always a good thing for me.
And also took the focus.
Sometimes I try to convince myself I'm going to write on a trip.
And that's stupid, too, because it sets the whole vacation up for failure.
You're not going to write in Las Vegas.
And I didn't.
I just said, I'm going to go and have a nice time.
My industry is not even allowing me to work.
I should not be feeling any guilt for wanting to take a nice relaxing time off.
And I did.
I went out.
I had some fun.
I have a story to share, but I need to decide if I want to share it here or not
before I just launch into it.
I don't want to tell it and regret it, but quite an anecdote to share.
But I had a lot of fun.
And then as is often the case when I go to Vegas, I come back and my throat is killing me
because I am never, ever, ever around cigarette smoke in any capacity.
Right.
And when you're in Vegas, it is everywhere.
And it's just not good for you.
Like when I was a kid and you're around adults who are smoking and some spars in Missouri
allow smoking, you get used to it.
But yeah, there's just something about the air there that's just tough on me.
So I woke up yesterday feeling like I had COVID.
I actually took a test because my throat hurts so horribly.
But it went away in a sort of beautiful way.
I went to bed last night at midnight.
I woke up at 8 .30 feeling a little bit better.
And I was like, you know what?
I'm going to press on with this sleep and just try to knock this incoming cold out.
And I slept another four or five hours.
So we're talking about 12 to 13 hours of sleep.
And now here I am on podcast three.
My throat feels fantastic.
Feel ready to deep throats somebody, you know?
Late Friday night, I thought I might be getting a bit of a flu.
It was probably just my body going, the whiskey's wearing off.
What's happening?
I thought I felt like a flu coming on.
And I can't tell you the excitement I felt.
Sure.
I was like, oh, let's go, baby.
Give me that sweet five days in the house.
Like, come on, baby.
And it didn't happen.
Yeah.
Fortunately, I'm well.
But, God, you get older.
Truthfully, and I hate to keep saying it, talking about the benefits of being sober,
but I blew past my 30 -day marker with no alcohol or marijuana or carbs or sugar.
And I'm at about 35 days now.
The truth is that generally when I feel that sore throat kick in,
my immediate turn to would be whiskey.
It kills the pain, but I wind up with a five -day sore throat.
I think just simply being like, I'm going to do the sensible thing and sleep,
and my body just naturally fighting off disease and not being killed by the alcohol
is probably what helped me beat it.
I mean, it's only pros to giving up this stuff until you're in a moment of stress
and then you do absolutely anything to have a drink or a puff.
But for the most part, this has been very easy,
and I know that this gives Joe the hives,
but I'm starting to ponder never drinking again.
Yeah, well, all right.
Let's talk in a couple weeks.
It's hard to say that.
I know.
It's hard to even say.
Listen, I think it's good, and I think I say this with all sincerity.
I'm happy for you.
I think it sounds like you're doing a good thing for yourself,
and I think you don't have to ponder anything.
I think you just have to see where it takes you and let it ride.
And who knows?
Maybe you don't drink again.
Maybe you drink again in five years.
Maybe you drink again in six days.
Maybe you'd never touch this stuff.
Who the hell knows?
Who cares?
Maybe, Joe, I just went down and I'm pouring myself a glass of red wine.
I thought it would take a little longer, but no.
In a cartoon, it would go to the wide shot,
where I'm pouring myself a glass as we speak.
No, the benefits have been great.
Although I'm going into town for a wedding in a couple weeks,
going back to Missouri, my friends there are like,
hey, so if you're not drinking, do you not want to hit the bars or whatever?
And I'm like, I'm going to go back to St. Louis with the boys
and not hit the bars.
But you got to do what's best for yourself at the end of the day.
Well, and you might feel at that point that you're in a place of,
I can go to the bars and not drink.
I mean, I've been there.
Oh, I totally could. Totally could.
And you might still have fun, you know?
I mean, Christ, dude.
The last break I took, I went to Vegas.
Yeah.
I went to fucking Vegas and didn't drink.
And I'm talking like a week or two into it and didn't drink.
And I had a great time.
And I thought that I would have said, that's impossible.
You're insane.
And I ended up having some.
It's mind over matter.
Yeah.
The concerts I've gone to where I was like going out the door,
like, oh man, a sober concert.
This is going to suck.
They've all been really fun.
I can't deny it.
So I'm enjoying myself.
Good.
And just the waking up without feeling like I've got 10 shotguns
pointed at me every morning is worth it.
It's worth whatever else.
Yeah.
It's also the app's great because it tallies up how much money you're saving,
how many calories you're saving.
It just provides you each day with the information that's necessary to be like,
great.
The app's called I Am Sober.
It's free.
If you ever even want to take a couple of weeks off.
You just, you get the,
not only the feeling of accomplishment of I've done it and it cheers you on and
stuff, but it's also got testimonies from other people.
Hey, I'm on day 30 and I just did a bag of cocaine.
I fucked up.
What should I do?
And it's good to see people in bad situations.
It's also good to see people thriving.
And in terms of the calories and the money saved,
like those are some real benefits.
You know,
if you're a regular drinker or especially a regular weed person,
that money adds up as do edibles.
Sure.
But hey,
what else is going on in this big spinning globe?
I pay attention.
Since I got off Twitter,
I don't really pay attention to the news either.
I know we missed, of course, the big Titanic visitor sub,
you know,
I'm sure Ron Howard's working on that movie right now.
I know the Bidens are on vacation.
That's all I really know.
Bag of Coke at the white house.
That was a big one.
And who did that belong to?
Well,
the assumption is Hunter,
but they found a bag of Coke in the white house.
Would Hunter bring a bag of Coke to the white house?
Is he still having issues?
Yes.
He's.
I believe so.
It was in the West wing.
Like is Hunter often in the West wing?
He's he's there.
Well,
I mean,
maybe it wasn't,
I don't know.
My assumption was cocaine found at the white house in a different
location than previously reported sources say.
I mean,
who knows?
Maybe it was just a staffer had it.
Look,
I'm sure that ain't no easy job to stay awake.
You know,
it's like you're working long hours.
It's stressful.
I'm sure plenty of people have done Coke in the white house over the
years.
Somebody just had a hole in their pocket or was so fucked up.
They got sloppy.
Yeah.
My assumption was it was Hunter,
since this is the first time something like this has ever been reported
and the guys got.
Ridiculous,
you know,
more of a drug history.
Yeah.
Maybe it maybe it wasn't.
I might be,
it was found near the situation.
You should route.
White house.
Yeah.
Rule out Hunter is what the,
well,
that's what the New York post said.
Sure.
Which you got to take that with a grain of salt,
cause it's about the left and it's coming from the post,
but,
but I don't know.
It's a story.
There you go.
All the trumps seem like they love cocaine.
I don't get why in this day and age you wouldn't do at all.
I've been in enough writers rooms to know that like the modern day cocaine is Adderall.
It works in the exact same way, except it's legal.
You can do it in front of other people at your job and it'll make you exceed creatively.
Whereas cocaine makes no promises of that.
It just keeps you up.
Why not make the switch to Adderall?
I guess, you know, it's got its own issues, but I know a lot of people that have said
that Adderall makes them feel in a way that's bad, that surprisingly cocaine doesn't make
them feel.
So people just have their preferences, you know, people have their preferences.
Sometimes I imagine with somebody who does a lot of coke, it's because they enjoy the
immediate charge and rush that you get from it versus Adderall, which is a little more
of a, I know there's, I guess there's not time release Adderall, there's stuff that
hits you a little more quickly, but I do think it's probably a different experience for most
people and, and there's a reason why certain people can, you know, yeah, I think also too,
it's a mental thing.
It's, you know, it's, it's sure you say all the time going on that date with that girl
on, on Adderall.
I mean, I realized that that's just, just as potentially dangerous as cocaine.
Don't get me wrong.
Yeah.
You got to be careful with the Addie.
The Addie is, you know, and, uh, and also, uh, people that buy it on the street, it's
being found to have the same fentanyl issues that cocaine is having.
So I mean, shit, man, De Niro's 19 year old son just died of a fentanyl.
Oh, did it come out that that's what it was?
Yeah.
Yep.
Oh Jesus.
Was it his son or grandson?
Son.
Oh God.
That's brutal.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
He, him and Pacino are like in a, in a kid off grandson.
Okay.
Yeah.
I got him mixed up, but you know, just had a kid, a child.
So did De Niro.
Yeah.
It's wild.
Uh, yeah.
Uh, grandson, a fentanyl laced pills.
Jesus Christ, man.
Yeah.
It's wild.
Have I talked about on this show?
I just realized that there's nothing holding me back from saying this.
Uh, have I talked about on this show about the girl who went on the date with Robert
De Niro?
I don't know.
It's a quick tale.
Um, this was a friend of an old friend.
So already, I mean, we're talking about, this isn't somebody in my day to day life, but
I definitely believed her.
She was a very attractive young black woman.
That's important only because De Niro has a very strong preference for black women.
Almost all of his baby mamas, all of his ex wives, all of the people, you know, he has
a thing for young black women, beautiful black women, um, BBWs as they say.
He approaches her on the streets of New York.
He hits on her.
She said, he's very charming, very attractive.
This would have been 20 years ago.
Not that he's not now.
I'm just saying.
Um, he's flirty.
He's kind.
He says, you want to, you want to go up to my hotel room, have a drink?
He has a great view of the city.
She's like, I kind of knew what was going on, but it was Robert De Niro.
She goes up to his hotel room.
They get in the room.
He's just as charming, just as kind.
She's like, do you mind if I take a quick shower?
I've been walking around the city all day.
He's like, do what you got to do.
There's a, there's a robe and slippers and anything you want to do to feel comfortable.
I'll just be out here.
She's like, thank you so much.
But like, you know, she knows it's all she goes in.
She takes the shower.
She comes out of the bathroom and like a broad underwear, kind of
sexy, getting ready to go.
And Robert De Niro is completely naked.
Lying on the bed, sucking his own Dick.
I don't believe this.
I don't, I'm sorry.
That's okay.
And, and by the way, anyone listening is welcome to not believe it.
As I said, I didn't know this girl.
Well, however, I did not in any way doubt this girl's story.
And to me, at the time the girl was like 25, a girl bragging about fucking some
65 year old man that she had known for three minutes is just not really a story
she needs to tell, you know, although people lie about all sorts of shit.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm saying, I believe this in my heart.
She had the details down.
She said he's sucking his own Dick.
And she was like, Oh, Hey, and he's like, come on over here, you know?
And that was maybe his move.
She didn't ask him about it.
That's maybe how he gets hard.
She didn't ask him about it, but she's like, he's a very short man.
And it was just like, honestly, it looked like some sort of acrobatic move.
And he was nailing it was sucking his Dick and they had sex.
She said it was very nice.
He was very kind to her.
She left and that was it.
Um, take it or leave it, but it's a fascinating tale.
If that's how Robert gets himself ready to fuck, I bought it.
What lens credence to it is that she's telling it like, Hey, isn't that crazy?
That's just what happened and not going, what a fucking loser, right?
You know, all right.
No, I mean, look, I can't, I don't, I can't speak for all women, but I feel
like if you come out and the guy you're about to hook up with is sucking his own
Dick, you know, unless you're a, an extreme and strange homophobe where you find that
some sort of, uh, off putting thing, I can't imagine you'd be anything but impressed.
You know, it just seems like something you're rarely see.
Fair enough.
I, uh, I, I, I left a few things off the table about what I did this weekend.
One of them was I did suck my own Dick.
Okay.
I should have come clean that sooner.
I didn't think now that I know you won't judge me, I'm telling you that's what I did.
When I was in the depths of puberty and this was a story that I told to the
always sunny guys and it came so close to making it in the show and I begged them
not to cause it now I would love it, but it just felt too personal and intimate at
time, but I used to with my mom's ab roller, uh, you'd have to look up what
even those are some of you younger folks, but I would put my legs up into the
ab roller, which would bring my crotch very close to my face and I would spend
days in this uncomfortable stretch with the end goal of, of trying to suck my own
Dick.
Now, what I didn't realize is you can't be hard and get into this position
because it's deeply uncomfortable, but I was eventually able to touch lips to
tip at about age 13 that the part of having the Dick into my mouth is what
makes me not be intrigued by the thought of coming in my own mouth.
I could vomit right now thinking about it, but for some reason, like, especially
when you spend so much time trying to get your Dick in your mouth, um, any sort
of morals or decorum or whatever's keeping you, whatever's holding you back
here, Joe, you're just driven by that manly urge of just wanting to fucking do
it just to prove it to yourself.
And I got it there.
I never got it there enough where I would have been able to like suck myself to
but, um, I recommend the AB roller as, as a tool that can really help if that's a
goal of yours.
And I think a lot of young perverts going through puberty would, would have tried
anything to make this happen for themselves.
All right.
Fair enough.
I also thought for several years that a blow job was a woman blowing on your
penis.
I mean, I was, I was pretty out of touch.
Literally.
That's not a joke.
I thought someone told me that on the bus and I believed it just blindly for
years.
I wasn't laughing at a disbelief.
I was, you know, uh, I knew it wasn't a joke.
Um, let's go to that movie corner, by the way, Rex Reed, the review is
underwhelming, but Rex Reed said the title I enjoyed the boogeyman.
The only thing scary is how bad this movie is right to the point.
That's the, the, unfortunately, the reviews are as scathing as I wanted it to be.
Man fucking sucked, man.
I mean, I fucking suck.
Where does Rex Reed, uh, publishes reviews?
The observer.
That's okay.
No wonder.
I don't know what the fuck is.
Okay.
Um, all right.
I would like to start with just the most delightful surprise I had this week,
which was yesterday.
I got my one day of sickness.
I really did feel like shit.
I'm going to just lay here on the couch.
And I was like, I want to binge something.
What's, what's like a whole season I could watch today and Amazon prime.
I hate to shout them out because the WGA is wanting all of us to be posting
about Amazon crime.
That's an email we got like do wait, do this guys.
Hashtag Amazon crime.
You know, like guys, we've been out of work.
Did Fran Dresher's been out of work for 65 days here?
No, she's sag.
Oh, she's sag.
That's right.
Yeah.
I get, cause I get really convincing voicemails from her.
That I need to be aware of what's going on in the Hamptons, making
money, doing something else.
Should I, that people, I mean, look, people have been out of work now.
And I'm being just the writers.
No one, no one else has taken this hit, but the writers, we've been out of work
now 65 days and when you get stuff like this, like guys, don't forget to use
hashtag Amazon crime.
It, it just makes me very frustrated.
I know you can't say anything negative about the writers guild and I know they
won't even speak to us at this point, the, the studios.
So what can we really do?
You just feel like we can do more than this.
You know, it's, it's very frustrating.
Anyway, that these strikes set, you know, they have consequences.
There's no question about it.
Um, but I was sitting at home and on, for Amazon prime day, which is, I guess this
week, they had all these channels that you could get two months of for 99 cents each.
Then you have to remember to cancel them.
Of course, at that two months, I always just write it in my calendar.
Easy.
But I saw stars for 99 cents a month for two months.
Please do this for yourself to watch the new season of party down.
Uh, Joe, have you seen, are you a fan?
I remember the old show.
Yeah, I haven't seen all of them, but I always liked it.
I was, I was very funny.
I fucking loved it.
It started around the same time as always sunny.
And obviously always sunny went on to much, much greater success.
But the two shows had very similar sensibilities.
Uh, party down was always sort of more realistic, just about kind of sad caterers
who are in LA and surrounded by their dreams, but never quite get there.
And it gave birth to a lot of people who became the heavy hitters in comedy.
Um, Adam Scott, Jane Lynch, Jennifer Coolidge, Megan Mullally, uh, the list
goes on and on Lizzie Kaplan, who I have always loved and I think first saw on
this show, I really, really like her.
Um, Kent, the great Ken Marino, who really steals the show and they have
many, many great, yeah, many great guest stars, Kevin Hart and like a huge
people would come on the show all the time.
This is the show that really put Jane Lynch like on the map.
For sure.
Yeah.
Um, so anyway, I knew they were doing it again.
I was very excited.
I didn't know it was only six episodes, but to tell you how great it was, and
maybe I was delirious off that quill, that night quill day quill combo, but.
I groaned so hard.
I was so devastated when there was only six episodes of this show.
What's the last time you had that experience with anything where you
were devastated, there wasn't more of it.
Yeah.
Um, and I get it because these people have all become huge stars now.
And I get that that was an arrested development thing where
it was probably hard to schedule.
But I, man, I hope they are able to somehow do this for more.
It felt like kind of the end because already the show was canceled.
So who knows, but it's so fucking funny.
And it's funny much in the same way that we talked about how
Indiana Jones affected us.
They dive into what these people's actual lives would look like if they
add another 20 years of extreme disappointment and depression about
their careers and where they are in life.
So like Adam Scott, who now can be an annoying presence in things.
It tapped into why I fucking loved him in the step brothers party down era.
And, you know, I don't know what happened to the guy, but he, he is back.
He is, he's now freshly divorced.
Like the kids don't like him.
He doesn't seem to like his kids.
It's like that weatherman Nicholas cage kind of thing where he's
disgusted with his own kids half the time.
All right.
Uh, the Ken Marino character is living in a van.
He, he is homeless and sneaks into these parties to take
showers in the people's homes.
And in a, in a truly hilarious episode, he comes down and these
people are so rich that he recognizes this very hard to find shampoo.
And he's like, wait a minute.
You also use this shampoo.
It's really, when you get six episodes, it's that BBC thing, you know,
it's like the office, they pack so much laughs and so much really British style
humor, the humor of embarrassment into these people, they're going for the huge
laughs they're going for, uh, we got Ken Marino in one of these episodes with
food poisoning, but trying to put a good face on it and get out there and do his
job, even though you know, at some point in this episode that this man is going
to violently shit his pants, which just, it to me creates the best kind of comedy
suspense.
Um, it's, it's a comedy show, not afraid to go for fart noises, diarrhea sounds.
Well, it had me howling.
I can't recommend it highly enough.
Everybody is bringing their egg in, but the stands out stand out, uh, is Marino
who is just batting a million.
Um, and it's got kind of fun cameos without being distracting about it.
Like, um, Quinta Brunson and so forth.
Uh, Martin star is hilarious on it.
And the guy, Ryan Hansen, um, who was in the original is now a movie star, but
everybody else has this very shitty, shitty careers and Hansen has to come back
and cater with them because he just got canceled.
Oh, that's good.
All right.
It's great.
It's it's R rated.
It's hilarious.
Megan Malali is fucking hilarious.
I, I can't speak highly enough.
Joe, what do you got?
I watched Sarah Silverman's new special, someone to love.
Saw it.
It's just not good.
I don't know.
It's fine.
It's got a few moments in it that I'm like, yeah, that's kind of funny.
She's, it's not, it's not that she's not funny.
She Sarah Silverman's very funny.
We're all very aware of that and she's very talented.
Um, there's just, I, and I want to tread lightly here cause I'm, my friend is, is
her boyfriend and she's always been nice to me when I meet her and stuff.
She's nice.
Like she's a nice person.
Um, and I think she's obviously cemented her place in comedy as, as, as a, uh,
one of the icons or whatever for, for over the years, but I just don't know
who the person is anymore.
Like I want it more out of this.
I'm like, you've had so much controversy with backlash and having
to apologize for things or not having to, but choosing to apologize for
things and you talk so much about your own personal growth and all of these
things, and I wanted to see some of that in the special, especially when the
special very much delved into social commentary.
Like this was not a typical Sarah Silverman special.
It was funny all the way through.
Like it was jovial.
It's not like she's up there getting poignant and having like these deep
moments, but she's talking about like the patriarchy and sexism and things like that.
And, and I'm like, talk abortion rights and I'm like, talk about your thing.
Like talk about the shit you've gone through and like what you've learned,
you know, and, and what, like that seems to be important to you.
And it's just not there.
And it's just a pet peeve of mine, I guess, with people who seem to be in
quotes, learning lessons, you know, it's, there are a lot of famous people out
there that, that are, that seem to be learning lessons cause they're constantly
telling us on Twitter, how they're learning lessons and how we all need to
be learning lessons and yet every time they have a chance to really, now maybe
she does on her podcast, I don't know, but I just feel like every time this
was a major, it, this was a major opportunity for this person to explore
this and there was just none of it there.
It was just more of here's what the right side of history is.
If you don't think this, you're not really thinking straight.
She was more balanced in all of it in the approach night that I had
thought she would might be.
And you know, okay, fine.
But I think if you're going to take that route, when we all are very aware of
these public slip ups you've had and, and, and conflicts you've had, and you're
not going to address any of that, you're just going to address the people that
you think are wrong about things.
Um, uh, I don't know.
I maybe I'm not being fair.
Maybe I need to see it again, but it just, it was okay.
It was just like, okay.
It was a lot of, a lot of, okay.
Um, and, uh, I don't know.
That's what I feel like a lot of these comedy specials are now was why
millennials was so refreshing.
Cause I was like, no, man, he's like talking about the thing and
he's going straight at it.
And yeah, yeah, it was really great to see him go from being a joke machine
to being more personal and it was great to see a comic do 90 minutes and feel
like he was, he had much more to say.
And they were like pulling them off the stage, you know, I liked
Sarah Silverman special more than you did, but it definitely lacked a
certain urgency.
I would say that a special that I'm my, I might like a special to have.
And I had seen her do it at Largo, um, on a very funny night of comics
that, that Pete hosted and she did most of the special and it killed, but it
was, it felt like she was kind of working it out and that's sort of how
the special felt too.
Um, I don't know if that's what you're saying that it lacked a little through
line or that's a little, I don't need it.
But yeah, no, I don't, I don't necessarily need a through line, but that's part of
it is she does a special every five years.
She's only done three, if I'm not mistaken.
And it's like, and what I, what I would assume you feel, Joe, what I would assume
you feel I'm just helping you out here, especially because you have much more
chance of running into her, but she's one of the great joke writers.
She's just, she's an incredible joke writer.
Um, so for me, seeing one that felt a little more tossed off was maybe at
times frustrating, but there was enough great jokes that it carried me to the end.
She had some, she had some good, she had some good moments in it.
Um, I think I'm more disappointed that, yeah, there was a looseness to it
where I was like, well, she's always going to be loose, but I was like, it
seems, it seems like this could be punchier for the amount of time you take
to put something like this together.
But, but more importantly than that, I just was like, you're somebody
that's always talking about the virtue stuff, talk about it on here, which
you're doing, but also talk about your slip ups because goddamn, doesn't
that humanize you now and you're hitting it from multiple angles.
And I just didn't, I just didn't see much of that.
So it was okay.
I don't think anybody's going to watch it and be like, fuck this.
Like, you know, you, you might enjoy it.
You might be a little underwhelmed, but it was just, it was just okay.
I guess that's what I'm saying.
Yeah.
Um, I generally was not going to, and I'd never do them on letterbox just
cause I at least run in company circles generally, but it can be
good to talk about this shit.
I watched John early special on max.
Oh, how was it?
Great.
I mean, John early is one of the funniest people on earth.
I'm a big, uh, huge fan.
Huge fan and, uh, and his sketches as well with, with caperlant.
Right.
First time I did standup caperlant went on before me and died a horrible death.
Cause it's not for everybody.
That's one of the things I like about, I know.
Oh, sure.
I mean, but, but yeah, she was, uh, that night she was not for the crowd.
That's for sure.
This was very early in her career, but yeah, I got to see her bomb
and then see her destroyed, but.
Uh, John special is great.
It's just half music.
He's doing, um, what's the Neil Young song.
No idea.
Um, it's a beautiful song, but John early does like a.
Straightforward cover of that.
He does a straightforward cover of a Britney Spears song.
He does a lot of music.
That's entertaining.
But why, why are you doing covers?
Joe, that's what, that's what I'm saying.
It's, um, and I've heard nothing but raves about it and I'm, all I'm
going to do is add to the rave.
I had a great time.
However, um, when the show leans into the comedy, his standup, which, you
know, is a very, very revealing and hilarious and sharp and incisive look.
At his generation, he's maybe a little younger than me, but our generation ish,
um, of people obsessed with social media and obsessed with their phones
and obsessed with celebrities.
And it's really dark and really weird.
And I laughed out loud multiple times.
He's, he's a very, very gifted, uh, storyteller and comedian.
So while I enjoyed him performing straightforward versions of six to eight
songs, my frustration with the special is I obviously wanted more comedy.
Then again, it felt very balanced.
He does some, a few scripted scenes backstage that are all really, really
funny too, because he's a very funny comedic actor, obviously, if you've
seen search party, et cetera.
But, um, yeah, the balance felt a little off to me.
Like the, the sketch part brief, too brief, but hilarious, the
standup awesome at like transcendent at times, hilarious, perfect.
Um, but then six full songs performed without a real comedic twist on them.
Seems odd, but you know, that's, that's my review.
My review is only, it's, it's genius enough to make me wish that there was
more of that and less of just singing.
That's all.
There enough.
Um, I, uh, I have one more here.
I watched the New York times presents the legacy of Jay Dilla.
Jay Dilla.
Where's that Hulu?
I canceled my stream.
Christ.
I can't remember.
I think it was on max, I think.
Um, uh, if you're unfamiliar with Jay Dilla, Jay Dilla is one of the
most iconic producers in hip hop, uh, who sadly we lost at a very young age.
I don't even think he, I think it was in his thirties.
Um, he, uh, very sick and, uh, and, and passed, unfortunately, but, um,
a very iconic producer.
Uh, in fact, I have a book that was written about him.
That's I still haven't read, but it's apparently amazing.
Uh, and, uh, he, he, he brought a very unique approach to production and he.
You know, uh, uh, created a style of production that, that people had not
done prior to him and that it sounds like if you watch the documentary,
not a lot of people have done since like, for instance, playing the drum beat
pattern by hand through an entire track and changing it as you go the entire time,
instead of just making a perfect four bar loop that goes through, uh, a drum loop,
you know, uh, that's why it's called that.
Um, if I may real quick, if you, if you go to Amazon crime,
they have donuts, which is, you know, uh, a masterful collection of beats,
basically in samples and et cetera.
Um, but that's most people would steer you towards donuts as his best work.
And you can get that in a really cool special, uh, vinyl right now for like 1299
at Amazon crime, go pick that up.
Oh, that's very cool.
The, uh, he's produced, you know, he, he got his first big break with
tribe called quest and, uh, he and Q -tip and Alicia, he'd Muhammad started the
Uma or Emma, uh, production group and they produced a lot of stuff for tribe
and many other artists, Jay Dilla produced for, I'm just looking at his
production, uh, you know, the far side, um, uh, Fife Q -tip, Kanye,
common day law, you know, um, he, he was just, you know, he was a mastermind
and he was again, he's an iconic, iconic producer in the hip hop genre
that, uh, that certainly left a huge mark and, um, and a huge, uh, gap after
he left, after he was gone.
Uh, and the documentary just kind of gets into it, you know, it's what
you'd expect it's it gets into his earlier life, how he gets his start,
uh, him breaking through, uh, his rise to fame, uh, his sickness and then his
passing and, uh, you know, uh, you know, the, like, like most documentaries like
this, the, the quote mismanagement of his estate and quote, uh, which is a
controversial topic.
If you watch this, you'll see, um, but for the most part, it's, it's all
positives.
It's very few negatives, certainly nothing negative about him, just
meaning negatives about the situation, like since he's been gone with the money
and that sort of thing.
Um, but, uh, it's, it's just a really wonderful documentary.
It's very uplifting and, uh, it's inspiring.
It's as, as if you're somebody who appreciates art or create art, creates
art yourself, it's, it's a great watch to see somebody just kind of come at it
from their heart, their perspective, who they are doing their own thing.
I love that at his height, he's like, I'm not leaving Detroit anymore.
And he's like producing, I believe in his, the house where his mom lives.
And he's like, this is home.
This is where I'm doing it.
And tough shit if you don't like it.
And you're like, that kind of stuff is just so inspiring to me.
And this is pre, you know, Hey, you can live anywhere now because of the
internet, you know, uh, it's not that time period.
And the fact that he did that and remained entirely relevant is incredible.
So, um, watch it if you can.
It's great.
Where do we watch it, Joe?
I like, well, you had asked, I think it was on max, but I can't remember.
Oh, on max.
Okay.
Right.
Sorry.
I think that's all right.
When you said it was that New York times, I always think that's on Hulu, but maybe
I know things change all the time.
It might've been.
Okay.
I got no, I'll look it up because I want to say, I actually do want to say it.
Uh, I rewatched in glorious 4k Ronin, which just dropped in the 4k and I had seen the
reviews and they were like, uh, you know, this would be like reference quality.
Like when you bring friends over to, to explain the glories of 4k, you can show them
these car chases in 4k and I'll be damned if that wasn't the truth.
I really liked Ronin in theaters.
Do you say oof?
Cause you don't like it, Joe.
I, I, it's one, it's like Blade Runner.
It's like, God damn it.
Why don't I love this movie?
De Niro, like hard nose cops shit, uh, written by, co -written by David Mamet.
I'm like every part of this I should love.
And I just, God damn it.
I can't get it.
Wow.
I find it so boring.
Um, and I don't know.
Frankenheimer, you know, the director of like seconds, Manchurian candidate,
all these, all these classic movies.
I love John Frankenheimer as a director.
This is one of his last greats.
I even like fucking reindeer games, but it's a story for another time.
Um, I love De Niro in this.
He's really sort of, it's right around the casino times.
Like he's still, you know, looking like a young man to some degree.
Um, so this is, and I think they took this from pulp fiction and a lot of other things,
but it's a briefcase that nobody knows what's in it.
Irish terrorists want it.
The Russian mob wants it.
And we've got our team and we know that there's a mole inside.
It's a pretty, you know, the general setup for a heist type movie.
I love Stellan Skarsgård in this movie is like the ruthless dork of the group.
I love Jean Renault.
I love Natasha McKellan.
I love Jonathan Price.
I love Sean Bean.
I love the whole cast.
They got Katarina Witt figure skater fig figuring into the plot of the film.
Um, I don't know.
I had a blast with it.
I liked it more than I remembered liking it in high school when I was like,
sweet, these car chases are awesome, but it can't be overstated.
These are some of the best car chases in history.
Uh, I feel like mission impossible even kind of stole from one of the chases that they do,
which is against the traffic.
Um, it's just incredible.
You know, my friend said he bought the Audi from, from the movie.
He was like, I must have that car.
Like that's the only time he ever had that experience.
Um, and I get it.
If you have a 4k player, if I've convinced you, I would definitely pick this one up.
I would definitely give this movie another chance.
I saw Ken Hanley raving about it on a letter box.
If you guys don't follow him, give him a follow.
And, um, yeah, I love this movie.
And I think the mammot dialogue is a big selling point on it, Joe.
I would give it another chance unless you've tried many times.
I'll give it another chance.
You're right about those car chases and they're fucking awesome.
Just fucking awesome.
De Niro, uh, exceptional actor that he is.
Yeah.
He's the only actor I've ever seen do this.
And, and I remember seeing the cart, watching the car chase with, uh, with, uh,
Pinkstone, our friend of the pad pod and him saying he was watching De Niro and he goes,
man, that that's what it would be like.
Like if you were in a car chase, you would have to laser focus like that.
You have to be so concentrated, like, and that's how De Niro plays it.
And it, I do remember thinking that that was really brilliant.
Um, yeah, and it's just kind of as a, as Hanley was pointing out,
it shows you a lot of the aftermath and like the realities of the car chase.
Like it felt a lot like, um, you know, like French connection
or what, you know, it's always cited now as one of the all the time, right?
Car chase movies.
And I think it is that, but I also think the plot is sort of twisty enough
and fun enough and there's enough cool locations that compared to what we get now.
I think that when you go back sometimes and watch an action movie from like 1998,
like this, it's just starts to seem like a masterpiece because they wouldn't make
a movie unless it was ready to go back then, you know,
like Ronan makes sense.
The story makes sense.
The characters make sense.
The actors are great.
And it's a cohesive piece of work.
Like, you know, it's just compared to what we get now.
Um, it really, it read so much better today compared to the action movies of today,
because I just feel like we get a lot of action scenes that are impossible to follow
impossible to even pretend to care about.
I'm looking it up as we, as we speak.
It's I'm going to maybe I'll just buy it and give it a shot since the 4k looks so good.
But I just found out as in trying to find this right now, see if it was streaming.
Did you know Keno has a streamer service called Keno now?
No, I did not.
But I wound up buying all their four kids.
The marathon man is probably my favorite transfer I've seen.
That's a keynote.
Keno now is a streaming service.
Oh, dude, I'm on here now.
I'm downloading this tonight because they got, it's the only place you can rent
the Frankenheimer version of the Iceman Cometh.
Oh, nice.
Okay.
And I'm like, what the fuck is who's the star of that?
Lee Marvin.
But apparently Ebert gave it four out of four stars.
It was the highest possible achievement in cinema.
Wow.
You got Burt Reynolds heat right on the home page here of Keno now.
This is odd.
By the way, I think our next one we might need to tackle, Joe,
is rent a cop with Burt Reynolds and Liza Minnelli.
I'd watch it happily.
Are you still watching Arrested Development?
I am.
I just, I got sidetracked.
I jump in here.
I jump in there for an episode.
But has Liza been on?
She's on it.
She's very funny on it.
She's underrated because she's, everyone's like, oh, she's playing herself.
It's like, no, she's still got impeccable timing.
If you can play with these people at her level, she's got amazing comic timing.
She's a great, very gifted actress.
She did a scene in season two where she come, the gag in season two,
she's just come home from the hospital where they fixed her vertigo.
And they're doing like shots of her trying to get into the hospital with vertigo.
And she does a full fucking fall.
Like a full fall onto the fucking ground at like 65 or whatever,
how old she is when she's shooting this thing.
I'm like, Jesus Christ.
I thought she was incredible on that show.
I really did.
Yeah, she's great.
And the fact that she's fucking a buster.
Yeah.
It's a while.
Have you gotten to Martin Short yet?
No, still not yet.
I keep getting, there's just, I started watching and just like that.
Yeah, it's something.
It's really, it is something.
I can't get through two episodes of it.
It makes me so mad that I can't get through it.
And then it's always something.
Sonny, I watch every episode.
Sonny's really grabbed my attention again this season.
I just can't, I had lost faith after last season and I,
and the season before that wasn't great.
And the fact that they're now five in
and every episode except one has been laugh out loud funny.
And the one that was bad wasn't like, like cringe bad.
It was just like, yeah, that one was kind of whatever.
But this last one where they go to the risky rats pizzeria,
I was like, God damn it.
This is awesome.
Yeah.
That's my buddy, Rob Rosell.
Very talented, very funny man.
But I, listen, I love the show.
I have very little bad to say about it.
I think even when it swings and misses, it swings on a level that other shows don't.
They've gotten no recognition.
It's not just because I know them.
I don't know them that well.
I just think they're turning out comedy at such a high level after so long
that you got to just give them props.
You know, they, to me, this season was just as funny as something from 10 years ago.
It's been on forever.
It's, it's like a staple now.
And, uh, yeah, it's great.
I couldn't agree more.
Love it.
Yeah.
The, uh, the, uh, yeah, that thing in the last episode where the, the,
the duck doesn't stutter and D's being like, shut the fuck up.
I'm like, Jesus Christ.
Like they're really going for it.
It's really, really funny, man.
Anyway, uh, are you, I don't have any more for the corner unless you do.
I'm ready to talk.
No, no, I'm all good.
Renfield speak about the opposite of what we're saying.
Not funny.
I, I brought this up to Joe, uh, today because I was, I flipped over to Peacock.
I was looking for something and I realized that I had watched Renfield like a month
and a half ago and I was like, I'm not going to be the only one who had to watch Renfield.
I'm, I, I need to turn this into a positive and get to talk about it on the show.
So Joe, uh, very kindly agreed to watch it today.
I'm sure he deeply regrets it, but it's a piece of shit.
It sucks.
Nobody sets out to make a piece of shit.
Pinkstone went wrong here.
He saw it in the theater and he was like, dude, it sucks.
And I was like, yeah, I'm not going to see it.
Like, I don't care.
And then when you were like, look, it's on Peacock.
It's 90 minutes.
I was like, I'll watch it.
I don't give a fuck.
And, uh, it started, it starts pretty cool.
Like I was like, oh, this beginning is good.
He's in the support group.
That's a funny concept that he's in a support group for co -dependence
and abusive relationships.
I think that's funny.
Yeah.
It's like that, that right there, you're like, okay, I get somebody walked
in and pitched this off that I got it.
But where it goes, I mean, go ahead.
I'm sorry, but the opening, you're like, okay, this is a good cold open.
Now what else you got?
And the answer is just anything but the kitchen sink.
When he shows in that opening, when it cuts away to Dracula and it's the
fight that Dracula is having, it's actually a pretty cool Dracula fight.
And you're like, turns into the bats at one point and the smoke and I'm like,
this is pretty cool.
And yeah.
And then when it's hard, it's hard for me to get upset about CGI in a world
where all of our movies are CGI, but this one bothered me a lot.
The fight scenes had that feeling, just the opposite of what I was saying
with Ronan, the feeling that I'm watching a video game that I'm not playing.
And that's how I feel about these CGI people coming at each other.
I just don't give a shit.
When he walks out of the meeting, when cage is front and center,
at least it's compelling.
I'll give you that.
Yeah.
When, when he, when Nick, Nick, what the fuck's his name?
Nicholas Hoult, Holt, when he walks out of the meeting at the beginning,
and he says, I figured out a way to serve my master
and also help the people in my support group.
I bring him their abusers.
I bring him their abuse.
And I was like, okay, this is a good setup.
This is a good setup.
Like, where's it going now?
And the first moment where it was, there was, I was like, uh -oh,
we got some problems here.
He goes to like abduct this abusive boyfriend
of a girl that's in the meeting with him.
And the, the, the plot of the scene, the, the scene is,
is that the boyfriend's a drug dealer and he's stolen all this cocaine from a crime lord.
And they think that Nicholas Holt is a hit man showing up to kill him.
And he's not.
And he goes, and he goes, what do you, who do you think I am?
And he goes, I thought you're a hit man here to kill us.
And he goes, no, I am something far worse.
And he is kind of sinister.
And I'm like, this is okay.
I'm into this.
And then the actual hit man shows up and it's like a Batman villain.
It's like the, this huge guy in a hood that like uses special knives.
And when that happened, I was like, wait a minute, wait, what's going on here?
Like this, this is clearly supposed to be the real world
where Renfield and Dracula are way out of place.
And the only two unique, you know, oddball supernatural, whatever people, whatever in
this world, you've got this ridiculous hooded like sumo wrestler guy coming in.
And I was like, wait, this is way more comic booky than I thought.
This was, I don't understand.
And then from there, they introduced this fucking subplot with Ben Schwartz
being a crime Lord who's famous around the city and his city runs the, his family runs
the city and they've got the cops on their payroll and Awkwafina plays this cop who's
just basically like a traffic cop, but she's going to take down the crime family.
And she, they, they, she immediately knows who this crime Lord is, but they don't really
establish that how she knows him or that they're famous.
And it becomes this sort of Gotham city thing.
And you're like, what the fuck is going on?
Like, I don't understand.
Like what is, and why am I now watching a movie with a major plot line of Ben?
Guys, you had it.
Renfield in the support group, finding the bad people to feed to Dracula.
That's the movie.
Why am I watching a B plot with Ben Schwartz as a crime boss?
This is not.
It would seem like them saying, because this is what I could see a studio saying,
okay, you've got Nicolas Cage and Nicholas Holt, two white guys.
Let's add some diversity.
So they force in a plot, but then didn't get a diverse actor.
They cast another white guy, Ben Schwartz.
So you're just left with this pointless add -on story.
That's my guess of how this came to be, because why else would this even be added to this movie?
We all came to see Nicolas Cage play Dracula and suddenly we're spending an inordinate
amount of time with Ben Schwartz and his mom.
A lot of time.
I mean, it's, it's almost outweighing the Dracula bits.
Yeah.
It's almost like as a cop, then you're like, wait a minute.
Are they trying to convince us Aquafina and Nicholas Holt are romantically involved?
And then they go for that.
Yeah.
And you're just not buying it.
You just, you're not, they don't have any chemistry.
No, they do this.
They used to do chemistry tests, you know, like they used to cast movies.
Like they'd say, well, let's make sure the couple is believable together.
This movie feels like these two shook hands and then had to make out.
It's like, it just, it doesn't work.
There's nothing between them.
The final scene is them in the support group meeting and they just walk out
side by side without touching each other.
They never kiss.
Are they just friends?
What the fuck is going on here?
This doesn't make sense.
And then even the producers at some point were like, I'm not buying this guys.
Let's, let's abort.
I took the, I took the Schwartz plot line as they said, we're going to give
Renfield a love interest that love interest for some reason is going to be a cop.
And not just, and they make it a cop.
Why?
Because then they could do a thing where the cop is, is onto Renfield and, and he's
got to deceive his girlfriend as she is hunting somebody that's murdering people in the city.
But they do that for six seconds and immediately resolve it.
So that's pointless.
And then they team up and work through it.
Now Renfield has a girlfriend and the girlfriend needs something to do where
she's not defined by Renfield.
So they give her this plot of time, trying to take down this crime family.
This thing could have been, he falls in love with the girl from the fucking meeting he's in.
Right.
Yeah.
But then they go, no, but we'll add tension.
Cause then it'll date a cop and that'll be tense for this guy.
And it's like, well, it would have been if you did anything with it, but you don't.
So it doesn't make any sense.
Um, you're, you're watching Aquafina in a Paul Blart uniform.
Shooting, having shootouts with a crime family led by Ben Schwartz.
I mean, this is, this is big chunks of the film.
Yeah.
Your two, the two leads, two of your three leads in this movie are known for voicing
puppets and other movies.
Here they are firing guns at each other.
You're, you're, you don't know what's going on.
Uh, cage cage is funny.
He's the only funny part.
He's funny when he's go, you know, that thing where he's going,
I don't think I asked for too much.
A busload of cheerleaders.
Am I wrong?
Like he's, he plays it like that.
He's as funny as anybody could have been in that role.
He's, he's really funny, but you're left wondering where he is the whole time.
When he goes, well, this is clearly they got cage for two days and he's like,
here's my guys and they're like, oh, it'll be fun because it'll be vampires.
You realize, oh, oh, fuck.
I'm watching a Nicholas Holt Aquafina romance with Ben Schwartz as the villain.
I've been duped, you know, that, that scene is funny when cage is in Red Renfield's
apartment and he's going, and he's going, where were you?
Where was my dinner?
I guess I don't get my dinner tonight.
And Renfield's like, yeah, you know what happened?
And he's lying and in cage going, oh yeah, okay.
Okay.
It's funny.
It's, it's, it's, it's very, it's written very much like, like, like the, like the boss
in office space doubting Ron Livingston or something.
It's very funny.
But those parts are, as you've already said, few and far between
um, the makeup effects on cage when he's like disintegrated and needs to be revived
were pretty cool, but you know, they, they sit in that for two minutes and then it's done.
And then the rest of the movie, there's John, there's John Wick style fight scenes, like the
one in the hotel complex where there's like, again, CGI out the ass, which I get, I think
was clearly a pandemic movie, but there's this big John Wick fight scene with bouncing around
between, you know, and you're like, what am I watching guys?
Is it a comic book movie?
Is it John Wick?
Is it a sitcom?
And weirdly where it's most successful is as a sitcom with Holt and cage.
Yeah, that's where it works.
And you go from there to the, to the, uh, the support group and you got yourself a funny
little multicam sitcom.
That's what I'd like to watch.
But unfortunately I'm watching a 90 minute padded to the gills action movie because they
got caged for two days for a million dollars.
This would be a great, what we do in the shadows about Renfield and, and, and, and,
Oh yeah, exactly.
Um, the, I mean about Renfield and Dracula and, and then it gets really confused.
This is where it gets really confusing.
And I want to say something also about the style of jokes in the movie.
It gets really confusing because when Renfield tells the story of how he met Dracula,
they superimpose Nicholas cage and Nicholas Holt into the 1932 Dracula.
So you go, okay, this is a sequel to that movie.
That's what they're saying.
Then every time Nicholas Holt says Dracula to somebody, nobody knows what he's talking about.
Okay.
That would make sense in the universe of the 1932 Dracula.
Then all of a sudden Aquafina hears Dracula and goes, wait, Dracula is your boss.
And you're like, what fucking reality is this?
I don't know.
Like what's going on here?
There's zigzagging all over the place.
This thing was, this thing was noted to death.
This guy, this has studio notes.
Oh yeah.
I totally, it's, it can't decide.
It's just, it's a hard movie to like, you know, it's just like it's hyperactive and annoying.
And the only times it really kind of settles down and finds a comfortable groove
are with cage, but you're not getting much.
The joke style of the movie really bothers me outside of the cage humor.
It's, I don't know what the term is for it, but I would call it overly explanatory comedy.
It's a hackneyed device that I've seen a lot over the years.
At one point was sort of funny, but it's the thing where they go, like in the beginning,
there's the woman in the group is crying about what an asshole her boyfriend is.
And she goes, and I know that this is way down on the gripes list, but he loves ska.
That's a funny joke.
And then they go, everybody's good.
All the people in the meetings are going ska.
Is that the shit with all the horns and everything?
It's like kind of a funny bit.
And then she goes for the final punchline.
That is a gross oversimplification of what the music has done for the,
what is happening to me?
And you go, it's such a bad joke.
It's like the thing in black mirror will sell.
Salma Hayek goes, I am, I am somebody who speaks broken English.
Who's also dyslexic with a question on understanding of the it's stop it.
That over explanatory bit.
It's so bad.
It's terrible.
It's never funny anymore.
Yeah.
Again, it was sort of funny at one time.
That ska bit is so much funnier if the final punchline is just her going.
Yes, it's the one with the horn.
He sucks.
Like that's just so much funnier.
It's simple.
It's what you would actually say.
And you left.
There's another part where Nicholas Holt is explaining what Dracula is to the group
without saying Dracula.
And he said, I forget he says a guy.
Oh, one of the members of the group.
They're all guessing like, let me guess he does X, Y, and Z and Nicholas.
Yeah.
That's what he does.
Oh, let me guess.
He also does this.
And all of these things that describe an abusive person are applicable to Dracula.
And then one guy goes, he can control rats, which is kind of funny.
And the guy, the moderator of the group goes, he's on medication.
Don't pay attention to that.
And you're like, again, you're the moderator of a co -dependent.
You would never say that.
It's this over -explanatory thing.
We're going to talk literally.
We're going to talk in the most literal sense possible.
And that's where the joke comes from.
And it's just not funny.
And it's not believable.
And it doesn't sell the joke.
And I hate it.
They also do the hacky fucking thing in this, that running gag.
Shut the fuck up, Kyle.
How many times are we going to do the funny white person name punchline?
Okay, Susan.
You know what I mean?
Oh, my God, man.
That's like all hack from 10 years ago at this point.
Bad.
It's a bad movie.
To me, Joe watched it today.
I hadn't seen it in quite a while.
It came back like a burp.
It came back to haunt me when I thought about it.
But it's so...
I would say the word that if somebody said, okay,
one word on the CinemaScore card on your way out the door,
I would describe it as an exhausting movie.
It was exhausting to watch.
It's exhausting to watch these people try to prop up every scene with energy
by overcompensating with energy.
And just the overall effect being just draining and exhausting.
Boggs.
Way down.
Limp.
Limp like a body sucked dry of its blood by Dracula himself.
Yeah.
In a non -pleasurable way.
Limp and also coming out of a glacial pool.
Not a fan of Renfield.
There's your goddamn July episodes, people.
That's all four of them.
We'll be back in August with Mission Impossible Q &A,
a two -part Q &A episode.
And then most likely this insidious red door picture.
For sure.
I'm not going to plug again.
I plugged on the last two.
But Walsh, if you want to plug, go for it.
I'm not going to keep you from plugging.
No, I got nothing to say.
Check me out on the Good Christian Fun Pod,
talking about the movie Contact.
I think that's a really funny conversation.
A good little adjunct class to the main pod here.
And of course, I'll still be coming out with my solo movie, Corn.
See you all soon.
Follow us on See You in Hell Pod on Instagram for some best of material.
Thank you, Emily, for all you do.
Thank you for all the fans who keep us in business.
Thank you all.
We'll see you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.