Bones app, but your bonus app, but you're fucking
Where is that bonus app?
Pat how are you?
I'm good. I feel pretty
Great about our vocal performance kicking off the show. I thought it was Simon and Garf
More like Simon and barf
Yeah, folks, it's not
Hall and oats over here. This is all oats
on this podcast all
Oats. That's what we should call it actually all oats all the time honey bunches of oats
Joe, did you buy Susperia? I guess that didn't get you my copy so well
Well, first of all folks for the bonus app this week we're doing Susperia. Yeah, we're new one
We're reviewing Susperia as you know the bonus apps feature no segments or plugs. Oh right. It's just straight talk right
I believe but shouldn't we talk about some stuff
I mean, well, yeah, but I mean, we don't do the movie corner really coming in real hot about the experience
We don't do the movie corner. We don't do any of that. Sure. My point is is usually when we review a movie
We review it for about 10 or 15 minutes. Yes
At the end of the episode I feel so confident that we will have so much to say about Susperia that we will
We can fill a lot more of this episode than just that all right
But we don't have to start the review just yet to answer your question though
Did I buy Susperia?
As I hold it yeah brand new blu -ray copy of it in my hand. That's what you're really mad about is that you lost money
No, I actually I
Ordered it okay, so the day that I said okay, I'm gonna watch this tonight so we can review it this week. I went on
To rent it
And it was six bucks on every vent outlet to rent and for some reason that extra dollar really pisses me off
I don't know why
So I go on Amazon. I'm like how much is it on Amazon?
And it's like 18 bucks for the blu -ray. I'm like
It's worth the extra 13 just in case I like it. I agree. I buy any I I never rent a movie. I always buy that so
And it's and it they were offering same -day shipping. I'm like this is perfect
I got it order $20 worth of stuff. I found some shit. I actually needed yeah
Ordered it when I say I buy. I mean rarely. I'm not saying I buy every movie. I watch. Yeah, that's not bragging about my money
Go ahead promise is it'll be here by 8 p .m. Or whatever. Yeah, that's fine. I can keep myself busy to 8 p .m
sure
Busy getting busy probably right yeah getting real busy. Yeah
uh
Up in the hissy sure
Uh, anyway, take the dog out for a walk come back
I and then I go into the app. That's a euphemism right taking the dog out for a walk
Fuck forgetting busy. Yeah, it's all right go. I go into the app and I write taking you forever to drop this on the back porch
drop the package on the back porch right
I take the dog out for a walk sure enough if I get back sticker on the thing delivery attempted you weren't here
Yeah, I'm like what the fuck man
So I call Amazon I'm furious
And I'm like, you know guys
You say same day I put specific instructions on to where to leave the thing
The guy doesn't do it
Uh, you know, and they're like don't worry about it. We'll refund your money
They'll be bringing it back to us if by chance it shows up you do have the option to keep it and we will charge you at that point
I said fine
I wait the rest of the day. It no redelivery attempt. It never shows up right
So like fuck it. I'm just gonna rent it for six bucks. I rent the goddamn thing. I watch it
Next morning I walk outside the fucking box is sitting there and I needed the other two things that I ordered with it
So now I have the blu -ray and I'm like
I'll get into why I don't think I'm going to return it later. Oh
Cuz you secretly loved it
Uh
We got a lot to talk about. We got a lot to talk about but I had interrupted you comedically so many times there with a
With like sex jokes that I thought I had done it one too many times
But right after you said the phrase
I told them to drop the package on my back porch
And I was like god damn it's the juiciest setup yet, but I let you finish your story. Thank you
Thank you, you know dropping a package on somebody's back porch the screams out for a
Sextra Pat I gotta tell you something. This is something I've said my entire life. Sure. I am sex. Oh
Okay, it wafes off of me. I don't even know when I'm speaking that sultry. I don't even know it's coming out of my mouth see
There's another one
Yeah, I think everyone can agree
Joe is sex
Uh, how are you doing? It's good to see you. We had to do our catch -up off bike as usual
Yeah, I mean, I'm literally as I just showed I'm at the point of my life where somebody asked me how you're doing
And I start laughing like the Joker
Like yeah
Well, it's funny. You asked um
You're wearing the jacket of the show
It's probably it's just I don't have to think in the morning when I get out of bed
Okay, you know when you're nearly vomiting each morning you want to just get on something lightweight and quick
You're showing a lot of chest also. I want to point out to the listeners. Yeah, you're welcome
Those buttons go lower each week bad you're welcome
I'm not mad at it. No my
My life is a shambles
You know
Running a network television show for 22 episodes, you know, that's like 12 movies that you're doing in a six -month span and
Well, that's not right. That'd be if movies were an hour
Uh, so it's like six movies it's like six movies in six months. That's outrageous
Uh, and you deal with all the personalities and you deal with all the situations and you know, it's uh
It's a fucking lot. That's all I'll say. I'm exhausted, but we are one week ish
From the day where Joe and I can just frolic through the countryside together like we used to
Unfortunately, my schedule is getting busier now. Joe. So don't tell us. We're uh why do that's hurtful. Why do you say something like that?
We're uh, I mean, I'm hoping we can still go up and get a drink at 9 a .m. or something, you know
Are usual break time tell you what I did the other day and it was glorious. I
So I'm working simultaneously on two screenplays that I spent
A good amount of time outlining over the last few months or whatever. Yes
Outlining if you if you for any script writers out there, you know
sucks
It's fucking horrible
At least fun part. Yeah, so it takes
It takes me a long time to do because I'm not doing it for any staff
I'm just doing it for projects. I want to sell right and so it's hard to motivate so so once I finally got the outlines
Then I was like okay in two months. I'm gonna write this has been my commitment. I'm gonna write two scenes a day
Okay, either one two and one or one of each or whatever
uh, and
I'll have these things done within two months like you know
Which is fine. That's plenty of you know, that's there's that's that's that's quickly enough to get them done
and the other day was the first day and I don't know what pat
I don't know why this never dawned on me that you can do this. Yeah
I took my computer to a cafe sure. I bought a $20 bottle of Pinot Noir
And I sat there and drank it wrote
Sounds beautiful. It was amazing. Which cafe did you go for friends and family? It's a couple blocks away
Yeah, love it. Get the micro bowl next time you're there. It's healthy, but it's also very delicious. I don't go for that micro bowl. Shit
Okay, sorry. I recommended something. I like a big bowl. It's a big bowl. You put some chicken on it. You say Mac
Is it a macro? I think it's a macro. Yeah, there you go. It's a macro bowl. Sorry
um
Yeah, I generally don't
Go out just because I feel very self -conscious and pretentious especially where I live in the Los
Peel of Silver Lake area
Sitting at a place with my laptop. It makes me vaguely uncomfortable
Also, if I'm going to eat something that combination doesn't work food in a laptop. Who said eat you didn't need a goddamn thing
I'm talking about my struggles
Right, but like in terms of sitting at a bar with a drink. I can do it
But I guess what I'd rather do is sit at home and
Really my process and I advise this to any writers who aren't addicted to substances
is to
outline
you know
completely sober
To make sure you've got it locked and loaded
then to
Lay out the scenes so you're seeing headings that you want to write because I find the most annoying part of writing is coming up with the transit cut
Toes the fade -ins and all that shit. It just bothers me. That doesn't bother me. I hate writing the action part
I hate the action comes in covered in sweat. We can tell by the look on his face
He's you know, yeah, and you never know if you're being clear with how you're trying to convey it
But um, I'm too clear. I'm like I'm like up against I'm almost like putting pictures into this script
Yeah, then the director's people don't like that. That'd be annoying too
But I lay out all the scene heading so that I can basically is just like this workbook where I can fill in the blanks
My favorite thing if I have the time is to write boring versions of scenes meaning like okay
Here's what has to happen and I'll write the guy saying like why don't you go to the store with me
Okay, I'll go to the store with you then you go in and lay in jokes
so
Once you have the script kind of written and I usually sip a cocktail while I'm writing a script
Which I think the bar would be a great place
Although I wouldn't limit myself
I would continue ordering drinks or drinking a bottle of wine and the writing gets sloppy some point you got to stop
You lose motivation
but it's it can help you kind of
Go into it and shut off the parts of your brain that need to be shut off to be truly creative
Yeah, you can't get stewed
I mean all those Stephen King did his best work in blackouts, but he did and my truth is I can do a good version of a script
Especially a sitcom script and a couple of days
uh
Good one. I'm really happy with but all my scripts really take off
When I smoke a little weed or take a little edible
Let it start to kick in right be writing like so you're doing actually a lot of solid sober work for about an hour
Especially with an edible, but then as it starts kicking in you're seeing all these amazing jokes and opportunities for jokes
It's almost like playing with steroids, but it's completely legal right and uh for me
Oh, you know not all but a vast majority of my best jokes when I'm just writing a script at home
Are a little altered
I gotta be honest like because it for me my brain is so constantly gabbing on about your bad you suck
Everyone hates you everybody's talking about you
That I can't shut it off unless I get a little high and once I shut it off and my brain's like hey
We got all these sweet jokes over here, baby, and I'm like come on out and play
Uh, I don't have that uh, I find I'm snappier if I'm sober
Sure the and audience for my room of writers. Yeah, I can be on all day and pitch joke
No, I'm home. I'm not on as much. I just mean with dialogue like it comes out of life
It comes out of me a little better if I'm clear headed but I uh, but I don't I don't often drink when I do this
It's just nice to know. It's an option
Uh, and the booze I had like maybe a half a bottle I didn't drink the whole bottle, but I had about half of the bottle and bring it home like on your thumb
What do you mean the bottle or did you just leave it? I coaxed it and took it with me. Oh, okay
Why the fuck would I have left it? I thought it might be funny to see you swinging it with your thumb in the bottle
Is that a thing? Your thumb your thumb is working as a cork so like you're skipping home
With a bottle of wine like that's a picnic. Well the skipping skipping makes it funny
Okay, the thumb alone isn't gonna carry it. I was picturing the skipping so that's why I had to share it with you
Um, but I the the booze for me and coffee can sometimes do this too
Is a good uh sort of anchor to get going right, you know like to so you're sitting there
It's an activity basically, you know, sometimes I'll do it with big bags of candy too. Sure, but uh
But once I get rolling like now I only did that on Monday and then every day that I wrote well, it's only two other days
I wrote since but it was just
I didn't do that at all. I just did it sober and it was just like coming out but I'm I'm very also too I you write
Very differently than I do I rewrite constantly as I'm writing mm -hmm. So by the time I'm done the draft
It's like the third draft
Because I'm literally deliberating the entire time and rewording it whatever which can be painstaking
But again, I'm not a staff writer. So I don't have to right. I'm not on any kind of deadline. You know
Yeah, I mean, I do that with a with a movie or something for sure
But I think for me it helps just to get to the end which is not a ground -breaking tip
But if you get to the end then you can rewrite it and start fixing it
So I am always just on a beeline to finish it
Have something I can say I finished a script and now I am working to make it better as opposed to
I'm still on page five after three days of work because I'm trying to perfect
Well, I'm not like that
We're different people. I am efficient
We're different people the uh, but I am the kind of guy where it's like if if I'm writing a scene and I go
Oh the seed for this should be planted earlier
I don't just make a note and wait for the next pass. I go back to the scene
Sure, and I just put it in I can't I'm too OCD, man
You know I hear you. You know what I mean? I hear you. Do you hear me?
Well, I think the the drugs for the for me being less judgmental less hard on myself is huge
And honestly working as a showrunner is huge because
Knowing like we're taping a show on Friday night. Well, yeah, it forces you to like make
Decisions, you know, and often the snap decision is the best decision. I agree
You know, it can go wrong it can bite you in the face
But usually something we agonize over for an hour in the room
We're like want to go back to that great joke we had an hour ago that we thought we could beat
You know like there's something about the whole room laughing and being like that's it baby next
Yeah, and that staff writing thing kind of helps them. It's one of the things I hated about
Staffing with bigger staffs. Yeah, it's like we don't need 10 shots at this for sure
You need three or four very funny people for sure one two three. That's it. All right move. Right. You know what I mean?
And if we and then when we run it if it doesn't work on its feet then we'll rewrite it then
Yeah, it's uh, I try to inspire a lot of sort of improv quick creative energy and get things in and keep things moving
And working on it later because we do have the 10 person room
But what I don't like is 10 people sit and go hmm
What is funny? Hmm, but if everybody's talking and laughing and we're keeping things moving
It can be very helpful if you got a good writers assistant to get it all down
I don't know when this became a fucking script notes podcast of it now
You'll motivate your staff. I've heard
In the business because the the streets talk sure sure
Except where the streets have no name right exactly
You'll motivate your staff by spinning on the table correct
I'll spit on the staff you'll spit on the staff. I'll spit right on the spit get it in their hair
I've heard tales of you
dousing
uh
dousing like the the main the writers assistants computer with gasoline and holding a match up and saying you think I won't fucking do it
Right stuff like that just now you think you can't type any faster
Yeah, I've done that speaking of which yeah, sorry
She the teaser for the Irishman
You mean that I see three people's names come up on a black screen that teaser was awesome
I guess it's
It's just reminding you that that's something that's still being made there's not no artistry to it couldn't listen dude
And there can be an artistry to trailers by the way. I'm not a snob. It's a teaser. It sucked. It didn't
I'm like, oh finally we'll learn something but oh no, it's just a list of the people in the game
I know a lot about the movie because I know the story but to see
the
bullet
Scorsese returned to gangster movies the bullet making the eye in
It's the four fucking names kids deniro
Pachino
No, he was in it. No, he was in it. No, he was in it.
Seeing that that's coming and having the bullet make the eye in every one of their names as as pat
Pachino's going I heard japan houses, which is the title of the book. I got chills. I fucking loved it. Wow
All right, I mean, I think you're way too easy on it. No way do it. Why do a trailer?
It's a teaser pet. Why do I know the difference? I mean a gremlins teaser
We told you the roof
But then at the end you see the gremlins running around and having you're like, oh shit
I thought it was an awesome. Give me a sit show me
Pachino like slamming down a car hood and going like it's about to get real Irish
Something they're gonna do that you think they don't have that shot
This is them being like you know, it's coming fuckers. It's it's smart marketing man. I thought it was great
I thought it was great Eren go crazy
And like fire into the the backseat of a car. It's the worst joke of all time that I've ever heard and I'm sure it was great
Yeah, I'm sure it was written by your former boss. Oh no
It was yeah, I'm sure it was a bad. No, he's not he's not a patreon subscriber. I'm saying I'm sure it was
I'm painting this show gonna in the sequel sex in the city too. I know what you're saying
They have an Irish babysitter character played by the woman from she's out of your league. She's Alice Eve
Yeah, gorgeous woman gorgeous
They have this big -breasted hot woman as the babysitter just for this joke just for this joke so Samantha can go
Oh honey Eren go brawless
Just for that joke. Yeah, oh my god. I love sex in the city those movies are a fucking abomination
I like the first one. Oh come on second one is obviously fucking idiot. I mean the first one was just five episode of the show in a row it wasn't
To me it was it there was no different they broke up the gang in the in the movie you're waiting for this movie to come out
They break the over half the movie they're not speaking to one another like what is this? Well, I mean the second one drove the man and saying
I mean, yeah, that's second one them going to the desert and area. Oh my Christ. Well, that contains the line
Oh, look at me. I'm Lawrence of my labia. She says that
Yeah, I'm a streamer drink in your face and then they go girls. We're going to Dubai and then Samantha go or one of them goes
Yeah, but dabba Dubai
Oh, I thought you're gonna say Dubai shoes
That would have been a better job. Yeah
Well, there is the thing in it where she's like, you know, there's a market here where you can buy women shoes for five dollars
Yeah, that's here Jessica Parker's like it's almost like an Abbot and Castello thing like which like
Yeah, you know like oh god, yeah, it's something else
Pat we're about we're about 11 minutes away from chewing into the Susperia review
I want to I mean 11 minutes away. I want to start it at the 30 minute mark. All right fine
I think we started any well, we I mean we could start it sooner. Do you think that's getting strange something?
I'm just sitting here enjoying a conversation. You know, I think our listeners are too
Uh, well, why don't we start with this if I may let's talk a little bit about it the director of this movie because I feel that that is an extremely
Uh, more so than usual
Part of the discussion of this film in the movie. What's his name? Cara de la Guadilla Cara de la Guardia
Look at me look. Let me look at my lately delivered blue right here
And why would you list the cast and crew on the back of the fucking blue right where
Where that always goes. I think it's like Cara de la
Cara de la Guicia Luca. Luca. That's what I was saying. Guada
Guadriniio
I believe Luca guadinho
Screenplay by David
If you like Luca Guadriniio
David's last name. He thought the first guy's name was tough. All right
Uh
Now on your phone would you do the justice or the courtesy excuse me of telling me what else David wrote
Yeah, because I know what else Luca. He did call me by your name. Luca did call me by your name. Hey sweetheart
Call me by your name. He did several Italian films. I believe I think call me by your name was one of his first
Uh, like American breakthrough movies
I think right
Oh, and he also did uh, you can call me by your name just so long as you call me
He also did uh, he did another movie with Tilda Swinton and Dakota Johnson
I like that movie a bigger splash
And that's a sequel to splash correct
Yeah, it's uh, the mermaids fatter
David Kedgeganich
wrote a bigger splash
The
Terror which I heard was a very cool show on AMC. That's right. Okay true story which was an absolutely awful movie starring Jonah Hill and James Franco
only movie where the guy that the movie is about
The movie star is actually less attractive than the real person like it's what Jonah Hills playing him then at the end
You know how you're always like oh boy, this guy gotta get the good end of the deal, you know, yeah Julia Roberts playing air and brought whatever it is
This is the only time where you're like, ooh, but this guy was pissed
Brad and Jonah Hill
Um, and he did the invasion
With Kidman and Craig, which was absolutely a terrible remake
Of uh, invasion of the body snatchers. Okay, but
Everyone knows him from calling by your name and now of course, Susperia
Oh, that's what the director did what are the writer was giving you the writer. Oh, that was the writer
That was the writer and the director's three American things are calling by your name
Bigger splash in this I believe correct
Okay, so originally your splash is a pretty entertaining film. Is it a comedy?
It's sort of like a beautiful people in the south of France cheating on a wives
But it's got a nice style to it. I liked
Well, this guy's very stylistic, which is why I wanted to bring it up
I did not see call me by your name, but I would assume that was a very stylized film as well
Uh, it was. I mean, yeah, that movie left me a little colder than most. It's good. It has good moments
But I didn't actually way way less
stylistic as Susperia way less. Oh my god
It wasn't anywhere near as stylish as Susperia
It was more of a straightforward merchant ivory type production. Okay, I've never heard that term
Merchant ivory merchant ivory. Yeah
I mean, I've heard of the film with a view Howard Zand and all that. It's like oh, that's who people say Jesus like a freaking
I'm sure Dennis Miller has gone like I've seen more exciting plots in a merchant
production
But they're always like you know Anthony Hopkins and Emma Thompson looking at a window and stuff like that
No, I mean those are my least favorite movies of all time
We've just mine too until I went back and revisited a few of them
I think remains of the day is fucking awesome like some of them are surprisingly good
I don't think they're bad. I just don't like watching that kind of thing. I agree boring, generally
Um, now originally this picture was going to be remade by David Gordon green
Right of Danny uh, one of the most uneven directors
There is yeah, he makes about in masterpieces he makes
Disass like your highness was one of the most embarrassing comedies I've ever seen
Uh, in fact, I'm glad you mentioned that
Uh, he's bound down as a master because
Uh, what's your name was gonna be the main person which made a lot of sense to me actually casting wise
Not only portman. Oh, okay, in his version. Yeah, Argento
denounced his version
But you've never got made right?
Argento wasn't for it. Argento also does not like this new version
Um, okay
Well, now the poor man. I just would have been like too much like black swamp probably craziness and a bell
Academy, uh, I'll tell you this Argento black swarm
I never saw it. I fucking love black swarm. I'd love to watch it again. If you want to watch it
No interest you'd love it. It's great. Okay, I'll watch it
It's so like fun and cool and good. I'll watch it. It's a guy who did the wrestling airing off. I know
Yeah, I like air enough. Yeah, I just I was like, it's a ballet movie. I don't care
If you want to see everyone finger Natalie Portman, that's something that interests you
Yes, it does
No, it's uh, that is sort of the uh, there's a kind of big meal akunis family goodness. She's good on it
It's I'm telling you it's a good movie. You got Barbara Hershey coming back. I love Hersh
Yeah, the Hersh
All right carry on sorry. I used to call her that around the uh, around the actor studio. Oh, okay
I call the Hershey then of course, I always judge her. She told me you were talking to him, right?
Yeah, they go. No, I'm not talking to you. Somebody say my name. No, Judd
I'm not talking to you, Judd and then Judd Nelson would go me
No, not talking to you. The Judds would go me and like perfectly harmonize me me
Yeah, and we'd go no Winona the other Judd. We don't mean you. Yeah. Why are you two here? You're not the acting Judds
What was the mom's name? There's wine on others. Ashley was the actress of course, and then
The mom of Judd was your name. It wasn't mom. It was big mom of Judd. I think it was Elmer Judd
Uh, look her up
Thank you. Thank you. Um came around late
Look when owner of those sassy, brassy, you know, that's the daughter
Winona, yeah
And the sister of Ashley. Yeah, Ashley's my favorite I think
Yeah, she's great. I think I always like that mom to be honest with you
The mom well, I can't find her. I mean mom was a real
Naomi Judd. That's right. Naomi Judd was like a Morgan Fair child kind of vibe, and you just know she was always like
You're really eating again, Winona
Gonna have another Twinkie Winona like you know, that was the back story behind so I'd see
I think she would have been like eat child eat
No, no, no, but then it backfired. No, it might have been like
Uh, there might have been like a CBS movie about the judge or something. I just have this image of her in my mind to being like
You just keep on eating don't you want? No, no, maybe I dreamed it
Yeah, I mean they always seem like they got a lot pretty good
But it's show business who knows what's real show business. I always just imagine behind the scenes is rough
All right, well, you've been scored and hell has no fury as they said. That's true
Uh, what you asked me something about the movie though before we derailed on my
Judd bit I asked you you were talking about
Hersh barber Hersh barber Hersh black swan Natalie Portman was gonna be in was gonna be in
Oh, okay, so our gentlemen. Let's let's talk about our gento for a moment
Well, I'm memory. Uh, our gento denounced as I said the attempted David Gordon Green remake. He was heavily critical of this version
I want to talk for a minute about Dario our gento because he is considered
Horror royalty is
Dario our gento I found recently I learned recently that the way he would write is
He would have a dream
He would wake up the next morning. He would go down stairs
Where I guess he was staying with the guy he was working with whatever who was a writer
He would explain the dream to the writer the writer would then write it down and make it into a scene
And when they had enough of these compiled I had the dream. Yeah, when they had enough scene the dream
When they had enough of these compiled
Go ahead to get it out of your system. I thought maybe the guy's name could be just happy that he was described in the dreams too
Giuseppe Giapetto that I just thought
And when they had enough of these things compiled
They would make it a script which is why
Dario our gento movies make no fucking sense number one look beautiful
But make no fucking sense and number two why the man has made a handful of exceptional films and a
shitload of
horrific movies. Yeah Dario Dario our our gento's
Dracula 3d
starring
uh
Who was hobo with a shocked rucker how sorry rucker is
So unbelievably bad like I I was confused watching it. I was like is this guy fucking with me
Well, did you see it in 3d though?
No, but I guess because it was in 3d it was like
You know, it was like
Every every single backdrop in the film was fake right so it'll be like a guy like in his workshop
And it's like a fake background of a workshop because I guess so they could do the 3d effect cheaper or something
It looks so bad. It is so poorly written. It is so poorly shot
And that was what I got to tell you
That's what's most disheartening to me about the later Argento stuff. You see it and it is shot
Shit which makes me wonder
Was he a genius or was his cinematographer genius? Sure was he just the guy going like no the maker my vision
You know, and then there was like a sous chef there being like I got it buddy. I'll do it right fucking relax. That's just epic
Giuseppe exactly
So I I kind of think he's got a set of brass balls on him criticizing anything right uh, I don't
Well, we're here as criticisms of the new Susperia. Do you know? Let me let me try let me try to find it on give me your phone because your phones right here and I'll look it up
What do you got dick pics on it? Probably let me just look I'm not what are we looking up? I can google the fucking thing. What are we looking up?
God damn Dario Argento Susperia remake, you know, I don't know Dario are gentle. Let me look at your phone
Susperia remake. Why won't you let me google something on your phone you psycho? What can I do it?
Where's your phone? I don't have to it's charging so I don't have to dictate to you. I charge it
So I don't have to dictate to you what to look up. He says it betrayed the spirit of the original
But I would say there is no real spirit. So do you consider Susperia a classic film?
The original yeah, yeah, I think it is it is in the lexicon of classic horror movies
It's not one of my favorites, but I think it is tremendously shot
I think the imagery in it is is striking and at times breathtaking and I think it's got some genuine scary moments
Uh, and I understand why people love it as much as they do
I
Will say but before you talk can I say this? Yeah, maybe I won't
But you love it. I think you love it in the way that you love
A really good 80s action movie you have to overlook things you have to just let certain things slide sure
I don't think anybody is watching Susperia going
Wow, this is airtight you're watching it and going this is kind of a fever dream and it doesn't really make total sense
But hey, it's I really enjoy the visuals and and for the most part the story is interesting
I
Feel like I've checked off almost all classic directors except
Argento
I when I really sit down and think about it
I don't think I've seen any of his pictures except of viewing of Susperia when I was maybe 14
That I don't remember so I'm no expert by any means. I remember things Susperia was dull
I would probably like it more now. I hear it's one to see in a theater
But like I've never seen tenebrae or deep red or any of that shit that are supposed to be great
I've got inferno inferno never seen. Where is it? Oh, it's actually up there and I haven't watched it yet
I've seen Dante's peak
Really with Pierce Brosnan?
That's that's about his heroine correct. Oh my god
You sorry my joke was bad
My joke was the was
Uh, inferno I'm over there, which is the second. He's got the he's got the mothers. I think it's called the mother's trilogy
uh
Susperia is the first one inferno is the second one of the mother of tears is the third one starring his
Harrod daughter
Bad actress, you mean Asia. Oh, Asia
And why did you tell Asia to do what she did by the way? Is that a segment? I don't want to open it up. I know that's not a segment
That's how the segment I said, but hey, we don't need to talk about Asia. You're caught with your hand in the cookie jar
blame
Your boyfriend that committed suicide probably because of you. That's the strategy easy
Easy uh, she I don't endorse any of them. I believe she's well. You don't have to. It's just it's what you did
I just don't want to go to jail
jail
For what?
People are litigious
You're always saying I have to say allegedly about things that are clearly true. No, she blit she publicly blamed
anti -bordance and he made me give this boy hush money
And then the press there was a tons of speculation that the reason he killed himself was because he saw pictures of her in a
Newspaper with another man. Mm -hmm. So that's that's all I'm saying. You put the pieces to God the fuck
Yeah, I better better chance to date in Asia fucking our gentle
Okay
I want to do a thing called okay
Yeah, it's the name of the live show and Kyle Dunnigan who I love does an amazing bill marm impression
Which also involves a lot of okay's and I want to pitch to Kyle
I would love to see an impression of Bill Marb never seen one. It's it's fantastic. That would be great. His bill mar is fantastic
Uh
I can't do a good enough dentist bill or to pitch this to him
But I always wanted to pitch so good dentist moment that we could do we should do a one hour show like a live show called okay
And it's dentist bill or bill marm. Mm -hmm. And it's even perfect politically because they fall on different extreme sides
Yeah, and it's just you're just running off
Okay, like that kind of okay from marm. Yeah, yeah, and he does that a lot
There's a really thing he does is like nobody's laughing
At his like joke that would have been hacky in 1984
And he'll go like oh, I'm sorry was that one a little too rough for you guys
It's like no dude your jokes suck. We sorry am I a little too edgy for you. It's like no
No, Jay Leno would have been ashamed to give that joke
Dunning one of the Dunning in post on Instagram. Go on his Instagram. He done they're all on there
And he does like the face swap. He calls it the Dunstagram, right? Yeah, the Dunstagram
He uh, well, no, no wait, that's Kirsten Dunst. He calls it the Dunst again
Again, that's that's Kirsten. That's her second one. We're second. She got I got Dunst again. Yeah
uh
He uh, he uh, there's one on there where he's doing bilmar reading
Children's book to kids uh -huh
And he's like uh
Hey diddle diddle the fiddle the cow jumped over the moon now. How can a cow jump over a moon stop crying? Okay
Grow up a cow can't jump over a moon. Okay. Uh -huh. It's really funny. They're really really funny
And he does other amazing. He does these things where he's the entire gender family talking to each other on face time
Okay, it's fucking insane. Okay
Uh, maybe I'd rather be uh doing a podcast with him job. He's funny. I would to be honest
But you know, I take what I can get Pat I got to refill my drink uh, let's get into this review
But can you can you can you steer the cart while I make a freshie?
Yeah, if your problem is not to say that again, folks uh
We're talking about
lukega goobria gonjos
Susperia
um
Yeah, that's wild to look on the back of the box and not see the fucking credits
luca guadagnino
I'm quite certain I'm pretty not saying that right um
This is a film
About a young American ballet dancer
Who was played by the gal from 50 shades of gray
Who I gotta be honest. I like she's always like either
Like
Really good or just kind of embarrassing and not trying
But when she's on I like what she does. I liked her in this movie to be honest her name is Dakota Johnson
But uh
She goes to this kind of like ballet school. It's in the 70s. It's in Germany
Uh, she joins this dance company, but very quickly you learn and she learns
That it is a ballet company slash coven oh witches right uh and these witches kind of
Take these young girls and groom them to be witches. Yes
Dakota Johnson daughter of Don Johnson and Millenia Griffith. Correct
I'm a huge fan of hers after seeing her performance in this movie. Yeah, she's a chameleon
Because I'm watching this thing and I'm like who is this like 19 year old girl they got into this movie
Yeah, who's like carrying this whole thing. She's really good. Then I look it up and I'm like that's the 50 shades of gray lady
Right like and she also plays depth's wife and black man. So I'm like
Yeah, she's fucking chameleon. She's really good when she's good, but in the 50 shades movies
I mean she's the star, but her lines are like I want you to clamp my nipples
It's like nobody knows she's good because that's all people know her from yeah those movies suck. Yeah
So I've seen two of three of them though
She's uh, she's she's really wonderful in this uh, it's no it's no secret at this point till the Swinton is in multiple roles in the she she plays
She plays the the madam whatever the mother
Forget her mother whatever the fuck. She's one of the main heads which of the school
Well Marcos is the head witch that you never the head witch stress. Yeah, she's like right under Marcos or whatever right
The mysterious mother Marcos so you never see until the end
But till the Swinton also plays at the end is his mother Marcos and heavy makeup and then also in heavy makeup plays
The psychologist or psychiatrist that is investigating this school
Because his patient at the beginning of the film was Chloe Grace mortis
Marrette where that's and she disappears. I mean she's got fourth billing in this fucking thing
She's in it for four minutes. Right. I didn't even know it was her
Uh, it's really just in the opening scene. Yeah, it's
We're in in which he delivers the line. They'll eat my cunt on a platter. Yeah. Uh, it's a heavy
Lotta. I'll tell you folks with all the vaginal imagery in this film. It should have been called pusperia. Okay
Uh, all right. It's a lot of
You got a lot of shots of tunnels
Yeah, it's a it's a vaginal film for sure
You know, you'll see like a woman with bloody fingertips. It's a lot of
Vagina China reference. Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's a spirit folks
I
Don't understand. I guess it's just some sort of acting challenge, but I knew fairly quickly that till the Swinton was playing this old man
Right movie
But there's never a reveal I kept thinking like boy Heather. I was watching with my wife does not know
That this is told us when how fun it will be for that reveal and then they just didn't do it
Which I found kind of weird. I thought I guess she's just playing the characters and truly playing them
I thought it was very interesting that she plays the three pillars of authority in this film right
I thought there was a cool casting decision. I thought it's I was like, you know
That's something that's not done often often, but when it's done and it's done right it's pretty cool
Tarantino and Rodriguez did an industrial darn with Cheach Marin and I thought that was pretty fun. Yeah
But I will say this
Seeing her as that old man read vitalized my interest until the Swinton as an actor
Not that she had ever become bad
Yeah
But till the Swinton you know it
She's like a Tom Hanks or something you need a break after a while where like we get it
You can emote for two hours, please
But see her as that old man. I was like that she is fucking
Stunning in this portrayal like she is an old man. This is crazy like her man
Everything to the point that I was legitimately disappointed
That they did not pitch her voice down
In post
Because it's clearly a woman's voice
And I know that that's you know sort of the way you would do it in the theater
But it's not a play and when you're watching a film you scrutinize it much more closely
And you know, I don't think you'd know it sounded like an old man's voice to me
sounded a little a little too
But you knew going in she was playing this part. Well, that's true too. So maybe maybe I wouldn't know that's a good point
Um, but I thought uh, that's probably why you knew because you already knew that's probably right. Yeah
I thought she was she really hit a home run
I thought look every performance there wasn't a bad performance in the film. There wasn't one part where I said
Oh god, where do they drag this person in forever? You know, right every single performance was great
The thing is beautifully shot. Of course incredibly shot
You know, but now let's get into the to the meat of this. Is it a good movie?
uh
My first gripe
Before I even saw it was the original Susperia. I think is under 90 minutes. Yeah, this thing is two and a half hours solid right
So right away, I'm like here we go directors got a jerk himself off. Yeah, hours shit. We don't need
And you know, sure enough they lay real heavy into that terrorism backdrop of the 1970s in Germany
They didn't lean that heavily into the terrorists, but it's pretty fucking heavy, dude
They're they're showing footage of terrorist attacks and news stories frequently
And you're you're hearing the stuff on the radio
And look it has its place in the movie. I'm not saying it doesn't
But I'm saying a two and a half hour film. Do we need this
That's my I'm now I'm gonna go from initial impression to final impression
That's my initial impression for the first hour of this movie
Maybe even the first 90 minutes of this movie
My only thought was this guy managed to somehow make a more boring version of Susperia
Than the original Susperia
Again, it looks cool. The original one looks better. Right
But I thought I was here to watch a horror movie or at the very least a thriller
And what I have is a drama
About a dance academy
Where they keep talking about terrorism and vaginas. Yeah
So that's that's my initial that was my initial impression through the first about 90 minutes of this thing
Except for the scene where the girl does the she you know she her body's being controlled in that dance and they like
Well, yeah, I mean to like a pretzel or whatever. So let me meet you at where you're at in the film by saying
I
I don't always watch movies high. I usually try not to but Mandy for examples when I really wanted to get high for
I would have said it was my favorite movie of last year. I tried to watch it again sober
I still enjoyed the film very much, but it was a very different experience because I was nowhere near as into it
And that I thought that was a drug movie. Susperia
I feel the same way. I happened to be high whilst watching it
That first hour of this thing. Yeah, sure it wasn't like a thriller minute, but I was just riveted by it. I think
A
You know if I can just be disgusting
It's the art of dance. It's beautiful women dancing. I was enjoying watching it
I don't know what else to say. I liked the dancing
I liked it. I'm not a monster. I
Thought the performances were all really nice. I liked the kind of
Slowly I'll admit slowly growing sense of dread that was going on and I thought
How subdued it was made that first scare scene where the actress's body is like destroyed almost like a
Temple of Doom style voodoo doll
Right kind of situation like wherever whatever this woman dances in the room next door
The pain of it is felt by this lady and it like almost like a weird voodoo spiritual connection kind of thing
But that scene goes on for so long and is so disgusting and so graphic and the effects were so cool
That I was like man this movie really took me on a ride where if we saw that
Body being ripped apart in the first 10 minutes or something. I would have been like all right
There's gonna be just a
You know gross, you know gross out type movie and it was gross in spots
But I thought the sense of pacing and it was amazing again maybe because I was fucking high well
sure
Look pot'll do a hell of a thing for a movie that's very visual it will yeah
Now that's my this was my initial impression as as I said first now we're 90 minutes. I was texting you left it right
Yes, you know, I could tell from your tone. You didn't careful a lot of scenes were eight women of the same age or in a room with the door closed
Speaking in a foreign language and subtitles. I'm like who is saying what?
They have the same exact voice. I can't tell what's going on right now
Things like that were irking me, but this is the kind of movie for me
I very quickly
Know I can I can shut off that point of my brain that's analyzing it and making sure I'm following everything a hundred percent
And especially of course again when I'm high
I love being given that freedom that you get where it's like on a twin peaks
Okay, this one's just gonna be some wild series of images
I like knowing that so I can chill out and relax and enjoy it and
Susperia I sort of felt like the plot is not super important
well
As I moved along. Yes, the the again, I'm just gonna I'm mentioning my gripes first. Yeah
Oh, we always come to these issues you hit me on demon and it's a if it's just visuals you tend to check out
Right, and I didn't think which I understand. I didn't think this was just visual
I thought there was more to it, which is why it initially. I was annoyed at like could you please present this to me a little more clearly
Right because there's information in there that's important
They're talking about the ritual and they're talking about the mother marcos character who we don't see
And they keep referring to till the Swinton
Again, I forget her name, but I was like oh like it was halfway through the way
I was like oh that's till the Swinton's name. Yeah, you know, so it's like stuff like that
I'm like come on man like give me a little bit here. You don't need to spell it out, but right
Don't make it impossible
It also bothered me too that these witches had an ability to communicate through telepathy while they were
Speaking out loud about other things and doing other things
Yet they still felt the need to meet secretly in a room and talk out loud about their witch business
I'm like, why are you doing that ever?
I put it aside. I wasn't gonna let it ruin the movie for me
Around the 90 -minute mark is when I think we hit
The big dance recital
Yeah
Which seems very climactic, but it's not it's almost like the first of two climactic scenes in the film
Munchen in the style of a poltergeist if you will absolutely where you think you're done and then it's like oh
Yeah, so they hit that they hit that scene. Yeah, and when they hit that scene
And it's basically when the girl whose leg breaks
They make her leg break because she's figuring out like you know, what's a foot right underneath the school
Which that was one thing I found confusing. I didn't understand if the girls knew that it was a witch -cubbin or not
Because that girl that that kind of gets her leg broken and the dance didn't know like when they all go out to dinner or whatever
You get the feeling they all are definitely like we all know where witches
But then they all there's also an element of them being taken advantage of kind of yeah
So so again not not not terribly relevant, but it was one of the things that I was a little confused about
But anyway when that sequence hit
That's when I started to go
Okay
This has been leading somewhere that's good not that I thought it couldn't have been but I was like okay
I'm glad to see it was and it's hard for a movie to get you on track after 90 minutes of being checked out of it
Well, I stuck with it because you said you said stick with it you take you on the right yeah
And then from that point on I was fairly invested because I was like I want to see what happens here. I want to see how this plays out
I liked
I liked the whole thing with the old man psychiatrist guy like having the
the the the illusion of seeing his dead wife
Suddenly and like and then she's not there and you realize it's black magic. Yeah
And then they kidnap him and you're like
Shit man, where the fuck is this going and then finally
You hit which in my opinion that might surprise you when I say this
One of the greatest
horror movie payoffs I've ever seen
Because so happy to hear you say it and why I felt confident telling you to stick with it because I couldn't agree more
I that thing had me up out of my seat
I couldn't believe it
I was so mad. I didn't see it in the theater. I had all these emotions at once where I was like fuck
Yeah, it just just an insane ending to this movie
That is so well done and the makeup and the effects are so disgusting and amazing really
It is a revolting
Disturbing scene like almost like something out of dune or you're something like that to the point where
One of these this is kind of how I gauge like something being truly disturbing. Yeah
My mom's a big car fan of my mom said I want to watch this period. I would say don't don't watch it
Yeah, that's that that scene's gonna be too much for you. Yeah, but you've got and spoiler alerts
Or bound, but you know, I didn't know that was told us when I guess I assumed but I didn't know
But you got yeah, you got tell us when in this fucking as mother Marcos in this like tumored
Just disgusting legion -covered body. She's got baby arms growing out of her. It's like that weird to me was the worst the little hands coming out of her and stuff
And she starts fingering herself at one point. I mean, it's just fucking foul, man like I
Couldn't believe it. I couldn't believe it and Heather doesn't like scary
So I sold it to her as like it's like a thriller in a ballet academy. It'll be like black swan
The second you see that woman we were both like oh
It was insane and
Movies so rarely have the power to surprise me at all anymore or make me feel anything
So for me it was well worth a slow build up and the kind of like what's going on here?
And then okay like oh wow
This is way more violent than I thought it was gonna be and then oh wow
This is way more sick and disgusting
I was more than happy to go on that journey and to put up with a little slowness again
Admittedly, I was a little high, but I mean that's that's Kubrick too, you know
You're gonna have a bunch of long scenes around always and shit like that. I'm down with it
Sure, sometimes if you're in the mood great. I will say this the film the film is clearly this is you know
That that sequence when that finally kicked in that's when everything made sense to me
And I was like okay
This clearly is is modeled after this type of horror from the 70s where it's almost like a drama movie
Yeah, until the last whatever once the spirit did not go there did it? No, yeah, no we're near that right now
Here's the thing the um
You know if you watch a movie like the amity the original amity the horror
It's a slow burn and your payoff is is usually in those types of movies you get very little payoff like the in keepers tried to do it
Yeah, and you know your payoff ends up being five minutes
If that this
Was you know easily a 15 -minute sequence of just
Hell on earth
And even the background you know
I'll say I mentioned Temple of Doom earlier, but like
It had that it was our director to that point much like the Temple of Doom where like from when I was a kid to now
I'm like the coolest fucking set I've ever seen
Yeah, and was amazing and the dance women dancing, you know like but there were also demons like almost like a Broadway show or something like that
I was just into it. I just got into all of it. I loved it
Huge spoiler now. I liked the twist that Dakota Johnson was the mother
The other mother, you know mother Susperia and or whatever the fuck was was mother Marcos right and and and Dakota Johnson turned out
I guess to be the reincarnation of the of her rival witch. Yeah, and she ends up killing everybody that
Supported Marcos in the Academy over till to swim right
and
Unfortunately at this moment in the film
It goes into that really bad like sort of stop motion slow motion which I realize is there to cover effects a little bit
I can't think of any other good reason for it to be there. It looks terrible
It always looks terrible Peter Jackson uses it a lot. It never looks good
um
But it looks to me that it was there to kind of cover up the CG of people's heads exploding literally
The CGI
The CGI left a lot to be desired unfortunately like you know when Dakota Johnson rips her chest open
It looks yeah, it doesn't look good
And I'm like you guys did such beautiful practical work through this entire movie and camera why now
Why now dude why go to CGI there man?
Yeah
They come on you know, this isn't a budget issue clearly
um
That being said it's not enough to ruin the movie. It's just it leaves you wanting some better practical effects
Uh, or at least better CGI
What did you think of the Tom York score? I loved it. I loved it. Are you radio head fan? Uh, you know man
Look, I have okay computer as most people do. I've an on vinyl courtesy of you. Thank you
Of course, but I liked okay computer. I liked in rainbows. You know I radio heads got their albums that I like
Um, there were few that I would put on and listen to besides those two and a couple others
But a huge fan. I feel like at some point they lost something. I don't I don't mean like
Oh kid A now they're not using guitars anymore. I mean
It's been a recent sharper decline than most. I would say post in rainbows
I thought this score was exactly what Tom York and radio head should do
Because every rainwood does amazing scores. I'm sure I'm sure they went to him first
Johnny Greenwood who's the guitarist radio head did there will be blood and all that he does amazing score work
And uh, Tom York generally doesn't do this kind of thing, but I thought he did a nice job
I thought he did a great job and I think that even with the data to score
I know I think even with the best radio head records
I'm sort of still sitting there going. I really like this, but
I can't just listen to this like it has to go along with something else. It's very moody
So to hear
You know, Tom York's score to this film was almost like when you watch like Wizard of Oz with darks out of the moon
You know, it's like all of a sudden it takes this very slow dreamy record to this whole new place
Uh, and I thought that that worked really well and I think uh
Tom York should do a lot more of that kind of stuff
It was very haunting
Sounds like you really loved this movie. I thought you were going to spice it. I
I
I liked the little button at the end where she goes to the man and tells him and like and then you actually
Here's what I liked about this button where she goes and actually finally tells this man who's been searching for his dead wife
Is she dead? Is she alive because she had fled because of the Nazi invasion or the Nazi outbreak in Germany rather
Uh, she goes Dakota Johnson when she kind of takes her throne
She goes to him at the end and she tells him like you deserve to know what happened to your wife and she tells him the whole story
and
It's a kind of beautiful moment because you realize
There's a purity to the witchcraft, right
Marcos was rotten and was doing an impure which is why till this one says it has to be pure
It has to be poor something's wrong here, right
Uh
And it was cool to see at the end like that Dakota Johnson was like no, I'm like what this was supposed to be there
This isn't supposed to be sinister. Mm -hmm. This is supposed to be it's about community. Yeah
Yeah exactly
It's supposed to be about love, but if you fuck with us
Don't fuck with us, you know what I mean that kind of thing
Um, but if you fuck with us, don't fuck with us. Yeah, there he is. Of course. I know what you mean
So that all being said
When I walked out my front door the next morning and saw the box and said we god damn it the fucking blew right showed up
After I already rented it. Yeah
I thought
Do I want to keep this? I think you do and then I was like you know what deep down you do
I want to see this movie again. I want to watch it again. I want to know what you now know. Yeah exactly
I want to think about it more. I bet there's gonna be tons of shit you discover that you didn't realize
And you know, but the movie I always go back to
In that situation for reference for port of references heat
Heets one of my favorite movies of all time when I first saw heat. I was bored. I didn't get it really
I mean I got it. I was well though because I look I'm a fucking 17 -year -old kid
Wanting to or 18 -year -old kid how old I was wanting to see a movie with De Niro Pacino
I was a 14 -year -old kid. I fucking look although there was one of the few our rated movies
I was allowed to see I wanted to see a full
You know, you know tour to force of Pacino and De Niro together right and I had to separate myself from that till right just kill
Right exactly co -starring for dissent
So I just separate myself from that to understand the move and then also the slow pace of it
I was expecting a good fellas. It's not a good fellas. No casino was another good fellow. Yeah, yeah same year
Yeah, I think yeah, I think both of those movies come out in the same like two -week period
Who so can you imagine having a year like that now?
Just embarrassing where we're at, you know, it's an embarrassing time
You know, you wouldn't consider happy death day to you are heat
I haven't seen either of the films. I know they have their fans and I like to watch it. I've never seen it
I can't I'm just making a joke. I have no idea. I heard the first one is a, you know fun kind of 80s
homage horror picture
But then the second one is a romantic comedy that's being marketed as a horror movie and people are angry about it
It's a romantic
So I've heard so I've heard of you know what pet? I'm gonna read the wick peteous and obsis. I think I don't think it's gonna really ruin much more
No, go ahead
So yes, Susperia my hog is up
My hog is probably I thought I was gonna hate this fucking movie
My hog is way up. I knew I would like it. I kept telling myself to go to the theater and whenever I do that
I wind up really being angry at myself because this would have been
Just a dream movie and I didn't do many in the theater
You know like those were movies. I should have done the weed. Yeah, go on to the show and an uber
Maybe I hit up a shake shack after you know, I don't know where the day is gonna go
But now I'm gonna have time coming up. I'm gonna see a whole lot of movies. I'm very excited about it
Oh reading the real quick reading the reviews on the back of the box
Okay, yeah, Bolcher says a gorgeous hideous uncompromising film agree nice quote
Daily telegraph says
Five stars astonishing nice quote. Yeah screen daily says a feast of excess nice quote. Yeah collider says
A straight -up masterpiece
Straight -up take straight -up out of it
Take straight -up out of what are you 12 if you write a straight -up masterpiece. You're saying
I'd like to be on a blue -ray box. Yeah, that's why you say something like that
Andy wire called it a grim and glorious work of madness. I would agree with all of these
I don't know. I don't know if I would call it a straight -up masterpiece, but yeah
I don't think anybody in the world would agree with this but for me when I saw call me by your name
I was like oh
Everyone says this is the next exciting voice in American cinema
I find it to be a moderately entertaining little romantic movie
Then Susperia which everyone pretty much unanimously didn't care about
About 60 % I was like oh shit this
Has me excited to see the guys next movie. Yeah, and especially any guy who can make both those movies
I think it's something that is a kind of a lost art the old Howard Hawks thing where you do the thing and then you do his
Girl Friday and yeah, I always admire that. That's a much harder skill than people realized
I thought Susperia if I'm really being honest and especially after watching the Oscars
Which we will discuss on the podcast regular
I thought Susperia is one of my favorite movies of last year 2019
I loved it. It was fine work and I'm excited to watch it again
And I think I'm really gonna grow to love it and I'm it's gonna it's honestly
It's making me want to go back and watch the original again now because maybe I need to I don't remember my appreciation for that as well
Folks, that's our show no plugs ever on the special episodes. Thanks for listening
See you next time. We'll see you in hell
You