Welcome to we'll see you in hell it's time to talk about movies again.
Folks with your favorite boy. The boys are back in town. How's it going? I'm doing all right,
Joe. Do you remember that night? I think it was at your house where I kept talking about the thin
Lizzy song Jailbreak. I was very high and drunk, but I was like, they keep saying there's going to be
a Jailbreak somewhere in the town. You think it might be down at the Jail? I was walking. I said
it's a Vince, probably 25 times. And he was like, yeah, Pat. I just I thought it was so funny.
It is funny. It sounds vaguely familiar. But I'm sure it's somebody's bit. Yeah. No, no, no,
I'm saying it sounds you say it sounds vaguely familiar. But you know, who knows if you were high,
I was definitely fucked up. Yeah. One of my favorite character actress is Ed vaguely familiar.
I'm sorry. Yeah. I'm only a few sips into my coffee. It's got to I'm on no sleep. Joe just commented
that he's he doesn't like the way he's looking these days. And really you just look pale is all I would
say. You look like you need some song. You look like a ghost. Oh, it's you know, nothing makes you
want to go outside in the sun more than these nine degree days we're having here in New York. We're
32 down here, which is the coldest I've experienced in a long time. It's what is it right now in New
York? I'll tell you, Apple weather is always just wrong. I love how it's just Apple just gives you
services now that are just wrong. They just don't work and they don't fix it or anything. Apple,
I updated my phone after weeks of ignoring it. Finally, I was like, all right, let's just do it.
And what the only thing I can see that they changed is in Safari, the tab that you type in,
you know, I'm looking for the onion or whatever is now at the bottom of the screen. The exact
opposite of the way everyone's done it their entire life. So search bar. You mean the search bar
or were you type in the the address, but yeah, yeah. And it is so even though it's a minor change,
it's so fucking annoying because all anyone has ever known since the internet began is the bar
at the top. Why would you do that change? It helps nothing. It's not cool. It's not functional. Apple
they've slid now into with their phones at least into early droid phone territory where it's like
they're making things different just to be like, look how we do it. And it's like, yeah,
but just because it's different doesn't mean it's better. It's like that's a shit way to do it.
No, that's what early droid phones did. And you know, the Apple computers I'm still pretty happy with,
but the phone is just, but you know, they got you. They got you by the the Cahone's as they say.
You know what I really hate too, is like every contact in my phone, there's six of.
It's like every time you plug in the new phone or you get the new computer, it just keeps adding
to it. No one else I know has this problem, but I can't go through and delete all these fucking
contact. I just mean there's six duplicates of every contact. You need to merge your contacts.
How do I do that? You're beyond help in this deployment. Is it through iTunes?
I mean, in my opinion, I've looked up how to plug the phone in and I can tell you the last time
you've even plugged the phone into the computer. That's the issue. I've done it so many times,
try like googled how to merge contacts. I do it. Nothing works. Sometimes I wind up with more
contacts. I feel like I'm a goddamn, I'm working at lens crafters over here, the amount of contacts
I have. Oh man, good stuff. As you can tell folks, Pat is on a job and is it's sharp. The
you're a guy. I mean, just so the audience does, this is a man who every week, almost every time
we record, it has to figure out again, how do the microphone works. So I was all set up today,
baby, you were. You came right in today. You know what the issue 90 % of the time is and sometimes I
tell you it was the issue and sometimes I keep it to myself. Microphone wasn't on. It's the issue
almost every time. I've seen you turn it on on camera after like cursing. It'll be like no audio
because it's not turned on. I see him cursing and spitting and then he puts the switch on. It's
a real like albundi kind of and then I get on and neither of us talk about it. You know, don't
want to start on a tense note. We just kind of move forward. Joe, I'm sorry. I interrupted you.
You were about to tell us about the weather in New York and I'm sure we were all pretty excited
to hear that report. I know. I'm sorry. Apple is saying it's 36 degrees out here. I was just outside.
I didn't know damn 36 degrees cold as hell right now yesterday was telling me was the high was 61
and it only went to like 42 right? It's ridiculous. These apps just don't work. Even Apple weather is
lying to us. Yeah, it's disgraceful. Folks, just before I forget to mention it today's movie or today's
it's not a movie. It's a show. We're doing a midnight mass. Yes, reviewing that today. I know we said
last time it would be jackass, but I haven't had a chance to see it yet because of the staggering
depression. So no, I'm kidding. I haven't been able to see it yet because I haven't had a I can't
find a friend that's able to go with me when I want to go and I don't want to see jackass alone.
And then also the time I just I've been busy with the bar and stuff. But anyway, we'll do that next time
most likely along with Texas chainsaw in the new one. Yeah, which I'm hearing wildly different
things about. I from what I'm saying, people love the gore, but the everything else is a disaster
and they they tried to politicize it. And apparently that's the most embarrassing part of it. Oh,
God. They tried to politicize it with the last the last direct sequel, Texas chainsaw that they made
in 2008 or whatever that was. Yeah. And it was just an abomination of a movie where they tried
to make leather face and an anti hero. And it was just so stupid. That was the one where I told you
on the bonus features. The producer goes, you know, our movie opens with the town rising up on the
Sawyer family and committing vigilante justice. And he goes, now of course, these people did terrible
things, but everybody's got the right due process. And I'm like, what the fuck are we even talking
about? I would have loved to see leather face in a suit sitting in that courtroom whisper it lawyer
whispers to leather face leads over whispers back. Yeah, that's that's the movie I want. All right,
pen writing down on paper in front of it. We're going to it question mark, pass to taps on it with his
band, the lawyer. I mean, the good old days, what happened to the good old days of Toby Hooper?
It's like, here's the sequel. These freaks live in an underground circus tent now. And then they're
they made people still. That's all anybody needs. What are we talking about here? There's one
awesome shot in the trailer where he rises out of the cornfield. I was like, okay, great shot. And
iPhones at leather face and saying, you're going to be canceled. Yeah, that's that's not ideal.
I mean, as if none of these people would be scared of a chainsaw wielding maniac.
I I will say this about that. I haven't seen the movie yet. So I can't speak to it, but but but that
beat at least in the trailer, how it read to me in the trailer at least was I was like, oh, that's
that's interesting that they are taking. They're making a commentary about like the Gen Zs of the
world where it's like, you guys have no idea like what people are truly capable of because you've lived
your life on the internet. And you think like you're just going to wag a finger at this guy. And you
know what I mean? So I do think that's an interesting commentary, but whether or not they actually
executed properly or if that's even the point. I don't know, you know, there was certainly a bit of
that in screen five, I thought. But certainly more naturally a part of the screen franchise,
which is a comedy horror franchise. Also, you know, look, here's another one of these things where
this is the same problem I have with this new Halloween, which by the way, the reviews I'm seeing,
a lot of them are saying like, this is desperately trying to be the new Halloween, you know, like yeah,
it's like it's bringing back the original final girl of the first movie, different actor because
the original actor died. But you know, it's like this is it's their version of the new Halloween.
But you know, a similar issue I have with this that I also have with new Halloween movies is leather
faces now like 70. Yeah, yeah, he's like 70 and guys, I know 70 is the new 50 or whatever the hell
everybody says. But that's for people that live in metropolitan areas and take care of themselves.
This is a man, a man who's been living on animal bones for the last 50 years or whatever. It's like,
how is he still even capable of anything? cholesterol alone has got to be a pretty big issue for
old life. He's always been overweight. He's always been overweight. Yeah, that's true.
You know, social issues, he doesn't have a sounding board in his life. We'll listen to him.
It's bad news. But also they say having a spouse can extend your life by 10 years, you know,
that's not happening for LF. There's a good, there's a good cat skills style joke in there.
For sure. You could write it real quick. They said, having a spouse extend your life by 10 years
with my wife. So, yeah, with my, well, I was thinking more, that's why I killed my wife or
something like because he's desperate to die. But maybe that's where my head's based. I was thinking
my wife was short in my life. That kind of thing. No, I know. I know. I know. Okay. I went darker with
it. That's all right. That's okay. I've been a dark bit. I told people on the little chat,
the chat I joined, which was so fun. There's a therapy chat going on now for the hellians. There's
also a, the standard movie talk chat going on on the Zoom. And I wanted to remember, we always say
our own Instagrams, which is silly because I don't even use mine. See you in hell pod is our Instagram.
And there's always a lot of funny stuff going up over there. Thanks to Emily Florence and others
who submit stuff to her. But yeah, I told them and I will tell you, I'm writing for the show called
the miss Pat show, which is a BET show that's moving to Paramount Plus. Miss Pat is a very funny
comic who has a brand new Netflix special, which is very funny. She's very fun. It's been a great
experience. We're down in Atlanta, but the show is beyond our rated I texted Joe last night a sampling
of the emails we get where they talk about the language on the show. And it's like we object to the
43 uses of fucking. And then it says anatomical. We also object to the 65 uses of fucking
non parenthesis descriptive like and the dick pussy. So it's it's all rated. It's that's kind of
the thrill of it is that in the writers room, in the cafeteria, whatever you just hear the kind of talk
that's that even in my lifetime never happened in the workplace because it was never appropriate. But
everyone talks like it. And it's a thrill. And I am one of, you know, maybe three white guys on the
entire set. And that is a thrill for me. It's something I needed to do for myself. I grew up very
white. Like a lot of people I spent a lot of time over the pandemic and everything going on being like,
yeah, what what am I doing? A lot of people question themselves. Sure. And being completely immersed
fully in black culture culture has just been awesome. And if you ever get an opportunity to do it,
uh, maybe ideally your whole life has been a melting pot. Mine wasn't. There was never a black
person at my high school, you know, so, uh, and for those of you that was just listening, you can't see
Pat now. He is wearing the looney tunes. Hip hop t -shirt from the 90s. I thought you were going to
do shiki with like, you know, the, uh, condo forever, whatever they, you know, when, uh, they all took
the knee and, uh, supreme court of it. Uh, no, it's, uh, it's just been cool. And I'm not saying I've never
had black friends or met a black person or anything like that. I'm just saying when you are the white
person, you realize how black people feel. And every writer's room I've been in for the most part, when
you walk in and everyone is white and you're not, it's at first a little uncomfortable. And then it
becomes kind of a beautiful thing. Well, Jay, Jay Oakerson. Uh, and I always talked about that
because we both started at the Laugh House comedy club in, in Philadelphia. And that was a
predominantly, it was an all black room when we were one, I started about a year after him. So I
didn't meet him till after, but, but he was in the same position. I was in when I started, which was
being one of two white comics in this room. And we talk about all the time, like what an amazing
experience it was and like how great it was for you as a comic, like to be out of what you
had known as your comfort zone your entire life. Right. And, you know, having to really present
who you actually are and actually be yourself in a situation that's not, uh, familiar, as
familiar to you as your whole life has been. And also too, it's one of the reasons I think that he
and I both as comedians are not, are, are the types of comics that aren't precious about everything.
And this is not, I'm not going to get into some stupid, you know, because you see in this community,
it's, it's more real of it. I'm not going to get involved. It's all generalization, but all I'm,
but all I'm saying is, is like when it's what annoys me about the preciousness of, of a lot of the,
uh, liberal voices I see online because they're coming from white people most of the time who are
living in areas surrounded by people that think and look exactly like them. And I think that anytime
anybody gets out in, in, into a truly mixed environment or an environment where they're the minority,
you start to realize that theory is a lot of horseshit and practice is actually what it is. And,
integration and, and behavior and interaction and all these things, that's what it is. And it takes,
it, it just takes that preciousness away from you. And, and I mean that in a positive way, where
you're not, you're not tiptoeing around everything. You're, you're talking, you're, you're communicating,
you're discussing things. Yeah. Uh, it's a great, it's a great thing to do. Uh, it was great. I felt
to say very similarly when I went to China. Yeah. You know, there was, there were moments in China
where I was standing on street corners and like people were literally next to me, like staring at me,
like, like, like, like, you look out. Well, yeah, that is true. Yeah. Yeah. Uh, and I kept,
it didn't help that I kept saying, uh, calling it my egg roll and saying, uh, that I wanted to,
you got any duck sauce, miss? No, no, no, no for my egg roll. Uh, anyway, the, uh, I didn't do that.
But, uh, the point is is it's, you know, people would just sometimes stare at me like, you don't look
anything like anybody around here. And it's just interesting. It's an interesting, you know, it's,
I don't know. I think, uh, anyway, you get what I'm saying. I get what you're saying. It's, it's a
wonderful thing. I've, I've always loved alt comedy and I've also always loved black comedy. And
you're, you're not even your top, but a good black meeting can walk into any alt room and destroy
because the people are just like, whoa, we, the jokes. Oh my god. And then in an alt room, uh,
they can't cross over. You never see, uh, John Mulaney playing like, you know, some, some,
some black clubs somewhere. It just wouldn't happen. And I love John Mulaney. And I love, you know,
I think a scale Williams, but I think a skilled alt comic could. I actually think John Mulaney
would cross over, you know, Pat and Oswald, who was, you know, huge in that scene. He just played
in front of Chappelle's crowd. And I think Chappelle's crowd, uh, is, is, is, is at the very least quite mixed.
But, but you know, um, but also like, I used to want there were, there were some
alt guys when I was coming up that would come to the laughhouse and would do very well. My friend
Mike Robinson was one because he was so, he was so genuine and he was so funny and good at what he,
any, any committed to that was the thing I learned in doing, um, any city room, whether it was, um,
and I mean that across all ethnicities, just the mentality of a city room, which is they want
honesty more than anything. Yeah. And as long as you were genuine people, genuine people.
As long as you were genuine, they, they, they, they didn't care like you had a shot. The second
you were fake, yeah, then it was like you were in trouble. And it, and that went for whether you were in
uh, cause the Philly was the rooms were really segregated, man. So it was like, it was like,
you go to a black room and you go to an Italian room, right? So in an Irish room, you know,
everything was completely separate, um, at least at that time. So, um, but when every crowd wanted
with that, with that sort of inner city, um, um, you know, the inner city culture that they came
from was honesty. So a guy like a Malani, sure, but then, you know, a guy who was somebody we can
shit on from the old saying, uh, I mean, he would probably thrive. That was a bad example. But
no, no, no, no, we don't, we don't need to pick somebody necessarily, but there's a lot of
let's pick somebody. There's a lot of comedians whose whole thing is like, I'm, I'm, uh, you know,
it's almost a twee, like Wes Anderson style of joke writing that is never going to produce a belly laugh
though you might go, well, that's a well crafted joke, you know, and that's never going to fly
when they try and they don't try to treat Patrice Patrice O 'Neil had to, he put it the best way I
ever heard it put ever. He said comedy is ha ha not ah ha. And he was like, I have no time
for ah ha comedy. And he goes, and I have no time for dudes that aren't comedians that aren't fun. And
I remember I said, what do you mean by that? And he said, I don't give a fuck what you do on stage. He
goes, if, when you're hanging out with me and you're not fun, you're not a fucking comic to me.
Right. Like he's like, you know, if you can't sit around and like break balls and laugh with me,
like forget it, dude, you know, and he was right every it was so after he said it to me, I just
started to spot the wet blankets, uh huh, everywhere. And I'd be like, oh, this guy's nice enough,
but Christ almighty, you know, well, the entirety of modern scripted comedy, which I mean TV,
movies, et cetera, is ah ha funny. And it has been for about five years. There is no ah ha funny.
It's been obliterated from the culture. And I think it's terrible. Although, you know,
we had a live tape in last night. And it's like, you know, a lot of its shock value, sure. But I mean,
it's like when I went at adorable 12 year old boy walks in and miss pads like, what the fuck do you
want? And where do I, you know, there's something bracing and and very exciting and about it. And the
reaction that comes out is laughter. And that's a great thing. Yeah, she's she's great, man. She's been
she's been making a lot of noise for a long time now on the comedy circuit. I'm glad her show is
doing well. I'm glad you're working on it. And uh, I doubt she'll she remembers me, but we had a,
we had a fun night at the comedy store one night in the back bar. It was me and her and
I think Tony Hinchcliffe, I don't know, just where we're we're throwing them back back there.
Yeah, she might not remember your your name, but she probably remember you. She doesn't remember a lot
of names, but she's awesome. Let me fly down surprise her anytime. Her her her new special my aunt
actually was like, Hey, I watched her special and I was like, Oh boy. And she's like, what's up with
this uncle Cecil story? She has a story where it's a very famous story, but it's it's traumatic. She
really does spin trauma into gold. These people who get up and truthfully, I'm one of them who were like,
oh, I had such, you know, trauma when I was a kid. Her story is that her and her younger sister
had to prepare their mentally handicapped uncle Cecil whose legs were bent in different directions
and and sat in a back room like in that bed all day. And his father would would ask them to go prepare
him each week by which I mean, jerk him off to get him hard. And then they would pay a neighborhood
prostitute or sex worker to go in and have sex with Uncle Cecil and they would hold each of his
legs down while he would have sex with the woman to keep him balanced. Why does the prostitute prepare
because these prostitutes were not comfortable having sex with the mentally handicapped individual
who who had these deformities as well. So he was like, just get him ready. I'm going to pay them
almost nothing. They go and he gets he gets his nut and then they can leave. Wow. They had to sit
there and like essentially, well, I mean, not only be in the room, but hold him. And it's just like,
okay, that's a level of trauma that nobody talking about their past can go to. And she's making it
funny. Now there are moments where you're like, this is too much. You know, you can't bring this back
back to funny. But that's the beauty of her. She has no line. And that's that's I think why people
really respond to her. Anyway, I love it. She might wind up hating me in two weeks, who knows.
But for right now, I'm doing two seasons down here. I'm enjoying myself.
Sort of lacking in comedy these days. For sure. For sure. Glad.
I have a sort of a news psycho. All right. That will lead us to the movie corner. Beautiful.
Pat, this is one of those things where you I'm going to speak for myself. You don't have to go along
with me. Okay. Is she all right? Not agree with me. You might take it. Let's say.
And this will be my first movie corner too. I watched a documentary called It's been a pleasure
about Billy Connelly, the stand -up comedian. Yeah.
Polarious legend. And a replacement star of head of the class. Let's not. Yes. Yes. I couldn't
sleep the other night. I went for some reason went down a Billy Connelly rabbit hole on YouTube
because I was like, you know, this guy is so admired and respected. But like, I haven't seen
enough of his stand -up to me. He was always the head of the class guy. That's how I knew him. And
I was watching it. I was laughing. And I was really like, man, I should have been watching this guy
a long time ago. And I subscribed to his YouTube channel. And then I was like, where's he at now?
You know, what's he doing now? And then I saw a clip of him on Conan from two years ago. And I was
like, wow, he looks, he got old. Like, he got really old. Like, that's, wow, man. And then I looked
into his Wikipedia page to see how old he was. And I was like, oh, he's approaching 80. But also,
he has Parkinson's disease now. Right. And but he's still speared in whatever. And I was like,
oh, that's why he looked much older than I thought he was going to look. But he's doing well. That's
nice. I went and found subsequent interviews and things of him for recent months. And he's doing very
well, like, considering, which is great. And he's still funny. Although he doesn't tour anymore. But
this all led me to this documentary called It's been a pleasure that was about him and his career
and his impact in comedy, particularly overseas and Britain. But you know, and it had a lot of
interviews with a, you know, talking heads, Russell Brandt, Aislin B,
Elton John, Paul McCartney. I mean, the guy is just beloved. Yeah. I knew he was. I didn't know
to that. I didn't realize to what extent. And it was a joy to watch this thing. But the one
American, it's a wonderful documentary. It's spirited. It's uplifting. You see a guy that's faced with
the, you know, I don't want to say tragedy, but, you know, the unpleasant reality that he's got
Parkinson's and just doesn't let it get him down. And one point he says, he goes, I've got this
thing. And it's going to end me. But I'm okay with that. Like I'm living my life. Like he's,
he's just so, he's got such a grasp on things. So it's great, great, great, great to watch.
But the only American, the interview on this thing is Dustin Hoffman.
Okay. Right. And I was like, that's interesting. What year was this? And I was like, oh, 2020.
Holy shit. Is this the first thing Dustin Hoffman has done since the Me Too stuff came out?
Right. So I looked it up and I was like, yeah, the Me Too stuff was like 2017. And I was like, wow,
like, okay, Dustin Hoffman's like, because I for one, this is where I'm saying I'm speaking for myself.
Yeah. I for one, obviously, do not condone any of these accusations that were leveled against Dustin.
If they are true, I, that's, that is no way to behave. I also though didn't hear anything where I
thought this man should never be allowed to work again. And I, I have, I mean, he did that my,
my Robert's stories. And he was, I was right before though. That was really okay. Yeah. And then he's
been quiet about all this too. Yeah. So I was like, okay. All right. And then I looked up Dustin Hoffman.
This is the new psycho part. And in fact, he is making a return to Broadway. He's got one or two
movies coming out. And this, I get it. I'm on thin ice here. I get, it's a hard thing to put into
words the correct way. I'm just in a certain way relieved to see that you are able to redeem yourself
after some of these things. Now, whether or not people accept it, I don't know. But it seemed for
a while there that no matter what was lobbed against you and no matter who or whomever said it,
whatever it didn't matter, it was just you're done. And that's it. That's what it seemed like it was
going. Yeah. The reality is, no, it's not that. Now, I realize it's not that for guys that are
multi -multi -multi -millionaires and loved globally. Right. And, you know, I'm sure the, the,
the adversaries at least people would say that, well, that's why they're allowed to do that because
they have the money, you know, and that might be true too. I don't know. All I'm saying is, is
I was relieved to see that maybe there was a glimmer of hope that we might be willing to forgive
people who have made potential mistakes. That's all. I hear you and I don't, I don't remember
specifics of dozen often, but it seemed like mostly harassing a language, which isn't ideal. But as we
said on the show and what Matt Damon has come under fire for, there's a difference between harassing
language and sexual assault. So I don't know. I don't know what he did and maybe I'm wrong about that.
But I think with the reason it's starting to calm down a little bit is because the left is realizing,
it's only self -serving, of course, the left is realizing that they're alienating everyone.
They're not only alienating conservatives, they're alienating their own base with A with the COVID
stuff because people feel it's gone on long enough and too far. And B with the, can't the quote,
cancel culture or this outrage at every little thing anyone says or does. And I do think that's
stopping not because they give a shit because they didn't give a shit when they were canceling stuff
either. It's all posturing. I just think they're realizing now no one's ever going to vote for us
if we're the party of canceling anything that anyone might disagree with.
Right. And I do think the tide is turning slowly. But I'm not saying it's a great thing that people
who do terrible things are welcome back to society, but there does need to be some sort of forgiveness
at some point or else what are we doing? What is society? You know, I think a lot of people had
reckoning about things they've done in the past over the pandemic. Maybe it's just having the time to
solve for flex, but it's also just realizing things that especially the entertainment industry
shows you on a daily basis are okay as recently as last week in my case are not, you know, just saying
like, hey, just because you're in TV doesn't mean you can behave this way. So I hope there's a turn
around too. But people who do shit should of course be punished, you know, if they do agree just
shit, it's just it's what it used to be. You get punished for stuff if it's too much. And you
shouldn't be able to buy your way out of it. But you should, you always should you should be
at the original. You made enough money so you should be able to use it. They found another
Epstein associate, dead by quote suicide in his jail cell today. I just, it was anybody famous?
Yeah. It was one of his right -hand men. I just heard of somebody being on that plane.
When he was like, you know, they were on the Epstein plane, right? I was like, they were,
it was somebody Matt Grining was on one of the planes. Bill Clinton, of course. It was a weird one.
It was like a, you know, I'm like a mother Theresa or so that where I was like, wait, what?
Yeah. Or like, you know, like, well, that's the thing. Matt Grining. It was like Tom Bosley or something.
It was a weird, it wasn't Tom Bosley, but I just mean it was like some, like, you're, I was like,
what? You know, but I can't remember who it was now. Grining who does the Simpsons, obviously.
I don't know what, I don't think he has any involvement with it day to day anymore, but he's obviously
beyond rich off it. Yeah. I got a foot massage from like a 16 year old girl on the plane or something.
And he's no one, no one did anything to him. Snoop. And you know, I fucking love Snoop. I've
been an actor, a performer, of course, or just a comedic personality. He's great on Stern, whatever.
But he was accused of rape on Friday to my, to not that it's my decision, but in terms of reading
them, they seemed very credible accusations. And he performed at the Super Bowl two days later.
It's like, that's not necessarily the kind of forgiveness I'm looking for because I don't understand,
and I don't understand that. I don't get it. I read up on that story. I disagree with you. I felt
that it did not sound, and I'm not being funny. I felt that it sounded, I felt like there was a
smoking gun. There's something that's, that's the wrong term. Sorry. But something didn't add up
with that story, whereas I was reading it, the more and more I read, I was like, this doesn't sound
accurate to me, but, or not accurate, but it didn't, you know what I mean.
To me, it's a clear sign to your point that the immediate shutting down of somebody when there's
a little smoke is, it seems, does seem to be dying down. I mean, if we shut people down when there
was a little smoke, Snoop would have been shut down. Folks. Yeah. My two friends of mine and I
have started mostly because I'm very lonely out here, and I don't, I don't hang out with anybody
outside of work, but we've started watching real -time with Bill Marr, and kind of doing a group
text about how horrible it is, and how smug and obnoxious Bill is, and how horrible these jokes are.
Awful, fucking jokes. The jokes suck, but I like where he's coming from. Yeah, no. I mean, his
point of view sometimes is right, but like, I mean, he'll say a joke and sit there smirking,
staring at the audience until they start applauding just out of like, I guess we have to do this?
He drives me nuts. His panels are so boring, he can't get any guests on there anymore because
everybody's scared about being canceled. But yeah, he's talking last night about Snoop, and he had
a black woman on, and she's saying, you know, our mayor is trying to tell us that gangs don't exist,
and that's just not the case, and Margot's, well, obviously not. I mean, did you see Snoop at
the Super Bowl? And I'm like, that's horrifically racist, Bill, and you have the power to edit the show.
Like, what are you doing? Well, I don't get, what was he referring to? Just Snoop in general,
or was he saying like Snoop threw up gang signs or something? Snoop didn't throw up gang signs.
He was, he was being Snoop. I honestly, it felt like there was a black guy at the Super Bowl.
Like, you don't think gangs exist? That's what it felt like to me. And that's strange because he's,
I think, friendly with that whole, I'm sure, crew, I think. Bill Mar was weirdly like friends with
rappers, like it's odd. That blows my mind. But yeah, no, it's, you know, sometimes he says some
really stupid shit, but his overall perspective, I mean, look, he's considered a demon by most of
the left now too, because he says to them to stop protecting your Virgin ears and all that stuff.
But it's weird. His whole audience is still there. I don't know. I see this weird, you know, it's
kind of like a, you know, the center of the mattress where it dips in. Yeah. The concave center
part of the mattress, I feel like it's the libertarian zone. And I feel like unwillingly and
unknowingly, a lot of liberals and Republicans are sliding into that. Yeah.
For us over, you know, bad nobody wants to that because libertarians also say some
bad shit stuff, you know? For sure. I mean, it's just, we're fucked. It's all fucked.
Anyway, what's your movie corner? What's your first movie corner, Pat?
Let's do it. I soar. Oh, I know what I watched.
Wow. I've just, okay, here we go. Sorry. I watched Kemi. Steven Soderberg's Kemi.
Soderberg is in a place now where he releases a new movie to HBO Max every eight weeks.
And everybody raves about all of them. And look, I love Steven Soderberg. I always do.
I took a Steven Soderberg class in college where we watched his first eight films and discuss
them. And it was one of my favorite classes of all time. I think he's a brilliant director.
This stage of his career where he is now shooting movies in two days and and throwing them up
for you to watch or whatever, fine. And we can all marvel at what had how,
what do you call that when you make a lot of stuff, Joe? Starts with a pee, I want to say prolific.
We can all marvel at how prolific he is. But these are average movies at best that no sudden move.
And I love, I love a film noir. But it just kind of suck. And this Kemi has kind of cool parts.
But it's not Kemi. Kemi? Kemi.
Joe, you just sent me a text intended for your bar, I think. Oh, sorry.
Unless you're planning on giving me a drink, in which case, let's do it.
Um, if I was there, baby. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Kemi, Kemi stars Zoe Kravitz, who was an actress
who used to do absolutely nothing for me. And little by little, she's growing on me. I think she's
very talented and obviously very beautiful. Um, the movie has no other real stars.
The supporting cast is insane. Let me just read you some names. Derek Belgadio,
star of that Netflix, like magic special, Robin Givens, Kevin Ratray, the older brother from
home alone, Rita Wilson, it's just, it's nuts. Wait, the older brother from the original home alone.
Right. Buzz. He's become a, he's become a character actor. But now he's been canceled for beating his
girlfriend up. But Soderberg is at a point where he's like, everybody's tied up doing my other
movie. Who's who's available for this one? Yeah. He, I mean, he shoots these things seemingly
very quickly. This was another COVID thing. It actually takes place during COVID and it's mentioned.
And this woman who's scared of leaving her home, um, starts, she, she basically reviews the data that
goes into a, a Siri or one of those Amazon Alexa type things. And in reviewing all the details,
she hears what sounds like an assault. Um, and that's a cool premise. My guess is that Soderberg,
and his writer went in and said, we want to do the movie Blowout, Brian DePalma's amazing movie,
Blowout with Travolta. But we want to do it with an Alexa where somebody who's, who listens to hours
of that stuff, here's a crime and then gets involved. Not a bad idea. There's exciting scenes in it.
But the last 10 Soderberg movies, the one with Meryl Strebe and then this one and that one, uh,
I've said, it's cool, Steven, that you made this with an iPhone, you know, he gets pushed around in
a wheelchair with an iPhone and makes these movies in a week. But none of them are satisfying movies
to me at all. And I, I feel like we're sort of lost a great filmmaker, even though he's hiding in plain
sight. There was no real better commercial filmmaker. Look at those oceans pictures. You look at out
a site. I mean, he was making huge entertainment that really hit the masses, but they felt like 70s
movies. That's what was always so amazing about him to me. Um, and now he just seems to be this guy
who's content making little indies, but they're the kind of stuff that wouldn't even get released if
anybody else did them. So I'm a little bummed out, but it's, it's worth a watch and it's 89 minutes,
so you're not going to lose too much of your time. All right. Um, I got it, man, I haven't seen much,
but I'm going to go back to some Christmas things I never covered. I just believe it or not.
So I bought the Blu -ray of the Grinch this year for Christmas.
Cartoon, Jim Carrey. The second cartoon. Yeah. And the new special edition Blu -ray has the
other Grinch specials on it. Okay. One of them is called Halloween is Grinch Night, which is what
I want to talk about now. Uh, look, we got to be the only podcast where you're getting an in -depth
review of Halloween is Grinch Night. That much I know. I'd never seen this. I never knew there were
other Grinch specials. It was one of the reasons I felt the need to buy this new Blu -ray release.
You know, the whole thing with the Grinch is this beautiful story of this guy that hates Christmas,
and his heart is two sizes too small, and it's not his fault. And then the, the weable wobbles,
whatever the fuck they're called down in that village, make his heart grow, and he learns what love is,
and he learns to love the people, and they create a symbiotic relationship. And it's a beautiful story.
Halloween is Grinch Night, erases all of that completely. He's evil again. Yeah.
There's a, it's one of the most dire children's specials I've ever seen. It's so depressing.
There's a scene where his dog sings a song alone about how abused he is,
and the life he should have, but he doesn't, because he's prisoner of this awful Grinch.
Is this Christ? Does the dog even talk in the original Grinch?
No, I don't think so. And it's like, you know, he's kind of shitty to it, but it's like
kind of like funny shitty, you know what I mean? It's not like, it's not disturbing.
Yeah. This thing is like a fucking PETA commercial.
Sarah McClockland's thinking, yeah, yeah. And then like, yeah, it's literally that sad. I'm not,
I'm not exaggerating. And then I'm, and then it ends with the Grinch going back up into the hills,
cackling and saying like, I'll be back. I'll have my revenge. There's another sequence in this
where the kid, the main kid, and this one, it's a little boy instead of a little girl.
He's like going to face off with the Grinch. And like, the whole thing is just like, the Grinch is
going to, this kid's going to, is trying to be like, I have nothing to be afraid of. And the Grinch is
like, no, no, no, I'm going to give you something to be afraid of. It's so sinister.
And depressing that I just was like, I don't want to want, I don't think I want to watch this
ever again. Yeah. But it's worth a watch because I just couldn't, the 60s were a different time.
And 70s were just a different time. Like, it's, it's wild where they went with children's entertainment
back then. I didn't understand what the point of this thing was. I mean, we've talked so many times
about how kids, how scary kids movies were. And it's not because we were kids because they're
scary to this day. And I think that kids not having that darkness in their entertainment is going to
lead to a lot of fucked up kids. I mean, it helps to know there's darkness in the world. Maybe not
dogs being abused. But come on. Yeah. No, I even Beethoven, I think had dogs getting like shocked
and stuff. You know, like the kids need to know even in, even in family friendly entertainment,
that the world sucks. They, they need to be at least a little hint of that to kids or else
they're in for a very, very, very rude awakening. Yeah, I agree completely. And as a bonus
quickie, I tried to rewatch the Jim Carrey one on the heels of this. It is just a piece of shit. Yeah,
it's really moving. It is fucking terrible. I don't, my only explanation is potentially studio
intervention. I don't understand how this is a Ron Howard movie, the way it's pieced together.
I don't understand how this, this was, this was when Carrie was Carrie. I mean, this was supposed to
be huge. I just don't understand how they fucked it up so badly. But man, did they, did they ever?
It's terrible. The one thing I'll say about the Ron Howard, Jim Carrey Grinch is it's slightly
better than the Mike Myers cat in the hat. And they're similar movies. I prefer the Mike Myers
kind of hat just, just be caught, not because it's better, just because it, it's at least creepy.
No, it's at least like disturbing where you could watch it high and be like, what the fuck is going,
you know, the grants you can't even, there's not even that factor. You're just like, no, it's just sucks.
There were jokes in the cat in the hat where like you would see a hot woman and his hat would
grow like a boner. And you're like, what are you doing guys? Just absurd. I, for some
reason was reading about his new show, Mike Myers, The Pintavrit, which is something he used to
refer to when he was the Scottish father and so I married an axeman. He was like, I think it's The
Pintavrit, the Pintavrit, like a group of men who control the world, kind of like the Illuminati.
And he had this conspiracy theory about them. And now he's bringing it to Netflix. And look,
the guy's past his prime. But I think counting out a talent like that is, is an error because he's
a genius. I'm excited. The Super Bowl commercial he did was great. I was like, he's funny still.
Yeah, I mean, yes, I saw it. I wasn't laughing out loud at it. But I mean,
I love Dr. Evil and Austin Powers, of course. I'd had, it had real jokes in it. Like when she's like
the, the world isn't, the environment is a trouble. He goes, tear. Yeah, like it had really funny,
you know, I like that it had the whole, you know what, Scott? You're like, you know, it was fun.
It was making me laugh. But I was like, okay, this guy could be funny. Look, if you can make a,
if the Super Bowl commercial is this funny, yeah, he said there were some bad ones. Jesus Christ.
I want to recommend, I'm very excited to recommend, especially to our listeners who I know will love
this. And Joe, who I've already told he should watch this, the American scream, which I said it allowed
the other night and realized that it was a play on the American dream. I had, it didn't connect with
me until you just said that. I actually think it's a bad title because it's not clear that it's
upon at all. But it is available on to be. And as you know, things on to be are not there for long
sometimes. So I would recommend checking it out for free. But it is a documentary about, I think
four different groups of people who make haunted houses out of their own homes. And I'm not, so not
talking like the big, you know, corporate things you go to. These are neighborhood haunted houses,
one of whom has like a thousand person line at Halloween. They're doing it for no money. They're
doing it out of love. There is a guy who I saw so much of myself in that I know for a fact if I had
not followed my dream, I would be doing shit like this. I used to maybe inspired by the Rosanne
Halloween episodes. But I used to go all out. And I had, I once I had my mom crouch down in our
freezer. The big freezers where you lift the lid like a car hood. And I had her hiding out at the end
of it. She jumped out and scared people in a mask and then you know, the bowl of eyeballs that are
grapes and all that stuff. I used to get really into it. And it was just a creative outlet, you know.
So these people are people who are living for the most part soul sucking miserable jobs where
their boss is take advantage of them. And the guy whenever they ask him what he does, he's embarrassed
to say that he's like a computer engineer. And then he gets laid off at one point. He's worked
for this company for 30 years and they just let him go. And he's like, well, you know, I'm very excited
because I get a severance package. So I'm going to be able to put that towards my haunted house this
year. And they're just people who refuse to let that be their life. They refuse to let it be their
life that they go in and sit at a desk all day. They have this creative outlet. And this guy drives
his family nuts. He's like for all of October, he's like, my family pretty much hates me. He's got
them all working on things. Then they're because he's spending their food money on. No, it's
dangly skeletons from the Halloween adventure. Right. Well, so he's a tragic character. He keeps saying
like, you know, my family is so great. And I love them so much because they let me do this. And you're
like, they're, you know, the kids are like, you know, I always wanted a this for Christmas. And I
understand that I'm never going to get it because of the Halloween stuff. But there's sadness to it
for sure. There's a they don't say what's up with them. But there's some mental handicapped
inness in a guy about my age and his elderly father. They're both clearly not well. There should
have been a whole documentary about these two anyway. But they make a haunted house in their neighborhood.
And it's just a way to get out like they have so much pain in their lives. And to me, way better than
this fucking HBO station 11 about these people trying to put on a Shakespeare play as the world ends
due to a deadly virus pandemic. And well, the magic of Shakespeare, this movie has the exact same
theme, which is that art can save your life. But it's so on pretentious and so beautiful. And these
people are such tragic, amazing figures. It's very funny, of course. It's kind of like American
movie, which is another amazing documentary where, you know, these people aren't going to ever get
rich off their their creativity. But they need to do it to survive and get through the soul crushing
day. By the end of this movie, I was weeping out of nowhere. I was like, what is happening? But I
just related and it made me appreciate that even though there are ups and downs, I do get to live
a life where I am compensated for my creativity. Yeah. And this is why I hate when I hate too strong
the word. And I've got nothing against the man. But this is why I don't like to see like Ben
Stiller. We were talking about this the other day dipping his toe now into the horror pond.
Horror is the great underdog genre. And it should remain there. And that's it. Like, you know, it's like
I don't want to watch horror go from being like iced tea to MC Hammer. And that's not a knock at
MC Hammer. But my point is is like, it's better when it's not embraced by the mainstream. And even though
iced tea now is a cultural icon, you know, which is which is wild. And the honest man on Twitter.
Yeah. The funniest man on Twitter. Like, you know, it's just it's not the point. The point is
is like the iced tea still maintains like some sort of independence. Like he's still able to kind of
work in his own lane. And I think that I think that about horror. I don't want to see it get too big.
Yeah. And, you know, I worry a bit with even though they're great people out there like Mike
Flanagan who we're going to discuss today. I get nervous when people start to go, you know,
oh, this new horror thing is all the rage. It's like, no, no, no, don't I don't want it to be all
the rage. I want to go over here. I want the documentary about the horror people to remain on
Sun. Yeah. And a beautiful quiet little story. Yeah. I don't think there's any danger of a
becoming mainstream. Unless you're talking about a once in a 10 year thing like the sixth sense
which hits all the quadrants or whatever, because there are there's a huge subset of people.
My wife included who can't handle horror and don't want to want Vince Averalds another one. No,
I'll never watch a horror movie. So I think that will always keep it cool because some people can't
handle being scared. I hope so. I hope so. I just don't want it ever to become a one of the darling
genres because that's when the censorship and all that stuff comes in. But anyway, my last movie,
Christmas thing again, deck the halls. I always wanted to see it. Never saw it. Is this this
Davido and Broadway? Vito and Broderick. Yeah. Davido actually, I'm sorry, and then I'll shut up.
I the last speaking of Tooby, I woke up one morning. This is the last time I blacked out,
which was right before I came down here to Atlanta. And I had watched 45 minutes of deck the halls
and did not remember selecting it. So that's the impact it had on me. It's an interesting film. Yeah.
Look, it's a family holiday movie. It's got its charm. You're not going to put this in your
permanent rotation. But I love Davido. I love Broderick. Davido, just so you know, is married in the movie
to Christine Chenoworth in her prime. He's a car salesman who's very good at selling cars.
He's, you know, it's the classic thing. Broderick, you know, is like the toast of the town.
Everybody loves him. I think he might be the mayor or something. He's got the perfect family,
blah, blah, blah, blah. It's Christmas time. The annoying neighbor moves in, played by Danny
Davido. Sure. Him and his wife are a little wild for this neighborhood kind of thing. And Danny
Davido's character has one goal, which is to make his Christmas display on his lawn and house
so bright that it's able to be seen from space. That's the plot of the movie. All right.
And this task becomes a major annoyance and problem in Matthew Broderick's life because he lives
right across the street from him and the battle of the neighbors ensues. It's the classic whatever.
It had a few laughs. Again, this is the kind of thing. You know, I'd watch this with my mom or
something. Right. But I'm a sucker. I'm a sucker for Danny Davido. I mean, I can't. The guy can
do no wrong in my legend. Legend. Legend. You know, I've watched Hoffa three times last week.
I've owned the movie. I've seen it so many times. And I watched it three times last week because I
just couldn't get enough. But I wish we got more movies from him as a director because he's an
excellent director. He reminds me of Ben Stiller as a director, actually. I think Ben Stiller probably
learned a lot from him on reality bites. I remember telling a woman at a party once. She said at the time
she said, who's your favorite? Who's your favorite? I said, I don't know. She goes, well, who's the
director you love? And I said, I love Danny Davido. And she laughed at me. And I said, you're laughing
because you don't know what you're talking about. Yeah. Go watch some of his movies. He's an amazing
director. There is no better director of dark comedy. War of the Roses is a textbook.
Perfect black comedy. And the visual shitty doesn't it is amazing. Anyway, if you want to quench
a holiday thirst, deck the halls is a fun, harmless, but not benign holiday movie that you could
watch with the family or whatever. And what better time than late February? I've never seen Christmas
with the cranks either. And that's got a pretty powerhouse cast. My mom saw that movie. I won
Christmas. And I remember it was the only movie she had seen all year. Yeah. And she kept bringing up
how Christmas with the cranks wasn't as good as she thought it was going to be. That's how I feel
about surviving Christmas with Gandalfini and Affleck and Catherine O 'Hara. And it's in theory funny,
but it just I watch it every couple of years thinking it'll grow funny. And it just doesn't. Yeah.
Jingle all the ways like that. You're like, this is gotta be hilarious. It's Schwarzenegger and
Phil Hartman. What could go wrong? It's terrible. It really is terrible. I watched it this year again.
I do have all these Christmas ones. I'm like, I need a new Christmas staple. And then I'm like,
oh, ain't this. I would like to close briefly by recommending a
excellent thriller that I had never seen directed by the great Sydney Lumet. I've been
slowly trying to see all his movies. But of course, there's 150 of them all worthwhile. And of
course, he's got minimum 10 masterpieces. But Guilty of Sin was written by horror icon The Great Larry
Cohen. Oh, that's very cool. And it is such a good script. The combination of like, you know,
he's a he's a schlock master Larry Cohen, but one of the best to do it. The combination of like
a cheesy twisty kind of script with the legendary hand of Sydney Lumet makes for such a fun fucking
movie. It's Don Johnson. Best I've ever seen him as this guy who, I don't even want to spoil it,
but he comes into Joe, your favorite Rebecca De Mornay's office. She's a very hot lawyer.
And she's in her underwear immediately. Her boyfriend is played by this guy with a big mustache and
curly brown hair, who I kept thinking, who is this man? I know I've seen him. And then I realized
it was Steven Lang from Avatar who has like a curly fro in this movie. It is so great. Johnson
plays the biggest scumbag I've seen in a while. And he's essentially wanting De Mornay to defend
him for murdering his wife. But she is almost certain that he did it right off the bat. He
keeps tricking her. Like his thing is fucking with beautiful women. Like, and he's been able to
coast through life on his charm. He has a scene that I rewound and laughed at so many times,
where he's sitting at a bar. He finishes a scotch and this beautiful little homely to be honest
turns to him and she goes, Hey, yeah, can I buy you a drink? And he goes, no, but you can pay for
that one. Slides the bill and the empty glass tour and leaves. And he has no point in the movie
except to establish this guy as a piece of shit who you want to see get his come up. And De Mornay's
awesome. Lang is awesome. Jack Warden in one of his last roles is awesome as a mentor to De Mornay.
The only way you can find it is is plunking down the the 199 on Amazon. But I recommend that it's
really fun. Guilty as sin. And I got it here. Bookmarked. All right. All right, folks,
let's get to the show at hand. The review. Mike Flanagan's
I almost said nightmare alley. Jesus Christ. Midnight mass. I also want to go back to the Q &A episode
we previously did. One of the questions I can't I don't remember who asked it was, you know, who do
you think is out there right now doing great hard work or whatever consistently? I said,
Mick Harris, which I am happy about. It was a little bit of a cheat answer. He's been around for a
long, long time. I was just happy that he's still around doing stuff. But I would like to resubmit
and say for as far as newer blood, Mike Flanagan, I think, is probably the best I've seen in
a long time. The guy knows what he's doing. He really does. And he doesn't always hit the mark.
But he really, really knows what he's doing. He's very good. I love when he does other people stuff
more than his own. I thought his doctor sleep was as good a shining sequel as we could have ever
dreamed of at this stage of the game. Yeah. And the director's cut is even better.
I did not watch either of his hauntings. The haunting of Hill House or the haunting of blind
manner. But everybody loved them. And I want to watch them. I like him a lot. But I will say his stuff
always taps out at about the B plus range for me. I've never, I never go, I loved his Gerald's
game. He's a great match with Stephen King material. But his own stuff feels, it always feels very
derivative to me of Stephen King. Midnight Mass feels super derivative of a lot of things like Salem's
lot and so forth. But it's clearly very personal. It's a story about dealing with alcoholism and
guilt and grief and all this. And it wasn't always even a traditional horror thing. I mean,
a lot of it just plays like straight ahead drama. But what did you think overall, Joe?
I really, okay, so it took me a while to watch this.
Because first and foremost, it's another one of these shows where it's like seven hour plus
long episodes. You're like, all right, guys, this is three movies. Yeah. This is a trilogy. You're
asking me to sit down and watch here. So I, you know, and it's not, this is not a thing where you could watch
one movie and say, I didn't see the sequels. I'm good. Right. This is like, you're not getting the whole
story unless you finish it. So it's a commitment. So it took me a while to start it. I finally did sit
down and start it. The other reason it took me a while was I did watch haunting of Hill House. And
I thought it was well done, but it wasn't for me because it got a little too into the personal
lives of the characters. I just, it's stuff I just didn't really care about. I wanted to stay on the
horror. And then I saw Dr. Sleep and I loved it. And I was like, okay. And then I realized, oh,
this, he did Jones game. I like that quite a bit too. So anyway, I mean, two of the scariest scenes
in modern horror are the ones that stick with me are the hand cutting off in Gerald's game,
which will stay with me until the day I die. It's rough. And, and the Jacob Tremblay scene in Dr.
Sleep, the little boy, I was like, dear God, like people were looking around the theater like,
should I be watching this? It was so intense. Yeah, it's rough stuff. If he can, if he can sustain that
over a whole movie, which I don't think he's done yet, it's going to be something incredible.
Well, I agree that I don't think he's done it yet, but I also wonder if he wants to do it.
Yeah, I feel like he, I feel like he's a lot like he's a lot like a Mike Nichols or Woody Allen
in the sense that those directors decided to take a dramatic approach to comedy. And not right
for the most part, not, not produce and direct out and out comedies, but produce things that
had a lot of human weight to them that also had some very funny moments. I feel like he's doing that
with horror. I feel like he, he's starting from the place of the characters and the emotional journey,
kind of like Coppola with the Godfather where, you know, it's been discussed a million times and we've
talked about it on here. You could, you could set the Godfather in any world. It doesn't have to be the mob.
They could have been oil barons or something like it's about the family. Yeah.
And I think that Mike, or sorry, I think, yeah, Mike Flanagan, I don't think he makes self -conscious
horror. I think he makes stories about people that have horror elements to them.
I think that's brilliant, Joe. Let me just stop you. When you said Nichols and Woody Allen,
I was like, what the fuck are you talking about, Joe? How are you going to make this make sense? And
you're very much. But back to your original question, what did I think of it overall? I liked it
quite a bit. I thought it was too long for sure. The short review before we get into it is I liked
it quite a bit. I thought it really had it where it counted. I was intrigued. I wanted to see what
was happening. I wanted to see what was going to come next. It reminded me a lot of the outsider
in the sense that it came out swinging pretty good. And it ended on a very strong note.
But there were moments in the middle, you know, around episodes four or five, you start to go
Christ, can I just read the synopsis of this one? Do I need to watch this whole, you know what I mean?
Like, and then you go through it and you realize it was important to see. But I think it could have
been shorter. That's my major note. But, you know, plot -wise, you can't do much better for
it from my opinion in a horror sense. You know, you got, takes place in an isolated island with a
population of, you know, like four dozen people or something. You've got the plot of the town is
awaiting the great return of the mon senior of their church who went on a religious journey. We're
off to a good start. You find out the mon seniors old. He doesn't come back. In his stead comes a
young priest who's mysterious. And then like later, got us, got to call him out. Amazing performance.
That guy used to be the like comedic relief on the new adventures of old Christine.
That's funny. This is the first thing I ever saw him in. And I was like, this guy's amazing. I got
to look him up. And I'm like, Oh, he was like a sitcom guy. And I started watching his clips on
old Christine. And I'm like, Oh, he's like a goofy, like funny guy. Yeah, he was the goofy,
I think brother of Julia Louis Dreyfus. And I gave that show a couple years due to how much I love
her. And it's, it's a well -written show. But I had never, I was like, this guy is a great actor.
And how many actors are like that that nobody will ever take a chance on, you know? He's great.
And then miracles start to happen. And something's clearly a foot.
So it's a great premise. It's a great start. You know, pretty quickly, these miracles are
probably the result of something unholy that seems good at first, but it's going to turn out to not
be. But the cast is tremendous. Hey, Mish, as you said, I'm glad you remembered.
Zach Gilford from Friday night lights, who I'm, which you watch guys see, he's the guy who
kills the, Erie has the dy. Oh, he's the lead guy, Riley. Okay. My wife and I are rewatching Friday
night lights. And I loved him on that show. And then never saw him again. And I got it because
everybody else in that show was clearly destined for superstardom. And he's just a real in the pocket
kind of actor. But he's, he's great in this too. He's great. He's great.
Tomas. Tomas Henry Thomas Henry Thomas for kid for me. Yeah. Great seeing him again all over the
place. He's a Flanagan. I like what Flanagan does. He has a, he sort of has a repertoire
of actors that he uses. His, his wife is one. She plays the, I'm blanking on her name too.
I don't know any of their names because they're, I only ever see them in Mike Flanagan things.
But Kristen Laman. No, that's not his wife. His wife plays the pregnant lady. Oh,
wait, you mean his wife in real life? In real life. Yeah. I thought you meant Henry Thomas's wife
on the show. Yeah. No, she was great too, though. The lady that played Henry Thomas's wife.
Yes. The main female, the female leads in this are Flanagan's wife in real life, who's a tremendous
actor. She's great. Okay. And then the lady that plays like the evil chaplain lady.
She's fucking amazing, man. Where has this lady been? Samantha Sloughian. She had only been in Hush
by Mike Flanagan, which I really liked a lot. And she comes from like sort of acting royalty.
I looked her up and her parents were famous actors and her brothers and actor, I believe. But she's,
she's great. Like, God, she's one of the most hateful characters I have ever seen in the last
20 years, where you're like, you're the whole the entire series. You're like, somebody
give it to this bitch. Yeah. She reminded me of Marsha Gay. Yeah. She reminded me of Marsha Gay,
I liked it quite a bit. I would put it in the B plus range. I think everything you're saying
is true. The actress were incredible. I think I agree with you that it lagged a little in the middle
and could have been shorter, even though you need this stuff. But I, my issue with it, if I had an
issue that I had to bring up is that there's a lengthy monologue by every character, every couple of
minutes. And it's, it almost becomes comical by episode six and seven when that, you know,
it's like, why don't you just put a spotlight on him on a stool on all black stage and have
a delivery of these monologues. And, and that's just something, and Netflix, he's made so much money
for Netflix. He's not taking notes anymore. But that's the kind of note that he should have gotten.
Hey, you need to find a way to make this into dialogue because you just have characters being like,
I remember when I was, and he does it so much, yeah, that eventually started to take me out a bit of
bit. And I would say that's really my main issue. I mean, it's, it's, it's very well written. It's
clearly very personal. Flanagan got sober a couple of years ago. And I just think it's really well
done. It's very solid. It's very solemn. It's not scary, you know, but it's, it's scary parts though.
Yeah, it's spooky parts. It's very well done. It's very well done. Well, spoiler alert,
but well, first of all, to the point you just made, that was Pinkstone's major note on it too. He was
like, these monologues were like, it was out of control. And once he said that, I was like, oh,
yeah, Jesus, you're right. Yeah. He said that his wife, when they were watching it, would be like,
we get it, like, you know, like yelling that at the TV. It's acting like shit. You know, it's like,
come on. I was watching this. I was in Albany last night with Sal. He was playing the egg theater
up there. And I went up with him and opened for him. And I, in between shows, I was like, dude, I'm
sorry, but I got to watch the finale of Midnight Mass. I need to review it tomorrow. Yeah. And he
didn't know what it was. And he's like, yeah, I don't know, whatever, I don't care. And I didn't have
headphones. So I just had to sit there watching it on my iPad. And like, one of these speeches was
going. And he just at one point goes, it's a bit heavy handed. And I was like, yeah, it is. It's like,
yeah, they're these brooding monologues. But anyway, um, it, uh, that, that I, I, I, I, I agree with,
it was also forget this. Oh, oh, so spoiler. What you find out is happening is, it's a vampire story.
It's very Salem's lot, Pat, as you said, right? Yeah, Stephen King. Um, it's a vampire story. The
priest, this beloved priest, uh, Montsenior, you find out actually is the young priest who's returned
because he's been rejuvenated how, by what he thinks is an angel who bit his neck and gave him blood
to drink. And he thinks this was an angel from God because he feels revitalized and strong. And
at first, the town doesn't realize that this is actually the Montsenior. And this angel is clearly
a winged vampire demon thing. Uh, strangely, nobody in the town has heard of vampires or how they
work. I agree. That's, that's a little weird. That's a little weird. But so the, so most of them think
this thing's an angel too. But, uh, yeah. Uh, and anyway, obviously it all goes to shit. Um, you know,
you know, people's good things start happening for people, a crippled girl who's wonderful in this.
I then the young actress who plays the crippled girl, she's wonderful. She's able to walk again.
The, the, the, the, the, the doctor character, she's great. But then her mom is like this old
woman with dementia who, who by the way is played by the hottest actress that's ever lived. Uh,
and, and like, you know, through most of this thing, I thought it was legitimately a 90 year old woman.
And then see, I did to, to me, everyone who is revealed to be an old age makeup, I knew the second
I saw them that it was bad old age makeup. She was the only one I didn't pin it on. But I noticed
it with Henry Thomas though, because I was like, I'm pretty sure Henry Thomas is the same age as his
son. Yeah. Why is he playing the dad? I was like, Oh, they're going to de age some of these people.
But the old lady, I fell for that one for whatever reason. Um, but anyway, you know, the,
the mom becomes young again. And then you find out that she and the priest are actually the parents
of her daughter. And again, to go back to what I was saying earlier, this priest who's on this mission
to convert this town and make them drink the, and who secretly giving them the blood of this vampire.
And then it all culminates with him trying to convince them all to kill themselves so they can be reborn.
And he does successfully convince most of them to do so. His story ends with him seeing the error of his
ways. Falling back in love with the, with the now young mother of this doctor character,
the reveal that this doctor is their daughter. And him, you know, his journey ending with him saying,
I did this all for you. And I was wrong. And we need to try to stop it now. And that's what I mean with
Flanagan, like, what, what would have ended with most horror movies is the priest is evil. Yeah.
But he acts good, you know, which is fine too. It's one of the things I loved about Carnival. I
But this doesn't do that. It's like, no, the priest is misled. And you think that he's good. And
then you think that he's evil. And then you realize that he has a love that he lost because he was a
priest and it was forbidden. And he dies in the end with her by her side. And that was really what his
story was. And again, you take that out of the supernatural realm, you could put that into a million
different scenarios where it would make exactly as much emotional sense. But that's, I mean, basically
in the end, it's, it's a vampire story, you know, and interesting enough because I grew up very
Catholic and I went to Catholic school for 12 years. I never realized the parallels. So kudos to
Mike Flanagan. I never realized the parallels between the vampire mythology and the biblical
tales of Jesus where you drink Jesus's blood, you become eternal. The vampire makes you a turn. All
these parallels. I was like, oh, this because at first I was like, why is Mike Flanagan doing a
vampire? Do we have an vampire? And I was like, oh, because he's connected these very interesting dots
between religion and vampires. And wow, that's very cool. I've never seen that done before.
It's a, it's a very deep show in a lot of ways as a as a guy raised Catholic. I found a lot to kind of
think on about it. But you know, when I write a script, the first thing I always do is go back
and cut monologues because they're a writer being in love with his own voice. And I think if Flanagan
was working with a great producer who could tell him like, hey, man, come on. He'd be unstoppable.
And I do think that he's great. And I'm waiting for that, that original project from him that
dazzles me as much as Doc sleep did. I would like to see him start doing a, well, he, you know,
he did Oculus, which people really loved. Haven't seen it. I own it. Haven't seen it.
I saw it a bit of it when it first hit cable. And and I remember just kind of not being that into it.
But I feel like I deserve it deserves a revisit. But you know, he did Oculus. He did hush.
I like. These were pretty acclaimed, you know, harmless. And I hope I liked Ouija too.
I love that movie. I thought it was awesome. I love Gerald's game.
Yeah. So I'd like to see him return back to cinema more frequently with original ideas.
I would love to have seen what the, what a, what a two hour version of this story
might have looked like. You know, um, right. But um, and the same thing with haunting of Hill House.
I did not see the other one, Blimeander, but his third house, you know, he's doing a trilogy
of these house ones. So follow the House of Usher is the next one, which I'm so interested.
I love that. I love that Vincent Price movie. But that's a 70 minute movie that he's making a 10 -hour
thing. Yeah, it's weird. Cause I think it's a post do. I don't think Poe ever wrote any novels, right?
He only wrote short stories. Yeah. It's a Poe. So so my point is is how long is the short story?
Maybe it's a novella, but they're going to turn it into right. You know, 10 fucking hours. We'll see.
Anyway, um, my hog is up for midnight mass. My hog is up for midnight mass.
As it always was, when I was a kid and got dragged to midnight mass on Christmas Eve,
I would sit there with a boner feeling like Jesus was going to send me to hell because that's what
my parents told me. Um, yeah, it's, it's a real solid piece of work worth your time. And uh, see you
in hell, pod is the Instagram account, the pet wall, Twitter and Instagram.
Joe, Joe to Rosa comedy, Twitter and Instagram, uh, catch me at Joey roses or come through
if you're around. Joey roses NYC dot com for all info. We're open now Tuesday through Sunday.
And I'll be on tour, by the way, come see me in. So March is the next batch of shows,
Philadelphia, then I'll be at South by Southwest doing some stand up. You doing Atlanta?
I'm not doing Atlanta yet. I, I will. I, maybe you may come through and just say,
hello, good day. Play the, play the laughing school. Yes. Many times. Many times.
I'm doing the punchline more. Well, it's too short notice now. They're probably booked down through.
But usually do the punchline when I come through. But, but anyway, uh, Philly and South by Southwest
in uh, April, no, March, I'm sorry. Um, April, I'll be out west actually.
I'll be, uh, I'm supposed to do Irvine improv in the San Diego comedy, uh, the comedy club there.
And then, uh, uh, may be back in Austin again at the Creek and Cave. Anyway, go to joderosa info .com
for tickets and info. That's it for us folks. We'll see you next time. Yes, we will see you with our
best of 2021 special. And we will see you in hell.