Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Bet MGM game sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM dot com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Wager.
Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia only, games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal, durable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamber.
Talk about stepping on that.
It's time to level up your game, introducing the all -new ESPN app.
All of ESPN, all in one place, your home for the most life sports
and the best championship moment.
The electricity is palpable.
Step up your game with no annual contract required.
It's the ultimate fan experience.
Level up for more on the ESPN app or at Stream .esPN .com.
Sign up now.
here we are back with another episode of we'll see you in hell. Take it away Pat. Well,
all right. Happy Monday everybody. We got a big one this week. The remake of it. Joe and
and I saw an early screening, it's very exciting.
We got an IT, what was it, a 3D viewer?
What was that thing that gave us?
The worst swag I've ever received.
We're virtual reality headset.
So you look at virtual content online
and it springs to life and it's just one of those things
where your phone is capable of doing
being a virtual reality screens,
but you need to put it in like a headset piece.
So they that's the shittiest way to do it is a cardboard. I mean, if you really want to look like a fucking complete jackass
Aside from having virtual reality goggles on your face. They also are dorned with it
You know art work. Yeah, it seems to have nothing to do with one another. Nothing movie takes place in 1988
They barely had computers. Why not a stuffed clown? Wouldn't that have been cool? Well, I think I ever got was when I saw frankenweeny back when I was a movie critic
And they gave you a little frankenweeny and it was awesome. I got stuff frankenweeny
Yeah, I will say this thing we went to was referred to as a premiere
Yeah, we were off in some goddamn side theater with people that looked like
People that I wouldn't want I wouldn't live led into the movie on a regular day
I know well, that's what that when you're a critic like the
You know the celebs nothing it had any celebs, but the stars will walk down the red carpet and the critics you like start
You start to you start to go towards the red carpet like go into the movie theater and they'll just grab you back
No, no, no, no, sir. You're you're over here with these hideous troll
You can't sit with the famous people anyway folks, but before we get too far into this I I guess I'd like to get on with with the show and
At the same time on
With the Joe
Ooh, very nice, very nice, Pat.
It's getting hard to think of variants on it.
I've done them all.
I miss the, I think if you circle back around
to the old stuff to like,
I'll bring it back.
The band does.
I hit one that I could not surpass,
or I would shatter my vocal,
I would have like a polyp on my vocal cords.
I went too far once in a,
you gotta get back to your roots with this thing.
But anyway, when you went to the it premiere, I running a Warner Brothers show, I have an
assistant.
So I was like, look, I don't ask you to do anything.
I've never asked him to pick up my dry cloud.
I've never asked him to do one thing for me.
You go, give me into this fucking it.
It's a Warner Brothers movie.
I run a fucking Warner Brothers show.
Give me into this fucking movie.
Yeah.
And then I threw my iced coffee into his eyes.
So then sure enough, I asked him one day, I think he had probably forgotten the request to be honest, but I asked him and he's like, yeah, let me check and then he goes, it's tonight you want to go. I was like, hell yeah.
Text Joe, it's in like three hours, Joe had nothing to do.
Yeah, I was psyched.
We were both real pumped.
I mean, I
And the review by the way
We won't bleed into the review just yet because we do our little segment thing sure sure, but but we were both there
Yeah, sorry. We were both pumped and and maybe we were
Satisfied
Maybe we weren't but they weren't the mystery really keeps you hanging on cut to an ad
We're doing we're gonna do like two minutes of talk and then another ad Pat's movie corner
That's a movie corner, we're getting right into it.
Oh, but that would, wait, shout out to a new friend.
I think there's no four play anymore in this one.
Well, shout out to a new friend.
We went to Pat and I went to a bar after the show.
Oh, yeah.
And as soon as we won before the show.
Yeah, as I'm before.
As soon as we walked into the post bar.
Yes.
Very kismet strange scenario.
We went to like three bars, they all sucked.
Pat was like in the, in the 11th hour was like,
oh, there's this great place we should go to.
I just remembered we're right near it. I said, okay, let's go boarders. Give him a little shout out. We walk in
First thing I say to Pat hey
that's
Dana DeLorenzo from ash versus evil did we ended up meeting Dana DeLorenzo the friending her having drinks with her
She was awesome. We met her friends two of her friends were parents of one of the kid of the main kid that plays
he's built in it, right?
Very strange like universe evening of everything.
And Dana did say, I wanna come on the show.
Should be our first guest.
Yeah, we've never had a guest.
I'd like to have her on.
I'd like to get Doug Benson on.
Yeah, I'd like to get the mug Benson guys on.
Full on asked me, like over Twitter, like hey,
I hear you gotta do my podcast.
People keep tweeting at me, you wanna come on?
Sure, I'd love to, never heard back.
remind me to remind Doug I feel like that guy's probably got a sharp memory I
don't know why you would need to remind him about it the guy that his whole
persona is weed yeah you're like he's on it and then I think as I've told in
the show before three years ago four years ago longer than that maybe when I was
working with Pete he goes go easy here he's a friend of Doug's a friend of mine go
easy. I'm not going to go hard. I didn't. Why? I've never met him. Just a little pre -lamp.
I think I've told the story in the podcast, but Pete goes, you got to do Douglas Moves. You
guys would love each other. You have the exact same humor. You'd love him and you guys
could talk movies. It'd be so fun. So email. And I always hate this move, but Pete does it a lot.
Email's Doug Benson and CC's me. Just want to put intro YouTube or whatever. So then he's
like Doug Pat is one of my dear friends. He's hilarious. He loves movies. He'd be perfect for
your show. He's done comedy and so. And then Doug writes back, I would like to hope he knew I
was CC'd, but maybe he didn't. Right. And it was like, hey, great. Maybe I'll just start booking all
kinds of people I have no idea who they are. You know, something to that effect. I was like, well,
that was unnecessary. Well, two things. That's very funny. But the second, that's not a shot at you.
That's him saying to Pete. Yeah, don't fucking put me on the spot like that man
He probably meant it to just go to Pete. I was no need for me to see that response
That's that's I really think that's all that was I wasn't that upset by well
And I'm still talking about it three years ago. He's a great man
And we'll let Joe Joe put a word in for you. I don't even I don't even need to go on it
Frequent guest on Doug loves movies. No, I won many times by the way
Yeah, is it still the same format all these years later? It's yeah, I think it's just the
game show yeah basically but it's fun but who we we we went deep the other night when I was on
and I did plug our show thank you very much but we went deep the other night with the last game
is like you got to just keep naming movies of an actor so people start tapping out I wouldn't
tap out Johnny Depp and Roger Moore were the two actors I do a lot better with depth and more yes
well I lucked out nobody could remember the names of the pirates of the Caribbean movies okay so I
hit all five of those in a row. And they wouldn't they wouldn't lie to say five. No, you had to say like
the full title. In fact, Dan Soder did a, uh, uh, Sweeney Todd and it didn't count because he
didn't say the demon barber. Yeah. That's fucked up. So that's not right. But it came down to it came
down to everybody tapped out as me versus Benson in the end. And, uh, and I took it. I took it.
What was your winning? Was it Nick of time? It wasn't it was transcendence everybody forgot about transcendence
It's a shitty movie. Yeah, I know finish that. I also nice square with lost in Lamontia. Oh nice sure
Yeah, I don't know if see weirdly. I would have counted Sweeney Todd over lost in Lamontia
It's a documentary still movie on an IMDb page
All right, it's technically a movie so could you say like 21 Jump Street because of his little cameo? Yep
But also got a nice deep cut with Freddy's dead the final nightmare.
Sure.
So, I get almost do his career in order up until he started sucking him at.
There's few actors I've made a bigger turn on in my life than, uh, Dep.
I used to just love him and now you see he's had something and it's almost a red flag.
He'll be back.
He'll come back.
Well, black mass was great.
It wasn't great.
I, Joe, I saw it sitting right next to you.
You didn't think that much of it.
I thought it was okay in the theater.
I've watched it two or three times since then,
and I really like it now.
All right, really grew on me.
All right.
Is that okay?
It's a four -man's breast.
It's going for breast go.
Didn't get there.
Am I allowed to revise my opinion?
Yes.
We should have to review every movie as characters from the movie.
So that's the black mask character.
I don't remember the black mask.
I thought the movie was good in subsequent viewings.
Uh -huh.
We won't be doing that today with it.
All right, Pat's movie corner.
Is that enough for play for you 12 minutes of work in your clit?
It did nothing for me a dry fumbling affair, but yes
I as I told Joe I took my first swing at red box. I was out of the grocery store. I was like, you know what?
Had a real hard week. I'm gonna watch three movies tonight like I used to in the old days rent movies at the store, right great
And boy did I strike out folks. I got this movie with Woody Harrelson called what's
it called Thompson or something like that. Yeah. The Gordon. I never dreamed that I
would become this guy. But I. Is it Gordon? I guess your memory just goes. No, it's not
Gordon. It's let me start with another one and I'll get it. It's by the guy that did the
movie Green Blast or whatever with Ben Stiller. Green Blast. Greenberg. What was the movie with?
No, it's not by that guy at all. What's that movie called? Greenberg. Greenberg. But this
is not that movie. I thought it was the same writer, director guy, right? No. It's the guy who
did the guy who directed the skeleton twins, which was a very overrated movie with Kristen Wig and
Bill Hader, but the guy who wrote it, Mr., let me bring this up, Wilson, Mr. Wilson,
Dennis the Menace style, Daniel Close.
So I'm a big fan of Daniel Close's graphic novels.
I have this big collection called Eight Ball of his graphic novels.
I don't even like graphic novels.
One of his long -running comics became the movie Ghost World, which is a favorite of mine.
I love the movie Ghost World.
He also did a lot of the movie hate the comic. No, okay, because then the movie form
It's quite charming as a comic book. I'm like, what am I looking at? I'm looking at normal people and pictures
It's just I don't like stuff like that. He also wrote art school confidential
Which I thought was a very funny movie lesser movie, but fun good flick
Dark so now he'd be rarely right shit and Wilson is based on his graphic novel and he wrote the screenplay
And I mean, I hope this thing was noted to death or else this guy's just completely lost his edge is talent
Just a piece of shit
It was a Woody Harrelson and like I
Guess at first he's again in one scene. He'll be like autistic like I'll say something really
Rude and cutting to somebody and then the next scene. He's like really sweet and like
You know crime like sobbing because his dad is dying and so like there it's the most all over the place character I've seen
And a whip, whip point in the movie, does he decide to take on an army of apes?
It's a different movie.
I think you knew that, you know.
Hear that forced laugh out of wall.
You're not a fan of that.
That's all I got, but I like that bit.
All right, go ahead, sorry.
It's just, I mean, Laura Dern was in it, who is on a real role these days.
And just nothing clicked.
They have, he has this estranged daughter who's like a, you know, a heavy golf girl.
And just there isn't a laugh in it.
There's nothing. The only decent moment is he's coming out of like a bathroom and he gets tangled up in a bunch of balloons
Uh -huh, and it's kind of I thought that's kind of funny and then when I stopped the movie
They had that as the DVD menu because they were like oh make sure you grab the balloon bit that's the only thing
Anyone will care about it. Well, it's also a bad scene when the best joke in a movie is like an old Chevy Chase Gerald
Foolish like thing, you know exactly. Um, it wasn't great. All right. So that's strike one. What's strike two?
So strike one, strike two, and I would say folks significantly worse than Wilson, which
I just shat all over, was Baywatch.
What makes a man of your age, of your status even push the button, give me B15, I want
Baywatch.
Why would you even try?
Well, the truth is like everyone, I spent a lot of my adolescence pausing and jerking
it off to Baywatch. So as a kid, you're like, when will I see it be able to see an R -rated
Baywatch? What a dream that would be. Then it comes out. I'm like, okay, and I want to
make something very clear to Hall, and I'm sure all the Hollywood executives listen.
Because you're not getting it, okay? You need to know that Zac Efron is not funny. You need
to know that Dwayne the Rock Johnson is not funny. So you can't put any buddy comedy to not
funny people as the buddies, you have to pair them with somebody who is funny.
Right.
I agree with that.
I think they're decent like straightish men to better comedians.
They're okay, but the two of them bouncing off each other, you want to talk about nothing.
And then every female role is just a giant -titted nothing.
Well, that's the thing, Dwayne Johnson, who I'm a fan of, I don't really like his movies,
they usually are bad, but they're bad.
I think the rock is the greatest wrestler of all time.
I really mean that.
You watch the heyday of rock, the speeches and everything.
It is stand -up comedy hilarious.
So everybody goes, well, he's hilarious.
And it's like, well, no, that character is hilarious.
And even when that character is improperly written
which started to happen towards the end,
it's not funny anymore.
So, you know, it's like, you're not putting,
it's like, you don't put, you don't put,
like the adventures of Ford Fair and Lane,
They were like dice be dice. Yeah, because that's we want that character that's funny right and they don't do that with the rock
And and then like everybody's like, well, why isn't this fun? It's like well because he's not like you said
It's like you got to pair him with Kevin hard or something like you know, it was also
Longer than two hours. That's insane and joke. I'm gonna tell you something now that might make your head explode
You don't see
the butt cheek one, you don't see tit one.
Right, there's no nudity in this movie of any kind.
Except the, and even, which I'll get to with it as well,
movie fat guys are at an all time low.
Funny movie fat guy, like we used to like churn them out,
like eggs and a chicken factory, hilarious fat guys.
The one in this movie is such a fucking turd so you see him naked if you want to do that and then I said as a kid that I
Mean I meant it like great school in high school
I'd always say like I had a dream that one day I'd have a fat best friend
Yeah, because they were always the best part of the movie. You always wanted to be friend John candy correct
I mean the last time they really got it right. I would have to say is like super bad 15 years ago
Yeah, Jonah Hill, I mean that's I haven't seen better. I mean that recently they're not
inventing new actually the fact kids in like 21 what's that movie project X they were
repellent. I hated him so much. You can't make the fact I hateable. No, we haven't had
a good one in a while because everybody's everybody's got to be healthy now. So then Jonah Hill
get skinny. You know, Joe, if you're listening, I don't care for it. Right. I like you fat
and funny. On entertainment tonight or whatever, they'll be like, look how hot Jonah Hill,
no, he's still horrible looking, but now he's not, but now he's not funny anymore. So you
want to be funny or don't you? Oh, that's too far. Shots fired. That's too far. The
wash Hill. Look, I'm not saying I'm, uh, uh, you know, Freddie Prince Jr. over here
either. We're like Freddie Kruger Jr. I had a great joke today at my friend who's got a big
gut. Uh, uh, it's, it's a bad joke, but that's why it's a good joke. He was like years ago when
I lived in Miami, I lived at the Morton tower and I go judging from your waistline, it looks
like you lived at the Morton steakhouse. Did he enjoy it? Yeah, we laughed hardily. It's a great
shitty joke. Oh, sorry. Go ahead. I'm sorry. Oh, you don't need to apologize to me, Joe.
Uh, how much I almost I almost said how much more podcast has this civil become?
How much more civil has this has this podcast become? I hate it. Yeah. I mean, I don't hate it.
I like that we get along and it's nice. But I do. I don't know. Hollywood is doing such a bad job
anymore. We can't disagree. And now we need to try something crazy. We really disagree on. But
I mean, we don't on this week's either excited for this new idea. And by the way,
Okay, let me say this now on the air.
I think next week's app should be us reviewing
the finale of Twin Peaks.
Okay.
The two -hour finale we would have done it this week,
but it is just too big and you got to talk about it.
You got like a hundred and fifty million dollars.
So that's, so by the way, here's what bothers me
about the no -no -duty in Baywatch.
I don't ever watch movies for nudity.
I watch porn for it.
But when your entire ad campaign is dick, ass,
and tit jokes, to the point where it's
You do see a corpse is dick in it, so you do see some nudity.
And they were like, that's so edgy.
Yeah. So my point is, when that's your whole ad campaign, when it's borderline sexual harassment,
as you walk through a New York subway tunnel, and the tits and cocks are so big in your face on the posters,
and then you don't have any nudity in the, like, fuck off.
Fuck off. It's one of the biggest bombs of 2017, by the way.
It's unwatchable and then you know what happens at the end folks at the end of this two hour plus movie
Dwayne and the Rajasvan walks in to like a an islands like that chain where you get burgers
They're all like sitting there eating on the beach and Dwayne comes in and he's like
Guys got some good news for you
You're not trainees anymore. You're all lifeguards. They're all like yeah
This thing was like an episode of say by the bell Hawaiian style right that that's about how much plot there was to it
Then they'll try to drum up like oh, that's it. That's the end of the move.
In other words, you're going to say and then there's this terrible Pam Anderson cameo or something.
Oh, there is. Actually, you're right. And that is after that, I think.
Yeah, they go, they go, oh, I think we've got someone else to join us or someone else who might
want to join us today for dinner or something. And then it's Pam Anderson looking very odd.
Yeah, and somebody says, is that a corpse that hasn't eaten in two months?
Yeah, jeez.
Hasselhoff makes an appearance as well.
And then they try to do what 21 Jump Street and its sequel did really well.
And they miss again and again where they'll be like, wait, why are we solving crimes?
We're just lifeguards, right?
That's kind of weird.
And then they cut over to Zac Efron and he's like, I know it sounds like the plot from some
terrible TV show from the 80s.
Oh my god fuck you you fucking there are three scenes all three scenes where that's the joke
And it goes on and on and on by people who are not comedians
So Bayway I mean Bayway was one of the worst movies I've seen all year unquestionably. It's terrible
And
Then the third was the best I would say a noble failure called a cure for wellness
But it's still a strike three
It was, I think Gore Verbinski is an excellent visual director, loved the ring, glad to
see him getting back to horror.
I love, I love mouse hunt back in the thing.
I'm going to say this about Gore Verbinski, yeah, really man, I mean not fairly man, weather
man.
Love it.
Uh, more, uh, well, I might be wrong, he's, he's, he's approaching more strikes than hits
at this point.
For sure.
I like all the pirates.
Correct.
Yeah, and I like dog shit this well I like the first one in the third one quite a bit
I think the second one is is whatever I
Think I did not like the ring. We've talked about it. That's crazy. It's not crazy
It's not there's one scary part and then it's a mystery movie for the rest of it
It's very safe. It's boring. I just I don't know. I didn't I didn't like it. I didn't think it was that interesting
We should do the ring
And I've also talked about how I hate when a ghost uses technology.
I can't stand that.
So anyway,
ring two is terrible, obviously.
So it didn't like the ring.
I didn't, I did, I did like mouse hunt, but, you know, he did the lone ranger,
which I found enjoyable because I watched it with my mom.
I would probably never watch it ever again.
Yeah.
You know, and now the cure for wellness is like I wanted to see it at first, but then I was like,
you know, this looks like shutter island. I'm not a huge shutter island fan. Looks like it's all
gonna be in the guy's head at the end or something and it was a lot like shutter island. I can't,
I mean, like clearly influenced by it, and I love shutter. It was not that good. I'm gonna put it at
like a B minus because it certainly held my interest and it was two and a half hours long. I don't
Well, that's why I didn't go see it either doing the shit with every movie now, but I mean for that guy to be the star of a movie that
Expensive that dude who kind of looks like the caprio. I
Don't understand what's going on with that dude. No, no offense to him, but
Every movie he's been in has been a flop. He was in he was in that movie. He was in Spider -Man 2
Right as as Green Goblin, right. He was in love place beyond the ponds. I never saw that
It's a great movie. He's in Valerian city of a thousand planets like he's in all these major
Every movie he's in they go. Let's put this kid dead front and center. Yeah, he's too weird looking
I mean, oh he's the kid from that's right. He's from
What's the found footage movie where they get the superpowers chronicle. He's that kid
Yeah, they push him because he looks like DiCaprio, but he looks like a more evil, less appealing
DiCaprio.
And that's why all those movies bombed.
It's like he's a good looking guy.
So everybody forgets that DiCaprio the early years was like, he a white trashy looking
like some ratty kid, like he developed into Leonardo DiCaprio, you know.
out. So anyway, yeah, too long. I just, you know, not for me. I'm glad you saw three
because I don't think I've seen anything come this week except the Twin Peaks finale
and it. So we'll do both of those over these next two episodes. Do you have anything else
or no go for Joe scary stuff really really really really really to excuse me
excellent an excellent video game on Nintendo Switch which I really am
loving owning they're very hard to come by but I was lucky enough to find
one at the Nintendo store in New York. Mr. Shifty fucking incredible game you're
You're a guy that has superpowers.
Your superpower is you can teleport short distances and it's a tower run game.
So it's, it's a tower beat them up.
So it's you going into this building, trying to get to the top guy and just beating the living
shit out of everybody as you teleport around them and they can't shoot you because you're moving
too fast and disappearing.
It's like the opening.
I saw somebody review it online and they said it's, the game is exactly like the opening
seen an X -Men 2 where night crawlers going through the White House. That's exactly what it's like.
So fucking fun. So hard to find as it's sold out. No, it's just, you know, it's a fantasy, you know,
this is for fantasy horror sci -fi stuff just like the show. So go check that out. I think it's
$14 .99 to download it. And you can get it on other platforms other than Switch. So it's on Steam,
and I think it might be on Xbox and PlayStation.
I've never heard of Steam.
Steam is the year to switch.
Steam is the end.
You had heard of the Nintendo Switch?
Well, you've mentioned it.
It's the latest video game craze thing.
Anyway, so that's it for that.
We don't have to do a new segment this week.
Nothing too.
Well, here's my new segment.
Let's start the review with this.
All right.
Every so -called horror aficionado under the fucking sun is saying that it is
mesmerizing, is phenomenal, is terrifying, is a wonderful adaptation of the
book, and I think you have all lost your fucking minds. What the fuck are you
talking about? I mentioned all the time. I mentioned them all the time. He's a fantastic
follow on Twitter, gave my first job at the Cinematical website, Now Defunct, Scott Weinberg,
my favorite horror guy. If you like us, you'll love him on Twitter. He's great. Raven about this
it. Raven about it. And I get liking it. I get liking it. I get raving about it. I
religiously visit bloody disgusting. I religiously visit movie web. Yeah.
I, a lot of the time, most of the time, agree with the reviews on those sites.
These fucking guys are like, the headline is, it's like, it's pure nightmare fuel.
I'm like, what are you talking about?
I'm looking now, Rod Tomatoes 87%.
I agree with your statement.
You can like it.
It is not a movie to be loved, and here's why I'm taking a harder shot at the horror people
that like it.
If you know the source material, you know this is not a good adaptation.
That's true.
I'm saying to everybody, you know, some lady at work was like, am I going to like it?
I'm going to go with my daughter instead of you read the book?
No.
Yeah.
You probably like it.
If you read the book, you're not going to like it.
The mini series did a better job, a much better job, surprisingly.
It's scarier and it's like kind of like a classier movie and they use effects very sparingly.
And this, I mean, a clown is supposed to be scary on its own.
Every time they show you Pennywise, big eel comes out of his mouth or something, or
your jumps at the camera.
It's scary enough, except it wasn't because he doesn't look like a normal clown.
Well he looks like, you know, way too made up.
He looks like an evil clown which makes it not scary anymore.
Tim Curry was scary because you just see this clown standing there staring at you and he
wasn't going out of his way to be like, look how crazy my eyebrows look right now.
He just was, and it was scary because it let you imagine horrible things and this doesn't
do it.
The, the effects in the original miniseries were better because they did practical effects
for like Pennywise's fangs coming out and all that shit.
This was all CG'd, which it didn't look as good.
Now I will say this, I had a really great online discussion
with Eliza Skinner today about the movie,
and she made some great points.
So I'm gonna echo some of her points
because I also think the same thing.
I thought the movie started great.
Like I was pissed off that they took out Bill giving Georgie
like shit because that's why he feels guilty later when his brother's dead. But I was like, okay,
I can get past that. No big deal. Do you see the kids arm get bit off? I'm like, oh my god,
they're fucking going for this. And then they proceeded from that point on to do nothing
except remove every element of this story that makes it a valuable story. The whole purpose of
it is Pennywise, the dead, they don't even say the fucking dead lights, they never even
say it once in the goddamn movie, holy shit, I just remembered that, but anyway, Pennywise,
all that shit, the whole point is he's a creature that awakens every 27 years and feeds specifically
on people from the town of Dairy, not just children, because there is such a history of hatred,
unjustified hatred in the town.
Now, that's the plot of the movie.
That's why he, and then why does he target these kids
over any other group of people?
Because they're the Losers Club.
Why are they the Losers Club?
Because one's a black kid who gets racist treatment
all the time.
One's a Jewish kid who gets anti -Semitic treatment.
One's a fat kid who gets fat shame.
Beverly Marsh gets slut -shamed all the time.
And molested by her dad, which by the way,
that's the only thing they kept in the movie.
They took everything out except the sexualization
of a 14 -year -old girl.
And weirdly, you could almost watch it and think, maybe I read too much into that.
It's almost too subtle.
I don't want to see a sex scene, but if you're going to do it, don't have him put his hand
on her shoulder and that's it.
And then why was the pharmacist hitting on her to distract from her dad hitting on her?
What was that about?
Because she's a sexy kid, is that the...
That's my point.
It's like the only thing they did, the only thing they kept from the book was that she was
being inappropriately sexualized.
And then also, I said this to you after we saw it,
the film depicting, she was depicted in a way
in the film where it was troublesome to me.
There's a shot of her looking at tampons
and it's clear to me that you're supposed to be focused
on her ass in the fucking shot.
And I was like, that's weird to me.
That's weird.
Don't show me a 14 -year -old kid from the back
wearing like daisy dukes.
You know what I mean? It's odd.
I do.
Like when she was walking, when she walks past them like in slow motion in a bikini to
jump into the water, I was like, this feels a little odd.
That's what I'm saying.
That's seem to, however, let me also, by the way, not a bikini.
Her bra and underwear, which I get it.
The boys were also in their underpants, but can we actually get it's not the same exact
fucking thing since boys already have to take their shirts off?
Well, they're also not doing slow motion lingering.
Well, that too.
Things over their packages.
Well, that's what Eliza sent me was a was I don't remember who sent it to her or who she retweeted it from,
but she said it was a woman wrote walking home alone from seeing it.
Not frightened at all except for the fact that I was terrified by the camera violating like the 14 -year -old girl in the movie all the time and I thought that
That was pretty spot on but let me say because here's what I thought of I
I felt it was a little weird at the time and then read a couple articles about it. I was like, yeah, I
Hold on my Alexa off Alexa my Alexa went off. Go ahead. Sure
You say it again. Yeah, but but I it made me think back to like when I was
13 let's say and I saw the sand lot
They're kind of sexualized in that lifeguard too, but the lifeguard in that movie is probably like 16 or something and
and their little boys looking up to her.
So I wonder if the Sandlock came out now,
and I haven't seen it in years, but of course,
it's a classic for kids.
I always love that movie.
Right.
I wonder if they'd be accused of the same thing back then.
I think there's a big difference between saying,
here's a movie about a group of adolescent boys,
and one tiny aspect of their life
is they're all in love with the hot life guard
that's three years older than four years older than the pool.
and then taking this movie and saying,
the only female character we're gonna focus on,
and the only inappropriate treatment
we're gonna take out of the book,
is how everybody wants to have sex with her.
It's weird.
It's fucking weird.
And if you're telling me,
somehow that's more palatable to an audience
than a scene about racism or fat -chaming
or something like that, that's crazy to me.
As we talked about it in this podcast before
and we've discussed how much you and I both love
Stephen King's depiction of bullies, the only time really where bullies feel like as real as they did when I was a kid because they're just like
sociopaths, monsters
So in this movie, they'll bring out the switchblade and I you might have even pointed this out after we saw it, but
Spoiler, this is just spoiler, but go ahead. I've seen it. This isn't really a spoiler
But the they're holding up a switchblade to the fact kids stomach. It's got a shirt off
But no one calls them fat. No, and then you watch
Henry Bowers carve an H into the kid's stomach, literally.
I'm not saying like the camera pulls away,
and that's what he does.
You see a close up of the knife
carving the H into the kid's stomach.
So that's okay,
yet they take out the part where they call him fat.
They take out all the other unfair treatment of the kids.
They're beating the shit out of a black kid
and never mentioned that he's black.
They instead, again,
they do like a weird insinuation thing.
But now here's the problem.
This is not obviously me saying I want racism in my movies what this is say you want realism in them though
Well, but the point of the the whole point is
unjustified hatred is now this thing can exist as a monster and feed on the town when you take that out of it
Now you have the goonies have to fight a monster
Strange friends what you yeah, and there are that's exactly what they wanted by the way
Yeah, and there are a couple bullies in town that are jerks
and they do shitty stuff to these kids
because one of them is a psycho
and that's about it.
It's like, okay, so this is sort of just like
my life growing up now, like I don't want my life.
I want to see the kids from the book.
They suffered worse and that's what made them heroes
at the end.
I guess it's to not, well, it's already movies.
So if they don't put bullying in movies
because they think maybe it'll inspire kids to bully,
why the fuck are the kids saying that?
Well, they don't adapt it.
They don't adapt it.
You know, and don't make, and don't make,
then don't make, and by the way,
don't make a fucking R -rated movie
that's meant for children to see.
It is clearly meant for kids.
It's ridiculous.
They ruin, they ruin the richy character.
They take all of his, like, you know,
his whole thing is like he does all these different voices
and stuff.
Some of them, yes, are inappropriate and racist,
but he thinks they're funny in the book.
It's part of why he's an interesting character.
You don't have to agree with, you disagree with him
I'm doing the voice, but you're like,
this kid is a fuck around.
He doesn't take anything seriously
to the point of doing offensive voices to people.
And then he goes to the movie theater,
sees the werewolf movie,
and then has the werewolf encounter
and gets scared straight and stops fucking around.
And that's not in the fucking movie.
He took the fucking werewolf thing out of the movie.
It's not in the goddamn movie.
I mean, it wasn't in the many series either.
No, it is.
It is, Richie encounters like a wolf man
There's the scene in the miniseries where Richie is in the basement or the boiler room and encounters a monster.
Oh, yeah, you're right. And I think they do the Wolfman. I'm pretty sure.
But they show Richie straight in the fuck up in the miniseries.
Yeah, they do show that.
And they didn't do it in this. All they did was have the kid from Stranger Things, put on glasses and say fuck every three seconds.
A lot of fucks.
It was Joe Pesci, a amount of fucks.
my issue is especially at this time in American history and
You have a movie that is at its core about how hatred racism fear brings out a monster
Why would you remove that from your fucking movie?
It's insane. It's crazy because it had the book is a masterpiece and it has the potential to be a masterpiece of a movie
So it sounds like they got scared off by what the true detective guy was doing. I'd like to hope that would be a
But a movie I'd prefer more, but maybe it wouldn't have done $200 million this weekend. No, it was all the care about this is a sanitized
Which in the wrong ways at times very inappropriate. Yes
Movie it is boring
I think it was disrespectful to the characters in the book
to portray them this way.
I really do think that I can't fucking believe
that Stephen King is giving a rave reviews over and over.
I mean, Jesus Christ, there was a time
where you mentioned the shining to the guy
and he practically bit your fucking nose off over it.
You know, and it's like, he's like,
I had to see it twice, I wasn't prepared.
It was so great.
I'm like, what the fuck are you talking about, man?
Like this is, you know, I get it, he's also 75
and he's probably just like, you know, I don't need to fight the models anymore, but I just,
I don't understand. I feel like everybody is on, and I'm saying this jokingly, I'm not making
any attention. I feel like everybody's like on payola or something. I'm like, how do this many
people that love horror think that this is so great? Well, the truth is if I'm comparing it to
horror in general. Like if I went then saw this and it was the new scary clown movie from
the guy who made Mama. Right. I'd probably be like, it was way better than most horror
movies. I agree. But you're the bar is set very high with that source material and we're
never going to see that definitive version and they're not going to get it right the second
time around. No, no. And they are they have committed to it too of course. Well we ended
up with here. And look, maybe a two will write the wrongs of the first movie. Why not do it Lord
of the Ring style and do three and really just tell the fucking book and you can still you'd still
be eliminating a lot by the way, but I mean even at two and a half hours it just it felt very empty
and it felt like they were not getting under the surface of it. It's this it is it speaks in my
opinion to this country's sick and weird obsession with children, the glorifying of
children everywhere you look, the constant praising of children.
And it started with Twitter, it started with social media, it started with...
I didn't expect this to go into an anti -children rant.
Well, I mean, but it started with this Twitter and social media hit and all of a sudden
and it was children need a voice that is as loud as adults.
And I believe we need to listen
to the children in this country.
I don't think they need to be as loud as we are.
And I do think a lot of adults are idiots
and need to put the fucking check
and told the shut up too.
But I think this movie speaks to the worst side
of that equation.
And it was very clearly to me an attempt to...
I knew it was gonna be a problem.
Once you started watching those fucking MTV award shows and it was like the it kids are here
I was like here we go here we fucking go. Yeah, this is this is a campaign to make six kids
celebrities
This is what this is.
This is what it's been reduced.
They did it for a strange of things.
Yes.
Everything about this new hit, everything about them firing that first director, it all
comes from a strange of things, because they're like, oh, we can do this now when an actuality
these Stranger Things owes everything to it.
They don't get that.
They think, well now we should rip off
the thing that ripped off it.
Right.
And the thing and everything else that it ripped off.
And I do want to say that as somebody who's excited
for season two of Stranger Things.
And I want to explain it.
Like Tarantino, they blend up their omajas.
I like the show.
But let's stop pretending it's the first time.
I'm becoming, I'm becoming,
I love the trailer for season two.
I'm becoming less excited as it approaches though
because I can't stand everywhere I fucking look.
I see those kids and I'm like, guys, for Christ's sakes,
there are a bunch of kids.
They're good actors.
Can you stop making me try to love them or whatever?
It's like weird.
And then also too, it's not even a way.
It's just celebrity shit.
It's like, stop it.
Stop telling me who I'm supposed to love.
It's annoying.
But I will say this, and this is a very positive thing.
I mean, sincerely, every kid in this movie,
every kid in this, every actor in this movie,
Fucking Sartzgard, all of them.
They were great.
This was a great cast.
It was a beautifully shot fit.
Well, they had the best fat kid in ages.
Fat kid used to get, you know, sandlot, et cetera.
Yeah.
There hasn't been a great fat kid in a while.
This kid, right when I saw him, I was like,
I love this kid.
Yeah.
It was a very, very much to do.
No.
Well, that's what I'm getting at.
Very well shot, very well directed, very well acted.
terrible material though, the script sucks.
And in fact, when I met the parents of the kid,
they were like, did you like it?
You just saw it tonight.
And I was like, I think your son was great in it.
I really do.
He was excellent.
All the kids were great.
This is gonna do very well for him.
This is a congratulations on that.
Honestly though, I didn't like the movie that much.
They changed too many things
that I thought should have been in there.
That being said, doesn't matter.
or it's gonna do $600 gazillion this weekend.
You know, did they love it, huh?
Did they love the movie?
They didn't say.
But they were also, you know,
it's a very cordial exchange
and I was actually kind of happy with myself
that I didn't just go, oh my God, so good, so good.
And I met what I said,
that kids a great fucking actor, man.
He's a great actor.
This movie just, I don't like the movie.
No, I agree. Anyway. All right. That's our show. Goddamn it. All right. We'll be back in
three years with the review of it too. And yeah, it seemed like you guys liked it a bit
more than watching the old Facebook page. And certainly the reviews show it. But I don't
great a film. So I'm gonna sign signing off. This is Joe DeRosa at Joe DeRosa
comedy on Twitter and Instagram. This comes out what Monday. So this week I'm
in the at the DC Drafthouse in Washington DC. Five shows. If you're in the area
come on out and say hi. Should be a good time. And at the end of the month I'll
be at Scoops Fest in Vegas with Kurt Brown and Holer doing emotional hangs live
and also we'll be co -headlining a show. So come out to that if you're in the
Vegas area and check out emotional hangs if you can and my penthouse column
monthly you let me down. Patty? I'm on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick
Walsh and tapings of my sitcom by the book are three out of four Friday nights
a month at Warner Brothers Studios in Burbank had a hellion come out to the show
the other night left a real nice review and also a nice review of Joseph folks
because they showed the pilot before. If you want to come to a taping it's very
easy to do just Google it or shoot me a DM or something I'll get you in. Other than
that it's all I got we'll see you next week with probably twin peaks and we'll
see you in hell.