I'll see you in the next one.
Welcome to We'll See You In Hell, it's your favorite podcast.
Yes, discussing movies, revealing movies, all that, that, that, that, that, you know it,
you know what, you know what, the show is, Christ sakes, Joe, you're getting a little
lax in the intros, I got to say, a little too relaxed, you want me to do it again?
I'll do it again.
No, that's fine, hello everybody, it's Pat, it's Joe, this week we're doing the Kevin James
Nazi picture, Becky, it is available, do you ever think you'd say that sentence?
No, but you know, it sounds right, it sounds like it could be a headline in today's
world, today's crazy, mix them up world, but yeah, we're going to be doing Becky, it is
available to rent on demand for like $6 .99 or something like that, and I'm sure let's
be real, it'll be on one of the streaming services, probably in a month, so put a pin in this
one if you haven't seen it yet, you don't want to spend the money, but we had to discuss.
We had to discuss also guaranteed to be in your local Walmart DB, oh yeah, quickly, yeah,
if your Walmart is open, but we'll get to the movie later, I got a, I got a few scary stuff
things to bring to your attention, Pat, I feel like it's been months since we've seen the scary
stuff.
Yeah, I've got a couple things I'd like to talk about, have you watched the David Lynch
weather report on YouTube? I saw his old ones, but I haven't seen the new ones. Yeah, he's
doing his weather reports every day, they're like 40 seconds long, okay. I was watching them
old man. Yeah, he's crazy. He's, we talked on the last episode about like dad humor by crazy
old man, I mean, he's, he's very dad -ish, like he's like a kind of like it's weird that he makes such
disturbing, jarring, you know, atmospheric art, because he's very dad -ish, like he's kind of
a corn ball and he's like, he does these weather, he's during these reports, so he's literally like
here in LA, the clouds are parting and it's a clear, beautiful day, 85 degrees. What more could
you ask for people? Okay, I'll see you tomorrow, like it's, it's so odd, but I think odd the way I would
think David Lynch would be odd, odd the way like you like your grandpa's odd. I think part of it is
a character with him and part of it is him being genuinely odd, but I do think those weather reports
he's doing a bit of a I'm David Lynch bit in my opinion. Okay. Well, they're a joy to watch
these things. Why I say that is like, you know, if you see him, I've never heard anything good
things about him, but if you see him like on a behind the scenes thing, like recently they've done
quite a few of his on criteria, they're finally putting out elephant man next month, which I'm very
excited about, hasn't even been on blue right yet. Elephant man, I've never, you know, I've never seen it
because I'm scared to watch it. It's just makeup, Joe. You mean he's not really an elephant?
Yeah, they do have somebody with elephantitis and under the skin, Scarlett Johansson.
That's why I've never watched it. I find it, I find it very upsetting. I can't, it upsets me
greatly, and I don't mean that in a shallow way. It's just I don't know it's I find it upsetting.
Well, maybe you more than anyone need to watch the elephant man and learn its powerful lessons
and truths. I've always wanted to see it. It is strangely sort of beautiful. And it does kind of
get thrown a little bit into the horror genre sometimes. I think it's the black and white of it and
that it, you know, people think it's about a monster and not about just a dude, but it's a great,
great movie produced by Mel Brooks, who loved Eraserhead and brought him into direct the elephant man,
which is crazy. And then they produce the fly. Mel Brooks really likes to produce a very upsetting
body. Yeah, I'm glad he did. I'm glad he did. But what the hell are we talking about, Joe?
David Lynch. David Lynch. When you see him on the, sorry, we had a little
hiccup and I got off track, but I've seen him like, people will ask, hey, should we cut somebody
asked him behind the scenes on one of these things, twin peaks or whatever. Should we cut? And he
turns around and is like, shouldn't we cut? Should we cut? Why are you asking me? Why the fuck are you
asked? Like, start screaming at it? Right. And I'm not saying that's the true David Lynch, but I'm
saying this like, hello, everybody is a little bit of an act. I think there's a, okay. I think
there's a much more real person in there with anger and other issues. And the whole folksy thing is
a little bit of a play. Okay. Fair enough. But he's undoubtedly weird. He kept a fetus on his
desk and in like, Brian for years. Yeah, in Brian, you know, whatever, whatever you, oh,
formaldehyde or something, you know what I mean? Here's another thinking of Seth Rogan's an American
pickle. Oh boy, maybe we review that for the show. It does fall into
it does kind of fall into what the show, it is a fantasy movie. We could, you know,
it does fall into our theory. I'll watch it. This is not so much a scary stuff.
Well, it's just bringing something to your attention. You and the listeners.
And it's just because I like to shit on this movie any chance I get mid -summer. You've heard
us argue with people. You've heard us argue about this goddamn thing. You've got some
a new issue with it. Did you know there was already a movie called mid -summer? No.
I'm trying to, of course, now I can't find the goddamn thing.
Oh, you really, you really did it in a mic drop kind of voice too. And then didn't have the juice
to back it up. I got the juice. I got all the juice. I need the seats.
I can find it this way, movie. So yeah, there was already a movie. Okay, here's the remake.
Okay, here we go. Got it. Mid -summer. Already a movie called mid -summer, which isn't a crime.
Sometimes movies have the same title. This picture is from 2003.
Psychological horror. We shave a little bit closer.
Let me just just just shoot the plot of the film at you from Wikipedia. The story revolves
around a group of Danish students who celebrate their graduation in a Swedish forest.
When they encounter a supernatural presence at parts different, seemingly connected to who?
The main character whose sister has committed suicide and was hesitant to go on the trip
to celebrate solstice mid -summer. So, Ariaster, the great genius has he been accused of this or what?
Is this news? I literally was just, I don't even know how the fuck I stumbled on this.
I was on Google. I don't even remember what the fuck I was looking up. It might have been on YouTube.
And I just saw a trailer. And I was like, what the fuck is that? Mid -summer.
2003. And I looked it up. And I was like, I wouldn't it be so funny? And you know what, Pat,
I'm going to use a word I've never used in this way ever in my life.
Wouldn't it be delicious? Yes. If this somehow shaved kind of close to the Ariaster movie,
and I could make fun of that, apart from the title, and I went to Wikipedia and read the sources,
and it literally said, a girl whose sister commits suicide hesitantly goes on a trip into the woods
to celebrate graduation with her student friends. Is it by Ariaster? Is it a short?
No, no, in fact, why has no one brought this up? It's by Danish film.
Okay. So it cuts even a little bit deeper because then it almost looks like,
did you lift something from actual Danish people? Yeah. This film was remade, excuse me,
as a picture called Solstice in 2008, same exact plot. So he had two chances to see this thing
to hear of it. And also, this is really interesting to me. The original one is spelled M -I -D -S -O -M -M -E -R.
His is spelled A -R, which to me screams, hey, there's another movie called Mid -summer already,
so you can't spell it that way, you got to change a letter or something. So then he goes with
a different spelling of it, which means somebody told him about the movie, which means he probably,
at some point, was curious about, well, what is this other thing that's got the same name as my thing?
Maybe he's seen the other thing. This is what it smells like to me because I've seen comics do
this with jokes. What they'll do is they'll hear a comic do a bit and they'll go,
I could do that better and they'll do the same, I don't want to name names. There's a comic who
does an impression in his act of David Caruso at the beginning of, what's that fucking shitty cop show he
was on NYPD Blue or CSI? CSI. He, a big bit in his act where he does David Caruso,
like, oh, every CSI starts like this. Right. You know, and that's the joke. He told me, I saw Jim
Carrey do that on the tonight show and I was like, I could do that better. So even though his punch lines
and wording aren't the same as Jim Carrey's, it's like, no, I'm just going to take the launch point
of your thing and your idea. And then I'm just going to kind of go off in my own direction with it.
That to me is what this smells like. It smells like Ariester said, well, what if this movie did this
instead? Well, if it's that flagrant and with the same title, then this will have to come to light
at some point, somebody will sue or the lawsuits and the works, or they knew about it and settled ahead
of time. You know, who knows? I have no idea, but that's crazy. You think he'd at least change some
elements to take you off the center. Well, once they get to the solstice thing, then things get
different. Yeah, to an extent. But it is a very good in. I mean, it's a great end to a horror movie.
Yeah. So I see why you would steal that aspect of it. I mean, well, you don't condone stealing, Pat,
you take that back right now. No, of course, I don't. I said, I'm saying I see why you would do it.
If you I see why the guy would do it, it's a good idea to steal.
I don't know. I don't know that I think are you confessing now? Did you
how many two broke girl? I'm just saying rip off from Dana's television. Yeah, a lot of those 2BG plots.
2BG, they could have only come from Dana's TV. That's how fresh they were.
And let me hit you with a new psycho to two two two scary's is enough for this episode. Yeah,
I've got more for the future. I'm stockpiling. I'm going to hit you with a news psycho.
Well, I kind of did I wanted to talk about the Bill and Ted trailer, but we talked about in the last
episode. So this is the more interesting of the two things that I jotted down. There is now the
commercials out. You can see it on Netflix. It's a Netflix show. There is now an animated show
called Jurassic World. And it's called like camp. Something are there. Mike, if you can find it,
I'd appreciate it. It's called Jurassic World Colin camp craters or some shit. I don't
fucking remember. Okay. The plot is six kids go away to a Jurassic World camp. It's a camp.
What parent wouldn't send their children? Especially with the long rich history of
dinosaurs eating people at these places. Cranp camp, Cretaceous, it's called. Thank you, Mike. Okay.
Yeah. What parent wouldn't send their kids to a dinosaur camp, especially amidst the well -documented
incidence of the Jurassic Park. Right. Disaster. There's been movies made about the murders.
And they get to the camp and the trailer, it starts all kind of bubbly and whatever. And I'm like,
oh, that's, I see they're doing like, they're going to do like a kind of like endearing
take on Jurassic World. Like where it's not a disaster. And now within two seconds, a
dinosaurs wreck shows up. And the camp goes sideways and all the kids are running for their lives.
I'm like, how? This show comes out on the eve of Jurassic World 3 coming up. And a Jurassic World
live action TV show is in the works. How many fucking times can they tell this story? Kids will always
love dinosaurs. Kids will always love dinosaurs. And I'll always go see this. It's not just kids watching
this shit. They got 13 sequels out of land before time. Listen, but the dinosaurs are doing
different shit. But you know, by the end of that lab, before time series, we were up to time.
They, they made it. We were after time by the end of this thing. It was just going to say more
like land after time, folks. I haven't been before time when the franchise started 100 years ago.
Folks, this thing's been going on since the actual dinosaurs were alive. The first one was a
documentary. The documentary. Here's the thing. A Dino entry. I like the term Dino. Dino
entry is much better. You're right. Here's the thing. That's different. You're talking about
sequels with the same character. Land before time six. They open a pizzeria, whatever the fuck it is.
You know what I mean? It's different plots. Right. Every Jurassic Park movie is they go to the park
and the dinosaurs get loose. Every single movie. Yeah. I had a joke in my act about it when Jurassic
World 2 came out and I go, somebody had to sit in a fucking in a in a in the universe of Jurassic World.
There's a boardroom meeting where a guy's going, come on, it won't happen a fifth time.
It's so crazy that they've rehashed this this many times at this point that anybody in the living
universe would go back to this place and think that somehow it would be okay. They'll make
them as long as people go to see them. They'll make them until it's like Jurassic World in space.
And then finally the franchise will grind to a halt. They'll make they'll go too far. But they
haven't done it yet because people still go see them. I mean, I don't know why it works me up
that I've never been a fan of franchises. You know, but God really gets me going. It drives me crazy.
One classic and that's the original. Everything else varies from bad to pretty good. So
I watched a and I was going to save it for movie corner, but I won't I'll just say it now.
I watched a documentary about Ray Harryhausen called Special Effects Titan.
That's so weird. I was about to say I had watched two of his movies in the movie corner. Go ahead.
It's great. It's a great documentary. What a what a amazing guy that did amazing stuff for
Special Effects and blah, blah, blah, blah, all that stuff. But it's really interesting because
he says it's so funny. Like I love when they interview people that speak on behalf of the other
the person that the movie's about, but you're like, do you? Did you ever met this person?
Right. When they're interviewing James Cameron, the dipshit of all dipshits.
I mean, if you at least will be out of America for the next 40 years, making avatars in New Zealand.
So you don't worry about him. That's what we all wanted. Yeah. God. I mean, to commit to four of them.
Oh, it's insane. I mean, if that last terminator didn't prove my
take on James Cameron, I mean, that thing was you got you got the terminator robot slicing lines
for Corona's. Literally. Directive. No, no, I remember. I think I texted you that one. I saw it.
The director came out and said that basically in so many, you know, you know, you need to be
tackful, but in so many words said, yeah, it sucked because James Cameron insisted that I did all the
shit in the movie. He was like, he was like, don't kill John Connor right away. What are you doing?
Cameron was like, no, that's the way to do it, baby. We're going to throw him off the
sent to the translate. Anyway, it doesn't matter. It's not. Anyway,
what was I going to say? Oh, oh, Ray Harry. So James Cameron, they're interviewing the movie.
And he goes, he goes, I think I think it's Cameron that says this and not Spielberg. He goes,
I'd have to think if Harry was still working day, he'd absolutely use computer technology where
his imagination would not allow him to not use it. That's the kind of man he has smash cut,
Ray Harryhausen. I retired. I just, that's computer stuff. I don't like it. I don't get it. Yeah,
it doesn't look real to me. Right. So it's just funny. You know,
well, let me take you to the movie corner, if I may, and start with Ray Harryhausen.
There he's not a director. He's always the special effect guy in these movies, but they always give him
a credit that's like larger than the director's name because he's such a crucial part of these movies.
He said in the doc that he's he refers himself as a filmmaker because he says he's in like the ground
floor level script development through the entire process because of what he does and how it has to
be implemented into the movie. I thought I had seen his work and I had really not outside of clips.
So I watched back to back Jason and the Argonauts and Clash of the Titans. I had never seen either.
Clash of the Titans is like 1981, Harry Hamlin and Burgess Meredith and the talking owl and all.
I thought they were both equally entertaining, charming, good. The effects were really fun. The
fights were great. Neither was a great movie. Let's be real. But I probably would give the
slight edge to Clash of the Titans. I know Jason and the Argonauts is the favorite in the classic,
but Clash of the Titans was probably a little more fun to me, but all the creatures and effects are
the highlights. The two headed dog and the Medusa and all that. It's the whole reason you watch the
movie. They're amazing and looks so much better and cooler and more fun than computer effects.
So I just rewatch Clash of the Titans. It was one of my favorite movies growing up as a kid and I
hadn't seen it in a long time. And after I watched the documentary, I wanted to see it again because
that was Harryhausen's final film. Right. And I kind of saw it for what it was for the first time.
It's not a good movie, but it's got elements that are really fun and really fantastic.
Mainly the creature effects. The Medusa sequence, primarily, I still find terrifying.
Yeah. And, you know, aside from that, there's some other cool, you know, the scorpion sequence is
pretty cool. The two headed dog, as you said, is cool. But it's kind of like, you know, rewatching
it was kind of like what I was saying on the last episode about Invisible Man.
It's had some fun sequences. It has some great sequences, but it's just not a good movie.
You know what I mean? And it's because the Clash of the script is real. It's paper fucking thin.
Harry Hamlin is, I think they thought he was going to be this like new leading man and he's
just kind of boring to watch. Like complete zero. It's amazing. He had the career he did. He's
generically handsome. He has no acting talent or charisma of any kind.
The Burgess Meredith is functional in it, you know, but it's kind of a waste because again,
it's this paper thin character that a great actor has nothing to do with.
I mean, you got to imagine when Burgess Meredith is on set in the heat at age 76 talking about
all robot. He's got to give himself a hard look in the mirror back in that trailer. You know,
think about what he's doing. Goes it does the de caprio once upon a time and Hollywood speed.
Yeah, exactly. So yeah, but all right. So what do I got here? I watched, excuse me,
Rambo five, the Mexican border one, the most recent one. Yeah. So on a theater's pile of shit,
this thing was, oh my god, it was one of the wildermos I've ever seen released, you know,
it almost seemed like it had been like found somewhere and not actually made by a studio.
I think Stallone made it at his house. I think that's just his house that he lives in.
That's just and also his bunker that they can take him into Mexico to kill Mexicans.
Yeah, I got it covered. I got this down in my place in Texas.
I was never a huge fan of the Rambo franchise. I don't think any for I love first blood. I think
after that, they're all particularly from from middling to bad. I go I go first blood hot shots part
do. Right. Rambo two. Rambo three. Well, actually, Rambo remake was fun. It wasn't as good as
Rocky Balboa, but it was fun. I go horrifically violent. I go first blood. Rambo remake. Yeah,
then also hot shots part two. Yeah, then Charlie Sheen HIV announcement over the remaining
Rambo films. See, I didn't know that was considered canon and part of the franchise, but thank you for
sharing. So Rambo five, here's your plot. Stallone wrote this thing like on the toilet in 15 minutes.
It's literally, he for some reason is now living with an old woman who has a daughter or a grand
daughter, I guess it is. They never explain why he's living there. They never explain how he knows
these people as he fucking the old woman. Nobody knows what's going on. He for some reason has built
tunnels under the house and an under a series of tunnels under the house and an underground bunker
filled with weaponry. Again, no real explanation for any of this. This now gets into like,
you know, you're supposed to just go, well, after what he's been through, he would do something like
this gets into like that Halloween remake territory for me where I'm like, she build a
transformable bunker instead of just leaving the town where the murderer lived. Like, you know,
it's that bunker would have cost $500 ,000. Honestly, yeah, you're really, you're scratching your head.
And so Stallone, if I want to put an addition on my deck, it's a quarter of a mill.
So Rambo five. Yes. He's got this, he's Bruce Wayne. He's got fucking Wayne Manor in the
bad cave now underneath his surrogate Mexican daughter that lives with him. Again, we don't know what
this fucking relationship is never never been a part of the franchise at all to this point.
Never never been involved in the franchise. She decides to go looking for her father.
Rambo warns her not to she goes anyway. She goes to Mexico and gets kidnapped into sex trafficking
by a cartel Mexican cartel almost immediately. Yeah, you're talking 12 minutes into the film.
This is happening already. Yeah. Oh, by the way, she has a one of the first scenes in the movies.
She's having a graduation party from high school. And she's having all my friends over and then
they're all drinking and shit and Stallone goes, take them down into the tunnel. Tells her to take
seven drunk teens into a room of weaponry and machine guns connecting Mexico to America at a time
where the border is a constant hotbed of controversy and violence. So anyway,
and the scene makes no sense that you think like there's going to be a consequence of this
going in and there isn't. It's literally just a scene for you to see the bunk. It's so stupid.
Anyway, Stallone goes into Mexico after the girl. He finds out that she has been kidnapped.
He starts investigating the cartels as one I guess does in that situation. They
horrifically beat the living shit out of him. They mutilate him.
inexplicably, inexplicably, let him live.
inexplicably, let him, these are the drug cartels of Mexico. They're literally known for leaving
like the capitated heads along the border. He'll crazy shit. They let Rambo live
merely because Stallone doesn't know how to write something where Rambo gets to live.
He just doesn't know how to write the scene. So he let him live.
I don't know if Stallone wrote this one. He definitely wrote the other one, but
I believe Stallone wrote this and directed it by the way. I know he wrote it. Yeah,
which is painfully obvious because Stallone, he's not a good director. He doesn't know how to build
tension. He doesn't know to build suspense. He knows to say we need an aerial camera for that
explosion. That's kind of where it ends for him. And I'm a fan of Stallone, but
sounds like he's not good at this stuff. Story by David Gordon and Silvestre Stallone. By the way,
you shouldn't know that you were in trouble with Rambo 5. The author of First Blood, the guy that
wrote the book. For the first time in the history of this franchise, he said, I'm embarrassed my name
is on this movie. That's how bad this movie is. Anyway, by the way, that's a guy that doesn't have
to say shit, but sit back and collect checks. Right. Yeah. And he's like, no, I need to step forward
and risk cutting off my money source. Anyway, so the cartel that Stallone live,
Stallone finds his young lady friend. He takes her back home.
And this would seemingly be the end of the movie because they have now left Mexico, but
those that cartel, that sneaky cartel decides to follow Stallone back to his house where now we realize
he has built these tunnels for this very predicament that I guess he knew was coming.
I guess it's kind of like our government with the pandemic. They should have had more preparations
in order. Stallone was ready. He knew this was possible. He knew this was coming. He equipped it with
homelone style traps. Yeah. I guess homelone two style because they're more violent.
Yeah. And that's how this was described to me. When you and Avril, did you see events in the theater?
No, I saw it so long. Okay. When Vince saw them in the theater, I texted him and I said, how was it
and he goes, it was homelone except with Rambo. That's exactly how he described it. Because yeah,
then it's a zany like wily coyote 22 minutes of like like Mexican cartel members like tripping over
like explosive. It's ridiculous. It's absurd. And then it's homelone down to Stallone,
like hiding around a corner, setting off a booby trap, then scurrying quickly to like a tight
rope line sliding down. You know what I mean, it's so fucking absurd. I couldn't believe Stallone
added the sound effect for when he scurried over to the thing. And he was on his tippy toes. I just
I couldn't believe that he actually got up on his tippy toes to make that move. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I thought I also thought it was ridiculous when the cartel member got electrocuted and he turned
into a skeleton for a minute. I don't remember strong specifics about Rambo. I remember them
cutting to a greatest hits reel of Rambo before the end credits, which is what he's done in the last
three. Rocky as well. And he did it at the end of the last Rambo. Yeah, including Rambo on
up riding on a horse, which made the audience laugh very hard. But it's sort of ludicrous franchise
that's never been great outside of one really good B movie in first blood. Yeah. And by the way,
Stallone's at a point, he won't even put in the hair extensions to play Rambo anymore. He just
looks like Balboa now, except he has knives and guns. Like it's the characters. It's all mixing
together. At one point, I think Rambo's mentions Creed. It's all just bleeding together at this point.
There's no separation with it. Well, I mean, what I imagine happened is Stallone
strolled on a set day one wearing the Rambo wig and the producers were like, who's going to tell
them? Who's going to tell them he can't pull this wig off anymore? This is ridiculous.
It's not a good film. Terrible. I watched Come and See from 1985, which I've always seen on these
lists of the best movies ever made. And just never saw it anywhere. I never saw it on television or
in any video store. And I guess it was out of print. It is a Russian film. And I was very curious
about it. So when Criterion brought it out, they re -released it for like a week in theaters and I missed
it. But I wish I had seen it out of the theater because it's like, you know, it was an absolutely
incredible war movie. It's very depressing. It is about sort of the starting of the Holocaust.
It's Russian Jews and a German invasion. And for the first half, it's sort of a kid's eye view of
this. Actually, the whole movie, it's a kid's eye view. But at the beginning, you're basically just
with these little kids kind of playing and having fun and playing war. And then the actual invasion
heads and things get much, much more serious. It's a movie with a way darker second half than first.
But it was one of the best war movies I've ever seen. One of the best shot movies I've ever seen.
They had Roger Deacons, who was the best, you know, Shot Fargo and all kinds of movies.
Just give a talk for 30 minutes on the criteria. And Blu -ray about how amazing the cinematography
is in Come and See and how he looked at it before 1917. You totally see the 1917 influence
except in that movie, it felt like a gimmick. And in Come and See, it just feels like
you're part of the Holocaust, which might not be an experience you want to have, you know?
Obviously. It's very rough. The back half is rough. But I would guarantee it was a big influence on
St. Private Ryan and Schindler's List. And many of these other kind of masterpieces that came
in later. I thought Come and See was amazing. Check it out. Criterion Blu -ray has out.
Get it for 20 bucks on Amazon. Well worth it. I'll stick with my theme of action films.
I tried because Pat, you asked me if I would want to ever do an episode covering the entire
dirty, fiery franchise. Yeah. And I said, yeah, possibly. I've never really watched any of them.
I watched them all like in one day. Yeah. Thanks to quarantine.
You were like live texting me through the entire series. I have good days in Badger.
I got through maybe two and a half of these things. Christ almighty, I hated these movies.
They just did nothing for me. I couldn't do it. I tried to press on. I was like, I just get through the
I just found them painfully fucking boring and ludicrous too. I mean, it's just and Clint Eastwood is
I would dare say bad in these films. Like it's the acting. Like Clint Eastwood is a good act. I think
a good actor. I think. But I mean, just unforgiving is great. But I mean, he can do one thing
or he can do a slightly lighter version of that one thing. If you've never seen the dirty,
Harry films, it's Clint Eastwood walking around for two hours, looking constipated. That's the
face he's making. Right. Just I mean, by the third movie, he's got 38 murders under his belt,
easy on the job on the clock. Right. Nobody's asking questions. The captains just being like,
oh, foe, Harry. His, his partner dies so many times in every movie that they literally have to
make like a joke about it by the third film of like, you can't partner me with somebody. You know
what happens. And then an Asian guy and then he's just like kind of killed off. It's like, let's
bring in this guy for diversity and then immediately murder. Yeah. That you know, some fun lines,
some fun lines, some classic movie lines, obviously. But yeah. I just I hated it, man. I hated it.
I really thought I was going to like get into this like sort of classic, you know, this is one of
these like classic guy movies. And I was like, yeah, I don't think I like guy movies. I thought I
maybe would. But to me, there remind me of my grandpa drinking a case of Bush while watching a
double feature of them edited with commercials on channel 11 on a Sunday. I feel like I had never
really sat down and watched them until the other day. So for me, dirty Harry, which is considered
the classic is is a very good 70s police thriller. You know, I liked it. Follow up, which was done by
John Millius who wrote poplips now and all kinds of shit. I didn't see that one. I didn't see the second
magnum force is good. You know, I thought it was solid. The enforcer, the third one is the least
good to me. He's pardoned with time daily. Yeah. I was watching some of that. She's great in it. And
you know, they have chemistry, but it's like, it was nuts. I watched some of that. You know,
I remember the scene where he's like disgusted. Yeah. That's not like that. It's funny.
To make fun of him. He's disgusted by woman. He's not. He's he gets angry. He's kind of
promoting a woman for like, like diversity purposes at the department. Right. And he's mad that like
that they're doing it just because she's a woman, but then she proves her salt or whatever. But yeah,
he has kind of disgusted. Real hard fucking racial jokes in the first one. Couple real doosies.
For sure. Well, actually, I didn't rewatch one because I hadn't seen it many times, but yeah,
it's kind of a rough one. Pauline Kale, famously called Dirty Harry, the first fascist movie,
the first pro fascist movie. Then his partner and that one is Poppy, by the way. That's right.
You were very excited about that. Yeah. To me, the best in the franchise is for somehow the fourth,
which is never the case, but I think sudden impact is an excellent action movie and super fun. And
sort of the perfect line of winking at Dirty Harry and keeping him real.
Let's go ahead and make my day. That's sudden impact. Yes.
Great. Sudden impact. The is I did moderately enjoy sudden impact.
It's amped up. I mean, there's a lot of sexual assault in it. I mean, it's it's
tall. The plot is a woman who was raped and then goes and shoots the men that did it in their
decks. Yes. And it was being developed for which is this is exactly how feminism worked in Hollywood
back then. Clint Eastwood wanted to make a movie for his girlfriend, Sandra Locke, who is, by the way,
not much of an actress. And I don't know how Clint Eastwood was obsessed with her for so long.
But no offense to to the actress, but Sandra Locke, they were like, I want to do a movie just for her.
And it was that was the plot. She was going to have been raped and go back and shoot all these
guys in the dick and kill them. And then Clint Eastwood after trying to develop a project for his
girlfriend, they decide they're going to just make it a dirty Harry movie with Clint Eastwood starring
it. They were like, they were like, hey, this turned out pretty good. This movie that you made
as a lark for your girlfriend. They said, we actually like this script. Great. Let's make it a dirty
hairy picture. So that's what they did. But to me, that was the most kind of fun because they just
went for it. It was trashy. It was a good time. I liked it. The end of sudden impact, I admit it was,
like I said, there were some there were some interesting sequences. That's when they basically blow up
the guy's dick at the end. It's so crazy. The end. He turns himself literally into Batman at the end of
Eastwood. He directed the film too. Yeah. Well, see, he now there's a man who is a great director
of action and doesn't get the credit deserves for it. No, because everything comes up to 10. He
wanted to direct it because he's like, yeah, this has some great set pieces and I know I can do
them right. Yeah. He comes in at the end of the finale. The finale of this movie, he comes in
to kill the two main bad guys and save the girl. And he's draped in shadow. And it starts playing
like this bongo heavy disco beat. And the criminals who are armed, armed are literally so scared.
They don't shoot. They're paralyzed by fear. And he hangs on this fucking shadow shot for it's
literally Batman. He walks in darkness. And then finally at the end of a 60 second stroll, he draws
his gun and shoots one of the guys like in the eye or something something so crazy. Yeah, it's
I believe that movie got a lot of criticism because people said, you know, but at this point,
it's the characters is absurd. It's a superhero. And and to me, that's what everybody wanted.
I mean, it's the most successful of them. It's everything you want the dirty hairy franchise to be
and it kind of isn't except for that one great movie. The fifth one, the Deadpool is an absolute
nightmare. It's terrible. Jim Carrey is plant. He's acting in a horror movie where for some reason,
he's got to lip sync the entirety of welcome to the jungle. It's suppose, well, he's a musician
in the movie and that's his song in the movie. That's supposed to which it's so they didn't write an
original. They just gave him welcome to the jungle. Yeah. And it was just it's confusing because it's
like guys don't use a hit record. That's crazy. I mean, it's like, yeah, I thought he was
lip syncing it in the movie. I was very confused. Now that it's a very convoluted thing where he's
making a movie that's an it's like John Landis with thriller. Right. Okay. He's making like an extended
video or something. But I watched the beginning of that one just to see the Jim Carrey stuff. Yeah.
And that one starts with dirty Harry inexplicably being run off the road by people that want to kill him.
His car turns sideways. So the driver's side door is up in the air. Uh -huh. A guy with a machine gun
jumps up on top of the car to look down through the window. The right side window to make sure dirty
Harry's dead. You hear the guy falls back dead. Harry emerges with his classic magnum as like literally
like sitcom uplifting music place. Yeah. Like it's like, ah, there he is. There's your guy. He's back at it again.
It's a crazy franchise. It's really nuts. It definitely is. The deadpool eventually builds up to
a long car chase involving a remote control car heavily involving a remote control car like
going pound for pound with the full -size cars on the street. To me, it falls off big time there.
But Gran Turino should have been the 630 Harry film. I agree. And if not, now is the time to do a
dirty Harry. Like it would have such a massive audience. Now is so much the time he's too old,
but there's a million ways you could do it. I touched you by ideas that they don't. Yeah. I texted you
and I said, I really think this is a good idea. They should do a thing. He's 90. They should do a thing
where San Francisco, the San Francisco police department is honoring him because he's the oldest living
retired cop. And then amidst him getting honored, which he doesn't want anyway because he thinks it's
all bullshit. Right. All of the shit he's done starts coming out. And it's a it's a fucking
smear campaign in the press. And they're just killing him. And it's a disgrace. So then you get
into all the racial and political and social commentaries, the cops, all that stuff. And then
in the end of the film because it would be ridiculous if he's running around shooting people's
tool. But in the end of the film, he somehow like kills or brings in a cop that's in the backdrop of
the movie the whole time who kills a like a George Floyd thing where he kills like a black guy at
the beginning of the movie's a dirty cop and Harry brings him in. And like that's Harry's like redeeming.
He redeems himself in the end with the public, even though he's kind of a flawed guy or whatever.
That would be a fucking great movie, I think. They should make it. By the way, at the end of the trailer,
it would be your canceled. And he would shoot the guy. You also pitched to me, he's chasing a man
with a face mask on because of quarantine. And he gets so mad that he pulls the face mask off and
shoots it, which I thought was a fun. Yeah, he shoots the mask. And I did one of those record tech
so I can do my masterful. Clint Eastwood impression. But then he says something to the mask.
There was a I had a quip. I had definitely you just said go ahead and make my day, but he's saying
it through the mask and the criminal. Oh yeah, that would be the trailer. He's going,
and the guy in the ground's like, I can't understand you, man. What are you saying? And then Eastwood
rips the mask off, shoots it and he goes, I said, go ahead, make my day.
I'd like you to give him a new line there, though. What's that? By the way, that's the best my
Clint Eastwood's ever been. Your canceled goes there. Give him a new don't make him rehash. Give
him a new line. Well, this is just the teaser trailer. This isn't even a footage from the movie.
Oh, oh, I see this is like you're saying it was a scene. This is like, we better get word out
there quick, because Clint's going to die in two weeks maybe to make this face. I mean,
they're already operating in like a Marion net at this point. Anyway, we talk so much about the
the dirty Harry franchise that maybe we should just move on to other matters. You want to get to the
movie or you don't want to do another? Oh, do I got another movie? I just think shooting the shit
about dirty Harry with you. I can do a third. Absolutely. I saw a picture. Cool.
You know what I watched? I don't bet. You know what I watched? I rewatched the rock.
Michael Bayes, the rock. Here's another material collection. It is. That is absurd.
The rock and Armageddon are on the DVD come or here in collection. I own them both.
And there are some of the most extras packed. I mean, those are true. I think those are so awesome
because you could be an expert on how to make an action movie watching the extras on Armageddon
and the rock. Honestly, they and Michael Bay, everybody has their issues with them and what he did
to cutting and frankly, I think he played a large role in bringing us to this new age of movie
cutting like with the superhero movies where you don't even know who's fighting who. And more
importantly, you don't give a shit. I understand what people hate, Michael Bay. However,
there's a man who knows how to put together a fucking picture. I mean, the rock is in my opinion,
sort of his masterpiece, if you want to call it that. But it is so perfectly shot. The action is so
exciting. Nicholas Cage is very funny and insane and it was kind of the start of crazy action movie
Nick Cage. Sean Connery is funny and it dialogues good. I think Tarantino did a punch up on it as
with Crimson Tide and you can kind of tell sometimes. But it just, you know, there's so much I remembered
about it from seeing it in theaters when I was like 16. It was one of the first R -rated movies I saw in
the theater. But like the thing they pull out with the green balls that disintegrate, like make
your face melt or whatever, like it's almost like comic book shit. And that's why I think the
rock is so fun is that it's believable. Ed Harris keeps it super believable by playing it like a
huge bad ass the whole time that you and everybody, you know, he's playing it like it's 100 %
life or death. So you believe all the craziness around it even when it gets too joky, even when it's
just like, hey, let's have them in a mind shaft chase like out of Indiana Jones, the Temple of
Doom, which is for some reason in the basement of Alcatraz, a mind shaft roller coaster. But I think
that's the fun of it. It's fun and the same reason the Temple of Doom is funny, which is that it's
just strictly a machine for awesome action sequences. And if that's not what you want out of an action movie,
I don't understand why you like them really. To me, it's about as fun as an action movie can get is the
rock. All right. And I'll close this out with a rewatch of Tim Burton's Batman.
I always liked the film. There was a time where I said I didn't think it was a great comic book movie
necessarily. But I did think it was a good movie. I've changed my opinion. I actually on this rewatch,
I was like, this is a fantastic comic book movie. Tim Burton really, really nailed a lot of the
tropes he needed to nail to make that a good comic book movie. And primarily the fact that
I don't even know who the hell wrote that movie. I don't even know who wrote it. But honestly,
and it sounds like a joke, but his name is Sam Hamm, I believe. Okay. Well, the writer, I should say,
knowing, and look, it could have been a studio note because they recently said that they were worried
about not giving Heath Ledger's Joker an origin story. And they had to just trust Christopher
Nolan that it was the right move. But the writer of the Burton Batman, I think really,
really hit what he needed to hit to make a text to get a really solid comic book movie,
stuff that comic fans wanted to see in a movie like that. And you know, showing the Joker's origin
and access chemicals and just putting all the little details in and also Warren scaring it says here,
like says, the two writers names are Sam Hamm and Warren Scarron. That is the craziest thing
I've ever heard of in my life. That's crazy. It's just it's just a lot of little
things. We learn they're just alternate personalities and Tim Burton. Yeah, yeah.
You know, the having the two sort of cameo scenes with Harvey Dent,
you know, the way they build up to the way they execute or explain or not explain. But
just the way they convey the criminals are scared of Batman. That's a thing that you don't see
enough in Batman movies. And that's a big thing with Batman in the comics. It's not just a guy in a
suit running around after criminals. It's like criminals are fucking afraid of him. They don't know
what he is. And they think he's like this monster or something. They just kind of hit all of that.
And the way it builds up to him giving the bath signal. It ends with the signal, you know, unveiling.
It's a really, really great comic book movie. It bothers me that they got selfish or short -sighted,
I should say, and killed Joker at the end of the movie because they should never have killed Joker.
Joker should have been around for all of those movies. And then because they killed Joker,
and you kind of kill your big fish, that's why every Batman movie after that, I think, had two criminals
in it, which were wasteful because then they were like, why do we live up to Nicholson's Joker? Well,
get Davido and Fyfer, get Tommy Lee Jones and Jim Care. And it's like, dude, you're burning through
these fucking bad guys, man. The thing is, the Undicolson got 20 mil for the original Batman,
and then they can get Fyfer and Davido for five each. So I think he was making more than
Keaton on that movie. But to me, it's the template for these movies. I mean, it's a perfect superhero
movie. It's one of the, it's one of the few that I love. And I equally love, perhaps more so love,
bad memory turns. I know you disagree with me on that, but I think it's everything great about
the first one, amped up. And I dug that one too. I'm a big fan of those two movies. The reason, the reason
I don't like Batman Returns is because it's the opposite of what I'm saying. Like every, every part
where they should have been a ascension paid to detail of who this character is, they ignored it
to the extent of why does, why does the Penguin have a clown army? You sure? The Joker's the clown got.
Like, guys, like, come on, man, like, come. Yeah, the reasons that, that that one would piss you off,
don't affect me because I was just, I, I met Batman when I saw the first Batman movie. So I was like,
okay, cool. I'll go with it. But yeah, I mean, sometimes with these things, a fan's going to see
it very, very different. I'm just not a fan. But love wanted to. But anyway, onto our film of the day.
Yes, fed it up, Joe. A little picture called Becky.
Misleading title, strange title for a movie like this because what is the plot of Becky? The plot of
Nazi who breaks out of prison because he is searching for a very valuable key that is never explained
what it is. No. Why the Nazis want it? What it means? What it stands for? What it's worth? Or most
importantly, why this key is buried for some reason in the bowels of the guy from community's house.
Right. I always call him Hal Jordan. What the fuck is this? I forget his house. Farps to the original guy,
you're thinking of Joel McCale. Joel McCale. But you, yes, you wait the entire movie confident and
secure in the knowledge that at the end you'll find out what this key does, why it's so important,
why we witnessed all the bloodshed, we witnessed it in pursuit of the key. But you know,
and we went, I watched this movie with some friends and I was with Jay Okerson. And Jay always
goes on a distance. Yeah, socially distance. Jay always goes on to YouTube when he doesn't like
understand a movie. And he's like, let's look up the explanation. Like I need somebody smarter to
explain what, but this all right. And we searched high and low for YouTube video that could explain
anything. There, there's nothing to, it's not like, oh, it was, that's an old Nazi legend and they
just don't explain it. There is no thing. Well, I watched it with Heather and she assumed it was
setting up a sequel. And I was just kind of like, but they don't really make it seem like there's
one coming. And I don't know that they're going to get the funding if they want to make it
to explain what the key is. Like, I don't think people are leaving it so desperate to know what the
key is. They're going to come back for Becky to the, the beckoning. And by the way, nobody's,
oh, Becky, by the way, is Joel McKell's daughter, who once again, for some reason has a
just a, just a working knowledge of how to set up Rambo homoloam style death contraptions.
Right. It's a coincidence that the key is in the house of like somebody trained and heavy artillery
and artillery artillery artillery. Jesus Christ.
They never explain that. It's, it doesn't make any sense. I mean, this is a 12 year old girl and she's
killing like 250 pound grown men who are hard and criminals. Yeah, I mean, in pursuit of the key.
So it's, it's Joel McKell, his girlfriend, who becomes his fiance, fiance's daughter and then
Becky. And they're going to some sun, fiance son, son, sorry, they're going to a weekend get away
at Joel McKell's like summer house or whatever. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
the house is the house that Becky, Joel McKell and the dead mother lived in together,
is currently. So Joel McKell at the top of this film decides to in one fell swoop,
bring Becky to the house where she thought they were having to move out of. He goes, we're not
moving anymore. Drops that honor. She's thrilled. Then his girlfriend shows up who Becky hates.
Why is she here? She's spending the night with us. Becky's furious. Two minutes later,
Becky, we're getting married. Just taking this girl through an emotional roller coaster
of a day of it. And I guess that's, I'm sure that was a note, like you've got to set up why Becky
can do all this. So I think that was their way of trying to do it is tell you that she's in this
angry place. But it's a ludicrous movie. You just got to go with that, I think. But the quickness
with which it goes through those events, like at the beginning of the movie is part of what I
really liked about it. The movie is a hundred minutes that felt kind of like 60 minutes, really.
It feels like a Warner Bros. cartoon in a lot of ways. But the Nazis get there to the house and
they're like, we want this key. So randomly, like the same day, these people escaped from prison
looking for this key. That's in a house that randomly this guy's going to that very day. Right.
Randomly, the girl there is able to defeat all of them using powers that she doesn't have. But
what you want to know, what you came here for is how is Kevin James in a role that originally
Simon Pegg had. Yeah. So clearly, they were trying to cast against type there. And
the big left of picture clearly seeing the writing on the wall. This thing is going to be a
fucking disaster. But I know actually I do letterboxed, which is how I keep track of what I've watched.
And on this movie, the very first comment, one of the few comments is the director of Becky.
And he gives it five stars and he goes, it's my movie. So of course, I loved it. And I was like,
oh boy, this is embarrassing. Anywho. Kevin James is, I'll say, fine plus. You know,
everybody wants to get so excited when a comedian does something serious. He's fine plus. He's not
quite good. He's not quite amazing. But he pulls off the role. At one point in the movie, he's
supposed to take his shirt off and reveal his tattoos. And clearly part of his contract is that you
only see the top eighth of his top of his body. Because they give you no shots of anything like
below the tip on Kevin James, which who, by the way, is walking around through the entire movie with a
swastika tattooed on the back of his head. Correct. I mean, they committed to this 110%. Yeah,
every review I read of this movie is said, not every review. Many reviews, I read said,
this movie makes no sense whatsoever. And they're not playing it for comedy. If this was a comedy,
it would have been hilarious. Yeah. Like if they just made this the craziest comedy ever, it would have
been great. And it's not, it's not funny at all. It's just nuts. I do think though that some of
these Gore scenes are going for an evil dead two style tongue in cheek humor. Like when
they do the riding lawnmower and shred up that guy's face, Kevin James face, or the boat motor,
where it tears up the guy, those scenes are so over the top. Gory, I do think they know there's
a little bit of humor to this. Both of the gory is deaths in this movie. We're stolen from other
movies too. That seems right. The motorboat thing is from Friday the 13th part, six I believe.
And the lawnmower thing is from insidious. Oh yeah. Not insidious, not insidious, sinister. Excuse me,
sinister. That's why I always give videos. But this, well, the craziest scene is Becky somehow
stabs Kevin James in the eye or something. Which is crazy. And then Kevin James is in the kitchen
and he's holding his eye because he just got stabbed in it. And he takes his hand away. And his eyeball
is hanging out of the socket, connected to like a vein or something. As if that's what would happen
when you got stabbed in the eye. It would burst or something. You know what I mean? It's so
crazy. It's hanging off like with unembilical cord, like one of Crang's arms or something.
It's a big long -hanging pink thing. And he needs his friend to cut it off and his friend can't do it.
And Kevin James then puts his head down on a cutting board and slices off his own eye with a knife.
And then from there on out, and this was one of my favorite things about the movie,
just wild inconsistencies with Kevin James wearing this like eye patch to hold the bleeding. By the
way, all he does is he puts up like a bandage over it. And there's like, it's like, it's like a faint
crimson. Right. Gush, you bleed if you don't be a fight. You know what I mean? Fountain of blood.
Everybody knows from pirate movies, you stick a ruby in there.
Exactly. It stops the bleeding and you look great.
So he's got this thing over his eye. And just from shot to shot, it's not even seem to seem.
Shot to shot. It's getting wider. It's getting smaller. There's less blood. There's more blood.
It is all over the fucking place, man. It's great. And to me, that was a big part of its charm because
of right now where we're at, the only movie theater is really going our drive -ins. And I know Becky has
done pretty well on the drive -in circuit. And that to me makes it feel like it's 1975 or something because
Becky is the kind of movie that would have played on a drive -in circuit. It's a kind of movie I bet
but it's to me, it was really fun. It looked more professional than a lot of your
super low budget ones that look like they're filmed with iPhones and are kind of hard to look at.
It was well done. I was going to have a pretty good budget. The Gore effects were super
inventive and cool and funny, I thought. And I think it's over the top and it's sort of disregard to
believe ability were pluses in the end because I was just watching it to have some fun. And I did.
We watched it. A group of us watched it for all the wrong reasons. I brought it to everybody's
attention. And I said, there's a movie where Kevin James plays in neo -nazi and it's supposed to be
really violent. And everybody said, you're joking. And I said, no, I'm dead serious. And they said,
is it a comedy? And I said, no, it's not a comedy. It's serious. But it'll be really funny
to watch. And it did not disappoint. We laughed our fucking balls off for all the wrong reasons.
And it did fly by. It was a fast watch. It's a good, it's a good, bad fun watch, I guess is the way I
would put it. Yeah, it's really like very, very, very well paced. It never lets you down. It never
gets boring. You kind of root for the Becky girl. The actress playing her as fun. I was more into it
than I expected a bit. Here's the crazy part. The videos we did find on it. Yeah.
Bonus feature videos. Right. This is where it got crazy. Kevin James goes,
well, you know, I wanted to do something different. And of course, the script had to be good.
And the script was excellent. And I was so excited. Once you see them talking about the movie,
you're like, these theories that we're spouting about here, like, it's a fun like 70s to,
I don't think it is. I think they did that accidentally. I think they really think they made like a
deep, like heavy thing. There's a real commentary to this. Well, I think so did the people in the 70s,
the vast majority of the time. And that's why a lot of them kind of stand this as time is they
took them seriously. To go, for me, that's what made it work. When they try to make a 70s,
like a parody movie, like, it never works for me. It's never scary or funny. So it's not worth
I guess what I'm saying is like a Craig Zahler. Yes. Clearly is giving a nod to a certain type
of movie from 40 years ago. Right. He does it in an excellent way. I don't think that's what I don't
think Becky was going for that. I think they just stumbled into it by accident. Agreed. Yes. So
anyway, folks, that's our show. I hope you enjoyed it. We enjoyed bringing it to you. Check out
the podcast without a country. If you need to hear more of me, God knows why you would want to. But if
you do, it's a fun show talking about the news and stuff like that. You can use promo code WAC
on the gas digital network. It's a free 30 day trial. And you'll get first access to our live
stream every Tuesday. And if you're not joining gas digital, you can get the show anywhere you get
your podcast on Saturdays. New podcasts will be coming soon with me in South Volcano as well,
talking food. And that's it for me. Also, everyone, big announcement. We are switching to a
four episode a month model. So for those of you who spend the seven a month to get the two apps,
you can now get the four apps for $5 more, $12. If you don't want to do it, you do not have to do it.
It's just, you know, like like everyone else, we're looking for a way to make money during this time.
It's fun. We are happy to bring you more episodes. We have a lot more time to watch it,
a lot more time to talk about it. So I hope you enjoy them. And if that's out of your price range,
by all means, don't do it. I'm still doing my monthly hour long -ish
Pat's movie corners. Watch for those. Joe's going to start trying to do some rants on there as well.
Yeah. And that stuff will remain free to everybody. You know, it's the trickiness everybody
of just trying to find the balance of sustaining something while also
understanding that everybody's strapped right now. So we're just trying to make it work in the
best way we can and offer you some extra content. If you want it, if you want it, if you don't,
no worries. It's no biggie. And again, we're not jacking up the price of the original. It's
the same deal. It's just if you want additional, you can afford it. You like listening to us and
and have some company in your time of horror that we are all in. Then great. We thank you,
guys. Thank you for spreading the word. Some people still don't know we're on Patreon. So please
let them know. We are on Instagram at C1HellPod. We thank Emily for all of her hard work on the show.
We thank all of you who are doing the amazing fan art and sending it into us. You can check out
merchandise on the Etsy page at the Hoghouse. And I think that's it. Thank you all very much.
Joe and I, if you want to know what to catch up on before our next episodes, although
these could be at any time, but in the future, we're going to do the Phantasm series one through
Ravager. So if you haven't ever seen those catch on up. And what else have we talked about, Joe?
We're going to do that. We're going to do it. We're going to do the, sorry, yeah, and search
a darkness, the new shutter, the four -hour 80s horror documentary we want you to do.
We're going to do cats. We're the new thing, the movie cats. We're going to do one cut of the dead.
That's probably the next four things will be those. Yeah. Anyway, so that's it folks. Thanks a lot.