Welcome to We'll see you in hell, it's your boys, Joe and Pat.
Hello, Joe, and hello to all of you. Welcome to We'll see you in hell. I hope that there's a
seriousness in my voice because I was just talking to Joe. Hey, do we have any good news stories
we can talk about today and we're like, all right, we can do this, we can do that. But folks,
I just saw a news story. This is breaking news. Joe, I'm going to be teaching you about this now as well.
Okay. Perfect strangers reboot in the works at HBO Max. It was a matter of time.
Original cast. Two black women, Robin Thede and London Hughes set as the leads.
Okay. It will be written by Robin Thede, who does a black lady sketch show, which I have not seen,
but a lot of people love. Half hour multi -camera comedy. They're doing it. It will follow perfect
strangers. DJ played by Thede, so we're doing whole different names and everything. And Poppy,
played by Hughes, balls and not to go with Balke, who unexpectedly discovered they are half sisters
when they both inherit a one -bedroom apartment above a trap yoga studio in Fort Green, Brooklyn.
Polar opposites, they must learn how to live and work together.
So this isn't even, they're not even doing the
me post. Correct, which is strange. But, all right, you know, and it's not in Chicago,
and it's, well, they wouldn't touch that. They wouldn't do foreign or character these days with a
10 -foot pole. Yeah, right, you're right. So now, it's just, so that's, it's going to be two
broke girls basically. That's, and in Brooklyn, no less. It's exactly two broke girls, yeah.
All right. Look, Godspeed. I just, I saw this as I was clicking like accept to start the recording,
and I was like, whoa, this is meant meant to be. I got a new psycho. That was our like Walter
Cronkite breaking in with the Kennedy assassination. Breaking news. Yeah. Go ahead. Pictures came out
this week online from the set of Indiana Jones five. I'm very excited about this movie as I predicted.
There, so the first pictures that came out were of a train with swastikas on it. So he's obviously,
there's some Nazi thing going on in the movie. But, as I predicted, I don't remember if I ever said it
on the show or not. I probably did. Actually, that was just Mel Gibson's trailer. He was shooting
a hammy of folks. Oh, pictures of Harrison Ford leaked. He looks amazing. He does, he does.
And he's got the motion captured dots on his costume. So I was, I've been keep saying. I'm like,
they're, they're delayed this so they could deage him somewhere or whatever. But believe it or not,
the thing I was most excited about was the one of the pictures that leaked because he wasn't
announcing the cast was with Toby Jones. And I was like, Oh, that's perfect. Toby Jones is
built for Indiana Jones. So if you told me he was in crystal skull, I would have said, Oh, yeah,
I remember Toby Jones. I thought he was in it. So I'm getting excited for the film. Mads,
Michelson is the villain. You know, he's great. Love him. And I also like that mangold
rewrote a whole new script after all the script changes and everything. Mangold wrote a new script
with the two guys. I think the same two guys he wrote Ford versus Ferrari with.
And I was looking at some of their other credits. And it looks like it's all in about the right
place. Spielberg producing. I wish Lucas was producing, but he's not. But I'm excited. I'm excited
for the movie. I'm excited to see where it goes. And it's just fun seeing the pictures start to come
out now. I stumbled upon last night James mangled going in hard on on two guys who had a
podcast that sounded a lot like yours in mind, Joe. I what do you see this? Yeah. He
did. He looks like he might have taken it down. But he these guys in a podcast were like, look,
not interested in the new Indiana Jones. Spielberg's not directing. You know, they went through their
list of grievances and problems they have with it. And mangled for some reason saw this,
went in on them hard. He was making fun of their studio where they recorded. You know, he's like,
no, if you're going to talk shit about my friends and my support system who I work with, you know,
it was it was pretty, pretty rough. You know, he was like, if it's me and I'm James mangled,
making $10 million direct this movie, I'd probably let it go. But he's also much older than I
thought he was mangled. Yeah. I mean, I guess he's the right age. He's like 54. But like, for some
reason, I thought he was like in his like late 30s or something. You know, yeah. So I feel like
that's, you know, but you know, mangled of course, the writer and director of the great
cop land. One of my favorite movies of all time. So I'm not mad at it. Look, I wasn't a fan of
the Wolverine films. But people that were a fan enjoyed those films because they said he did
right by the character. So I think he's going to do right by this character. And I'm excited, man.
I'm excited. They also teased some sort of return back to the the grail location from the end of
last crusade. So I keep saying, I think this is going to be an anthology in the end of
you. I think there's going to be a wrap around story with old Indiana Jones telling
like three stories of his life that got us to this point of the wrap around. And that's it. I
think that's what it's going to be. But I might be wrong. So we'll see. We'll see. The podcast
was named here. I found it Matthew Catish. It says to anyone thinking Indiana Jones five might be
good. Just let me point out. Steven Spielberg is not directing. Kathleen Kennedy is producing it.
Harrison Ford is 78 years old. It's written by Jonathan Castin who wrote solo. And then a
image of Justin Timberlake looking at you like, you know, whatever these gifts mean.
Well, I like solo. I think solo would be a good template for a new Indiana Jones.
I love solo. And Lawrence Castin wrote Raiders of the Lost Ark. He also co -wrote Empire.
Or no, he wrote Empire and then co -wrote Jedi. His son captured
everything he needed to capture and solo because he's got it into his blood. He's he gets it.
He just gets it. So I love the castin was involved in this. His dad knows that's not Frank Marshall's
producing who was the producer of every Indiana Jones movie. Kathleen Kennedy has already produced
on Indiana Jones. Like she's well mangled correct some here. He writes back. And again
people are I think very rightly given him shit. This guy's got 4 ,000 dollars and a little
movie podcasts like maybe leave him alone. But he says thanks Matt. Keep making the world a better place
by crapping on things in the first week of production from your basement. Never seen a script by John
nothing against him just reality. The Butterworths and I started from a blank page. So I guess they're not
using the castin script. Yeah. Right. And then one to three are hugely talented and all at my side
meaning Spielberg, Kennedy and Ford. And they go they went back and forth all day. If you want to go
back and read these tweets, they you just kept going and I get I get the Kennedy criticism because of
how what she did with Star Wars and I get that. But you know, I was bummed when Spielberg stepped
down. But then I was like Lucas stepped down from directing Star Wars after the first one. And I
still love the movies. So it's like what you know, that happens. I'm not too worried about that. He's
there as a producer. And I got to tell you folks, I love Spielberg. You know, it isn't really hitting
him out of the park anymore with the action popcorn summer movies. You know, so I don't remember the last
great Spielberg. What was it? Catch me if you can. I mean, it was like bridge of spies, but it's
that's a totally different movie. You know what I mean? Like, yeah, you know, the last popcorn movie
he made was fucking ready player one. It was an abomination. Yeah. You know, and Lucas said very recently
about when he was still on the project, when he when they couldn't not reach five, six years ago,
when they couldn't get a story down. He said, and I don't think he meant it as a dig. He just was
like he was like, look, I'm I'm trying to move into the future with this franchise. I want to do
something new and different and Steve has really locked in the past. Yeah. And even though I like
Crystal Skull, that was one of the biggest criticisms about it was that it didn't incorporate anything new
and interesting. It just felt like they were kind of retreading old techniques and things. So I don't
know, man, we'll see what happens. You know, we'll see. We I mean, everyone can talk to shit. We all
know we'll be watching it when it comes out. So why not keep an open mind. I can't wait. I'm excited.
I'm excited. I got a scary stuff here.
Picked up a copy of Resident Evil Village, which is Resident Evil Part 8.
For my Xbox series X, holy shit. What a ride this thing is, man, if you like horror and you like
first person shooters, boy, oh boy, you got to get your hands on a copy of this thing. Takes place
directly after Resident Evil 7, which I never played, kicks up the action. It's freaky. It's scary.
I don't want to give away too many spoilers, but right off the bat, you're fighting like
likens and werewolves and shit. It's wild, wild, violent, gory, crazy fun shit. And they really lean
into the supernatural aspect of this chapter of Resident Evil, which sometimes they don't. Sometimes it
gets way too like militaristic for me. And like, you know, I don't know. It's just a lot of, you
know, getting, we got to get to the chopper and stop the outbreak. It's a lot of that shit.
Right. This is more like you're in some fucking village that is clearly Eastern European. Yet
everybody just has an American accent. That was confusing. But you're a dude.
You're there looking for someone from your family. It is desperate from the jump.
It's just awesome, man. It's just really fun. I can't wait to play it again tonight. I'm
very excited. I've only seen the original movie and I know there's been a bunch, but they also just
announced a new series on Netflix, a new Resident Evil. Yeah. And they're saying that the series now
will be a little closer to the source material. Because the earlier versions of Resident Evil,
the earlier entries into the game franchise were a little more haunted housey spooky, right?
You know, there was still all the umbrella corporation shit and everything like that, but the
movies really turned it into like, you know, sort of World War Z style. Yeah. For World War Z. But
you know what I mean? So yeah, I mean, look, you know, I'll check it out. I never really was a big
fan of the movies, but I'm curious to see what they do with the TV show. Yeah, that might be fun.
It's the guys who did supernatural. A lot of people love that show. I didn't see it. And do we talk
on here yet about how they're rebooting head of the class as well? To my good friends are working on it.
That's all I know. What's the plot like inner city? It's, you know, it's a very,
uh, it's just a much more diverse show. Of course, it's a, it's a new teacher. The teacher is a
woman, but I think it's, I guess the general setup of the original, which I don't even remember how
that started. Was it just a teacher or what? The original is Howard has been plays a struggling actor
who substitutes teachers in a spare time. He gets assigned to the, you know, AP class.
Yes. To teach them history. Uh -huh. He falls in love with the kids. The original teacher decides
not to come back and he stays as their permanent teacher. Got you. Okay. Yeah, I mean, it is, you know
what? It's sort of like, it's these, these boomers. I talk with my friends about boomers fairly often
and how like my dad and a lot of people in this age group, they can, they just talk.
They talk at you. They don't listen. They don't really care what you have to say.
And they just unload and talk about everything that's on their mind, just saying it out loud.
And I had a cab driver like that this weekend. I went to a wedding in Michigan. Before my
ass had hit the floor, he goes, you Detroit Tigers fan. And I go, no, no, no, I don't, I don't
follow any sports. He talks me for the entire 45 -minute ride about Detroit Tigers baseball,
how the minor league team was doing. I would maybe every five minutes go, uh -huh. That's
the extent of what I said. And I think now that it's that mindset that is the reason that boomers
are getting everything they enjoyed, every TV show, every movie, every everything that they enjoyed.
And the first half of their life, they're just getting it again. It's like the, like my dad won't,
doesn't want to watch anything new. You know, he's always like, yeah, I don't know. I don't
know what that is. It looks stupid, whatever. They're just, they're making these people
relive their life because that's what they want to do. They want to go back to a time when they were
happier and things were better. We're just getting all these shows again. They all so far have been
worse, you know, for the most part. And I really hope it ends every day. Like it's not an exaggeration
to say every day there was a new announcement of a reboot of something from the 80s, a new one,
at least one. And you know, I was excited about fucking Kingpin too as well. I'm not immune,
but it's like, at some point we're going to have to start coming up with new ideas, guys. Are the
cultural end as the world is ending? Well, this is what the business has always done, you know? I mean,
how many times do this extend? Well, there's never been this many platforms, right? That's true.
That's the thing too. It's like, you know, there was never this thing before of, you know,
Paramount is now going to bring content directly to the people. You know, there was a studio system in
place, but you know, a lot of it had to do with distribution. And there were other, there were other
cooks in that kitchen. It's not like that anymore. Netflix can do whatever it wants. Yeah, whenever
it wants. And there is no will theaters carry this? Will these people be interested in it? It doesn't
matter. That's true. So, you know, I think it's just, I think like anything else, it's all just
amplified. The worst of everything is just amplified now in ways that it never was. I also think the best
of things are amplified. I am tickled pink that I have friends with podcasts that most people will
never hear of. And then I go on their Patreon and they are making a yearly salary because they have
an extremely loyal fan base. Our podcast is not an exception to that. We are virtually unknown
podcasts outside of a very, very loyal fan base that we have. And the financial support for this
show is incredible. We're, we're always taken aback by it every month. It continues somehow to grow.
And, but that's also something you couldn't have done 20 years ago. So everything is amplified
now. The best and the worst. And it's just kind of where you want to live and where you want to put
your focus at this point. I mean, I can't believe I'm saying something this level headed and
positive. But, no, it's true. It's, it's, it, people are, if, if you want to hear something different
than, you know, a show you watched when you were five. And you should, by the way, it's like,
I'm, I'm 40. I used to watch out of the class when I was 10. I would have zero desire to watch
anything to do with fucking head of the class ever again. It's like, it was a, it was a tired idea
when I was 10. It's not really even an idea. It's, it's like a mixture of taxi and welcome back,
Mr. Carter, you know, like they threw two darts at a board. And that's it. But like, yeah,
God to be rebooting an idea that generic is so stupid. We, Joe, you and I talk about us all the time
on here too. Do a great show about, you know, a woman going in to teach a class and being a substitute
teacher, whatever, you don't have to pay for the name head of the class. Well, what it is is, is, it's
the, I think that aspect is the laziness and incompetence of development, and executives,
yeah, saying we can't risk and also living just within, just, just constant terror of lawsuits.
We can't take a chance in making something that could somehow be linked back to this other thing.
So let's just make the other things so we don't get in trouble. Right. And we already own the
other thing. So then we're not going to have to pay anybody any extra money or anything. I think
that's really all it is. Yeah. You know, like, and then, hey, if we get a little extra audience,
because somebody remembers the character of Dennis Blunden, well, great.
Or Arvind. Yeah. I mean, but I mean, these, these reboots, you know, to your point
or remakes, I don't know what the fuck you even call them anymore, but it's like it used to be
at least, it was like we were talking about the last episode about comedy sequels. Like,
you know, at least in Caddy Shack 2, they bring back Chevy Chase. You know what I mean? At least in
Ghostbusters 2, it's the Ghostbusters again, at least, you know, even though, but these, they're doing
like son of the mask approach stuff to everything now where it's like, you know, a few years back,
it would have at least been like, Arvind returns to teach the class. There would have been some
link, some link, you know, and this is not even the same way. Yeah. I've been trying to say,
I've been sued, you know, a show about two black women living in Brooklyn, the makers of perfect
strangers would not have sued you for that. I don't get what they're getting. You know, it doesn't,
not if it makes sense. I'm not making these decisions, but I know they added an inheritance thing.
Yeah. Like, it's got nothing to do with the original. So it's just strange. It's just strange,
but I guess they're banking on, hey, you know, perfect strangers is still popular. And whenever,
you know, entertainment weekly does that, where are they now in sitcom reunions, whatever their
perfect strangers is in there. So let's do it again. You know, meanwhile, every show on earth
has ripped off Seinfeld and never gotten sued or had a problem. I mean, Seinfeld is modern single
cam comedy. It would not exist without Seinfeld. And they've never been sued. And curb, curb takes it,
you know, to further down the road or whatever. Yeah. But, you know, I don't know, it's weird.
It's very distressing. It's very distressing to know that if I want to sell a pitch for the remainder
of my career, I need a book, an existing IP, they call it an existing something or I need a star
attachment. It's just not a world where you can walk in with with a sheet of paper and say,
I have this great idea and I'd love you to buy it. That happens. I'm sure, but it's, it's becoming
almost a non a non a non a non. And what do you call me trying to say? It never happens.
It's not existing. Non -existent. And that sucks. You know, yeah, let's go over to the movie corner.
I want to get through the movie corners. We can get to today's movie, Army of the Dead. Army of the
Dead. Yeah. I saw a movie called The Rental, which was a speaking of John Krasinski, maybe not
being suited to directing. This is a Dave Franco picture. And look, he does a fine job. It's a
it's a very, very traditional thriller. It's a group of people, group of young people, two young
couples by an Arab or rent an Airbnb. They have problems amongst them. You know, there's some sort
of cheating. There's some there's some issues within the relationships. And that's the first half
is kind of following their interpersonal problems. And then they discover that there are cameras set
up in the Airbnb. And the guy who let them in might be a real creep. And it might be like a fucked
up situation. They accidentally kill the man. And then from there, it becomes much more of a thriller.
It's pretty well done. You know, it's I love these kind of thrillers. I'm trying to get one launched
at the moment. You know, I miss those 90s, like unlawful entry style thrillers. This is not as good
as those, but it's solid. And I'm glad that they're still being made, even though they tend to go this
lower budget route. And it's, you know, it's supposed to be kind of a mix of a thriller and a
mumble core movie that whole genre of like kind of improv and like very naturalistic dialogue and
performances. And as that as a little experiment, it works. It's from Franco wrote it with the dude
who did a creep. If you saw that our Netflix or creep two. And it's a similar kind of feel. I like
an indie thriller, you know, it's like if if they're not going to give you $40 million to make one
anymore, I like the idea of doing one for $1 million, you know, there, there, it's an easy genre to do
that on. So it's Joe Swanberg, who is kind of the head of the mumble core movement. And Dave Franco,
the cast is Alison Brie, who if we hadn't been chided, I would tell you I find very attractive.
It's solid, you know, it's something you're not going to regret watching. It's an 88 minute thriller and
it's it's kind of fun kind of nasty and it works. Well, speaking of low budget, I watched a movie
called Sledgehammer on Shutter. This is a made on VHS movie from 1983. Watched it to Joe with Joe
Bob. What can I say? Do I think it's a good movie? No. Do I think it's pretty impressive for
its time and and the constraints and the means. Yeah. There were moments where I was really impressed
at some of the cool things they did with that you could only do with videotape and the limitations of
that and all that stuff. Some people love this thing. They say it's a must see cult classic. I
think that's ridiculous. But I do think it's an enjoyable little venture into a weird super subgenre
horror movies. And it's going to take about 70 minutes of your time. Yeah, I watched it and I watched
the other one they aired, which was called Things. And that was also kind of done on VHS. It
it was considered one of the worst movies ever and and you know, yeah. The I don't need to see
these ever again. There's there's something kind of a fun historical aspect of the shot on VHS
movement, but I didn't think either of these were worth my time. Even though I watched them both.
Was things also a VHS? Yeah. Yeah. Did Joe Bob like Sledgehammer?
You know, both of them. Well, he said he kept saying things is about as bad as movies get
in Sledgehammer. He had a little more affection for I think, but the spirit of the whole thing is
very endearing, but it is. It's I would have preferred a documentary about the VHS movement,
I think, then then we have having watched three hours worth these movies.
But I started watching Friday nights, Joe Bob, and he looked fantastic. So I don't know if he got
some rest or what, but I was worried about his health during the pandemic and he looked great.
I saw one hour photo I rewatched with Rob and Williams. I had not seen it since the theater.
And it's not as good as I recall. It's Mark Romanek, who's a big music video director,
directed some of the most famous music videos of all time. He's got a great visual style.
There's some really cool shots in it. I like Rob and Williams' performance in the movie,
but yeah, it doesn't really generate any real suspense. Everybody in the movie is kind of unlikable.
I don't know. I consider this one a little average. It's gotten that reputation as being like this
excellent film, and it's not quite there for me, but I liked it. Once I got over seeing Rob and
Williams play a bad guy, I didn't give a shit anymore. Final season of the Kaminsky method hit Netflix.
Very happy to get a conclusion to this series. I was a big fan of the series. Very disappointed
that Adam Allen Arkin is not in it, but he told them apparently from the beginning, you're getting
me for two seasons, and that's it. It was also disappointed that Nancy Travis didn't return,
but I'm assuming again that was, look, this was probably done during COVID and whatever, so
I'm sure between scheduling and whatever else, maybe some people just couldn't come back. But overall,
it was an enjoyable season. Michael Douglas was great, and the standout as Kathleen Turner, she comes
back in playing as ex -wife for a big, big part of the season. Love it. And they do a lot together.
So it was very obvious to me that it was like, well, we're not getting Arkin back. We're not able
to pursue the relationship between him and Nancy Travis. What's the next best thing we can do?
And it's like, let's get him and turn her back together. It's great, man, they're just,
she just shits on him, and it's funny, and it's a believable relationship. It's really endearing.
Paul Reiser back as the daughter's boyfriend, very funny. It's enjoyable, and it comes to a nice
ending. There's a very, very funny, they take a real, some real hard swipes at like Wilcoly Wood.
There's a plot line that they're rebooting Quincy MD, except this time he's black, and it's Morgan
Freeman. And there's a scene of him operating on a, you know, or whatever the fuck he's not operating,
but you know, there's what's that called on the cadaver's autopsy. It's just blood and shit
ever. It's so gory and disgusting. And then like his assistant is talking to him, and she's like,
so what did he say? And Morgan Freeman keeps going, they, what did they say? He keeps correcting her.
Morgan Freeman is in the commencement. Yeah, he's in it. He plays himself. It's just, it's very
funny. It's a very funny satire thing. And there's also, they also do the thing I love when they show
Paul Reiser watching him and Michael Douglas are watching Diner. Yeah, the movie. And Paul and Paul
Reiser, it's the scene with Paul Reiser in it. And Kevin Bacon and Paul Reiser goes, Kevin Bacon,
is he a jerk? I've heard he's a jerk. So I like when they do that, like sort of met a weird shit,
sure. But I liked it. It was, it was an enjoyable season. Okay. I saw
those who wish me dead, which is available on HBO Max starring Angelina Jolie. So it's this guy
Taylor Sheridan, who now is the show runner on, what do you call it? Yellowstone,
wrote Sicario and the sequel, hella high water, wind river, you know, very busy prolific writer,
director. And I've liked most of what he's done. This movie sucks. Those who wish me dead is terrible.
Angelina Jolie, the miscasting here is just off the chain. She's playing a firefighter.
My, my buddy I was talking to was like, you never see her with the hose. Like you can't imagine her
being able to lift a hose. She, her, her, it's, it's one, I mean, again, here we are talking about
women's appearance, but she, she's skin and bone. And they have to make a point of it at one point.
Somebody's like, but you're so thin. And she's like, I'm not thin. I'm lean. And it's like, okay,
so if you need to write in a line like that to explain how you can do your job, like maybe we cast
somebody a little tougher. It didn't work. There's some really interesting stuff up front
that I kind of like. There's a few kind of jumps that, that worked on me, but basically it's a
teenage murder witness who finds himself pursued by twin assassins in the Montana wilderness.
With a survival expert tasked with protecting him and a forest fire threatening to consume them all.
It's your standard kind of kind of thriller, but with the added mix of forest fires in the
background, anyone living in California doesn't need to see more footage of forest fires ravaging
homes. You know, it's just kind of, nothing about it works. It was sort of boring. And then about
halfway through Tyler Perry comes in as an actor. You're like, what's happening? What's going on?
It just nothing works. Nothing works in it. I didn't like it. Moving on.
As for not least, I guess my theme here is today is endearing things.
I watched a documentary called Stallone, Frank that is.
Documentary about Frank Stallone. Uh -huh. Man, did I love this thing.
All right. What a guy. What a just what a guy. You know, Stallone is Frank Stallone,
I think it's one of these guys that kind of gets a bit written off.
You know, it's always, oh, he's the kid brother of Sly. Sly's the star. Right. What does Frank Stallone
do? He does music. What? They go through his whole music career. This guy is so insanely talented.
He's such an amazing musician. It's crazy. Are these albums? Yeah. Yeah. A bunch. I guarantee you,
he's his biggest hit. I forget the name of it. You know it. If you heard it, you'd be like,
wait, that's Frank Stallone. That's how it goes. Ben, Ben and Ben and Ben and and and and.
And remember that song from the 80s? This is the end. Well, yeah, that's Frank Stallone. Okay.
So, you know, he sings take me back and take her back and Rocky's one of the guys singing around
the trash can, but he, like, I think he wrote that. Right. You did the entire soundtrack to staying alive.
and it was a huge soundtrack for the movie,
even though the movie didn't do well.
He did a lot of stuff.
His brother really looked out for him
and with the music and stuff,
but he kept trucking all his life.
Bad luck scenario after bad luck scenario.
He feels so bad for the guy.
It's just like every single fucking thing
that's supposed to work out goes, goes awry somehow.
But none of it is because he's a drunk or a drug addict
or an asshole, it's just bad luck.
Right. And he's still out there.
He doesn't show in Vegas now.
He's still out there just going like,
I know what's gonna happen.
I know what's gonna.
It's one of the most endearing things
and then seeing him and Stallone together,
like still be like brothers with a real relationship
and like, you know, and like Slimey
and like would that meet head tell you?
Get him in here, he's an idiot, you know?
Like just watching them be brothers
and like talk like at one point Stallone goes,
we he goes the fact that either of us here is crazy.
We should be slicing deli meat somewhere, you know?
He's not wrong.
Yeah, so how much money does Frank have?
I would imagine that he is living comfortably,
but not like, you know, I don't think he can stop.
You don't see his home or anything?
Yeah, you'd see, you see, you know,
but he leads meager, you know, it's like it's nothing,
you know, and he's also an awesome actor.
Cause again, you don't hear a lot about his acting.
You see, you know, the movies that he headlined in,
he admittedly, he says, it was like, they're not great.
But the movies that he did supporting roles in
as he was trying to break more into real Hollywood,
he's in bar fly, he's got a lot of stuff
and he's fucking great, man.
That was a time where just being a guy's brother
could get you like a five movie career,
like Joey Travolta and all those guys, you know?
Yeah, so, you know, they get into all that,
living in the shadow of the brother,
the whole thing of like he did his own thing.
It was, that's why I feel bad for him.
I feel like he's kind of misjudged
as being a guy riding his brother's co -tales
and it's not like that.
He had his own career.
He's, he had like music, he'd record label deals and stuff.
Like he toured around playing music, that's what he did.
He had, you know, so like, it's a great documentary.
It's really, really great.
It's really fun to watch.
Tell you shires and it's,
then mine isn't it?
Norm McDonald's weekend updates,
where he talks about Frank's alone.
I think they might actually put one of those jokes in there.
Yeah, you know, because that's the sort of running theme
through this thing is like the shadow of his brother
and like fucking aim, man.
Like I do all my own stuff.
Like I don't understand why I can't separate myself,
you know, self, right.
But the fact that they still love each other
and it's not, there's not resentment or whatever.
Yeah, it's a good flick.
I'm going to shut my cat up.
You want to talk us about army of the dead?
I'll be back in two sets.
So folks, this week's movie is Army of the Dead
or this episode's movie is Army of the Dead, Zack Snyder.
Back for more on HBO Max.
What can I say to get us rolling here?
This is a quasi sequel to Dawn of the Dead,
the Zack Snyder version, not the George Romero version.
Snyder went out of his way to claim
that this was in no way related to Dawn of the Dead,
yet there's an easter egg in the movie
that shows a guy on his phone reading a news story
about the events that happened in Dawn of the Dead.
So Zack Snyder being confusing for no apparent reason,
which is sort of a Zack Snyder, in my opinion, trademark.
They're also making another of these, as we speak.
Two hours and 40 minutes, I think this thing is
or two and a half somewhere in there.
Another Zack Snyder trademark.
It's got to be super long.
Big ensemble cast overloaded with people I don't care about.
An actor's I'm not that interested in.
Another Zack Snyder trademark.
And this is coming after I gave praise to Justice League.
So it's not always the case.
But as I said to my friend,
we're all just gonna have to accept the fact
that each of us loves two of Zack Snyder's movies.
That's it.
We all love two of his movies.
It doesn't matter which two they are,
but each one of us loves about two of his movies.
I love one.
Everything else is to me.
It's just like, come on, man.
So this thing, now this did come out before
trained to Busan presents peninsula
because I initially was annoyed that this had the same plot,
which was gang mercenaries have to go into
a zombie -ridden territory to recover some money.
Peninsula came out after this.
This has been in development hell since 2005.
So at the time, this was I guess a quasi -original plot,
but the problem is it's not 2005 anymore.
It's now 2021.
The idea of mercenaries trying to recover money
amidst the zombie outbreak is it's just been tread.
It's boring.
It's not interesting.
It doesn't hold a candle to the social commentaries
and depths of dawn of the dead, either version.
It doesn't hold a candle to train a Busan, the bridge.
It's wide and watch peninsula,
because I was like, I don't care about a high zombie thing.
But here we are.
Another, what is becoming a trope of Zack Snyder
happens in this where he takes a popular song
and then has a woman sing it over piano
while it sounds like she's about to weep.
They do that with Viva Las Vegas
at the beginning of the movie.
At the end, they do zombie.
Oh, yeah, they just play zombie, which I mean, my God.
That's like filmmaking 101 No No.
Even though the song is about a very specific events
and has nothing to do with zombies,
it's just like, hey, are there any songs with zombie
in the title?
I mean, that's literally what the thought must have been here.
Yeah, and we'll get to the story itself
in the quality of the film in a second,
but just another glaring, glaring awkward thing
that doesn't work is the Tignotaro replacement of Kristalia.
It's like every time they show TIG,
they've got blurred environment around her head
because that's how they were able to position her into them.
It looks ridiculous.
You can tell she's not acting across from people.
Yeah, they talk about how it costs millions of dollars to do
and it doesn't look like it.
It looks like they did it on the cheap, you know?
They went to Costco studios to fix it or something.
And she's just not right for the role.
TIG is like Woody Allen.
She's good at playing that thing that she does.
She is not right for this role.
Not granted.
She's probably, you know, acting across
from a pinball, you know, tennis ball with a face drawn on it.
So I feel for her in that sense, but at the same time,
it's like she's just, she's just not right for the role.
Like she's playing this like charismatic fly boy,
cigar chomping helicopter pilot, and she's doing it like TIG.
I mean, you know, we did a bit with her
on the p -home show called Cool Down Committee
and where she would bring her out in front of the audience
to cool off the audience.
It's like, it's like, this is not,
this is not like, you know, the loose can in crazy pilot
fighter person, you know?
So that said, another casting error.
I mean, Dave, what's also interesting in these is like,
what a punishment you're doing here to crystal clear?
You paid him a million dollars to the movie.
He keeps it.
He's now not in this bad movie, but that's your punishment.
You're giving him a million dollars.
Yeah, thanks guys.
And I'm the movie anymore.
I appreciate it.
It sucked.
Oh, I don't have to be in this piece of shit.
But they got Batista at the lead of this thing.
Batista is not a leading man.
It's like, it's, it's, it's, he stinks.
That's where this thing real.
And I'm, I'm looking here on the Wikipedia page.
He was talking about he was going back and forth
between this and suicide squad
and what would be the better move for his career.
And he wanted to do more dramatic roles.
And it's like, God, Dave Batista
is as bad an actor as is currently working.
He is terrible.
I have seen him do comedic roles and stuber.
I've seen him do all that.
He's so bad.
They're trying to make him the next rock.
He was a wrestler, right?
Dave Batista.
Yeah, yeah, yes.
I always get confused if he was MMA or wrestling.
He was a wrestler.
I mean, you're, you're talking,
you talked about Frank's alone.
I mean, the comparison to him and the rock
is basically Sylvester and Frank.
I mean, this guy is not an actor.
And no, I disagree.
Frank is a good actor.
Okay.
Well, I've never seen him hit really tried.
Dave Batista is not a good actor.
He's good.
Again, he, you want to sit him in a corner
with blue makeup all over his body
and have him say strangely awkward things to people?
Then sure.
Yeah, he can do that.
Yeah.
But you know, I'm not buying him as a dad
that, that, it's just, it's just not enough.
He's just not good.
He's terrible in it.
Zack Snyder is clearly going through some stuff
with the suicide of his daughter.
I understand that.
I think that's terrible.
Of course, my sympathies are with him and his family.
But it is now bleeding into everything he does
and it's getting weird.
I mean, the stuff between Batista
and his teenage daughter at the end of this,
you're like, oh boy, like they did not earn this
at all and like, why are they both crying here
in this movie where, you know, like 10 seconds ago
there was stupid comedy happening
and it's just that nothing in it works.
The supporting cast is stacked as you say
with all these actors.
None of them really makes any sort of, you know, impact.
They don't really have any chemistry.
There are scenes that just sort of seem like,
like the scene where Garrett Dillahunt is fighting the tiger
or basically just getting killed by the zombie tiger.
I'm like, all right, his zombie tiger
is kind of a cool idea.
But what is it doing in this movie, you know, like,
it's just, it seemed like it had nothing to do
with anything else.
At least, like did they say he escaped
from a cigarette Roy type show or something?
Yeah, they, I think they made some comment about that
but who cares?
It's like, they're going into zombie territory.
It's like, guys, you know, you could just kill this tiger.
Yeah, yeah.
And they don't.
They talk about how they have this barter system
with the Alphazombies, which is another thing.
There's Alphazombies and, and, and, and,
like sort of stoic, for rumors or whatever the fuck they're called.
Yeah.
And which are the more just stumble around zombies.
So it's like you, you do this thing
where you call out to the Alphazombies to get passage
and trade for giving them another person
to add to their army.
Why would you do that?
Why wouldn't you just call to the Alphazombies
and when they come out, kill them?
And then when the next couple come out, kill them.
And then when the next couple come out, kill them,
you wouldn't do it.
This makes no sense.
It's dumb that there's Alphazombies.
It's really fucking dumb
that the two head Alphazombies are man and woman
and she somehow gets pregnant.
Yeah, that's fucking ridiculous.
And again, once again, we find herself
a familiar territory on this podcast
where things are just conveniently done
because the writing needs them
to be done that way in a moment.
So if we need a person to get bit
and turn immediately,
because that's what services this scene will do that.
If we need a person to get bit
and not change for three days
because we need an ending to this thing
and show a guy landing someplace else
even though he's infected, we'll do that.
If they start turning like as a door is shutting,
that happens so many times,
exactly when they need it plot -wise to happen,
then suddenly he's a zombie.
It was really cheap.
They rip off train to Busan in the dark,
they do that sequence with the dark
where they're in the dark
and the zombies are like sleeping
and they have to walk through them or whatever,
which was pretty much a rip off train.
I thought they lack complete lack of attention to detail.
They go through a secret passageway
from a refugee camp on the side
somewhere near Vegas.
That's close enough to Vegas
that you can sneak into Vegas
through this camp, through this secret passageway.
They come out of the secret passageway
and they leave the door open.
I mean, it's like Zach, what are you doing here, dude?
There's piles of dead zombies outside of the door
where they say these were the zombies
that weren't smart enough to get out of the sun
so they dehydrated, which again,
doesn't make any fucking sense.
A zombie can't, that's not what a zombie,
you can't dehydrate as a zombie.
And then they said when it rains,
they come back to what, what the fuck are you talking about?
So that doesn't make any sense.
The head alpha zombie somehow has figured out
how to craft an iron helmet for himself.
That's bulletproof because he knows
that he needs to protect his brain
because that's the only way.
Once again, you can kill the zombie.
Yet he doesn't make them for the rest of his army.
Yeah, why not just do that?
And then your whole army is covered.
They don't do that.
A nuclear bomb goes off at the end of the movie
to wipe out Wallace Vegas,
yet Dave Batista gives his daughter $5 ,000
and says this will get your friends out of that refugee
or out of that internment camp.
What?
A fucking nuclear bomb just went off
and wiped out half the state.
What the fuck are you talking about?
It was right.
It's just logic drop after logic drop after logic drop.
It makes no fucking sense.
None of it.
It's also poorly pieced together.
It's also stupid.
There's no science to any of it.
There's no rhyme or reason or logic to any of it.
It's poorly acted.
It's riddled with cliches down to the moment
of Dave Batista's daughter and him having this conversation
where he's like, I just, I know I should have been there,
but I wasn't that the fucking,
they got a character in here
that's supposed to be like a safe cracker
who clearly was supposed to have been played by Alan Tudduck,
but he said no.
Yep.
So they got this other guy in there
whoever the fuck he is.
That was Tudduck for a minute.
So yeah.
And the daughter and Batista stuff,
it's the kind of shit that you'd hate
even if it was like Will Smith or somebody
who's a great charismatic actor.
You'd be like, all right, let's get back to the action.
But when it's Batista, just this big pile of beef,
you know, like to ask him to do all this dramatic heavy lifting
is just, it's wrong.
I mean, it's painful.
It's, there's another thing where they have to go through
a series of like Indiana Jones style booby traps
to get safely up to the safe to crack it open.
First of all, it's ridiculous.
One of them is like you step on a panel
and machine guns blow you to bits.
It's fucking ridiculous.
But aside from that, they've been commissioned
by the guy that owns the casino to go crack the safe.
Wouldn't you tell your crew this?
Wouldn't you say, here's how you get through this guys,
just so you know, because they're not done with them.
They do need to get into the safe.
That's crucial.
And they don't, it's just fucking dumb.
It's a bad movie.
It really is.
And nothing about it works.
I haven't talked to anyone who liked it.
Even the most ardent Zack Snyder aficionados are like,
oh, man, the length is absurd for this kind of material.
It's just like, it's absolutely absurd to pretend
that it's not of a piece with Dawn of the Dead,
which is the one Zack Snyder movie I love, is nuts.
He's got Richard cheese doing the covers of stuff.
That's what they did in Dawn of the Dead.
It's like, you've made similar music choices.
Don't pretend they're not in the same family.
They're making now.
So I read here the head of Netflix, Zack Snyder goes in
and he's talking about some movie ideas he has.
And apparently the head of Netflix said to him,
go write that movie and we'll make it.
Go write it tomorrow and we'll shoot it in a week.
So just simply saying, yeah, zombies in Las Vegas,
there were like, here's 90 million dollars
to go make this movie.
If you write it tomorrow, meaning if it takes you 24 hours
to write it and it's not ready,
we'll still green light this thing.
It's like no wonder everything is so fucking shitty, you know?
It's funny.
I was watching a tale from the dark side last night
that I like, an episode I like a lot about a struggling,
it's about a novelist.
But he's struggling, he's starving.
Yeah.
And he signs with this agent.
I forget the actor's name, but this big huge fat agent
who's always eating and everything.
And it's a great character.
And he tells the guy like basically the way the way
the industry works in Hollywood is through black magic.
You have to practice black magic or whatever.
So the way you're going to be able to sell your books
is you have to start getting into animal sacrifice.
But not wrong by the way.
Right, yeah.
But one of the things, this is 1983,
one of the things the agent says is he's like,
he's like, you got a Western, my boy, I need a Western.
And the guy goes, no, this is about incest
and the dark side of the human heart or whatever.
And he's like, can you make it a Western?
And then the guy's like, I know, I write from here.
You know, and the agent's like, okay,
tell that to your stomach or whatever.
So that's what it is.
It's like Netflix isn't thinking,
is it a good movie?
Is it an original idea?
Is it this or is that they're thinking?
Zombie, sells, good, do it.
And that's it.
It's, you know, reading through this Wikipedia thing
that it's like, there's so much here
to just be infuriated about that it's like,
there's no quality control.
And then Zack Snyder says, this was not a film made by committee.
It's definitely a movie that's incredibly personal
and singular.
No, it isn't, man.
No, it isn't.
I mean, just because you put a lot of your daughter trauma
into the movie and that aspect of it is personal to you
does not mean that translates to us.
It still just feels like a big bloated piece
of Hollywood shit.
No, this is like when Spielberg was going around going,
where are the worlds?
This is actually a tiny film.
It's about it.
Yeah, fuck up.
Yeah, and looking here, Netflix has Greenlit
and they did this by the way before the movie was released.
So now nobody likes it, but they've already got
an entire cinematic universe in production
at a cost of hundreds of millions of dollars.
Again, perhaps not the smartest way to do things.
September, 2020, Netflix announced
that they had Greenlit too prequels to army of the dead.
One is a film called Army of Thieves
set before the events of Army of the Dead
that follows the character Ludwig Dieter
who I don't even remember in this movie.
I just thought.
That's the safe cracker.
The safe cracker, okay.
Yeah.
Yeah, they're going to do that.
Production on the film concluded in 2020,
so that'll come out later this year.
Prequel to a movie nobody liked.
They're also doing an anime style series
called Army of the Dead Lost Vegas, an animated show
that's also a prequel and it follows
pretty much everybody from this movie.
Like you really want to know how they all came to be.
It's got Nataro and everybody.
They're acting as though like people want to know
everything about these characters.
These beloved army of the dead characters
and that if somebody is putting hundreds of millions
of dollars into this, they should lose their job.
This is not, this is these characters
you couldn't care less about them.
They do nothing to introduce you to any of them
to endear them to you in any way
before you're supposed to suddenly give a shit
about them being endangered.
It's, you know, this is basic, basic,
basic horror movie stuff.
Like you got to make the people care about the characters
or hate them.
So that way when they're, when they die,
you give a shit, they do none of that in this at all.
You don't even get like the one sentence thing
like if you're pitching a series
and you've got like 10 characters,
some of them might, you might just go,
here's a quick little synopsis of each one.
I wouldn't even know what to say about these characters.
Like there's nothing about them.
They're completely interchangeable,
completely boring, completely bland.
More depth went into the Magroober recruiting
pro wrestlers scene in Magroober.
Like this is a terrible, terrible movie.
Zack Snyder is not good,
which stop hashtagging release the Snyder cut
of sucker punch.
That's trending.
What sucker punch is as bad as movies get?
Horrible film.
Yeah, this just isn't good.
Zack Snyder is not good.
He's, he, he, he, he looks out sometimes
and, and that's it.
There were more, because he shot this too.
There were moments in this, especially in the first half
where I was like, that's a really good shot.
I mean, he knows how to shoot,
but the guy should be a cinematographer or something.
It's his music choices and his story choices
and it's like he's clearly got his like fetishes
and his things that he obsesses about
and they're not in line with anyone else in America.
It's just, he's not the guy, you know?
And he's, he's talking about doing a sequel here.
It continues the zombie story.
It takes it even further.
What are you talking about?
There is no story.
What are you taking further?
And there is no further.
And you had five people in a city overrun with zombies.
There is no further.
That's as far as there's a lot of most zombie movies
that have ever been.
So he says the sequel would be set in New Mexico.
We think there's still more story to tell.
What?
It's two hours and 40 minutes.
If you can't tell a zombie story in two hours and 40 minutes,
get out, get out.
I mean, this really was a depressing movie.
I watched it in over the course of four nights.
Yeah, it took me a few years.
Each time I would return to it was like
as if I had a gun to my head.
Yeah, I had to do it in installments as well
and same thing.
I'd put it on like, like just, I could stomach it
like when I was like eating dinner.
And I was like, yeah, I'll just sit through this as like
because I'm satisfying myself in a different way right now.
Yeah.
But yeah, two dead hogs down for Army of the Darkness.
I'm the Army of Darkness.
Oh, Army of the Dead, sorry.
Yeah.
And that's our show folks.
Thanks for tuning in.
We'll be back next month with conjuring three.
And you know what we should do, Pat,
is the amusement park.
George Romero's lost film just hit shutter.
I'm down, I'm down.
Also look, look at sometime in the near future
for a dentist and dentist to episode.
Yeah.
Corbin Burntson special.
It's dentist to a shutter.
Can I get it on there?
It was, but they took it off.
It's on 2B.
Okay.
But yeah, we'll be back.
Emily, again, as always, thanks for running the social needs.
Thank you.
We keep going up on the Patreon.
Thanks.
If it's due to talking, if it's due to Joe's taste buds
that we don't know, but thank you for spreading the word.
It means a lot.
It keeps us doing the show and it keeps us in business.
We appreciate it.
We love all you guys comments.
I do read them always.
It may take me a couple months,
but I always read them on the Patreon.
We've got my special bonus app coming up
at some point during the month.
Hope you guys are well.
Hope you're getting back out
to society.
Hope you're starting to feel a little better.
And I am, which is a good thing.
And we love you guys.
I am the Patrick Walsh, Twitter and Instagram.
Joe, you already do your thing.
Joe DeRosa, Comedy, Instagram and Twitter.
See you next time and see you in hell.