Hello.
Helen's.
You're welcome to the high -outs.
Welcome everyone.
How are you?
Sit the fuck down.
I'm kidding.
Sit down at your leisure.
Hello, I was just telling Joe I'm extremely nervous for some reason.
This is why I stopped doing stand -up comedy.
My hands will be shaking probably throughout the night, but it's fun.
Well, this is for you.
You kill it with a drink like Bradley Cooper and a star is bull.
It worked out good for him.
I don't know if you guys have seen it, but everything turned out great for him in the end.
I haven't seen it.
But it's based on Bradley Cooper's actual life, correct?
I believe it is.
It's a biopic.
I haven't seen it.
How was it?
I'll get to it in the movie corner.
Very good.
Welcome to.
We'll see you in hell.
Your favorite podcast covering horror sci -fi fantasy films.
Thanks for being here everybody.
We're really touched that all of you came and some of you flew, which we don't understand.
I'm telling you right now you're going to regret it.
You're going to regret it.
I've never flown for anything.
Not even barely family.
No, absolutely not.
But it's very touching and nice.
You're the only reason I'm on Facebook opening myself up to my bank account being cleaned out.
My family being targeted and assassinated.
Really, I want to get off.
I like it for reading your guys' comments and I read all of them.
And then I like it for bragging about my career to my enemies as well.
Right.
I have no use.
I'm still not on it.
I can't stand to look at people even digitally anymore.
I'm off of all social media.
What's going on Pat?
How was your day today?
My day was good.
As I said, there was a lot of nerve diarrhea.
A lot of pacing.
I don't understand.
I like performing.
This is why I walked away from the spotlight when I was at the top.
You know, less like Destiny's Child.
They were like this, this can't sustain itself.
I was the same way.
Pat backstage, much like in bookie nights, stared into the mirror for a good 10 minutes.
Calling himself a star.
With his dick out.
I figure we're there.
We've become very close.
This is so much nicer than our usual setup.
Usually I am looking down Joe's billowing Gymshoes.
Or watching his dog defecate on the carpet.
This is a really nice setup.
Beautiful.
I love the toe of my ribs.
Thank you for hosting our first ever watching.
Thank you.
Before I go much further, Joe, I'd like to get on with the show.
And at the same time, on with the...
Joe, my mom, I'm in fear for my life.
I'm in the heart.
Here you are crying, you're so scared, and all alone.
I don't know anymore, isn't it?
How do you...
The Supers Hot The Beer is Cold!
We're going to Broadway!
So let's hit the Danny's!
How do we miss that after we actually saw sticks.
How did you not do that as the honor of the Joe?
I don't know. I don't know. That's wild. Pat, it's good to see you. I watched episode
four of Cool Kids today. Did you like it? Yeah, we just got picked up for a full
season. Pretty exciting. I enjoyed it very much. Thank you. It's a fun show.
That Leslie Jordan kills me. He's a killer. If you're in LA he's at a live show
in November sometime. It's supposed to be the filthiest thing you've ever seen. So I'm
excited to see that. And I like the show. You know by today's standards is it's
pretty edgy. You're getting away with some, some Joe before team folks. But you're
going to watch it. The recurring joke in that episode has been Leslie Jordan's
several people. My son doesn't know I'm gang and then people laugh hysterically in
his face. Yeah, it's a, it's a, that's an edgy joke. Sure, yeah, yeah. I won't pat
me on the back. Back? Thanks. You're welcome. Yeah. How was your day, Joe? I just
told you I watched Cool Kids. That was some total of your day. That's the saddest
thing I've ever heard. I wonder what I got a ton of time on my hands here. What did I do?
I watched Cool Kids. We got it. And I watched. You know my favorite joke was in
this episode was Leslie Jordan. Now I watched Cool Kids. And then I went to a
place called the Toasted Bun and had breakfast at the counter by myself like a
drifter. And I wrote, I wrote at the counter. And then I came home and I watched
Halloween H2O in my bed. All right. And then I made a oven pizza from home run in.
It's home run in. It's a, it's apparently where they're not in the pizzas out of the
park. I don't know. It's a frozen pizza. I ordered online. I got it delivered. I've been
getting my groceries delivered. I'm preparing for the point where I don't even get
out of bed anymore. So I'm having groceries delivered. Home run in. Made a pizza and then
watched two episodes of cheers while I ate the pizza. Okay. Very nice day. How was the pizza?
Disgusting. No offense to home run in. But it's, I mean, I haven't had a frozen pizza forever.
I know Ilios is very popular. Disgusting. Ilios is dog shit. It enfants me that people like
that fucking pizza. And I'll tell you something else. Mama Celeste sticks. And these are your two
leading brand pizzas. This is why the fucking country is in the toilet right now. Nobody knows
quality anymore. That might be true. Yeah. You never heard of Mama Celeste? Not to my knowledge.
Says, I've been Don's on the box. What's up in Don's? Delicious. Her mind fucking mouth.
Oh, I'm Don's Italian. I mean, it means eat. No, that's mom's yet. I don't know. It means
good or something. Make a strong point there, Joe. So that's all I get. Okay. What else did I do?
Oh, I went to Vaughn's supermarket and I bought liquor because you know, you're all invited
obviously. We're drinking with everybody after the second show. And the venue was kind enough
to say, you guys can just do it here. And I said, great, but you don't have liquor. And they said,
now we don't sell liquor. We sell beer and wine. I said, well, can I break liquor for free and just
can Pat and I just break free liquor and give it to people for free. And they said, yeah, totally.
So Pat and I don't want a shitload of sticker. Give it to people. I brought a lot more than Joe.
I brought maybe three times as much as Joe said. I know he's trying to kind of loop us in as one big
unit, but I brought a lot more than you. You did. I went to Vaughn's because it is the cheapest.
Sure. Why didn't you just order it from your pizza delivery? Because I ordered once from
the one grocery store. Now I'm afraid they know where I live. And I've got to switch it up.
I've got to find a new shirt. I'm telling you, but pretty soon you will be the only person I ever
speak to via this podcast. A lot of you. All right. As long as it's just that hour between.
Yeah. I don't want more than that. I'm pissed. I got to do this right now. Is it extra hour
this week that I have to spend with you? Do it. Folks, what I'd like to do up top here is I know
we all enjoy Joe's theme song. Joe wrote it. He performed it. And we like it. It's getting a little
stale. Am I right? No. Oh, thank you. No, I love it too, people. But help me out with the
fucking bit. It's getting a little old. Am I right? That song took me minutes to write.
Yeah, I have to do this now. So this will clear up most of my nerves. But I felt what our theme song
was lacking. Sorry. It was emotion. I thought it didn't quite paint the story of how you and I were
once, you know, bitter rivals screaming at each other on here. Now dear friends, it didn't quite paint
the full emotional picture. I'm sorry. I didn't have that foresight before we ever recorded it.
And I wrote the song. But I've written a new song. I've written a new thing song for the show.
Three people want to hear it. I told you how nervous I am and they reception there made me doubly so.
But I'm going to do it. Is this my gone? Yeah, okay. I believe so. I guess I'll do it there.
So those of you at home Pat went backstage and got an acoustic guitar.
Now I've heard the song. Hello. Oh yeah. And it is much in the vein of Pat's favorite band,
The Gin Blossoms. Which played nonstop as the house music tonight just so everybody can see how
fucking wrong you are. I didn't know Joe was going to play all Gin Blossoms before the show. He requested
his kind of a joke. I would have said I only really approve of the first album in a half. We were
here in some deep. Rolled over on him immediately. I heard a live Gin Blossoms track in the next.
And I apologize to you for that. Okay, so here we go. What's the name of the song? We'll see you in half.
I'll probably mess this up. You see how bad my hands are shaking? It's not great folks.
Do you need the lyrics? You left them over here. I don't have a lyrics over here. I know you're in my head.
All right, I think we're good.
Like Larry and Balkie. Like Keenan and Cal.
We'll see you in hell. We'll see you in hell.
We'll see you in hell.
Like Elf and the Dad on Elf.
Like Jerms and Purell.
We'll see you in hell.
That's food in the corner.
We're just scared of stuff.
I think I got to figure it out this week.
Joe says I'm not good enough.
You're not.
See you in Hell.
See yo in hell.
See yah yo in hell.
That was a, that was very good. It was very good. I would have written a song too, but
I didn't know we were showing off tonight. We always were showing off, Joe. Why don't
you, you want to take his first stroll? A stroll over to Pat's movie corner. He's just
describing the song, sure. It's a wonderful song. Thank you. Let's kick it off with
the stars, born. Okay. I saw it. Does anyone see it? Okay. I mean it's long.
Pressing his hell. Bradley Cooper is good. The entire time he's doing a Sam Elliott
impression, comically so. Really no different than yours or mine. Okay. He'll probably
win Best Actor for doing it. You know, we're giving it away for free week after week. But what is he,
what does he say? Let me touch your nose. There's like a ten -minute scene where he's like, you
know, flicking her nose like a clitoris. I can't think. If you've seen it, I'm not
scared. There's a lot of nose sexuality in the film. I got a big nose and he's like, I love
your fucking nose. Let me suck on that nose. And I'm like, should I be watching this? Maybe
we cut this. I can't think of one lady Gaga song. What is one called in a bad romance? Yeah.
Oh, yeah, you got me in a bad romance there. And there's a, oh, log. I think that's the same song.
Yeah. Sam's on. Oh, yeah. I'm not a wrong man. Yeah. Okay. There's a, you are beautiful. No
matter what you say. No, that's Christina Aguilera. Hit me, baby, one more time. There's a Vogue. Yeah.
No, give me, I do need to hear one, what is one more lady? Oh, yeah. Yeah. I sing that at the
poker table in Vegas. I sit down and I'm like, pop, pop, pop. It really freaks them out. They
don't know how to respond. I'm like, I fold and I move to another table. I yell, do you guys know
the tales from the crypt episode cutting cards? Just clap if you know it. Okay, because that's
what I was, a few people know it. That's what I was. I yell lines from that episode at dealers
in Casino's. They don't know what the fuck I'm talking about. Like they'll be putting the cards out.
I'll go, come on, deal them good this time. Guys, I get, don't please don't yell at me. Like, no,
it's an episode of tales from the crypt. My favorite episode, they're like, sir, leave. I get that. I get
that. Yeah, so it was, it was a good movie. It was well made. It's the same story they've
told 50 times before. Guy discovers a girl. She outshines him. He's jealous. He drinks himself
into a stupor. That's what it's about. Yeah. I thought it was about. He was like, you're not that
pretty, but you got spun. It's that too. It's, it's that too. That's what they make it look like
in the commercial. No, that's about that as well. And then Chipel comes in and goes, I'm worried
about you, my end. Yeah. Fall in love with he's not pretty girl. Well, Chipel's got one say,
I feel remember from last week's episode, Joe asked if Dave Chappelle played Lady Gaga's dad.
It was not making a joke, but so Sam Elliott at some point shows up in the picture as Bradley Cooper's
brother. I think, although it was very confusing, he's his brother, even though he's 900 years older
than Bradley. And then so they keep arguing and it's like, listen, I told you when you started in
this business. And then they keep talking. And finally, Sam Elliott goes, you stole my voice.
So I was like, all right, they acknowledged it at least. But clearly he was like a vocal coach on
the movie, Sam Elliott. I can't tell if that what you just said was true. It's all true. It's all true.
He says you stole my voice. I swear to God, it's a line from the movie. Why was you stole my voice?
They're yelling at each other's face and Bradley Cooper is doing a Sam Elliott. That's right,
Kim's a fucking, that's like in the, we're not the next show. Today's movie, by the way,
is Tales of Halloween. Tales of Halloween. We're reviewing, we're reviewing, T -O -H. Yeah.
We're reviewing the new Halloween on the next show. But I want to reference the new Halloween right now,
what you just said. That's like in the new Halloween, when Jamie Lee Curtis is the doctor. Oh,
so you're the new loomist. Right. Oh, for fuck's sake. By the way, you cast an actor that doesn't have
the exact same voice as Donald Pleasant. I hear it. Anyway, all right. So the reason you're going
to love stars, born is that Lady Gaga's dad is played by a mystery. Yeah, you're a fucking star.
Talk about a star being born over here. Honey, bend over. Show me your star. It's his daughter.
It's his daughter. Dice wouldn't care. Dice wouldn't. Not the dice sign. He's got a funny running bit,
where like every time they they pan by and he's going, you know, Frank, he said,
not to have told me I was the best singer he ever heard. He doesn't like 10 times in the movie.
He's probably going to be nominated. Andrew Dice Clay. I'm not sure. He's a great actor. He's
great in Blue Jasmine. He is good in Blue Jasmine. Yeah. And that reminds me, why did you tell Woody Allen
to do what he did? I didn't think he'd go through with it. I was just spit -balling. So was he.
Folks. Just a terrible joke. Conjuring images of Woody Allen's spit -balling with his young
Asian daughter. You don't need it. You don't want it, but it's there now. Thank you for jumping in
on that because I felt like I took it too far. They're buried folks. It's fine. They have a great
relationship. Soon ye and woods. I see him at the dog park. They seem very happy.
Dice. I have a question. Is it uncouth to fuck your stepdaughter?
It doesn't sound too much to me, baby. Coat on Coat. Who gave you a fuck?
Let's get off of this immediately. I'm going to do one that I suggested we review on the pod.
You never saw it. I don't think we're ever going to do it.
By the way, it's watching a YouTube video. It's checked out. It's funny. I love this angry video game
here. Anyway, this is one I suggested we do on the pod, but you haven't seen it. I'm not going
to subject you to seeing it, so I'm going to review it now. The none.
The latest installment in the why the fuck is it not stopped yet? Conjuring universe.
When I heard an early supporter, Conjuring one, solid. Conjuring two, I thought slightly better
because it was an R -rated version of Conjuring one. After that, everything sucked. Everything.
What else did they do in the Conjuring? Two Annabels. The none? That's three.
That's true. That's more bad than good. Both Annabels were terrible. I thought the none is a fucking
travesty. It is an insult to horror fans in so many ways, the biggest way, other than it not being
scary and relying on stupid jolts and things. It's all it is is jump scares anymore. There's no
atmosphere anymore. Every scare relies on, well, that wasn't scary, but put the sound effect of a
piano and a door slamming behind it. That'll be scary enough. That's like every fucking scare and
that's all the none is, but what I was most offended by was I have never seen a movie steal from another
movie so shamelessly. Which film? So Tales from the Crypt Demon Knight, which were fans of. The none
lifted. Okay, ready for this? You remember Demon Knight, right? I do. Okay, ready for this? So the
none is a demon, first of all. Right. She needs not hold up. Hold up. Hold up. There's lots of movies
about this. Let me take you down the road. All right, take me down the road. None's a demon, first of all.
Sure. Who's got a face off with her? Female lead character. Okay, those are two similarities to Demon
Knight. Not enough to say, hey, this was copied already. Obviously. You're not even getting in the
courtroom with that case. Yeah, let's keep going. All right. How do you stop this demon? Well, you got
a seal off the portal from which she came getting a little closer to demon night. How do you seal off
the portal? We just happened to have the blood of Christ. Now we're in demon night. What do you
have the blood of Christ in and amulet that you wear around your neck? This is fucking demon night.
This is demon night. And how does she kill the none at the end of the movie with a demon night?
By secretly drinking the blood and spitting it in the demon's face. Exactly the end of demon night.
It looks like the levels. We didn't give them that big a swing. Sorry. We thought we'd stay in
it. Come on. It's a complete fucking rip off and it's a bad movie and it sucks. But how was
Moopy Goldberg as the none? She was great. The musical numbers were fantastic. I heard they were
dining. But yeah, it's a bad movie. It's terrible. I couldn't even, I couldn't be good conscious
say watch this just even because it'll be so bad you'll like it. It's just the right time. And it's
good conscience. What did I say? Good conscious. That's like when you're not unconscious.
How about I slap your fucking face? All right, go ahead. I mean, honestly, fine. You know,
couldn't we all just use a slap in the face once in a while? We could.
Joe texted me the other day. What did you text me? It didn't. He rattled me. I hate. I wrote to
fat. I didn't interact with somebody on Instagram. It really pissed me off because every time I post
something that somebody doesn't like, the only people I get attacked by are my so -called friends on
Instagram. This happened this way. Jared Lido. Yeah. You know, Jerry O 'Connell, you know what I mean?
The cast of Sliders, really. I was going on my so -called life thing. So my friend comes after me.
I got so mad and I'm like, it's always a friend. And I text Pat, I go, I hate everyone we know.
And he wrote back, sure, sure. The only time we spoke all day. You get me. Yeah, I get it. We're
the next picture I saw was called Quincy. It's a documentary about Quincy Jones.
Best known probably as being the father of Rashida Jones. And nothing else. So, no, I think she directed it.
It was good. You know, is anyone seeing that one?
You know, Quincy Jones is obviously a very fascinating man, but it's just kind of intercutting his
amazing accomplishments, which they're just checking off, like on a list. He, you know, he produced
We Are the World. He produced Thriller. And there's like three seconds of each major event. And then
a 10 -minute segment of him going like, man, I wish I could drink some vodka. And they're like,
you can't Quincy, you'll die. He's like, but vodka. And he's like, no, no, no. It's the whole movie.
Was he an alcoholic? It's an alcoholic. And he's not doing well, health -wise. So then he just
keeps asking for alcohol, really. And it's like 98. Let him drink. I couldn't, could not agree more.
But he said all kinds of major health problems and stuff. And there's like a long thing
of him doing Tai Chi with some girl. And you know, I just don't care about anything. And if you have a man
with literally one of the most fascinating careers in all of music, why are you devoting an hour
of the documentary to him doing calisthenics and asking for vodka? I can't get that at home. Folks,
that's time. That's like, did you ever see the Elaine Strich documentary? I did. Yeah, it's
the same thing. It's called like one old bitch or something? Yeah, an old bitch in tights. Yeah,
it's, yeah. And it's the same thing. She's like 102. Do it her 78th Broadway show. She's like, I can't
drink. I'm a mess. And it's like, clearly, you're doing fine. You're still on Broadway in 102. Yeah.
Just fucking get bombed. I've gifted shit at this point. Yeah, great. And she dies.
But not cause of drinking. No, sober she dies. You know, I have heard that Hollywood treasure,
Betty White, has two strong martinis every night. And she's like 102 years old.
Sound something, folks. It pickles your insides. Keeps them strong. I agree. Keeps them strong. I agree.
I watched an old, well, no, this is new. I watched a TV series, a new anthology series called
Likely Stories by Neil Gaiman on the Shutter Network. It's only four episodes, I believe. Maybe six.
Fantastic. It's a wonderful anthology. You can only get it on Shutter. It's a shutter exclusive.
It's based on Neil Gaiman's short stories. He sort of cameos weirdly into each episode. And they
venture more into odd territory than straight up horror. But there are some real like freaky elements in
it. And it's just a real, Neil Gaiman's the man. So it's like, you can't go wrong. You're getting
you're getting four or six episodes based on stories he wrote. And it's just a it's a fantastic anthology
that I never even would have fucking known was there. You know, Shutter. Yeah, it gets no, it got
tells from the hood too all over the place with, you know, advertisements and stuff. Neil Gaiman,
nothing. Where are you seeing tales from the hood too, advertisements? Buses, billboards? I moved
to a rural home. There's a lot of talk about the show. But no, it's a really, really great anthology
show. And I feel like nobody's going to see it because it's kind of buried in the TV section of the
Shutter app. No, it's people will watch it. But what a great title like on these stories. It's no,
you should. You'll like it. All right. And they're, dude, they're like 22 minutes each. Any scars?
No. Maybe that. Yeah. That's what you're talking about. The opera. Downgraded to the O. My Ribs
Raptors. It's like yelling out heckles. I used to be in the opera house. Hecklin over at O. My Ribs.
I love O. My Ribs. But you know, the fan of the opera would have a bigger venue. You understand.
I hope that he finds you as his inspiration after the show and he travels around stalking you. By
not why. Yes, no, no, no, it seems to make sense. It's laughter. Oh, my ribs. I know, but oh,
my ribs. And oh, these ribs. Why not? It's two on the nose. All right. No, no stars. Some renowned
actors from England, but it's all, it's all shot over there and done over there. And it's very well
done. And I really highly recommend it to everybody. All right. Great. Yeah. What else you got? I
saw the kindergarten teacher with mags, Jill and Hall, sister of Jake. It's good. It was on Netflix.
I don't want to see in that picture. Sorry, Maggie. Better scoop up another Batman. People ain't
watching. You're in these shit. It was very good. It was, I'll never watch it again. It was
miserable. It's on Netflix, which has now become like, they release more independent movies than
the cinema. It's, it's absurd. But that's kind of cool. I mean, I've seen all kinds of great
little movies that like I wouldn't have left my house to go see. I would have waited and it was
cool. The kindergarten teacher is about Maggie Jill and Hall. There's something off about her from
the jump. She's like obsessed with this little kid who's really good at poetry. Anytime there's a
movie about someone who's really good at poetry, the poem sucks. So you don't ever believe the movie.
So they're like, where do you hear this poem and they keep building it up and then you hear it? And it's
like, the sun shines on my house. My house is sunny. And then everybody in the audience is like,
he says, I'm a dais again. I'm a dais didn't write poetry. No, I know. But they they reference
on the dais a lot. Wow, you sound like a fucking moron when you say it wrong. You sound like an idiot
when you say it wrong. If you look aside the poems being shitty, she's like obsessed with him and she's
like, this kid's going to be a great artist. But he doesn't have the best home life. So she takes it upon
herself to like start becoming really obsessed with nurturing him as a poet and you realize it's because
she failed as a poet herself. And then she starts using the kid's poems to fuck her poetry teacher
even though she's married with kids. And then at a certain point, it gets way darker than that.
And she is like stealing the kid. And then you're like, does she want to fuck the kid? Does she want
to kill the kid? It gets very weird. And I recommend it, although you won't like it. It's not fun at all,
but she's like, she's a really good actress. She's a very underrated actress. I don't think she's
underrated at all. She's overrated. I'm sick of her. She's very celebrated. She's a wonderful actor,
actor, brave actor. I don't know why you're able to say actress and define gender with it. I don't see
it because I like when I like when she plays anybody that's a little off. She's super off.
You know, super off. Yeah, I didn't like her in the Batman movies because she played too clean
cut. Yeah, I didn't care. Home shut the bed really. Why did home step out? She didn't want to do it.
Because Tom Cruise had implanted chips in her head. I didn't even understand. I don't get a lot
about Scientology, but the tortilla chips in the brain I've always just been baffled by.
Gives a new, yeah, forget it. I realized halfway through it. It did make sense. I'm backing out of it.
Pat, I'm going to bring us to a mutual close here with a final third thing from both of us
that we can discuss. Bringing us both to a mutual close sounded like we're going to have a
circle jerk. No, no, no, no, no. I'm going to, I'm going to let us close on the same third thing.
Oh, okay. She's doing a third one. I've done three. You've done three? Son of a bitch.
I was never good at math. Go sing. Well, no, fuck them. I'm not going to do. Yeah, fuck it. I'll do it.
The scariest thing I've seen all week, and that was premiere of The Conor.
You're you're asking me to talk about an industry I work in, which is tricky, but I saw it and I'll
I'll go with you to a certain point. We got a goddamn friend in the show. In and on. Yes. Sarah
and the scene. Sarah G, as I stated once on this podcast, when I got the boot from your sitcom,
thanks for looking out. But when I got the boot from Pat show, Sarah G was the first one to text me
and say this sucks. Fuck this. You're great. I love you. Yeah. She's she's wonderful. Sarah Gilbert,
she's not in witness protection. I call her Sarah G. We're on that kind of level. Let's pick up that name,
Joe. But she's wonderful. She's the best. She's great on the show. Yeah. I loved her on the original
Rosanne incarnation or reincarnation rather, but this show is I don't know if any of you haven't seen
it. Let me try to explain it. You know, when sitcoms would do not a very special episode, not that,
they would do like the dark episode, like the family ties where all the lights are out and they
keep shining spotlights and corners. You're like, what the fuck man? And you're having nightmares about
family ties all of a sudden. Was there one with Alan's? Be keeping on a stool in the dark,
talking about drunk driving? Yeah, yeah, yeah. Picture that except the whole show is those episodes.
The whole show is going to be, I mean, Jesus Christ, this episode ends with Dan tossing and turning
in bed because he can't get used to sleeping without Rosanne there. Now a woman that they've thrown
into the streets and that's the weird part about the show. That's the really weird part about the show.
Everybody's like, I love turn. It's like night and just fired with good cause, but why are you still doing
this? Everybody in the show is crying about Rosanne. Yeah, but they're crying about the fictional
Rosanne, right? Who's based on the real Rosanne? Who they, oh, chest eyes. Yeah. I don't know,
man. I just, it feels like happy days after Ron Howard left. It's just not right. My issue with it
was a drama. It was, it was devoid of even attempts at jokes and it was so much comedy is now.
They're relapsed. The balance is so shifted that you're surprised to hear a joke in comedy nowadays,
and I, I didn't really get it. They got Mary Steenberger showing up and being like, I didn't sell her
the pills that killed her. She was a pill addict screaming and good man's face and I'm like, what's
going on? I just come to the corners to laugh. I can't, I can't. I just, I need Rosanne back on
and I think they made a mistake by I understand why they fired her, get all that stuff. Why did you write
that tweet for her? Let's get it out now. You don't have to answer that. No, but I look, I get why they
fired her. But leave it open ended. Why do they have to finalize every, leave it like she's off
in an asylum for a while? Because maybe you smooth things over eventually with Rosanne and she comes
back to the show and it's the fucking show again. Yeah. This would be like if you did the Cosby show
without Cosby and it's, well I know, not a great example. But that was the best one I could think of.
Let's, let's dig a little deeper, for example. But me and look, it's like the Kevin Spacey hour without
Kevin Spacey. You don't get the great songs, the great jokes. Would you, would you watch it,
guys, or so say movie without Kevin Spacey? No, I wouldn't. Yeah, that's my point. You mean like
young sozi or something? Old sozi. For somebody good, I'd do it. Sozi makes it out of the end.
Yeah. All right. My point is it's, it's, it's the titular character, if you will. Yeah. And fine,
if you don't want it to be on the show, fine. But then you can't do the show. It doesn't make any
goddamn sense anymore. Yeah. You know what I mean? You don't have to say it by the bell without
Mario Lopez or Zach or Zach. That's a good point. I love Laurie Metcalf. I don't need to see her
wide eyed having a nervous breakdown about plates in the kitchen for 15 fucking minutes of the episode.
I'm sorry. It's just not, it's not entertaining to me. It's, it's depressing. I hear you. I don't,
I don't think it'll be around too long. I think it just felt kind of weird. But hopefully they shake
it off and move on to comedy. I'll keep watching. Also is John Goodman dying? Every line.
He's like, hey, sport heavy. Well, he goes a bunch of ways. Yeah, you lose weight and you sound
worse. Yeah. I watched. When he used to narrate diners,
drive -ins and dives, that what it's called? That was Guy Fieri. No, no, no. But he narrated one of
those shows and it was like, he would be drooling describing the food. You could hear it. And he
like, you could hear the salivating. He putter drill. It was just like, it was a wet sound.
And again, I'm not lashing out at ribs. I want to say to the orders of home my ribs. I just use it
as an example. It's disgusting. I watched on the today show this way. I watched it later. I wasn't
watching today show, but they interviewed for 30 minutes Goodman Bridges and Buscemi about the 20 -year
anniversary of Lebowski. Oh, that's cool. It was awesome. I recommend looking up to 30 -minute
interview with some idiot who keeps pointing at each of them when he asks them a question. So he's like,
did you like the Cohen Brothers? They're not on trial here. They're sitting in a booth at a
restaurant. I hate the interviewer, but everybody else is good. The sad thing about it, though, is
they're like, what's your favorite line? And every time, every question, all three of them are like,
they can't remember anything. So good, they're like, did you ever work with the Cohen Brothers before?
Goodman's like, yeah, before Lebowski, I had done, what's that movie called? And then they're like
raising Arizona. Raising Arizona, yes. It's like, that's dark. He's in all of them. He's in all
there, but he's part and think and all, yeah. I'll go brother or out there, etc. Yeah.
All right, well, I mean, we'll see where the Conner's goes. I wish them well. I'm not wishing,
I don't wish. Well, I wish, you know, again, Sarah G, dear friend.
I wish. Johnny G, her, her boyfriend, Johnny G is going to be on it. Yes.
Golecks, Juliet Lewis, recently. Don't give a shit about it.
I heard an HBO's camping for some reason. Oh, God. Me when I talk, well, we've already
shit on the show. It's tough, man. You get into this business. You got friends that just do these
pieces of shit and you can't talk about it publicly. Except we do, which is why I'm not well -liked.
Yeah. Pat, can we do some? It was Joe, Joe dated Tervolta for a while. When Battlefield
came out, I remember that being particularly rough. It was a tough one. He was, that hair wasn't
for the movie. So like he bring, he bring Tervolta to a party and he'd have the battlefield earth
dreads. Yeah. And it was like, boy, you know, we tell Joe that this relationship isn't going to
work out. Yeah. That was a tough time for me. Let alone him being married.
So I met her through Kelly Preston, who I was having in a fairy. Yeah, sure. Yeah.
Joe, why don't you take us over to whatever the hell you're?
Column is called. Column segment. No respect for me. Let's do a little Joe scary stuff.
I'm going to, we're doing something different tonight. We're not going to discuss any scary stuff.
We're just going to give scary stuff away to audience members. We each have five things to give away.
We never discussed how we were going to decide who gets them. Yeah.
I mean, like, cannon, fire, like a t -shirt cannon? I mean, let's just announce what we have
and then whoever gets the most excited gets it. Sure. Within reason.
I mean, that's fine, right? No. No good. I mean, I wouldn't jump up to get a prize.
I had no interest in. So you're on your honor system.
These are from our private collection. We didn't buy these today.
This is a graphic novel called Neo -Nomicon written by Alan Moore.
I read it once. Yeah. It's of some of the H .P. love craft, whatever, because everybody thinks
the squid monster is scary. And I read it once. And it's pretty good.
So good. He's giving it away.
Till the main character sucks the squid monster's tick toward the end.
Really? Yeah, that happens. And I thought, you know, Alan, you've been living in that cabin
with those two witch wives years for too long. But it is a good book. Any takers on Neo -Nomicon?
Wow. Again, this was mine. I did own it. Part of my private collection in the deal, I don't think.
All right. There you go. There you go. Excellent. What's your name, sir?
What's your name? Nick, thank you. Enjoy it.
I am offering you two copies of Poltergeist, because I have it on Blu -ray and don't need the DVDs.
Two copies. You can take one. You can take them both.
And it's just one is shittier DVDs. This is actually covered in dust.
And you know how the sticker won't come off sometimes of DVDs. It's got that sticker residue.
So it might make it more valuable, I don't know. But this is the better addition.
This and can be calls it marvelously spooky if that sweetens the DVD.
Oh, sure. There you go. Emily, everybody.
Well, we'll give her her due later. Let's keep the focus here.
But thank you. I've got a stack of prints. These are cool. Yeah, these are great.
These literally the only reason I'm giving these away is because I moved into a new apartment and I
didn't have room to hang these up. But I would have. And I thought, you know, why keep them in a closet
until you've decided you'll never get a bigger place than this. Your ambition ends here.
I don't think you understand when I keep telling you how to cutting myself off from the world.
Okay, but I didn't have room for these and I thought they were really cool and some higher fans should
get them here as a print of Edgar Allen Poe's murders in the Rue Morg. Very nice. You can hang
this up or sleep next to it, whatever you want to do with it. Use it as a placement. I don't give a
shit. It's once it's yours. It's yours. Just take it. Who wants it? There we go.
This is this is a dark segment. People have flown from across the country and they're like,
still no. What do you got? I think I'm about to change this up a little bit with something
truly scary. A last man standing blank. No. They're my lead in that. I thought you were.
I thought you were kidding when you said you found that. No, you had that. Are you a fan of
Allen who I heard as a massive asshole? Yeah, he's supposed to be terrible. Yeah, I bet it does.
They're not swapping any jokes out. I'll tell you that one. Look, I love the Fox Network. Yeah,
this is a this is a great political move on your part. Shitting on your lead in show. That's true.
I just watched it and I'm like, why do we get notes from people? If they're putting this on,
I'll drop it. I would. All right. Here's another print. It's no home improvement, folks.
That this is of the old, dark house of horror classic. Any takers? Yeah, all right. These are going quick.
Enjoy it, sir. I'm offering a four disc collectors edition of the most boring movie ever made,
Blade Runner. I know a lot of you love it. Reveal yourself. All right, good.
Oh, my God. Now, will you watch all four shitty versions of that terrible movie?
The two unicorn version, the note. How many there's there's I think more than four on that thing?
It's like Ridley Scots. They have Tony Scott come in and direct one.
Adam Scott directs the version. Does his added of it, which I've heard is actually better than
the others. Scott Beo does a cut. He directed a top of the unicorn, which they have footage of on the
documentary. Not the horror. This, this is a movie I'm unfamiliar with, but it was just such a cool
poster that I bought it. This is a film called The Phantom Empire. And it's just, I'm going to say
the Phantom broadcast. Well, it says both. Oh, Phantom, chapter number four of The Phantom broadcast.
So I guess this was some sort of weird serial science fiction thing from back in the day,
but it's just so fucking cool, the electricity going through the writing and you know, these guys,
whatever they're doing. You know, cheer at typical. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know.
We did bring alcohol, everybody. I don't know what it is. Does anybody want this?
Yeah. Woman yelled, woo. This is the last one. And the best one. I have a movie frequently
discussed on the show as perhaps the scariest non -horror scene, certainly in all of, of cinema,
Mulholland Drive on digital video disc, digital versatile disc. Is it digital versatile or digital
video disc? Then you don't get it. Is it, is anyone not versatile? First of all, thank you.
All right, we're good. We have, I have one more because I brought five for each show.
Okay, great. By the way, it's in in the meba bag. Does anyone go to a meba on your trip?
Pretty cool, right? How many people traveled in for this that don't live in California?
Wow. Thank you very much. How many people don't, how many people live in California, but aren't?
In LA. Okay. Al Hombra.
Surid House. Valley Village.
All right, I'm done. This is the best one that I have, and it's from the most famous of all
horror movies. It's a classic. It was remade by John Carpenter. Not a good remake, but this is the
original children of the damned, very cool poster. Yeah, wear the eyes that paralyze.
Okay.
Deserve. Hang it right next to your bed, so every time you wake up, that's staring at you.
So Pat, our movie today, did you all do your homework and watch Tales of Halloween?
Yeah.
Right. Raise your hand if you liked it. Oh my god.
So right, like why is it this acclaimed movie? It's not.
Where is it acclaimed? There was a lot of buzz about it at the Oscars last year, but I know people
love that and trick our treat, and I've seen them both. I think they're fine. Trick or treat is bet much
better. Okay. Not great, but trick or treat solid. You just don't
kind of just don't give a fuck about anybody in it. This got really good reviews. Tales of Halloween.
And Brian Cox, once again playing, is that guy play anything except a creep that potentially
touches kids on his block? Jesus Christ. It's a session. There's no potential kid touching. He's an
asshole. He's always a prick. Yeah. Yeah. What is that accent he's got? It's British, right? No.
That's why I asked. Well, what is it? Well, I think it's well. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. Anyway.
He's an adaptation. He plays Robert McKee, the script. If you want to write a script,
that sounds like Jack Palin's. You are my number one guy and die. It's from Batman.
The original. All right. So tell me. Not the original. I guess that would be Adam West.
No, that's not the original. The original is the 1940s. 1940s serials.
Yeah. I own them. All right. They ever make a choice. chose to keep those for some reason.
Did they make it into a movie? No, they were serial. So the original would probably be the first Batman
feature -length movie was the Adam West film, which came after the TV show, which came after the 1940s
serials. That's right. That's the first film. If you watch any documentary about the history of
Batman and cinema, they'll start with the serials because the serials played in theaters. Now,
by serials, you mean like, oh, don't, don't, don't. Stop it. Count -chalk your life. Stop it. That's
what we fought in those early serials. He fought Count -chalk your life. He fought the Lucky Charms
Leprechaun. He fought in my favor. He fought Captain Crunch. This is what it takes to write for
television, everybody. There you go. That's why I get the big blankets. Enjoy that, sir.
I don't like just straight alcohol. I don't do that anymore. You're doing it now.
All right. She's about to get messy. I'm feeling, I'm feeling great. That first, it burned. That first
movie, so you guys know, The Towns of Halloween. It's a anthology film. Every story centers around
Halloween. We're going to go through each story here tonight. I wrote the list down because there's
none of them are memorable. No, I mean, I'm sorry. I was like, okay, sweet tooth. And I was thinking
about and I was like, okay, look, some of them are cooler than others. I don't think you can get much
going in 10 minutes. That's my issue with it. There was some I'd like to see a little longer version
of, I guess. That's my first beat for the movie. The 10 stories. Yeah. The beginning of this thing,
they keep, in the credits, they announce all the stories that you're going to see and they keep
going. It's like some night of too many stars. Credit opening. How are they doing all this? The credits
went on forever. That's true. And it's also subjected to this thing that is done now in anthology,
which I don't understand where or why this started, but every movie is directed and written by a different
person or every segment, which leads to a complete lack of continuity through the whole thing. You've
got one that's zany. You've got one that's terribly dark. You've got one that's sort of scary. You've
got one that's goofy. It doesn't, it doesn't add for some glue. And then also they have,
I have to stop you. It doesn't add for some glue. It doesn't make for glue to glue everything together.
I meant, it doesn't make for good connective tissue. All right, that works. All right.
And they did the thing that is being done, they might have done it first, but they're doing that,
they did the thing and it that's being done now in every anthology film. I feel like that I see
which is there is a radio personality. Adrian Barbos. Yeah. And in the Christmas one, it's it's
Shatner. Yeah. In Southland. It's it's a different radio person out, whatever. But I feel like that's
kind of becoming hard for the course. Yeah. I mean, for me, even though they were all done by a different
director, they all looked the same and they all looked to me like software porn without the pornographer.
They were live in the same way. They were very like everything just looked boring and
drab to me and like it was shot on an iPhone or something. But we can go through them one by one.
Sweet tooth is the one where this kid eats all the Halloween candy. And this is the best one. It was
too, usually I liked it. Yeah. But you're in trouble. If somebody told you at the top of the movie,
this is the best one you're going to see. I mean, it's not great. No. My biggest gripe is sweet tooth
is about a demon who is a child that that died because he ate the candy out of his own stomach
because he couldn't get enough candy. Right. Kind of a weird thing. It's not my cat eats. Yeah.
Just no, no bottom, no end. Just like you'll eat this massive bowl and then be like,
Yeah. Yeah. It's just no, there's no satisfying. That's how my dog is. It's, it's, it's animals. That's
what animals. And then I'll be like, blah. Yeah. Right back like rattling that bowl. Yeah.
Like you're sitting in a pile of cat pew. Maybe think about what you've done before demanding
fourths. You realize it's not a person, right? Yes. It's a cat. I do. It's got to bring the
size of a peanut. I know. But it's an idiot fucking cat. I don't know what you expect out of this thing.
The stomach drags on the steps when it's going on stairs. Push the bowl away. Yeah.
So sweet tooth about, about a kid who turns into a demon because he dies for meeting the candy
out of his own stomach as it, you know, when he's nine or 10. Yet when the demon of the kid comes back,
it's a 78 year old man, which I don't understand. Sure. And that pisses me off. That's just a lack
of attention to detail. I don't know if it's lack of attention. That's a choice they made. It'd be
scarier if it was a 10 year old demon kid. I don't think they said, though, hey, do you think
this 74 guy looks like this kid and the director went, yeah, yeah, yeah. I think that's him.
It's exactly what they did. That would be a lack of attention to detail. That's exactly what they did.
All right. Oh, that looks scary. Yeah, but he looks 78. Make it look like a demon kid. Sure.
Well, then they had a 78 year old demon, a different one. In the next one, the night Billy raised
hell, the Barry Bostwick of Spin City fame as Satan. That was the guy from Spin City. That's correct.
The guy that played Cameron and Ferris Bueller, no, that's Alan Ruck. Okay. Barry Bostwick was the
mayor. That was the mayor from Spin City. He didn't look like him. Yeah. No, he doesn't. And Barry
Bostwick auditioned for the coolest audition three times for the cool kids and I hope I don't even need
to say, oh, he doesn't listen to this podcast. But it looked as though he looked at 10 a .m. audition
and he came in just like, look like he had held a jug of Scotch up and just be like, what are you doing?
What are you doing tonight? What are you doing on this thing? This isn't the gossip co -op hot pit.
Cindy, a goddamn Hollywood fucking minute pod. He probably wasn't drunk, but
so you were in a Barry Bostwick. Barry Bostwick played Cameron in Ferris Bueller.
I honestly don't kidding. I'm joking. I'm joking. Folks, I look into his eyes and I'm not sure
he was joking. Remember the early days of the podcast? We talked about you working on two
broke girls. If I'd pretend like I didn't understand it, it wasn't an extension of the Thor movies.
Yes, that was a funny bet. Yeah, I liked it. Yeah, it was a good bet.
I watched, I blocked out so much of that show. And I, some nights, of what? Spin City,
a two broke girl. Okay. And I was, I mean, it was a terrible time of my life. And the other night,
I was going to bed and the end of one was on. And here was the last joke. This episode had my name
on it, but this was not my joke. I assure you. It's Kat and Beth and they're sitting there. And then
the whole episode was about the Kronut craze, and they were trying to make something that was both
sweet and salty, because they made cupcakes and shit. Thanks, Jim. And she goes, it's just like us.
It's sweet and salty. She goes, I'm the sweet. And then Kat goes, and I've been assaulted. And then
you've boasted to me that you were most proud of that joke. Well, that's the problem when the guy
who ran it, he'd rewrite your script and add jokes. And you'd be like, this is the most racist thing I've
ever seen in my life. And you have to go around to the cast and be like, I'm sorry. But that people
don't know that. I think you write every word with your names on the script. Now you've burned a bridge
with him, too. That bridge is long gone, long gone. The night break is the next one. Yes, I was going
to say the night billy race hell was pretty good. It was fun. It was kind of like problem child sort
of what you know I love. Trick, trick was what the fuck was trick about? Trick was that was the one
where those kids are like punishing them because those those pothads were also torturing kids in the
pool house. That's not weak and wicked. Maybe it is. What is trick? Anyone know? Third story. I think
that was it. Oh, was it? That one made no goddamn sense. It's like so these people are pothads.
I tell you. I've known a lot of pothads. I dabble in it myself, folks. You can't be a pothad and also
kill kids in the shed. It's one or the other. Who had that joke about? Remember David Crosby
from Crosby Stills and Nash? Yeah, I remember. Now some kind of got a joke about him in the 80s.
He was like, you know, David, you can't be fat and a co -cat. That's true. The only thing I ever
liked that Rob Thomas of Matchbox 20 said was he was like, I was the only guy who got fatter on co -cane.
Yeah. Because remember there was those years of Matchbox 20 where you were like, oh, we're like
Matchbox 220. Folks. Folks. Very good.
I want to push you around. Well, I will. Well, I will try to push because he's so fat.
That's what I was going to say. I wanted to help out, but you took the whole joke for yourself.
Rob Thomas. We all love Matchbox 20. But it was weekend wicked. Which one was that?
Those two blend together from me. Anyone know what weekend wicked? It wasn't a standout,
clearly. There was grim, grinning ghost where it was a whole thing about a girl being like,
am I going to see a ghost? She doesn't for nine minutes and then at the 930 mark, there's a ghost.
Cool. And that was the one with the lady from Insidious. Yes. Lin Shea.
Lin Shea. Yeah. How the fuck did they get her into this thing? Well, I know her as a lady from
Kingpin. How'd they get her? Did she feel no offers? I mean, Insidious is not an entrepreneur.
Insidious. I love Lin Shea. Sensitive, proud to know. Insidious is a big franchise. I wouldn't
think she needed to do some short film. All right. Fair enough. I mean, I don't know.
Maybe it was her kid that made it or some shit. Well, Lin Shea is the sister of the former head of
New Line Cinema. Yes. She plays the teacher in the original Nightmare on Elm Street,
by the kids remember. The next one is Ding Dong. Hold on. I was going to say, real quick,
the grinning ghost. Terrible. Terrible. Terrible. Terrible story. Piece of shit. Still better than
Insidious 3 and 4. I would say. Honestly, I'm being honest. I agree. You go ahead.
Ding Dong. I thought was the most interesting because I love Lucky McKee. I know I've
recommended it on the podcast, but he made an amazing movie called May. It's Ana Ferris in a
supporting role, but it's a horror with touches of comedy. Like a lot of breeders on the soundtrack.
Well, I love, I recommend that. It's a really cool horror comedy. But Ding Dong, I want the
witch that wants the baby. That's correct. That one sucked. I like that was good. No, Joe. I
don't think any of these were good. I like that it took a swing and it felt different than the other.
It had a different visual style, which I'm sure. I thought they had her husband,
Hansel or whatever. That was an embarrassing performance. That was just an embarrassing fucking
performance. This fucking thing made no sense. No. It made no sense. Yeah. It looked like the Swiss
myths. It's dressed up as like the hot chocolate. Oh my God. And then she was the witch. I
thought she was good. She's in a movie that he made called the woods, the woods. I think I'll,
yeah, the one called the woods is, yeah. I thought she was great. And as a newly single man
watching this for the podcast, I immediately, I immediately looked her up to see like if I could
have some sort of criss -gast Jamie Lee Curtis meet through the agents kind of like it has her
career and life gotten bad enough. Much like Rebecca DeMorne, who you thought you stood a chance
she's married anyway. Yes. The lady from the witch. That's what I think that's what was keeping you
guys apart. You know, I think, you know, she probably gets just as scared lonely in this big crazy
town as I did. That's true. That's true. This means war was the worst of the lot. I mean,
I told Joe I liked it better the first time when it was called Deck the Holes. Folks. I mean,
it's people competing over their Halloween displays in their front yard. There's really no
horror to it. And it wasn't funny. This is what I mean about tonally. This is what fucking happens
when you let eight different guys and gals direct and write these fucking things. There's no
goddamn connective tissue. You said you didn't see gender. See what? You said you didn't see gender
earlier, but now you're dividing people into guys and gals. But when I said gals, I meant guys when
I said guys I meant gals, because that's how I'm progressive I am. He's good. He's good.
You're good. All right. So this means war. Now here's what's kind of interesting and it didn't work out.
I tried to get Dana Gould down here tonight as our first ever live guest, along with Jennifer
Runyon from Ghostbusters. Jennifer was very kind and she was doing a signing and some convention
down to the airport. She's like, I can't make it and she was very bummed that she couldn't be here.
But she was really great. Never heard back from Dana. But I'm glad we didn't because I was like,
how are we going to have Dana on and then shit on? Yeah. Well, if it was there, I guarantee you would have
been like, it was great, Dan. Well, clearly the standout of the bunge. Did you just slip
into a little Dana Carvee, George H. Dobby. And it was great, Dan. I think I heard the Dana.
Real good. Loved it. Now, remember when Wayne's World Two has some, I just really watched
the other day. Well, I love both of them, of course. But Kim Basin goes, she goes, take me
off. And he goes, take you where? I'm a little on gas and you need a jacket.
Fine. Pretty funny. I love the Wayne's World movies. My favorite. Yeah, they're great. My favorite
Dana Carvee thing though is the Regis filmin. Sure. Impression. It's sure this thing. Yeah. When she
goes, he goes, Kathy just had a baby. What did you name it? She goes Cody. And he goes, Cody,
my Regis, did I tell the Regis story ever on the podcast? I like that I can ask now. So I'm
not repeating myself. I worked at Blockbuster. Again, not bragging. I got out. When I got out,
there was a bird, like a big pigeon type bird eating human vomit. And I was like, Jesus, cry.
And then I decided that day I need to get out of Missouri. And I went in and opened the store. I was
a manager. Again, I'm not trying to break. And I turned on the TV. You opened the store at 9 a .m.
to open at 10. And they had Regis and Kathy Lee at the time on. I'm watching it. I'm kind of
like putting tapes on the shelf and hearing it in the background. And then Matthew McConaughey came out.
And Regis goes, he decided he was just, oh, I thought you meant into, I tuned out for a second. I
thought you meant he came into Blockbuster. No, no, no, I was like, holy shit. So McConaughey comes out.
And then Regis is sitting and looking at him like this. And McConaughey is kind of weirded out.
And he goes, take a look at hey, hey, McConaughey. Would you take a look at hey, hey, McConaughey?
This man is beautiful. Take a look at hey, hey, McConaughey. He does it 50 times. And you see
McConaughey getting very agitated. And he's a cool guy. But he was like, I want to talk about the movie.
So then Regis keeps shooting at him. And it got very tense. And then I was like sitting on the floor
watching this. And it built to a point where they clearly didn't like each other. And McConaughey is
talking about the movie called The Wedding Planner with Jennifer Lopez. So when we thought he was
done, that's when we were like, this McConaughey guy is bidding back. Yeah. But Regis is like, tell us
about The Wedding Planner. What's it about? And he goes, well, you know, when the movie starts, I'm about
to marry this woman that's just completely wrong for me. And Regis interrupts him and goes,
not if The Wedding Planner's got something to say about it. Just shitting on the movie. And I
Anyway, we need to we need to get through this. For the 31st is the most embarrassing with the
alien. What the fuck was that? Oh my god. Just bad special effects, bad comedy. Too many things going on.
It had Jason kind of from Friday the 13th, fighting an alien who says, Twick or Tweet.
It was it was it was dark. I almost didn't get through the movie at that point. Yeah. That point was like
this when the second finger gets into your asshole. And I was like, you know, I said I wanted to try
this, but it's it's going too far. Yeah. Sure. At least trim the nails. Yeah. Toughs.
Yeah.
Ransom of Rusty Rex. I don't know. Ransom of Rusty Rex, they steal like a freak kid.
Is that appropriate? Freak kid. Yeah. He's like a monster kid. He was a monster. That one is
actually not that bad. And I am a big fan of Sam Whitworth. John Landis played the dad, which was
on a cool terrible performance. And the man killed a Vietnamese family in 1983. But it was good
to see him working again. I've told this I read a book about it. I'm very well versed. He did kill a
family. I've told his relentless pursuit of success. And Spielberg backed him up if this books to be
believed. But you just keep seeing war horse. Don't you? I told the thriller story on the podcast
before, right? When I was watching the making of thriller with my mom or did I not? Okay, great.
I was watching the making of thriller with my mom. I'm like six. Yeah. I love Michael Jackson
obsessed with this thing. Sure. Watch the making of it. There's a part where they're interviewing
John Landis who directed thriller. And he goes, I got a call to do it. But my family and I were up in
Canada for some reason. I can't remember why. My mom goes, because you murdered somebody
inside of a bitch. I know. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But ransom a restaurant. Little fun movie,
fact trivia, whatever you want to call it. Sam Whitworth who was also in the mist plays the
Love the Mist. The Army kid in the mist. He does all the voices. That was the story of the founder
of Sierra Mist. Correct? Yes. Sort of like that. Michael Keaton played in my believe. Yeah. Yeah.
What a bastard. And he was like, I want Mountain Dew, but I want it to be fizzier.
That was the trail around me. And America agreed. He does a lot of the voices for the Star Wars
animated stuff. He did the voice of Darth Maul and Solo actually. There's a lot of stars. So
Sam Whitworth is okay in my book. All right. Last one was from the guy who did the descent. Neil Marshall.
I was offended by this one. This one was so eating people stupid. I was like, what is happening
right now? I think I liked it more because I love the descent. I know that guy is a good director.
But and I thought the pumpkin running around eating people. There was something kind of funny and stupid
about it. It felt like critters or ghoulies or something. But yeah, none of these were good for sure.
So two hogs down. Two hogs. Way down. Two hogs.
Guys, we've got about 10 minutes left here before we have to stop to do the next show.
How many are coming to the next show? Oh boy, it's way more than I thought it was going to be.
We would have to think of other shit. I'm also good off the cuff.
Joe, everything Joe said the night he wrote earlier. Every single word he said was written earlier
and memorized. That's dark. It is true. That's not true. Right. When you said that just now,
I saw it backstage. That's not true. And you wrote two times next to it. I wrote it three days ago.
No, we wanted to do a Q and A. If anybody wants to do a live Q and A, if you don't want to,
don't worry about it. I'm going to call on the first. Let's get a hand in the air.
Again, if you don't want to, don't worry. We're not so arrogant that we're like, here in the white
shirt. Yeah. Yeah. So regarding your activities today, why would you get a frozen piece of
delivers? Well, I got actually a question. Honestly, great way to kick it off.
Well, I'm ashamed that I missed that question. I can explain. Do you live here in LA?
So you're aware that nothing good exists here, including pizza that's hot.
I had a fresh brother the other day that was great. You're a fucking trash pig.
Shut the fuck up. Fresh brothers, fucking disgusting.
They had it work. I had a piece. It was pretty good. I got groceries delivered.
And one of the things I was like, oh, I'll try this $10 frozen pizza. That's pretty much the top
of the heap when it comes to frozen pizza prices. And I was wrong. But I got other shit delivered,
too. I got some chicken broth and orange juice.
Joe and Joe and I had a romantic Italian dinner last night. Joe was telling the waitress about how he
prepares meals with chicken broth. They went on for like 20 minutes.
She liked it. I don't know. Next cue. Yes, sir.
I haven't. I have. I've done the haunted hay riding River Park, which is sort of ages six to eight.
Kind of. But it's fun. I took my mom. I took my mom to Halloween hard nights when she was
visiting. My mom has some mobility issues. So if we've got to do a lot of moving, she's got to get a
wheelchair. She can't walk for long periods of time. So we went with her and my dad and my friend
Scott and we wheeled her through the haunted houses. Do they take it easier on a lady? No, not at all.
Just slashing in her face, screaming the entire time. But she loved it. But my mom has always been
super scared of the exorcist because she's Catholic. And she's always like, you know, if you watch that
kind of stuff, it opens your mind up to the bean posit like, you know, all that stuff. And the first one
we went to was the exorcist house. And like, she fucking loved it. It was cool. It was fun. Have you been
doing it? It's great, right? That's pretty cool. Do people like, do you have to know anything about
the movie to enjoy the thing? All right. We were laughing. My friend, Pinkstone, who I mentioned
frequently on the podcast, we were laughing because he was, he's a big Rick and Morty fan. He was talking
about they did it at Nightmare on Elm Street Rev episode where Freddy's chasing them and he keeps
saying, bitch. And they in the Rick and Morty like this guy really says, bitch, a lot, you know.
And Jim called me and he's like, I never realized it. He says it so much. And I was like, yeah, you're
right. And then I called him because the year I went to Halloween, Halloween, or whatever the fun.
Dana Freddy versus Jason Mays. And the first thing you hear when you walk it is welcome to my Nightmare
bitch. He doesn't do it beyond the child murdering, beyond the tormenting people in their nightmares.
I always hated the misogyny. I thought that was his worst quality. Yes. Get ready for him to be on the gold
bergs. Anyway, anybody else? Do I? No. Yeah, it's funny. When you go on a man's radio show that
he's had for eight years and call him a content front of his entire audience, you're not invited back.
We haven't spoken, but here's the best part. So during the argument we had, if anybody heard it,
we started arguing about Atlanta and he was being really condescending and he goes, I got to
leave all the time like that, which became a drop on the Jim and Sam show and on the bonfire with Jay
and Dan Soder. Yeah. I, right after I left there, I went to China and Japan and do shows that I went to
Atlanta to record my new record, which I'm giving exclusively to serious XM. And they were like, what
do you think? And I thought serious was going to be like, come on, dude, like, please don't, just don't.
And they were like, that's fucking hilarious. Right?
Anyone else? Yes sir? Do you guys have a pattern of how we navigate through what we
want to go at the same section first? We always dovetail immediately. And it's never even
discussed. We just go to different sections. I think the drive there is enough time together for us
and then a little spacing out. Joe usually goes to rap first. I go to rock and then we make a trade.
Sometimes we'll hit the DVD upstairs together. That's sort of the dessert. Joe always goes there.
I mean, to me, they're, in a world where Amazon exists and I know Amazon has a lot of problems,
their prices are way too high. They're buying back prices are also way too low. I've given them new
albums. They're like 60 cents. Vince Avril says it's all who you get. And I agree with it. It is.
One time I went in there with so much shit and I got like $28 or something. And I was like, come on.
Another time I went in with three things. The lady's like, well, 63 bucks or whatever.
And I was like, what the fuck is going on in this place? Well, you had a hotel room key in your bag
that you slept to her. I remember. Yeah. Yeah. And I winked. Yeah.
Here's the good part about me, but though, even though you're right about the prices and the buyback
rates, you'll find shit in there that's like out of print. That is so fucking cheap.
Oh, yeah. I mean, I found the vinyl here. The prices are second to none. I love that place.
Where do you start, sir? 45. Nice. Okay. Nice. I just want to hear you talk again.
You have a commanding voice. I like it. Congrats. I love my voice sucks.
I love upstairs and to me, but that is far in a way. I can't bring myself to purchase any DVD or
Blu -ray in there. It's so over. Right. Market value. Yeah. Like, you know, season one of suits.
And it's like $38. Look, I wouldn't take suits free, but where you get off of this $38.
And VHS copy, no less. We had time for one more question if anybody has one.
Great. Oh, okay. Yes, I've seen Mississippi grind. You mean because I like to gamble.
Yeah, I thought there was a pretty good movie. It is a, it is very similar to
California's split with Elliott Gould, which is a Robert Altman movie, I believe.
In many ways, too similar. And that's a better movie, but I thought Mississippi grind was great.
That is Mendelssohn, right? And Rand Reynolds. I always like Reynolds.
California's split is also quite similar to a film called Banana Split about a gambling chimp.
Should we go out on a high?
I don't know.
Not medium rare.
It's funny to picture a chimp playing cards in my head. Nobody is arcing.
Ladies and gentlemen, this was awesome. Thank you so much for coming.
Before we finish, please, Emily Florence, come up here and introduce yourself.
She does it all. She put this whole thing together.
She runs the group. She runs the merch. She does everything.
We're not a couple without Emily. We are very lazy. Thank you, Emily.
Guys, thank you for being here. We can't express our gratitude enough.
We really, really, really mean that from the bottom of our hearts and we'll see
some of you at the next show and hopefully we'll see all of you at the after party.
Like, please, if you're not safe at the next show, come back and drink with us.
Don't be a fuck up. You know what I mean? Like, come on, just do it.
Yeah, it'll be here. And also, this is, we completely missed it,
but it was our 100th episode, like two weeks ago.
Oh yeah.
A celebration of that.
That's another thing Emily pointed out to us.
That we didn't know.
That we missed it.
Cheers, everybody.
We'll see you next time.
We'll see you in half.