Huff, puff, and spin the house down at Golden Nugget Online Casino!
Right now, new players can deposit just 5 bucks and get 500 total spins on Huff and
more puff!
The slot that's blowing players away!
Download the Golden Nugget Online Casino app and use promo code Nugget1.
That's code Nugget1 to enjoy 50 spins a day for your first 10 days!
All on our players, favorite game of the summer!
Now's the time to score daily bonuses and spin for all of the bacon on the game everyone's
huff at about!
At Golden Nugget Online Casino!
Gambleing Problem Call 1 -800 -Gambleer, please play responsibly, 21 and over, physically
president Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia only, void an Ontario, new
customers only.
Non -withdrawable casino spins issued as 50 spins per day for 10 days valid for featured game
only and expire each day after 24 hours.
See terms at GoldenNuggetCasino .com slash promos ends at 11 .59 p .m. Eastern on August
31st, 2025.
The football season is full of guarantees and here's another, no other sportsbook has
an offer this good!
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan
cash, guaranteed!
Switch to Fanatic Sportsbook, winning hits different here!
Monthly 21 plus, Gambleing Problem Call 1 -800 -Gambleer, offer not available in all
states, terms apply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
This is a Headgun Podcast.
Hey folks, we'll see you in hell, your favorite podcast!
About them, Science, Fiction, and Horror, and Fantasy Films.
My name is Joe DeRosa, and over there is Mr. Patrick Walsh.
Hey, oh, hi guys, how do you do?
I do well from, you know, everyone I've asked after, I do it well, doing it and doing it
well, and doing it well.
Did you enjoy the rap of L .O. Kool -Jay?
I did.
I think knowing what I know about the man now, which is just his acting career, it's hard for
me to return to those rap albums and still like them.
Deep blue sea, the NCIS, whatever the hell he's on.
Yeah, I mean, I don't hate his acting, I'm just, for some reason like host the Grammys
all the time and he's bad at that.
Yeah, I don't like, I like when he just wraps, sure, mostly, but he seems like a nice
fella.
He does seem nice.
Folks, weird episode, it's not even an episode this week.
This is just an announcement that we are officially going on hiatus.
Season four has run its course and we're going to take a break here.
As we record this, we're at the eve of Pat's wedding and then he's going away for the
extended honeymoon and quite frankly, I need a break from you people.
Yeah, I mean, if we have 52 or 53 episodes in this quote fourth season and I don't think
we skipped a week, that means a year of uninterrupted, we'll see you in hell.
It's too much.
It doesn't seem like a year, but we're going to go ahead and call it a year and we're just
taking a little break here.
We're going to regroup, you know, you let the mind rest, recharge, reflect, exactly.
And then we'll be back with season five.
We also wanted to leave you guys with a bit of a cliffhanger, given that last controversial
episode we did.
Now, you're hanging out there, you know, is that format going to come back or not?
We don't know.
You don't know.
Nobody's going to know till season five.
The format of people explaining movies to each other?
Yes.
Yeah.
It's not going to become a permanent thing.
I'll tell you that much.
None of these are permanent.
No, but we want to come back with season five with kind of a new recharge thing.
We might try some new segments, you know, we got burned out on the all with the Joe's
and et cetera.
We got to find some new things.
I agree.
But we weren't going to leave you guys hanging without this announcement and the promise
that we will be back sooner than later.
You know, we're talking about a month or two here.
We're not talking about a year.
And also your shout outs for the month of May.
That's right.
Thank you to everybody who's been contributing to the Patreon site.
We will put it on pause as of June 1st and restart it.
You know, you'll stay registered and everything and we'll just reopen it when when we begin
again and you won't get charged in that little interim period.
And then also thank you just to everybody buying merch and in the Facebook group and anybody
sending us messages and listening to the show and any capacity.
We are floored by the amount of support.
And if you haven't done the Patreon, now when we're about to go off for a month, would be
a great time because there's several lengthy episodes that you have not heard.
And we are we just uploaded a 90 minute Q &A with all your guys questions from the Facebook
page.
Thank you for those as well.
Yes.
Thank you very much for the support.
You're not going to get charged for June because we're not going to do any shows.
Yeah.
Hopefully we'll be back in July.
All right.
Let's get the shout outs.
Ready?
Do it.
Anthony V.
Minito.
A .K.
Party McFly.
Chuck Eggs.
J. Miller.
Clayton Stamper.
Paul Neenan.
Amanda Lancaster.
Michael Bolas.
Ethan Gammage.
James Garolamo.
Derek Adams.
Sean Hall.
Adam Lownsbury.
Claudia Bersera.
Gary Mossblik.
Brett Frangela.
Toby Bell.
Vincent Franks.
Natalie Hartline.
Joseph Regosa.
Steve Burton.
Tripp Cook.
Anna DiMario.
Bo Aaron Roberts.
Ash Ogden.
Andrew Telekin.
Telekin I believe.
Or television.
Sorry.
Michael Whitsitt.
Scott John Ben Mettie.
Tegan McLeod.
Kevin Eason.
Nicholas McCausland.
Thomas Koza.
Rich Tillman.
Sarah Catherine.
Jeff Jordan.
Paul Francis Merchie.
Ken Hanley.
The man that started it all.
Scott Squeezy.
Greg Sarrinson.
Kara Konini.
I believe that is.
Joshua Taz.
Taj Bozeman.
Taylor.
Chuck Andrews.
Neil Dolby.
Thompson Zonjic.
I hope I said that right.
Holly Barnes.
Brooke Adams.
Tom Laverick.
Tucker Rouch.
John Smith.
Edmund Agabo.
Andrew.
Christopher Musiel.
Brian.
Wow.
There you go.
That's one.
Brian.
Brian Buellerier.
I think.
Will Helms.
Jennifer Anna.
Bryce Buckmaster.
TJ Monholin.
Melissa Alvarez.
John Jane Doe.
Excuse me.
Jake Bullock.
Follow at Zulu Fox for lessons on skull fucking.
Yeah, guys.
Just so you know, you can write anything you want.
Yes, your Patriots.
That's true.
And I'll read it.
Matt Crawford.
Jenna.
Richard Deming.
Brian Callis.
Tim Drain.
Michael Madrigal.
Go to Mr.
Suit Records in Lancaster, Pennsylvania.
Richard Halenstein.
Bretton Fraser.
Sean Luke.
Syah.
Luke.
Oh my boy.
Oh my lord.
Syah.
I don't have to say that.
I've seen that one on there.
I think Syah seems right.
Okay.
Karen Kocharif.
My favorite murder.
Oh.
Go and listen to Karen and Georgia Heart Starks podcast.
My favorite murder.
If you don't already listen to it, it's wonderful.
And their dear friends.
Thank you, Karen.
Inventor of the term, the big, un -thick dick house.
That's true.
I believe it was.
Jack O 'Steal.
Tyler Sanderson.
Joey Mueller.
Shelby Al.
Dan Hapanowitz.
Nathan Baskett.
Gary Myron.
John Paul Rees.
Sairad Dillon -Lar.
Phil Barrell.
Edmund Dillon.
The black magic ninja.
Scott Pauline Surrell.
Patrick Baxter.
Adam Waxwell.
Maxwell Kent.
Casey Sturgeon.
Chris Marsh.
Daphne Kellogg.
Ryan Marks.
Tristan Avery.
Hunk Masterson.
Richard Eiman.
Matthew J. Brown.
Julie Aguire.
Charity Ferguson.
Hank Gustafson.
Nick Walther.
Alex C. Alexanderstein.
Tyler Keatley.
Emily Marvel.
Heather Anderson.
John B. Watt.
Check out John's store on Etsy.
And of course, I'm blanking on the name of it now.
Sorry, John.
I know you told me a bunch of times I forgot.
Mori Benjamin.
Nicholas Burns.
Alex Nelson.
Will Pittman.
Jeremy Cool.
Derek Clark.
Alex Shipley.
Sean Pinnock.
Amanda Liebsen.
Timothy Letzo.
Shane Nazarene.
John King.
Smelly Bubbles.
James Nazman.
Jeff Summ.
Confidence.
David Bellinger.
Tyler Zach.
Hunter McDonald.
John Woll.
Justin Bohager.
Adam Bembernick.
Ben Benick.
Mani Rios.
Demonio Rubio.
Brandon Gash.
Paul Pickler.
Jake Ferote.
Tony Quinn.
Rob Lines.
Danny Rudd.
Jacob Barrett.
Jordan C. Maxwell Ashcroft.
Ryan Kohler.
Barbara Allen.
Jonathan Face.
Rebecca Cohen.
Chris Bowen.
Mike Gibbons.
Donnier Joyce.
Michael Dawson.
Jennifer Smith.
Connor Danahee.
Michael.
Stephen Calpa.
Kevin Swistowicz.
Swistowicz.
I believe I said that right.
Anthony J. Guajardo.
Annie Johanison.
Timmy Kay.
Sean Florin.
Megan Lybrandt.
Scott Blikensdurfer.
Alec Walker.
Brett Wemmer.
Tristan Carlson.
Laura Sexton.
Anthony Guajardo.
Weston Thomas Veadhill.
Jared Blair.
Josh Small Ridge.
Richie Verdugo.
Chris Hopper.
Emily Griffith.
Emily Florence.
Hello, Emily.
And thank you for all that you do.
Sean L. Dave Kalmerick.
Abby Manuel Kim DeAngelo.
Jonathan Galat.
Michael McBee.
Carla O. Stephanie Power.
Sterling Abrego.
Juran Sanderson.
Diego Campos.
Stefan Mazoo.
Zoe Blaskovic.
Ashley Kivinsland.
Dan McLeod.
Lorenz Bunganiers.
Alejandro Salgado.
Papa Spusch.
Tracy Reddington.
Sean Thomas.
Amanda Alzamora.
Jason Weibel.
Charlie Hodg.
The man who brings me my scarves.
I don't know what that means, but it's funny.
Drew Spindler.
Andrew Koval.
Sam Mitchell.
Aaron Melanowski.
Scott Nolan.
Jack Gertz.
Ben Misty Zavar.
Molly Russell's Wart.
Dogeney Wilford.
Johnny Ferg.
Matthias Paljo.
Michael Gold.
Thank you for the pronunciation thing too.
Matthias.
Michael Gold.
Danielle Doer.
Eric Lamora.
Stephen Reese.
Ken Marcenek.
Erica Branding.
Lawrence Anderson.
Jared Smallridge.
Will Potter.
Natalie Craig.
Anthony Kyle Kinsley.
Ann Arsland.
The man whose name we cannot speak.
Ani Babaduk.
Scott Patton.
Julie Bailey.
I think, right, Bailey?
Michael Ayiello.
Reed Estetic.
Robert Pearson.
Max Unwraith.
Brian England.
And John Weisengruber.
The list is astounding.
It never ceases to impress an amaze.
Thank you, everybody, for your support.
You've been amazing, and we'll see you in season five.
Thank you, everybody.
We will see you in season five.
And we will see you alive.
Question mark.
Like maybe we'll kill you.
Or maybe we'll die.
Maybe we'll die.
We'll see you in hell.
Thank you, guys.
That was a hitdown podcast.