I'm here for Bet Rivers online casino and sportsbook with poker icon Phil Helmuth.
And now thanks to the excitement of Bet Rivers, I'm also a slots icon.
That's great! And a same game, Parley icon.
Cool, cool. A Blackjack icon, a Moneyline icon,
A Roulette icon. Take it from Phil Helmuth.
If you love games, Bet Rivers is the place to play in Bet.
Bet Rivers. Games on.
Must be 21 plus in present in West Virginia.
Void were prohibited. Terms in conditions apply.
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gambling.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October,
if your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 -plus gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberler, often not available in those days
terms apply, see Phenatic Sports Book App.
There's a new podcast app that delivers chilling true crime stories straight to your
mobile device every day.
They release a new episode that investigates the gruesome true acts of America's war
serial killers, and you can explore into the minds of psychopaths and murderers.
To get started, find and download Murder Minute from the App Store or visit murderminute .com.
That's M -U -R -D -E -R -M -I -N -U -T -E dot com to get your daily dose of true crime, creeping
is delivered straight to your mobile device.
It's a good show.
Welcome to We'll see you in hell.
your favorite podcast about harm movies fantasy movies in sci -fi films and I'm
sitting here with my dear friend Pat Walsh and he said Joe how do you want to
start the show today and I say Pat let's start it like this yeah I think I'd
like to join here cracking open a nice cold coolers light at 12 15 on the
lords day. Look, I'm not proud of it, but I'm also not not proud of it. Yeah, I was gonna say I'm
not ashamed of it. Joe and I just had a lovely diner breakfast at the Astro diner. It was inside
of me for roughly eight minutes and then came flying out of it. You did make a beeline for that.
I don't know if we should eat there anymore. It always seems like a good idea and then I never
Not fit against the astro diner. There's nothing wrong with their food. I just never feel great after. I
Tend to, you know, I tend to try to do egg whites and shit and today I did the whole I did a chilly omelette like you're not not not brown chili
but chili peppers and
Then you did eat a bowl of brown chili, which I thought was a little a little much
Yeah, it's just the second I put the fork down. I was like I need this out of me
And, you know, lo and behold, it came out, uh, I had the, the, uh, disaster artist at the
opening scenes of it are there. It's, it's got a 50s vibe and they use it in movies all
the time. Yes. But if you ever wanted to do a James Franco tour, yeah, LA, that's one of
your stops. Yeah, stop there and then go inappropriately touch a girl's ass. Hey, folks, why did you
tell James Franco to do what he did? Uh, you know, I just kind of thought it would potentially
Shuffle amount of the mix more quickly. Sure. He's still around. He's rocking that doose, and they're just like, yeah
So what do you want to say something to us?
He's in it. So what do you want to do? Speaking of the doose? HBO's like it doesn't care. Yep. Are dear friend
Dave Cremholtz is on the doose. He's fantastic. He's great
Dave you got to stop with the selfies babe
a lot of selfies. He's an actor. A lot of selfies. A lot of, look at my new
airtension. Yeah. It's an actor. I love you Dave, but come on. I asked him what
they were going to do because he's lost about a hundred pounds. He lost 50
pounds between the pilot and episode two of the show we did together. Yeah, I
know. And he goes, he thought he was just going to lose the part but then this
takes place. It's one of those five years have passed things. He was like
perfect. Right. I'll just have lost the weight. Right. I urge you to check it out. I mean,
I watched and enjoyed the first season. It's, it's strange. It came too close on the heels
of vinyl. It's much better than vinyl. It is very, it's got a similar vibe to vinyl. Yeah.
I liked what I've seen in the show. I don't need Franco and dual roles playing a twin brother
of a twin Franco and single roles, but I mean, I like, I think Franco's a pretty good actor
if he's in the right thing. He's like a Nicholas cage. If he's in the right thing, it could
be great. He's in the wrong thing. You're like, what, what is happening right now? You know, yeah,
I, you know, I like him in Pineapple Express. I 127 hours just made me a complete basket case
for whatever reason. He's good in things. Freaks and geeks. Now, you used to cut yourself. Am I wrong?
I've never cut myself. No, I must have been another guy in mind. I as I told you at breakfast
I've been watching sharp objects where Amy Adams cuts herself almost as like a what'll
the word be this week like a fun game? I was gonna ask you as a cutter. Yeah. Is it what do you
do you think you'd be able to saw your own arm off? I'm sure it's easier for a cutter. Right because
because you're in that area.
I thought you were a cutter, so I'm sorry, you know.
The scene of when he cuts into his arm there,
what they do to the audio,
like that almost like the operation thing
when you hit a tendon or something.
It was really troubling for me.
The sound was more troubling than the visual on that one.
What's he cut it off with?
He uses like a cheap pocket knife
to like saw his arm off.
You've never seen it?
Yeah.
I don't know if it would have, if it would have the same effect on me, but when I saw it,
I wound up running ahead of my friends because I was embarrassed at how much I was crying.
I ran ahead of them to the car.
The movie's got nothing for me.
You got Franco in a solo performance.
You got mountain climbing.
I would have said the same thing.
I don't want to see this damn thing.
It actually, I think the reason it hit me and the reason it would probably hit you
is the it's really about how some people generally men have an inability to
open themselves up to love and relationship. You know that's what you were
crying about. Yes. Yeah. And nothing to do with that arm. No, it wasn't the
arm. But you know, it was a metaphor for the father and son spawned. If he had
told anyone that he was going on this hike in the middle of the desert, then he
would you would have been completely fine. But he wants to do everything
himself and he's very stubborn and blowable. It's a really good story. Okay. Now, who does Jonah
Hill play in this one? Jonah Hill is the voice of an owl that taunts Franco while he's trapped
in the crevasse. Represents his conscience. Yeah. Okay. And when does Seth Rogan come into it?
Rogan is not in the film. No. But I'm sure he had a writing credit or something on it.
All right fair enough
Joe
What's going on with you?
Well at breakfast today I
ate something called the old quartet the old quartet. Yeah almost based on the name alone
I ordered it. Yeah, it was two pancakes two eggs two sausage links two bases of bacon. I
Feel terrible right now. I you're gonna want to do what I did and then you'll feel much better
Well, we we already started recording and I have one rule in podcasting is I won't break to shit during a podcast
I appreciate that. It's kind of like how Walter windshield used to drink a lot of water
So he had to pee before he would go on the air
So like revs up. Okay, that's what I do. I hold I didn't know that I hold a full shit in through an entire podcast
All right. It gives me my energy. Yeah, gives me my center
You know, I hear it. It helps me
But I just was filming he's like I want it I want this because I want the pancake so if I get the quartet
I can get the pancake comes over I order the omelette. I want she says you want toaster pancakes
Easiest pie
And anyway, what the hell kind of deal is that toast or pancakes? I thought it was nuts and it was this there was no add -on to my bill
You know, I can't be in pancakes either. I mean
Just we shouldn't have done that
Joe initially proposed Mimi's cafe one of the shittiest restaurants in the world. I'll tell you what we would feel better. The breakfast is much better at Mimi's
Mimi's is a good breakfast and a delicious coffee. All right. I don't know why everybody you guys hate on Mimi's for for no reason
You and I went to Mimi's and it was terribly a terrible service and terrible food. What did we get?
I had some sort of egg wide deal and their breakfast is good. I mean I wouldn't go in there and get the fucking turkey dinner
No, but they have crepes, which there was a period of time where I would always order the Thanksgiving
or anywhere, like at a diner, anything.
I've got the Thanksgiving.
Really?
Like the cranberry.
I like putting it on the stuffing, moving it around.
There's something about a Thanksgiving plate.
Yeah.
For some reason, when you make turkey the base of the plate,
yeah, you get all kinds of extra shit.
It's true.
And you get a steak they're giving you one, maybe two sides.
Yeah.
Chicken same thing.
For some reason you say turkey, there's cranberry sauce,
there's stuffing, there's mashed potatoes,
here's a green.
It may be that if you just eat turkey, it's very bland and dry and you want some help.
Yeah, it's a terrible meat by itself.
But I went to the Tamoshan or the other day, wonderful, and got the, you know, we talked
often on here about their carving station.
I went with the turkey carving because I said, let me eat something reasonably healthy here.
And two sides plus a dollop of cranberry sauce.
You don't get that cranberry sauce with any of the other meats and it's cheaper than the other meats. You don't get it on the corn beef
Now you don't get it on the prime rib
Folks, if you don't live in LA, this is probably not a great segment for you us discussing restaurants within a one mile radius of our
apartments our homes, but
Here we are. I would like to
Get started if I may
by getting on with the show and at the same time on with the I know I don't have one in the chamber.
I've done Joe your own way. I gotta write I gotta here's what I'm gonna do. I'm gonna put a list
about it before the mic is in front of me. I'm gonna put a list in my phone. I thought I would just
start talking and something would come out.
Oh, well, fly by the seat of your damn pants.
I'll pick a song and I'll go through it.
And I'm like, there's got to be an O sound.
And then I'll be deep in the chorus.
And there's no O. It's happened week after week.
You could do a stew in suspicious minds.
Oh, I know what you could do.
A shitty song by a shitty band that we talked about at breakfast
today that you like for some reason.
Solar silent, gold.
I feel like you could put Joe in place of the gold.
I'd buy that black jolt. Yeah, I'd buy that black jolena night sky won't you feel
up the tank? Let's go for a ride. I don't care about no wheelchair. I got so much
Joe much left to do with my life magic. Yeah. I like black gold. I like
I was telling Joe that's the best of the songs black old's great and somebody to shove is great
That's a great riff. Don't you want somebody to shove
How that goes somebody to love how does somebody to shove go
But I'm for the watch is the grand for the clock
You don't know this one
No, I'm waiting by the phone
Waitin' for you to call me up and tell me I'm not alone.
It's just so much white angst in that music.
That was the time.
It was just so much white.
Ang, I come from a steel -making town and my daddy didn't care.
He bought me cigarettes for Christmas.
That was the time. It's one of those towns.
And my favorite of their songs is called Misery.
Frustrated Incorporated.
And it should have been misery, parenthesis, frustrated, incorporated friends.
He told me this at breakfast today, I almost lunged my butter knife into his eye.
Let me tell you the lyrics.
It helps a little bit to know that they were intentionally trying to make a bad number
one hit single.
But here, no, no, don't say bad.
That part is not in the story.
They were trying to make a hit single, but they never said bad.
They did a kind of tongue in cheek, I think.
Well, you said it.
And it wound up becoming a big hit.
It's a theory they played over the end of clerks to I know and it almost it's it's it's it ruins the movie more for me than the
Donkey fucking sequence. That's a weird sequence. Yeah
clerks 2 has its moments, but here's the verse
They say misery
Love's company
We could start a company
That makes misery for a straighted
Incorporated.
I'll come over there and kick you.
Great song.
Then at the end when they really get it going.
It's dog shit.
You don't really like that song.
You're just saying that.
This is like when you say I just say I hate things because they're popular or whatever.
You don't really like that song.
My playlist songs with a Z,
followable on Spotify.
Contains that song.
It's a song that I listen to at the gym.
It's a song that I have always loved.
I can't help it.
This is like when you said the gin blossoms
were better than Pearl Jam.
I saw the craziest statements I've ever heard
of human being make.
I stand by it.
They had better songs.
Where do you put the Goo Goo Dolls in this hole?
I never liked the Goo Goo Dolls.
Oh, okay, so you even you have limits.
Yeah, the only good good old Goo Goo Dowl song. I like is on the Angus soundtrack
Is it which is a fantastic like pop punk soundtrack the there's that green day song on there green day
They have J .A .R. Which is a maybe one of their best songs
Weezer they have you gave your love to me softly. It's a great soundtrack great to what is the smoking popes?
It's a little more rock and then there are other shit. It's not the high point of the Angus sound. Oh, it's a little more rock and then I don't know what to say when you say.
I don't want the world to seem I should have saved that for the next one where he I believe he's on a swing set in the video
I believe so he's singing it. You know they were a punk band when they started out that the
The angus song is more of that feel they kind of sounded like there were placements
They were trying to be like there were placements. Well the earliest stuff is they're straight up punk right yeah in there
They suck they got suck as bad as the later records just for different reasons right they had that like super heavy set basis with like a
flake of seagulls hair just as silly silly band that guy there's always one guy in the band where
you're like man he must have known you forever yeah because you were definitely the guy the label
was like what do you say we get rid of yeah the guy that's always pasty right and put a good looking
base player in there you know well I so I was watching from last night from 12 till 3am I watched
90s bands performing on either Letterman or Conan I even a great band. I will not show them
objects. After yeah, four episodes of Sheriff objects was a big night. So there are these bands
like I always like this band super drag. You know them. Yeah. Who sucked out the feeling. Yeah,
yeah, I remember that song. So they're playing sucked out on Conan and the lead guy is dressed like
like hard day's night era beetles, like with the suit and the little frilly thing.
The bassist is dressed like Jimmy Hendrix, bell bottoms, skin tight shirt.
The guitarist is dressed grunge and then the drummer is like a 40 year old very overweight
guy in acid wash jeans and a tucked in button up shirt and like a dork haircut.
And I was like sucked out. I hadn't heard it in forever. The song is killer. I know it was a modest hit
But that whole first album is great regretfully yours super drag. They're a good band. They're kind of like a lesser weezer
But then you see him and you're like, oh, that's why they didn't hit
They you got to pick at least a uniform. You can have one wild card. You can't all be a wild card. Right, right
They looked ridiculous on stage. Right. Yeah, I never I don't remember what they looked like. I just remember that video
That guy is screaming at the camera. I don't know if I've ever seen the video
It's who sucked out it makes you like the song less because he's so annoying when he's screaming it sure
But it's a good song
It's I love watching that stuff as you can see who can really hang and who actually has the the pipes
Like there's some bands where like Paul Schaefer and everyone in the band is
Playing the song with the band because clearly at rehearsal they were like we can't air this right so like
you know, like Green Day or something,
it'll just be the three of them.
Because, you know, there were always a tight live band.
But there are groups up there where the lead guitar
is being played by Paul Schaefer.
You can hear his amp is up louder than everybody else's.
The guitar, Schaefer doesn't play guitar, does he?
Schaefer plays everything.
He does, I didn't know that.
I thought he only played this.
He has his old band play.
They had the pro climbers, which I watched, 500 miles,
which I'm sorry, you're not gonna like this either.
I love that song.
Oh, all right.
Those guys come walking out, those guys come walking out, you can tell the audience is like this is not what I was expecting. It's their first ever TV performance.
They destroy 500 miles.
And then Letterman, which I have almost never seen him do with a band, waves them over.
And then he's like, what a song.
Oh, what a song was like, where are you from?
And they're like, I'm from Scotland.
And he's like, oh, wow, look at that voice.
It's like he felt falling in love with them.
But that's it's always excited to watch when Letterman gets excited.
When he got future islands was the last one before he left the stage that you saw him get
really genuinely turned on by a band.
What happened to the pro climbers?
They still big overseas.
I bet they play the bar circuit, you know, because that was their only head, but they had
other songs.
They had a song in the Shrek soundtrack.
I feel like in Scott when they're probably still huge.
That's true.
I'm going to look it up.
Let's see here.
Or you could join me in this podcast.
I'm joining you.
You looked up a thing.
Can't I look up a thing?
I don't think I looked up a thing.
Yeah.
A minute ago you said, I'm going to look this up.
I don't remember what the hell it was folks. Let me take you over to Pat's movie corner if I may
Let me just look it up
Jesus Christ the proclaimers a folk rock duo. Oh, wow
Now I'm looking at pictures of these guys. They are twin brothers. They do not look the way they used to well who does, you know, but I mean they look like
Like, dads now, like, like, sort of, late -error dads, yeah.
There they are, and there are, and all there are 500 miles, glory.
Also similar artists, Ugly Casanova, have you heard of them?
No.
Al Kayola?
There's no way these are similar artists.
King Missile I've heard of.
Strange that Al Kayola didn't become a big recording sensation.
It's a guy from the 50s who plays a guitar. It's like that. How was this a similar artist to the pro claimers?
I mean, I could get like the Everly brothers where it's like great harmonies and acoustic guitar. Well, this is calling them a folk rock duo. I don't think that's wrong.
I
That song man is just a powerhouse. Yeah, that's not a folk rock song, right? It's close enough
their last album angry cyclist 2018 debuted on the UK charts at number 17 so
they're still pretty relevant okay let's hear it for the dogs is one of their
records I think they were had a song in bottle rocket West Anderson was an
early fan what is the album Sunshine on Leath is that yeah that's the one with
500 miles four and a half stars. It's got on all music. I've never heard one of the other songs from it. Let's get married is a good one
They have good songs. Let's let's get married like
Let's get married
Something like that. It's not a cover of the algorithm
I saw a film called
Cretia
Which is available on Amazon Prime
and it is the debut
You, uh, Trey Schultz, who directed it, comes at night, which I never saw, but I know
it divided audience, which is very strongly.
Kreesha got a lot of comparisons to hereditary, but it is not a horror movie.
It's simply like a, it's like family horror, I would call it.
I was very excited to see it, but it's this woman whose name is Kreesha Jones.
Kreesha.
Fair child.
excuse me I have no idea why she would agree to have the title character share her name she's a one
of the most hateful characters I've ever seen but this woman she's like 65 she's a mess it starts
with her like carrying her suitcase up to Thanksgiving dinner at this house she steps in a pile of
dog shit she's muttering to herself and comedy so far now it's like they're doing like this tracking
shot on her and it's, it's even though it's just a woman walking up to a house, it's
immediately very, very tense. And then she goes into the house and everyone clearly has
major issues with her from the last time she came to a family event. There's nothing
really to spoil, but it's basically she is a recovering alcoholic who just can't seem
to get past it. And you just keep waiting kind of through your fingers for her to get back
on the sauce and fuck up this Thanksgiving, which of course she does, right?
You know, it wasn't pleasant. It was very tense and uncomfortable. I like that
sort of thing. I get the hereditary comparison because even scenes that were
just like a woman walking down a hallway, you felt very uncomfortable. I
recommend it. I thought it was a great low -budget horror movie. It's a 24. I
dug it. All right, I'll chuck it out. And by the way, when I say horror again, no
It's not, it's not horror. It's just a family, but it's intense. I'll check it out. I only have two for this week by the way. Go on.
I watched Margot Robbie's terminal.
Never even heard of it. It's a movie with her Simon Pegg and Mike Myers. It's a very, you know, it's sort of a Xerox.
just Tarantino E. Blade Runner E. Newark kind of thing.
Tarantino and Blade Runner, right?
It looks like Blade Runner sort of because it's a lot of neon and whatever, it's not
futuristic necessarily.
It's just a lot of neon and stuff.
And then it's written very Tarantino E. It's a very sin cityish, you know.
Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh
That's not that broad. It's just that he's doing like a cockney accent and he's got a lot of makeup and shit on okay, but
It's a terrible. Yeah, he's fine. All right. It's a look
The movie sucks ass. Yeah, so it's impossible to really judge anybody on anything in it. It's a terrible fucking movie
This is how bad the movie was I looked up Peter Traver's review of this thing worst movie critic there is
Yeah, the guy that says everything is great if a famous person is in it right
The title of his review was come back Suicide Squad,
all is forgiven.
Oh my God.
He trashed this fucking thing.
Like, I haven't seen somebody trash a goddamn movie.
Uh, so you know -
Are you gonna -
Are you gonna be directed?
No, she just stares in it.
Okay.
And it really annoyed me cause it's just like, you know,
and this goes for, this goes both ways.
This goes for men and women in Hollywood.
If you're hot enough, you just get chances.
Sure.
It's like she's a good actor, but dude she's made a couple fucking major stinkers right in a row and
there's still like
Robi will direct the next you know what it's like like she's got nominated for an Oscar. It's a little bit. Well, that's
She's fucking lucky that that one worked out. Yeah
She's but they do this with guys too all the fucking time like you know
She's like, well, why you know, it was like Keanu in the I like Keanu now, but like back you know in the day Keanu would just
Yeah, just stinking everything up, but they would just keep giving them shit. Yeah. I mean, Jesus Christ, man
Anyway, she's she's not a bad actor. She's actually a very good actor, but this movie sucks. All right
I mean to the I was like almost offended by how derivative it was and then I looked up the director
Because I'm like, you know, let me it's called again this film is called terminal not the terminal with Tom Hanks which
people I'll tell you if you thought they couldn't possibly make something worse
than the terminals during time they did it somehow. Yeah. You ever see terminal
velocity with sheen? No, it's pretty damn good. The they drop a car out of a plane
and you like fall with it. It had great action sequences. It's not a bad movie
Terminal velocity. Okay, now this is Sheen and John Cryer. No, that's two and a half men. Okay. Yeah, same thing. All right. Well, it's it sounds similar.
I was telling Joe about the only joke I've ever seen of two and a half men. I was flipping through when I was like, I'll watch one joke and
It's Charlie Sheen and a woman is in his bedroom and he's kind of trying to coerce her into the sack and she goes, boy, your bedroom is pretty sparsely decorated and
And he goes, I got all I need. Check in the nightstand. She opens the nightstand. She's
a Bible and nasal spray. He goes, yeah, the Bible because you're going to be screaming
oh God in a minute. And the nasal spray because you're going to need to breathe through your
nose. The show aired at 8 p .m. on Monday nights. In a church. By the way, by it. Still think
about that joke. That's a wild joke, man. I mean, awful, awful.
You got another one?
I do.
I watched the little hours also on Amazon Prime.
Now that's the one with Nicole Kidman and that's the hours.
Okay.
That's the normal sized.
Oh, the little, this is the one with all the sisters, right?
The nuns.
Oh, I'm thinking a little women.
What is, how are Mandels in this?
No, that's not a monster.
All right.
I don't know what it is.
What is Shirley's there on as Eileen Warnows? No, that's monster
No, little hours is
Written and directed by a poker friend of mine Jeff Baena who I played poker with and
I really enjoyed it. It's like it was a very original movie. It's taken it's like in
You know like the days of monks and nuns. I know they still have monks and nuns
It's basically a lot of nuns these days, that's true.
It's Dave Franco goes into a small village and just shakes up this group of nuns.
They all just want to fuck him and drives them all completely insane, basically.
So the nuns are, here does this take place, you know, long, long time ago.
They can make the 1700s or so.
Yeah, yeah.
Let me look.
But Dave Franco comes in as a monk.
He's like, you know, just kind of like a drifter going from town to town, sort of the medieval
nuns.
And yeah, so medieval times, whatever, whatever, I can't even, does he bang the nuns?
There's a couple pretty hot sex scenes, but it's largely a comedy.
Oh, it's a comedy.
Oh, the little hours with Kate.
It's Alison Brie, Aubrey Plaza, Kate McCoucheet.
Yeah, where they're like the foul mouth nuns. Right. I heard that's very funny. There's great performances by Molly Shannon, John C. Rylee, Nick Arferman's very funny and at Fred Armason is very funny in it.
And it's just like one of those where it's not like where they're all talking like hey
dude and bro but they just have sort of a modern cadence and still talking that language
and it was being really funny.
I was having a hard time like picturing Dave Franco taking on a very serious experience.
It's got a very interesting vibe to it and it's almost like one of those movies that
tries like the Cohen Brothers where you kind of try to invent your own way of speaking,
but it's like modern -day language, but they're still using the terminology of those times,
and it winds up being a nice funny arrangement.
I don't know how else to explain it, but it's a very short, sexy, funny kind of picture.
And there's hot sex scenes in this thing.
in a comedy there's like a three -way where they got them but got Franco with a knife to his throat
and they're like taking advantage of him. I mean the three mentioned just now. It's plaza
which am I my perk the British girl from girls in Franco. There's a lot of scenes of just a
bunch of like naked women running around a campfire. It's a wild time. All right. Lots of graphic nudity.
I recommend it. It felt unlike any movie I've seen in quite some time. And I'm glad I liked it or I wouldn't have mentioned it because my friend made it.
My last one is a movie called Minutes Past Midnight. What are these movies? Maybe what are these movies?
You go watch your fucking shit and I'll watch mine leave me alone
But I haven't even heard of either of your picks this week
Terminal was a movie with Margot Robbie. It was in movie theater. All right. I don't know what to tell you
That first one you meant. What was the first one you mentioned? I don't even remember it now
The first one I mentioned. Yeah. Oh Chris. Oh, you're right. Yeah, I mean come on
Yeah, we like to showcase some indies here, you know
I mean, it's past midnight is a very, very fun horror anthology.
You can watch it for free on Amazon Prime.
It's streaming.
It was recommended to me by my, our dear friend, James Pinkstone.
And it's a hilarious, sorry, it's a really fun horror anthology movie.
Not every story is a home run, but there's about eight or nine stories.
And I'd say five or six of them are really solid.
All right.
It's just a lot of fun.
It's very, you know, obviously in the vein of, you know,
creep show and all that great stuff.
Well, and today's film, Tales from the Hood,
which we've got to tell you that's,
we're doing Slyther right now.
Tales from the Hood is next week.
Well, you didn't say.
How am I supposed to know which one we're doing?
When you came in from your huge shit,
I said, I've got us cute up for Slyther first, okay?
And you went, okay, great.
Okay, all right. I didn't listen. So next week, Tails from this week's letter, I assume
we do them in the order. I watched them this week. I don't know if you know this, but
I don't keep tabs on your fucking life. Now, uh, who's in moments after midnight? What,
like what? Man, it's past midnight. Who's in minutes past midnight? Nobody. Nobody famous.
I mean, at least over here, nobody famous. Uh, there's, there's some, there's some foreign
language segments and and there's some like English and Scottish actors. They might be big overseas.
I don't know. Yeah. But it's it's a lot of fun. Each each short is directed and written by a
different writer -director and they're all very well done. Okay. And they're just a lot of fun. It was
really it was a really fun movie for anthology fans. Now when I was trying to watch it based on the
recommendation I accidentally searched for minutes to midnight. Sure. And it came up and it wasn't
streaming and I was like this one this movie was streaming for free so they're
all right I'll rent it spent four or five bucks to rent it and got a Richard
Greco William Baldwin horror movie that looked like it was shot on an
iPhone okay about 32 minutes into this thing I'm like they're still in the same
fucking first story what what the hell is this and then realized I had rented the
wrong movie right and was not done to please did you finish it no I have the option
to because it's still in my, my thing, but I, I don't think I can finish it, man.
My last one is another, I like doing these three, I'm doing three on a theme.
I'll give you one more indie this week called Briggs Be Bear.
Co -written by SNL's Kyle Mooney and also starring him as well, who I believe you played beer
pong with recently.
Yes.
I did play beer pong against him.
He did not like me.
I get that. Well, I talk a lot of shit when I play beer pong. That's the fun of beer pong.
Otherwise, it's grown men throwing ping pong balls at each other. That's true. Yeah.
And he did not seem to care for that, especially when I called him Spielberg from the 70s,
because he had a ball cap glasses and a beard and a long curly hair.
So you call him Spielberg from the 70s? Do others laugh?
I don't remember. I was a little tipsy at the time, but he didn't laugh. He did not find it funny. Did he say anything to you like fuck you or just let it go? No, he just didn't, you know, he just was clearly annoyed and then later on that night I saw him and I go, hey man, that was fun. Yeah, and he was like, yeah, yeah.
And then about a week after that, I saw my buddies whose party it was, he was him and his
girlfriend.
We were out together and I go, I go, you know, that Kyle Mooney guy did not like me.
And his, you know, his girlfriend goes, what did you say to him, by the way, which means there's
been conversation.
Yeah.
But then they thought it was funny.
They were laughing.
They're like, oh, it's fine.
It cares.
I was like, I don't care.
It doesn't care.
I think, you know, I have a bit of this too.
I love dishing it out and then certain things people will say
Remind me of being bullied and you and you you get really angry. You can't help it
So that's probably what happened and it is your fence. He wasn't really dishing it out. I came in with like
This is how I play beer pong energy. Sure and because it's LA
the other person
expects you immediately to adapt to their energy of course, and if you don't do so then
then it's just a miserable experience.
So that's what happened.
I didn't expect him to adapt to my energy.
Yes.
I just thought maybe we could have a little fun
for a competitive fun.
But we live in a city of,
if they could somehow make lines illegal in LA,
they would because they make people feel too left out
or whatever.
So it's just not a competitive scene out here.
Well, regardless of the energy the man brings
to the, uh, sorry, the beer pong court.
See, I'm like a nice man.
This movie is really good.
I liked it.
It's very original.
Uh, it is about a guy who is kidnapped from his parents as a baby, uh, by Mark Hamill,
and his wife, and they raise him showing him videos that they make themselves about this
character named Briggsby Bear because they're trying to keep him from the outside world.
So he's like in a bunker essentially and as far as he knows these Briggsby Bear videos are like
Like entertainment, but his parents are making them for him to teach him like
Messages that they want to teach him. It's kind of fucked. That's a fucked up aspect of the story. He grows up
He escapes. He finds his actual parents and then he wants to keep making these Briggsby Bear videos
So it's really like let's put on a show
So they make him and his friends decide to make a Briggsby Bear movie and I know this
sounds like an insane setup and it is, but it was very charming.
It wasn't like a laugh a minute, but it was just a visually cool, very interesting movie
I liked it.
Okay.
You know.
It sounds like a fun movie.
I saw the trailers.
It looked good.
It was cool.
And Hamill was great in it.
Ham was a good actor.
It's rare to see him in a non -Star Wars vehicle
All right, well nice
I saw that on stars, but that might be on Amazon as well. Now if I ever read the movie
Do you think Kyle Mooney is a podcast where he'll discuss it?
No, okay. No, I don't mean either. That's fine. I don't give to take Pat. Yeah, I give to give
and it reminded me of just what a welcome presence Keneer always is.
I like him.
Where's he been?
I even liked him in that movie about the invention of the windshield wipers.
I wasn't on board for that one.
That was up there with a joy about the lady that invented the mop.
I was like, for Christ's sake, guys, are we out of inventors to write stories about at this point?
I was too pissed to enjoy that one because I had been working for years on my screenplay
about the woman who invented the mop.
So it really kind of stole my thumb right and it was called soft correct. Yes, yeah, yeah more of a erotic take on on the story
but
Flash of genius which is the terrible title of the
windshield wipers movie I like that movie. Have you actually seen it? No, it's I
Like it to it's pretty interesting that made it windshield wipers. It's ridiculous
Well, you've never been, like, turn your windshield
and thought, I wonder.
I swear to God, I have wondered drop ceilings
were the ones that I would always say to my friends
when I was in a place that I'd drop ceiling.
I'd go, you know what's crazy?
Some guy or lady or whoever invented that thing.
Yeah.
They're probably fucking gazillionaires.
Right.
We just go, yeah, it's a drop ceiling.
You never think about that.
So I appreciate there's this idea of,
hey, there are things that you encounter every day
that seemed quite mundane, that somebody actually had to invent and they served a real purpose
in our lives. But I don't want, look, I love bookshelves. I don't want to see a fucking
movie about the guy that invented them. I don't care. What are drop ceilings?
It's like when there's like the foam panels, the foam's the wrong word, but like the almost
like styrofoam looking panels, you know, the squares. Yeah. And there's like, it's like
a grid and that you can you can push the panel up okay yeah that's a drop seal why do they have
those again I don't know I'm assuming so you can get into your ceiling and fix pipes and shit
okay and somebody was probably like oh my god in an industrial building this is brilliant yeah it's
gonna save us so much money so you want to see like a movie called drop it like it's hot no I don't
want to see starring Paul Reiser as the inventor of drop ceilings. Now I want to see it, not until
you said Reiser. Yeah, regular ceilings, not so much. I like a drop ceiling. By the way,
Paul Reiser has an incredibly funny, one minute top scene in the little hours. Oh, great. He's like
brought his daughter who's a nun like a care package and he's dropping it off. It's a funny movie.
I don't doubt it. Yeah, I thought it looked funny when I saw the check it out
Check it out
So yeah, we're gonna talk about slither slither directed by James gun and why did you tell James gun to do what he did?
What we haven't addressed that I mean that's a
Whole controversy as well and all fairness
What I did do was I told the kids to tweet about what James gun had done to them
Okay, and then somehow it got back to him and he thought I'm supposed to tweet about ping on kids heads or something sure
He didn't do anything to kids. I'm kidding. It's a joke. The jokes he made on Twitter that he got trouble for were pedophile jokes
I'm just joking. Yeah, I mean the the jokes especially when you read you know read them through this lens of today and everything word
a yeah bad jokes be not funny see and bad taste but I
I mean, as long as that's all there were as jokes, I think what's happened here is completely
insane.
I think anybody, if they meant it as a joke, you got to give them a pass.
Yeah.
It's the intention.
It's not the effect.
Right.
People go, well, if it's funny, then it's fine.
It's like, oh, well, who the fuck gets to decide that?
That's true.
Every comedian has done a joke on stage where everybody is dying, laughing, and two people walk
out offended.
Right.
it's so it's the intention the guy was fucking joking obviously I think he
was obviously joking the the bigger issue is he's making movies for Disney and
I see that that puts Disney in a bad position well the guy who outed him
quote Mike Surnovitch is one of the biggest scumbags in the world who has
quite a record himself you want to look into him but you know James gun
my life's not any bleak or not having him direct movies. It's okay. I feel bad. I feel bad for the guy. Absolutely. I'm gonna say it. It was just jokes. It was just jokes. I would bet my life on it. And I'd say I'll fucking say this right now, too. I felt fucking bad for Roseanne.
I don't think she's a fucking dirty racist. I think she made a joke that fucking was a major misfire. And every nobody gave her a fucking chance to goddamn breathe.
Right, and it's like dude, well the issue with her is
She was mentally ill when they hired her and they knew it
They absolutely knew it James Gunn is a man who seems completely stable and reasonable. It's also 52
Which I didn't know he is this is an a normal human being but the reason this what's the guy's name? Chenoworth?
Mike Surnovitch Surnovitch and Kristen Chenoweth. She's great
it. Cernovich, the reason he does this shit is because it's it's it's I'm not
justifying it. Yeah, it's this fucking reactionary bullshit that everybody
does now where they go, well, you did this to one of ours. So now we're gonna do
this one here. It was it's interesting to choose James Gunn, though. Like he that's not
Roseanne. That's not an equivalent. It was good fellow shit. Yeah. Yeah. You okay
with what your dogs doing by the way? What's he doing? Stripping a tennis ball. I'm just
I don't want you to get it on the court tomorrow and find that you've got a, uh, a faulty
ball.
Well, oh, the tennis ball, you mean, uh, I know we've got that seven AM court times.
But yeah, no, it was, it was Billy Bats shit, yeah, you know, and, and it's a shame that
that that's where we're at, but nobody wants to listen to anybody, nobody wants to let anybody
breathe.
So now it's just mob hits.
Yeah.
That's all it is.
It's you whacked our guy.
Now we're going to whack your guy.
And look, I can't get mad at somebody.
Well, I don't agree with somebody reacting like that.
I certainly understand spite, I'm a spiteful man myself, but you know, we got to sort
of applying these standards to everybody, you know, it's like nobody, nobody chastised
Dave Batista for defending James Gunn, right?
Everybody chastised Monique, a black woman, for defending Rosanne and saying, look, when
And nobody gave a fuck about me.
There was one woman that cared.
It was Rosanne.
I don't think she's racist.
I think she made a mistake.
And that's a very...
A man I'm working with, who I won't mention, worked with Rosanne for many years, just
I don't know if he wanted to mention, but he said there's no way in hell she is a racist.
It just gives...
I think that tweet is unquestionably racist.
Look, nobody saying it was a good tweet.
Nobody saying it was a good tweet, and then it didn't push the wrong buttons.
Right what I'm saying is is that's why I go back to intention you go all right that was a bad joke
Say you're fucking sorry. Yeah, which she was very quick to do
So it was gun. Yeah, you know, it's like we're gonna split hairs over
Pissing on a three -year -old versus right a racist. I mean, it's all awful shit. You know what I mean? I
Ultimately guess I just don't care enough, but I don't I guess I don't either I don't know where I'm I mean
It's just, it made me uncomfortable enough to go back and delete, like I searched 300 words
and then went back and deleted tweets that were even mildly questionable.
I don't love that I had to do that, but I felt like I did have to do that, you know?
I, and the things I were deleting, even somebody who's combing through tweets looking to have a problem with me,
would have had a hard time, you know, proving that I had hate in my heart for these things.
There was nothing, no racist things, no anything.
But I was just kind of like this,
if somebody hated me and wanted to ruin my life,
this tweet with enough heat
and hatred behind the person coming at me,
could have a case.
I know a lot of friends in comedy and not
who did the same thing.
You know what I mean?
And some who took down their accounts completely
because it's just not worth the rest.
Well, I took down my account.
Yeah, and I don't think I've,
I don't think I've ever tweeted anything that crazy.
Yeah, but I took it down and I was just the here's why I took it down though
Yeah, because I remember when you were deleting and that same day I went on movie web and they had a data story on
movie web which
You know, I talk about movie web quite a bit on this on this podcast and I do go there for a lot of movie news
I'm not crazy about the site. It is becoming more and more every day like the national inquiry or movie sites
So I'm not crazy that David ran the story, but they did run a story where they said, Ryan
Johnson deletes 20 ,000 tweets, what's the deal or whatever, A, you shouldn't have 20 ,000
tweets.
But okay.
And I sent you that link, and I remember saying, now they're keeping tabs on who's deleting.
And I immediately went on Twitter, and I said, given the state of Twitter and the way people
are reacting to jokes, fuck this shit.
You guys have a good time.
I'll see you later. Yeah, and that was the last thing I've retweeted and then they
counts down. It's like, I'm not, I'm not playing this fucking game. I took Instagram
off my phone. I use it when I need to. I put up my hard bod vids sometimes, you know,
for fun. But it's just like, this, this is fucking ridiculous. What's going on right now? It's
just crazy. I don't know why you don't even want to dance in that fucking. People are like,
just don't react to it. It's like, why even go into the school yard with these people?
a gun, you know, never has to make another dollar again as long as it's alive, but to
know that like some stupid jokes he put on a blog or something 10 years ago, it costs
him, let's be real here, probably upwards of a hundred million dollars, is pretty nuts,
it's pretty nuts.
And that's what I mean, and that's what I mean by, it's all reactionary, it's all mop.
Everybody is acting out of passion right now right nobody saying Roseanne made a good tweet nobody saying the joke was in good taste
Nobody saying it wasn't a misfire
All I'm saying is is when you go no no mercy. I don't want to hear it. I don't care what you say you're dead
That's it right then when one of your guys does it you have to do it to him because you're like well
Now we're gonna look like fucking hypocrites if we don't and you start eating yourself at that point. Yeah
The other thing is a tweet from 2008, 2008, before the society became what it is, a lot
of things from a lot of people are going to look kind of shocking, like words you could
say, things that were acceptable 10 years ago, doesn't mean they were great, and people
I think have gotten smarter now about what offends people, what hurts people, what holds
back groups, et cetera, but to point at something written 10 years ago and say, this is offensive.
Well, nobody commented on it then because it fit right in everything else that was happening.
No, it's that it's that fucking, it's that fucking bullshit that Molly Ringwald said about
what's his face. John Hughes. She's like, I can't believe he missed that, that, that glaring
out of place in this movie. Molly, you fucking missed it too. Everybody missed it
because you lived in a different time. That's how progress works. Exactly. You
look back and go, remember when we used to do that and that wasn't cool, now we
don't do that anymore. Good for us. Oh God, it drives me fucking crazy, man. Yeah,
you know, made six movies with the man that made her entire career what it is. The
Now, pile on a dead guy, the only thing that Hughes has in his movies that always kind
of makes me take a step back and go, okay, are the fucking gongs with long duck dong?
It's like, all right, I was three in 1984, but I think even when I was a little kid, that
always felt pretty weird today, right.
You know, the character is already such a broad caricature.
The only thing that buys you any good will is that the actor had no issue with it and
still talks about how he had no issue with it.
And the actor the character is very lovable and almost treated like a hero
But the gongs are inexcusable
Yeah, but like
It's it's true people change tastes change things change was it right then no, but but again
In in in line with our conversation. Yeah, you can have a misfire and not be a complete piece of shit
Sure, it is possible sure to make a mistake. Yeah
which everybody has seemed to have forgotten.
Yeah, and doing these tapings, you know,
we had to do a scene where these two friends,
David Allen Greer and Martin Mueller,
keep insulting each other.
So the other night, we ran in like 30 all of them
insulting each other and it would be like,
laugh, laugh, laugh.
And then one would go too far.
And the audience would go,
oh, right, which just meant like,
but okay, these guys are friends.
I don't want to see them be that mean to each other.
And then you're like, okay, got it.
So we'll do one that's between this one and that one.
That's how comedy works.
You know, it's, you can't do comedy unless you're occasionally stepping on people's toes.
I don't think what Roseanne was doing on Twitter can be considered comedy, but it's a bad
listen.
It's a bad joke.
Yeah.
But if you want to, if you want to start dancing in that fucking arena of what's an okay joke
which is versus what is not, I'm saying I don't think she was making joke attempts.
She was more a political commentator at that point because all she was doing was talking about
Vaccines and Trump and everything else the
Well, look and that might be the case too. I don't know but it's I'm not in her head. Thank God
Are you
Let's talk about James Guns
Not his first film because what's that head?
Who what I said whose head are you in?
You said I'm not in her head. Thank God. I said, who's head are you? I'm in mine. Although I you know, that's not much better
I assure you you're really not listening to me today. I didn't hear you say who's head. That's it
What is what what what what did I do to you today? What are you what's up? What's up? What did I do?
Why don't you we're having a great conversation? I know kidding. You are again presenting your genitals to me like an animal
I'm not present sitting across this is what folks. I wish you could see this. I'm sitting across from you with my legs up
I don't understand what I'm supposed to do.
All right, where do you want me to put my legs?
It just makes it so I almost can't look at you
because I'm looking at your balls and jean shorts.
Pat, I'd prefer it that you stare at the ground
when we speak.
James Gunn Slyther.
James Gunn Slyther may be,
I don't have confirmation on this,
but it might be the first movie I saw
upon moving to Los Angeles in 2006,
a very mild fun fact for you.
But James gun prior to slither had done like Tromeo and Juliet. I never saw any of those
trauma trauma trauma trauma pictures. Do you watch those things I've tried to watch
some of them. I appreciate with those that whole team does over there. I think it's a
lot of fun and it's great. They're just not really my style. Gun wrote the Scooby -Doo movies
neither of which I saw he was one was great really yeah I'll see that and he wrote the dawn of
the dead remake which I think is one of the best horror movies of the 2000s yeah slither straddles
the horror comedy line I watched the documentary on the which I don't know if you want to do scary stuff
we don't have time we're at 54 minutes we have a short time but I watch the screen factory DVD and
And on the Blu -ray gun, it's a modern day interview, modern day but before this all happened.
And he is basically saying he was so excited and they were excited about the movie and they
didn't want to send it to critics but he insisted and it got amazingly good reviews and he was
all excited.
But then right before it came out, some movie web or something did a post on the most successful
horror comedies of all time and they maxed out at like $15 million. And he was reading through
this list and was like every horror comedy has bombed. This is gonna bomb and it bombed. So it's
a genre that for whatever reason people don't roll with. They're never successful outside of like
funny enough to be a comedy and not being scary enough to be horror, that said I enjoyed
it. It's basically about, you know, a virus that comes down from space and then people
pass it to each other and they become zombies. But the makeup effects, some of the practical
special effects in the movie, the giant, the woman that's blown up into like a giant blob,
the makeup on Michael Rooker, some pretty incredible shit.
The practical effects are amazing. Yeah, the CGA effects leave a lot to be desired, but the practical effects were fantastic
Yeah, and it's it's gross in like a fun way
you know, I
Like the cast a lot
It had that 80s vibe to it. I just never found myself laughing out loud and I never found myself scared
So it's hard to call it a huge success
But it's a very enjoyable movie. I thought I laughed a few times
I found some of the jokes quite funny.
Others were just jokes you'd kind of expect in a movie like this.
Right.
Again, I thought the makeup effects were great.
I thought there were some genuinely creepy parts.
I did think the film was just night of the creeps, though.
I mean, night of the creeps is about...
Never seen it.
These worm things that come down from outer space.
They look exactly like the things in this movie.
Yeah, they crawl in through your mouth and then they turn you into a zombie right in this they crawl on through your mouth
they turn you into a zombie that also wants to eat
meat and
You know become part of the conscious and physical part of this this greater being or whatever. Yeah
But I mean, you know again split hairs. It's like it's like it's like it's kind of the same thing
None of the creeps is a great 80s harm movie you would love it, right and this was a fun movie
What's night of the comet? That is I think it also was I'll be you know I have the VHS over there
I've never watched it yet. Okay, I've heard it's amazing. I don't know why I might have both
When I bought a bunch of those screen factories. I think I have both
But but you know, it's a pretty good movie the cast, you know
You got Nathan Philly and who I always love because I'm a big firefly fan. You got Elizabeth Banks or we's good great
Michael Rucker always good. I guess it's it, right? Everybody else is kind of a. Yeah, there's
that, you know, Jenna Fisher who was James Gunn's wife. Yeah, that's a small part. But, you know,
look, what I appreciated about it more than anything was, it seemed to me that James Gunn really has an
affinity for a certain type of horror. And for a certain type of fun in his movies as, you know,
as he obviously tries to do with Guardians of the Galaxy and stuff like that.
And I appreciate that he puts that on screen at times. You know, with this movie,
I appreciate it more than I do with Guardians. Those movies kind of rub me the wrong way.
But you know, he's not the greatest writer of all time. He's not the greatest director of all time,
but he doesn't know how to get that sort of nostalgia up on the screen.
Yeah, and and his fandom up on the screen and that's pretty cool. It's it's you know
It's a movie I'd certainly watch again, but I happened to own it. I bought it on blind faith. Yeah
And I'm not gonna sell it. I'm gonna keep it, but it's something I'd watch again
But if I didn't own it, I wouldn't feel that I need to go buy this was this the first viewing for you? Yes. Oh, okay
The mayor character was funny. I liked his mr. Pib rant
That was funny. I like the running joke that he says cock sucker to everybody. Yeah, that's
that was very funny. Yeah, it's, you know, it just lost a little steam at a certain point
for me. It's, I don't know, it's, it's not a, not the classic that I think it's made out to be a lot
these days. But I think if it was made in the 80s, I'd probably have a lot more affection for it.
I like to that that the ridiculous marriage between Elizabeth Banks and Michael Rucker sure
You know everybody is saying in the town like
Clearly she's taking this guy for a ride. I mean she's gorgeous and he's 20 years older than her whatever it is
Yeah, I actually liked that
When when it when it came down to it you saw that she actually did love him that stuff and was like
Yeah, like King Kong or something that worked really well.
I thought it was kind of weirdly sweet.
Yeah, I thought that was a nice turn because it would have been easy to go the other way.
And be like, oh, she can't wait to happen to bed with the hot sheriff or whatever.
And then also when Rooker goes out in the woods and is going to bang that woman,
he's like, I can't, I'm married.
Like, you know, they didn't take the easy way out on those things.
Yeah, which was interesting.
Yeah.
Above average, one of these kinds of movies, you know, and I think some really great low -budget
effects unquestionably. Like that's, that's, I don't remember whole movies I saw 10 years ago,
but when I started to watch this this weekend for the second time, I was like, I remember all
of this stuff. The giant blob lady, the, the crate with the, that naked fact guy getting absorbed
into the creature, which is particularly disgusting. There's lots of really cool stuff that I hadn't
I've seen before, a visual one.
Yeah, the makeup was certainly a throwback to society, which is another really great
practical effects horror movie, horror comedy.
Societies and movie about how the elite, the group of elite people in this one affluent
suburb turn out to be like aliens and secret that actually connect together and feed on the
poor people.
Okay.
Yeah.
And that's the secret society, the elite class, yeah.
It's a pretty fun movie.
I would say sort of a horror comedy.
It was definitely an influence on this film.
Yeah, it was interesting to watch this documentary.
He references movies as inspirations that clearly were not as big of influences as the ones
that he ripped off because I think he didn't want to admit that he had ripped them off.
So there's no mention of Night of the Creeps or anything like that.
He says he was influenced by the thing and a few other movies that any horror movie
has been influenced by.
The thing.
I don't see that.
No.
Really in here.
But, well, I guess a little bit.
Yeah.
I remember a lot at the time of people accusing him of ripping off Night of the Creeps and then
other reviews were like, he rips off every movie.
Like, it's hard to be upset about this one.
but, you know, horror is, I mean, it's not a good movie.
It's not about what?
Maybe this isn't a good movie with Slither?
I had a good time with it.
It's not a great movie.
It's no tremors.
I mean, what is?
What is?
I was one other, you know what I can't say.
I'm just too much with Spoiler.
Well, no, we always do Spoilers.
Of Slither?
Yeah, go ahead.
I like the setup at the beginning
when the cops are getting guns again like armed up to go like hunt this thing yeah and the
one deputy goes like we got that hand grenade from the time I confiscated it for you know
should we bring that and he's like no I think we'll be all right without it and when you first see
that in the movie I'm like my god that was a hard setup uh -huh but they did they do great with it
because they sure enough they do go back and get the hand grenade and it it fails them right it's like
I was like, oh, that's funny.
He got me with that.
Yeah.
That was a good, that was a good little device.
Anyway, see Slither if you want, if you don't, frankly, people, I don't give a shit.
What you do with your time.
This is our show.
What do you, I guess we're in September here.
Well, look, if you're in the Atlanta area last weekend of this month, I'll be doing the
Red Clay Comedy Festival on the Sunday night.
the last Sunday in September I will be recording my new album and I am recording it exclusively for
Sirius at XM radio will only be released there so come on down we're doing two shows at the
Earl 7 and 9 30 on that Sunday night I hope to see you there and if for some reason you're
living in China or Japan I'll be over there prior the week prior in Shanghai and then Tokyo so
So I hope to see all the y 'all and after the album recording going to do, I think a few
shows around the southeastern United States.
So a lot of stuff coming up, a lot of new material.
And I'm excited about this newest hour.
So come on out.
Oh, Joe DeRose, a comedy on Instagram.
I'm the Patrick Walsh, Twitter and Instagram, follow CU and HellPod on Instagram, follow or
join that we'll see you in hell page on Facebook run by Emily Florence can
handle it. They're doing great work. They've also set up our October 28th live
shows in Los Angeles. I'm sorry. October 20th live shows in Los Angeles. It's 7 .30
and 9 .30. We are officially sold out. There may be a standby line. Watch the Facebook
page or the Instagram for that info. Cool kids September 28th on Fox 7 .38 .30.
It's a very funny show that's all I got we'll see you next time with tails from the
food, and we'll see you in hell.