Welcome to we'll see you in hell today.
We're talking the flash.
I'm Joe DeRosa and I'm Patrick Walsh and I need to get ahead of this.
I saw the wrong flash.
It was about a guy who walks around in an oversized trench coat, gets the
attention of a woman and then throws it open to reveal his naked penis.
Very good.
So that's all I'll be able to talk about today.
It was honestly a good penis and a decent movie.
But I did not see the new flash that we're talking about, but on theme,
he does run away after he does it.
Not very quickly, but still there's running and the plot point is running
is as it was one of the points.
Yeah.
Um, that was a, that's something that's gone away.
There, there was a lot of streaking and I know it was popular in the
seventies, but, um, I S I still remember that going on at baseball games and
stuff, I was at a Cardinals game once where a naked man ran onto the field.
There's not enough of that anymore.
Do you think that's considered a crime?
Yeah.
Well, like, is that like a me too?
Now streaking when I, when I, I'd streak in college and it was just considered
funny, like, you know, but now it's probably right.
Yeah.
Um, no, I'm sure it's a sex crime.
I mean, certainly flashing someone as a sex crime.
Right.
I wonder if it's one of the, it's one of the lesser ones, but even, uh, you
know, jacking off in your car or even like the news story I read last week
and sent to you when we discussed, uh, the man who was making love to his
collie all over the park, uh, 64 year old, like lauded decorated chemistry
professor, having sex with his dog all over a public park in various positions.
Like it was like the dog was tonguing his anus in one of the videos.
Um, and he wore a mask, but neglected to cover his license plates.
He wants to get immediately.
And he begged the policeman to shoot him when they arrived,
please shoot me.
And they would not.
Jesus.
Just, yeah, one of the darkest things I ever read.
It actually led to me, uh, doing the thing I've been meaning to do, which
is get an alarm clock and start leaving my phone upstairs away from my bed.
Because I woke up and I always wake up in a horrible mood.
Like my head's on fire panic and everything lately it goes away very
quickly, but I woke up and the first thing I saw was that news story, man
fucked his dog a hundred times and then begged the cops to shoot him in the head.
And I was like, I gotta start waking up different, baby.
I, uh, I had a very odd dream less last night as we talk about sleep.
Yeah, I dreamt this happens to me with every.
Star Wars movie that comes out and it's happened to me with crystal skull.
And now with this new Indiana Jones, I'll have a dream that I go see them a new
movie and it's beyond bad.
It's beyond like anything I could imagine, like where it doesn't make sense.
And so I had this dream.
It's always about a week out of the premiere or release, whatever.
So I had this dream last night that I went to see dial destiny in the dream.
It was directed by Martin Scorsese because of the D aging.
They had, they had hired Scorsese to do it.
Get the expert.
Yeah.
And throughout the movie, there's a voiceover of Jerry Seinfeld.
Uh, doesn't sound bad at all, but he's not narrating the movie.
They're just playing his material as if it reflects what's happening in the scene.
It was like this real weird artistic choice.
So then like the scene, a new scene would start and I'd be in the
room, I'd be like, okay, finally that Seinfeld thing is done.
We're going to get into like the movie.
And then as characters were talking, the Seinfeld voiceover would come in again.
And it wasn't even voiceover.
It wasn't like, what's the deal with these boulders?
I know it was run away from these boulders.
It was material.
He had his own material and, um, and they didn't even rerecorded.
It was like the audience was still, it was just taken from the.
I'm special.
So he's doing like dating material while action scenes are going on.
Yeah.
And, um, and then when I woke up, I realized what had happened was I had gone
to sleep to a Jerry Seinfeld special, and then I had this dream and then the
special was playing and interacting with the dream and then it made sense.
Um, it was a horrible dream.
It was a horrible, horrible dream.
I was very upset.
Uh, I gotta tell you, if this indie picture is bad, it might,
that might be the end for me.
I, that might be the last straw for me.
It might break me permanently.
I'm, uh, I'm going to rewatch crystal skull be my second time and rewatch
the whole trilogy and 4k before I go.
And my plan is to just hope that it's as good as crystal skull.
And I didn't really like crystal skull, but that's all I can hope.
If it's better than that, great.
You know, most, most reviews are saying, not most, but a lot of
reviews are saying it's better than crystal skull.
Yeah.
Uh, the, here's the, here's the trade -off though.
It doesn't have any lows as low as the lows in crystal skull, which when it
hits, when crystal skull hits a low, it's bad.
So they say there's nothing that, well, not, well, the monkeys swinging
on guns, you know, so they said there's nothing as egregious as any of that in
it, but the trade -off is it also doesn't have any of the Spielberg magic.
So it's a, it's, it's sort of like, I feel like it's like a good analogy would
be like, um, taking like meds for like your depression where it's like, well,
I don't hit any bad lows anymore, but I'm just kind of evenly numb.
So like, I feel like that's sort of what people are saying about the movie,
which, and then other people are using the word dreary, which I'm excited about.
I kind of like that.
It might be this somber last chapter.
Um,
well, see when you say that it's, it's, uh, like a comp, but it sounds like
it's like a competent action movie without the Spielberg magic.
Like you're saying that reminds me of like Terminator three.
I know you don't like one and two, but like one and two have, whether you
liked the James Cameron magic or not, they, they have the James Cameron
magic in spades and Terminator three is a solid action movie, but certainly
doesn't feel like it's a great continuation of this amazing franchise.
Hopefully that's what it's like.
I'd be down with a good action movie.
That's, that's what the consensus seems to be.
Like, it's like, if you're looking for being swept away, like the first three,
that's not going to happen, but if you're looking for a competent Indiana
Jones movie, you're going to get it.
Good enough.
Maybe it'd be like the best episode of the young Indiana Jones chronicles.
Uh, that's fine with me.
I mean, that's what I've, that's all you can ask for anymore.
Um, I, uh, this guy who the only guy who's Twitter I check now that I'm not on
Twitter, the insnider Jeff Snyder made a great point because the mission
impossible, uh, the new one reviews are oddly not great.
And I was kind of thrown by that because it's just been such a quality
franchise and people are like, fuck you.
What do you know?
Whatever.
All these critics said it was great.
And he said, made a great point.
Oh, all the people who got a free, all expense paid trip to Rome for the
premier liked it crazy.
And I was like, yeah, I hadn't thought about that.
Cause you know, sometimes they do that.
That's what started with.
Ain't it cool news?
You know, it's, it's basically payola.
You know, they give you these lavish gifts and bring you out to a big premiere.
It still goes on constantly, but, um, even something like, even something like
con when there's a glorious reaction to something like this movie, or it's a
seven minute standing ovation or whatever the fuck it is, or seven minutes bad
these days, it's gotta be in the doubles.
Or the opposite.
When it's, when it's Lars von Trier and they're all screaming at him for
what a piggy is or whatever, you know, the con reactions, you know, it's kind
of hard to take them at face value.
Cause it's like, you know, these people, it's like, I've been drinking wine
since nine AM fucked a supermodel in an elevator looking over at a pebble
white sand beach, it's like, who's in their right mindset at that festival.
It's insane.
And, and movie critics, even, even your top movie critics are making nothing.
It's like, you know, they, they don't get these vacations.
It's no judgment of them.
I love that they, they still love to do it, you know, but there's
no money in that game anymore.
So I think the whole, I barely read any reviews anymore.
I can't think of a guy who's like work.
I always check.
Like I used to do with Ebert.
It just doesn't happen.
No, I can't.
Speaking of critics, um, yes, you got a new Rex Reed?
Well, I, as promised, I'm going to read you some excerpts from the book club.
The next chapter review that he has called Jane Fonda's cinematic joy.
Uh, and let me put a quick pause on this.
My mother's review of every movie since 1977 has been, it's pretty good.
You know, she just doesn't give you much more than that either way.
She thought book club was terrible.
And then when I asked her about some movie I saw the other day, uh, no,
she saw the Sebastian Maniscalco movie.
And I was like, Oh man, that didn't look too good.
Well, it was sure better than book club.
That's like her new bottom is, is book club the next chapter.
So carry on Jim.
Now, keep in mind, this is what I like about this review.
Keep in mind, he liked this movie.
Keep that in mind.
Yeah.
As a sequel to the popular 2018 comedy about four middle -aged women in Los
Angeles who keep their friendship alive, da da da da da da book club.
The next chapter follows the current trend of joining Jane Fonda with a
trio of fading screen stars who are women in their eighties.
We're all there.
One's hating in their 80s who are still ambulatory and sending them all on
location, hoping they're funny.
How old are you?
Rex, how old are you opening to a movie he liked?
Yeah.
The abysmal 80 for Brady dragged Jane, Lily Tomlin, Sally field, and Rita
Marino off to the super bowl with dismal results book club.
The next chapter reunites Jane, Candice Bergen, Diane Keaton, and Mary
Steenburgen as the plucked pedicured and camera ready septuagenarians.
They played in the original.
It's somewhat parentheses, but not very superior to its recent all -star
predecessors starring glamorous seniors.
But even when it stumbles, the stars have never been more welcome.
So you're sort of off to a decent start.
Still, this is, you know, anyway, the ladies whose lives were radically.
We're missing a word there changed, I guess is the word missing after
reading 50 shades of gray, still guzzle Chardonnay.
But now instead of meeting each other's lavish in each other's
lavish kitchens, they do it on zoom.
All right.
By the way, this is, I don't ever want to see a zoom scene in a movie again.
What are you doing enough?
We don't like looking at zoom.
You're ready for this now people, I know for years men have mismatched
themselves with women in movies.
Woody Allen is the best example of, you know, he'd be the star and there'd be
some gorgeous, you know, Julia, uh, uh, what's her face from Kevin James and
Rosario Dawson.
Yeah, that's a good one.
But people can we get real here?
Candice Bergen's love interest in this is Andy Garcia.
Are you nuts?
Doesn't seem shocking to me.
Is Candy not a beautiful woman?
I guess, you know, are there's the age difference?
Great.
That seems reasonable.
Don't picture you want to set him up with a Mary Steen.
I'll, I'll take it.
I'm sorry.
I know I'm being rude.
I know I'm being mean.
I'm sorry.
I just don't, I just don't see it.
They got, I think Garcia's age just as gracefully as, as Candy Bergen.
I mean, he's put on some pounds.
He doesn't look like he did in the Godfather three.
I buy it.
Yeah.
Candy Bergen to me.
She's just, she's just, she's just such a drag.
You're thinking of Murphy Brown.
Yeah.
I just picture her with like, you know, like Ned Beatty or something.
Like, you know, I don't know.
I'm sorry.
I know he seems like one of the most fun men on earth.
Uh, okay.
So he, he says, this is what Rick says.
These icons still have a measurable charm and charisma, but in the meandering
mechanics that follow, they need a miracle to enhance the lip direction
and dwindling screenplay.
He gave this movie three and a half out of four stars.
Three and a half.
Oh, wow.
I mean, yeah, he's three, three out of four, three out of four.
This is how he talks about a three out of four star movie.
Uh, surprisingly in the interim, yeah.
Yeah.
He's, uh, he is steinberg.
I do love correct.
Probably.
I love.
Yeah.
Uh, surprisingly in the interim, uh, they've lost some of their zest
and sparkle and so has the premise.
I didn't believe the way everyone's luggage disappears in Rome before they
unpack with everything in it, including Diane's late husband's ashes, forcing
them to buy fabulous new clothes, turning the rest of the movie into a fashion
show, and I found even more implausible the reason they even spend a night in
jail, he likes this movie.
Yeah.
By the way, how was it implausible that you lose your luggage and you got to
buy new fancy clothes, Rex, that seems like a pretty natural plot point for a
calm, calm, a friend of mine just watched.
I mean, you think I'm bad with this shit.
My friend just watched evil dead rise.
And I said, he asked me, he goes, I need a good horror movie to watch for my
daughter.
I said, you should see evil that rise.
He watched it.
I go, what'd you think?
He goes, I didn't buy the apartment they lived in.
It's like, this is your criticism is the apartment aesthetic.
And then he watched it again.
He's like, I was being a little crazy.
I was like, yeah.
I've never even heard somebody that that's a hell of a thing to hone in on.
Uh, yeah, it's, it's nice to have you in that position.
Yes.
Which, which it's rare and it's nice.
Uh, by the way, having said all that, this is Rex Reed, having said all this,
I fear I've given the bogus impression that this is a sequel.
I don't give a hang about quite the contrary.
It's the kind of film that exists for the sole purpose of entertainment,
which it provides consistently.
So Rex is at least calling out.
I know how I sound.
That's growth, Rex.
It's growth.
Got it.
What do you think the chances are we could actually get him on this podcast?
I don't, I think I would be too scared, honestly.
I think he'd come on and be like, Oh, uh, somebody didn't take a shower this
morning, you know, I just think he'd be, he'd be mean and hurt our feelings.
So Pat and I, uh, this is more than appropriate reading the Rex Reed interview.
And then also what Pat just said of me being in this position, Pat and I got
in, I wouldn't say it was an argument, but we had a tense texting, uh, on
Sunday when you went to go see the flash.
I had already seen it.
Uh, and it started with, I started it.
You told me that, well, you said the first that you were dreading seeing the
flash and then I got annoyed and then it went from there.
And then that was kind of.
Yeah.
I mean, so, you know, I said, I'm sitting here having breakfast, kind
of dreading going to see this long superhero movie, just cause I don't
like superhero movies, but what it led to is I was talking about Drew Carey
and how he was paying for, for anyone in the writer's guild for the duration
of the strike, which might go till December, uh, he's paying at two
different LA restaurants, you know, diner style restaurants, one Bob's
big boy on kind of the low end, one swingers on kind of the high end.
He's paying for drinks.
He's paying for anything you want.
No limit tip included.
And I was telling Joe about this and Joe's Joe says, well, at no
wonder, nobody pickets in New York.
He's not doing anything for the people of New York.
And I was reading this like, what?
And I looked up and watched this elderly man alone at the counter.
I was also alone at the counter with a shaky hand, hand over his
writer's guild card and they're, they're comping his meal.
And I was just like, how can Joe see this beautiful situation like this?
How, how, how Drew Carey is doing this wonderful thing.
And then I mentioned that I was at swingers and then Joe's like,
ah, swingers sucks too.
Swingers is the most, the frou frou restaurant in LA, whatever you
were saying, it's, it's too upscale or too snobby or enjoy your quinoa.
You know, that, that kind of thing.
And that quinoa omelet sure.
And it was just that kind of morning.
And as a, you know, Joe and I apologize to each other this morning,
started by Joe, of course.
And, um, I was in the wrong as well.
We were both in the wrong, but what happened was that that opposite day
feeling just kept continuing because then Joe was like, I'm talking about
how much he loved the flash and then I was sitting in the flash like, boy,
I bet Joe hated this and Joe was like, no, I love that.
Then afterwards he was like that Queens of the Stone Age album that you
told me was a huge letdown.
I loved it.
And I was like, I guess it's possible that Joe has the exact opposite
opinion of me or of everyone all the time, but sometimes it just feels
like a Puccino style devil's advocate.
And sometimes it's annoying.
I love watching it happen to others like Sal on the taste buds podcast
and see how angry he gets.
But, um, in that moment, it was very frustrating to me.
And I would say it was a very mild argument, especially compared
to what we used to have, but, um, we do need to get that, that apology time down.
I should have apologized then and there instead.
I silenced notifications, which was also a shot at Joe because he
always has notifications silenced.
I've never done it.
I just simply did it so I could stop talking to Joe that morning.
So annoying.
Oh, I didn't know that.
All right.
I actually had to Google how to silence notifications.
Cause I was like, if I keep reading these, I'm going to get upset.
I that's it.
But as I told Joe this morning, we all bring our own shit.
It was triggering shit for me and blah, blah, blah.
I, uh, I will say this.
My, my opinions, there's a, there's a dual thing happening here.
My opinions usually are honest.
I don't try to take the other side just to take it, but that is coupled
with an uncompromising thing that I have where if everybody tells me
something's awesome, I immediately get annoyed because I don't like
people in groups, period, any group of people.
I don't like it at all, which I think that's what I was saying, which I
think really, and then I'll shut up.
That's what I think was really bothering you.
Cause I ever, everyone hates criticism.
I was basically like, um, you go into, he was telling me you went into
the flash expecting to hate it.
And that's why you hated it.
But I don't really do that.
I, you know, I, I, and I, so I mentioned, you know, I went in
in a pretty good mood and sober, blah, blah, blah.
And Joe was like, what does sober have to do with it?
I was like, just cause I would normally have to be fucked up to watch
a two and a half hour superhero movie.
But, um, yeah, it's like, I was, I was saying to Joe, if everybody loves
something, you usually go in arms folded.
Midsummer is our most famous example.
And Joe was like, I don't do that at all.
And I was like, Oh, come on, Joe.
And that was kind of the end of the conversation.
Well, you said, you said, this is what you do with every movie you watch.
And I said, it's not, and that was an exaggeration.
Yeah.
And that was an exaggeration.
So, and I will say, I do honestly, very honestly, I quite like the
new Queens of the stone age, but I knew you hated it.
So I sent that, that text in order to stoke the flames.
And it was, and we were deep in it.
When that hit, I was like, God damn it.
Just because honestly, I, I, that we, I get three things a year.
Now that I'm excited for maybe one in music, one in movies, one in TV.
It used to be a lot more than that.
So this Queens of stone age album let me down so hard that
I'm actually sad about it.
I really am.
And my other friends who love Queens, like I have a couple of friends who love
them as much as I do are all feeling this.
Like I gave it another try this morning and it just made me so sad.
And then Joe, Sandy loved it.
I, you know, it bothered me.
I understand.
And I really do like it, but I was saying that in a prickly way at the, it was, it
was strategic, but what was coming up for me, honestly, this is very funny.
This is all very, what was coming up for me.
I had texted Pat when I think you should leave season three came out.
Yeah.
And I said, I'm looking forward to it, but my worry is that this season he's
going to just say normal things in a crazy voice, way too much.
And Pat said, Joe, it's the only funny TV on TV show on earth.
Shut your goddamn mouth for once.
So it was a little bit of a shutdown.
Fine.
I watched it.
I did think that's a little bit of a shutdown.
I did think that what I was saying was true, but here's the funny part.
Several people that I've talked to about the season since that our
few have been like, I feel like he just says like normal shit and a funny voice
too much this season.
I was like, God damn it, son of a bitch.
And like, I was like, I don't just say these things.
Sometimes I have a point.
So when we were getting into the thing about every everything on
Sunday, that was coming up in me.
I was wrong.
I handled it poorly.
I also, like you said, I also only get three things a year.
One of those things this year for me was Keaton's return.
And I'm doing everything I could just to enjoy it and also to get you to enjoy it.
Cause I wanted us to be like tear in the eye.
It was good seeing the guy back in the suit.
I don't think that's how this review is going to go, but that's what I was trying to do.
And then, um, it didn't happen.
Um, but then, and then the third part is what Drew Carey did is awesome swingers.
It's stupid to say that a diner in LA is triggering for me, but it just reminded
me of every fucking time I wanted to go get food late night.
And I'd say to somebody in LA in the entertainment business, like, let's go
to house of pies and they would be like, we can do a little better than that.
Let's go to swingers.
And it's like this fucking place, another fucking place that the every, like it's
little Dom's mess hall and swingers.
Like it's like, and it just, just the thought of it set me off.
And then I pictured all of these writers like going in with like thousands and
thousands of dollars in the bank.
Just, just fucking getting the free fucking food.
And I, this was, this was my first time doing it, but yeah, no, this was my
first time doing it and I really was surprised.
She was, I mean, the waitress was basically like, you know, you can get
whatever you want.
Cause I got like an omelet and coffee and, um, you know, it, what I really
love about it, I've always thought Drew Carey seemed like a nice enough guy
while not enjoying his comedy per se.
But, um, I just, and he did it apparently during the last strike too, you know,
everybody's and then you hear people and it's not, it's not just you either job.
I think everyone is just depressed, obviously myself very much included, but
he, you hear people say things like they're finding fault with it and it's, and
it had been bothering me for weeks and I had never called anybody out like on the
picket line or anything until you, because just, we were more culture with
each other, but, um, yeah, people are like, I just, you know, it's like, I'm
in a Valley village, so it's like for me to go to swingers is like a 45 minute
drive and I just want to choke these people.
I'm just like, guys, he, you know, he can't send everyone on the writers
guild $500 and say like, go and like, he's just trying to do his part.
And the other thing that made it, that makes it seem so special to me is that
nobody else is doing anything.
And you see these bajillionaires bajillionaires talk in support of the
writers guild and do absolutely nothing.
They send their tweet.
I have your back.
We'd be nothing without the writers to me, Drew Carey, offering up what could
be millions of dollars in diner food is a lot more substantial and the kind of
thing all of our wealthy should be doing.
And I've just heard a lot of weird criticism about it and, and I get it,
but I also don't really get it at all.
It's just kind of like, he's doing something.
So I love him for that.
And thank you.
You're right.
And I was, this is an instance where I was, where I was being
needlessly prickish or prickly or whatever word you want to use.
But cause I complained about Seinfeld during, and look, I'm not one of these
guys that goes, Elon Musk has this much money.
He should do this with it.
It's like, it's his money.
I don't give a fuck, but it does bother me when like, you know, like when the
lockdown happened and then like, I'm watching like Seinfeld and Chuck Schumer
do a press conference from Gotham comedy club talking about how desperately we
need to raise money to save comedy clubs in New York because New York's comedy
scene is so vital to, to art.
And it's like, Jerry, you could literally to a million dollars, maybe two million
out of your pocket, save every club through this horrible time they're going
through and you'd be a hero truly mean it would mean nothing to him by the way.
I love Jerry Seinfeld a thousand times more than Drew Carey.
His comedy, his TV show meant a thousand, 10 ,000 more to me than Drew Carey.
But I hate Jerry Seinfeld for that.
I think it's, it's disgusting and it is emblematic of what is wrong with our
country and you know, if Jerry Seinfeld had just stayed home, I wouldn't think of him.
It's exactly what Joe's saying.
It's like, if you're going to come forward and be like, guys, hey, everybody
who makes 25 K a year, why aren't you supporting these comedy clubs?
And Jerry, if you sold 10 % of your cars, you could own every
comedy club in New York.
Just shut up without selling, but not help.
He could sell it without selling the cars.
Well, of course.
Yeah.
I'm just saying, like, you know, speaking of something frivolous that he doesn't
need, like you're not driving all these stupid cars, he'd show up with a different
car every day on comedians and cars, car, car, like the John Ford Model T to go
pick up Michael Richards.
It's like, dude, you don't need all this.
It bothers me.
That's what's wrong.
It's what's killing our country.
We all know this.
Um, swingers to me, like little doms, like mess hall are maybe places where
the hipster crowd kind of goes, but I do like them.
I mean, swingers is a good diner with a, with a good jukebox.
Actually, I was listening to the Pixies all morning.
I didn't see a lot of riff raff around there.
I'll tell you what does bother me is I just went to buy tickets to Peewee's
big adventure at the Hollywood forever cemetery.
And that is a, has always been since I moved here in 2006, that has been a
reliable, great, cheap date, you know, it's like we'll sit in the cemetery.
It's romantic.
We bring a bottle of wine.
We watch a great movie.
We cuddle up in a blanket, you know, and I went to buy tickets.
And they were $45 a piece parking, not included.
Why are they that much?
That's the new price.
Cause I was like, Oh, I can't believe this isn't sold out.
They, it always used to be sold out because it would be a $20
movie you could stream on Netflix right now.
Exactly.
And they, they used to sell out constantly at 20 bucks.
Last year it was 20 bucks.
It's now 45.
Like the, the, the Jackson prices are getting insane.
Like usually that would be 20 to 25.
Nobody's going to bat a fucking eye.
45 you're edging out.
I used to love just being there and seeing all these families have their big
night out and sit on a blanket and bring a picnic and stuff.
They're just trying to kill fun for people without money.
It's awful to me.
Um, anyway, I didn't buy tickets in protest.
It's like, you know, is $90 going to, going to ruin my life?
No, but I just, I'm just like, fuck this.
And I'm glad they're not selling out anymore because this is gross.
Well, you know, it's, it's very hard.
It's very hard to tell anymore.
Um, you know, there's a twofold thing happening, uh, and, and I can speak
from some personal experience with having opened this, this place in New York, but
you've got the big box places that are capitalizing on inflation and saying,
you know, the best example of it is, is when meat, when inflation happened
in meat prices, meat, the meat market was doing well, the meat industry
inflated prices and said, well, we can just get away with it because
inflation is happening right now.
We don't need to, but we can, so we will.
So that's a good example of what the, the, the big box sort of industry is doing.
But then that's being coupled or met with Indies and mom and pops having to
jack their prices because they need to survive in this recession and this
horrible economic climate we're living in.
So who knows?
So, so what you're left with is a situation where you're paying $45 to see
a screening at the Hollywood for Emma Cemetery and that's such a perfect right
up the middle where you're like, is this the cemetery saying if we're going to
keep doing this, this is the only way we can afford to do it is by setting the
price of this or is it the entertainment industry gouging fans and what, who knows?
I don't know.
And you don't know most of the time anymore.
And it's terrible gouging, you know, it's fan gouging.
They, it's, it's, it's fan gouging.
It's they know they got you over a fucking barrel and like little by
little we're making strides.
Like that, that cure concert where Robert Smith, um, that was at the bowl.
He found out about all these ticket master fees and was like, listen, this is
fucking outrageous and like, you're not going to do this anymore.
And he's made a difference.
I don't like Pearl Jam, but I always respected the hell out of Eddie Vedder
for taking on ticket master, but they've only gotten worse and these places will
just slowly stick the knife in over time so that it feels normal, uh, you know,
ticket master at this point, if you're buying tickets for a show that are under
$25, you're usually going to spend more on fees than the ticket almost every time.
So I really love now that the, just one guy stepping forward, like they're,
they're having to be more transparent.
I'm sure they hate it, but these places will do anything.
Like the rise from 20 to 45 is not a gradual build.
Everyone can deal with a gradual build.
That's inflation.
This is more than doubling the price of a ticket.
Yeah.
Um, it's just a bummer.
I don't know.
Was that, was that cure concert good?
I'm supposed to go tonight to MSG and I'm like, I'm so on the fence
cause I'm like, you know, they're legendary.
It would be cool to see them, I guess.
But, and I have some of their records, but I feel like they're not going to play
a lot from the records I own because they're the earlier records and I'm
like, I don't know enough.
And I'm like, you're totally wrong.
They do, they do a three hour show.
They're playing.
I mean, look, you're, you're not going to mind.
I'm telling you, I went in as a fan of the hits basically, you know, I,
just like heaven is one of my top 10 songs of all time, but I love the hits.
And I saw, I remember I saw them in Vegas three hour show and it ended and I was
just like, when can I see them again?
I bought tickets to every show they had within like 10 miles of Los Angeles.
And I went to all of them.
They're, they're so good live.
And I didn't even get to go to that show this year.
I wound up having an issue, but, um, an issue with ticket master where they
told me I had tickets and then I didn't actually, because I think they were
trying to fuck over people because they were so pissed that the cure exposed them.
Um, I had many people friends with ticket issues, but I would,
I would always go see them.
They're a band where they're still vital.
And in five years, he already looks ridiculous in the golf makeup.
Don't get me wrong.
But it's not going to get any better as he ages.
You know, I would, uh, I would see him, Joe, especially cause you seem
to be getting into them, so do it.
All right.
They played the song from the crow, you know, burn, which is a great song.
Hit me with the, take us to that movie quarter.
I will.
I saw her speaking to Craig T.
I got a shout out the show parenthood.
When I was a kid, I think the first PG 13 movie I saw was parenthood.
And I still love parenthood with Steve Martin, Rick Moranis, Mary
Steen, um, Tom holes, all kinds of folks.
But, um, there is a scene where Steve Martin comes out of the back room
with what he thinks is a candle because the power goes out and it is a dildo.
And he turns it on and it starts vibrating and he starts laughing
in a very, very funny way when the lights come back on.
I remember my mom and my aunt cackling at that.
And it was one of those early things, you know, where the adults are laughing
and you're trying to figure out what's funny.
I had no idea what a dildo was at that point.
And it's a very R rated joke in a very PG 13 movie, but I loved the movie
parenthood and there was already a show parenthood when I was a kid with
Ed Begley Jr and a young Leonardo DiCaprio actually, and I really liked it,
but it was canceled immediately.
So I never watched this new parenthood, but, um, I, as soon as the strike is
over, we'll hopefully, um, be out pitching a show that I am doing, which
is a very, I keep describing it as a fucked up parenthood, but the truth is
I've never seen the show parenthood.
And I was like, I should see this.
I've heard it's great.
It's from the guy who did Friday night lights and I wound up watching two
seasons in about a week.
It's, it is a network drama, you know, so it's not, it doesn't have like the
sex and violence and craziness of cable TV, but just like how, you know, Joe,
I think it's very soothed by the old sitcoms.
There's something very soothing about it.
I'm going to bed to two episodes at night.
Uh, it's a, it's a very functional family, but they don't shy away
from very real problems.
It's a show about very small problems, small problems in relationships.
And I just love it.
And the, the head of the family, the Jason Robards part is played by Craig
T.
Nelson and I gotta say it's the, it's the best he's ever been.
I mean, I love him in poltergeist, but man, he's great on the show as like.
The, the stuck in his ways, dad who is struggling to do his best to like be a
better father partner to his wife, Bonnie Bedelia from diehard.
Um, I just love it.
I love the cast.
It's Peter Krause from six feet under Lauren Graham from Gilmore girls,
Erica Christiansen from traffic, um, Dak Shepard, who is very
charming on the show.
Uh, it's just great.
If, if you have never seen it, I urge you to check it out.
It's on Hulu.
Um, I just started an episode where Dick Dreyfus is the guest star, Richard
Dreyfus, Michael B.
Jordan is a guest star on the show frequently.
So you get to see all these, uh, you know, stars before their time and big
stars come back and do guest spots.
Ray Romano apparently has a great guest spot coming up.
Um, great show.
It was on NBC and now it is on, uh, Hulu.
So check it out if you never saw it.
I unfortunately only have one thing for the movie corner was away on vacation
and then traveling to do shows on the road.
Uh, shout outs to the impractical jokers.
Did three shows with them was really fun.
Um, but, uh, I have, uh, I was only able to see one thing, but I saw
Blackberry and, uh, I loved it.
I thought it was an awesome movie.
Yeah.
Um, you reviewed it and, uh, you said it, the said the same thought
Glenn Howerton was fantastic.
I thought Jay Barshell was fantastic.
Everybody was great in it.
Um, how about Michael Ironside?
Yeah, that was a wild, I forgot you had said he was in it.
So when he came into it, I was like, Holy shit.
Like, wow, that's scary as fuck.
He's like, he's so fat now and just mean and great.
Yeah.
And I wonder if he, if the character called for the weight or if they wrote
it into the script, cause they, his, the guy says at some point, like you've
got that 300 pound monster out there or whatever.
And I was like, I guess the guy in real life was big.
I don't know, but I loved it.
I read a big article after the fact and apparently almost none of it is true.
It's like, it's the guy Howerton played ballsy or whatever.
They're like, he didn't, he didn't face any jail time for tax fraud.
He didn't commit tax fraud.
He did a thing or investor fraud rather.
He did a thing with investors where he had to pay a fine.
And it sounded like par for the course, big business bullshit.
Um, the guy that the, the headband character, they were like, that
guy never wore a headband.
Uh, there was never a movie night.
Oh, Blackberry in fact did go on for a while until quite recently, actually.
So they, they were just kind of like everybody that in real life that watched
it, they were like, well, it wasn't what happened, but it was good movie.
So, uh, that's, that's weird because I would have just assumed that's
beat for beat exactly what happened.
That's what I hoped.
Um, that's the power of cinema.
It was great though.
It's a great movie.
Uh, it's, it's, it's riveting.
Uh, the performances are stellar.
It's fun.
It's funny.
It's dramatic.
Uh, it's heartbreaking.
Uh, I really liked it.
And for that type of movie, excuse me.
They did a good, they did a really good job.
Uh, cause you know, it's a biopic biopic, wherever you say it, essentially
that's what it is and it didn't ever feel like paint by numbers.
One of the biggest things in the movie where I was like, wow, it worked
really well in the movie, um, but in real life, they were like, he actually
did see the iPhone as a threat.
He actually did realize the significance of a touch screen phone.
Like in the movie, he's like, it's a toy that will fail.
That was one of my favorite things was like his ego about all that.
So I was actually kind of bummed to hear like, no, he recognized that it was.
That it was actually a huge threat to them.
But, uh, but I, I,
I, Michelle has, has the much trickier part.
You know, uh, Glenn has the, like, I'm going for an Oscar part
and he beyond destroys it, but Jay has a very difficult role.
And I think he is just as good as Glenn in his own way.
It's just less showy because I found myself, uh, so disappointed in him
because he's so sweet at the beginning.
And when he starts to become the big corporate monster, I felt like a parent.
I was just like, don't do this.
Don't do this.
You know, he's really great at selling both sides of it.
Yeah.
And somehow doesn't look insane with the white wig.
Like somehow it's fine.
Like it's so weird.
You think it's going to be crazy, but it's not.
So anyway, Blackberry, I highly recommend it.
I thought it was great.
Yeah, it's a, I don't think I've, I'd have to think about it.
I don't think I've seen anything better this year.
Um, and I'll, I'll wrap mine up all at once here by talking briefly
about this, uh, horror marathon.
I went to on Saturday night at the new Beverly theater,
Quentin Tarantino's theater.
And it was like a grind house Halloween theme or halfway to Halloween,
I guess is what it was called.
Um, but it was one of those where they don't tell you what the
movie is until it starts rolling, which is great.
However, I had the deep misfortune of having just watched all of
these movies on shutter.
I couldn't believe it four in a row that I had watched within
the last six months on shutter.
However, um, they were, they were so bad that I wasn't really paying attention.
And a bad movie is only truly fun with an audience.
And this was a sold out house and it wound up being a blast.
Anyway, but, um, those movies were first up was, uh, sorry.
Lost it night of the demons.
And I thought this was, you know, pretty stupid fair.
When I watched it on shutter, I was always scared of the box.
Also scared of the box of night of the demons too, where the demon has
like a eyeball on a lollipop.
But night of the demons with a crowd became a whole new experience.
Just like explosive laughs throughout.
It's a total, there's a, there's the standard fat guy in the movie who calls
his girlfriend a bitch 5 ,000 times.
Like every time his girlfriend speaks, he's like, shut up, bitch.
It's crazy.
And you wonder if it's like a satire at some point, because there's also
genuinely funny comedy in it at points.
Um, it's got Leanna Quigley from return of the living dead.
It's got some of the most gratuitous, like almost like gynecological
shots in it, um, of like nudity and stuff.
And seeing that with a crowd is wild these days, just because
we're so puritanical.
Um, I liked it.
It's an insane movie.
Uh, as far as eighties horror goes, I think it's, I'd up, I'd upgrade
to sort of a lost gym.
I really liked night of the demons.
Um, also one of the only people to survive in it, the black guy, which
is pretty crazy for a horror movie from 1985, um, after that up came idle
hands, a movie I had not seen since the theater, which, uh, I remember loving it.
I really did.
I was pleasantly surprised by how funny it was.
And I was this time around too.
Seth Green's really funny in it.
Devin Sawa, the lead is really funny in it.
Um, it's a guy whose hand gets overtaken by a demon and his friends also are dead,
but they come back from the dead and they get in adventures and try to fuck
Jessica Alba and go to the big high school dance and everything, but there's
a lot of really funny stoner humor in this, uh, it was very well directed.
And I wondered kind of what became of the guy afterwards.
And it wasn't pretty.
And I realized that's because idle hands lost a lot of money because it was a
movie, uh, that was released like three days after Columbine, I read the
Wikipedia and it's a movie where kids are dying high school kids, no less
are dying left and right.
And, uh, it kind of killed his career, which is very unfortunate.
I like idle hands.
You seen that one, Joe?
No, I never saw it.
It came out when I was in college and I was, you know, broke and I didn't see
much in the theater in those days.
And then it got, you know, then I lost track of it, but I'll check it out.
It's really fun.
My, my one grievance is the kid's dad is played by Fred Willard and it's a, the
audience just lit up when he hit the screen and it's a straight role.
He has no comedy in the movie, but he's dead very quickly.
So don't worry about it.
Yeah.
One of the biggest wastes of Fred Willard, surprisingly is Anchorman.
They give him almost nothing funny to do.
And you're like, of all the movies, God damn it.
Anyway, he's got, he's got some stuff on the, uh, on the extended and the, you
know, the cut scenes and stuff, but yeah, I agree.
Um, third up was hack a lantern, which I didn't even look at when it was on Joe
Bob and I remember just being like, this is not worth my time and maybe looking
at my laptop or something, but again, with an audience, this is one, this is
like a room, the room level bad movie.
The villain in it is hilarious, absolutely hilarious.
And it's got weird, creepy incest vibes.
I realized Matt McCarthy told me this actually, but I don't know how I missed
it.
The lead of the movie is Max dad from always sunny who I've never seen really
in anything else, but he's like the lead of it and the movie makes no sense.
It's, it seems like it was translated from another language.
There are huge laughs throughout, but again, watching it at home, you might
not, your results may vary.
Uh, then fourth up was trick or treat, which is one of the great anthology
movies, anthology, horror movies.
I really like it.
Uh, especially like how they tie all the stories together, which is not even
something that a lot of anthology or movies attempt to do.
Um, but I left because it was starting at, you know, two in the morning and I
had just watched it, but trick or treats a great movie.
And if you get a chance to go to one of these, I'm also going to the 80s action
marathon at the new Beverly next month.
They do one a month.
You gotta, you gotta get tickets very quick cause it sells out instantly.
But if you want that whole theater uniting as a group kind of vibe, you
really can't do better than the new Beverly horror fest.
Joe and I went to a fest down at the, uh, the Alamo draft house that was so bad
and so expensive that I never went to that theater again, but the new Beverly
really knows how to do it.
They put up, you know, there's Looney Tunes shorts that are on theme.
We watched something where Sylvester went to hell and Tweety like sent him
there, um, and then they showed three trailers before each movie and you had
to guess the theme.
So like before trick or treat, there was trailers for creep show tales from the
dark side, dead time stories, you know, it's just so much fun.
They, they really are, uh, lovers of, of movies there, and I would recommend
going to one if you've never been, especially horror fans for God's sake.
All right, let's hit it.
The flash, the flash I, uh, well, I mean the, just a breakdown of what this movie
is, obviously we can avoid all the Ezra Miller controversy.
Everybody's very aware of it.
Uh, but this movie is a sequel to Zack Snyder's justice league.
Uh, it's taking Ezra's character as Barry, uh, the flash and showing you
starting the movie with where he is at in his life right now.
Um, where he is at is he is known as the flash.
Uh, he is a famous superhero as all superheroes are in this universe and
the Snyder verse at this point.
Uh, but he is struggling with the fact that his mother was murdered when he
was young and his father is in jail as the prime suspect when his father is
innocent, he's, this is something he's always wanted to fix Barry discovers
early in the movie that if he runs fast enough, he can actually go back in time.
And he decides he is going to do this to try to save his mother's life.
Um, that's basically the plot of the movie.
He does go, but he is warned by Ben Affleck to not do this.
He doesn't does it anyway.
And he ends up in an alternate universe or an alternate reality of the multiverse
where he, a younger, a slightly younger version of himself exists
already pre superpowers, uh, Superman does not exist in this world, but
Supergirl does, uh, and, uh, Batman does exist, but it's Michael Keaton, Batman.
Uh, Zod is attacking.
It's the, it's, it's the moment in which, uh, Zod is attacking the earth.
Uh, but it's an alternate version there.
They explained that there are crossovers in, in, in alternate timelines
where some people are the same.
And in this universe, Zod is still Michael Shannon's odd, but anyway,
they go back to the moment in, in, in Man of Steel when Zod attacks the earth
to find Superman, but in this movie, it's Supergirl anyway.
And then Barry in the meantime, is teaching his younger self on how to get his powers
and how to utilize his powers.
So this movie is doing three things at once.
It's, it's serving as a sequel.
It's serving as an origin story for the flash.
Cause you can see him for the first time gaining his powers and learning them.
And then it's also serving as a major reset for the DC universe.
James Gunn has come in.
Uh, he is, has said they're wiping the slate clean and starting over again.
And this movie is doing that.
And I do think with those three aspects of the movie, it succeeds very well.
It balances all three of those things very, very well.
Um, it can be a little confusing, obviously can be a little bat shit,
obviously, but I do think it succeeds in that department.
Uh, I also personally think I was swept away seeing Keaton back as Batman.
He's doing his little Keaton mannerisms.
There's a scene when they first meet old Bruce Wayne where he's making spaghetti
and he's tasting the spaghetti and doing like Keaton faces and stuff.
And it really was making me laugh.
Um, and just seeing him back in the, in the suit was exciting for me.
You know, I got, I got what I wanted out of this movie, which was another run
with Keaton as Batman that was very action heavy, my gripe, as I've said
many times on this show with Batman returns was that it went too far in
a weird sexual, whatever direction.
It didn't have any of the fun.
I like Batman returns now it's taken a long time for it to grow on me, but
it just didn't have any of the heroics of that original Tim Burton movie.
I thought, and I felt like this did.
It was fun seeing Keaton again in the suit, kicking ass, fucking deflecting
bullets with his cape, getting into the bat plane, they did all kinds of cool
new shit with the bat plane that we never got to see in the original Burton movie.
And there were moments where he springs into action and the Elfman theme kicks
in and it's fucking awesome.
And I got really, really excited.
This all said the movie leans far too heavy into the Ezra Miller comedy.
It does get annoying.
It in fact gets addressed in the movie itself in a very weird meta moment.
But I did not.
He, when he's talking to his younger self, he's like, he says at one point,
he's like, you don't take anything seriously and all you do is make jokes.
And it's really annoying.
And now I know how everybody else feels.
And I was like, that was actually a good moment.
Like he's still lean into it too much.
Was that also an inside thing when he's like the, the, uh, the DC, whatever he
said is, is not, uh, great on mental health.
Trust me.
Do you think that was some allegiance?
Why can't I speak?
You think that was an illusion to him, his mental health struggles
or just part of the movie?
I don't think it was like one of the first scenes.
I don't think it wasn't, but I also think it was the, the
broad stroke joke is like, look at Batman.
He's a fucking psychopath, you know, like, which is the running gag now.
But, um, but, um, you know, I thought it leaned too heavy into the, I
thought also too they could have, this is, and this is a running issue in all
of these types of movies now where they're bringing the old, this is why I
say like, I'm actually happy that some of the critics are pissing and moaning
that Indiana Jones is too dreary.
Let it be dreary.
I want emotional depth in these characters.
These are characters for all intents and purposes, when you put them under a
microscope are extremely egomaniacal.
They're psychotic in many ways.
They're very selfish in many ways, but they're also, that's
also what drives them to be heroes.
I want it to be dark.
I want it to have emotional baggage.
I felt like with Keaton in this, when they say, why aren't you Batman anymore?
He's just like, I did what I had to do.
Gotham doesn't need me anymore.
It's one of the safest cities on the planet.
Okay, fine.
They also find him living in squalor inside Wayne Manor and it's just
chalked up to this is how a guy like this lives when he has nobody
taken care of him anymore.
I'm like, you could have had three lines of dialogue in this where he said,
Alfred died, I have nobody and I was done.
And then that way, when he comes back, it means so much more.
I have a feeling that dialogue was in there somewhere and it got cut because
at the end of the movie, Keaton says when Ezra, I don't want to spoil too much.
Well, fuck it.
These are spoilers that if you want to see it, don't listen anymore.
But at the end of the movie, Keaton's character dies in one of the realities.
And he, he says, Ezra Miller says, I can save you and Keaton's I can bring you
back and Keaton says you already did.
And then he dies.
You're like that line means a lot more.
If you explained to us why the fuck you left and not just, I did a
great job and they don't need me.
That's not sad.
That's not something you need redemption.
So that part, I didn't really understand.
Like these are simple things.
This is the kind of stuff they left out of the new Star Wars movies where I'm
like, God damn it, three fucking lines of dialogue would have made that mean so
much more and made it make sense.
And they leave it out.
Um, yeah, it's possible that they thought they couldn't do a more emotional version
of the Alfred Batman thing than Christopher Nolan did.
I actually found myself tearing up in the dark night rises when Michael
Kane tears up, which in a Batman movie is nuts, but they really landed it.
Now part of that's Michael Kane's an amazing actor, but I, for me, the
Keaton Batman stuff, I mean, I didn't feel anything, you know, I, I felt
like most of the time was spent with him shooting people from a plane.
Um, he did do the, do a little flying and I liked the little parachute
scene with him where he's like, I don't need to parachute or whatever.
But, um, I completely agree.
I, I, and I know I'm going to these movies for the wrong reasons, but the
only way I can attach to these movies is if they go into the characters.
They did a good job of that actually with Ezra Miller and his mother.
That story was kind of touching, you know, it's, it's too much for
this movie probably to handle.
But I thought they handled that pretty well to be real.
Um, the Batman stuff, what you're saying about Alfred is a hundred percent right.
Give us something.
I didn't buy that the Bruce Wayne of Batman is now a slob with
like pizza boxes on the floor.
And also, why is he an amazing, if there's pizza boxes and beer bottles everywhere.
Why is he what it cut out in amazing shape, you know, like, I guess they
didn't want to have him with a big pot belly or something, but it's like, this
is a guy who's 65 who were to believe has just let himself go to shit, but
he still looks great.
Um, they did give him the long hair, but then again, this opening scene where
he's doing all these karate moves around his house and throwing stuff at them.
Um, I'm like, I'm not looking at Michael Keaton even it's just a stunt
man with gray hair covering his face.
And that's kind of how I felt throughout is that I was looking at Michael Keaton
either being superimposed into scenes or flying something or driving something.
And I just didn't get enough that I wanted.
There are two moments where he says exact lines from Batman.
You want to get nuts, let's get nuts.
And then of course I'm Batman, but man, they did not have the impact on me
that I thought they would.
And I love, those are my favorite superhero movies.
The first two Batman movies.
Why I love Batman returns is because it's a, it's a whole different thing.
It's got a different flavor.
It's like, let's look at the really fucked up psyche of Batman and these two
villains, you know, let's get their origins.
Let's get what made them the way they are.
And that's why I respond to that once so much, you know, it's always great to see
Michael Keaton, but I just can't say it was like a triumphant moment for me when
he, when he came back into this, maybe if I didn't know he was in it, it would
have been cool, but you know, everyone knows everything now there are some
cameos I was, I was not expecting.
There's also like a trip to the wax museum at the end where they're showing
you like, you know, a hologram of Christopher Reeve and stuff, which I
just found weird.
Um, Hey, I remember that, that guy.
I remember that guy.
I remember that guy was just a weird bit.
I thought that that was a cool moment.
Um, you know, it didn't have any real significance other than it was showing
you that a multiverse existed and it was DC saying like, we're, you know, it
all crosses over, which by the way, DC.
Invented the multiverse in comics.
They did it before Marvel.
Everybody thinks Marvel did it for it.
They didn't, but, um, I thought that was just a kind of a cool moment.
It was fun seeing the Nicholas cage Superman, uh, and he went
back to him many times.
Yeah.
And he was fighting a spider, which was the big Kevin Smith story that the
executive wanted him fighting a spider for no reason.
So I thought that was funny.
Yeah.
And then my favorite part of the whole movie.
And I was, I saw this when we were, when I was on the road with the
jokers, me and, uh, Q went to go see this together, we were laughing really
hard at the very last moment where Ezra Miller thinks he's back in his reality
again, and then he gets his D actually proves his dad's innocence and his dad
gets out of jail with this wonderful moment and Bruce Wayne calls him and
says, congrats, and he's all excited.
And there's all these people crowding Bruce Wayne's car cars.
He's about to get out and it starts playing the Burton theme again.
And you're like, Holy shit.
It's going to be Keaton.
He's not dead and he's not back in his universe.
And then it's George Clooney.
And I thought that that was really, really funny.
Uh, it was just a really fun, funny moment.
Yeah.
It's one of the rare, I hate cameos used as punch lines, which has been all
comedy is for about 20 years now, but that was, you know, when you have
George Clooney and he's just there for that little moment.
I love that too.
I think that could have thrown a bone to Val Kilmer, even though I know he's ill.
But yeah, those end jokes, the end jokes about, um, Eric Stoltz
playing Marty McFly were fun.
I don't think they needed to go back to that again.
And that's really my issue in a, in a movie where you're not telling
us what happened to Alfred and making that emotional connection and stuff.
Why are you going so hard into comedy?
And that is this movie's issue.
Ezra Miller is in a dual role for the entire film.
And I find Ezra Miller, when he was a kid, I mean, we need to talk about Kevin.
I think that's maybe the best child performance of all time.
He's, he exudes evil in a way I've never seen a kid do before.
Um, but I don't, I don't love him or hate him as an actor.
I don't personally care about anything he did.
I just know that he is not a gifted comedic actor and him playing both
like a dumb 18 year old and then like a slightly less dumb 24 year old.
We're not talking to Keaton in multiplicity found a way to give you a
different flavor with each of those characters.
Ezra Miller really doesn't.
You've got this screechy annoying guy who was the centerpiece of your movie.
Then you double him and make him do broad comedy, which is not his strong
suit.
So the very first scene of this movie is like a wacky sitcom style bit at
Starbucks where he's placing his order.
And I was like, I'm not going to be able to finish this thing.
It did get better from there, but the comedy in it is pretty tough
throughout and it's rampant.
I mean, it's hard to take anything seriously because it's, it's easily as
jokey as the Marvel stuff.
Now that's probably the DC heads saying guys, they think we're too serious,
too depressing, too dour.
Uh, we got to spruce it up, but to me it was a little too much.
Um, I love that.
I loved super girl.
I thought super girl was awesome.
Who was that at first?
I thought it was the girl from, um, the act.
What's her name?
Yeah, no, it's not her.
It's she's, she's, she's a working actor, but I don't, she's not like a
household name.
I think she will be soon, but she's, she was excellent.
She was awesome.
That was just an awesome take on the character.
Uh, and I'm glad that she apparently is in talks to do more as super girl.
Cause I was like, I want to see more of that.
That was awesome.
Um, you know, overall I'd say my takeaway of the movie is, you know, it got me
where I needed to be with Keaton.
That was enough for me.
Would I watch this move?
Would I buy this movie?
No.
Would I watch it again?
Yeah.
In theory.
Um, would I watch the Keaton parts again?
Absolutely.
Um, but you know, sadly this is where we're at.
Like, you know, I thought I really loved it and maybe I did because it swept me
away for the two and a half hours.
I was in the theater, but I gotta admit as Pat talked to me more and I talked
to Q more about it, cause Q was like, wait, so who killed his mom?
They never told us, right?
Right.
I was like, yeah, maybe that's another part too.
I don't know, but.
Yeah.
And he was like, well, in the comics it's reverse flash.
And I was like, yeah.
And they were kind of doing reverse flash at the end where he confronts himself
and he's become this like twisted version of himself because he keeps trying
to fix everything and it's damaging him.
And I was like, but then they never went anywhere with that.
And then I started to really think about like, wait a minute, why didn't they?
And then the, then then it becomes that thing where the more I thought about it,
I was like, you know what, this probably isn't really a good movie.
I just really liked the Keaton parts and that's kind of where I'm at.
I would say my hog is straight out on this one, uh, you know, and I hope
that they utilize Keaton more and that's kind of, I could care less if I ever
see Ezra again as the flash and I want to see more Supergirl so that hog
straight out for me on the flash.
And my, you know, as you came down on it in the time since you've seen it, I've
slightly up on it.
My hog is down, but the kind of down where maybe you just took a piss and it's
sort of like longer and thicker than normal, but, um, it's not hard by any means.
I liked it, this multiverse thing.
So my big issue with, with these superhero movies and maybe it's dumb,
but it really is my issue is that when you're watching eight, they're always
two and a half to three hours now.
Uh, and when you were watching a movie that long.
And if any of your characters dies, they can all come back to life because
of they're like a the incredible Hulk or they're a superhero or whatever.
That takes all stakes out of it.
And I don't care.
Now, when you add in the multiverse where you know that anyone can, can be
living in 12 different, you know, somebody could have died in a movie in
1978 and come back now into the multiverse.
Why do I care?
You know, there are no stakes to that to me.
And everybody just punching each other and shooting each other
has no stakes and no effect.
That's my issue.
That's my hangup.
And maybe I need to just get past that if I want to keep seeing these movies.
But the multiverse is exhausting to me, especially when into the spider
verse, I gotta say did such a beautiful job and it is animation granted, but
they did such a beautiful job of making every single place they go in the
multiverse feel different and new and creative and visually spectacular and
exciting.
This movie is pretty ugly.
The CGI in this movie for the most part is pretty ugly.
And it looks like an Xbox, you know, or something.
It just didn't, didn't hold me in that way.
I will say though, they did a good job of the emotional beats of the flash that
when you mentioned Ron Livingston and that story with trying to find the real
killer, they, they handled it well, you know, those are real emotional moments
that land and they're not, um, just like stupid, you know, bullshit.
They actually tried to make them connect and I think they succeeded.
So the flash is not a disaster, but it's not great in my opinion.
We'll be back with probably the boogie.
Well, no Indies early July boogie man.
It will either be doing the boogie.
I haven't seen boogie man yet.
I'm trying to see it this week.
I know you are too.
So, um, or did you see it?
I haven't either, but yeah, if my guess is, uh, if we don't see it by.
Thursday, it's going to leave theaters.
So hopefully we'll go see the boogie man and get back to you on that one.
We got Indy coming up.
We got all the big summer movies coming up.
I'm on Instagram at the Patrick Walsh.
The Ms.
Pat show is now streaming on BET plus and studios.
Please pay us our money so we can get off strike.
Thank you.
Uh, Joe DeRosa comedy, Instagram and Twitter, uh, Joe DeRosa .com.
Uh, Philadelphia.
The theater of the living arts.
It's happening November 11th.
Biggest show I've ever done in Philly.
Biggest show I've ever done ever.
Uh, pre -sale is happening now through my website.
Use promo code Rose garden.
Uh, and many new dates are coming soon.
Also my new album, the penthouse papers selected readings is out
now on a special thing records.
Get that digitally wherever you get your digital stuff.
Uh, and then we will have an announcement for this show coming
soon about a fall live, uh, podcast performance.
It sounds like, so we'll keep you posted on that.
We'll see you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.