I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell
And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say
I'll see you in hell, you know I will
Folks, it's we'll see you in hell
We're back, we're back, we're back
To talk about American fiction
We're back, a dinosaur's story, remember that?
Mm -hmm
Don't they all talk about the kids?
That won't get to see Jurassic Park and they have big stupid animated dinosaurs for them
But nobody went
Didn't they die at the end?
No, that was the land before time
Okay
That was actually kind of cool land before time but they made like 100 sequels to it
Yeah, I didn't give a shit about any of it
Have you seen any of these clips of fucking Austin Butler still talking in the Elvis voice?
I've heard about this but I've not seen it
He actually seems to be doing a Brad Pitt impression more like he's just
It's really sad to watch in my opinion but
They ask him like what was your favorite movie when you were a kid and no matter who you ask
Robert De Niro or whoever it was a letterboxed event or something
Their eyes light up and they really think back to when they were a kid and what movie they liked
And they ask him and he's like
I guess I'd have to see the good the bad and the ugly
You know that definitely would have been one of my favorites
Mm -hmm
Shut your fucking mouth
A three -hour western Austin and how old are you nine that was your favorite you dunce
I really hate everything
What's an album that you really love that an album you really like and he goes
I have to say the one I've really been jamming on lately is In Rainbows by Radiohead
It's just it's got every texture every he goes that or Chet Baker sings
Which is an album like that Woody Allen uses like from the 1950s
And then Chameleon sitting next to him he goes that album is so good. It's so good
And I realized I'm old. I realized watching that interview that I'm old. I wanted to strangle them both
You're not old. They just suck
You don't feel that way about every
Young person and you would have felt that way about them when you were young. That's the difference. Yeah
That's the difference in this new one i'm playing sort of the king of the worms
Isn't austin butler english
No, I don't think so. I think he's just a dude
But boy, he's doing that Elvis hard. He's doing it real hard
Um, what do I think of zendaya? Oh, she's just a queen
Oh, she's she's just a queen you want to see this tennis movie where she fucks two dudes at once or whatever
Hell yeah. Oh god, why because I miss sex in the movies joe
Yeah, but it won't be good sex no, it'll be dry as a bone
No, if there is nudity, it'll be like a floppy dong
You know this this movie in the 80s would have been a romp like a zany tennis school
Yeah, but he is called like getting bald, you know
Yeah, yeah, you're you're served
Yeah, they made a bunch of them and I used to sneak them out of the video star hard bodies
Uh hard bodies, too
Uh, then there was they were ones that had big stars. There was a fraternity vacation with johnny depp
Bunch of them. I used to watch all all nudity
per day
Well, the first breaths I saw were in a movie called hamburger the motion picture. Oh, yeah, that was a good one
I think jim varney was in it. No really today where they were talking about how for years, uh
Carrot top wanted to
remake earnest
Like look i'm not gonna sit here in bad mouth carrot top and you know, I love earnest
Why would carrot top remake earnest? They're larry the cable guy remaking earnest, even though I would hate it makes sense
I
Mean sure casting wise but I guess carrot top was a big fan and was like I can do it
That's my assumption. But you know
You don't remake you don't remake a character
that somebody else
has uh, uh
Uh, what is the term? Uh immortalized it's like you I I don't mean like like you can recast
Han solo as as much as fans may say that sacrilege you can do it harrison ford didn't invent han solo
He just perfected it
Jim varney is verne
It's an odd thing to do. No, he's earnest or earnest. I mean
But but do you see what i'm saying? It's like, yeah, it's odd to to to recreate a thing
That that the guy that's only been done by the guy who created it
Something you could say that they do it they do it with like the pink panther
But they rarely do it successfully, but that's not created
By uh peter cellars. He just played the character
So
I'm trying to think of another exam. It's like it's like being like i'm gonna make a dame edna movie
Where i'm gonna be dame edna. It's like no the guy that made it obviously didn't happen for a reason
But yeah, I mean, I don't know why he thought he'd be the guy
It was because he's character needed money problem
um
I don't think that that it was a money play but pat i'm gonna push back on that and
That that carrot tops the idea for a fast buck was remaking earnest
Yeah, I guess he does. All right, people see his veg fucking
Kind of ralph crammed in scheme is that I can't miss i'll be back on top
Um
I picture him blowing a rail of coke the the size of the county state line
I know what i'm gonna play earnest. Okay carrot. Just I want to see austin butler's earnest
um, I was gonna say I gotta ask you one question do you uh
Do you know what I mean bern?
Hamburger the motion picture no relation to hot dog the motion picture. No, that's a ski picture
What was hamburger?
And then there's ski patrol which had I believe two of my uh, my old co -stars leslie jordan and martin mull
What was hamburger that wasn't skiing as well?
Hamburger if if memory serves had jim barney in it, but it was one of these where it was a secret hamburger recipe
And there were they made girls horny. I think it was that stupid like they just took their tops off. It was that bad
Jesus christ on international woman's day. We're discussing this the plot of I mean this was in my lifetime, too
This was in the 80s
All right look up the so that's just might just be my sweet imagination
Let me look at the actual plot of hamburger the motion picture
1986 teen sex comedy this would have been on my friend who had cable so a few years after that
Um russell procco
Has been expelled from multiple schools because of his crude behavior predominantly having women throw themselves at him even when he is in no mood
He was given a large trust fund, but his grandfather's will stipulated that it is frozen
God, this was the plot of so many movies unless he earns a college diploma
While trying to mull over his problem at a local buster burger owned by a friend of his who said he had a similar problem
And that he earned the equivalent of a college diploma after finishing buster burger university
Russell agrees that this may be his way to get the trust fund unfrozen. This sounds way more boring than I thought
Uh, and jim barney is not even involved. I was wrong
Um
So there you go the memory is a tricky thing I just saw a headline on uh
Movie web
The movie I was thinking of was fast food
That was jim varney and that is about a secret sauce at a fast food restaurant that makes people horny
So, um, I got it mixed up. I just saw a headline on movie web
Yeah
Surfing the net over there the no i'm just looking through it for a new psycho
But I saw this other headline the difference between wicked and oz the great and powerful
Explanation
Okay
Do we need this? This is what I don't know. It's who's confused
Who the fuck even remembers oz the great and powerful?
These articles are just getting wild. I mean it's like when I
I see that they are clickbait, but it's like who if people really want this then society is doomed
Um, this is the headline I was looking for because I knew I had a new psycho over here
And I couldn't remember because I forgot to write it down
Zack snider thinks batman
Uh, zack snider thinks batman not killing is making the dc icon irrelevant
So
Snider thinks that batman's no killing rule is is causing dc to make zack. Can you go away?
Can you go away?
Haven't we had enough zack of your dark take on everything like I I defended this guy forever and I liked
He's insisting that rebel moon is a lost masterpiece as are many in our patreon comments, by the way
You gotta love when the guy that made it is saying it's a it's a lost masterpiece. Yeah, exactly
I mean this 200 million dollar movie really slipped through the cracks
What did
Who what does what secrets does this man have on the industry that he's just continually?
I mean a passion a fan base will get you far in life
I guess
I guess where's the fan base showing up to give him a good rotten tomato score?
Yeah, uh, yeah
Did rebel moon get a good audience score? I don't think so. No, not at all
Got a good his fan base score who are like do or die
Yeah, but but that would mean that the that the audience score and rotten tomatoes would be good because they would have but no
His fans don't make up the entire world
Well, but the fans have proved in a toxic or non -toxic direction that they can they can review bomb something to the point
That it sways the score greatly. It's only at a 58
Yeah, I mean, I don't know. I can't imagine watching it after that last whenever that one was zombie one army of zombie army of the dead
Yeah, that was tough. That was tough. Oh, yeah
I'm exhausted for this shit
I I got my new 4k of blood simple the cohen brothers classic that started it all
and uh
It looks fantastic
It is after all though a independent movie a lower budget movie. So it's one of those 4ks that
No while being a huge upgrade. It's not like it looks immaculate or something. It's very filmic
But um, I feel like it's a cohen brothers one movie that a lot of people haven't seen
It's really great. It's it's
The early punk version of something that they perfected many times over down the line
But kind of have you seen blood simple jim? Yeah only once
Yeah
I love it. I really do. I think it's because I saw it so young and I think I saw raising arizona
And then this maybe those were the first two
but um
It's john gets who I like but he was kind of boring. It's dan hadaya who I always love
M m at walsh steals the movie as like a scumbag in a yellow suit and then early early francis mcdormand
But it's your classic, you know guys sleeping with his boss's wife and and film noir and back double crossing and etc
But it's shot so cool. It's it's when they were with barry sonnenfeld
which is when I think the cohen's kind of made their most exciting looking movies because sonnenfeld
You know up before he became a director was one of the most
Consistent he made so many great movies as a cinematographer
Uh in addition to the cohen's but he did raising arizona when harry met sally blah blah blah on and on and this movie
Looks awesome. Um
The twists keep coming. I love it. There's so much in it that
I dug it's actually a movie that made hollywood at the time
Want the cohen brothers to be action directors?
Joel silver really wanted them to make an action movie and that wound up being the hud sucker proxy
They took his money and did not make an action movie for him. That's but um, that's what they did, you know
Even back in those days. It would be like just like what they do now
Let's try to take this great interesting young filmmaker and make them something they're not but you just back then could never do
That with the cone the uh, the cohen's
I'm excited and also scared to see what happens to them as separate entities because I don't hear a lot of raves about this
driveaway dolls movie
um
And I don't know why you would break up a good thing after 30 years of the best movies
but we'll see where it goes and also the um
What's their faces are breaking up?
Who?
Uncut joms
Oh, they are safty brothers. Yeah, they're going they're going their own way as well. Yeah
Pat I want you to look in the chat at the picture. I just sent
If you don't mind sure
I can't I can't stop thinking about this
Now that is a
So is this i'll give you the background I watched um, I watched one of those youtube things like upcoming movie trailers 2024
Yeah
Uh, I watched it last night
uh some
Sort of exciting looking things. There's a new shamalan produced
Uh horror movie coming out that looks kind of cool
Um
About these invisible monsters that are watching people in a room or something. I can't remember what it's called
There's also a sequel to twister coming out called twisters with none of the returning cast
30 years in the night away. I think they got hunt actually joe
I think hunts hunt in the ends like i'll tell you something about tornadoes
Okay. Oh, oh she's gonna come in like linda blair at the end of believer
um
So anyway
one of the
Trailers is this movie called I think it's called saga
Uh an american
No horizon an american saga is the name of the thing. So it's kevin costner movie. I'm watching this thing
I'm like that's his like two -part epic, right?
Yeah, and i'm like man
They haven't made a movie like this in a long time like one of these big like period piece like
You know look like dances with wolves or the postman or or one of the many costner films
Yeah, and i'm like, you know, these were never my type of movie
But this this is i'm interested that they actually made another one of these and they keep cutting to
jamie campbell who was the second lead in the film
And I mean look at him. He looks like he just walked off a fucking runway
After a spray tan. I truly don't know who jamie campbell is and when you sent me this picture
I did not know who this was. I assume this was a cw show about pilgrims
Hot pilgrims the entire trailer everything looks super authentic and then it keeps cutting away to jamie campbell because clearly
These fucking studios
have to put
Like a panty dropper and everything they can't who is he who's he from some young actor? I don't fucking know
He's uh, he looks ridiculous. He's even prettier than like lido
He's the guy from uh, I think he was in that hold on now. We know him from stuff. Hold on. I'll tell you in a second
He's the guy from he was in stranger things
Okay, uh
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah, okay
He's the weird guy in the institute in stranger things that turns into the monster
Oh, yeah, you can just see i'm like kevin. You gotta get somebody young in there somebody from stranger things
All right, who's available? But it just drives me crazy. Of course instagram. He's got 4 .5 million followers a guy that nobody
Seemingly knows by name
um
But it just drives me crazy. It's like guy. Oh, he was in harry potter. So I guess that's maybe where he got his first
whatever, but um
It's like
Put the pretty guy in there fine make it look real guys
Can he not have highlights?
What are we doing? What are we doing? It's ridiculous chin
I complained about this about the we talked about the northman last episode and I complained about this in the northman
It didn't bother you bothered me
You're gonna have plastic surgery a thousand times over nicole kidman as the lee as the queen in a fucking viking barbarian
What are we doing guys? What are we doing?
Yeah, I think the black and white helped that for me. What's your what's your color most of the movie?
There's a lot of black and white well
And a lot of color too most of kidman was was being dubs
I don't I don't think so unless i'm misremembering the film. I think you're thinking of the lighthouse
Kidman's not in the lighthouse. No, no, no, i'm saying the the northman wasn't in black and white. It was in color
All right, but i'm saying there's some there's some black and white now. I gotta watch it again. All right, fair enough
But my point is is I mean just for god's sakes guys. Can we just have a little?
I
Don't know this shit just bugs me man. It just really does like it's I don't know
Yeah, the tray I watched some trailers the other day and I was like
I guess i'll just be because we're hitting the point where there's nothing going to be coming out because nothing got made for a while
Yeah
Anyway, what do you got? Uh, you want to go to that movie corner? We did I did blood simple now
Oh, I didn't realize that was the beginning. Ah, Jesus
I'm sorry. Sorry now. I feel bad. I'm no fucking good
Well, I will start with high praise of something. How about that? Sure
I am watching and i'm fully caught up. I only have the finale to go and it hasn't been released yet. So i'm fully caught up
Feud capote versus the swans. This is the best piece of television I have seen in years
Did you watch the other feud which I very much enjoyed? I did not see the first feud
I thought I didn't care about this one. I wasn't even going to watch it. Oh man. It's amazing. It's amazing
I can't say enough good stuff every single cast member in this hits a home run
uh
But stealers of the show
Are I got to pull up the cast here because I don't want to I don't want to leave anybody out
And they're all actors for the most part that I already know
but uh
stealing the show
is uh
Tom hollander as truman capote who literally is a different human being
Yeah in this in this show. I can't even get over it
We're easy to think we need another capote but but i'll take your word. I'll take your word
I agree. That's why I initially didn't really care because I was like well
How many capote things are they going to do this this but I will say this the capote capote?
Every capote project is focused on a different part of his life
The movie with philip seymour hoffman focused on the in cold blood phase this focuses on after that
Him
Starting to write the book answered prayers the betrayal of these socialites in new york that he referred to as his swans
And the feud that ensues
uh, it really
Hones in on his severe alcoholism. It's very dark. It's very funny at times
Uh, and it's very heartbreaking at times. It's amazing, but the tom hollander as truman capote is is outstanding
diane lane, uh
Is the other?
In my opinion show stealer i've never seen her play somebody like vicious and conniving and manipulative before
And man is she fucking amazing
Naomi watts fantastic
Uh, uh molly ringwald fantastic
uh
Very fun seeing treat williams and callista flockhart
um
R .I .P. True williams. Yeah, uh, and and there's you know, chloe zevignet zevignet demi more. There's it's just a great cast
Um, it's it's expertly written. It is extraordinarily well directed, especially in the pilot by gus van sant
um
I'm just it's an amazing amazing amazing show
I haven't seen a show like this in a long time that immediately got its hooks in me
And I was like, oh my god, like I have to watch all of this right now
um
It's fantastic. I can't wait for the finale. I can't wait to see how it all comes together in the end
All right. Yeah, I had zero interest until you said that now, but I usually like I like the uh fossey one
I like all that stuff. So i'll give it a shot
Yeah, you know the fossey is not a feud I thought that too it's not that's true, but it's in that vein
I love the true crime ones. Whatever. Those are the people versus oj. I love the one about the the fashion guy loved
um
versace
I
On my 4k kick
continued with after hours scorsese's after hours, I
Have long held on to my dvd of this movie which was only available as part of some scorsese box set
Um weirdly a really hard movie to come by and usually that's because of music rights
But the movie doesn't have that much like hard to come by music in it
I don't know what was going on really with after hours, but it was a fairly cheap independent movie made by
Scorsese to sort of prove that he still had it if you can believe it
But after a few failures, uh, new york new york with the nero and lisa minnelli
These aren't failures by anybody else's standards. They're amazing movies, but he lost a bunch of money
Sure
And he said I want to do this little tiny movie by the guy who wrote vampire's kiss
Which is the movie where nicolas cage eats the cockroach?
And they're both very similar. They both have really similar
Uh looks at life as being a horrific wasteland especially
Life as a young single man in new york city
And clearly the guy had some issues
But you can see why a very coked out depressed down his luck martin scorsese would relate to this movie
There is something really kind of ugly and depressing about it, even though it is a comedy
I don't laugh out loud a bunch at it. I just find it really fascinating. I think a lot of people put it on the same
Conversation as king of comedy, but I think king of comedy is a much better much funnier much more entertaining movie
Uh much deeper movie this movie is really just a guy out in new york
Having a series of bad encounters with women which led people to label it
Misogynistic, but if you date a lot in new york or los angeles or anywhere
You'll find a lot of bad women or a lot of bad men really everybody he encounters in this movie is nuts
It's a real kind of kafka -esque as they say journey where things get worse and worse until it's literally down to him
Falling to his knees and saying like what do you want from me?
Lord is how bad this night gets I had many a night in new york that felt like that
And i've had many a night in la that felt like that
The movie is not quite the masterpiece that everyone wants it to be and says that it is
Um
But I love it there is something really fascinating about it
I think a big part of it is as much as I like griffin dunn
It's hard to get that excited about a griffin dunn movie, but the supporting cast is terry garr
Katherine o 'hara john hurd, you know, it's full of all kinds of great people
Um, and it's scorcese having fun at a low budget. You rarely get to see that
So if you've never seen it now's the time the 4k criterion looks amazing check it out joe
Yeah, I I agree with your take. I think it's an interesting enough movie, but i'm not a big fan
I feel it's I feel it's scorcese's most overrated underrated movie
It's the one that everybody says is the lost classic and I I just don't agree. It's
It's a little too straightforward and it's a little too claustrophobic in my opinion
Um, but it but it's clearly not trying to be it doesn't feel small enough for how small it is
Um and big enough for how big it's trying to be
um
I uh
I think that it it is though it is the prototype
I will say
um, it's the prototype for this became like a sort of a genre of film or subgenre of film of
the guy that
It's kind of like the honestly not kidding
It's kind of the prototype for like harold and kumar like the guy living this mundane life
Who yeah needs a break and then get in in pursuit of that little break
His world is turned absolutely upside down
All for it to just sort of date a few years later with bruce willis and kim bassinger was that
Meet the parents in a lot of ways is that just somebody's kind of yeah somebody's night getting worse and worse for sure
All three i'm doing are 4ks that are kind of pioneers blood simple was the first of the cohen's thing
Uh after hours, yes, and then third i'm gonna be doing
Main streets, which of course was kind of the start of the scorsese deal. But yeah, go ahead. Yeah
The uh, but yeah, it's um, it's very interesting to me
because uh, they're they're you know, as I was saying there's that
weird subgenre
And and a key component to that subgenre is the next morning
The guy has to end up back in his mundane position
Right where nobody around him is any the wiser and he kind of has this little secret now of you know
You'll never guess what happened to me last night
Yeah
This is I feel like this was supposed to
I'll make this my number two because i'm talking about it at length, but I feel like this this was supposed to
Launch
Um
I I mean not that griffin dunn and rosanna arquette did not become very established
They did but I feel like this movie was really supposed to cement them as stars. I mean they're they're on the poster
They are the two leads. I love rosanna arquette, uh her and griffin dunn from the jump
We're always just too weird to be big movie stars
Like you just don't they work in this movie great, but they don't have the chops to be like carrying big movies
I don't think either one of them. I I yeah, they're a little too offbeat or eccentric or something. Um, you know funny enough
Uh, so the supporting roles in this are the movie are the people that became much more popular so to speak terry gar
Right, you know, uh, just to name one and then the smallest role ends up being the biggest of everybody katherin o 'hara
She's got this tiny part in this
Cheech and chong. Yeah, cheech and chong, right? But you know, um
Yeah after hours, I I agree with you on your take. Um, you go ahead and then i'll do my third
Okay. Yeah, i'll do uh
The latest 4k i've been mostly trying out the new 4ks lately because they're coming hard and fast. That's what he said
That's what she said. I got me in streets and i'm hoping
praying that criterion is going to continue down this path of doing all the scorsese greats because we are really do
A special spruced up edition of casino goodfellas cape fear
King of comedy. I got
I got goodfellas 4k. It's out
You got it in 4k, but it's like a it's like one of the first 4ks and there's not much special on it
You know what I mean? Like we're just we're doing some upgrades like i'm really excited about the cameron ones coming out
I know you're not joe, but those are big ones coming out next week
Um the you're talking about the kirk cameron religious
Movie box left behind two and then uh, the one left behind with uh, jesus and him as buddies
Jesus flying a plane or something something with jesus in a plane. I don't remember i'll never leave you behind kirk
I uh
Look, i'm gonna be real with you. So all three of these after hours
Blood simple and mean streets are all movies that I have held in the highest of regard my entire life
When I used to kill the boredom in class
I used to make my 100 favorite movie list and I would edit it and make it every single day in class
And these movies would always be somewhere on the list and I think it's just because deep down
I knew them to be considered the greats or considered to be really influential or whatever
but
Looking at all three. I think blood simple became
much better movies later on I think the cohens
were
Amazingly confident and great out of the gate and made an awesome first debut movie
However, i'd rather watch
Fargo miller's crossing raising arizona. No country for old men serious men, etc. Etc
uh after hours, I think is maybe my
14th favorite martin scorsese movie, you know
And just because more people don't love it doesn't mean I suddenly rank it as my favorite
And lastly with mean streets not to do it on another scorsese, but
I think the man got got sort of better as he went
I think taxi driver and raging bull as his touchstones are his early masterpieces
And the other stuff is kind of hit and miss more interesting we talked about alice doesn't live here anymore
Which I like more than joe, but you know, not a perfect movie, etc, etc
but mean streets
It's the template it's everything that he does later
infinitely better
The only thing that I can say I really love about mean streets and the stuff that stayed with me and I remembered
Was a a young exciting horny crazy robert de niro
Which is fun to watch and be way more animated than he is today
And be the great uses of classic rock music be it the stones be it whatever else
Which mostly are just kind of scenes of harvey kytel dancing around a bar and like cool music playing
it's all
flashy and fun and cool
But to me mean streets leaves almost zero impression. I gotta say
This is definitely not nowhere near my top 10 favorite scorsese movies mean streets
I've been holding it in too high a regard
But if you're a fan and i'm a fan i've seen it 10 times don't i'm not saying I don't like the movie
I'm saying it's not top tier scorsese. The 4k looks incredible, especially for like a 50th anniversary release
Uh, check it out for that reason. But yeah, I was surprised to say mean streets for me
Doesn't hold up
um, I yeah, I mean look I I I wouldn't disagree i'm um
I've never been a huge mean streets fan. I appreciate it for what it is. It's the it's the first, you know
It's the first album
Mean streets is the prototype for what what is to come as you said it sets the stage for for all of his new york
gangstery whatever stuff that he's going to do and uh, and
You know up there should be a box set of mean streets goodfellas casino and the irishman like those all go together
and
in their own ways
What not the departed?
No, because it's not
I'm talking about the stuff he does that deals with very much the italian mob sure whatever specifically
and um
You know, they all they all fit together in their own ways
But the mean streets very much plays like the first record that's done on the four track and then and then the the later ones get
In the right ways more elaborate and better and bigger
um, but
The the the performances are what saved the movie
um, or what make the movie I should say but um, but you know, it's it's
Scorsese to me is always better when he has some breathing room
uh, even though sometimes it bites him in the ass, but um
You know, it's why I
It's why I like bringing out the dead, but I don't love it. You know, i'm just like yeah, it's interesting cool
You know, it's it's it's that kind of movie
uh to me
Yeah, but see like what always would have been sacrilege and what I never would have said when I was going to film school
At age 21 or whatever is that?
I prefer bringing out the dead to main streets. I'd rather watch bringing out the dead
I don't blame you. It's like fucking people that say clerks is the best kevin smith movie
It's not it's not by a long shot dogma is 900 times a better movie. It's funnier. It's better directed
It's better acted, but people have to go no, but the thing in the beginning with it. Shut up. Shut up
You know, uh, you know, so mean street. I agree with you on mean streets. I I agree. I like it but but yeah, you're not
There are a few aside from
I'm a mook that part. What am I a mook?
What's a mook aside from that scene? Like there's no real scene in mean streets where people are going
Oh, you got to see the scene where this happens, you know, it's just kind of like it's kind of it's very it's like
The pope of greenwich village. I actually like the pope of greenwich village a little bit better to be honest
I like it more than mean streets, too
I had very similar movie though
It really and I think it says a lot to how pristine and amazing these movies look
I gotta say because all three of these kind of like took me back to when I watched them for the first time
At mean streets
I remember watching with my dad and I had built it up so much
Because it was number seven in my hundred greatest movies of all time book
And I couldn't believe my dad was gonna let me watch it because I was only like 13 and I left the room during the nudity scenes
but
All I remember from that viewing was just people walking in the back of their heads to like cool music
And sure enough, you know 30 years later. That's all that really sticks with me still
It's kind of a style over substance movie
They criticized scorsese of that later and they're wrong, but I think in mean streets you could just say
It's almost like an extension of his student films and a great filmmaker sort of finding his style
And what's special about his storytelling which is talking about his neighborhood and his people
but yeah
by the way
Speaking of deserving of a 4k
Hope of greenwich village. I don't even think there's a fucking blu -ray release of this movie. Oh, I don't know that there is
Yeah, there's there's a double feature where you where you have to take desperate hours with it
That's what I have and I actually I sold it for like 80 bucks. Yeah, it's desperate hours sucks currently selling for
$65 on ebay
desperate hours has a scene
in it where
Kelly lynch, I think maybe this woman that was married to stephen sigal. She's running out of a courtroom
She's playing a lawyer and her
Hit falls out of her blouse her bare tit and it's not commented on she just puts it back away
And they continue on with the dramatic scene
Okay, and I was like did that just happen organically and william friedkin is such a perv. He kept it in probably
Wait, did he even do desperate hours? I have no idea. I've never seen it looking it up. It's a the most average movie
It's not great
Oh, it was it was chimino michael chimino the guy who did the deer hunter
Oh, okay
I might actually buy the $10 vhs of pope of greenwich village
That's a vhs movie. That's for sure. Um, all right
on to today's
Topic speaking of small films character films
Simple stories, uh american fiction I think fits into that genre. This is a comedy
Starring the great
great jeffrey wright
who
In my opinion could arguably be our finest living actor. Uh, I put him
you know, I mean these days he him
him rockwell and uh
Him and rockwell my two faves, I
uh can't get it
Oh denzel's my all -time favorite, but um
uh, this is a this is sort of
Sort of like the movie bamboozled, uh, but it's about a black writer
who
Is very mad at the publishing industry because the publishing industry seems to only be publishing authors
that
exploit the the pain
of the black experience in america
And and nothing else he's very upset about that slavery trauma porn, etc. Yeah
um
Issa ray plays
Yes, i'm sorry or issa ray, excuse me plays. This is really funny. Her name is oh no
I'm reading it wrong. It's sin tara golden. I thought it was sinatra golden. I was like, that's really funny. Uh
sin tara golden she plays the the premiere like best -selling new author on the scene
and um, and he's he's quite cross about that
And and and also cross about the subject matter of her book
uh
So anyway, he eventually writes
Scathingly
Uh what is a fake memoir of of an ex -convict who talks about like basically killing his own father and
And he's exploiting all the worst aspects
of of of the struggle of of certain black people in america
And he's doing it as a fuck you
But his publisher ends up sending out the manuscript
Uh, it ends up getting a lot of traction and all of a sudden he finds fame
And he has to now pretend to be this person kind of behind closed doors because he wrote it under a pseudonym
He can't actually reveal that he is the the person that that wrote this blah blah blah. It's sort of like the movie the hoax
Uh with richard gear. It's sort of like
It's sort of like a lot of movies it's sort of like, uh, hollywood shuffle
You mentioned bamboozled. Yes. Um, it's sort of like the
Okay, if they like racist shit will out racist them and give them what they want. It's also kind of the producers
You know, we want something that's going to close right away. So we'll push bad taste whatever. Yeah
And to me I think and this is a problem for me and i've talked about it with joe on the show before
Where like
You can't help it and especially living in la or especially getting the the screeners
That you just start to build up resentment toward movies just because they get shoved down your throat so much every time you open your email
There's like a new email from american fiction. I get 10 a day. I have four copies of the blu -ray sitting in my house right now
And you just get tired of it
To me when I watched this it was after all the hype and I was kind of like
I've seen this a billion times
It felt sort of like a new yorker story or like an npr podcast or something
I know where it's going
The satire is kind of it's there. It's gentle. It's the kind of stuff people laugh
performatively at in theaters
Ha ha I get this joke i'm i'm better than this i'm a good white person, etc
There's that to this movie there's something irritating about the culture around it sort of I don't know why that is
But the movie itself I didn't think was anything
Amazing I think it's stuff that's kind of been said before what I loved about it was the cast
Um
Like you said joe, I thought sterling hayden should you know very very well should have been nominated for a supporting actor
He's great in it. These are great in it. Yeah, they're um, everybody's really great
Yeah, john over tease, you know adam brody and a little part everybody's good in it brody's very funny
As that executive or whatever the fuck he plays he it's yeah
I just have I get to a point where i'm like
And it's not fair to the movies but i'm like guys can we can we stop pretending
This is like an all -time scathing amazing hollywood satire or something
But that is not the fault of the movie
The movie didn't set out and say i'm going to it the movie's hype has been thrust upon it
And i'm talking about a larger issue than the film itself i'm talking about
This award season has been going on for over a year because of the strikes
So it's not like they shut awards down
They kept them going through the strikes like they're the billboards for vote for my show have been going on for literally over a year in los angeles
And i've just got some fatigue, you know, but that's separate from the from the movie itself
So the movie itself to me felt like a pleasant comedy in the b plus range
Something that used to get made a lot in the 90s
And would not have been seen as any sort of awards contender
But since we get so few movies for adults about adult topics and about real people
I think this struck a nerve with people and kind of
Made its way into the part of awards discussion. I was shocked by the way. I don't think anything this year is amazing
So there you go. I was shocked that this is not based on a book. I thought for sure it was but it it is
It is are you sure?
Erasure by perceval everett shit. All right. Well, never mind. Uh, okay. Never mind
um
Uh, maybe I was surprised it was based on a book then I don't know. I thought it wasn't anyway, um
I well, I want to talk about the things I saw in this movie that I that I felt that I hadn't seen
Before that I that I loved
uh
It made white liberals look really fucking stupid and it's about fucking time
One of these movies took shots in that direction because the shots are always at some fucking paper thin maga character
Uh, and it's just worn thin. It's worn thin. We've seen it a million times we get it
There are some people out there that love donald trump that are racist
There are people out there that love them that aren't racist. There are black people that love donald trump
But my point is is making the bad guy or or the target rather
The maga white guy is just old it's boring and it's and it's also not all -encompassing and the fact that this movie
right off the bat starts with a scene where a
Howdy white woman
Is trying to scold jeffrey wright's character on his use of racial language
And slurs and he says if I can handle this you should be able to and she leaves crying
I I loved
Those elements of this movie so much. I also loved that it took shots at
Uh white people in power that that were dismissive
Uh were exploitative of of the black experience
Uh, I also loved that it posed questions of
one black artist
with it within the um, um, uh in their perspective of another black artist
I thought it really addressed
From all angles almost in the way funny enough very different movie obviously
But almost in the way that that that the craig zoller movies
Like dragged across concrete
Are not as simple as cops are bad and the and the crooks are okay
And and this guy got a shitty run of it and this guy's just an asshole and he's racist
What I he really did a great job of balancing it all out and going let's just see
If we can have empathy for everybody kind of and that's what I thought this movie did
I thought it kind of created a weird
Uh, it cast its net very fairly
um
That said and I hate to say this
Because it made me laugh and I really enjoyed the performances at the end of the movie and maybe this was the point
I didn't understand where we ended up
When he finally confronts the waynes world ending they give you three endings
The clue ending that that I didn't mind where where he's like saying
How everything comes to a head at the award ceremony and and then it cuts to him
On a movie set with adam brody and you realize they're making a movie about his experience pretending to be this writer
and
They don't have an ending for the movie. So they have to make up an ending like that didn't bother me
I thought that was kind of funny and very true
But the fact that he ended the fact that he confronts easer ray
And there's never and again, maybe this is just the point there's never really an answer as to
Either of them being justified in their stance or them learning anything from one another
It almost seems like he kind of submits to her take
Which maybe that's the point. I don't know
It was just a little confusing to me and then in the end he ends up working with adam brody kind of a dildo
Right. I was like
But I was like I guess that's the point like it's just another day of a of a guy being black in hollywood
This is how it goes using the white guy. Yeah
Yes, so or yeah, so um, I agree I think constructurally
Structurally, excuse me. It's not a great movie. I agree that in the 90s this probably would have been another like
Uh the opposite of sex or one of those kinds of things right, you know well -respected indie film
Um, you know has a has a little bit of an amateurish quality at times, but overall it's very enjoyable
um
But I also think now
you know
We as you said we see so few movies that are actually addressing anything
Make their way all the way into a theater
That something like this is going to shine so that makes me happy that that that's even happening and it's getting attention
Yeah, it's really hard to nitpick when you know usually on here
I in particular i'm complaining about it
We have no movies for adults where where people are talking in a room or you know
stories about human beings, etc
Um, and I don't mean to be dismissive of it because I enjoyed it. I think it's a good b -plus comedy
um
And that it raises issues and talks about them in interesting ways, you know kudos. I just
I'll see what the guy does for does again cord jefferson. He's a big tv writer
um
and uh, yeah, I heard him on the talking pictures podcast, which is
Something i'll i'll recommend as a parting gift if I haven't already but it's turner classic movies talking pictures
And they interview people about their influences. It's great if you're into more movie podcasts
And by the way, let's leslie uggams is awesome in it as the mother with dementia
Yep, uh
Keith david great to see keith david always great and uh, and and the sterling k brown
Storyline his character in this
The storyline of that character is so great where he plays the brother of jeffrey wright's
Uh character
Yeah, but he also is gay, but he was married to a woman and he left his wife and now he's with men
He's also I thought this was interesting. He he openly does coke
And parties and has frivolous promiscuous sex and none of it is passed with any judgment
I thought the moment was coming where they were kind of kind when they come home for the for the wedding
Uh, or they're yeah
It was the wedding and and and they're gonna have it at the beach house and they catch him with the half naked dude
Doing coke in the house. I thought that that was gonna be this big moment of like you need help
Right and you're out of and instead he's just kind of like clean your shit up and get your fucking shit together
And then the guy does and then he still hangs out for the party
And and he hangs out for the wedding and then him and uh, uh, jeffrey wright ended up having a beautiful moment with one another
That night like a really heartfelt moment and i'm like I kind of liked that
They went that route with it and it was like this is not about lessons or anything like that
We're just gonna kind of talk show you an experience
I kept seeing more movies. I'd rather be watching in the fringes of this movie. I would say
Like I i'd rather not be lectured to i'd rather watch the story of two brothers sterling sterling and um
Uh, what's his name joe help me out jeffrey wright jeffrey wright. Yeah, I think I think
I just want to say jeffrey rush. Did he get cancelled? I haven't seen him in anything in 10 years rush
Yeah, you know from shine pirates of the caribbean. Yeah. No, I don't think so. He's just 80
Yeah, I guess you're right, I guess you're right, um, I I think I I want to give american fiction another watch
I I wonder if on a second watch it'll hit me a little harder, but but that said I did like the movie
My hog is up. It's not
gleaming
Lee up, but it's up. It's it's well coming
Yeah, it's up. Yeah. Um, yeah as I said as I said, it's a solid, uh up for me as well
It's an entertaining
Uh breezy satire, I would say but I tend to like my satire a little more ruthless
But then again, it wouldn't be as popular. So what do I know?
Um, thank you everybody
We are at see you in hell pod on instagram. We are patreon only now spread the word
Um, we love you joe
Yeah, we'll be back definitely with ghostbusters without a doubt and oh, yeah
The other movie will probably be
spaceman or maybe poor things because poor things has finally hit hulu, so
One of those two, uh, most likely but definitely ghostbusters and uh, we'll see you next time
And i'll be bringing your dune two requests, uh of discussion to the solo movie corner because joe won't see it which I have to respect
Uh, we'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell