You see,
All right, it's, we'll see you in hell. Welcome to the show. Sorry for the hesitant start
there. Just making sure that everything's working on this end. We're having some zoom issues
today. When you say so, Pat, I don't know if I'd call them zoom issues. Wait, we got mic issues,
uh, Apple issue. I got a new laptop and I, you know, it's been way too long. I've had this old
monster for years. Get the new one, plug in the microphone. No, it just doesn't work. Doesn't
turn on. The, the phone, I get a new iPhone as well because I've been, I, the entire pandemic
I've been using a cracked iPhone because I thought it would keep me from staring at my phone
all day. It didn't. I just looked at it through a, a prism, if you will. You plug in the phone.
It's like, here's all you got to do. Plug in the phone to the new laptop and you'll have everything
that you had in your old phone. It'll, it'll take three seconds. It took days. They, they're the
biggest company on earth. Nothing works. They're, they're expensive. Right. It's very kind of
have to buy them. I mean, you can't be one of these people out. What do you have? Joe, some sort of
Nissan galaxy or something? No, I have the iPhone 12. Oh, thank you very much. But yeah, I tried
to do the Samsung for a while. The problem is is you, you, you get so roped in with Apple that
you can't, you can't get out and then you're stuck. But I'm, I'm, I'm getting closer and closer
every day. I think the next laptop I buy won't be an Apple laptop. You got to get what my dad gets,
which is like a 50 pound Dell that he carries around in a plastic shopping bag. Yeah, it's,
it's I'm a little tired of the cute shit. I'm a, I'm tired of my track pad doing, you know, 80
different things. If I give it the finger, it knows that it means all caps or whatever, you know,
like, I'm just, I'm just really tired of these. Is that a real one? No, no. Of course, look,
that's exactly the sort of cutesy thing Apple would come up with. Yeah, it's annoying. Now, let's,
like instead of that, why don't you make your goddamn phone work? Let's not fully blame Apple,
because I saw Pat do a thing today that I've never seen a human even attempt. At one point,
when he was trying to get the mic to work, he took the lightning plug for the phone and said,
I'm just going to try to plug it into the USB C and see if it might work, which was outrageous. I
mean, if you were like, I'm going to plug this coaxial cable into this RCA, it's like, it's just,
it was wild. It didn't work, but the, the, the, they give me one cord. So I'm like, okay, I'll use
this one cord. You've given me to plug in the microphone and then it doesn't get it. Why doesn't it
get it? Probably they want me to order some new fucking cord from Apple, but I'm probably going to
wind up getting some Amazon basics cable, give Steve Bezos more money. Jeff Bezos. Jeff Bezos.
Steve Jobs. Yeah. You hear about this. Steve Bezos.
No, I'm, I don't know. I don't know. How are you Joe?
Are you? Look, for being one of the world's most powerful and richest men
and not the most generous guy, he at least hooks you up. He at least hooks you up at Amazon
basics. Well, cost you $7 .99. You're out the door. It's to the, it's, it's at your house the next day.
Apple, they don't even hook you up. That's true. Amazon does pass the savings onto you, which I appreciate.
But that's, that's the system. Unfortunately, it's like, man, I don't even look it up anymore,
because I'm like, yeah, the wife's starting to talk like, you know, we can't do Amazon anymore.
We can't do Amazon. And I'm like, all right. I hope this doesn't turn into something where I'm having
packages delivered at midnight, slipping out under cover of darkness. But I would, that'd be grounds
for divorce for me. I feel like I'm sorry. She's, I mean, she never really puts the foot down. She'll
just start to hint until eventually I realize she's tricked me and I'm doing what she wanted me to do
all along. I feel, look, I have Amazon guilt sometimes. And I try to do, look, I drove, I put my money
where my mouth is though. Do I use Amazon? Yes. Did I also drive two full hours
last week to go to a DVD store and Blu -ray store called the archive in Bridgeport, Connecticut,
because I heard they carried vinegar syndrome DVDs and arrow stuff and whatever. I drove two hours
to go support that shop. But I bought stuff up there found out it's actually the shop for vinegar
syndrome. It's actually where they do the vinegar syndrome. What's that called? You know,
nothing. No, where they retouch, you know, where they redo the mastery, master, you know,
yeah, yeah, the new transfers and all that shit that they put out. But you haven't done with the
English language mastering. Okay. Thank you. So I, I, I support, you know, but as I said to them,
I said, man, some of these titles I'm looking for, this is literally the only store I've ever been
to that would have them. I go, right, sometimes you have, I said, I go, sometimes you have to go to
Amazon to get some of this shit, because it's the only place that has some of it. That's true. You
I didn't know you were a fan. To me, the vinegar syndrome seems so obscure that I don't go with them,
but maybe I should. They've got a lot of cult stuff. It's a lot of cult stuff. They do a lot of sex
sexploitation re -releases. I'm not into those. I'm into the horror stuff that they do. They
mean it's mostly horror. But they do pretty obscure shit, but, but that's why some of it is so
fucking magnificent. I read an article on bloody disgusting the other day. It was like five
Mexican horror movies you need to see. Uh -huh. And one of them was called Cemetery of Terror,
and it was one of the only ones I was able to find, and it was vinegar syndrome. I was like, that's
they're pretty cool. Well, I, it recently, I started following, I'll give you a great Twitter
follow. I don't, I don't watch their YouTube videos, although I probably should, but they're called
the Jess the Disks podcast. I also don't listen to the podcast, but if you follow, I'm sure it's great.
They go through Blu -rays, but the feed is great at keeping you updated on when the sales come up.
So if you've got a spending issue, don't follow them, but I had a near psychotic break over the past
couple weeks. I really was down in the dumps. I went on a big spending spree. It kind of helped. I
watched the region, same with Arrow. I got to make sure it's not region B, unless you own
a free player. And I have two. That's not much more expensive to get one of those, is it?
No, the cheapest Blu -ray player I ever bought was a Sony in its region free, and the PS4 is region free.
Is it? Yeah, for Blu -rays and stuff. I got that's, I wish I had fucking known that. God damn it.
The PS4. Yeah, I play all kinds of shit on that PS4.
Shit, I always forget that that works. Yeah, and if it is for some reason is locked, you can unlock it.
Okay, Sony helps you out. Yeah, indicator had an amazing sale. The Warner's sale, they do the
four for 44, Arca, I've classics. That sale was a huge success. To the extent that Warner,
the shop is now done. They're like we, we made enough that we can kind of announce that we're
done. So they'll be a run on those titles. I made some arrow purchases. I made, what's that
you? I missed both of those sales. I didn't know about them. I should have told you I'm sorry. That's
all right. I was sale I hit up on the grindhouse site. Yes, grindhouse. And then I think, I know we
mentioned last time, the amazing new site, Hamilton book, which gave you a bunch of great stuff as
well. So yeah, another order over there. Yeah, this was the first time because of how amazing my
Amazon sales have been going. I just found myself with a ton of cash because I had been making,
I'm selling vinyl records at a hundred dollars a clip all day. So if you're in a bind or if not,
if you just have some old records that you want to get rid of, I had stuff and I'm like, I bought
this five years ago. It's unopened. You get on, it's going for like 150 or whatever. So I turned it
around, bought these. I like doing that. I buy stuff that goes out of print. Sometimes if it's not
open, they can go up to like $500 for collecting stuff. You know, I'm essentially running a used shop out
of my home. And for me, it just keeps my mind distracted. It's like a hobby. And it's a nice way to make
a little money. Yeah, I like to, if I, you know, if I ever trade stuff at a shop, I always take the
trade credit instead of the cash. Anything I ever make from getting rid of media, I try to sink back
into new media, you know, same. I just feel like it's a way to keep your collection going and
going in a way that you are still utilizing it. The, yeah, I've gotten some great, I got some great
stuff at that archive shop. Check it out if you ever in Bridgeport, Connecticut. But
and unfortunately, they don't do mail order. You can mail order any of the vinegar syndrome stuff
just from the vinegar syndrome website. But the stuff in the shop is not for, for, they don't do shipping.
But I got a, I got a three pack of jungle horror movies. One of them is jungle holocaust by the
insane like Spanish -speaking horror movie on Blu -ray over there. I got a copy of Night of the Demon
Finally. Wanting that for a long time. Is jungle holocaust a sequel to cannibal holocaust? Because
it sounds way less scary. Jungle less supposed to cannibal. I think it is, it's about cannibals.
Okay, sure. So, yeah, sequel tries to, you know, die harder. You try to up it a little bit. But
just now we're just in the jungle. I think he was probably like, I blew the load with cannibal
holocaust. I got a, I should have saved that. Or maybe cannibal holocaust is a sequel to jungle
holocaust. I don't know. Like make it naked cannibal holocaust or something. Get that, get the
purve crowd in. Yeah, yeah, yeah, the trench coat crowd. Yeah. I do that. You ever go to a time
square movie house wearing only a trench coat. And then when the lights dim, you masterbent. I have
in time square, not in a movie house. At the burger king, I would do that. Yeah. They used to have
the burger king bar. Do you remember that? Were you around for that burger king bar?
No, that you could drink at burger king? Yeah, time square had a burger king. And it was called
the burger king bar. And it was as far as I know, the only burger king in the country that had an
operating bar bar. And so I would think so. I used to do my drinking at this bowling alley.
Art, it was an arcade that is no longer there in time square next to the big AMC theater.
And they would do dollar beers. And I would just sit there and then stumble over to the
port authority back to Jersey City. Did I am a sucker for it to this day? You put a bar in a unique
location. I am beside myself. I'm so excited. I like, I will fall for it every time, man. Yeah,
every time. Have I ever talked about on here? I don't even know if they still have these things.
I imagine these were a casualty of COVID probably. But when I first moved to New York, I'm 22, 23,
whatever. And I would go out and, you know, drink party with friends till four in the morning. I'd
often miss my port authority bus back to Jersey City, meaning I'd have to then wait five, six hours.
Right. Always a nightmare. So I was wandering around in time square. They also have a bunch in
union square, all these porno shops. And I go in and I'm like, what are these booths in the back?
And they're like, oh, it's just they play porn. And I'm like, see, you go in and look at
point. It was, it wasn't pre -internet. I mean, I don't really understand the appeal. I think
they're just a holdover from a time where you couldn't get porn. But I went into one. I put in,
you know, a couple bucks. And I'm like, okay, so there's a hundred channels of porn. It's like having,
you know, access to pay -per -view, basically, and you flip around. It's, you have to kind of block out
the fact that you're touching an arrow that anyone else who's been in this booth has touched.
Right. And you know some guys are going to for two and three -fers in that thing. So there's
on that button. But, you know, I was fresh off the off the bus from Missouri and Barry Naive. But I'm
sitting there and I'm kind of washing the porn. I'm standing, you know, I'm not like getting
hard or anything. I'm just like, I'm trying to really figure out what the appeal of this would be
when I hear, I look down and then through a mail slot to my right comes a shriveled, uncircumcised
penis. And I realized what they have these four is you go into the booths and then you can
jack each other off or suck each other off. It's just like glory holds. Now, these have to be gone in
the world of COVID, I would think. But I didn't want to make the man feel bad by saying what the
fuck or something like that. I just simply excused myself from the booth. You know, perhaps I could have
done a solid and brought them to completion. But it's just I'd like you to check since you live
in New York, Joe, if these things still exist for me. Go back there and wait. I was in one of those,
it didn't have the slot. It was just some do some. You could watch live girls strip. You're in your own
private like your own private little booth and you could pick a phone up and they'd say dirty shit to
you and stuff. Yeah. Again, you're touching the New York to the more so an Amsterdam, you know,
that's like in closer the the Mike Nichols movie. They use those Natalie Portman's one of those
stripping. It's a stay for a way for a girl to strip. There was one where the girl would sit in the
middle of all the booths so you could see the other creeps. Yeah. That was an Amsterdam. I didn't care
for that. I wanted one of those. But I mean, the phone thing is troubling because you're, you know,
God knows what's on that mouthpiece and it's going right to your lips. I didn't use a phone,
yeah. So but you know, this was a good old, good old days of whatever you want to call it,
but it's a porn. It's not really, it's not, I mean, I guess it's technically sex work, but not
really. I don't know. It is. I guess so, right? Yeah. I mean, I, I learned the other day that
prostitute is is no longer allowed. I knew horror was out, but I think prostitute is now out and
I think anyone working in sex is sex worker. And sometimes I can't say prostitute prostitute.
Unless I mean, granted it was somebody on Twitter who's always extremely really in your face about
this sort of thing, but name names or no, no, no, do I know them? No, no, okay. But yeah,
prostitute is apparently on the way out. Horror has been out and you're just supposed to say sex worker.
Now to me, and I'm really not trying to be funny here, I'm just simply talking some antics, sex worker
as an all encompassing thing, it seems worse to me than saying the word prostitute, which has been
around since that, you know, the dawn of time, it's the oldest profession. It's like how, you know,
midget is no longer acceptable and it shouldn't be, but why is a little person better? A little person
doesn't sound better to me. It's a game we're all playing. Yeah. It's why I get so disgusting. It's
curiosity more than anything else. I'm not trying to do some sort of rift or I guess say this. I just,
I always am curious who decided. I wonder if everyone who's being called that now agrees with that
change, because I know in many cases they don't. I just think it's, I think it's, I don't care,
I have no real instinct in it. I just think it's people kidding themselves into, you know, now obviously
I'm not talking about like hard slurs and stuff like that, you know, that are used to hurt.
And even midget, I get that one too. But when you start getting into this bullshit about like,
you know, the one that kills me is people of color. It's like you're saying colored people.
You're saying the same thing except just in reverse. And the first thing was offensive. So you're,
now it's just this game. It's the stupid fucking, you know, I don't know. I don't get it. I don't get it.
So, and when the, when the left gets upset about it, who's the saying whore by the way?
Yeah, no one's saying, hey, there was a period where like, you know, Tina Fey caught a bunch of
flack for using the word whore all the time. And so funny word. I'm saying, say the word,
but who's going up to a prost? Sorry, a sex worker saying, hello whore. Yeah, you know,
like, it's a funny word to use in other, as an insult or something. But
I've only seen that like from Norm Mcdonald in in dirty work where he's just referring to them all
as whores or sopranos did it as well, where it was who. But we're going to say when the left gets
upset, then the right one happens. Yeah, I mean, look, I'm left, you know, but I recognize their major
flaws and faults. When when the people on the left are upset about the terminology,
it just gives the right more kindling for the fire. You know, that's the reason now that every
night on Fox News and Tucker Carlson, it's, can you believe that they're going to take this away?
Can you believe that's there? You're just playing into their hands and they've been doing it for years.
But yeah, the changing of words and the oversensitivity is now that what is fueling the right to attack
the left. And it'll hit a certain point where people on the left will say, well, God, I don't want
to be on the right. Guys, what are we supposed to do here? Like, can we chill out? I think we're hitting
the first time in history. This is fascinating to me. A common thing amongst a lot of sort of
prog socially progressive people was they would say, I'm politically, I'm fiscally conservative, but
I'm very socially liberal. Sure. I honestly think it's flipping. I think people are starting to be
like, well, no, I'm actually more socially conservative because I don't get upset about
off -color jokes or I don't think we should be banning cartoon episodes or whatever else.
But I'm more federally, I guess, is the better term than fiscally liberal. I like some of their
policies better. I like what they're doing with this. So I don't know. It's a weird time.
But I'm glad you brought it up, Pat. Let's dig into what's going on in Minneapolis right now.
Look, I had been off Twitter, so I don't, I truly don't know the specifics,
and I don't want to talk about it. I'm kidding. I'm joking. I just wanted to make all the
fans go, please, I tune in to get away from the Craig Kilborn has been killing it with,
man, he had a video today where he was, I mean, it wasn't today, but I watched it today.
What is a recent post where he's like, he's like, people ask me, hey, Craig,
I'm, he's got a martini. There's so much hate and anger in the world. How do you isolate yourself
from it? And he starts describing martini because after this, I'm going to take a nice nap with
visions of sugar plums dancing in my head. And when I wake, I'll be eating around 3 p .m.
Some pulled pork that's been slow cooking since 8 a .m. So yeah, I guess I just managed to block
it all out. Yeah, that's funny. I followed him for a bit. And then it was like, it's how I always
follow people. It becomes too much almost immediately. I think more than a post a day I'm out.
I think he literally just hangs out at his house. Yeah. And drinks. Yeah, I think that's all he
does. Like yeah, yeah. Like I think that's his day. He like does work around his house. Yeah.
And he like hangs out in his house and drinks. Some people should just take that hint, you know,
like it's, it's these people who are like, why do you still need this? Why do you need more?
Like why wouldn't you relax? You have a hundred million dollars. Yeah. I don't understand. But then
again, I've been in my home for a year and I've finally lost my mind. So I get that you got to
get out there and be productive. But you'll be out soon. Yeah, no, I know. I go out, you know,
occasionally it's just the world is bleak as we all know. But it's getting into the deep heavy
breathing which helps because it doesn't let my mind attack me, which is what it's been doing lately.
I've always had a mind that will turn on me in a second, just be like, you piece of shit.
Yeah. And lately it's just been the only voice that I'm hearing. And the meditation and the deep
breathing, I usually only do it in a time of like deep crisis. But lately I've just been
in through the nose, out through the mouth all day. And it helps because you're just thinking
about the breath. You're not thinking about the other shit. And then like random things like the
other night, I went to bed at 11 and I woke up at noon for a total of 13 hours of sleep. Now that's
feels great in some way. But it's also like, what is going on with me? Yeah, that's tough. That's
tough. I'm not going to lie to you. But I've been there. I've been there. You know, New York somehow
magically just reopening now. Everything? I haven't seen Cuomo in quite some time.
He is out, baby. You know, these fucking people are all the same. These politicians, they'll run
their fucking mouths about their ethics and everything. And the second the heat turns up,
they're fucking gone, dude. So yeah, I don't know. None of it makes sense. Look, I got
vaccinated because I'm just like, I don't give a shit. I just want to get vaccinated. I don't
want to be able to go out. I don't care. Right. But you read the, you go read the CDC guidelines for
the vaccine. Doesn't make any fucking sense. They can contradict themselves in their own guidelines.
It's like, if you, if you're vaccinated, you can safely hang out with other vaccinated people. Also,
you can travel without getting tested or quarantining. It's like, yeah, but, but then that would mean that I
could, you just said I could potentially be a danger to somebody who's not fit. So then I would
have to quarantine after I travel because it doesn't make any fucking sense. No, it's all opening up.
Like, it's like, okay, you want to talk about, like, heart stopping experiences. My dad out of nowhere,
one week ago was like, hey, I'm coming to stay with you. Oh, boy. And he's coming this weekend.
So he really likes to kind of spring these things on you. But he's like, I'm coming out. I've
been fully vaccinated. So they say it's fine. And I said, okay, well, I'm not. So, you know, I'm close,
but I'm not there. And he's like, it's fine. It's fine. Then he leaves this panicked message where he's
like, Patrick, I just pushed order on the ticket. And they're telling me that I need to quarantine for 10
days. I cannot afford to get a hotel for 10 days. I just cannot afford it. So, you know, I know when I
talk to you, I said, I'd be staying with you for three nights. Now, it looks like we're going to need to
make that 13. I will be staying with you if that's okay. Let's talk. Give me a call.
And then, you know, I call Heather. I'm like, we need to figure this out. So this doesn't happen.
And then immediately he texted, he's like, never mind. I read the small print. I don't have to
quarantine. Everything's fine. And I was like, well, great. But why don't you have to quarantine? If
it's like, it's like, some people are saying, some people are saying you can't get it if you're
vaccinated. Some people are saying you can get it. But you won't get it bad. Some people are saying
you can't give it. I'm choosing to do the following hanging out with people that go, oh, you're vaccinated.
Okay. Cool. Yeah. No worries. Yeah. That's it. You just got to go hang out with who you agree with now.
And just try to have a good time. Like, I don't know what else to do. Every, every bit of information is
contradictory. I don't know what else to do. And there's no way we're getting the full truth about
anything. It's embarrassing, but it is what it is. So, you know, whatever. Yeah. I think now,
the, you know, it always used to be conspiracy theory people that were like, that was me hitting a
bomb. Like, you just don't understand, man. Like the government is out to get you and all that.
And you're like, okay, whatever smokey, you know, go, but now I think that's pretty much the norm.
I think even your most tried and true, like government suburban dad is like,
our government is trying to kill us. There is fucked up. There is absolutely a narrative that is
provided by both sides of the media and their, those narratives contradict one another. Okay. So,
liberals are right when they say there's a conservative narrative. Conservatives are right when they
say there's a liberal narrative, just depends on which news outlets you're watching. All of them are
in communications that are made and how contradictory they are. You know, Johnson and Johnson's
vaccine just got fully halted. Yeah, I saw that because eight women got blood clots. Now,
eight women out of however many, right. It's an extremely small percentage, but it's still alarming.
And the New York Times reports on it and they're saying things like, it's important you keep in mind.
This is a very, very rare occurrence. Also, lots of things cause blood clots. And it's like,
you were the same outlet that when it was COVID, something one person their skin fell off or whatever
crazy shit happened, right? It was like, COVID can make your skin fall off. It was never, let's try to
talk about likelihood. Let's try to stay rational. Let's try to do this. So, it's just gross. It's all
just, it's all just moving product and it's all gross. And so, so like I said, folks, you don't
want to get vaccinated. Fine, just hang on with people that don't give a shit if you're not vaccinated.
You want to get vaccinated. Fine, hang on with people that you got vaccinated and go out and have sex
and get drunk. That's it. I do think also just for a peace of mind and everything else, everyone needs
to be vaccinated in my opinion. That's not going to happen, but I think a lot of people are sitting
in their homes waiting for like a call from their local pharmacist to say, come on down. We've
pulled your number. We're beyond that. The system is beyond fucked. If you have an opportunity to
get a vaccine and you're not slapping it out of the hand of a less fortunate person, do so. You
know, like everyone here in Los Angeles who spends all their day on Twitter telling you, you must wait
your turn is going from Walgreens to Walgreens every day trying to get an abandoned dose, you know. So
but also too, I look, I'm not in this camp, but I could also I will say, look, I can't blame
me if you're not trusting of it after you see these these blood clot stories and whatever. So,
I don't know, man, it's sad to me. It's sad to me this were at New York. All that weight your
turn shit is done every there was kids on the street today outside of the trader Joe's like, come
get your vaccine. We can sign you up. It's free. It's fast. We can say like that's how prevalent it
is in New York now. Yeah. Like it's just like you can get it at a fucking Dwayne Reed, you know,
as a 17 year old or whatever. You don't have to be 65. You know, so maybe six months into this thing
that people who have COVID have they they can develop serious mental issues like severe anxiety,
severe depression, etc. And I'm like, how do you know that how do you know that six months inside
a year inside a year and a half inside isn't causing these mental disorders? You don't. However,
I've spent the last two weeks getting progressively worse since I got my first shot mentally.
So the point where two nights ago, I'm rocking back and forth breathing like I'm a pregnant woman,
you know, in Lamas class. And I'm like, did the vaccine cause this weird spiral I'm having?
Probably not, but you don't know. It's it's it's it is scary. Well, call me when you're down like
this is one of your closest friends. This particular night was a very late and then you're three hours
later than me and blah, blah, blah. You never know what I'm up to. I'm out with the celebs half the time
till 4 a .m. I mean, call a friend when you're feeling down, man. I should. I had no idea you were
in the state till today on the podcast. I find out. Yeah. Yeah. No, I know. I know.
Yeah, it's fine. We're all struggling, folks. We're all struggling. We're all struggling. Let's go
to something more positive. I'd like to be cornered. Yeah. Let's go to the movie corner. Also,
I'd be remiss if I didn't say, folks, Joe really, really wanted us to say here and we should have
said it at the top. RIP Bernie made off. Oh, yeah. That's right. Yeah. He's one of the greats. Absolutely
one of the greats. So I'm going to do three documentaries today. You know, the guy they should have
called him Bernie made off with my money. Oh, boy. Right. I saw someone do that at a stand -up show,
like two years ago. It happens. Yeah. Okay. I saw the orange years, the Nickelodeon story.
This is a documentary that was about seven bucks to order two weeks ago and now it's on Hulu.
I could not afford Nickelodeon as a child or my family, we didn't have cable. So I never saw
a lot of these shows. You're all that. You're keen in a kill. You're Rocco's modern life. You're
dug. You're rug rats. But everyone sort of my age and younger was obsessed with them and knows
everything about them. So I thought this would be a good way to kind of educate myself on the Nickelodeon
experience. I had seen some of the shows at friends houses like Legends of the Hidden Temple. I
used to love that like raised the Lost Ark style kids game show. Yeah. Double Dare. I loved. I was
never a huge double dare fan. My friends all loved it. I like the crazier ones. You know, like the one
you just said, the Aztec temple and all that. Yeah. Yeah. And they had guts, which was fun. The more
like American gladiators type. Yeah. But look, the documentary is fine. It's your standard kind of
talking heads thing with a bunch of clips. Some very funny interviews with a much heavier and
clearly stoned Kenan, which I mean, Kenan's the best. But the it's entertaining. If you were a fan
and you grew up on these shows, then you'll find a lot to love here. If you're like me and you kind of
wash it as like what was Nickelodeon all about? It's a good little primer. It overlaps quite a bit
with the Ren and Stimpy documentary that came out. Although my grievance with this doc is 90 minutes,
it's fun. It's bubbly. It's a great story about how these people created something out of nothing
and resisted marketing it for the longest time until it became this massive, massive corporation,
of course. But they don't go into the controversy. They don't go into the stuff with, I always want to
say John Fruciante, which is not not his name, but the guy that created Red Hat Chili Peppers. The guy
that played in Red Hat Chili Peppers is Fruciani. The guy who did know Fruciante is John Watt. John Fruciante's
Red Hat Chili Peppers. Isn't that what I said? John Fruciante? No, you said Fruciani or something. Oh, I
think the guy John, something or other who created Ren and Stimpy was grooming and being in
relationships with very young girls. They go into that in the Ren and Stimpy doc, which was troubling,
interesting. But they don't go into the controversy here. You see Dan Schneider at one point,
of head of the class fame, I believe. There's rumors that he impregnated some of his young stars,
who were like 15. So at some point, I think we'd all like to see that Nickelodeon expose that
might have been a more juicy documentary. This one focuses on the positive. It's probably they,
you know, were threatened with legal action, so they maybe cut that stuff. But yeah, it's
it's cute, fun little doc worth worth watching. All right, I'll do documentaries too. I watched
the last blockbuster. I enjoyed it. I enjoyed it. I enjoyed some of it. I overall enjoyed it
because overall at the end of the day, it's really about this woman who is running the last blockbuster
in existence and how she basically runs it like a mom and pop video store. It's in a location that
used to be a mom and pop video store that blockbuster bought out so they could take the location over.
So I like the the juxtaposition of this thing about this corporate greedy, awful video store chain
that came around and destroyed mom and pop businesses being at the end of the day about a mom and pop
business. It's a great irony. It makes it a great story and it actually does make you miss blockbuster in
in in your own way, whatever that may be. The part of the documentary I didn't like was all of the
quasi celebrity interviews and everybody is talking as if blockbuster was so awesome.
Blockbuster was never so awesome. Blockbuster was a last resort. It was the last video store we ever
wanted to go to as kids because they didn't have gross and dirty shit. They didn't have raw shit.
Like when you're 12, 13 years old, you want to go to a video store because your parents went to your
grandmums for the day and left you and your buddies home and you want to rent. I spit on your grave
and you know, you want to try to pull off rent a porno movie or whatever it is. You want to you want
to see the shit that you can't watch when your folks are around and blockbuster to me was always
overpriced candy and sterile and I hated the smell. But you know, it was fine if you wanted to go buy
a few movies for 15 bucks that were on sale or you know, they definitely had the video game rental
side of things blocked pretty sewn up. You know, so I wasn't against the place. I just saw it for
what it was. It was like going to you know, came art instead of the town store or whatever. It's
it is what it is. So that aspect of it I kind of was a little annoyed with and then there's this
other part. It's a Netflix documentary and they talk a lot in the documentary about how Netflix is
rumored to have put blockbuster out of business. But that's not really what happened and they get into
fiscally what actually happened and how it actually ended up going out of business. But then there's
this thing where they do a section where it's like we had an offer from Netflix to buy them out
and we passed. And again, it cuts to all these celebrities, heavy quotes, celebrities. And
they're all going like you blew it blockbuster. It's like is everybody just a corporate fucking
chill at this point? I mean, is everybody just sitting there going like isn't this the greatest thing
in the world? Oh, we just happened to also be on the thing where we're praising the new version of
blockbuster that's running other things out of business and making it hard for content creators
and whatever else. It's like, you know, Netflix is net. Again, I use it. I see it for what it is.
I'm not saying you need to go out and boycott it or anything like that. I have said it in the past.
I've changed my tune. My point is is just see it for what the fuck it is. Like I just can't
this whole thing anymore, man, has gotten so out of fucking control that money and notoriety
means that you are a success in life. If I see one more fucking trailer for one more stupid fucking
TV show where four women are walking down the street in slow motion and it says take over the world
across the bottom. It's like, why do you have to take over the world? Yeah. That's that's what Hitler wanted
to do. Yeah. And we thought it was a bad idea. Why is everything like royalty and take over the
world? And I'm magnificent and I'm this and I'm that and it's like, just stop, man. Jesus fucking
Christ. It's the you can be anything you want to be and you're going to run the world. You're going
to rule the world, etc. You know, it's it's fine in theory. 95 % of people can't be what they want to
be. Not even close. It killed them. You know, every second of every day it breaks their spirit.
If you ever sort of looked at your dad soaking around the house or sneaking a cigarette or screaming
at you, whatever, as you get older, you realize your dad was broken by life. You know, he wanted more
and he didn't get it. So with every message being run the world, I completely agree with you. It's
a it's a fucked up message just to give to people because when you inevitably don't run the world
or become the CEO of a Fortune 500 company or the president, you're going to feel like even more
of a failure than you would have. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. All right. Well, anyway, that's the last
blockbuster check it out. It's it's an enjoyable documentary. It's fine. Yeah. If if you hate the smell
of blockbuster, try to live working there for three years as I did. But you know what I found they didn't
mention in the blockbuster doc that I found weird is that blockbuster video did do a Netflix.
Yeah. I remember. Yeah. It was terrible. I mean, I only signed up for the free trials once in a while
and they were awful. They had a terrible selection. But Netflix basically had anything you could have
wanted when they would send the redhead below up to your house back in the day. And blockbuster just
kind of sucked and they they joined the party way too late and you could tell the writing was on the wall.
It's a pretty big step to leave out of this like 80 -minute documentary I felt. But what do I? Yeah.
No. It was they talk they talk briefly about that in there and and it's funny. When blockbuster did
that, I remember my friends feeling bad for Netflix. Oh, okay. Because Netflix was so the underdog
at the time. Yeah. And they were like, I don't respect it. Netflix did this really cool original thing
and they're really for the customer and all that's good to know. Yeah. It's going to now be
17, 99 a month because we have to put a show out every Tuesday. There's a new series every Tuesday.
New three new series and three new movies and none of them you want to watch. Yeah. Anyway,
I watched, you know, another kind of frothy documentary called Kid 90 that wound up all these are
actually Hulu documentary. But Kid 90 is Salemoon Fries documentary. She portrayed
punky Brewster, which is a show I watched when I was a kid. I feel like it was on around the same time
as Al and I clearly made my choice. But you're real excited for this reboot. They just launched,
right? New punky. Yeah. Yeah. New punky. No, no, same punk. New Brewster. Still punk. Same Brewster.
There's a tag in the trailer that literally says still punk. Is there anything less punk
than peacock? Yeah. That's one service peacock. In this Nickelodeon documentary, they talk about
how punk Clarissa explains it all was because she liked they might be giants. But anyway, Kid 90.
And I'm being shitty. I think that kind of stuff is revolutionary for kids. Honestly, when you see a
they might be giants on animaniacs or whatever. It can be a lot of kids window into cooler music.
I'm not talking. I discovered them on Nickelodeon. I thought Nickelodeon was like any other network.
They used to do really cool and they did what they could. And when they and when you're new,
you can do indie type stuff. And as you get bigger, that stuff starts to fade away sadly. But
for sure. Yes. Kid 90. So I know nothing about Salemoon Fries. When you first see her today,
I mean, she's absolutely stunning woman. But you know, she's very LA actress type, which is a type.
You run into them a lot here. Also, there are actor types. So there's a lot of talk about being
grateful and learning about love and that sort of stuff. But what it is is a collection of her
home movies. She's one of these people who I would never have associated with. I would have been like,
get that fucking camera out of my face. But she filmed every aspect of her life for years. So you
get to kind of watch the journey of a child star. And there are cameo appearances from most of
you know, the people who were big at that time. Some who still are. So you see like a young
Leonardo Caprio hanging out over at her house. Some are sad tales. Actually eight of her friends
committed suicide or had drug overdoses. Jonathan Brandis. And you know, some more famous than
others. But they just talked about drugs. You know, there's a there's a really kind of moving
interview with David Arquette where he talks about his struggle with drugs. And he
solace shows him a video of her daughter like running around and having fun. And he's like
he seems troubled. You know, he seems deeply troubled. So like when he's watching the two of them
as 16 year olds like having fun and doing drugs and stuff. He's like, that's my daughter's age.
You look exactly like my daughter. I want to be sick. Like there's people are dealing with a lot
of residual stuff from what went on in the 90s. In the teen teen world, the clothes that you see,
that's kind of the fun of it. You know, that you see the 90s fashions, you know, the 90s hair styles,
whatever. But this is a 71 minute documentary that feels pretty padded. And it's not going to
revolutionize your life. But if you want to see a bunch of stars, when they were kids, you know,
my dear friend, Jay Ferguson, your friend as well, Joe. See a quick flash at him. He was in the
the outsider's TV show. So it was funny to see him look and tough.
He was also by the way, a member of what was called the pussy posse.
Pussy posse. Believe it or not, he does not enjoy talking about that time of his life.
I, it came up one time on the bonfire. Jay and Dan Soder. We're talking about it. And they said,
who was in that thing? And they sort of read the names. And they go, Jay are Ferguson? Who's that?
I go as a good friend of mine. I was a shower. He's a classic tale of just meeting the right
woman and like becoming tamed. You know, like he was just like, I would be absolutely dead if I
had not met my wife. He's the, he's the sweetest man on earth. I love, I love Fergie. And, and I love
Fergie too. Sure. Uh, you know, she's a little 2 ,000 in late, but, but beyond that, I'm a fan.
Yeah. Kid 90 is, is, you know, there's some, what's interesting is what she deems troubling. Like,
she has a breast reduction surgery right after punky. And they show some clips of her. She's on
teen win loser draw, which made me laugh. It's like, there were sped -offs of win loser draw. I
watched it when it was hosted by Bert Reynolds. And I watched it when it was hosted by Vicki Lawrence,
of course. I did not know they had a teen version. But the, the host is like, look at you, it seems
like two weeks ago, you were little punky Brewster. Now you're big punky Brewster. And, you know,
she's 16 or whatever. So she gets a breast reduction, you know, that's a big part of the doc. She
has some reason that's a big part of the doc. I remember hearing about that. Uh, several of them
kill themselves as well. Um, so a lot of people have deep regrets. And, you know, it sounds like a
nightmare to me facing your past in that way, watching all these tapes of, it's like my, you know,
again, my dad, but he sent me this big collection of videos for my childhood. And I'm like, I don't
want to watch this. Right. I'd rather die. But, uh, the one thing I do want to mention about this is
that Solay talks about how she'd lost her virginity. And it took her, she was the last one of her
friends. She did it like the day she turned 18. And she goes, and I wound up losing it to, first,
first she very tragically talks about being assaulted by a boyfriend. She's like, I don't consider
that losing my virginity. And so I, I did finally lose it with, uh, somebody really special.
Somebody really sweet. Um, and it's Charlie Sheen. And she tells this like it is one of the
great romances where the day she turns 18, a 29 year old Charlie Sheen calls her, they fuck like
it's not, it's not maybe the day, but it's, it's very close to her birthday. She, and she talks about
this magical time where Charlie Sheen swoops in, takes her virginity. At this point, the man is doing
like the chase with Christie Swanson. This is 10 years after Ferris Bueller. He's doing like
terminal velocity. And, um, yeah, it's, it's a wild part of the documentary because I'm sure she
told Charlie, I talk about you in a very sweet way. And it's all very loving. And he goes, okay,
fine. When you watch it, any normal person who's not her goes, this is the definition of what they're
describing as grooming now. He was your friend until the day you turned 18. Uh, anyway, it's,
it's sort of a fun watch. If you grew up in the 90s, if not, you'll have no interest.
Yeah. Yeah. She said publicly, she's a good egg recently, I guess, because she told the story.
Yeah. You know, like in a flattering way or whatever. Yeah. Her, it's, uh, it's a, it's a, it's a
loving Brian Austin green. I'm a big fan of Brian Austin green. He said, honestly, I,
I think he seems like a grounded guy. I like that. I mean, I don't like that he's heartbroken,
but I liked that he was kind of heartbroken when his marriage broke up. Yeah. You know, and then,
and then also that, that like, that she left Megan Foxx left him for that fucking knob. Oh,
good. That was killing me. Uh, and I liked that Austin Green was kind of like the one that was like,
I was like, oh, he, he actually was like the, the, the romantic one. And like you would have
thought it was, I would have thought from the jump, it was the other way around because he was kind of
the hot shot when they got together. But I don't know. And I really liked him on that 90210 reboot.
I thought that show was pretty cool. I don't know that I've ever seen him act. He just, he put the child
star thing so beautifully, like it made me want to watch a documentary about him. But he's like,
he talks about putting out a rap album and he goes, the only music I had ever listened to in my
whole life was hip -hop. It's the only music I liked or cared about. So of course, when the opportunity
came along, that's the genre I chose because the CD came out and they show a couple of their views.
They're like one of the least, one of the least essential albums of the 90s, one of the worst albums
of the 90s, whatever. And he goes, and I felt like for 18 years, like everything had gone my way,
I was happy when you're a kid. You don't question anything. You wear what you want. You say what you want.
You're happy all the time. And he goes, and then I saw that and I was like, oh, people don't like
me. People hate me. Like, I thought everyone loved me. And he said, then the next 20 years was sort of
a horrible struggle trying to get some sort of self -esteem back. And I was like, God, that's a great
way to put it. But also it's, I mean, you see why so many of these kids don't make it out. But man,
it's just a nightmare. But it's a good thing we've learned our lesson by continually blowing up
children into millionaires on TikTok and whatever else, whatever the newest grooming tool is for
Hollywood to exploit the youth. And you know, anyway, I'll do, I'll do two in one shot. It's around
mine out because the first ones are super quick. I've been watching the docu series Remastered on Netflix
which is basically every episode centers around a music scandal of some kind. A lot of them are
murder related. So there's an episode called The Two Deaths of Sam Cook that highlight
the strange and scandalous way in which he died and how there's two completely different versions of
the story of what went on. I watched last night, which was my favorite episode so far, was who killed
Jam Master J. And it got into what was going on in Jam Master J's life and what was surrounding him when
he got mysteriously murdered at that studio and why they still haven't caught the guy that did it.
It's that kind of stuff. It's that kind of stuff. It's a really interesting docu series. It did not feel
from what I've seen of it. It did not feel exploitative. They did great. It's probably a year old.
There's a Robert Johnson episode that's really, really riveting.
But that leads me to that led me to another docu series that I've been
watched in its entirety last night, which is called Who Killed Malcolm X? Or is it who shot Malcolm?
I think it's who killed Malcolm X. I think it's who killed, yeah.
And it's this guy who's like, hey man, I'm a Muslim. I'm not a lawyer. I'm not a cop. I don't work
in criminal justice. I was just highly influenced by Malcolm X. This case has a lot of weird
smoke around it. The wrong people went to jail. I want to figure out who actually killed this guy
and whatever. And it's just eight six or eight episodes of that of him investigating. And the deeper
in he gets, it's riveting. The deeper in he gets, the more people that were close to that situation
and one way or the other are like, leave it alone, dude. Yeah.
Like leave it alone. Like, you know, and he's like, but why? And they're like, this is not stuff you
want to dig up. And there's amazing moments where he's talking to, like he's talking to the lieutenant
governor, who is a black female in New Jersey, or at least the time of this, that's who the lieutenant
governor was. I don't know if she still is. And she attends the funeral of the guy. These are
major spoilers guys. So if you want to watch it, you got to plug your ears. She attends the funeral
of the guy that all roads seem to lead to as most probably being the guy that killed Malcolm X and
got away with it. And he interviews her and brings that up. He's like, you were at his funeral.
And she's like, yep, yeah, yeah, I knew the man well. And he was a community pillar and all that's
10. And he's like, you know that, did you know that he was, it's very rumored and people think that he
killed Malcolm X. And she's like, yes, I've heard that. And he's less kind of like, what the fuck?
Why is everybody just kind of accepting it? Like, it's, it's, it's strange, man. And it's interesting.
The guy does a great job. Does it leave it with the lady with an answer or just kind of speculation?
When he's literally about to confront in the final episode, he's literally on his way to confront the guy.
Yeah. And the guy dies. Oh boy. And it kind of ends with him saying like, I'll never have the closure.
I've worked for years on this. And I'll never have the definitive answer. It kills me. But what I've
learned in this process is I, what's more important is my son and my life and my family. And I have to
kind of let it go. And would, you know, like, it's great. It's a great series. It's great. All right.
I'll check it out. I'll just do a super quick one. We work colon or the making and breaking of a $47
billion unicorn. For some, somehow I completely missed we work. I've never read an article about it.
I knew nothing about it. My wife saw that it was on who last night and was like, we were,
what's that about? We work. I'd never heard of it. So for me, it was educational, informative. I
always love a documentary tracking a narcissist's rise and eventual fall. And that's what this is.
I mean, this guy is like the Tommy Wiseau of the investment world. He's odd. He's very, but he's
very, you see how people fall under his spell. And he started very much a cult like system of
business in New York that was being overvalued by billions of dollars. This, this, some foreign
money came into it and kind of blew them up. And then the whole thing fell apart. He's married
to the cousin of Winath Paltrow, who's clearly kind of pulling the strings. And she seems like she's
really wants this to be a fucking cult. Okay. So look, if you like that sort of rise and fall
thing, as I always do, it's a pretty juicy one, pretty entertaining one, pretty well done. Check
around. All right. Pat, why don't you introduce our movie for today? Yes. How the people what we're
going to be reviewing in a little bit about the film? Our picture today is called Train to Besan.
This is a South Korean film. It came out three, four years ago, 2016. And it was a huge hit in Korea.
It grossed $80 million in South Korea, which is a bigger deal there than here.
And it says here was the highest grossing film of the year in Malaysia, Hong Kong, Singapore,
South Korea. So look, it's a huge hit. I had been hearing tell about it being really entertaining. And
for whatever reason, I never caught up with it. Joe hadn't either. A lot of you have been asking about
it. What's the deal when you guys doing Train to Besan, et cetera, et cetera. And the answer is now
the movie is about zombies. Essentially, there's a chemical leak at a biotech plant,
you know, shades of like Chernobyl or something like that. And it is turning, you know, it's that old
thing. It's the virus. Zombies as virus, basically, which is one of the most standard explanations
of how zombies come to be. It's either they're back from the dead or it's usually some sort of virus
or outbreak. Where this zombie movie feels different to me and feels better is in its character and
it's plotting. We complain every week about these big action movies and how the characters are
non -existent, the stories non -existent. And I think people often take that sort of review as like I
want everything to be pulp fiction or I want everything to be, you know, a masterpiece. It's not the
case at all. You know, I actually like a lot of just trashy shit if the characters are good and the
plot is entertaining and the twists keep coming or whatever. And this is a movie that just does everything
right in terms of giving us a pretty extensive cast of characters that you care about. And a plot
that is, you know, it's certainly not reinventing the wheel. The zombie attacks are not reinventing the
wheel. They felt kind of influenced by World War Z and also, you know, 20 days later that style of
zombie. But basically they're trying to get from one side of the train to another. It's a pretty simple
setup and they just keep it fresh. They keep it interesting. They keep it entertaining. I enjoyed it,
Joe. Yeah, I enjoyed it as well. I was, I had zero interest initially when this film first came out
because I was like, man, I'm zombie now. And on top of it, we're not even getting the good crawl out of
the ground zombies. I was never a big fan of the virus zombies, right? Because they're never rotting,
you know, that's like the park that I like. But so I never really wanted to watch it. I wasn't
terribly interested. And then Pat mentioned doing it on the show and I thought, yeah, all right.
You know, I should, I should see this like it's a popular horror movie. And Pat had said that people
were requesting that we review it. And Pinkstone had told me many times that it was amazing. He's like,
look, dude, I know it's probably not for you because it's a zombie movie. But he was like, I almost
see it as like a sequel to the Zack Snyder dawn of the dead. Like he's like, it's in that vein. And it
seems like the next step in that direction or whatever. So, so anyway, I was happy to sit down finally
and watch it. And right away from the jump, I was like, this is really interesting. I care immediately
about this guy. I care immediately about his relationship with his daughter. And I can tell
something bad is going to happen, you know. And the first zombie attack in the film is very, very
well done. It's, it's haunting. And the first time you see somebody on the train turn, it's, it's
freaky. And they manage to make them look really cool without decomposition. And it's just on when
it when it steps on the gas, that's it. You're on the ride. It does not let up. It doesn't let up for
so long that by the end of it, I was there was a little part of me that was like, Jesus Christ.
Like give this guy a fucking break already. But it's almost exhausting in a good way. Yeah. But,
but I thought it was great. I really liked the characters. I really, my favorite character was the
was the couple, like the big guy. The big guy steals the movie. His name is, and I'm going to,
I'm going to do my best. Ma Dong, Siok, or Suk, maybe Ma Dong Suk. I apologize. I should know that
and I don't, but he has it. I looked him up because I loved him so much in the movie. And yeah, he's
kind of a heavy set Jackie Chan sort of vibe where he's just like a complete ass kicker. He's
completely steals the movie. And they're going to have him in the new film with Kid Harrington and
Kumail and others, the, the, the eternal's the next Marvel movie he's supposed to be in.
He, he's, he has, he also has an American name. The last name is Lee. I forget his, I forget his
full name because he does do American stuff too. So, uh, but he's apparently one of the biggest actors
in South Korea. And also too, he, uh, he's, uh, he's, he's weird. In this movie, I was like, he,
he looked like a fat guy, but like, yeah, I looked up pictures of him and he's like, Jack, he's like a
Dave Batista. Yeah, kind of guy. This was 2016. So he might have gotten Jack, but I mean, for me, the idea
of a, of a heavy set action hero, I was like, I fucking love this. It's big part of the reason I liked him
so much. Yeah, I liked it. I liked that he was so caring of his wife. Yes, I liked that he was
this big and posing guy. And she was really like very comically condescending to him all the time and
calling him an idiot and stuff. Like, it's just a funny relationship. It was endearing. And the fact
that he's pregnant, rups the ante, obviously, uh, his opening scene. You see this big, awesome dude.
And he's like, you know, he's whispering into the bathroom like, are you about done peeing, honey? And
like it's the, it's, they, they introduce every character perfectly because you have to keep a lot
of people straight. Um, it just goes the little extra mile that, that we always are complaining that we
wish these movies would take. Yeah, just an extra 10 minutes of characterization. Some great twists and
plot details that I've never seen in a zombie movie when they show up to the quarantine site at one
point and debored the train. Uh, they, they go to meet the military and the military has all
been infected. And the entire guard that is there to, to, to conceivably help them, attacks them. And
I was like, wow, that's a great twist. I didn't see that coming. Um, they, they really, really hit some
really nice details like that. I liked the detail of if they can't see you, they don't know you're there.
Right. Um, which added some really nice moments for the film where they would turn out when they
would go through tunnels on the train and they would figure out where it's a sneak past the zombies
because zombies couldn't see them anymore. Little stuff like that. I have two small criticisms.
Uh, the one is there, there's a guy in this thing who's a businessman. Every one of these zombie
survival movies always says a businessman who's a complete fucking prick. Yeah. Uh, there's always the
guy that's like the hot shot doesn't care about anybody else. Blah blah blah. Once to buy his way out
of the situation, there's a guy in this, I'll give you $5 ,000 not to eat my brain. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
There's a guy in this who is the best example of it I've ever seen. He has a complete piece of
fucking shit. Uh, and he gets his in the end. But it bothered me that he doesn't get it bad enough.
He just turned, he just gets turned. And then he's the guy responsible for biting the dad in the end
and the reason the dad dies. I didn't want to see the dad die. I wanted to see this new version of
a weird family that he acquired as he was on this train trip with his daughter. And now this pregnant
woman that he promised the big guy he would look after, I wanted to see the three of them make it.
And it's like, oh, this is like the family that's going to plant the seeds for the new society
or whatever. I was very, very upset to see the dad die. I thought it was too much on the little
girl because you know the mom's dead too. Right. I just felt so fucked. I wish they had kept them alive.
Because they did a sequel, which I'm curious to see. I haven't seen it. But I don't know what it is
or what it's about. The sequel is directed by the same, same writer director, I believe.
It didn't interest me. It was like, these soldiers have to go recover some buried money.
I was like, I was like, it was one of those things where I was like, do they know what they did
with the first one? Are they aware? Like why that was awesome? Like, are there any zombies in it?
Yeah. They have to go into like the zombie zone to get this. But I was like, this just,
this sounds just like any, it sounds like any zombie thing that you know what I mean, that you'd
ever see. But it sounds like it's like there's two of the legend of Pearl is going.
So anyway, those are my two criticisms. I didn't like that the asshole kind of got one up on my
favorite character by turning the dad. And I didn't like that the dad died. And I didn't like that I
didn't get, I wanted to see that fucking asshole get like his guts ripped out of him. I hear you
know. And like, like, and it was like it, and so that's it. Small criticisms. Yeah. Great fucking movie
through and through suspenseful action packed frantic gory and all the right ways.
I said my hog is up. My hog is up as well. It's very well done. You know, they just, they take the time.
They take five additional minutes to make you care about each person understand who they are.
Understand what their goals are. And the villain like Joe said, he's a piece of shit and you're
rooting for him to die. You go see almost any movie these days. The villain is just a big blob who
wants the world to end in general. You know, it's it's just it's it's it was refreshing to have real
human characters throughout. And you know, it's a great little screenwriting tip that I learned early
on. You got to you got to have the problem have problems amongst the characters when the zombies
arrive or when the Titanic hits the iceberg or when the whatever, you know, like too many movies just
start with the problem. And you don't know anything about the people facing the problem so you don't
give a shit about them. You take that it can be as simple as two minutes at the beginning to let
you know who these people are and have them involved in a little problem that doesn't involve the aliens
coming to earth or whatever else because then you can carry that interpersonal conflict through the
movie and give you something to go to other than just look out. There's this giant thing trying to
kill me, which is all movies are now. Yeah, it's a good it's a very well written movie. I'm realizing
as I talk about it that I kind of underrated it. It's it's it's really good. Check out trying to be
son. Joe and I will be back next time with one of those movies I'm talking about right now Kong versus
Godzilla. Um, thank you all for time. I can't remember which way it goes. It's I think it is
Godzilla versus Kong, which you think could be alphabetical and it is so good. Um, thank you to Emily
for all your hard work. Yeah. Thank you to all of you for staying with us here on Patreon and supporting
us. We've we've been much happier with this with this new arrangement than we ever were on any of
the networks and the only reason we can keep it afloat is because of you guys and we appreciate it.
It's hard to grow a show when you're Patreon only. It really can only happen through friend Rex.
So, um, please do if you get that opportunity, if you think a friend would dig us, let them know.
All right, folks, that's the show and we'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell.