I'll see you in hell.
Welcome to we'll see you in hell.
This is the podcast talking genre movies.
These horror sci -fi, what have you, we're here to review them, we're here to discuss them,
we're here to get into them.
Patty Walsh joins me, Joe DeRosa, we're here, Pat.
It is made that Walsh, I'm here, I'm queer, get used to it, you know.
We are talking today about not one of the most popular horror franchises, but certainly
one of the most cultishly beloved and that is Phantasm, Phantasm 1, 2, 3, 4 and ravager.
This is a franchise I had seen Phantasm decades ago and was kind of scooped out by it but
I had never really seen the others and then I went through and watched them.
One and then 3, 4, 5 are all on shutter with Joe Bob Commentary, that's the way I did it,
it's very fun.
Two is a little tricky to track down, I had one of those 4 movies on 2 DVDs, little box sets
that were always available for 10 bucks at Target or something and Phantasm 2 happened to be
on one of them so that's the one that's a little tricky to find but the other ones are all
on shutter and I'm sure you can buy part two somewhere if you want to catch up with us.
You can get the entire Phantasm series in HD on DVD for about $11 at Best Buy.
There was a blue ray box set that was also released that has become even more expensive
now because it's out of print but as far as I can tell the reviews I read of that box
set said that the movies really weren't that were indecernably the same as the DVDs like
and they couldn't tell the difference between the blue ray transfers and the DVD transfers.
That's disappointing.
The DVD prints are, the problem is the packaging is terrible on the DVD prints, the blue
ray thing comes in this glorious white box with a ball in it and all this shit.
The DVD set looks like it would be tossed in like a gas station bargain bin but you're actually
getting like 1080p transfers in the movies so it's got the remastered Phantasm that JJ Abrams remastered
himself and then first time ever HD transfers of the other four movies so you can find them and you
can get into it. I mean we got a lot to cover here usually on these apps we don't do any
other segments.
Well I will say before we do real quick if you are hurting for cash and I was telling
this to Joe as well go through your music and movie collections and I don't know if it is
because Amazon is currently out of stock on things as you can imagine with what the world
is going through but I have been listing some records some blue rays and getting amazing, amazing
prices for that especially coming from a guy who as Joe knows we've been through a lot of
disappointments up at the Amoeba music check in thing they'll give you two bucks you know so if
you get online I think a lot of things have gone out of print a lot of things are harder to find I
think they're stopping to make blue rays so more and more things are going to be going out of print.
So these collections especially since they're not going to be bringing anything out to replace them
like when laser discs went under DVDs were not far behind and then blue rays were not far behind
but once they stop making physical media this time out that's going to be it I'm fairly certain we're
just going with downloading and streaming I think that's where America has decided we're going
and that's very sad and that's its own episode for another time but I am finding like movies I
didn't even care about gone with the wind I told you I made a bunch of money off of and I was never
going to wash it so I was like great let's get it out of the house but like I sold the death proof
soundtrack Tarantino's death proof soundtrack probably his least memorable soundtrack sold the vinyl
of that like a hundred and fifty bucks the other day. What the hell did you have the death proof
soundtrack for? I bought it for ten bucks and I liked the music in it I had all of Tarantino sound
tracks but yeah I was like is this worth being a hundred and fifty dollars and having it in my
collection note isn't so especially what you have all this time I've been basically running a little
store I'm doing two sales a day you know it's kind of fun so it's a good side hustle if you're looking
for a little money there's money to be made on Amazon and also if you're looking to sell something
especially Criterions you can't do it on a laptop here's a little hint that I'm I'm almost
not knowing if I should be sharing with you but if you do it on your phone you can sell anything
so a lot of times you go to sell a Criterion Blu -ray on your on your desktop computer and they'll
go Amazon will not let you sell this but then you do it on your phone and they do so highly
recommended if you're in a bind a lot of people have a trouble making rent etc and it's a fun
side hustle if you got old Blu -rays and vinyl I'm getting money for them I've never gotten before
beautiful all right beautiful and you're still telling your uh body as well
yes yeah that's that goes without saying right you know glory all type stuff because of COVID but
sure and I'll be selling DVDs of Pat selling his body
yeah those will be just not great sellers I'm going to tell you in advance all right let's get into
phantasm for those of you unfamiliar with the premise of this series it relies very heavily on the
the title itself phantasm phantasm is a vision sort of a fever dream an illusion a delusion whatever
and basically this film revolves around a young man named or boy in the first film named Mike
whose parents have died and his brother Jody and Jody's best friend Reggie are concerned about
Mike because Mike has not dealt well with his parents death right he's been having nightmares
and that sort of thing this is all linked to a new funeral director who has come into town
who is very strange and mysterious and seems to be doing odd things around town as people are starting
to turn up dead Mike takes it upon himself to sort of explore this and as things unfold we come to
know this funeral director as the tall man he's a supernatural being he is excavating graves and using
the dead bodies for some purpose which we find out later is to turn these dead bodies into his minions
so he can I guess eventually take over the world that's sort of the rough
concept here of the phantasm films yeah it's it's worth shouting out
Angus Scrim as the tall man he is this franchises Michael Myers for Fred Cruz
and much more well you know you don't get a whole lot of personality from him he's good he doesn't say
a lot but this is a guy much like the old man and Pulitzer guys too who I thought was the same guy for
years as a kid they get a lot of mileage off of how scary they look angus Scrim RIP and no offense
very disturbing looking man the original phantasm has it's interesting it has this feel I see why
JJ Abrams liked it and he did an amazing restoration of it it's one of my favorite things JJ Abrams has
done but it's got kind of that feel of like because it's kids getting caught up in horrific stuff
of like a goonies or an ET type thing however it's so much stranger than that I mean the the
comparison I would make would be like David Lynch meets goonies but it's not it's not that at all
that's not even a good comparison it kind of creates its own tone in that it is a kind of
uncompromising dream world that doesn't really care if it makes sense for moment to moment while also
being that like coming of age type kids action movie it's got a tone unlike anything else that's
what I love about the first phantasm yeah and the series created by Don Coscarelli he wrote and
directed all five well he only produced in co -wrote five but the first four I believe are solely written
and directed and produced by Coscarelli yes yeah it is a strange sort of it does have that sort
of strange goonies you know stranger things vibe to it to an extent but yeah it is this sort of
crazed fever dream they repeatedly hammer home the concept in this movie or in these movies of you
can't believe anything you see which relies heavily on what the term phantasm means and it's the title
the first film is I think unarguably the best in the franchise and I noticed something when
I was watching this film and I rewatched all five of these do this episode and when I was watching
the first one I realized something I wrote it down and then as I kept watching the movies I just
kept taking note after note after note after note and then I actually took my theories online to see
if they compared with anybody else's and sure enough I found critics who had very similar theories
to the film but the setup is the film kind of opens up with a funeral where Jody who's Mike's older brother
Mike is the kid Jody's Mike's older brother he said their friend has been killed and Jody says basically
he wouldn't let Mike come to this funeral because their parents died a few weeks ago
or a little while ago and Mike has had nightmares for weeks ever since and it dawned on me suddenly
that this entire series is all in Mike's head this is a delusional journey that Mike is on because the
event of his parents death was so unthinkable to him and he was so unable to digest it that he has
set into course this sort of fantastic series of events in his head and sure enough at the top of
the film he goes to a fortune teller to sort of deal with these emotions of loss that he's going
through and the fortune teller says put your hand in this box this black box and Mike puts his hand
in it and then he starts to say it's it hurts it hurts it hurts and then when he finally gets his
hand out he says what was that that really hurt she says the pain was all in your mind it's a reflection
of yourself and to me that kind of set off this concept in my head that everybody in this film is
an invention of Mike yeah it's a kid dealing with his parents death he's terrified of death so he
personifies death in his head death becomes literally the tall man a man that goes from town to town
spreading a plague that kills people that he takes their bodies and turns them into his minions
reggie who is the ponytail kind of ass kicking ass chasing buddy of the ass of the franchise he's very
funny yeah and they lean into what to what makes them so funny as the franchise goes which is
a very average looking guy who is constantly chasing hot women and getting them and constantly
inexplicably kicking the shit out of everybody yeah so yeah he's great and then there's Jody who's
Mike's older brother and and so as I'm watching this I'm saying to myself Reggie is the id
he's the he's the set of uncoordinated instinctual desires he's all about sex and violence and whatever
Jody Mike's older brother who he idolizes to a stalk literally a stalker level in the first movie
watches his brother have set yeah that's Jody by the way the tall man
yeah who turns into a woman sometimes he is if you really look at this he's fucking the tall man
yeah Jody is the super ego he plays the critical and like moralizing an unattainable role
and Mike is the ego he's the organized realistic agent that kind of mediates everything between
all these people and his fear of death is the tall man and that's what this movie is he and so my
first clue in the first movie is when you watch there are a couple nightmare scenes that take place in
Mike's bedroom I don't think this is any coincidence I think this was fully done by Cosgrolly on
Mike's bedroom has a floor to ceiling picture of a moon landscape on it yeah the wall directly
next to his bed if you look at the portion of the bed and it's shot like this a few times and I
believe it's very much on purpose if you look at the portion of the bed from about Mike's waist up
which they frame it like that a lot the portion of the poster you see behind him looks identical to
the marbling in the mortuary of the walls it looks like the mortuary wall I think and then there's
a scene where the tall man is literally standing over Mike's bed yeah I think that that is blatantly
telling you this is an extension of Mike himself the tall man is not real by the way the end of the
movie Reggie says repeatedly this tall man of yours is not real they do this a lot throughout these
movies he's not real this is a kid that has gone deep into his head in a in a in a way of dealing
with his own grief and creating a fantastic universe for himself I think that's a fascinating take have
you not Cosgrolly at least according to the way Joe Bob lays it out was a big stoner and he made
these movies or at least he made the first movie very young with like money from his parents right you
think that all that was intentional have you read interviews with Cosgrolly or that's just
I didn't read interviews with Cosgrolly but I did read some reviews of the first film and that that
echoed these concepts not exactly to what I'm saying but some of it I mean but it'll go
something to further illustrate what I'm saying is he gives Mike gives these characters superhuman
qualities Jody at the end of the movie they have to date the plot is we have to lure the tall man up
to this there's like a mine shaft right and and and Jody says if you can just get the tall man to
like fall into this mine shaft we can it's a cartoonish childlike concept I mean it's it's insane it's
almost like Scooby -Doo shit which to me says a or sorry which is which is the part A of what I'm
would see a solving a situation like this a child thinks he could trap death it's crazy it's it's
it's absurd then once they pull that off Jody his older brother who to me is just again just another
part of Mike who Mike wishes he could be literally pushes boulders with his bare hands down a mountain
side to seal the the shaft up yeah it's insane it's it's so crazy so now you've got a kid imagining
the person he idolizes doing something literally superhuman it's literally literally superhuman
the other thing I think that explains that Mike is the tall man and this gets illustrated more and
more throughout these sequels he's in it the tall man is inexplicably obsessed with Mike inexplicably
it makes it makes no sense it's never explained and to me that is the egocentric concept of death
why does death have to happen to me why me why me fuck you what happens to everybody you're not
special but we all feel like when it happens to us it's special that we somehow been singled out you
know you you made me want to watch it again I you know I'm looking at the wikipedia page now
costarelli says he wanted to do it about how our culture handles death so it seems like you're you're
correct there also so this idea was inspired by something wicked this way comes costarelli wanted
to cut that into a movie they were like we're already making it into a movie so he went this way
with it which is kind of interesting but well and very similar because that's about the strange
older man that comes to town that has some connection to the funeral parlor whatever that is
obsessed with this young boy and is able to prevent people from dying you know I never I never knew
that there was a connection there but I love that movie what a great movie I've never seen it but
I mean to me that's a perfect example of why people should do more original movies and yes you can
be inspired by things everybody is but take it in your own direction I mean I'm so glad the world
has fantasism instead of don costarelli something that wikipedia this way comes then we never had
this franchise now we have sure so this movie on a budget of like 300 grand is spookier scarier has
more of a sense of what freaks people out then most huge budget horror movies I think fantasism
is definitely the classic of them I think each one except for which we'll get to the later movies
have big pluses about them but fantasism is sort of the most creative the most world building you
know it sets up a lot of stuff in this early one and all the stuff in the mausoleum with the flying balls
the effects are better down the line like in two the there's there's more behind them there's there's
they were able to do what they wanted on a bigger and better scale but there's something about one
and it's low budgetness that makes it the scariest of the bunch by far right yeah one is definitely
the scariest two gets into aliens actually I think that's a great comparison alien and aliens is kind
of like phantasm one and phantasm two the sequel is the sort of action version of the first film
and the last part version I'm often compared to evil dead and evil dead too just because yes phantasm
two is just sort of like a bigger budget remake of the one I see there is a you know a cup just
a couple other things that we're gonna see repeat it throughout this franchise that I think support my
interpretation of it we see Reggie die in the first movie and then at the end he's alive yeah
we don't see Jodie die and then at the end Reggie says Jodie died in a car crash right this sort of
playing around with continuity and whatnot to me supports this concept that these people are just
extensions of Mike like he's just these are the it's a fantasy world he's having where where it's
different versions of himself that he's seeing dying returning everybody kind of comes back
throughout this thing throughout the series dies they leave they're not dead they're dead
in for instance in part two at the end of part one excuse me at the end of part one mic is
taken by the tall man that's sort of the last shock of the film right great shock yes part two opens
up directly at the moment that that happens it opens up immediately as that when that happens
we see I say you that that picture very strange the ending of Phantasm when Reggie is sitting
with his arms around the boy on like a bare skin rug in front of the fireplace I just can't believe
when shooting that they weren't like let's restage this in some way it looks very romantic between
the two and he's an ice cream man and and people always have to remember about them but it feels strange
if in the fireplace does it help yeah they're in front of a roaring fire it looks like a couple like
in a burnt rental movie or something so throughout the film throughout part one this house
there and at the end this is Mike's house we've seen them all in it yeah where we see Mike and his
brother and it repeatedly yes part two opens at the exact moment when Mike gets abducted upstairs
Reggie runs upstairs fights the tall man or fights the little minions you know kicks him ass
ends up blowing up the house to kill the tall man whatever as he barely escapes with his life
and manages to save Mike yeah we jump forward 10 years or so Mike is now getting out of an insane
asylum Reggie picks him up one of the first things Reggie says to him is Mike this is all in your head
this crazy story of me blowing up my own house yeah so the second film now you have Reggie
referring to the house he blew up as his own which it was it it was Mike and Jody's house
well so the barracuda that Jody drives through the entire first film is now just suddenly Reggie's car
Reggie's the guy that always in the barracuda so now this is where this begins in the series
you start to see character traits and things we identify certain characters with
just being shifted back and forth without any explanation whatsoever
which again says to me these are people he's creating his head they're not real people
this is just some weird fantasy trip he's on where he's like well what if we could fight death
and literally destroy it right um anyway part two is a lot of fun it's not as scary as part one
it's not as good of a movie as part one but it's a lot of fun I would say would you agree
I think two is awesome I mean uh my I had a buddy when I was a kid who was obsessed with
phantasm too and to the extent that like we never even discussed the other ones he was always
watching phantasm too um Mike is played by James LaGros who is an actor if you've ever seen an
independent movie made between 1988 and 1998 he was in it um and it's crazy that they thought he was
like a bigger name for the franchise James LaGros but he's fine I mean I liked him in the movie I didn't
mind the trade -out but like for a franchise with such huge fans it does seem pretty shitty to swap
out your main guy for one movie but the studio it was a studio thing yeah this is what the studio
is do they think nobody gives a shit they're asking Reggie locally is still in there the action is
awesome apparently the idea to kind of take it on this uh take to franchise on the road trip was
inspired by Salem's lot okay but it works really well like it's the to me all this stuff that you
read more into I was just seeing is kind of dream logic and honestly Joe Bob was backing that up he was
like these movies make no sense they're all over the place they're wild so I just kind of thought to
myself well yeah I won't try to read anymore into it it just doesn't make sense and that's fine
and you got to go with it like a dream but your theories seem to lend some credence to their being
more thought to this stuff than then then we initially realized uh part two has several evil dead
nods to it evil dead two nods yeah I came out a year after evil dead two yeah um first of all the weapons
Reggie at one point has a crazy you know this is where he creates the four barrel
sold off shotgun right uses through the next four movies um but at one point Reggie is actually
holding a shotgun and a chainsaw together which is an ash nod Reggie's personality is not ash like in
the first film it becomes completely ash like in this one this one has far more comedic moments
and goofiness to it uh like in with his interactions with the monsters and thing
there's even a guy that has to cut off his own hand at one point uh to get away uh
and then of course the ashes that they show in the mausoleum at one point say Sam Raimi on them
there's a lot of evil dead two nods here yeah clearly they're friends um but it's a fun movie
he really is it's it's just grosser it's bigger uh everywhere there was one killer ball and the original
there's six in part two um so for me i mean especially if i had been like my buddy i just wasn't
into horror when i was a kid but if i had seen phantasm one at age seven and then at age 10 phantasm two
comes along i would have been like yeah this is what i'm talking about you get you get older and
you know you see it strikes and weaknesses but it is just kind of the rambo two the evil dead two
the uh it's it's what you liked about the first one ramped up action -wise budget -wise special
effect -wise but lacking some in terms of character development in terms of you know real good scares
etc so so that brings us to to uh to part three um part three is called Lord of the Dead that's
subtitle for it um part three ramps it up another level now part three gets even
fucking more batshit so the end of part two ends with them escaping the mortuary they're in the car
they're in a hurry with reggie's got the chick that he uh is in love with and has banged at the
beginning of the movie or the middle of the movie rather uh Mike has been telepathically communicating
with this blonde girl who also was aware of the tall man and his doings whatever the four of them
escape in one piece at the end of the film only to see that uh the girl that reggie is slept with
is actually one of the tall man's minions now she's been infected or whatever you want to call it
yeah uh they uh she kills reggie again reggie this is the second time we've seen reggie die he does
at the end of the movie and uh the woman that Mike is in love with is pulled out of the car by
the tall man uh part three opens up the the in that moment in that moment reggie again inexplicably
just alive yeah it's not dead um and uh he announced Mike the original actor is back uh in this one
which is great it's good to see him back now this one as this franchise goes
i love Mike as a kid as an adult he does not work as well especially in the later
parts i mean it's cool to have an actor play it from like a kid all the way up like you know
horror boyhood style or something but he's not super effective as the the lead of an action horror
franchise what will you get down to it after he's a kid yeah things kind of slide off in my opinion yeah
he's not he doesn't have the ass kicking this of reggie no or the lines you know like if reggie wasn't
there we wouldn't be talking about this franchise because he's in nothing right so this film is
interesting and i'll take my fur my theory a little bit further um
what happens here is reggie and Mike get separated almost right from the straight to jump of this thing
uh reggie then fairly quickly into the film meets a young boy named Timmy yeah
what Timmy's a kid whose parents were killed by the tall man and is this complete badass
he there's a scene right out of the jump you meet him as he kills two adults with like these crazy
contraptions he's made right to protect himself he's living on his own he's like 11 years old
and he's surviving and he's kicking ass and there's literally a scene in front of a fireplace between
reggie and Timmy that models are that that mirrors the scene between reggie and Mike in the first film
at the end and so now i'm saying Timmy is has taken the place of Mike this is Mike's fantasy now
this is the kid i wish i could have been right this is the kid i wish i could have been in the face of
death and i failed this is this is who i wish i was and and he's not which i find very interesting
i find very interesting and then they also do a thing where in part one Mike has to escape to tall man
who has minions uh they attack a car he's in and he jumps out of through the black window of a moving car
rolls across the street Timmy does the exact same thing in this one the exact same thing he jumps out
of the back of a her through the window rolls across the street yeah so these parallels are i find
very interesting to uh to support this idea that that i have that this is all fake uh yet i mean
i wish i had to have this going into the franchise because i really did just kind of shed my brain
off and enjoy the uh the dream like visuals of it but it seems like you're on a road track might be
time for a rewatch for me by the way i read one random line from the plots andopsis on the wikipedia page
and that one was as he explains they witnessed him removing the brain of a newly shrunken dwarfs
and placing it into a sphere thus turning the body into a drone and the mind into a killer
and this is an insane collective a newly shrunken dwarf because there were also dwarves running around
that look kind of like e -walks you know they have the the hoods and the bdi's and the
java's they look at the java's the desert yeah yeah but i mean it's it is funny
i rewatched these all with arie chaffir uh because he had never seen them so i said i'm gonna come
over we're gonna watch the fantasy movies yeah and that's what he was saying he was like they look
like those java's and you know like it was and it was fun to watch these with some of you that never
even didn't even know what the franchise was yeah because it was a lot of like your friend going
what the fuck you know like because you're like yeah they're bad shit man these are having a rough
we watched three and then i went home and watched four myself and five myself um he really
really locked out arie's fear uh when the torment now here's the thing here's the thing um
jody when when when now jody comes back in this one as a sphere yes when he comes back he explains to
mic uh or at some point in this film i can't remember if it's when jody comes back he says it or
they just remember it but they show in this film that that jody dies in a in the car wreck okay the
car wreck they show is the is the footage of the car wreck that mike and reggie get into in part one
yes wild wild do you think that i mean do you think that that was to save money do you think
that that was part of however he views this plot because they did use footage from later fantasms
in i think i think i think there's more to it on purpose than meets the eye yeah but i also
think that when you're creating a series like this you you almost get into this sort of auto pilot
mode where you're planting things that you might not even realize you're even planting yes do you know
what i mean yeah um so so i think it's a little bit of both probably but but this one it what's
also interesting to me is this is the this is the uh episode of the franchise that starts to explain
or elaborate in my opinion the on the concept that that of death of this all just being a concept of
death to mike because this is when the tall man starts letting mike go inexplicably he's obsessed with
him yet he's not taking him and he says uh at one like people are dying senselessly left and right
yet the tall man starts letting mike and reggie go with this idea of like it's not your time yet
well that's how death works when it's your time it's your time yeah you know what i mean mike
dies at the beginning of the movie and is sent back yeah he lives through death at the beginning of the movie
so uh that's interesting and the other thing i really liked about three is they did some nice callbacks
like i like that in the first one one of the tall man severed fingers becomes a bug
and this one the hand it turns into this little they cut off one of his hands and it becomes like a
little monster that's pretty fun uh i also noticed that that this movie and also in four uh we have
four movies in a row of a car spiraling through the air right at some point um i like the zombie nurse
at the beginning of this thing i really like the zombie trio of like crux that looked like they were
out of like the gang that couldn't shoot straight or something you know um i love three for me
you know three is the is the army of darkness uh it is it expands the world they don't they clearly
don't quite have the budget of two i mean two was just like all right we got some fucking money
let's have some fucking fun three seems like a step back in terms of budget which required a step up
in terms of kind of creativity and craziness and they delivered i mean this this to me was
where i fully expected the franchise to start dropping off and instead i completely loved
the direction they went especially with reggie this is where i started realizing what a
great and funny and unusual character reggie is because and they said they were basically playing
themselves so my thinking is the guy that plays reggie must just be this you know everybody's got a friend
who is not attractive and is randomly a ladies man for me it's Joe um all right uh he is so right
and you know i texted Joe i was like who knew at this time wherever movie you're watching is so
amazingly woke and stepping over it's back to check every box and make everybody happy and this
absolutely ridiculous horror movie from 1994 has a completely casual and not commented on interracial
relationship and sexual in count you know he's having sex with this girl a beautiful woman and he never
really acted again much glory a lin henry she was like an extra and uh definitely he's an advocate
but yeah she's more of a musician okay i read up on her own like budget for this film by the way
2 .5 million budget for part part two was three million yeah um this one really ups the
anti with the balls this one is where they have like the fucking like army of sphere balls which is
really cool lot of balls i mean the the ball thing where it goes into your head then the little drill
comes out and then the puffs coming out and everything there's just a lot of awesome fucking visuals
and as they get the money to do them the way they want you're like that's fucking sweet uh well worth
watching with all the joe bobs they bring in like this sweet 65 year old woman who looks like your mom
who designed all the balls for phantasm you know like i don't know they it's such it was such a treat
i watched them all in one night and it was such a treat to watch them with joe bob and all these people
because they put so much love into these movies as you can tell but i mean yeah to finish the point
there's a progressive feeling about these movies in a weird way they're like
i i i loved him just having this relationship with a black woman i don't know what to tell you
it's like uh that was at a time in american movies where that would have to be commented on
yeah and and and you know i love that i used to have a joke in my act that i stopped doing because
it was way way way too narrow for most audiences but i used to have a joke where i'd say double dragon
is the most tolerant video game of all time you're going through the street you're beating the shit
out of men women there's a few trans people in there for sure you're using little cat whips like
it's wild everybody's wearing leather to me that's what phantasm is it's everybody's on an even playing
field the men the women they're all hitting each other everybody's fighting everybody's fucking
nothing is precious like it truly isn't even because it's a barren wasteland yeah um yeah i mean for
me i i'm not going to say three is my is my favorite but it was the biggest surprise in that
i was just delighted by how funny it was how cool it was and i mean in many ways a step up from two
for me and it's a it's fun to see jody come back it was fun to see jody come back from part one that's
a nice little surprise and he actually becomes part of the story from here on out uh to further my
theory of the tallman being Mike in a mad you know something that Mike has imagined Mike this
film ends with Mike being implanted with a silver ball in his brain yeah uh again he's the only one
the tallman ever does this too yes and now he is the fucking tallman basically he's a reflection of
the tallman to an extent right um which brings us to part four by the way another fascinating fact
from the wikipedia part three had a two week theatrical run in only two markets baton Rouge and my
hometown of st. Louis in both markets phantasm three was the highest grossing film the two weeks
of play but that's it that's weird anytime you read about any movie there are choices made where you're
like what the fuck were people thinking uh this is a time when harry there was just no respect for harry
this was the these were the dead years and you're talking about the mid 90s because
which means the harry that they did want to put out there it would if it didn't emulate scream they
wanted nothing to fucking do with it right scream this might be pre -screen but you know
pre -screen scream was 96 but yeah okay but this is you know we're getting into that zone of like if
it's not a bunch of teens right in some sort of you know uh dire situation being hunted down
away you know um anyway part four picks up exactly where part three leaves off uh reggie is left
alone in the uh tall man's mortuary uh and um timmy is mysteriously gone he gets sort of sucked out
of the window at the end exactly in that by the way exactly in the same way at the end of three
timmy gets sucked out exactly the same way mike does at the end of part one again just a mirror of
mike but timmy now is mysteriously gone it's never explained he's never mentioned ever again
it's it's as if he was a figment of somebody's imagination right uh reggie is trapped by the tall man
and the tall man just lets reggie go inexplicably uh and says play carefully the final game begins or whatever
you know and it's uh again these are i'm just making points to support my theories we go here i
don't need to hammer it every time uh there was a severe budget cut in part four part four
so like uh and uh i don't even know if if joe bob went into this but roger avry who co -wrote pulled
fiction yeah he went on to do uh killings oe which is a really underrated uh heist movie with
eric stolt great movie yeah um and now he's got some new weird thing on amazon so he is still making
movies just on a lower scale but roger avry was a huge fan of the phantasm movies he's coming off
pulled fiction at this time and he wrote this epic screenplay called phantasm 1999 ad uh what a great
title yeah it was supposed to cost our Bruce Campbell and this thing as i'm reading here ran into financing
difficulties and so they did for instead on a much lower budget a much lower scale so this movie as joe
was kind of telling me beforehand with used a lot of footage that was unused from phantasm wanted to
mainly most mostly one it's mostly one because it's mostly young flash flashbacks of young mike
yeah their budget was cut to six hundred fifty thousand dollars that's a hell of a cut
you completely feel it i mean this this movie like i often think okay if i was gonna make uh a low budget
indie movie i i always think why don't more people do stuff in the desert we're close to it
you can go out you don't need any permits you know nobody's gonna follow you out into the desert and
you get immediate production value you know so why not write something set in the desert
my guess is that's what cost really thought here i lived two hours away from great desert i can get
a Lawrence of Arabia looking movie on a six hundred thousand dollar budget um the truth is i have no
idea why this movie spends so much time in the desert oh i read up on it it's because of the budget
well yeah okay it's the yeah it's the only it's the only phantasm movie did not feature a more
trowary even part five does yeah part five is by far the lowest budget um but it's the only one
to not feature a more trowary and uh he shot a lot of it in the desert because he couldn't
afford you know it was cheaper it was cheaper to shoot outside which is nuts because again you've got
one or two spiraling car crashes into explosions in this there's a sequence in this film
where reggie is pulled over by a cop who turns into like a zombie cop yeah that eventually ends in
the car exploding and the cop walking around on completely on this is a stunt this stunt must cost
a must cost 50 grand it must have and you're going why don't you just not do the fire stunt
yeah kill the zombie in a different way and then you could maybe do a mortuary sequence in this
or something you know it's kind of strange to me you can't do uh a phantasm
phantasm movie without the mortuary it's it's why people are coming you know uh
nothing about four worked four was what i feared three would be and i was i think i was so
surprised and delighted by three i really did love three that four just seemed like more of a kick
in the teeth it just felt cheap it felt you know it had it's better maybe again because of the desert
stuff but it had that 90s music video vibe that kind of guns and roses uh bad music video vibe leather
out in the desert right and the comedy didn't really click for me nothing really clicked on four i
was disappointed to say the least um here Bob's out there saying it's one of the best horror sequels
ever made like sometimes i think the country and the more i watch about it yeah i think if you're not
going to get off on the all the unseen footage from part one which is very cool to see sure but if
that's not enough to get you off on this movie that that's the only way i think you could say that
this is such a great sequel like it's not i think it's the worst in the series which i know we will
disagree on probably uh but let me read you again one random line from the plots and obses of phantasm
4 in the desert mike realizes he is slowly developing telekinesis when he kills a dwarf with a large
boulder then let me read you one more awakening on an embalming slab mike uses the tuning fork to
immobilize jody and the tall man as they attempt to cut open his head with a buzz saw equipped sphere
i mean it's insanity and that's turning that outline into the studio you know so let's
let's let's go back to the concept that these people are these characters are all just extensions of
mike mike now is cute has impossibly used a boulder to kill something as his brother jody did in the first
one reggie has now taken mike's place as the phone protagonist and narrator of the films
yes reggie has become mike and vice versa well clearly they aren't that audiences are responding way
more to reggie well yes i'm sure that's it too uh but i also think that they use that as an
opportunity to go further down this road yeah um and then there's a lot of just passive stuff to
to to sort of support the idea that this is all just if someone's fantasy reggie keeps somehow
magically fixing this car even though it's been wrecked three times and that they're in a wasteland
that's all like auto body shops are open uh what else oh the tall man says to mike you have no one but me
right you know that's a pretty hit you over the headline uh reggie has a dream at one point
where he sees mike as the tall man uh mike becomes so irrational about avoiding death
the tall man that he tries to commit suicide you know um it's a wild ride it's a wild ride uh fun cameo
on this one the psychic old lady from the first one uh who's also mute um i earlier i said she says
this as i was mispeaking her granddaughter says it that character comes back in a few ghostly visions
um that's kind of the only time this movie is ever sort of like spooky yeah um yeah it feels more
of an action move yeah uh and then suddenly this concept is introduced where mike suddenly doesn't trust
jody his brother this is the person he was obsessed with and idolized through the first three films
now suddenly mike doesn't trust him and i think that that's a metaphor for mike saying he can't trust
himself yeah he implicitly trust reggie because reggie shows his represents a side of mike that
mike does trust jody now represents the side of mike that will succumb to the tall man reggie
represents the side of him that will fight him um this movie ends with reggie going through a portal
for some reason in his ice cream man suit i don't know why he puts it back on he just that was
insane to me it's clearly like they're trying to get a pause from people in the theater when he puts
the suit back on but unfortunately theater play theater and uh it it seems absolutely nuts when you
laugh yeah that's really supposed to be like blade putting the sunglasses back on but it never held
that kind of significance no no no it's basically a little crazy polo tie thing this makes me look so stupid
all right oh also part five does this but part four also do this and i thought this was really
cool stylistic thing to do i like that they incorporate the number the roman numeral the film into the
title so part four is called oblivion and the i and the v is the four and in part five is called
ravager and the v the for the five is the v and ravager and they just did a nice thing where
they just found perfect words where the the the roman numeral fit directly in the middle yeah
and it's just a very cool stylistic choice i thought uh i agree i actually just noticed it while
looking at the poster for it but um that brings us to five ravager and i didn't go see five when
it was playing theatrical in la which it did for a short time because i was not familiar with the movies
between part one and part five so i came to this because i remembered it getting good press you know
if not great reviews it seemed like fans the franchise were really pumped on it and everything else
so again my my expectations were just clearly too high ravager to me is the worst of the franchise by
by a country mile um the the one sort of interesting choice they make that is such a fucking bummer
is to give Reggie Alzheimer's that so the the awesome sex loving hero that you've enjoyed is now
sitting like in a wheelchair with an afghan over his lap in a in a home with Alzheimer's
me my biggest fear is Alzheimer's so uh i was unable to have any fun i hate when that's even
mentioned it like ruins my day but they also i don't think did anything cool with its story wise
the story is all over the place and doesn't make sense which is not new for for phantasm
but i think in this one more than the others it was it came from them running out of money and having
big problems with the production which they did i don't know what the budget for this was my guess is
almost non -existent when they go to like held basically the CGI and that scene is mortified i mean
they should they needed to scrap that segment it does not work um budget was very low for this this
started as a series of internet shorts that was eventually expanded on and cobbled into a film
yeah um i think that this movie is now when i first let me let me explain when i first saw this film
i was very disappointed yeah uh because i was expect i was excited i there hadn't been a new
phantasm film in a long time i was really excited and this was a secretly made film uh they really
played played it well in the press by saying they weren't gonna do it and whenever and then it
just dropped and it was like what you know so that was really cool and then when i saw it and it
looked like it was shot on an iPhone 2 uh it was hard to it looks terrible i can't be overstated it looks
terrible so that all said when i went into it this time i said look it's not good quality but i'm
gonna look at this as the final chapter in this in this series right uh and that's how i watched it
and i really really enjoyed it okay and for some i guess just based off of hitting them all on a
row like that yeah that was enough to carry me past the quality issue and really follow it through
as the as more of a focusing on the story of this and whatever so i do think reggie gets his moments in
this i like that they play the Alzheimer's thing as um as you know reggie's like this is one of the tall
man's tricks it's not like reggie's walking around dribbling and shit like that he doesn't believe
he has Alzheimer's everybody's telling him he's crazy just like everybody's whole mic mic was crazy
yeah fully switched places now but reggie was the one saying mic you're crazy this didn't happen now
mic is the one saying to reggie you're crazy this tall man doesn't exist mic now has a ponytail
so now they're starting to physically emulate one another in this final chapter it's not a good look
on reggie either uh it works better for reggie yeah so now they're physically in a way emulating one
another they've completely switched places this to me really nails at home mic is reggie they're the same
person yes um and this now jumps amongst a bunch of different realities uh the past the present
the future uh this is the only film i've felt out of the series that finally shows you
what the tall man's destruction is because in every one of these movies they keep saying he goes from
town to town and he decimates it and whatever yet everybody is sort of living as if oh just the next
town over will be normal again you know what i mean and this one finally it was like now the effects
are not great as you said but this one finally depicted no it's a fucking wasteland it's awful everybody's
dead um i like the plotline of mic mill the post apocalyptic future thing because in that
ver in that storyline in this movie mic is the leader of this faction that are fighting the tall man
literally with guns uh and i like i thought that spoke a lot to the concept that that that was
set into motion in the first film here's a guy that's so bad at dealing with death he literally
militarizes himself against it yeah i'm gonna fight death now like on a military scale i think that's
a really fitting end uh to what they set in motion in the first film um again mic and reggie
switching places i think is a really really fitting into all of this um reggie's death
uh i i think that basically what this film could be saying is maybe reggie actually finally
died and this is the way mic coped with reggie dying now i don't know but the last shot of this film
essentially not the last last shot but the essentially the last shot is mic jody and reggie riding
off into basically the sunset yes you know and again it's this sort of escapist childish
fantasy we would all like to have about wouldn't it be nice if when you died that's what it was like
you just wrote off into the sunset with your best friend and your and your brother and everybody
ever loved uh i felt like this film really really tied up everything i thought it was a very fitting
end it does reflect a lot of the elements that were supposed to be in there were those two scripts there
was phantasm 1999 AD which was the avery one then there was another thing called phantasm's end
this reflects some of what was supposed to be in those films was supposed to be this big epic post
apocalyptic thing and then finally this was the first movie since to me part two that i legitimately
scary moments in it like it was cool when he brought the woman back from part one that he turns into
that fox with reggie and fox or enough or fox jody excuse me in the first movie it was cool seeing
her come back when she gets like that witch faced it was actually creepy when reggie has the dream
sequence where he's in the hospital bed and the tall man is his roommate in the hospital and he's being
he's being jeb a die of the man who he was before he became the tall man and he's being nice and
and endearing and then all of a sudden he switches personalities and becomes the tall man and then the
camera tilts down and she's under the bed like all bald up yeah there were like legit creepy fucking
moments like that in this you know it's a shame the effects were not great this had some really
solid jump scares that were that were set amidst other parts that were very suspenseful but i can't
see how anybody would watch this film without being a die hard phantasm freak and walk away and
go you know i was into that you know what i mean like this is this is the last chapter of the book
for you we'd have to be very well versed in phantasm to even have any clue what's going on or care
for for me what i would say is why are you doing your most ambitious
blockbuster version of this story when you have the least money uh it makes no sense i wish they had
you know you could do a really cool movie based on Alzheimer's i know i said i hate Alzheimer's
stories and i wouldn't want to see it but like just digging into that and keeping it on a personal
level keeping it in this home that he's at or something i think they would have had a much a much
better time and i think they could have gotten it more right because here like i can't imagine
that sitting in the editing booth i've said in a few edited booths what stuff i've done and
you know it hasn't happened many times but you'll see a scene once in a while where you're like
oh this doesn't work i'm gonna have to really dig in here and make this scene work and when they're
looking at the vision of hell or the vision of this alternate world and it looks that bad
and i mean it looks really bad i just cannot believe they didn't go we got to scrap this we don't have
the budget for this scene let's come up with some different ending for it um because to me i i i wasn't
able to let my imagination take over and and fix what they couldn't um i just it's too ambitious for
its budget for i'll tell you what might have helped me with that when i rewatched at this time i
watched it on my ipad and i think watching it on a smaller screen that stuff was nowhere near as
glaring as i had remembered it being and when i originally watched it i watched on my flat screen
tv right so that might add something to do with it but it is interesting i do agree with you that
they could have done a very small concept you know that that all transpired in the darkened hallways
of of a mental institution and it would have been really scary and really creepy um but that said my
hats off to him that they pulled off what they did for clearly under a million dollars i mean i'm looking
at the wikipedia page right now for the john carpenter film the ward which i don't know if you ever saw
it but it's very boring uh it's not very good it's a little bit of a return to form for carpenter but
it's not great uh this is a thing all shot in one location basically very stripped down this
fucking budget on this thing is ten million dollars you're going to what the fuck man so the fact that
coscarelli and i forget the director of part five forgive me um
david apartman the fact that the two of them pulled this off on essentially consumer
dv cams my hats off to them man like i i know it was ambitious and i think this was just coscarelli
saying hey man we're never gonna get the money raised to do the thing we want to do
fuck it let's give it our best shot and they did and i think for fans it was it was satisfying
and and it was enough of a fitting and i mean it's kind of 57 % on ron tomatoes you know like that's
pretty high for a movie this fucking low budget um but trace thurman who have actually i'm friends with
on some social media thing he writes for blooded disgusting he called it one of the five worst horror
movies of 2016 which i also thought you know uh john squires loved it uh they both agreed though that
it looked like a cheaply made student film yeah so i think it's all valid i don't know how
coscarelli came in touch with his heart and i and and no offense to him but it's like i just can't
believe they couldn't find a better even student director because the scenes just aren't put together
well in my opinion they aren't directed well but um and i don't know why coscarelli didn't do it
unless he got sick of the business which would make total sense but i don't know why he didn't do it
either i will say though uh and i really did pay attention to the directing on this rewatch
i think the directing is much better than then it gets credit for
it's just so hard to tell when it's when the camera quality is that bad yeah a camera movement doesn't
look good anymore you know what i mean right so and it's john because we live in an age where you can
do a really low budget movie with not great cameras and have it look fantastic soda bird does
movies on iPhones it this looks unusually bad i don't know why i can't explain the one thing i don't
get is which they could have done and this is what i don't understand it maybe it was i guess just
for streaming purposes they could have spent i don't know what it would cost i mean what is it
cost to a film transfer you could have done a film transfer yeah of the uh and it would have
added a graininess to it and it would have made it work a lot more i would love it if they did that
with part five because i think that would really just yeah that would give it another and hd that
never could grow at all it's it's what kind of ruin multi -cam sitcoms is that it's this hd
way of shooting on this really primitive antiquated set you know it looks bad but um
to to to discuss that you know the franchise as a whole i think basically
led by joe bob in a way i looked at it as turn your brain off and enjoy this like wild and sane
anything goes dream world of the phantasm universe joe on this latest viewing tried to get much more
out of it uh read more into it and i think had a much more rewarding time i'd like to do that again
myself in the future rewatch with with some new thoughts in mind but um for me the ranking goes one two
three four five right down the line i think it's a good but not great franchise i think the original is
the classic and the the remaster looks great i agree with basically everything you just said except i
put five over four i would a rather three just ended and then it jumps to five yeah i don't need
four four to me is just connective tissue that i don't need you know literally showing you like
this is how reggae ends up in the ice cream uniform at the beginning of five you're like right
all right guys uh you know um for me the big the big the nicest surprise was three i have always heard
from people that either one or two are the best it seems pretty divided um but nobody ever
mentions three and i thought three was fucking awesome i really did anyway folks that's our show
you know where to find us don't need to plug everything at the end of every show uh but it's been
fun talking to you you Pat it's been fun talking all of you uh and thanks for your support we really
really appreciate it um next episodes probably uh gonna probably what what do we got coming up
your pat we said we're gonna do zoom or sorry we said we're gonna do host we're gonna do Capone
we're gonna launch the lodge um yeah that's all we got really planned yeah that's it for right now
yeah we're gonna probably start getting this into some classics we'll have to at some point because
there's not gonna be any new movies coming out but um yes thank you so much for taking this
patreon journey with us we very much appreciate it there's now a new tier as you know four episodes
a month or 12 thank you to those who have made the jump tell those who don't know about it
and from Emily and thank you Emily for all your hard work as always please download the episode this
way you'll always have them and and as we make these patreon adjustments it tends to fuck people up and
take away their access to things until we fix it the easiest way to make sure you never have that
problem is to download the apps and not stream them so please do that in the future um but now everything
should be fixed and ready to go if you still have complaints let Emily know let us know but you
should have access to everything that you're paying for thank you guys very much we will see you next
time and we will see you in hell