I'm here for Bet Rivers online casino and sportsbook with poker icon Phil Helmuth.
And now thanks to the excitement of Bet Rivers, I'm also a slots icon.
That's great! And a same -game parlay icon. Cool, cool. A blackjack icon,
a money -line icon, a roulette. Take it from Phil Helmuth. If you love games,
Bet Rivers is the place to play in Bet. Bet Rivers. Games on.
Must be 21 plus in present in West Virginia. Void were prohibited. Terms in conditions apply.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another, no other sportsbook has
an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning, or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
winning hits different here must be 21 plus gambling problem called winning 100
gambler offer not available in all states terms apply see fanatic sports book
app
Hi everybody, welcome to, we'll see you in hell.
You know that this podcast is part of the Fingoria Podcast Network, it's how you found
it.
For more information about the network, including other programs, how to follow us or
find other episodes of, we'll see you in hell.
Visit Fingoria .com now on with the show, it actually says that in the text.
Oh, that's nice.
It says now on with the show.
I didn't write it Ken Ed Fangoria wrote it. Do you know of a comedian Asian?
Obviously named by the name of Henry Cho. Yes. He's still out there working. I
Think so I don't know personally. Okay, he used to it was it's all things these in Asian guy with the Southern accent
Yeah, and he used to host Friday night videos
Which was the only way I could see music videos because I'd have MTV when I was a kid right and
Every time come back from commercial they would go and now back to the
Joe!
Exactly like that.
Really?
Which I actually thought was sort of a funny way to say it to get around the terrible pun.
Now, speaking of puns, we get a lot to cover here tonight.
We're talking ghost busters on this episode, but before we get to it, the new one,
well, probably all things ghost busters.
But before we get to it, speaking of puns, I'm at a party last night.
okay everybody had had a few drinks everybody had smoked a little bit of
reef but we were all feeling good sure and I'm with Georgia who is our
friend Vince Abel's wife and also Georgia Hartziger I was a very funny
comedian and co -host the my favorite murder podcast shout out her and Karen
Colgara do a fantastic job discussing murders and that podcast has already
blown this one out of the water, so I guess I don't need to recommend it, but it's great.
They're in the top 10 consistently, they got shattered out and rolling stone this week.
I saw it. Pretty great. So a couple of dorks on Twitter, uh, shattered us out.
Yes. Well, that's nice. I don't mind it. I love we, we are dorks. We do this for dorks. We live for
the dorks. And, uh, I just would like to send my compliments over to party McFly on Twitter for
Just coming out boldly shitting on tremors, but then immediately someone came up and said you're an idiot
Yeah, so I a pair those are the dorks. I was referring to
Only because the one I hated that he agreed with you. I couldn't quite handle that. I
I loved it and then equally hated when the other man disagreed with me
I also think it's crazy that the guys actual Christian name is party McFlaun
I can't believe it speaking of party perfect transition. You're out with Georgia hearts
Yeah, a little party right back in party fly there. It's that's another pun
Yeah, right? Joe take us back to the future and tell us the story of who we are. God, I'm good. So we're talking
Friday night Vince Averill our dear friend and dear friend
He and I went to see the art of Raptor. Yep
At the palladium, which you bought tickets you got us tickets and you weren't able to attend unfortunately
But we went to the show. I don't worry. I only lost $40 on my ticket. Yeah, well, I did to myself
So we're at the show, or we go to the show is a great time.
It's iced tea, public enemy mob D, BPMD, Curtis Blow, busy bee.
It was nuts. It was great.
So I'm at the party the next night.
I'm standing with Georgia and a writer who I'm not going to name.
Okay.
But whom I've worked with, sort of.
Uh -huh.
And I've never ever had a problem with the guy.
We've always got along smashingly.
It's mashingly, it's always been very endearing.
A lot of smiles, how you doing, great stuff.
Can't wait till I hear this person's name off my mic.
So we're seeing, they're talking about the concert.
And I said, my favorite part of the whole concert
was the T -shirt that Flavor Flav was wearing.
And they said, what was the T -shirt?
And I said, 10 years ago, my friend Jim Pinkstone,
gave me a T -shirt for Christmas,
and it was the Warner Brothers symbol.
Yes.
And it said if you see the police Warner brother and I thought it was a really funny play on words and I again and also
Solid social commentary very solid. So flavor flame. I've never seen the shirt otherwise right
Flavor flame comes running out ten years later. He's got the shirt on. I'm going crazy, right?
I called Jim the next day. I'm freaking out. Can you believe he's wearing that he was wearing the shirt?
I'm telling this story at the party and as I'm telling it I'm laughing because I go it's just such a brilliant pun
It just really makes me laugh. Yeah, yeah, and
And we're all enjoying it and George is going that's really cool this writer
Okay, cuts in and he just goes, huh, you don't read much. Do you?
This is what he says
You don't read much do you now?
Now, it's so insulting, and I'm so high, I'm like, you're imagining this.
This isn't happening.
The weed is getting the better of you right now, and I go, I'm sorry, why, what do you
mean?
I'm just, wait, what do you mean?
And he goes, you don't read much to you, and he goes, it's not that good of a pun, dude.
And I go, wow, and then Georgia steps in and goes, well, he didn't say it was the greatest
thing ever written.
He just said he thought it was funny, and he thinks it's funny. That's all I know. Yeah, and then the guy starts trying to back pedal
And he goes dude, it's oh believe me none of us have the right to tell each other what's funny or not
None of us have the right to do that and then I go well, it is Hollywood so maybe we should be telling each other what should or shouldn't be funny
Right, buddy? And then he gets paranoid
And he's like what are you doing with the fuck's that supposed to mean what are you doing now? What are you doing now?
And I just go I'll see you man. I got to go to the bathroom and then I go to the bathroom
I'm and his Vince is coming out of the bathroom going into the room adjacent to it where I just was
He's walking out and I yelled the guy's name. I go that that that that is getting real weird in there with me
I'm getting paranoid hearing the story which I think he might have heard because he disappeared from the party after he just snuck out
Quickly putting my needs above the listeners. Can you cover your mic and mouth who it is?
sure did you get that one more time one more time okay yes you know I'm
talking about I do I do indeed what do you think of that okay never met him
and I can't talk about him at all now so I won't I like one thing he did I know
that I'm a fan of the man's work yeah okay great it's always been a heavy
exchange of compliments every time I don't understand where where he maybe he
thought it was funny and it came out wrong and then didn't have the guts to
just be like hey dude I'm sorry I meant to be funny and that was shitty yeah you
know like there's some people where it's just their fucking tone whereas if you
were talking about us amazing pun and I you know I'm sitting on the couch and I
It's not that great a pun job. We don't laugh and move pat and you'd be like fuck you
or whatever right but somebody who says something like that very seriously like his opinion is correct
You're stupid for feeling that way right. There's nothing affectionate about it and it really ruins the evening and then also
I don't know you like that. Yeah, true. I know you like that so you as well make the joke
You I go pets fucking with me. This guy says it also I wouldn't go you don't read much do you in a serious tone of voice
don't read much as he was constantly laughing at me.
This, by the way, then sent me into,
I mean, you can imagine the paranoia spiral
for sure on out for the rest of the night.
I mean, I thought everybody was working with me.
It was like crazy back there with that guy.
A lot of that.
I didn't say any of that.
I just quietly interpreted every conversation I was having
from that point on as somebody just dressing me down
and secretly hating me.
I mean, it doesn't put you on the right track, you know.
I had just I'm glad I never go that way with any of that stuff really. Oh, I keep it pretty light
Would you mean in conversation? I mean with
mind -altering drugs
You don't get paranoid. You mean no, I don't you know if I if I smoke a little bit
I don't sit and back. Oh everybody's out to get me. I don't have that
I you know
I wasn't having it till that happened and then it's like well anything's possible at this point
Yeah, when something like that happens
You go well anything at any point any person in this party that I think is friends of a friend of mine could just turn on me
Evidently very true. It's doesn't it's just it's terrible
Now
Now before again we get into the movie Pat we got an elephant in the room. We need to address it
Pat and I had a, Pat and I had a little tip last week we did uh it wasn't that bad no there was no
yelling it was all done via text yeah I think you know you're always calling uh and I don't
answer and I kept waiting for the call and it didn't come and I was like these texts saying no
one's getting their point across this isn't going well um didn't call out a respect for your I hate the
phone sure and I was like the last it would have it would have helped I felt like the last thing I
needed to do was was call you and then it's gonna get I didn't know what was
gonna happen but a scheduling issue we you know I guess on Tuesday Joe was
like are you free to do the podcast this weekend because Joe's about to leave for
a tour comedy tour Edinburgh French Fest and double the phone comedy fest and he
said are you free this weekend I go yeah it should be fun next day I'm supposed to
notes on a script. Folks, I'm not trying to tune my own horn here. There were no notes
on that script. They were like, it's beautiful, baby. We'll see you Monday. I'd already been
off a week at this point. Right. I'm like, all right. I guess I'll take another week. Heather,
my girlfriend is going to Europe for three weeks tomorrow. Right. And I'm like, you know
what? Heather, let's go to Vegas. Right. She's off. I say, fine. I tell Joe, look, I can't
make a podcast. So can we just reschedule? Joe's like, well, I'm leaving Wednesday. I'm
like, all right, can we do it Monday or Tuesday? No. Can we do it Sunday after your shows?
No, I got an early day Monday and there was the rub. Right. Because then that got swishing
you didn't have an early day Monday and this worked out perfectly. If that had been the case,
we would have been like, all right, I'll see you then, dear friend. Right. Of course.
But of course, and of course had I known initially this was a like Heather was going away and whatever I would yeah
I wasn't pulling that card or anything because I didn't think it was serious and then all of a sudden I was like
I don't care for this motherfucker's tone
I didn't care for it. I was like well, we should have I
Wish we would have talked about this. I've been sitting home with nothing to do for two or three days
And you're like we did talk about it yesterday
day. I'm like, whoa, whoa, whoa. Well, that wasn't the tone of that text. That wasn't the tone of
that text. But when I saw it, I was like, I don't like this. The period we did talk about a period
yesterday period. I was like, nope. It's getting a little fresh. Well, I also thought the comment you
made was fresh when you said, I wish we were to talk about I just been sitting home because on Sunday,
I tried to convince you to go out an hour earlier and you're like, I can't, I gotta do, I am buried with
this script man so I was like obviously you know what that extra hour probably got me that no note
review well look first of all let me say that I'm not too small a man to say I'm happy about the
no notes thing thanks I am too you know second of all I'm glad you're here I'm glad you're sitting here
it worked out great you know I was like the tech exchange was getting a little weird and I explain
to Joe I never have any I've never really had a fight with any friend of mine that I can recall maybe
you know, one or two giant ones in my life, but never anything big.
It's like we always seem to dip into little little heated patches.
I would like to address that actually.
Please. I did this. I did some math or a last heated tiff November.
Yeah. No, that's not bad. Not bad at all. That's not bad. Not bad at all.
But I said, Joe, we're just too similar. You said it's all out of love.
We were saying the same thing. We're too similar. But I said, uh, you know,
If it's not gonna if you can't make it work Monday or Tuesday, I don't know what to tell you and you're like
Just be here at three on Sunday, and I'm like well now
Then I'm leaving a vacation early
I said I could probably make it and I think I will but if I hit traffic we might be fuck at this point. We're still
It's kind of dancing around a potential
explosion
But we're all just gonna be just kind of keep stating our cases and then I also I didn't go just be here
I said, can you please just be here by three o 'clock?
I said, yeah, and I said, I absolutely will and will do my level best.
I was back today by two, actually, but I said, you know, I don't know if I can't say
for sure.
I'll be there.
You don't know with Vegas on the traffic.
I realize that kind of stuff.
You know, if we don't do it, then we're not going to do it.
We're going to get backed up.
Then here's where I hit a snag, folks.
I'm telling Joe now I didn't mean this the way it came across and I'm telling you the
listener I said this is an unpaid podcast which it is we do it out of love right
it's not a priority of mine period at all period inspired by Joe's other
period not not a priority of mine at all and what I really meant by that was
we're doing this for free out of love for you the listener and we should never
be bending over backwards or like stressing out over trying to make it. But then again,
I'm not going out of town for two months either. But I said that as soon as I explained,
it's not what I meant. Joe apologized, usually takes me an extra day to work up to an apology.
Joe, quick, nipped it in the bud quickly and all was fun. Yeah, a few hours later,
set you a text, which was 100 % true. Some for some reason started reading the Wikipedia
bios of the what's happening cast. Got to Fred rerun berries and I mean it is
some dark stuff. I imagine. It's some bad times. It's typical. It's it's typical
like the typical Hollywood story. It's like the guys on a hit sitcom. He's a
millionaire. He's 300 pounds. It gets canceled because he would ever I don't
Malrow he he his reps claim it's because they didn't give him enough money and if they did it would have been a better show and it wouldn't have gotten
Get all this stuff
He thinks like I'm the star. I'll be fine. Of course. He's not fine. Yeah, he's not in anything
He can't get out of the rerun shadow right
Married six times in his life. Yeah, six times becomes an alcoholic and a drug addict
Gets clean does what's happening now?
again, leaves after the first season, you know, I think because like he wants more money
or whatever.
Yeah.
And then ends up the rest of his days being like rerun it things like like showing up
in at best music videos, and at worst, the face of a West Virginia real estate company or something
like that.
Right.
It's like money is green.
Yeah.
And the way he said it was, he goes, he goes,
was I'm the Ronald McDonald of real estate.
And it's like, no, you're not.
You are for that little company that I don't know.
Yeah, Ronald McDonald isn't, you know,
South Dakota's local pubs, spokespersons.
It was really a rough ride and then he died at like 50.
And he didn't want that to happen.
I was sitting there going, life's too short
and this town is too sick, this is stupid.
And that's when I texted you and the lead sentence was,
sitting here reading a haunting bio about Fred rerun berry.
Yes, we both apologize and then, you know, how the fight ended, you know, Joe, Joe
used the word offensive. Like that is offensive to me about eight times in a
text. And I was like, all right, Joseph set. Let this one blow over. I get a text from
Vince, our friend who we mentioned earlier. Hey, I guess Joe's asking me to do the
podcast with him this week like that mother I was pull over the car and I'm
like do it cuz I'm out baby like and then immediately it was all washed on
the bridge I was like he can be a damn guest but you can't do we'll see you
in hell with Pat Joe scratch out Pat right in Finn no he was a guest for one
episode that's all no I know yeah he wasn't you know nobody was replacing Pat
Well, well, that wasn't happening. And then I sat here getting sad thinking it's not going to be the same
Sure and and the people the people what are the people going to say yeah
And then Vince doesn't need the abuse of the online community
preparing him to me
I'll never get out of bed again and you also in a very nice gesture after we all made up and everything you said
You said hey, dude if you still when I've Vince guest. I don't mind sitting out one
And I said, of course, not like we're doing this.
It's season three.
Yeah, new format.
Let's get back to basics.
I didn't even come in here with any degree of tension
and might not have even remembered.
I would have remembered it, but it wasn't on my mind.
It wasn't on my mind other than, I guess it's only proper
to address that that happened in some way.
And because we're Hollywood phonies,
we do it live on a podcast.
I mean, exactly.
We exchange seven words before we hit record.
We had Joe start talking about his opinion on Ghostbusters. I'm like, why don't you hit the damn record button?
We're talking about Ghostbusters on a podcast.
Which, and let's get to it before we're there.
Yeah. Well, I had said if we're going to do a guest format, which I was never even really seriously discussed, but I was like,
we need to get in Karen Cogara for our dear friend.
Yes.
To talk about Ghostbusters because who wants to hear another couple wide dude talk about Ghostbusters?
but I think we have, I think we have a point of view that is both supportive of the cause,
and also I think a more realistic representation of what that movie is, and I tweeted and
Karen immediately shot out at me, and I was like, if Karen's a little miffed, this needs to come down,
because Karen's the best, and other people might go nuts. All I said was afterwards, after the movie,
I tweeted out, I don't care about ghostbusters. I love women. I don't believe you like
ghostbusters as much as you said you did. Right. You know, it was basically the gist
of it. And Karen, when I scrolled back, had posted a glowing review of it on Twitter. I was
like, she probably thought it was about her, wasn't ahead in seeing it. We ran into some people
at the theater I was like yeah you can see it in their eyes when you talk to
people they didn't love the movie but they have to say they love it and I don't
get it so my my point was spy you and I saw it together as well yeah I didn't
like it now I I love all four women and ghostbusters I think are for the
funniest women in the world yes I didn't laugh at the movie spy Melissa McCarthy
It's a big budget action comedy starring a woman.
Why did this whole thing not happen then?
Why wasn't it, oh, you have to like spy, I think people thought spy suck.
We thought spy suck.
I think because there wasn't the online backlash.
There was such a misogynistic backlash to it.
Is that what the female ghost busters, that this movie sort of became a beacon for feminism
and for women, the hope of women in general.
Which I understood
But there there are many like grab I think the biggest box off his head of the past couple years is gravity probably
Starings are bulk. You know, that's why I don't really understand. It was because of the reaction
So that's what yeah, so but this that's interestingly you bring it up because that's what bothered me about this this whole thing was I
Look I turned you after the cold open. I go I'm in. Yeah, this is great. I
it got to a place where I was like,
okay, this really isn't good anymore.
And like, this has been like a rough patch in the movie.
And then it never got better.
And then it just kept being sort of cheesy.
It just like was being less and less sense
as it went along.
It was more taped together as it went along.
Whatever, I don't care.
I'm not mad at it.
It's just like, it is what it is.
It's like I would not give the movie a passing grade
structurally as a film.
So what bothered me was, I've gotten some shit for that for people, for people.
Because I got to say, there are just as many more women that I've said to, I didn't
really like it, understood what I was saying, than women that attacked me needlessly.
But I have gotten a few like cheap jabs from some women that I'm friends with actually,
because I didn't like it, and they sort of try to twist it into some sort of sexist perspective.
And my response to that is, hey, do you own the movie nine to five?
That's literally the movie about feminism in the workplace.
Right.
That is like so ahead of its time and so groundbreaking.
Do you own it?
Do you champion that movie to young females when you meet them at comedy shows that say they've
never seen it?
Right.
Because I do.
And I don't do that for a paddle in the back.
I literally genuinely say to like, if I mean like a twenty two year old comic who's a girl
who's never seen it, I go, you got to see this movie.
This is the feminism movie.
Yeah, it's amazing. It's hilarious. It's it's a grand slam movie. So it's like I just I just didn't think I thought ghost busters
I've said and I do mean this. I've said many times since I've seen it. If the original cast of ghost busters was in that movie
I would have left saying they somehow made a worse sequel than ghost busters, too, and I don't know how that was possible.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, and everybody is by the way the worst links in the movie are
Bill Murray for Christ's sake he comes in it's the least funny he's ever been
including his dramas and then when he comes back for that second scene dressed in
like a jaunty tweed suit and a cartoon hat I'm like okay here comes the funny
scene and then I thought to myself and I don't think this is the case is this
some sort of meta commentary by Paul Fee and the writer Katie Dippold that they
have every man in the movie be a very underwritten boring not particularly funny
interesting character because that's what women usually have to deal with.
I don't think that's the case. You want, you have Bill Murray in your movie, you want
him to be funny. If that is the case, it should have been done better and more apparently,
because it wasn't, it wasn't a pair of some jokes, I guess. The Liam Helmsworth character is Chris,
or Chris Helmsworth. Is it Helms or him? Helms. It's an unbearable character. I mean, it's like,
Yeah, it's, it's, again, I'm not saying that women have not been shittily portrayed
in movies.
Of course.
I'm saying that that character is not believable.
Yeah.
It's kind of funny at first.
Then it gets to a point where he's so stupid that you're like, I'm like, my god, there
are people with literal, major mental deficiencies that are more capable than he is as a man with,
you know, a functioning brain or, you know, a fully functioning brain.
You know, it's like, we go to dinner after him, we're saying like, we're at the diner.
Hey, you know, I guess I didn't really like it or whatever.
And the whole table kind of turned, and me and Joe wound up kind of whispering to each other
at the end of the table, and I was very uncomfortable.
It was a bad scene.
And I'm like, what are we, this is ghost busters, it's a movie for children.
And that's what this town does to people.
Yeah, but us against them and then we turn on each other right days later
I also didn't say I hate this fucking shit. I said, you know
I didn't really like it over and people put so much into that you know
All Karen said to me on Twitter was O .B. You love who's Harry Crumb
Well, I do right I can't help what I like and what I don't I know that one makes me laugh and and
Ghostbusters didn't here's my thing. I write I sat on the original ghostbusters last
Yeah, I didn't shit on it, but it's it's a little overrated and this new one. I don't I
Only wanted it to be good. I didn't walk in the arms folded like try and entertain me
Well, I felt the same way. I am not a ghost buster's protector. I think the first movie is
Is a solid film from the 80s? We talked about it last week. I never have the urge to watch it
I think the sequel and everything that came after is is awful. None of it's good. Sure
And what bothered me about this movie is I wanted it to be great. I was excited. And then you got some like Melissa McCarty who's down right hilarious.
And you give her barely any funny shit to do. I thought Leslie Jones was the funniest person in the movie.
They did the same thing with wig. They kind of like like she's kind of like the awkward Kristen wig character for a while. But like they it seemed like they were throwing everything to Kate McKinnon and Leslie Jones.
And they were funny. Yeah, but that doesn't take away from the fact that I'm watching the other two and going like
Why aren't these two getting any like Leslie Jones
Was funny. I will say I didn't laugh at the movie at all, but I thought Leslie Jones was the funniest
We again McCarthy. They're not playing other strengths. You know, it's almost like they were like hey don't make us the zany
One this time or you know, I don't know what they thought but neither one of them they were endearing. They were likeable
they always are. I was upset that there was no Melissa McCarthy scene where she's like you
fucking cocksucker ghost mother fucker like I'm like and I know they couldn't say that because it
wasn't hard or you know create you know they Christmas vacation he he ran for two minutes screaming
it doesn't cost you know it's just like get creative with it but McKinnon the things I've seen on Twitter
like a true game changer. I was weeping when McKinnon started shooting the
ghosts and she was one of the one of the greatest comedic performances of all
time I read. I don't know what's going on. I don't know. I don't know. I guess I
can believe people they said they're crying when Kate McKinnon is shooting
ghosts because it was women empowerment but folks we talked about alien and
aliens last week as well these aren't it's not the first time it's happened of course
women are underrepresented right but what I don't know why that this movie became such
a lightning rod unless it is just the controversy I think it's just I think it's the controversy
turned it into that but I mean we're getting closer to the meat of the thing which is why yet
another reason why I got upset when anybody was saying to me that it was some sort of gender
commentary that I didn't like the film. It absolutely was not. I have shit on on
this podcast openly and on other podcasts openly and in conversation and in
public and in workplaces openly about the slew of movies that I think are terrible.
Look when when the night before came out we debated I remember giving you shit.
You were like I think it looks funny and I remember saying to you a for
for Christ's sakes, Pat.
How many fucking times are they gonna make this movie?
Oh, they do mushrooms again?
Like, yeah.
No, it's the only comedy that gets made now
is that essential plot.
And I'm not shitting on Seth Rogan,
just like I'm not shitting on Melissa McCarthy.
But I think a lot of the movie season aren't great
and a lot of them suck.
And so for me, I was like, don't give me
the equal quality to a shitty Seth Rogan movie
And then tell me it's brilliant. It's not brilliant. It could have been but if there were men in this movie
I wouldn't have liked it. It wasn't a good movie. I you know, many many a time. I'll shit on a movie on Twitter
I do it all the time or to people or whatever and you just you're saving your opinion and you wouldn't even think to be
Paranoid about saying all that movie fucking suck
But something about this I won't talk about it with people again the couple of times I have been directly asked I
I didn't think it was great.
And it still causes an uncomfortable exchange
with the person you're talking to.
I will say the same thing about,
there is a dearth of representation of female characters
in cinema without question.
There's a dearth of female directors and writers
and producers without question.
The other thing, maybe a woman should have directed it
if it's gonna be this.
Well, I guess they didn't plan on it
being this lightning rod.
I don't think they did.
And I think they just thought we're going to go make a fun movie and whatever.
Yeah.
I agree that I agree that the white male is overly represented in almost everything.
Of course.
I'll never argue any of that.
That being said, I think there needs to be more, I was behind Oscars so white, 100 % agree
with it completely.
And I don't think the problem is with necessarily the Oscars.
I think that's a byproduct of the bigger problem, which is the projects aren't getting
let to begin with. Right. Green let to begin with. We put all that on here. But you're
never going to get me to say that I think Tyler Perry makes good movies. No. Do you
know what I mean? Like I think Spike Lee is a fucking genius. I think he makes great work.
I think John Singleton's made a lot of great stuff. I'm not going to sit here and say because
we need this Tyler Perry's Medias Halloween. Right. It's good. Like I'm it's just not it's
not a good movie. Well and like I actually didn't see that one. That's not out yet. But you
or any of the other ones they saw.
Medias Boo.
You mentioning Singleton, it wasn't him,
it was this guy, F. Gary Gray, who did Friday
and the devotion and stuff.
Very underrated director.
Black dude.
And he directed a movie, 96, I believe, called Set It Off.
Great movie, Vivica Fox, Jada Pinkett, Queen Latif
for their female bank robbers.
They're all black.
You know, it made some money,
but no one really talks about it anymore.
I was shown in a film class oddly enough about how you know different
How you it's always good to service underrepresented groups, you know, but if set it off comes out this weekend
And it's four black women in their bank robbers. I don't think it's getting this talk
I don't think it's guys. We got to get out there and I don't think that's anything racist either
I just think we're just kind of randomly picking what movie that's gonna be I think you call it a lightning rod earlier
or I think that was a perfect term for it.
I think what happens with these things,
with all of these causes that we all debate
and discuss socially, I think something comes along
that represents it, and it becomes a very easy way
for people to think they're promoting the discussion.
Yeah, and at the end of the day,
loving or hating Ghostbusters is not promoting
any discussion.
And I am somebody that is 100 % of the mindset.
When I was watching the movie and I didn't like it that much,
I remember thinking to myself, you know what?
This is still a moment for women.
This is a good thing that's happening.
My opinion doesn't really matter.
And then it was when we were casually talking about it.
And we were like, like you said at the diner,
and we were just like, wow, it was okay.
You know, like now that you're asking, I'm not going to lie.
right I wasn't gonna go out of my way to tell anybody didn't like it you know
like but it got tense and you know you're like you're like I you know I guess all
the guys were worthless and they all got killed I guess that was supposed to be
part and you know the response was like that's what women have to face every time
we go to move well that's not true however in the scripts I have written I write
right for a show with two women movie scripts always add a woman to the
friend group, add in the lane, you know.
I signed if I wasn't the first to do it, but you get a whole other perspective on things.
And I'm sure that women get sick of getting sent scripts where it's like, I think Elizabeth
Banks once was like, if I handed my script to Jim Carey and was like, well, you read my
part.
Like if she's playing his wife, the more a tyranny and liar, liar role, you read my part
And tell me how
Fun it is to be the woman in this movie, right always the woman has no jokes and is there to support the guy in almost every movie sure
Now a movie that kind of came along and and change that as though it was the first female comedy
Which of course it wasn't was bridesmaids bridesmaids was my favorite movie of that year probably I
Still watch it. I still love it. It's over long. It's a little padded, but huge huge laughs the emotional arc really works
That's eight hilarious women given the chance to like unbelievably shine play to their
strength written by women directed by Feig again, but Feig does mostly female driven stuff
these days.
I like to heat a lot, you know, like I think he's got a good focus on empowering women
in his films, which I think is I think is a great thing doesn't mean every movie is going
to be good.
No, and if I love bridesmaids and hate Ghostbusters, the takeaway from a lot of people right
now seems to be more than you don't like women. And I saw this a lot of tweets like,
hey, males, nobody wants to hear your fucking opinion on ghost busters. It's like, well,
but that's all Twitter is. You go, I just saw it get hard and it sucked.
Well, also two, also two, equality is being able to speak to one another freely. Yes.
And, I'm not saying in terms of negative speech, harassment and all the shitty other things
guys do to women, that all sucks, it's horrible, I'm against it too.
Sure.
But it's like if we're going to talk a disaster, it wasn't, I stuck up for as much as I
could because I put on the receiving end of fucking miserable, an army of miserable internet
trolls and it fucking sucks and you feel alone.
Yeah.
And I love her on Twitter, her live tweeting everything she watches, I think she's fucking
hilarious.
And I laughed quite a bit at her in the film. I thought she was very funny, but like, yeah, all that shit was disgusting and
you know, but aside from
The obvious which is yeah, you know, the stuff people on Twitter were saying was awful, which again, maybe it's not that obvious because it took
five fucking
Websites blogging about it before Twitter fucking banned anybody from the goddamn thing. But anyway, I'm digressing my point is is that
Um, uh, the hell was my point. God damn it. What were we saying, uh, people harassing
Leslie Jones. The thing about people talking shit on Twitter. Oh, the thing about like
hey, males, nobody needs your appointment. Opinions shut up. It's like no, like that's what
equal genders means. It means that if you do something and I don't think it's good, I can
and say to you constructively,
I don't think this was good.
Yeah.
It's not me beating up on you.
It's not me condescending you.
It's me saying to you,
if this was men doing this,
I don't think it would be good.
So that's what I'm saying.
If you don't want me to say that,
well, then that's not a quality at that point.
Yeah.
That's pandering and that's that's that's
babying like that's not what anybody wants.
You don't want to be you don't want to be condescended to.
No.
And a lot a lot of the stuff in there,
Slymer and his family stay puffed whatever it was all just kind of lazy and shittily done,
you know, and that had nothing to do with women.
Folks went Aussie Osborne in a joke that would have been dated in 2003, goes, show it,
am I having an acid trip?
Flashback.
That happens in this movie.
Aussie Osborne is randomly standing there.
He just divorced Sharon the joke is over
But like how somebody didn't cut it and that's what I thought about spy which I thought was you know a pretty
You know dole movie to me. I didn't laugh, but
It devoted 30 minutes to that 50 cent subplot at the end
50 cent hasn't had a hit song in a decade. Yeah, I was weirdly. Yeah, that was
What is this it just felt awkward and desperate? No, the Aussie thing was way out of place
It was a terrible cameo and as I said to somebody recently when we were sort of the film I go I go it was my
It was it was my exact tap out point of the movie I go when they did the same cameo that they did in the jerky boys movie
Which is a shit show of a film as I was in the jerky boys, man
It's the same thing as he comes up and he's like, where's the fucking band?
Yeah, and then the jerky boys are like they got a gig with the monkeys
They skipped town and then dodgy's like the fucking monkeys you're kidding like yeah, it's just Aussie coming in and being Aussie
And it's like and I again
I love the jerky boys that movie is a pile of shit. Right. I want the jerky boys to remain successful
Right or be successful again or whatever, but I'm not gonna say that the movie they made was good. It wasn't good. No
I think that's all we're saying.
That's it.
And I feel fine.
And I feel like we're fine posting it.
It was really that weekend where it just felt really terrible.
And I had, you know, I had a couple of massive tweets about Ghostbusters.
I deleted that one pretty quickly.
The other was by Sunday, all these people that have been saying, if you don't like Ghostbusters
to hate women are now saying fuck you Taylor Swift you lied to Kanye America's
sweetheart like it's just a trash bag of a human being and people are like
fuck you ha ha Kim Kardashian got you Taylor yeah it's go Kim it's like what
what are you doing now it's right Swift is a strong one of the one of the most
successful women in all of music in the history of pop music really she does
her own shit she does it her way you can like it or not she has strong you
know she doesn't put her music on certain you know whatever it is
Spotify whatever takes care of her career handles her business and everyone's like
hey fuck you Taylor Swift I don't get it it's I was I was I was I'm not saying
this as a as a fan or or anything it's the thing it's the don't care it's the
The thing that drives me nuts with all the people, not all the people, with the majority
of people that wave a flag for cause.
Most people don't want to get their hands dirty, and I say it all the time about nonprofits
and stuff like that, the battles they choose to fight.
The battles they choose to fight, and I'm not saying the battles they choose to fight are
worthless battles, but it's always a pretty easy battle, a lot of these things.
Yeah, they're non -controversial battles. It's easy to make a campaign that centers
around a movie. It's easy to throw your arms up in the air about something a guy said
during a speech that he probably shouldn't have said or whatever. Yeah, these are easy battles.
They're black and white, they're non -controversial, they're not going to make anybody from the government
to to private donations to whatever giving you who gives you money feel
uncomfortable yeah or anything the real fight the real fights out there
require such sacrifice if you're gonna really get your hands dirty and go out
there and get into the real mix of what's happening with with true abuse and
true violence and true discrimination and all these things you're gonna have
have to get your hands dirty and you're also going to make your life a living hell, that's
just the way it is.
You don't do that kind of work without facing the backlash of all the awful people on the
other side of it that hate you for trying to do good.
That's not what the average person wants to do.
The average person wants to go, look how good I was today, see?
And it's like, yeah, good for you, man.
You stuck up for a fucking thing that we're all going to forget about in six months or you
I told Taylor Swift she was an asshole, right?
Oh, I feel like that and Ghostbusters
are essentially forgotten.
Of course they are.
Oh, week later.
Ghostbusters did okay business,
especially for something of its budget.
I wish it had done better,
but the people saying the sky is falling
and if everyone doesn't go
and talk about how much they love this movie,
they'll never make another movie with women in it again.
It's not true.
It's crazy.
easy. And, you know, everyone in that, well, you know, now, I probably Leslie Jones
and definitely McKinnon will be able to have their own projects. Leslie Jones might
always, you know, kind of be a supporting role. I don't know about two hours of Jones,
but or McKinnon for that matter, although I liked her way less than most, but Wig and McCarthy
can always get a big movie made, you know, they, they just can. Right. You know, and probably,
I guarantee Melissa McCarty's making bigger movies at this point then Ben Stiller, Jim
Kerry, Jack Black, whoever.
Totally.
There are stars have fallen.
She's the biggest comedy star there is pretty much.
I can't think of anybody bigger.
Totally.
And that's not a joke about her weight.
I think she looks fantastic.
Yeah.
And I really love her.
I've been writing something forever that I want her to be in.
Well, and here's the thing, too.
Here's the thing, too.
to take a page out of the Natasha Lazaro handbook when she got all that shit for making
that World War II joke on the countdown New Year's Eve thing, her retort and her blog
was.
Instead of making a big deal out of the stupid joke that I made where I obviously wasn't
trying to hurt anybody, why don't you go donate to a veterans fund or something like that.
So instead of screaming at people that they have to love ghost busters when they might not
have. Why don't you go back and champion the other movies that women have been in that
are unsung. McCarthy has quite a few. Yeah, you know, nobody was screaming up and down
when Tammy got 11 % on rotten tomatoes or whatever. It's, you know, and I got to tell
you and, you know, people are going to really come at me for this if they want. Tammy, to
me, while far from perfect, I had a better time than I did at Ghostbusters. That's fine.
And that's completely her movie a thousand percent. I didn't see the boss. I thought it looked pretty funny
You know, I
Thought the boss looked funny too. I wanted to see it. I just don't know why we're not doing this every
Every time and that's and that's my point
Kristen Wigg does makes makes tons of movies many of which are the stellar independent movies
I thought probably couldn't or welcome to me. Yeah, which is one of my favorite movies of that year and she was beyond
amazing in that movie. She should have been nominated for an Oscar, she should have won the Oscar and I mentioned it
9 out of 10 women at this table had not seen the movie and the one who had was like, eh, I don't like it
So it's like well then guys. I mean that to me that's far more important of a thing to support
It's like here's here's a here's a female actor who is making films that probably wouldn't get made if she was not attaching
yourself to them. Welcome to me never would have been and then they turn out to be fantastic movies
because she sees it and it gets made and then and then people will actually watch it now but far
from a lot of people are watching that to me that's the thing you route but again what does that mean?
It means getting your hand it's not getting your hands dirty but that's hard work. It's hard work to go
everybody needs to champion this independent film that was on a shoestring budget and this
that's a lot harder than just going shut up go see ghost busters right you know
it's a lot easier to say shut up and go see just ghost busters then jumping
into the fight with with Leslie Jones and and facing a bunch of fucking
psychotic racist on twitter yeah you know and i got to tell you for the amount of
people i saw
swooning over ghost busters i didn't see any fucking people in that god damn
fight yeah all right and i did jump in and i did get her back because i thought
It was disgraceful and I'll tell you the numbers of people supporting her in that situation were far fewer than the people saying
You got to go see this movie. I never really say anything serious on Twitter
But my you know, and it was the same thing with the police shootings or whatever. I'll
Retweet something. I'll say something kind of vague about the situation in general
But like as far as me going hey these guys are assholes who trolled Leslie Jones
I don't know that my voice needs to be heard there
and I guess I can see the point that my negative voice on Ghostbusters doesn't
need to be heard either. But at the end of the day I can sort of pick and choose
whatever I want to talk about and so can you. I did it out of solidarity as a
comic and I was like I've been I'm a comic and I've been in this situation and it's
not a racist one. Yeah, yeah. I've been in a different situation with probably the
same trolls quite frankly. And I was like this sucks you feel all alone. Right. You're
beyond yourself. You want to rip your hair out. You're you know she was literally in
tears yeah that's like she needs other comics to step up and be like hey we got
you do don't worry about it like this will pass and and and keep keep up the
good fight
so look in closing yes ghost busters all of it from from the
The first one in 1983 to now, none of it's been great.
Absolutely not.
The original is kind of funny.
It looks a little more dated each year.
And what I do like seeing is when people send in their pictures of their little girls and
go asbestos uniforms with a proton pack.
I love it.
Keep it above the belt, Pat.
This is it.
Jesus.
I love that they get their, you know, their heroes, but I will also say, you know, like where
Where were you when Pixar's Brave came out?
I just, I mean, all these people, everyone has to see Brave this weekend to give kids
a positive aroma.
Nobody saw Brave, everybody doesn't like Brave.
I just don't know how you can pick and choose.
I think, you know, go watch all of Nicole Hall of Sessner's movies.
There's a strong, hilarious, excellent female writer director.
I would recommend enough set her most recent with Gandalfini and Joy Louis
Dreyfus. I love that movie. Love that movie and everything she did before it
is equally as good. There's my little part. Don't watch that and set it
Ghostbusters. Support that woman. She makes her movies for, you know, probably
the the last 50 ,000 she has in the bank. And if you haven't seen it, go, go buy
nine to five. Don't rent it by it. Yeah, it's great. And it's a wonderful film, Lily
Tomland, Dolly Parton, Jane Fonda, and Dabney Coleman, Dabney Coleman, guaranteed coffee
breath. I think I've said it before. If anyone in the world has coffee breath at all
times, it's Dabney Coleman. I was talking to somebody about nine to five and they were
saying that they wish that had been the plot of Ghostbusters that they, for some reason,
needed to kidnap Dabney Coleman. I'll tell you this, those, those same four in a remake
of nine to five, which is a movie that kind of needs a light shown on it and could very
well be updated for a modern audience then we would be fantastic it would it
would be well and will Farrell is the boss there you go there you go and I'll
tell you I'll tell you how they did remake nine to five without paying the
original people any money a little bit called horrible bosses starring all men is
it the same it is the same thing isn't it sort of it's essentially the same
exact thing plugs look I but the time this comes out I'll probably already be in
Scotland. So, uh, if you're in, if, if I'm in Dublin right now, come see me in Dublin
at the Vodafone Comedy Festival. Here's your pickup line over there. Hey, uh, are you Irish?
Because my penis is Dublin, just looking at you. Really? All right, maybe, maybe they'll
love it. I was going to say, I was going to say, hey, hey, Dublin, I've drank so much since
I got here. I'm seeing trippling. That's what I was going to say. Also good. That's not really pick -up line.
But in all of August, the second through the end of the month, I'll be at the Edinburgh
fringe, residency, go to my website, joderosacomity .com for details, all the info's on there,
the dates, and all that stuff. So I'll see you soon, UK. Yeah, I'm on some episode of Rode's coming up
the ninth episode, Twitter via Instagram, V Patrick Walsh, and as always guys we love getting
your feedback, we screen grab and send them to each other. If you can at me and Joe with anything
even if you're just talking to me or Joe because we get a kick out of them.
And thank you for the great reviews. We had so many five star and awesome reviews on iTunes. I was
blown away. I went through and read them all. Thank you guys so much for doing that. Appreciate it.
Shout out to my lifelong friend Mike Curry who put up a great one as well. Mike, I know you'll listen. I love you
Thank you, baby, like your wife. I hope you're doing well. Oh one last plug. My fiction column has debuted
Despite accusations from certain writers that I don't read much
My fiction column on fangoria was website is up some severe situations first stories called something in the water
All that you're doing them one a month one a month
Continuing that one or a new one, new one, the anthologies every month.
So next one will be out next month and go read the new one.
I hope you like it.
All right, this has been, we'll see you in how a presentation of the Fangoria podcast
network produced by Thomas DeFail, executive produced by Ken Hanley of Fangoria Entertainment
for press opportunities, advertising, inquiry, and information about.
We'll see you in how contact Ken, his email is kenatfangoria .com, see you later.
You