Folks, it's We'll See You in Hell, our final episode for the month of March, and this March
Madness, we will be speaking about Speak No Evil, of course, the American remake produced
by our faves, Blomhausen, it's going to be good.
Yes, we reviewed the original Speak No Evil back in 2022.
That film was Danish and very rough and disturbing.
It was on shutter, nihilistic, you would almost say, bleak to an insane degree with a miserable
ending.
This film tells largely beat for beat the same story, but since this is Hollywood and
this is Blomhausen, a much more positive ending.
And this one was directed by James Watkins, who's had a very bizarre career.
He did Eden Lake, which I know I saw, I don't remember, but it's always in like most underrated
horror movie lists, Eden Lake.
I think it's always on shutter too.
Have you seen that one, Joe?
No, I need to see it.
It's a I know I watched it at the time, but I don't remember it.
Then he's the second unit director on The Descent Part Two.
He wrote it, but went down to second unit.
I mean, I've never seen a director make that move.
It's it's I can't imagine his team would have wanted him to make that move.
Well, maybe he's friends with the director and was like, yeah, let's have a go at this.
Could be, could be.
It's just it's it's rare.
Then three years later, he did The Woman in Black, which Joe, didn't we review The Woman
in Black?
God, I if we didn't review it, we've at least spoken about it.
The Daniel Radcliffe, that's weird.
Somebody just brought that up to me the other day and I was like, yeah, there's a better
version, the original version.
And they were like, oh, there's another one.
I was like, yeah, that's a remake.
And, you know, that Radcliffe one is fine.
You know, I thought we reviewed it, but maybe we just watched it on streaming because this
is 2012.
So that was kind of before our time.
Bastille Day, which I've never heard of starring.
What's his face? Idris Elba.
OK, and then Speak No Evil.
It's kind of a very sort of thrown together career here.
I'm surprised he got the gig, but he does a good job.
I mean, it's certainly a suspenseful movie.
We'll get there. We'll talk about it.
Joe, what's going on in your neck of the woods?
Nothing, nothing too much.
You know, my big my big story was was, you know, going to England with Shane and then
watching Alec Baldwin talk about his wife's ex -boyfriend's cock.
Mm hmm. You know, those were the big moments in my life this week.
Yeah. Did you see that clip or did you watch the whole episode of the show?
I just saw the clip on Instagram.
OK. And which I took off my phone today and off my iPad.
It was you got to you got to take it off.
It's it's it's sick.
It gets in there. It gets in there.
I realized, well, you learn a lot when you pull when you pull your vices.
And for me, it's I was I wrote a whole Miss Pat about it this season because I was like
thinking about it all the time.
And I was like, I think this applies to Miss Pat as well.
I can just write as her character.
I can't stand the silence, you know, I can't stand just like sitting there.
I can't. And if I'm high, I don't mind it.
If I'm drunk, I don't mind it.
But with nothing, it's like, OK, I'm walking to the bathroom.
I need to be watching something on Instagram or turning on a podcast to accompany me on my
walk to the bathroom and then going to the bathroom.
And then, like, I'm walking, you know, getting my steps at work.
We have this giant warehouse we shoot in and I'm walking around and around the building.
But I'm like on my phone while I'm walking.
And I just keep noticing that.
Like, it happens more and more when there's no vice to take the heat.
I just need a constant distraction.
And I got to stop that.
I got to get more comfortable sitting with myself.
That's the key. But it's impossible sometimes.
It's tough, man. It's tough.
I was writing about this last night.
The noise, you know, how can anybody sleep when the noise is so loud?
It's just, you know, it's not a great time.
It's not a great time.
And yeah, these devices do not do not help.
I'm terrible, man.
I'll be in bed all of a white noise machine going.
I'll have YouTube on my iPad playing, trying to fall asleep.
Can't sleep. Then I take my phone out.
I'm looking at my phone while the iPad is on.
It's nuts. I mean, it's just nuts.
I was waking up at 3am every night and I go to bed now at a pretty good time,
usually by 11pm, and every night I was waking up at 3 o 'clock
and it was driving me fucking nuts.
So now I've been off the substances, whatever you want to call them,
for a couple months and the sleep pattern wasn't changing.
And I was like, well, fuck, I thought that's what it was.
And I realized if you look at three seconds of Instagram reels before bed,
your sleep is going to be destroyed.
And if you look at two hours of Instagram reels before bed,
your sleep will be destroyed.
You won't be able to go to sleep because you'll be so jacked up on dopamine.
And you will wake up feeling like you didn't sleep at all
and you won't be able to think or focus the whole next day.
It's it's more harmful, I would say, than drugs and alcohol, the Instagram.
I delete it from my phone once a month.
But then, you know, you start to need a distraction at home.
That's sex. I can't have sex out here.
Well, yeah, and that's that, you know, that's that stuff, too.
It's like going, you know, the porn stream and, you know,
there's nothing wrong with porn.
But my God, it's like at this intake is just nuts, man.
It's just nuts.
This content intake is just crazy, whether it's Instagram or
or even YouTube. I love YouTube.
I really love YouTube.
It's my number one source of entertainment.
And I see a lot of wonderful stuff on there.
But Jesus, God, man, it's just it's you.
You could refresh your YouTube
every 30 seconds for 24 straight hours
and not see the same thing pop up twice.
I mean, it's bad shit, man. It's bad shit.
And then this thing, too, of like I clicked on a video once and now I will forever.
I keep seeing psoriasis of the scalp videos
because one time I clicked on one like, like, what is that?
What is going on?
Like, I'm not interested in psoriasis or something.
I've had to say it five times.
And it was one of the one of the things, not the video itself,
but it was one of the reasons I took Instagram off my phone.
I was like, it's not even listening to me anymore.
Like, this is crazy.
It's become a marriage to you.
Yes. Speaking of YouTube, by the way,
shout outs to to our boy, Joe,
Joe from Hats Off Entertainment, Joe Ramone.
I was talking to him this week.
Nice guy. He's the nicest guy.
We were texting this week, too, talking about.
Did you see his great outdoors?
No, I need to catch up on all his stuff when I'm back.
I told him I have the Uncle Buck 4K here in Atlanta,
but I have no way to play it.
So I got to get back in L .A.
We should we should try to do the episode with him next month
and we could do Uncle Buck and just talk about it.
Yeah, for sure.
If he's down.
But he he told me that the thank you for this, Joe.
It's huge praise.
But he said that this show has become one of his go tos for movie
fun and news or whatever.
And he's paying for it, right?
He must be paying for it.
Trying to figure out how to hook up a friend or two once in a while,
but there ain't no way to do it.
There's no offense to the patrons.
I'm kidding.
But yeah, seem like a very nice dude.
And I told him how excited I was to have any sort of commentary on Uncle Buck,
because I was obsessed with it since I was 10 years old or nine years old.
I walked in and then the morning it was August 8th on a Friday in the summer.
And I said to my mom, we're not waiting for the dollar show, baby.
You need to get off that couch and you need to grab your purse because we're
going to see Uncle Buck today.
And she took me.
And God, that I love it.
And there's been very, very little information about it.
Even in the John Hughes books I have, there's very little information about it.
So I'm curious as to where he got his info, because I've been looking ever since.
And I'm also curious what he's got.
So I can't wait.
I truly can't wait.
It'll be the second thing I do once I get home after I assume taking a giant bowel movement.
The girl that played the daughter duct tape over her mouth in his basement.
The video's going to drop by 7 AM.
Talk.
You don't want to know my methods, but I got the info.
He, well, anyway, in his Great Outdoors video, which I'm a big fan of that movie,
he talks about how Hughes was supposed to direct the Great Outdoors.
And the guy that directed the Great Outdoors was supposed to direct planes,
trains, and automobiles.
Then they cast Steve Martin.
And Hughes said, can I please direct it?
I'm such a Steve Martin fan.
And the guy said, sure, I'll do Great Outdoors.
And what a blessing.
And I never knew that, having researched both those movies.
Howard Deutsch, the other director.
He said that those two movies, and then there was a third one.
I can't remember what the third movie is right now.
But he said, basically, they're spiritual.
It's a spiritual sort of trilogy.
Like, they're all sort of connected in their own way.
She's having a baby, probably, because there's the audio clip of that movie
in Plants Trans with Kevin Bacon.
And Kevin Bacon appears at the beginning.
And it's about adults.
Said to him, I can't stop thinking about this.
But ever since you said that, and I love Ackroyd and Great Outdoors.
It's my favorite Ackroyd role.
But I was like, ever since you said that, I keep imagining if they had followed
planes, trains with the Great Outdoors, but with Steve Martin.
And now it was flipped where Steve Martin is the brash kind of annoying guy.
And Candy is the lead that you kind of feel a little bad for, or whatever.
And he was like, oh my god, man, that would be nuts.
I'm like, yeah, I can't stop thinking about it.
That would have been so cool.
Yeah, I mean, I think Great Outdoors, especially at that time,
would have been a little beneath Steve Martin.
But yeah, it would have been cool, for sure.
Great Outdoors, the problem is he still had one foot in the teenage world.
And those teenage love story aspects of Great Outdoors are death.
Yeah.
They're bad.
Dude, you knew teenagers better than anybody on Earth.
How did you suddenly forget it for this movie?
Well, because he didn't direct it.
I think because he didn't direct it, it was missing just a certain,
not saying the guy that did did a bad job.
I liked the movie a lot.
But I think there was just a certain maybe subtlety those teenage scenes needed.
They're a little heavy handed.
Yeah.
He had a lot of proteges do his movies.
Howard Deutsch was a big one who's married to Lee Thompson now.
I think that's who directed it.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
Oh, OK, sorry.
So he had a lot of proteges where he would write and produce, but not direct.
He did it with Career Opportunities as well,
which I think is pretty underrated with a great cameo from.
Wait, did he direct Career Opportunities Hughes?
I don't think so.
Cameo from John Candy.
I don't think he did either.
Yeah, that was another protege, Brian Gordon,
who would go on to direct many films.
And then he had Peter Feynman do Dutch, which we all love Dutch.
But John Hughes would have made that movie into a classic
because I think it's really good.
It's just not super well directed.
Well, with the exception of Home Alone, and this was always another one.
Chris Columbus.
Biggest success.
This was always my problem with Dutch.
With the exception of Home Alone, you feel the absence of Hughes.
It's missing an undefinable magic that Hughes puts in there.
Dutch is the perfect example.
I watched Dutch as a kid.
And even as a kid, I was like, I should love this, and I just don't.
There's something missing here.
I don't know what it is.
I loved it.
But like all those movies I just mentioned, including Great Outdoors,
I felt like they were missing a bit of that Hughes touch
or that he was putting his second tier efforts off on somebody else,
not with Home Alone.
But I'm sure if he knew how big that would be, he would have directed it.
But Columbus, forget just nailing the Hughes tone.
I think Chris Columbus is a super underrated director
who followed kind of the same trajectory as our boys Zemeckis
that we talked about last week.
He was making amazing movies, and then he just stopped doing that.
He was like doing Bicentennial Man and shit.
Just lost the Rent musical.
Remember that one when they adapted that?
He was just the wrong guy for the wrong movies for a long time.
He came back in with Harry.
He did the first Harry Potter.
First two.
And he doesn't get the credit he deserves for like, he made that.
He created all that with a team, of course.
But like, I mean, talk about perfect casting, perfect everything.
Oof, you did Pixels.
Yeah.
Pixels, you know, it's bad, but it's not the worst.
It's, Pat, come on, man.
I might prefer Pixels to Little Nicky, which I tried to watch this weekend.
Little Nicky sucks.
Oh my God, it's terrible.
I mean, and that was right during his prime.
That one is bad.
This is odd.
He did the Christmas Chronicles 2, but not the Christmas Chronicles.
Produced.
Yeah, I guess he produced, but didn't direct.
Well, no, he didn't even produce the Christmas Chronicles.
He just he directed and produced the second one and wrote it.
But the first one is not listed here.
Well, yeah, Columbus, I mean, I'll do the same thing I did for Zemeckis.
His first is Adventures in Babysitting, which is a classic John Hughes ripoff,
a perfect John Hughes ripoff.
It's so good.
I love that movie.
Then Heartbreak Hotel, which sucks.
Then Hughes, for some reason, gives him the keys to Home Alone, which I guess at the time
it was, we all thought it was just going to be some little kid's movie.
Who knew?
But God, did he nail that.
Only the Lonely with John Candy.
About as romantic as they ever let him be.
And it's such a sweet, wonderful movie that we've discussed on this show.
Home Alone 2, underrated.
Mrs. Doubtfire, overrated.
Nine months, underrated.
Stepmom, not good.
Bicentennial Man, not good.
The Harry Potter's, classics.
Rent, terrible.
I love you, Beth Cooper.
Hold on, you skipped Christmas with the cranks.
He did that one.
That's right.
Oh, he produced it.
He didn't direct it.
But he wrote it.
He did write it, yeah.
Well, he also wrote fucking Gremlins, thank you very much.
And Goonies.
And Goonies, yeah.
But yeah, then Percy Jackson, which was a Harry Potter ripoff.
Pixels.
And he actually didn't get as far into the weeds as Zemeckis did.
I just really hated Bicentennial Man.
No, and in fact, I think Christmas Chronicles 2 was well received.
They were both entertaining.
Yeah.
And he's got this new one coming out called The Thursday Murder Club,
starring Helen Mirren, David Tennant, Ben Kingsley, Pierce Brosnan.
All right, I'm listening.
Are you a young Sherlock Holmes fan?
He wrote that, too.
I've never seen it, though.
Man, when I was a kid, I loved that movie.
Holy shit.
I own it.
I've never watched it.
Yeah, it's great.
You should watch it.
It's fun.
I mean, I remember it being fun.
I don't know.
You know, yeah, I remember it being quite good.
And featured the first ever, I think, CGI character ever.
There's a scene.
The movie's about an epidemic happening in London where there's a guy going around
and he's shooting these like poisoned darts into people.
And the darts are making the drug on the darts are making the people
mass hallucinations and do crazy shit.
And there's a part where there's a guy in a church.
He gets shot with the dart.
And a knight from the stained glass window jumps out of the window.
And it's like a stained glass knight that tries to kill the guy.
And I remember seeing the making of the movie on HBO.
And they were talking about how nobody's ever done this in a movie,
like made a character out of with a computer.
Yeah, it was Lucasfilm.
Lucasfilm did.
Yeah, interesting.
Yeah, anyway, that's your Chris Columbus.
That's your Chris Columbus.
Speaking of directors, they just announced Darren Aronofsky doing Cujo.
So it's going to be like, you know, little boy getting ass to ass with a St. Bernard.
I don't really know.
He did Requiem for a Dream, The Wrestler, and Mother, for Christ's sake.
The Whale.
So, you know, look, it's a harrowing book.
And he does harrowing movies.
So maybe it'll be good.
I'm glad they went with a serious director and not somebody who directed
like one Shudder original that, you know, a few critics liked,
which is what they seem to do with like Pet Sematary and all these giant franchises.
Just give them to any kid who's shot a little movie, anything.
So it's kind of cool to go the other way.
Darren Aronofsky trying a lowbrow Stephen King.
Great.
And I also don't hold that original in high regard.
No.
I think it's effective in the dog scenes, but the rest of the movie is like,
boy, it's strictly a testament to the acting of the little boy and the mom
that we care at all because the movie gives them no help.
Like we don't know or give a shit about them,
except all we know about the wife is she's having an affair.
And they get thrown into this situation.
It's like, I don't know.
I was surprised when I watched it again recently on the 4K, how not great it was.
I got good news for you, Pat.
With Aronofsky directing, you might finally get those dog monologues
that you thought were in the book.
He's he'll be the guy to do it.
I don't know, man.
You know, of all the pretty lousy day.
But then I saw this car pull in, you know, I I'm sure there's a lot more depth to the book.
I read I never read the book, but I read the synopsis of the book when we reviewed the movie.
It doesn't seem that far off from the beats.
If I remember correctly, from the beats of the actual movie,
I don't know how much more there is to mine there.
I don't really quite understand why there's a great interest in remaking Ku Joe
of all the Stephen King properties.
You know, God almighty, man, the dark half, which I really like the Romero version.
That's a fucking awesome story, man, that you could redo and make really cool
and make it your own.
You know, fire is coming.
I've been dreading misery because they can't improve on it, but it's coming.
You know, it's coming.
They won't do the shining again, I don't think, but they'll do.
I promise you they'll do the shining again.
I think of all of them, that's that stands the best chance
because of Doctor Sleep and because of the success.
But that wasn't a hit.
That's the only reason they won't do the shining again.
But, you know, even like Firestarter, they still have not adapted that well.
Both versions suck.
Just Ku Joe, it's like the the the fucking movie, the original is fine.
It's good enough.
Like it's like, I don't know.
Yeah, it's a rabid dog that traps him in the car.
I don't think it's that interesting.
But my guess is he's going to write it and bring a lot to it is the hope
because what he won't do, hopefully, is follow the father out on his
job selling cereal additives, which is like half of Ku Joe is the dad out,
you know, going to conferences trying to sell food additives.
Like he's Clark Griswold.
That's that's a big part of the book.
So I don't think Aronofsky is going to go, hey, we should bring this stuff back.
My guess is he'll take it in a new direction, hopefully.
Well, there's far, I'm assuming, far more focus in the book on the troubles
of the marriage and the affair that the mother has and all that stuff.
So it's like, maybe that's where Aronofsky is going to really delve in
and get into like here, you know, here are the problems.
Does she have an affair with Ku Joe?
So he'll have a guy not even in makeup playing the dog.
Yeah.
Just walking around representing the dog.
But I don't know, I liked Mother.
You just kind of groaned at it.
I liked Mother and I liked, wait, what was the one after that?
The whale.
I liked the whale quite a bit, but you weren't as crazy about it.
I hated it, but The Wrestler is one of my favorite movies of all time.
I thought the whale was essentially a fat wrestler remake.
It was the same story just told way, way worse with the exact same ending.
All right.
Which is, you know, the wrestler ends with him jumping into the air
and it's like, is he going to live or die?
Probably die.
And the whale ends with him jumping into the air
and it's like, is he going to live or die?
Probably die.
Yeah.
Well, he floats, he ascends, which means he just died.
I was trying to give them the benefit of the doubt
and pretend that he jumped
because that was the stupidest fucking ending I ever saw.
All right.
Why don't you take us that movie corner?
Joe, I sure will.
I sure.
Did you, oh, you were saying that semi -pro held up.
Yeah, I think it's funny.
Because I watched Blades of Glory again,
thinking it was semi -pro going off your recommendation.
Blades of Glory is not good.
Blades of Glory, Joe, is not good.
It's got all the elements to be good,
but as soon as, you know, six writers appear on screen
and then you look it up and it's like,
busy Phillips claims that she originated the idea for the movie
and sued successfully,
so now she's supposed to have a credit on it.
Seth Rogen said him and Evan Goldberg
contributed most of the funniest stuff in the movie
and got no credit on it.
And it feels like that kind of movie, you know?
It's like we got Feral for three months.
Let's just make this thing.
And it wasn't ready.
It's like you have so many funny people there.
You have a funny premise,
which is basically these guys have to team up
and be ice skating partners,
which just basically leads to gay jokes for the most part.
One very funny gay joke where they're basically 69ing
while they skate and each one has their face
and the other one's crotch and is trying to not look at it.
That made me laugh, I'll admit.
It was supposed to be Feral and Stiller,
which I think would have made,
neither one of them would have let this movie
be as sloppy as it is.
Feral would have, Stiller wouldn't have.
And Stiller just said,
I've played this part too many times before.
And he's right.
He played way too many times,
even though they were all funny.
That guy from Dodgeball, from Heavyweights,
from Billy Madison, et cetera.
And they instead swap in John Heater,
who really has no character.
They tried him in School for Scoundrels
and these other movies,
but it's like when they tried to make McLovin
into something else.
He's Napoleon Dynamite.
There's not a lot of other gears there.
So with his character,
they just go to a lot of gross out stuff.
It doesn't work.
You got Amy Poehler and Will Arnett
trying their best, but not quite hitting,
not having the material to hit.
You got Craig T. Nelson, Nick Swarsden,
Jenna Fischer, William Fickner, Andy Richter,
Rob Cordray.
Everybody that shows up is funny,
but you're just not really laughing.
So they made a ton of these.
My hope was that when you go back,
they're all going to be like
that semi -pro experience Joe had
where you're like,
this thing's actually really funny,
but that's not the case with Blades of Glory.
Joseph?
No, I watched, rewatched.
I hadn't watched it in a while.
House of Games, the David Mamet movie.
David Mamet is interesting.
For me, most of the time he hits the mark
and has written some of my favorite,
he's my favorite writer
and certainly my favorite playwright.
And most of the time he writes something
that at the very least has me interested
and hooked in and at its best riveted.
But sometimes when he misses the mark,
the worst I can say is
that it's just kind of boring or something.
House of Games, I like the movie.
It's his first film.
I will say this is the only thing he's ever done
where you could watch it and go,
does he not know what he's doing?
It's interesting.
It's a caper.
It's about a psychiatrist or therapist
or psychologist, one of the three.
It's played by Lindsay Krauss, his first wife,
who gets through one of her patients
roped into the world of short con
and long con and con men
led by a pack of con men
led by Joe Montagna.
You got Ricky Jay in there.
You got a lot of the Mamet players showing up.
Um, you know, and watch it for yourself.
There's a lot of little twists and turns
and things and as it unfolds,
it becomes more and more interesting.
But it is one of these things
where by the end of it,
you're kind of like, wait a minute,
hold on a second.
How did they know that she would do this
at this point?
It's a little too, you know,
as luck would have it,
she's in the right place
right when they need her to do this thing
so they can then make her do that thing.
And Heist, the DeVito Gene Hackman movie
does a bit of that,
but Heist is just for whatever reason,
a little more palatable.
House of Games is also one of these Mamet movies
where everybody is going super Mamet in it.
Everybody is going.
Do you understand?
Do you understand what I am saying?
Do you understand what I'm saying to you,
to you right now?
Do you understand me?
Everybody is doing the Mamet speak thing,
probably because he directed it.
But there are other movies he directed
where they just don't do that.
Heist is a good example.
It happens at moments,
but for the most part,
the actors do their thing the way they do it.
It's also weird that in his scripts
he writes for others,
that's not a part of it,
like Untouchables or Hannibal.
People aren't talking like that.
He's not directing those.
No, I know.
It's just like,
and I don't know why you have to write
everything that way when it's your project,
I guess because it's his style,
his signature style.
Well, I'm saying he writes it that way
a lot of the time when it's not his project,
but he's not directing it,
so it's not as evident.
I got you.
He's real big on,
say the words.
I don't want to hear any shit about your character.
He's real big on that.
Anyway, it's an enjoyable movie.
I think the Criterion 4K just came out.
I will buy it.
I do want to own it,
and it holds a special place in my heart,
I suppose,
but it's a little bit of a head scratcher.
I rewatched the movie
that the first time I saw it,
I got my first kiss,
and then I became sort of obsessed with the movie,
maybe because of the kiss.
I don't know.
Untamed Heart came out in 93.
I didn't really remember anything about it.
It's Christian Slater.
I remembered that he had a baboon heart,
even though that's never confirmed
whether that's true or not,
but he's a mute for half the movie.
He's borderline mentally challenged.
He works at a diner as a busboy.
Also working at the diner
is the always delightful Rosie Perez,
like one year after White Men Can't Jump,
and the always delightful Miss Marisa Tomei,
who I know I said
has never looked better than in The Wrestler,
but she looks better in Untamed Heart.
I fell in love with her when I was a kid.
I remember I was like,
why would I watch this movie so often?
What did it offer a 13 -year -old boy?
The answer watching it now is nothing.
It's not a good movie,
except Tomei is running around in her underwear a lot,
and it's like a white Hanes top and bottom.
You never see that on an actress.
They're always wearing something sexy,
something about it.
I love a white top and bottom, though.
I got to be honest.
That's what I'm saying, Joe.
That's what I'm saying.
It won me over.
She comes home from her job at the diner,
and she's going out with her boyfriend,
so she takes it all off,
and she's running around the house in her underwear.
I immediately felt like I was 13 again.
I was like, I see why I watch this movie every weekend.
And then there was boobs.
She's getting it on with Slater.
She takes her shirt off, and she's topless.
I was like, okay, it's all coming back to me now,
as Celine Dion once sang.
The movie is pretty embarrassing.
It's so stupid, but she's so good in it.
She basically works at the diner.
Of course, it's Christian Slater,
so you're like, oh, there's this cute guy here,
but he's, as you know, Rosie Presley is like,
I do him, but he's so fucking weird.
He's so fucking weird.
She's hilarious in it.
They're both great.
Slater is what he is,
but he follows her home every night.
This is what I learned at 13 that women like.
He follows her home every night.
Two guys try to rape her.
Slater happens to be there
because he follows her home every night
and beats the shit out of these guys,
and then she falls in love with him.
She's like, why were you even here?
And he's like, I follow you home every night.
She's like, oh my God, that's so sweet.
He walks her home.
One morning she wakes up
and she's got a Christmas tree put up in her living room,
and she's flattered by it.
And then the next day he admits
that he's broken into her home,
set up a Christmas tree for her,
and she's flattered by it.
And he goes, well, that wasn't the first time.
She goes, what do you mean?
He goes, I break into your house all the time
and we'll just watch you sleep.
And she's moved by it.
Jesus Christ.
Like, we wonder why men have problems.
You grow up watching this shit.
The mildest example is Say Anything.
She dumps John Cusack
and he shows up with the boombox playing their song.
That's mild.
You do that in a movie today,
nobody's going to lose their shit.
But pretty much everything beyond that
that went on back in the day was insane.
And it's always a male screenwriter
showing you that women love to be stalked.
It's kind of nuts.
And then the movie plays out like Love Story
or any one of these classic romantic tragedies.
You know he's got a baboon heart,
they don't go into it.
And then all of a sudden,
at about exactly the 90 minute mark, he dies.
And she cries and reads a letter from him
and the movie ends.
It's a movie just designed to make you
fall in love with these people
while they're falling in love
and then cry at the end because he dies.
It sucks, but I was glad I watched it
because it really took me back
to a certain time of my life.
Joe?
I rewatched a movie I hadn't seen since I was a kid
and I always hated.
Then I read something about it not being so bad
and I thought, let me give it another shot.
Dolf Lundgren's The Punisher.
It was an official Marvel release.
It was back before Marvel became Marvel,
as we know it.
And certainly before they were ruling the cinema.
I always thought this was a lousy adaptation
of the move of the comic book
because he doesn't wear the costume
with the skull on it.
I got to tell you, folks, I watched this thing.
I went right to Amazon, made a purchase.
It was at my front door the next day.
I was like, I got to own this.
This thing is wildly violent.
It's Dolf Lundgren at his most stoic
and cold and callous.
It's a hell of a fucking ride.
Cartooning mobsters just getting killed
in insane ways for 90 minutes by Dolf Lundgren.
This movie is a lot of fun.
It's not going to make it onto any lists
for film courses in any schools.
But I'm telling you, if you want to just enjoy yourself
stupidly for 90 minutes
and you want some good juicy prime time,
Dolf Lundgren, go watch this Punisher movie.
You will enjoy it.
Never seen that or the Tommy Jane Punisher.
The Thomas Jane one sucks.
Okay.
The Ray, is it Ray Winstone?
Not Ray Winstone.
Yeah.
No, it's, no, but it's, I know Ray Winstone's a guy,
but it's the other guy, Ray, the guy that just died.
Hold on.
Raymond Burr.
Raymond Burr as the Punisher.
Ray Stevenson.
You punished me.
Now I punish you.
He's talking to a cupcake.
Punisher Warzone is the Ray Stevenson one.
That one is also awesome.
And it reminds me now of the Dolf Lundgren one.
Louis Gossett Jr. also in the Dolf Lundgren one
is Jake Berkowitz, the head detective
who's trying to figure out who the Punisher is
and all that stuff.
Everybody else I never really had heard of,
but man, it's fun, dude.
It's just a fun, insane movie.
And it's kind of cool seeing a Marvel movie
that's gritty and not shiny and bright and fluffy
and riddled with every movie star that's ever lived.
So anyway, good stuff.
No whips, I would imagine.
Yeah, but not like Marvel these days, one or two,
but no, it's way more Rambo than...
Yeah, I was saying I didn't think there would be quips.
Oh, sorry.
I thought you said, okay.
Anyway, I thought you were saying you were okay, Spider.
I watched Dario Argento's opera
because Joe Bob did the original 1925 Phantom of the Opera,
which was celebrating its 100th anniversary.
And he also did Argento's opera,
which luckily was one of the few Argentos
or at least the classic Argentos that I had never seen.
And it basically tells the Phantom of the Opera story, kind of,
but he added all kinds of weird shit in it.
And it's a beautiful movie.
I mean, Argento makes movies with like amazing colors
and amazing cinematography
and the kills are always so good
and both beautiful and scary and fun.
And opera's no exception.
I would say it's maybe his best shot movie.
It looks incredible.
He's got this big budget.
The camera's always swooping around
and he's doing POVs from crows.
And it was great.
The kills were awesome.
There's a shot through a peephole that's really awesome.
There's the most famous sort of shot
that I know influenced Saw and many others.
I didn't influence Clockwork Orange,
but similar setup where this woman has nails or spikes
attached to her lower eyelid.
So if she blinks, it's gonna stab her in the eye
and they get real close on her eye
and they make her watch, you know,
the killer makes her watch this horrible murder
with her eyes pinned open.
Very memorable.
It's the poster for the movie.
Everything about it is just like awesome.
And it's really how I felt about,
how I feel about all Argentos.
He makes some of the coolest looking shit,
but from a story screenplay standpoint,
it's always just a goddamn mess.
Even Suspiria to some degree.
And I don't think it's always the language barrier with him.
I think it's just maybe he doesn't have the patience
to sit down and actually make things make sense.
In this movie, Opera, you know,
it's one of those where it's like,
oh, we finally got the killer.
And then there's a reveal that,
no, he threw a mannequin into the fire.
And then you're like,
so he came to her house to kill her
with a mannequin of himself
that was so convincing that the police fell for it?
Like, what are you talking about, Dario?
And there's too much of that in his movies, quite frankly.
If he ever met a great screenplay,
meaning one that he didn't write
or at least one he had help with,
he'd be considered one of the greats,
but he insisted on shooting his own,
often very shoddy screenplays.
And I think Opera, unfortunately, is that
because it's arguably his best looking movie.
I loved the way it looked.
It just, the story was so stupid,
you couldn't take it seriously.
Well, I couldn't agree more about Dario Argento.
He allegedly wrote his movies by waking up from sleeping.
Yeah.
Going downstairs and describing the dreams he had to a writer
who would write it down,
and that's why none of the movies make any fucking sense.
I agree completely.
They look beautiful.
They make no sense.
And by the way, they only look beautiful
for as long as he's working with the right DP,
because the second the DP -
Well, he is on this one for sure, yeah.
I mean, Christ, you watch that, Argento's Dracula,
it looks like a guy that's never seen a movie before made it.
I mean, it's insane.
It's insane.
Yeah, Joe Bob talks a little bit about how this was like
one of his best collaborators,
and like he was only as good as his collaborators and so forth,
but he's got a big touch of that Shyamalan thing.
Shyamalan just won't admit that he needs a little help
on the scripting front at this point.
He just won't.
And so we get movies like Trap, unfortunately.
Even though people dig it, I know, and more power to you.
Our movie of the day is a remake of Speak No Evil.
Joe and I, I remember giving it a hog up for sure.
I liked it, but it was very bleak.
I don't know if Joe gave it a hog up.
Do you recall, Joe?
I remember saying I wasn't quite sure who the movie was meant for,
because it was so bleak that outside of some sort of social commentary,
I just wasn't quite sure why anybody would watch this for entertainment,
which was a lot like...
What was that movie about crazy women in the 1650s or whatever the fuck?
The Devil's Bathtub or something?
That was a tough one.
Real tough, yeah.
It was like that.
Yeah, it's like where you're like,
I understand that the message is important,
but I'm just like, who the fuck is watching this to enjoy it?
This is, it's just so depressing.
That's how I thought about the original Speak No Evil.
I will say, though, after seeing this one,
my respect for the original has risen.
This one was not as bad as I thought it was going to be,
and it had its moments.
It was well directed.
It was very well acted, particularly by James McAvoy.
The guy is good.
Yeah, he was great in it.
As his wife, or was it his wife?
No, it was the other guy's wife, Mackenzie Davis.
It was his wife, yeah, sorry.
Wait, no, Mackenzie Davis is the other guy's wife, I thought.
Oh, and the other guy is Scoot McNary.
Why do they have him listed like 12th?
Yeah, Scoot McNary.
Okay, fine, got it.
Mackenzie Davis plays the American wife.
Yes.
Scoot McNary plays the American husband.
James McAvoy plays the English husband,
and Aisling Franciosi plays the English wife.
Excuse me, so the premise here is this, people.
An American couple are on vacation at a resort in Italy.
They meet an English couple.
The English couple and them, the two couples hit it off.
The English couple is the sort of fun, carefree,
who gives a shit, we're going to have a good time couple at the resort.
The American couple is a little more reserved,
and you can see that there's a bit of disappointment,
particularly in the husband,
that they don't cut loose quite like these English folks do.
They get an invite to go out to the English people's farm,
and at the time, this American couple is living in London,
they say, sure, when we get back to London, we'll drive out.
They do.
They bring their daughter.
The English couple has a son.
The son has a condition where his tongue did not grow properly,
so he cannot speak.
And of course, once they get out to the homestead of the English people,
things get odder, and then awkward, and then evil,
and the shit goes down.
It's the same exact plot.
So I was just going to say, it's almost beat for beat, the original, to a point.
Yeah, it's the same exact plot as the original.
The only difference occurs in the third act,
and in the third act, which was heavily criticized
by the original director of the original film,
the third act lets things end.
And in American terms, and it's still a somber note,
but certainly a much more hopeful note than the original does.
The original ends with the family being stoned to death by the crazy people.
And the reason they're doing this is because they meet the crazy people,
they meet a couple, they kill the couple,
steal all their money by having them wire whatever they have
into their bank account, steal any of their valuables,
and then abduct their kid in this mission to find the right child for them as a couple.
And the assumption is that they're also killing the other kids
because the other kids don't meet the grade or whatever, make the grade.
They never really get into why they're doing this.
They're trying to make this into some like,
this would probably be like the kind of guy who listens to Joe Rogan kind of thing
in a lot of the reviews and the press for it,
but that's not really there in the movie.
That he's a right -winger or something.
They want to tie everything to Trump now,
and that's not really the vibe this movie gives, in my opinion.
He says, they're only saying that because he says,
when James McAvoy has become standoffish with them,
and he is kind of making a good point.
He's like, you know, you make me sick,
like all of your choices are based in privilege,
and you know, you sit there and act like you're saving the world with your causes,
and I forget, I'm paraphrasing, but it is true.
There is an arrogance that a person like that has,
as being, you know, it's why the term white savior exists.
But then, of course, he's batshit,
and he goes in a terrible direction with all of these thoughts,
but yeah, I didn't think it served as a political commentary.
I thought it served a little more as a social commentary
on the fact that people who are out there trying to save the world
aren't really great at saving their own self and their family,
because when this all goes down,
there's a million chances these people have to leave.
They have a million chances to leave and save themselves,
and they continually don't.
And as frustrating as that is to watch,
that is kind of the point of like, it's people who are being polite,
it's people who are not recognizing the real threat when it's in front of them,
it's people being focused on the big problem and not the micro problem,
and this is right here, right now, address it, do it.
There is a great part where they finally are driving off,
and then they see, they've figured out what McAvoy's plot is,
and the family's driving off, and he oddly lets them,
and you're like, why is he letting them go?
And then he takes the young boy that's supposed to be their son,
who you find out is just a kid they kidnapped,
and he throws him into a lake and the kid can't swim,
and they turn around and go back to save the kid.
And then that's what leads them into McAvoy's grasp, ultimately.
And there's a line where they say, like, the mom says, I love my family,
and he says, if you loved your family, you would have let this kid drown.
And you're like, wow, that's fucking cold, man.
There were some pretty cool sinister parts like that,
where I was like, okay, I'm buying this villain, he's good.
But, you know, my biggest issue with this movie was the third act.
It turns into essentially a reverse home invasion movie in the third act.
They're trapped inside of the killer's house,
and the killer is trying to get to them and kill them.
And, you know, it's Blumhouse.
This is not me knocking the abilities of one gender versus another,
anything like that, but it's Blumhouse.
So, of course, the dad has to be this sort of
cucky, terrified guy that can't take any action,
that literally needs to be told by his wife at one point,
snap out of it and save your family.
They need you.
It's a little absurd after a while.
You're like, guys, the guy's survival instinct would kick.
I mean, come on.
And the wife leads the charge, and that's fine,
but it's just like, we get it.
We get it, Blum.
We get it.
Or the kid ends up beating him to death, if I recall correctly, correct?
The young son puts the final death blows on James McAvoy.
But, you know, and...
I think the third act was your problem with the original as well,
which was that they just are too dumb, the couple and the original.
I think I remember you having that problem.
Yeah, and that's one of the points of the movie.
I realized after the fact that it was annoying me,
and then I read the original director's take on it.
He goes, no, this is about polite society and how it can get you killed.
Yeah, well, that's what I love about both movies
and thought they did really, really well.
Is the slow, gradual...
We've all been there.
You go on a double date, and the other couple is just really weird,
and it keeps getting weirder.
And then maybe you go out for drinks, and then it gets even weirder.
Yes.
You don't know, are these guys trying to fuck me?
Are they trying to kill me? What's going on?
They handle that really, really well.
And all the stuff that McAvoy does in the first half
would definitely make me uncomfortable,
but I don't know that I would say something.
And that's where the great discomfort lies, you know?
And then when it flips and gets evil,
I think one movie has the courage to stick to its convictions.
And obviously it had different goals than the remake.
The remake was much more about entertaining an audience
in a Cape Fear type way.
Yes.
You know, Cape Fear was a very bleak movie by the end.
But, you know, it's more of a popcorn entertainment.
And the original really sticks to its guns,
and that's the one that's going to stick with me, you know?
I thought McAvoy was really, really good,
probably better than whoever played the part in the original.
And sometimes the movie just goes down smoother
when you're watching it in your native language.
Of course.
But I would still say I preferred the original to this one
just because it did what it set out to do.
And this one felt like a cop -out in the end.
It felt like every other thriller
after building up a lot of really well -sustained tension
for a long time.
It didn't really honor that in the right way for me.
I don't remember if this was a twist in the original or not,
but I liked it in this.
There was the reveal that McAvoy's wife
was one of the kids he initially kidnapped,
and she grew into the role of his wife.
And I thought that that added a little extra evil to the whole thing.
I also don't remember there being a subplot in the original
about the wife almost cheating on the husband,
the American wife almost cheating on the husband,
and having another guy's dick pics on her phone.
Again, it's like they just go so out of the...
It doesn't need that aspect.
It doesn't need the aspect of the weak husband.
The point of the movie is not that.
The point of the movie is
people that are striving to accommodate other people
and also striving to save the world
end up in a situation like this
and become quite compromised as a result of those two things.
That's the point.
That's all you need.
What's more interesting is not that one's an alpha
and one's a complete cuck.
What would be interesting is how an alpha
can make a normal guy either act out
and become more macho than he normally would to compete,
like an animal,
or become sort of a cowering version of himself
because it's like,
okay, well, this guy's clearly running the show.
But you kind of fuck up any dynamic
if the guy is a sniveling loser
who lets his wife have dick pics on her phone.
You're messing up the point of the movie a little bit to me.
Yeah, it's odd.
Well, he didn't let her.
He was pissed about it.
Well, yeah, but he also was taking a trip with her.
I did not know the...
I said her name.
I apologize.
I'm forgetting.
Mackenzie Davis or the Italian?
No, no, no.
The Aisling Franciosa.
Yeah, I guess she was Italian.
I was unfamiliar with her.
But she...
Well, wait, stop.
Oh, she's the girl in stop motion.
I didn't realize that.
She's the stop motion artist in stop motion.
Oh, okay.
All right.
That's where I knew her from.
And then what is Mackenzie Davis from?
She looked really familiar.
She's been in a lot of stuff.
She was in like, I want to say Rocket Man,
the Elton John biopic, which I liked quite a bit.
Oh, I thought you meant the Harlan Williams.
No, but I saw that theatrically.
Oh, that's right.
She was in Terminator Dark Fate.
There you go.
She portrayed Tully in Diablo Cody's Tully.
She was not in Rocket Man.
I was wrong about that.
The one thing I knew her from, I was incorrect about.
Blade Runner 2049.
I thought Charlize Theron was Tully.
She was Tully.
Well, no, there was another girl in there.
Like, Tully was the nanny.
Oh.
I don't want to spoil Tully for you,
but Tully is the nanny.
There is.
There's a huge twist in Tully.
I'm not even kidding.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
I know it sounded funny, but I'm not kidding.
It's gotten so dark in my house, and I can't get up to turn the light on,
so I'm doing it like scary movie style.
I can't see at all.
I mean, it's wild.
Now you can, right?
It looks worse like this.
I'd rather you just go to the darkness.
Yeah, this looks crazy.
Yeah.
Well, I haven't gotten a haircut in a while.
I look like Charles Manson.
She was in Blade Runner 2045.
Yeah.
I don't remember who she played in that.
I don't remember much of that movie.
Anyway, I liked her a lot.
I thought she was really good.
I thought she did a very good job of playing the dynamic of a woman
who is repeatedly put in a position where she has to accommodate her hosts,
but also still not just lie down and not express herself.
She played that awkwardness very well,
like when they were having the arguments about meat
and that sort of thing.
And McAvoy really played the whole thing well of a guy that's fucking with you.
Because there were a lot of moments where he would be like,
I'm not a doctor.
Did I say that?
I'm sorry.
Sometimes I just say things.
And they're all freaked out.
And then he starts laughing.
And he's like, of course I'm a doctor.
He just played those moments so believably where I was like,
God, I've had this guy do this to me.
Up until the part where he kidnaps my family and tries to murder us.
And that's coming.
No, it's really well acted, really well directed, really well done.
I miss these kinds of movies, these thrillers.
I think a lot of times when these thrillers would be made in the 90s,
they would be remakes of foreign movies.
And we just happened to see the original in this one,
so we have a comparison.
But it's a really good thriller if I didn't know the original.
And if it couldn't help but be a bit of a letdown the way the movie wraps up.
But it's good.
It's no Cape Fear.
But it can hang with some of those unlawful entry type 90s really fun,
romantic, not romantic, but you know what I mean.
I would say it was much better than Pacific Heights or unlawful entry or any of those.
It's better than Pacific Heights.
I happen to love unlawful entry.
But I hope it did a little business.
It's doing well on Peacock.
But I'm hoping there's more of these types of movies.
I love these types of thrillers, adult thrillers.
They went away just like comedies did and just like the erotic thriller did.
But I hope we get more of all of them.
And My Hog is certainly up for both versions of Speak No Evil.
Joe?
I don't know if My Hog is up for the original still.
I have gained, you know what?
Yeah, sure, because I have gained respect for it.
By watching this movie and also reading the director's commentary on both films.
And My Hog is up for this.
I know I started out sounding a little more negative.
I do think the original ending is better.
But the ending of this, whatever, it wasn't bad.
Like I said, my problems with the movie rely almost exclusively in the third act.
But that all said, it's not bad.
So My Hog is up, sure.
And I agree with Pat.
Let's get more of this kind of stuff out there.
Jarring, challenging, abrasive.
And I can't believe I'm saying it.
I like the Blumhouse movie.
Folks, we will be back next month in the month of April.
We're going to do Apartment 7A slash Rosemary's Baby for an episode.
Hopefully, we'll get Joe Ramone on and do Uncle Buck.
Hopefully, we'll do The Monkey and then something else.
You know how it goes.
By the way, I didn't realize how badly that fucking Mickey 17 had bombed
until I tried to go see it in Atlanta in its second week of release.
And they had pulled it from the fucking theater.
I go, didn't it come out last week?
They're like, nobody came to see it.
Not a single person.
$200 million, right?
Yeah.
Let's go check her out.
But yeah, we're probably not going to be reviewing that soon.
Folks, I'm on Instagram at ThePatrickWalsh.
We are at Instagram at SeeYouInHellPod.
I love you.
See you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.