folks it's we'll see you in hell we are here for the month of july
with some real fireworks for you hot episodes this month hot movies hot dogs that's the time
of year we're in today we are discussing the ugly stepsister which is another one of these
movies that i've called the wrong thing 18 times like when i get right for some reason i i like
the title ugly it sticks in my memory it's these ones that are like
let him in bring her back tell him hello those are the ones i get mixed up on
um but yes we will be doing that film today we will also be doing 28 years later and just a
warning joe and i hotly agree on that hotly disagree on that title oh yeah um oh yeah
how are we how are we joe i know you got a lot going on i hope the the family things are kind of
at least not in crisis
mode but maybe you'd rather not speak on it there's there's it's it's it's uh it's not
what's the best way to say it we're we're we're we're still deep in the forest but at least the
forest is not on fire at the moment i guess is the best way to put it so at least it's steady
for the moment uh i i can't remember no i wait no i i don't i don't think i talked about this yet
no i couldn't have because i was up in pennsylvania
um i uh i came back to my apartment in uh austin to find uh extensive water damage that was fun
so but the good news there is i found a great contractor and the insurance adjuster seems like
he did his inspection and seems like he agrees with the contractor so hopefully hopefully that
will all massage itself into where it needs to be and not be another nightmare
uh feeling better about the breakup but uh you know uh there's not much to i probably shouldn't
just shouldn't talk about that and that's fine well here's something i've certainly regretted
every time i've spoken about my romantic life uh here's something interesting uh i was invited
to see
uh the new ari aster movie i'm excited to see that by a good friend of mine in stand -up comedy
yeah who is a a quite notable person i'm not saying a name just because i don't want to sound
like i'm you know doing that thing it's earthquake it's earthquake and it's not shane it's somebody
else i know but anyway um he was like why don't you come with me man i've i got like an invite to
a private screening of the new ari aster movie and i was like why don't you come with me man i'm
coming tomorrow and i was like oh thanks man um yeah cool and then uh and then uh he's like yeah
you got to come and i go well i got kind of a busy day i'll try to make it and he's like what
are you talking about like this is gonna be fucking awesome like let's go and i was like
look man we've never really talked about movies it's just not a thing that we talk about in our
friendship but i fucking hate him uh i hate both of his movies i don't i don't want to see this
movie at all and he was like i'm not going to see this movie i'm not going to see this movie i'm not
you're forgetting bo is afraid yeah he was like you're fucking oh yeah bo's afraid i forgot about
it he goes you're fucking crazy i was like i we let's just agree to disagree i hate his movies
and uh and anyway he did go and see it and he claimed that it was awesome uh and that it looks
awesome he just assumed that you would agree with the rest of the world but you're joe de rosa
that's not how you operate um i found another person that hates him as much as i do uh my friend
uh amy who was a writer on tires her husband who's a very nice man and works in the biz i'm
not going to say his name or what he does as to protect his anonymity anonymity but she if you're
wondering just google tires writers find amy and then you can find her husband really easily
why would you
why would you i'm just saying that's that easy i mean i don't know who he is but i'm saying that
they can figure it out if they'd like to um well i don't want to you know given all the key
information you don't need a homicide detective to figure out who the man is this kid's i probably
shouldn't have said amy's name but uh this kid you know we talked off the record but i i i said
to her uh in the first week of work these these uh because she she used to work at a monkey
company
paul yeah jordan peele's company so we were talking about the you know current horror
and i just was like you know she was like so do you like you know did you like you know are you
big like with the the hereditary and i was like i fucking hate that movie so much and she was like
oh my god you have to meet my husband yeah he hates it and he's the only one he knows that
hates it and he's desperately trying to find but i was like please so every time i've seen him
there's been some sort of hate and i'm like i don't know what to do with him i don't know what
to do with him i don't know what to do with him i don't know what to do with him i don't know what
i asked or update either you know bo is afraid just hit streaming or now he's announced this
new movie with a bunch of a -listers about the pandemic uh i could be wrong but i think you
might love bo is afraid at least the first hour it is about what a hellscape it is to live in new
york with anxiety i mean i don't know that you'd love hour two and three and i didn't either but
that first hour is the funniest comedy in ages well if movies work that way and you could just
watch the first hour and say i don't know what to do with you i don't know what to do with you
you can it's on hbo max look are you still under my subscription by the way or did you have my own
i got my own and i got the ad free now by the way if there's more than one amy on the tires staff
just look for the one who also worked at monkey paw joe uh gave you more information to track her
down um i don't think it's i don't think i'm saying anything terrible it doesn't matter um
we're not gonna kill this guy for having an opinion the uh um what was i gonna say
i just i well but bo was afraid i'm i'm over joaquin there's a lot in that movie that i don't
need to see uh you know about a week after your house you came home to find water damage my
girlfriend came home from work to find everything in six inches of water in her apartment and her
dogs freaking out like they were gonna drown
and it was just a neighbor who had caused a fire completely stoned passed out caused a fire
sprinklers go off that's great in their apartment and the next unit and then they're like yeah sorry
it was just one of those things where they just completely fucked her over every step of the way
i hope it turns out better for you but they were like yeah we can't really pay you we can offer you
this shittier apartment that you'll have to pay more rent for see because you got a good deal
when you moved it they were trying to jack her rent in addition to everything else
i think she might have a lawsuit on her hands there yeah yeah i might have to strap on the old
white matlock suit and get to business um i'm about to sue the fucking city myself i i was
i felt like i was in bo was afraid things just kept piling up on me i get this notification in
and it says hey the street below mine where where the stalker lives there's brush overgrowing onto
the street and you need to you know weed whack it back to expose the curb and then you like like
here's to the inch how far you have to pull back this stuff so i go down there and i'm like oh okay
well i can easily you know trim this but there's also sheet rock and dirt and actual like boulders
that have fallen down it's a big downhill slope so when we get the rains this all falls onto the
street below mine it's all contained it's not ruining the street but it's like they're asking
me to clear sheet rock that can't be penetrated with a shovel so they're like if you don't
completely clear the curb the reason being so that emergency vehicles can get through
the trash truck gets by every week no problem but suddenly there's an emergency if you don't do this
we'll fine you eleven hundred dollars jesus so i'm like all right you know i asked this gardener guy
in the neighborhood hey can you scale this back he does
he's like but i can't penetrate this giant wall of rock that's and i'm like well fuck so what do
i do i call they go we'll just leave it the city will do it and they'll fine you eleven hundred
dollars i'm like yeah that's not going to work for me sorry so i get out there with the shovel
it's 100 degrees here so i'm doing it at like 7 a .m to 10 a .m just start bashing this i've
been doing this every morning just getting rage out bashing rock you know it's falling into the
street and i put it into my trash can designed for this
designed for waste you know yard waste and rock and dust dirt then it's so heavy i can't push it
back up to my house so i bring down another trash can i fill that halfway up i'm able to pull them
back up i put them out and i'm like well the trash man will empty these i can bring them down the day
after the trash comes refill them and i should be done and avoid this fine i come out both of my
trash cans yesterday on trash day are still full to the brim and they have
like little post -its on them that say too heavy yeah the trash can has a giant metal claw like in
the in aliens with sigourney weaver that picks them up like it's nothing i'm not asking you to
lift it on your back well it might be it might be that they can only take a certain level of weight
from each can in order to be able to complete the route properly or something like that there
might be a weight limit and they're saying so and so and so and so and so and so and so and so and so
sorry this is these are overfilled well that's fucking stupid and they didn't weigh the cans
and i also pay like three hundred dollars a month for trash pickup so we need to find something else
to do so now the city's coming today to check on my work and i i'm out there dumping dirt onto the
side of my house where is the i don't i'm not understanding the where is the sheet rock that
you have to what is this so there's my house on a street
and then the street below mine is also my property technically but it's just that they just want
stuff pulled back from this curb but since it's a hill from my house anytime it rains dirt and
rock falls down and just gets packed in tight okay stuff that doesn't roll into the street
just becomes like that's how rock formations happen they just sort of uh keep falling down
into the street and then become compact and really hard to penetrate but i mean i'm not
out there trying to hide dirt like i'm in a prison movie i'm dumping it into like every
potted plant i have and all to avoid this fee and at the end of the week after like
15 hours of work i'm like i should have just taken the fucking fine yeah i don't i don't
understand it would have cost you a similar amount to pay people to do it properly like
you have to look at it like that well if i really wanted to i could have hired one of these
migrant workers in my neighborhood to do it for probably 200 but now i'm just sort of i don't know
i'm not supposed to do that right now not supposed to do that right now um also one of these workers
robbed my home uh in the neighborhood and i just have to pretend and not go around uh accusing
everybody but that's so that's what happened i saw him on the on the fucking ring cam so
it's just annoying you know it
feels like that the city now is in on it meanwhile like you you didn't even look for
my wedding ring when my home got stolen you didn't follow any leads you treated it like
it was a fucking joke but now the city needs me to do this or you're gonna find me yeah but that's
the cops not the city or the cops not the city yeah you're talking about two completely different
departments here these are two that here's the thing joe when you bitch about something i give
you support you're taking the side of the city and the police i'm trying to yeah it's
i'm trying to give you some perspective well you know you might have overfilled the can
pat i mean what is this i'm trying to give you some perspective here i'm so you're saying i'm
trying to explain why they might not have taken the can i'm not saying you're wrong to be annoyed
but but the thing with the with the job itself it cost me four hundred dollars
once a month to have my property which is significantly smaller than yours de -weeded
yeah like weeds that grow because
because there's so much rain and then so much heat the weeds grow very quickly if i want to get
it de -weeded it's four hundred dollars that job of knocking that rock out if done properly would
have probably cost easily over eleven hundred so my point is is you just look at the the fine as
the fee that you would have paid anyway to get the job taken care of which is a it is a thing you
should have taken care of but the fact that the city is doing it in the way that they're doing it
is disgusting it's what coastal cities are doing to their residents um they are finding ways to
create situations where you are forced to pay them money uh you will be further treated like
it is your privilege to live there and not your right um and that's where it's at man you know
it's horrible yeah it's a it's a shakedown i mean the wording of the notice they gave me seven days
to do it so it's like what if i was out of town what if i was out of town what if i was out of town
what if i was this and then they're like we'll come on this day and if it's not done you know
we're gonna march the the fine right up to your door the day's come and gone it was an empty
threat but they're doing stuff it's like in raising arizona when they're like we're gonna
count to 800 and then drive back and the guy's like oh bullshit and then he sees them coming back
you know um it feels like mob shit because it is obviously they announced today that uh gavin
newsom is making low -income housing in the pacific palisades where that were just burned
down remember he was all giddy about that so it's like yeah this is fucked up you know that was the
the ritziest area of los angeles and now they're it's destroyed in a fire and now they're building
low -income housing there there's just it's like chinatown out here well you yeah i mean i don't
know you guys got a real mess on your hands out there the the the way that guy has conducted
everything uh yeah is you know we don't have to get into the podcast
politics of it but yeah it's it's i should say it's more like who framed roger rabbit in chinatown
they were skilled uh grifters and con men it's more like the toontown patrol yeah so gavin's gone
from uh never mind i was gonna i was gonna comment on his take on home his approach to
homelessness oh i mean well his people are gonna really try to walk it away when he starts shooting
homeless in the head when the olympics come to town
i mean you but you're this is also the guy that that was just like yeah have fun guys put a tent
up anywhere and it's like okay let's see how that goes guys yeah yeah okay it's fucking there's
there's a tent inside the lobby of your hallmark store yeah it's like guys well yeah that that is
actually sort of going away and then you you'll i'll there's a big tent city five minutes from me
and you'll drive by on a friday and it's like oh wow this is looking like a goddamn
flea market over here and then the next day there'll be nothing and it'll be completely
immaculate and you're like well what happened to those people you know um wild times wild times
my friends uh gardner was taken by ice who it's been like a family friend for years
he comes up uh and he's got this giant chunk taken out of his face they were like what
happened to you he's like um i i messed up with the saw
i'm not like what are you using a saw for you're a gardener and he's like i had a project i needed
to use a saw for like the next day he was taken by ice so they're like what happened to him with
the so like with the face thing everyone's just on high alert and uh i stay inside most days
i'm done i'm done uh i'm shot there's nothing left what's up i said joe was afraid
rate it yeah there's just nothing left in the tank i don't know i don't know i don't know
i don't care i'm drinking every day don't give a shit i i don't care anymore i don't care
there's no point to any of this there there's no control there's no change if i see one more
stupid fucking person talking about protesting on on instagram as if it is going to change
anything yeah at all i saw the at &t girl put a post up if protesting isn't convenient for you
other things you can do oh if if the laziest most pointless thing isn't convenient for you
that's the same girl who's doing only fans now no no no pat pat only philanthropy only
by the way no judgment to our our sweet sweet only fans entertainers i'm just saying
uh to talk about how you how uh apathy and how you're you're doing nothing while you're showing
off your cans online is is comical to me she said there
she dated my old roommate i actually know her a bit she said they will only be flirty pictures not
nude pictures but you know and for anybody listening that's like joe how could you knock
protesting it's using your voice it because it doesn't work i don't know how many fucking times
everybody has to see that a protest can only go so far before they bring in the national guard
yeah now if protests worked and
and i think when when this really hit got me into the red was during the pandemic people screaming
in your face back six feet back six feet and then 24 hours later marching side by side no mask pussy
hat on it's like well what are we doing which which issue are you angry about um if that worked
if that pussy hat protest work or if the black lives matter protest worked things would be
different we wouldn't be closing planned
hoods across america we wouldn't be doing ice ray it's you can say we don't like this but do you
think trump's like wait a minute these guys in los angeles my favorite city don't like what i'm doing
boys boys let's pull the plug well that's that's what i'm saying it's like when you when you say
when you say this i said it about occupy wall street and people would scream at me that i was
on the side of wall street i go i'm not on the fucking side of wall street i'm saying that this
isn't going to do anything
it's just not going to do anything the definition of insanity is doing the same thing over and over
and expecting a different result it's literally the definition of insanity and we are watching
people go crazy and spiral during these protests yeah for christ's sakes the people that are in
favor of the protests can't even get along with each other yeah true it like because some one
person says these are the boundaries another person says these these are the boundaries and
other person says you're not going far enough whatever it is guys it doesn't matter they don't
do anything you can argue that it sparks national discussion well so does will smith's latest
freestyle rap video there's a lot of ways i'm on action star oh my god that is a lot of ways
to to spark a national uh discussion and it's just i i i feel like protesting i i have a joke
about it in my new special by the way out july 21st available
now uh on the uh for pay -per -view if you go to my youtube at joe de rosa comedy you can click on
the you know the video and it'll and their link the link is in there to take you to an early access
pay -per -view of the special but if you don't want to see it early well i was going to watch it with
my lady friend and we couldn't find it and i'm fairly i'm fairly savvy we searched joe de rosa
on youtube and i couldn't find it in 10 minutes and i gave up so what do i need to do literally
what i just said uh go to my youtube channel and i'm going to go to my youtube channel and i'm going to
at joe de rosa comedy on youtube there's a big thing for the special you click it and then
there's a link to get to the all right i here's what i'm saying smirky snarky i wasn't being
snarky here's what i'm saying could there could there be an easier way to find it should you
maybe enter search terms or hashtags or something so when i type joe de rosa new stand -up special
it brings it up it's not on you i think we're miscommunicating here
it's not on youtube yet you can link to where it is through my youtube okay gotcha but it but if you
just search my name that makes sense if you just search my name you can go to my channel the very
thing at the top of the page it says it's i never promised you a rose garden you click on that the
trailer plays yeah and in that caption there's a link to go to this you could also just go to
disruptorcomedy .com and it's on there how about that all right disruptorcomedy .com we're right
there first thing on the on the screen and then you can go to my channel and you can go to my
page disruptorcomedy .com early access uncensored unedited unclothed check it out but anyway i i have
a joke in the special where i talk about protesting and uh and and i say i'll i'm
going to give away one of the jokes i say uh all protest protesting is all it is is it's laying on
the horn in traffic makes a lot of noise pisses a lot of people off doesn't change
the situation at all at all totally you're you're you're expressing to the world your impotence
your inability to do something about a terrible situation be it traffic or racism or whatever
and yeah i what what i get about it is that it's community i get that it's hey we're all united
where i you know i'm sure people hook up after these protests it's kind of like a party vibe
um
and then they always seem to get out of control you know and it's all all that is is giving the
right more opportunities to go look at these maniacs it's not and in my opinion it's it's i
hear you i hear your point i'm not arguing your point but in my opinion it's not community
and you would know that you you if you were in new york during uh occupy and you saw how local
mom and pop shop owners couldn't open their business
is because of the occupy area and the people in the barricading and whatever and then when those
people were challenged and asked you're hurting the uh business owners these are the people that
you're sticking up for yeah they would say casualties of war just sorry man collateral
damage but this is a bigger cause right uh if you watch the stuff about and look they fix wall
street though yeah exactly given that what
the difference it made when when the president that everybody thought was going to do zero wrong
ever bailed out did it the exact thing that they that they said dick cheney would have done
the exact thing um the um uh and if you watch the stuff about the ice protests
um you know and see the things where the shop owners are saying you know man like i'm appalled
by what's going on too uh but now i gotta repair my shop because it was
vandalized yeah for for what i didn't do anything i'm just down here yeah my my girl lives down
downtown los angeles and we went for a long walk down there on saturday night went and got dinner
and i was like this is a fallen state you know this this is not my city anymore it's a my city
in ruins it was it's like the cvs has these giant wood blocks you know instead of a door to the city
door like exactly what i did when my house got broken into just these and i'm like did somebody
break into this cvs she goes no every business down here replaced their doors with like crack
den wood for the protests in fear but what that does once the protests leave town is give one of
the biggest cities in america an appearance of being a you know a several mile wide crack den
it it looked like a
like a fallen city and it is let's be real i will it's only a matter of time i will
purchase an rv yeah and leave society it will happen into the wild style not into the wild no
i i will buy i will i'm i'm i've thought about this at length this is my this is because i'm
not a suicide
guy this is my version of suicide i wish i was yeah um i will buy no i will buy a nice rv like
a very livable rv i will get rid of many of my possessions probably all of them i'll keep a few
things a little you know one or two nintendos to plug into the tv and and you know my clothing
and a few books yeah a bluetooth speaker goodbye to the record collection um and and i will just
drive around and and plop down in different parks uh and and places that are affordable to rent for
the evening with my rv and that is what will be the rest of my life that is going to happen
walk the earth like kane and kung fu i i get it uh uh so i i'll just figure out when let me get
this special out first and then the new salsa windfall record out in the fall and uh and after
that you know that'll be that might be yeah no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no i uh you know we we joke i have spoken to the writers guild about when i can cash my pension out
recently and i you know i'm 20 years away from like thinking about retirement but lately i'm like
hmm i wonder um let's let's get on to something more positive movies i want to i want to discuss
the uh trailer for this new uh hail mary movie from the writer of the martian
gosling our only good actor our only good like hot actor you know and he's in this thing delivering
lines like so they ask him he needs to be an astronaut but he's not an astronaut and he
delivers the line in the trailer i mean i put the not an astronaut delivered like seriously like
it's a drama you know who's in this movie by the way cannavale no the at &t girls in this movie i
saw this trailer because i went to
her instagram today yeah when she made the announcement about the only philanthropy i was
like wait what is she doing and then i started scrolling i saw the protester post i got really
mad and then i saw this trailer what what possible reason and i'm sure they explain it it's based on a
on a beloved book but what possible reason could they need a man who's never been to space to be
an astronaut why that man
you know and then what is gosling's next movie a star wars movie from the director of deadpool
like stop it ryan how much money is enough you know you have the power to green light good
scripts yeah maybe this thing will prove me wrong the martian was entertaining i just no matter how
they explain it i'm not going to be able to accept that we need to send a man who's not an astronaut
into space it's like affleck's hilarious armageddon commentary
why are you training drillers to be astronauts and not astronauts to drill yeah and he said and
michael bay told me to shut the fuck up that by the way is the funniest commentary track ever made
it it made me uh unable to dislike ben affleck because he's hilarious in it um yeah this is i
mean this is like you know god love her but scar joe doing yeah jurassic world rebirth this thing's
got a 53 %
this thing is getting hating that movie like that of course you know i was walking around with my
buddy uh ben rogers who's a very if his he's got a great podcast two action boys uh with my friend
john gabrus and ben said hey he had seen it and there's um it's like this it's like the suicide
squad they're like there's narration and it's like this is the island where we put the dinosaurs who
are real bad
it's like no these are the the dinosaurs who rape you know like what are we talking about
yeah yeah and then and then though i promise you there'll be an interview somewhere along
the lines where gareth and is it gareth edwards yeah he'll be doing an interview
you see it was a commentary on deportation oh do these dinosaurs deserve to be put in the
on a bad boy's island or should they be allowed to stay you know the first immigrant really was
the mighty t -rex if you think about it that's what i saw james gunn out there on the red carpet
talking about how superman was an immigrant and i was like buddy you are so dumb you are so dumb
kill me because it's like james we're all very aware of the superman
story he's an alien stop twisting it to make it sound like you you were you were saying something
you made a superman movie yeah and then what i what i hear about the movie which is is pretty
fondly received so far is that it's a return to like the superman being like christopher reeve
levels of nice and how refreshing it is to even have a character that's like that nice and polite
and everything in a movie um great you know like your movie then should be about how niceness needs
to return to the present and that's what i hear about the movie and that's what i hear about the
return to earth like at this moment in time to make the biggest movie there is at a time when
movies are failing and come out and say hey i think half the country will hate this movie then
you're stupid you're stupid if you want to make a protest movie drop your budget by 250 million
dollars oh god oh yeah yeah it's just so fun this is how lost everybody is i'm gonna i'm gonna say
something it won't get back to the person i don't think
but it's somebody we know joe please tell me you're not going to give us more information
about this girl who rides for tires no no we've already found her okay this was a post by somebody
we both know and who i'm friendly with yeah but i gotta make fun of it it was because it was from
the superman premiere yeah oh i know who it is then and it said uh i saw it too hold on a second
i i want to i want to i want to make sure i don't quote this
incorrectly
you're gonna see it i assume right yeah i might actually go today uh i heard it's fun and you
know i'm curious i want to see what he's doing with this thing well i've um i i've said no more
superheroes and i pretty much meant it but i forgot crumholtz is in it so i'm gonna go so
we can do it on the show oh davy baby is in it yeah well then yeah that's that's a nice perk
by the way this move that's the reason i'm seeing it
david if you're live you're out there with this movie gun this i'm reading the caption with this
movie gun gets at something i believe in deeply keeping your heart open is the most punk rock
thing you can do yeah i saw to refer to it's a fucking 200 million dollar movie you're on the
red carpet in a dress that cost at least six grand yeah punk rock this is these words don't mean
anything anymore no
word means anything anymore by the way like something like suicide squad at least gets
closer to that label because it's r -rated and the humor is really edgy and so forth
not superman there is there is no punk rock superman okay there is no punk rock warner
brothers produced dc cinematic universe james gunn directed thing it's it's crazy this is crazy
anymore people the words need to retain
their meanings we're we have hyperbole out of control at this point it's insane everything's
the best everything's the worst yeah it's a lot there's no nuance in anything let's get to that
movie corn i'm gonna yeah i'm sorry i didn't mean to cut you off i'm actually gonna take up
my movie corner with a with a new segment i'm gonna bring a new segment into our
old segment
okay and you and this is a segment you can join into i don't have a name for it yet
okay but this is to be honest i never learned a few of the other ones so
this is a rant segment where i saw something that made me so mad about about movies that i want to
rant about it okay and admittedly because of my work schedule and uh more more importantly my
life crumbling uh
i haven't been able to see much so i've got some stuff in the movie corner but i might save it for
the next episode and i wanted to introduce this new segment anyway so uh you do your corner and
then i'm going to do this little segment all right um first off i saw sorry baby which is uh
an a24 um i i you know of course they're known for their horror and their disturbing shit
this is just a very classic
comedy drama along the lines of what like fox searchlight used to release you know
a little miss sunshine or something like that it's really interesting because it's a comedy
about sexual assault um it was written and directed by this woman eva victor it stars eva
victor and the plot is basically you're watching her her friend comes to town um there you know
her friend's having a baby they kind of gossip and giggle and have some laughs and there's a cute
guy next door played by lucas hedges who was in manchester by the sea and he was in every indie
movie there for a couple years it was good to see him i haven't seen him in a while very likable cast
you know and about half hour in something terrible happens she is sexually assaulted by a professor
at his house it is one of those
you know uh sort of not a gray area thing because it's very clear that it was an assault
but it's like she went there she was attracted to him um they start making out but she wasn't
really feeling it and then multiple times he puts his hand where it doesn't belong she tries to pull
it away he doesn't stop um i guess you would classify that as a date rape but as the comedian
hal spark says the date ends once the rape begins i think that is a pretty bullshit term date rape
um by the way that's the only time i will quote hal sparks it's just one of the jokes he made
where i was like yeah that's a good one i like that um anyway her life goes on and this was very
i don't want to say refreshing but it felt very true to life and realistic because when you are
and i have not been i don't know i i can't i can't speak to it but i would imagine
when you are assaulted you have to
go about your life you have to go to your shitty job you have to engage with friends and co -workers
and everything else and she is doing all this while trying to process the grief of this sexual
assault and surprisingly all of the comedy really works it is a comedy about how people don't know
how to react to you when you've been assaulted um people don't know how to help you your friends
don't know how to help you your your enemies your nobody knows what
to do you have to go about your life you have to go to your shitty job you have to engage with
what to do with you and you don't know what to do with you and you've got this grief pouring out of
you and it's kind of wrecking your life but also you got to go about your life and it felt very
true and very raw and it was very funny in parts there's a great cameo from john carroll lynch who
played francis mcdormand's husband in fargo um really great cast it's just full of great small
moments this would have been a classic to me if they didn't blow it with a final scene that i
just thought was a nothing it was a great scene and i think it's a great scene and i think it's
going i thought if they nail this final scene i love that when a movie is like funny funny it's
about schmidt's the best example funny funny funny and then it just knocks you out at the end
and the ending was the biggest shrug i wish she had rewritten that ending and i think we'd have
a classic movie about assault instead it's maybe the only comedy i've seen about rape and uh it
was pretty brilliant in spots also if you're writing and directing a movie
starring in it you can't have every other character refer to you as hot that that's a rule
that started to bother me yeah i i'd agree with that but overall uh it's a it's a must see it's
like there are no like good interesting little movies anymore so when one drops please run out
to the theater and see it uh even though it is backed by a24 which is basically the warner
brothers of the indie world they do have good taste and i think this is a really good movie
all right you want me to do all three or what
well however many you want to do if you i don't want to interrupt your rant once it's gone so i
guess so right why don't you do two and i'll do i'll do the rant you do one more and then we'll
do the movie you want to just do that uh yes i do um i would like to shout out a movie that's
on amazon prime right now another little indie on an even lower budget than sorry baby with even
less big stars but this thing is really really good joe you would love it i want
to say to anyone listening and loving this show you would love it as well it's called i like movies
i heard about this it is directed by a woman named chandler levac who just got a big or a bigger uh
budget and and some stars for her next project and good for her because this is a true original
that like really hit me it is a a a troubled young man whose father committed suicide he's
like a senior in high school very unpopular
and he is obsessed with movies and he lives alone with his mom uh she at times hates him
he like they don't soften him it's like you know how nick kroll has that great bit about how when
you're a kid you're just awful to your mom for no reason yeah it's great and that's what this kid is
it's like and at one point she's like i fucking hate you what's wrong with you and you're like
thank you like somebody needed to say that to this kid but she's saying it to you you know like i was
this i was never
mean to my mom or anything like that but i was this movie obsessed kid he gets a job at the local
video store and at first you're like okay this is just going to be a movie about you know a coming
of age story about a kid who's obsessed with movies and it is that and and the details are
spot on and super specific he recommends uh todd salon's happiness to like everyone that comes in
the door and of course they hate it and that's what i was too i would recommend great movies
to people i knew they wouldn't like it but i was like
if it keeps you up to date i would recommend it to people i would recommend it to people i would
biscuit you from renting this piece of shit than great um super relatable and then somebody calls
this kid out on like you are not nice you're not a good person and the movie kind of flips and
becomes deeper and a journey about growing up and and uh you know you you can be immature and love
movies and have that be your life but not at the expense of being a good person and human interaction
and yeah it was it's a real hit and i think that's exactly why i choose that i am a great凉
a really special movie it looks like it was made for ten dollars honestly the video store set i was
like boy i wish i could have given them a little money to make this this video store look better
um but it's very very well directed very funny great bits and if you if that was you if you were
a kid who subscribed to premiere magazine and couldn't wait to go to blockbuster on friday night
this is the movie for you it when his mom says to him like i'm not gonna sit there in the car for
two hours you pick out one movie and you get back in the car i was like yeah this was every friday
for me my mom was like i'm not going to wait for you forever um really enjoyed it check it out
all right um all right here's the uh whatever you want to call this i guess i guess
pardon me you could argue that this uh could fall under news psycho but it's it's it's
something slightly different it's not it's not movie news it's something that
sparked vitriol in me that's related to a a movie uh i think it'll become more clear as i go here
but i saw the trailer for i know what you did last summer okay here's how i can explain this
the the news cycle would be the new trailer for i know what you did last summer is out
about what do we think of the trailer what do we think of them making this movie whatever that's
news psycho it's about the event this is about something specific in the trailer that set me off
uh the trailer is out for i know what you did last summer
they show the slates at the beginning of the trailer of all the production companies attached
to it one of them is called original films
ah
original films yeah this movie is a remake slash reboot sequel of a series that already existed
it is telling the same exact story as the original movie it is bringing back the main
characters from the original movie plus the whole new it is the most paint by numbers version
of reboot that you could possibly do i re -watched it recently you're talking about a two and a half
star movie here to begin with yes now here's the thing they're doing this with a movie
that was already a rip -off of scream so i know what you did last summer the original
is a rip -off of scream now they're making it over again
but as a result of that they're doing this with a movie that's already a rip -off of scream
and the way they're doing the sequel
reboot is the way scream did their reboot sequel this could not be this is the literal epitome of
unoriginal it is as unoriginal as a movie could ever possibly be and the audacity the audacity of
a company called original films is the audacity of a company called original films is the audacity of
original films to produce something like this is everything we are talking about it's uh or we're
talking about earlier it's it's standing on a warner brothers carpet and referring to the event
as punk rock it is saying uh we are a24 and we make grassroots art entertainment yet we're
going to sell our company for five billion dollars and it's a company that's going to sell
out to do something with a title like original films and then immediately not doing it at all
it's a disgusting business it is driven completely by money it is vapid it is
fucking collapsing and it absolutely deserves to collapse it deserves it i'm glad now when i go into
a movie theater and it's fucking empty because it's what they deserve to be and it's what they deserve to be
at this point i'm tired it's it's it's filmmaking it used to be by committee and then now it's it's by
like accountant you know at least some of the people involved in the decision making liked
movies now they've turned over the decision making to the bean counters and the accounting people
and they will not green light something unless there is zero risk this star just made this much
on this movie so we can count on them to bring this much to this movie this you know
the scream thing i guarantee they point for point mimicked exactly what they did with the scream
reboot because that was a success uh by the way we're supposed we're supposed to be excited for
the return of freddie prince jr this man was a sub chris o'donnell talent did you see
um did you see the trailer uh just a little bit of it
um it's just my favorite part and it's literally it's shot exactly like the way they did it with
sydney prescott in the scream yeah five whatever it was the girl you know it's it's it's all building
oh my god we're these young kids and they the they know what we did last summer and all that
bullshit right and then you know you see freddie and whatever and then there's the big moment where
they're walking and they're like excuse me miss i'm talking to you
and there's the big dramatic turnaround to reveal jennifer love hewitt
yeah with some line about you know this ain't my first rodeo something uh -huh is geller in it
who the hell knows i feel like one of them must have died between the two sequels or the one
i still know what you did last summer um yeah i'm not excited about it at all i i have no desire to
even think about it i don't know i don't know i don't know i don't know i don't know i don't know
see it is it the same gordon's fisherman as the last one didn't they kill him uh i gotta be honest
pat i got that no i was in the i saw it in the theater so i must have seen the whole trailer i
don't think they showed the killer okay or maybe they did yeah and i'm sure it was i'm sure it was
the same you know but yeah uh i i started last night the shrouds the new david cronenberg movie
uh it's an exclusive premiere on criterion now cronenberg is a hero of mine
but his latest output has been disheartening at best um i know this movie to be about
i believe fucking corpses or like trying to uh reanimate the corpse of a loved one i'm like it's
you know all right i turn it on and for two two minutes and 15 seconds i watch nothing but title
cards of studios you know jukebox films so a salem film
heartland original content uh two two minutes and 15 seconds and i stopped it and i didn't see
any of the movie i was just like what are we doing that means cronenberg is taking like a thousand
dollars from each person like to make his movies now embarrassing yeah yeah we're not in a good way
man i mean
i always love that in the theater when that happens and it's always on an indie because
people just start laughing at a certain point it keeps coming and coming this is the most i have
ever seen how was the movie i i stopped it before the movie started i stopped it in the middle of
the title card oh i'm i'm sorry i didn't hear you say that part i thought you just i thought
you meant like you paused it and came back no before the before the credits even started i
was like i'm out i i'm not i will watch it but still oh boy well why don't we get to our
movie on hand here we've been yapping for quite a while we've covered life we've covered politics
yes we've covered movies we've covered problems uh this movie is called the ugly stepsister it's
a brand new film uh written and directed by emily christine blick felt she is norwegian
mm -hmm and the film is norwegian obviously it's or it's in uh you know it's subtitled
yeah and didn't bug me at all it generally doesn't but if if the movie's boring it can
start to become like a chore this was not a boring movie no um and it's the cinderella story
essentially you could say you could say well it's told from the point of view of the ugly stepsister
but we all kind of hate that shit you know at least i do like it's a it's a dark twist on the
grimm's fairy tale we've seen it a million times but this really does manage to feel fresh in my
uh due to the look of it due to the performances and the the kind of tongue -in -cheek dark humor of
it uh because of its theme and message which i thought was executed beautifully and most
importantly it's just great to have a really fun can't hardly look at the screen gross out horror
again um this speaking of cronenberg like she knows her cronenberg this movie was gross in a
great way yeah
um i i excuse me i loved uh this movie i also was a little disheartened at the top when i realized
shit i gotta be reading the whole time but that went away very quickly uh it is incredibly
incredibly gorgeous uh beautifully shot i texted you when i was like 30 20 minutes in i go and i
was like look ultimately i have no idea if this is going to be good or not but my god it's it's
beautiful uh it is very beautiful it's very beautiful it's very beautiful it's very beautiful
it's very very influenced by italian uh giallo uh horror filmmaking and there's a lot of argento
in there with the very far away uh very long zooms yeah the push -ins uh the colors uh you
know color plays a big part in this movie um it's very so fixation on eye trauma is also uh yes you
know you know that sewing her eyes or sewing eyelashes on her eyes was the toughest thing
for me to watch and that felt a lot like it was a lot like it was a lot like it was a lot like it
was a lot like um i believe it's inferno where they do that yeah um it's very sofia coppola like
with the use of modern music against a very clear period piece um killer score very modern score
which i love that i that was my favorite aspect of marie antoinette was seeing the strokes over
a period piece it's like why not you know yeah um man we talked about that we were at the we were
at uh the mothership last night we were in the green room and shane and i were talking about
best uh tarantino movies but we talked about the moment when we were like we didn't see it together
but we talked about the moment being in the movie theater watching django unchained and they start
playing the tupac song as he starts shooting up that lake how you you're just like screaming out
of your seat it's so awesome anyway um the movie the plot of the movie is that the it's it's it is
it is cinderella but it's from the perspective of the stepsister now in the
in the traditional story or at least the one that most of us know via disney or whatever
it's that the stepsisters are not attractive and uh the their her father has cinderella's father
has died uh and her wicked stepmother is now forcing her into a life of servitude uh the
prince is in love with cinderella but she's trying to pawn her daughters off onto the prince
um it is the same plot basically but the the big difference here is that the
at the beginning of the movie cinderella is sort of a she's not bad she's just sort of a brat
um but with good reason because she knows what the stepmother is up to
uh and the ugly stepsister who is our star um is a very very sympathetic character
and as the movie goes on and it starts to take form of the traditional cinderella story
you start to have less sympathy for the stepsister and more sympathy for cinderella
so they actually do kind of end it well ultimately without trying to spoil anything
they they actually do end up telling the cinderella story in a traditional sense it's not one of these
things where it's like well maybe the stepsister's like that because cinderella is actually the bad
guy it's not one of those um it's all very very uh very well told very grounded it does have some
very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very very
fantasy elements in it which which elevates the experience in my opinion they don't go crazy
but it's very cool um but man like pat said this is body horror this is i i described this movie
to somebody where i said it's like if the cobbling scene in misery was a whole movie
like it's just seen after because they have to they have to make the ugly stepsister attractive
so the prince will
marry her so this family can get the money that's the whole goal is they want the money from the
prince so they're literally doing plastic surgery to a young woman in the what year the hell year
are these stories from the 1500s the 1600s this felt you know renaissance to me yeah um but yeah
i mean that there is basically a plastic surgeon who shatters her nose in this scene and her
screaming in that scene will haunt me for a while it felt like animalistic
and very real the pain she was in and this guy he's like you know snorting cocaine and and
hammering her in the face and everything and very quickly the theme the theme is established and
then taken to its insane extreme this girl who's you know mousy homely i guess at the beginning but
has an incredible body and you know you wouldn't throw her out of bed for eating crackers but in
the desire to get the prince she
destroys herself through plastic surgery and through making modifications to her body
she'll she'll do anything to get this man and in the process she makes herself look significantly
worse it's it's the beverly hills story you know it's so timely it's so uh you know about
ozempic and about all the stuff that we do where you're destroying yourself in a desire to attract
someone who by the way the the prince is established as being sort of a drip
as the prince always is in these stories and it's like that's what this movie was saying to me is
that women will destroy themselves for a man who isn't shit um and and to what end you know to get
married yeah it's and the the the most heart -wrenching part is when they finally do get
to the big ball at the end uh or in the third act and the prince does seem like he's finally going
to choose this girl
yeah uh and then cinderella comes in and he chooses her instead and the girl is devastated
and she goes into another room and she's crying and then she starts violently vomiting uh because
she is earlier in the film eating a tapeworm egg so the tapeworm will eat all the food she eats so
she can lose weight which leads to a the exact climactic scene i wanted and they gave it to me
um but anyway
her mother comes in because her mother's at the ball and her mother is like stop crying there's
other men so this road that her mother sent her down this horrific road that she made her think
was so important when it doesn't work out the mom is like so what fuck off like shut up it didn't
work out because now her mom is more interested in getting herself laid and whatever and that's
such a great commentary on what it is it's like people make these modifications
yeah and then they're cast aside it's a lot like you know the substance went obviously explored this
um i i thought this was a better take on on the same topic uh as the substance and they both go
to insane extremes but i felt this movie worked better for me and and of course it got no attention
and and it got dumped on shutter and nobody's seen it and the substance is a phenomenon and
that's not really fair but that's the nature of the beast there's no stars and it's polish what
what are you going to do? But, um, yeah, that, that to me too, the, the mom, they go so, they
go so far with her at the end. She's just blowing some literally blowing on camera, some random dude
from the party. And you're like, holy shit. Like, because women will, will completely change their
appearance and their body, not just for men who aren't worthy of it, but also for women who
pressure them to do it, even though they don't give a shit, they're doing it out of boredom it.
And it, it does all this just kind of matter of factly, but it really works. It works really,
really well. Um, there's also all these, frankly, very arousing shots of the step -sister's body.
There, there's a closeup zoom of like her big juicy dump truck ass sitting down. And you're
like, God, what a great ass. There's this closeup of her chest. And you're like, man, she's this
girl.
Smoking. And there's a reason for that. It's like, look how good this woman looks. Who's
about to completely destroy what God has given her. Uh, very, very smart. And it really worked
for me. Yeah. I looked up the, uh, the, the, the young woman who stars in it. Her name is Leah
Myron or Mirren. Um, um, uh, she looks like she's been acting since she was a kid. She's only 24,
but, uh, but you know,
her Instagram feed is very artsy. Yeah. Uh, she looks like a very interesting person. Uh, I'm
going to follow her and I don't know. I want to see what else she does. Cause she's a really
amazing actor. Like Jesus got into those DMS. What do you got to lose? Well, probably the
language barrier would be the first issue. Um, she might speak English. You never know.
Uh, when I look, I laughed out loud at the end of this movie, it's like the, um, the mom's blowing
this rando and like,
nothing's worked out and it's very disturbing. And then in giant pink letters, it says
sloot S L U T T. And I started laughing. I thought it was a judgment from the director.
And then it says translated the end slot over there means the end. I was like, Oh, okay. All
right. Fine. Oh, there you go. Yeah. Yeah. She's been acting since 2009. So what's the math on that?
God almighty. My math 15 years ago, 16 years ago. So yeah, she's been acting since she was a kid.
Yeah. Um,
yeah. You know, so anyway, um, the ugly stepsister, I will be watching, uh, intently to see what comes
next from this team. Uh, uh, particularly the director, uh, again, Emily Blick felt, uh, who
doesn't have the Wikipedia page. So, um, but you know, yeah, she will, you know, if anyone's smart
in this business,
and you know, obviously there aren't many, but somebody will, will do exactly what happened with
the substance lady. See her first movie go, Holy shit. This woman has a, is a huge talent. Let's
give her a bigger budget, some American stars. That's probably the route she'll go or she'll
keep making movies in her homeland. I mean, there's, there's one of two paths to take basically,
but, um, I don't see how this woman doesn't have a very big career because it's just a
beautiful looking movie, a beautifully written movie and a,
a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a, a,
air to the body horror of, of like Cronenberg, the master. It really feels like that. The stuff
is especially that the eye stuff where they're threading those eyelashes and I stuff bugs me,
but you're reminded of clockwork orange, but it goes its own way with it. And it looks so real
that you're just like, Oh God. Um, loved it. Love the movie. I loved it too. I look forward
to Emily's next film, which I'm sure will be, uh, you know,
Deadpool spinoff. Yeah. Oh, they'll bring her over here. James Gunn has selected, uh, his,
his followup for the Superman sequel director. Yeah. Something like, um, all right, folks,
we'll be back next episode, 24 years later. Um, and that's it. Uh, check me out. Jota Rosa comedy
on Instagram, Jota Rosa comedian on Tik TOK again at Jota Rosa comedy on YouTube. Please go
like, and subscribe to the new channel I have there. Uh, you can link to disruptor comedy .com
through that page to see my new special early access for a few bucks. Uh, or you can just go
to disruptor of comedy .com and do it there. Uh, the special will be available to all of you
on YouTube on July 21st, but if you want to see it unedited, uh, you know, no ads early,
whatever, go over to disruptor. Um, and then I'm on tour, uh, comedy connection and, uh,
Denver, Colorado, uh, well, comedy connection in Rhode Island, excuse me. And then comedy works
in Denver, Colorado, uh, coming up in August. And then a bunch of other dates after that in
September and forward, go to Jota Rosa .com for details. Uh, I am at the Patrick Walsh on
Instagram. I did my buddy Bridger's podcast. Uh, I said, no gifts. You can see me there.
We are on Instagram at see you in hell pod.
And that's what I got. Thank you all very much. Our next episode will be 28 years later.
We will see you next time and we will see you in hell.