Summer is here and Bet MGM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer or check out our
exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz, only available at Bet MGM
Casino.
Spin on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only, games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as non -mustrable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another, no other sportsbook has
an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning, or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Monthly 21 Plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberler, offer not available in all states
terms apply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
Hello everybody. I am Patrick Walsh. I'm here with my dear sweet friend, Joe Derosa. We're very happy to announce the triumphant return of
we'll see you in hell. It's podcast discussing in general a horror sci -fi fantasy title each week, but usually
appearing into a bunch of side conversations.
Anyway, yeah, enough out of me, I guess.
Because we just sort of get on with the show
and in the meantime, on, who is the Jewel?
Paddy, what's up, Joe?
Well, that's me, it's good to see you.
It's great to see.
I'm going to upgrade it. Great to see you. Pat, been a month and a half.
I'll upgrade it. It's fantastic to see you.
All right. I love that we're seeing each other right now. I love that we're back in the
living room where it all began. Yes. I was back on, I was out on a month -long tour and
I can't tell you that I didn't meet a bunch of nice, we'll see you in health fans out there
on the road. And the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the, the elation. When I told,
I, particularly this one kid I met in Philly, his name's escaping me. He's, him and a bunch
of his friends were fans of the show and they came out to my show. And the elation when
I, when he goes, you know, man, I really hope that the podcast isn't done forever and whatever.
And it was like right after we, uh, we're talking about how we were going to do new episodes.
I said, Oh, no, man, it's coming back real soon. I mean, the kid was just thrilled. Yeah.
Well, you know, I think the reason a lot of people because I saw a lot of, you know, the tweets the Facebooks
People concerned that we were gone for good. It was a long time and to be honest, folks
Joe and I did consider stepping away from the spotlight
Jay Z style, but then Jay Z style we had to come back right out of retirement
Directly out of retirement a month later hell froze over the Eagles
me and Joe
And full transparency. It is quite a busy time for both Patrick and myself with various projects
and stuff. So we probably are going to go to a mainly two episode per month release schedule
for at least a little while. But we will get you at least that much for now and we'll try to
get you more. And, you know, the, the, the, the, the, I was called it the
Hyperion. What the hell was that thing called? The Patreon. The Patreon thing is not
off the table. Maybe we can figure out a way at some point to offer extra
episodes through that or something. It's not, it's not off the table at all. We
basically jumped ahead gum looking to kind of monetize this thing because it
does take up. What me and Joe were discussing is the only times we really get to
see each other and hang out, fall under the guise of a requirement because we
have to do the podcast, right. So of course, two friends should be excited
to each other, but there's like a duty about it. It's like, it's almost a
chore. And Joe and I weren't spending any time outside of the podcast.
It was a bummer. So we're just trying to space it out, give ourselves a little
more time and be fresher and better when we come back to you because some weeks
we don't have anything to say. And it does get a little complicated when you
think, you know, here in the podcast, we're peers, but on the set of Pat
Walsh's new TV show, I'm an on Janu and I'm, you know, I'm probably gonna get a little
lippy on set.
That's right.
How dare you get out of my shot.
I want to do another take, god damn it, you know, things like that.
Right.
And then we come in here and then we just have to be regular peers again.
And it doesn't.
It's true.
I mean, we'll see how the set relationship's gonna go.
It could be like Bert Reynolds on the set of evening shade.
you know, barking orders at everyone.
I'll tell you how it's going to go.
And that was an insane pronunciation of rentals.
You said rentals.
I'll tell you it's going to go.
It is going to go deloise rentals all the way, babe.
We're going to have a great time out there together.
Yeah, that's right.
And baking of deloise, well, I'll get to it.
But I finally saw your precious fatso, which we can discuss.
I had never seen it.
Well, we'll get to it because there's a few things to discuss.
us, and look, today's film is War for the Planet of the Apes.
War.
What's with your pronunciation today?
Is that, was that crazy?
You said war.
War?
Yeah.
Say you say war.
War.
There, there you go.
You're back on.
I am, sometimes the Missouri comes out.
Yeah.
I'm pretty like the hydrated I gave blood
and I'm nursing a whiskey.
It's going right to my head.
Yeah, me, mine too.
All I ate today was salad and some nuts.
Yeah.
So this is I was trying to go on our only beer and wine regimen, right?
Okay. I can't do it. The goddamn beer. It makes me feel tired.
Yeah, it's acidic. It's I'm a whiskey guy. I don't know what to tell you.
Yeah, I mean that beer just you feel you feel it on your face. You feel it. You feel like it's hanging off.
It makes you want to go to sleep. Yeah, it's not. I was watching a
Wrestling Pay Per View last night with my dear, our dear friend, excuse me, Vince A.
We had a great time at events and I saw Roger Waters. He told me I heard it was a
Elvis show and he gave me his assessment on what the best song of the new album is
and it's the song I the name just the title of songs escaped me but it's the
song where he goes picture a leader with no fucking brains yeah which I like that
song but I feel like that line is a little too on the nose well they had a pig
flying around with Trump's face on it, and then a lot of like Trump with a Hitler
mustache and stuff. So me and Vince turned to each other and we're like, look,
obviously, LA, this is going fine, but how does this show play around the globe?
And sure enough, Vince sent me an article where people were furious about this
Trump bashing, but the first song on the new Roger water out, water's album is like,
fuck your president Donald Trump. It's like the first thing it's called wake up and
and smell the roses or something.
Wake up, you American idiots.
Your president is a fascist pig.
And you're like, what?
Rock doesn't like Donald?
I was watching a re -run of Night Flight last night.
Right.
I was the guy who made the wall,
like Donald Trump as an authority figure.
Why would he?
How could he?
No, I know.
Well, that's surprising to me.
You have to be the Floyd fan and love Donald Trump.
I'm sorry.
That's surprising to me that people are going into this concert
in their shocks that brought your waters doesn't like that we got
the food off the stage in Tennessee or so. I was watching a re -run of night
flight last night on the night flight app which does not sponsor us but it's a
great app for you horror fans out there and sci -fi fans and cult fans cult movie
not the band but they were it was it was I clicked on it because the the thumbnail
was the was a was a screenshot from Hulk Hogan's I'm a real American video
which I remember as a kid really liking.
So I clicked on it and the theme of the episode
was all patriotism, all right.
So it was anything that had to do with patriotism
in the United States.
So it started with like some real pro -America shit
and then they're like, here's an anti -American video
from Billy Bragg that he performs for the Russians
and like, they're not knocking it.
He just sings this song called like,
and it's literally like the youth of America
I'm gonna rot now
Like what we were much and we seem like we had a much more open mind to to an exchange of ideas back there
Yeah, I don't know enough about the Billy Bragg punk where I only know his work with Wilco
Which is what did he do with them Billy Bragg and Wilco set to music?
Fuck the poetry of some fucking poet good what no or Woody Guthrie or let me look it up
But you don't you don't care Joe, but they're beautiful songs and the lyrics are great because they're written by this great Billy Bragg
Who I don't dislike
But I wouldn't say I'm a fan. I'm sort of indifferent about music, but he always is
He always fell into the category of the Pogs and like Marcy with me where I'm like, oh, you mean awesome
well you mean unbelievably awesome I'm like I think it's cool but I would
I don't think I'd ever buy a record you know sure all right I look more like it
I love Morrissey and the pokes just on record did you like that last Marcy
album with him with his dog in front of the graffiti wall in the cover it looked
like literally they didn't even look like it I look like a flip -flown
phone camera took that picture no I like Morrissey I saw him I saw him live many
times he's great well it was Woody Guthrie Woody Guthrie had written these
Lear X without music and they set them to music. All right, they're cool. You know, I'm not a Woody Guthrie fan either
But I like couldn't tell you what he got three songs. He's one of those guys like you know
He's like Hank Williams where I'm like, yeah, he's I'm supposed to respect him, right? Well, Hank Williams is the shit
Woody Guthrie was just always like to me a little on the nose Frank
You know, and I think I realized there are my two favorite songs of all time this
This week this last week, huh? Hips don't lie Shakira
In my close, I'd say you're bordering on warm.
Okay.
My other guess is all fired up by Best Pat Benetar.
No.
You heard that song?
That's why it's not on your number two.
No, I have not heard that song.
All right.
I love Heartbreaker by Pat Benetar.
Heartbreaker is obviously the bigger hit, but all fired up is a better song.
Maybe because it hasn't been overplayed.
But seek it out.
You were closer with hips. What was it? Hips don't lie. I was curious traveling Willberes hard to handle
Yeah, well not hard to handle or handle me with handle handle with care, right and
End of the line which is the first and last song on traveling Willberes volume one
I've listened those songs forever. I've loved those songs forever
I was listening them this week and I was playing them multiple times in a row and I was like they're both are these my two favorite songs of all time
I think they might be they're both really great song. I know those both
Harrison joints
Uh, I don't know. I think Hannah with care was everybody and the line might have been Harrison, but um
bought me an Orbison the best voice in the game. Orbison Petty's getting a lot of shine on those songs
Uh, you're your boy for me. I'll know Jeff Landbaby coming in with those fucking
Ashton Kutcher aviator sunglasses and just you know
Oh, now have you heard the Jenny Lewis M. Ward Ben Gibbard cover of that song?
No.
It's really great.
Well, all right.
I want Jenny Lewis to solo album, which is awesome.
I was going to say I didn't want to hear it because I think the song is perfection, but
I'll give it a chance.
You know, it's a great little indie rock cover of it.
I'll win the guy from my morning jacket as the fourth guy.
All right.
He's the Dylan.
I'll give it a shot.
But I bought a, the pop merch website that you've,
it's Physiasticity.
Yeah, well, somebody else who ain't giving us anything.
Well, you know, look, I went to the website,
I got some, I got some good deals on some albums.
Yeah.
I don't know why I bought this album.
And, you know what, I'm not trying to go out
on my way to shit on these guys,
but I got this rival Sun's vinyl.
Show, can I tell you?
I got a two because it was so cheap.
Yeah.
And because of their affiliation with like,
Queens of Stone Age, they opened for them.
I was like, maybe they're great.
Haven't listened to it yet,
because I don't think it's gonna be great.
It just sounds like the black keys.
Yeah, it sounds so, so do I,
but it sounds so much like the black keys.
I was like, this is the guy from the black keys, right?
And then when I saw it wasn't, I was like,
well, now I don't like this at all
because it just sounds like a guy copied the black keys.
Sure. Maybe I'm wrong.
Maybe they were around first.
I don't know.
I don't think they were though,
but it was so cheap.
And they're, which is very weird as they are
And some of you hardcore horror freaks out there
who are in the metal will realize how weird this is.
They're on earache records.
And earache records is an independent label
that puts out hardcore and like metal
and like industrial music.
And this is like the like blues rocky,
like you know, background female chorus singing
and you know, it just doesn't make any sense.
So so that's over there in my trade into amoeba pile. Yeah, I got one of those two
We got to go we got to go. I'm sure back in town. You're ready to head up. Listen, you think I'm not ready
I got a bag full of shitty DVDs. I'll go you think I won't go
We have a little dinner and a pop and holly wouldn't go to amoeba. Well, here's what we could do that
We uber over or of course folks. Okay, we go to that Italian place next to amoeba. We get dinner
Sure and a few drinks we go into amoeba. I thought I'd just said this but you're going well
Yeah, I'm just telling you how we do it, right? This is how we do it
Then we go to a meeting a little a little lit up where our money isn't even an option at that point
Uh, and then a or money an object. Excuse me. I said it wrong money is no option
And then we come back here and maybe we hit a bar on the way home. It sounds great. It sounds great. I love it
All right, let's talk about fatso. You don't yep, but real quick. Oh, sorry
And my name is Patrick. Thank you very much
Thank you, thanks folks, I wanted to say, because I'll forget it if I don't do it now, I essentially
am on the co -monitor of the Facebook page, Joe's not on Facebook, but I'm going to
log in with Joe one day and let him read all this shit because I die laughing every time
I go in there, I love all that you guys do and of course I love when you guys discuss
your favorite horror movies and shit like that, the best thing that you can do in terms of
making me and Joe laugh because I text these all to Joe immediately, is when you write
down like a court transcript or some section from one of the podcasts that like Joe and
I probably don't even remember saying, but they made me laugh very, very hard.
It's like this is very narcissistic, but it's like getting to, you know, see something you
wrote that you didn't remember writing.
So of course you're a fan of it because it's something you said.
I do.
I mean I read him and I'm like, oh yeah, it's like a nice little walk down memory lane. I find them hilarious as well
I have noticed a pattern where it's usually you besting me in some way. Those are the ones I like the best
Well, I've noticed that. The only ones he's ever sent me people are ones where he wins the thing at the end
Well, you would argue there's not many
Of the alternatives
I dumbed starting to think there's not but that's okay. No, though. I just I find them all very funny
So if you if you hear a particularly enjoyable passage, send it along. I met a lady in Atlanta once after a show
Where she sent Atlanta hot Atlanta. I did well. It's where the players play and yeah big boy had me over to his place
And took a few spins around that spinner that stripper pull and I know why we're going so music heavy this episode
But I gotta tell you folks
big boys first solo album Sir Lucius Dusty
for me a top five hip -hop album of all time I haven't heard it I think he is
criminally underrated it's got some bangers on there the best being back up
plan which should have been one of the biggest rap singles of all time was
not released as a single to my knowledge and they sleep on them because they all
think under a three thousand the genius because he wears colorful pants well I'm
here to tell you folks big boys got just as much talent as under two thousand he's
not as weird he's a little more traditional but he's also a lot more eclectic
unusual than you might think I love I love big boy I've been listening a
little bit to the new album I gotta give it a few more spins I just bought it
haven't listened but but but it is very good the but anyway I was in hot
lander and sometimes I'll call fat lander with a pH at the top yeah but
but a woman was there.
This is -
No, I'll call it fat landtas
with the SS at the end.
Fat landtas.
Oh, one was at the show as a fan of the podcast.
Yeah.
This goes back to where we're just talking about
about you besting me.
Right.
But she was like, I really like you,
but I love Pat.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I love Pat, and it got to a point where I was like,
it's okay, you're allowed to like Pat better.
I don't care.
It's like what what am I the the thinnest most vain person on planet earth?
You like it's fine cut to someone telling me they prefer Joe and me not speaking for six hours
Yeah, because I'm so good to you take their glass out of their hand and throw it against the wall in the floor splash
Another face all right
Yeah, so let's dive into Pat's movie corner, which is a fancy name for just saying we
list the movies we've seen, but actually now that I'm kind of making my own hours and
everything, I'm gotten into a schedule and I'm watching more movies.
I'll say right off the jump
That's so because Joe has mentioned it 30 times on here. It's one of your top three movies if I recall it
It's it's the number 10 tied with Malcolm X or my top 10 movies of all time
Now do you think and this is this is not a because I enjoy the movie very much. It's just a question. I'm always fascinated by
Home alone is always gonna be one of my favorite movies. Yes, but a big part of that
I know is because I was Kevin McCallister's age and I saw when I was nine years old. Yes
But even even now I can't separate like if I saw for the first time now what I love it as much probably not but I don't know sure
It's hard to say
Do you think your love of fatso because I would call it a
If you'll forgive me
Very well -made, but not not exceptional movie. Do you think you saw it in an impressionable age?
Do you know someone showed it to you that was important to you or no none of those things happened
And I saw it on a whim because I got on a Dom Del Louise kick and I rented it.
And I was like, well, this is one of the only movies I can find that stars Dom Del Louise.
It's not, he's not second -fiddled to anybody.
This is his movie.
And I thought it was not interesting that Anne Bancroft wrote and directed it.
Started Mel Brooks' production company.
Yeah.
Sweet as that.
It starts a production company to fund his wife's first movie.
So I watched it and I fell in love with it.
the only impressionable aspect of it for me,
I would say, was that it hit close to home.
My mom has struggled with weight issues.
So I found his struggle very relatable.
I found what he was saying about his food,
tendencies, and all these things, very, very relatable.
And then also you've never really seen a movie
about it before or since.
No, and also to the dynamic, the way they portrayed
the dynamic of the Italian American family from that era. I also found extremely relatable.
And I have not found it was, it is, if I really thought about it, I might be able to think
of another example, but it might be the only depiction I've ever seen on film where I'm
like, that is accurate. Yeah. This isn't, this isn't cartoonish. This isn't analyze this,
where there are hints of like, oh, that's how Italian people, I know how that goes. Right.
That was a very, very, the loud, like every,
down to Anne Bancroff when he goes,
when he goes, when they're dancing
and he gets out of breath and he goes,
and how upset she gets, and then he goes,
I'm tired, and she goes, you got damn tired.
Like every, it was so precisely crafted,
and I was like, this is my family, I get this.
Yeah, so I loved it, and then I noticed,
as I started to mention it to friends of mine
and who were also movie buffs, like Robert Kelly
and my friend Chip Jambrone.
They were also like, oh, I've seen it, it's great.
And I was like, holy shit, man.
Okay, so I'm not imagining this.
So I just love the film.
And I think it's an Oscar worthy performance
at a Dom Deloise.
The guy's on the verge of tears in almost every scene
over pizza.
He's describing like how sick he is with himself
for eating a large pizza.
He's weeping.
I've never seen Deloise
better. I've never really, I mean, I've always thought he was a funny guy, but he was,
he was really awesome in it. Tina Fey's favorite movie, by the way. Really? I know that because
Max Brooks, who's Mel Brooks and Anne Bancroff's son, who wrote World War Z, is a, is a power of mine
from back in the day. Okay. And he told me when he worked at SNL, he said Tina Fey was her, she was like,
like, oh my god, your mom made Fato,
it's like my favorite movie.
Oh, very interesting.
And I've seen echoes of that
and some of the Tina Fey stuff.
Like, there's stuff that she creates.
It's funny and it gets zany at times,
but it's very like, it's very true.
Like, you're like, I can relate to that, you know?
Yeah, I mean, another movie similar,
but Fato was about weight
and then a relationship was a separate thing.
I think the best movie ever made about like weight
and relationships, how it affects relationships,
is enough said with Gandalfeney.
I love that movie.
And Charlie Price.
Both of them, about as good as they've ever been,
if you've never saw enough said,
I urge you to check it out.
And then the fact that it cried, it's an amazing movie.
The fact that it came out after he died,
it like compounds the...
That's why I was crying, I think.
It's a beautiful movie.
There's another movie that a dear friend of mine
starred in, and it's called Pounds,
and that's spelled LBS Period.
And it's about a guy that it's almost like an into the it's a comedy, but it's a
drama, but it's almost like an end of the wild. It's about a guy that gets a
camper and he's tired of being fat and he goes up with this like mobile, the
shitty mobile and lives in the woods so he can like lose the way finally. And the guy
goes through the fucking weight transformation in the goddamn movie. Okay, that's
cool. It's it's my buddy Carmine stars in it. I think I wrote a if it were a sketch
the funnier way to go would be that he emerges from the woods and his
fatter. Yeah, it's been like gorging on animals and things. And then the
far stranger comes in play by Bruno Kirby and he goes, where the hell did
all the trees go? There you go. Potman, pot, beaver.
I might that might be a movie. Bruno Kirby's dad. He's dead, but we could find a
Kirby.
David Crumholz would be a good Bruno Kirby. He's an heir. Yes, an heir apparent to Bruno.
I was about to pitch him a show and he passed away called Bruno Kirby your enthusiasm.
Excited that it's coming back by the way. Could be more excited. My lovely girlfriend and I are
working through it. She had never seen it. Oh my god. Oh, I mean what a treasure trove. I truly don't
I don't take this for creepier than what I'm saying,
but I get why, like when you have a kid,
it's so exciting to show them a movie,
but I feel the same way with what I'm dating some.
I mean, when she said she hadn't seen it,
I was like, this is gonna be fucking incredible.
So, I get to see it again and see ones
that kind of fell through the cracks for me.
The huge vagina episode with the phone
and the vagina at the end.
It's incredible.
Garland, there's just been some amazing, amazing shit,
and I can't wait for the new season.
Garland's delivery no, not true at all huge for Jeff
Yeah, it's an it's yeah, it's an impeccable show. I really love it
It is and I have read from several people that the new season they're like
The like some of the actors were like I don't know if I want to participate in this like everyone's like
It's really really rough
Uncontrollable stuff and the particular they were talking to steam Virgin and she goes
She was, I'm not exaggerating when I say that like me and Ted had to really kind of give
Larry a couple weeks before we got back to him when we read the arc like we just did
not know if we were gonna be like this kind of, so her saying that I was like either it's
like really you know it's like about 9 -11 or something but when she said that I thought to
myself maybe it's some sort of thing where like Ted fucks Mary I did because of how
conflicted they were as a couple sure you know and that's not a spoiler because I'm guessing but
That would be nuts and just like how Larry and Cheryl divorce which threw me for a fuck. Oh you mean Ted fuck Cheryl
Mary's his wife already. I meant Larry fucks Mary Larry fucks me or Ted fuck Cheryl
Okay, yeah, that's the first thing I put in my head was like some sort of a swing or scenario. Yeah
Well, I mean in the last I bet he's got to do something with Trump
I mean the man's is liberal as they come yeah
Yeah, I would believe something in there about Trump is coming.
I wouldn't be surprised if we saw Bernie Sanders cameo in the season.
Yeah, that's true.
That's true.
But I'm very excited for it.
I love that he pushes the envelope and I love the show.
And as my cousin Kevin said the other day to me,
it's perfect.
Excine felt except they say fuck.
And I was like, yeah, that's as good as it can get for me.
That's exactly right.
On television.
right anyway patty uh... movie corner you know what i don't have much for
this i will say that i did see
uh...
i did see pirates of the care peon
it sucked but my parents loved it
and i did think it was a fitting and to the to the
to the series
i was blown away to see it was under two hours i mean that's at least something
they ended it properly they tied up the
Well, they weren't loose ends, but they ended everybody's storyline properly and then of course they do a post -credits scene
You're like don't do another one. Yeah, and it but it wasn't great
Well, it was like somebody walks the plank and then they float back up to the plank like oh
No, no, do you want me to tell you? No, I don't care. It doesn't matter
I'm gonna be plank action. There was no plank action
There was a very it was a very funny old school and there you get this is sort of a spoiler
There was a funny old school like comedy scene like almost like a WC field thing
We're Johnny Depp like to get out of being killed
Like the people that have captured them are like fine. We won't kill you
You have to marry my sister then and it's the sisters like obviously
Disgusting with like jagged brown teeth and he's like
Shoot me shoot me, you know, so I thought that was funny
In a suit of all like perfect strangers
Yeah, it was a very old school like sort of Abbot and Castello kind of gag, right, but it put it made me laugh
But yeah, the movie wasn't great. I was flying home the other day from Austin, Texas and I was terribly excited
that the flight I was on
Had free movies and the free movie that I was most excited about was T2 train spotting. I'm dying to see it. I'm dying to see it
I watched about half of it, granted it was very early in the morning.
I was very tired and I tried to power through because I really just wanted to see it.
And I watched half, I turned it off.
I am curious to see the second half, I'm not dying to see the second half.
I just over so far my impression was these stakes just aren't as interesting to me.
Right, the first movie is about guys that are stuck on heroin and
What's gonna happen? How are they gonna get off? Are they gonna get off? Whatever. Yeah
Then you have this movie
Pretty much they're not on heroin anymore and it's way more about like okay, what sort of petty crimes do they have to resort to
in order to stay afloat and
And it also starts with everybody being and this isn't really a spoiler
Everybody's hugely fucking mad at Renton, you know, you want me to Gregor, because he shows up for the first time in 20 years, and they're like, you stole all our fucking money.
Right.
So there's that part.
But I will say this, everybody's performance is great in it. Robert Carlisle particularly slides.
I was worried, I was like, after he did 18 seasons of Wish Upon a Star, whatever that fucking show was called, where he's playing like a sort of nice,
Rumpel Stiltskin, what are you talking about?
Once upon a time, is that what it's called?
The story book show?
On Oleg on ABC?
Yeah, okay.
He plays Rumpel Stiltskin on that.
I honestly thought like you had started hallucinating.
He plays Rumpel Stiltskin on that, but he's like.
We should upon a star starring Robert Carlisle.
But he's sort of a nice, he's like a,
sort of a conflicted guy.
He plays Rumpel Stiltskin?
Yeah, and he's like kind of a prick,
but he's kind of nice and sweet.
And I was like, he can't.
And then he also did that great,
There was that make that great movie called Go Now where he plays the guy that gets MS love go now and I love the fucking full
Monty while we're at it right so I was like he's not going to be able to slide back into this into this big B
Character who slides right back in his opening scene is him with his lawyer while he's in prison and I mean
He's just screaming at the lawyer through a through a Scottish action so thick. There should be subtitles
Yeah, I went across that with subtitles and the lawyer gets scared and goes to press like the panic button. Yeah, and he goes
So you want to press that button you're fucking
And then jumps up and slams his lawyers face into the table and then freeze frames. So I was like all right
You know, I'm in that sounds good. So I
Want to see the rest of it, but I was a little underwhelmed so far
Alright, well we'll cut it, we'll cut it short and our next movie corner we will
discuss baby driver which I saw did you see it, haven't seen it, don't really
have an interest in seeing it and we will discuss the big sick see it, didn't see
it, maybe you see a movie starring and directed by a close friend, two close
friends. I know everybody involved in the film. Yeah.
Ronald or dear friend. He's checking out supporting actor in it. I just haven't I haven't
checked out anything. I haven't been to the theater. But I would like to see the film
here being fun. Well, that was what my mom, I don't think my mom had to see the big sick.
It would have been a perfect move to take your pants. Really? Yeah. Oh, okay. It's like
it's a very tame R or you know. Well, I didn't know if it would be their kind of humor,
though. No, it's it's a well I mean we could get into it but I mean it's a well I don't
know I've been seen it. It's an extremely well -written lovely romantic comedy and it's
very funny. And then after the movie they're styling him. And then after the movie I have to
hear my mom say well why don't you have a movie for for for the next hour. I don't need that in my
life. Wouldn't she do that anyway though? Yeah you know so anyway you should see it while you're
back when we can get into it more next time, but obviously it's a great film and I want
to give them a plug.
How often do you get to plug something great by people you know and love?
Lug it away and I do want to see the film, I just haven't seen it yet, all right.
Let's get into our movie of the day of the episode war, war, for the planet of the
for the planet of the apes.
Quick synopsis.
Yeah, I, this one at least gave you
a little bit of a previously on.
Yeah, but as much as I liked Rise and Love Dawn,
although I don't know why Dawn doesn't come before Rise
as somebody in my Ryder's room pointed out the other night,
you gotta get Dawn before the Rise.
It's a good playing.
Got a point.
I love them and then kind of just immediately forgot them.
So I was still pretty in the dark during this one.
I followed it, and I liked it.
I don't think we're gonna be as different as you might have
thought we would be on more of the planet of the apes.
But my grievances with these kind of movies are a length.
We're talking about 225.
All apes, there's like three humans in it, 225.
So all that time is apes talking to each other.
Two hours and 25 minutes.
Barely talking to each other.
There's a lot of sign language.
It's a lot of subtitles.
give a quick quick quick synopsis though before we get into it because I'll
I'll boss something excuse me it takes place 15 years after rise of the
planet of the apes which by the way people was surprising to me because I'm so
dumb that I thought apes lived for like 200 years so I thought these movies were
taking place like hundreds of years after rise of the planets and it's like no
no it's like it that just happened you thought apes lived for hundreds of years
I thought they lived for like 150 years or something like that.
So like, wow.
Because I didn't get it.
I was like, how was everything gone to shit
this hard since Rise?
It's like, if you ever watch Mad Max
and you watch the road warrior,
you're like, it went this bad in a year?
Come on.
So anyway, it takes place 15 years after Rise,
a few years after Dawn.
And it's just basically about,
Now, here's what I thought it was about, the final battle for man and ape.
That's what the trailer says, I think, exactly.
Yes.
And it's not really about that.
It's about one of the final confrontations between man and ape, and this is, and that's
basically the plot of the movie.
And it's also a subplot is them trying to find their new home on a sort of a beach, a
territory geographical territory that's like a beach near the sea and some, which when
they first say that at the top, I was very excited because I go, oh my god, they're going
to where they live in the original Charlton, Heston, plan of they live in, like, on a beach.
That's like where the fucking forbidden zone and all that shit is.
That's what we're looking for.
Yeah, so I was very excited about that, but as the movie unfolded, it started to kind
of, I really like the film, but it bothered me that it was yet another like dawn movie
where apes were battling humans in a sort of dystopian rundown army base or whatever facility
in the snow surrounded by the forest and what I was like,
I would have much preferred as they go to the new place
where they're gonna live at the top of the film
and then it's them defending the new home.
Something bad, but then they also say in the movie,
this is not the final stand.
There are pockets of humans still around the world,
but what you would think like to give,
you know, to make some like political,
comparisons and shit. It's kind of a great story. They get their own beautiful
paradise island and the white man comes and wants to take it for himself and then
the aves fight them off. You know you get in some Native American stuff, some
Columbus stuff. You know you make some nice little parallels. Here's the other
thing that bugged me. Not that Native Americans are apes. I hope that was clear.
but the Apes would be representing.
Well, no, look, there's definitely a social
and racial commentary in these films,
without question.
But like, here's the thing,
does it have anything to bother me a little bit?
So this movie takes place in, essentially, 2017.
It's present day.
Caesar has his son.
Thought Caesar was Willem Defoe.
Looks exactly like Willem Defoe.
I know it's circus.
You thought it was Willem Defoe?
His face looks exactly like Willem Dafoe. Like I feel like they based it on Willem Dafoe.
It's because they do the ping pong balls on circus.
Speaking of Willem Dafoe, that death note show looks terrible.
What's death note?
That Netflix show that's coming out where he plays like some kind of banshee demon or something.
Oh, I'm not sure.
And he's like, just write the guy's name in this book and he'll die.
It doesn't look good.
You see a demon?
Yeah, but it looks really fake. It looks super like CGI.
And I was excited and the more I kept seeing about it. I was like, yeah, this doesn't look that great. I might be wrong
It might be great. Anyway, Steve's on is that other a Steve's on kind of steals the film Steve's on was great
But this what bug me Caesar who is the log giver as you know and in the original plan of the apes films
He's the one that sets the stipulations and laws for for ape society
He has a son in this movie and his son's name is Cornelius
And I was like, well, that's weird because Cornelius is the ape played by Roddy McDowell
in the original films who helps Charlton Heston.
He's not Caesar's son.
So here's where it starts getting confusing.
This is the first moment in this trilogy where I'm like, wait a minute, these aren't prequels.
They're just sort of doing like a new interpretation of this mythology.
I didn't know that.
I thought too.
I thought they were just prequels.
So this is where it starts to get confused.
The mute little girl that they find in the film,
her name is Nova.
Nova is the mute woman in the original planet of the apes
that Charlton has in falls in love with.
So the apes like Nova in this movie.
So I'm sitting there the whole time going,
why is Nova, wait a minute,
how does Nova go to be becoming imprisoned by the apes?
Like what the hell is going on here?
The Caesar not how does could it just be a little homage like do you think they
necessarily need to be the same people it isn't homage but that is a very
confusing homage if you made us if you said we're gonna make a a series of
Star Wars movies that are inspired by the original films but they're not
directly connected to them in any way and then you have a little kid and the
little kid goes my name is Luke Skywalker you're gonna be like well that's
Confusing I don't like like don't you don't you know, all right that makes sense
So so those aspects of the film bug me a little bit and and
I'm the type of person that likes to point out negatives before positives that all being said
Thought it was a very very well done movie. I thought it was extremely
Yeah, I mean for the love of the facts. I mean uh
Did the jungle book win best special effects? I don't know
I thought it was painfully boring.
I mean, maybe it was seeing it at the theater or something,
but I just saw all the animals were really awesome.
And in this one, even the first pan across like the ape camp,
I kind of noticed in the effects.
You know, when everything in a shot is a special effect,
everything's not gonna be 100 % perfect.
And I just kind of started,
I don't know, it was taking me out of it a little bit.
I didn't notice the effect.
The person was not up to snuff.
You know, he just seemed kind of checked out.
I don't agree with that at all.
I thought he was fantastic in it.
In fact, while we were leaving the theater, my mom said,
that Woody Harrell, he's a hell of an actor.
She didn't get his name right, but I agree with her.
I was like, I know.
I go, he was a real son of a bitch in that movie.
And she was like, you know, you'll watch him on chairs.
He's the most lovable sort of a loof guy.
And you're like, yeah, he's a really good actor.
I thought he was really good in it.
And I didn't think after seeing him in movies like Kingpin,
and I was going to be able to buy him as a general
and as a bastard one of that,
but I really liked him in it.
I really, really liked him in it.
I tend to like him in lighter things, I guess, you know.
Well, who does it?
Yeah, I just, he just didn't really bring a lot of pizzazz
to it for me.
There was a very kind of depressing tone
to a movie called War of the Planet of the Ages, you know?
Well, the title is very somber.
The title is misleading, war for the planet of the apes.
It's not a war for the planet of the apes.
That makes the assumption that the apes now have taken power and the humans need to take
the planet back.
That's not what it is.
It should be war of the planet of the apes, but it's not.
I know that's a big nitpicking, but as your friend said in the room, dawn versus rise.
I mean, you know, these things are a little misleading.
James Rolf, who I don't know at all,
but I'm a fan of, he plays the Angry Video Game Nerd
on YouTube.
His website, Cinemassacre, where they do a lot of movie
reviews and things, he did a review of the movie,
and he said that he thought the movie,
he said the tone of the film, he goes,
He was, he liked it very much.
And he said, you might go and expect an action movie.
And he goes, it's not really an action movie.
He goes, the best way to describe this
is if Jesus Christ was an ape
and then got dropped into a Nazi concentration camp.
And I was like, when I was watching, I was like, yeah,
that's, it does feel very shinlar's list, you know.
Like, it's dark, it's sad, it's sad.
And you're just, I saw with the buddy of mine
and he was like, I gotta tell you, man,
Like if I have to see one ape die, I'm gonna walk out of here.
I was like, I think you're gonna see a lot of apes.
But you see tons of apes die like up close,
like bullet to the head.
It's kind of weird.
You hear them squealing and yes, it's upsetting.
It's upsetting.
But it makes you care for the apes.
My mom was in goddamn tears at the end of the movie.
Right.
It does make you care for the apes.
It does make you hate the humans.
That is the one, not the one, but the most brilliant aspect
effect of this new trilogy is I think it is absolutely brilliant that the people behind
this trilogy said let's do planet of the apes in reverse. You know make it about the
apes where you're not rooting for the humans, you're rooting for the apes and you will get
to see how a benevolent race or species begins and then eventually at some point it goes
was wrong, which is, again, why was mad when I read? These aren't direct prequels. They're
just sort of inspired by the original philosophy. No, make the direct prequels. Like show
me how it happens. Maybe they will someday, Joe. I don't think they will. Maybe you should
pitch it a make it. You see, you see a hole, you should fill it. Hey, folks, let's stop talking
about my behavior at the end of the night and my favorite bar.
All right. And I'm not talking about Joe on Margarita Mondays.
Gang, we're so happy to be back.
Yes. And oh, we're quick. I have a, I have us Joe scary stuff.
Oh, yeah. Go ahead. We're real quick to close out with for the
Unintendo Switch folks out there. I got myself one of these damn things.
What it is God dammit. It's the new Nintendo. It is fucking great. It is it's amazing. I love it
It's the best travel companion I've ever had. Oh, it's a try. It's a portable
Well, it's a portable that is also an HDMI regular console
And it is the graphics are pretty much up to par with the current systems. It's it's a phenomenal
Phenomenal device if you can get your hands on one of these
I was lucky enough to find one at the Nintendo store in New York
They're hard to come by, but I can't recommend it highly enough. However, why does this relate to Joe scary stuff?
Here's why this week
July 28th
Coming out Namco classic I think it's called Namco classics or Namco arcade museum or something for the switch
Which does include the arcade port of splatter house, which as far as I know is the first ever horror video game
Like truly hard video. I know they were hard element haunted house on a tarry, you know, that's it
But this is the horror video again. This is the one that started it all
Where you play a
Hulking man in a hockey mask and you're running with a plank and
Splattering demons against a wall and whatever so I can't wait for this to come out. It comes out this week and
If you got a switch and you don't get this, I don't understand. It's that's just dumb. Anyway, we're happy to be back for my Joe
scary stuff, even though I'm not sure that this is what this segment is about.
Joe can tell me if it fits or not, a cameraman on the set of probably my
favorite horror movie, Poltergeist. Finally answered the question, did
Tobe Hooper or Steven Spielberg direct Poltergeist? It's credited as written by
Steven Spielberg directed by Tobe Hooper, but wide speculation was that
was stepping in and directing a lot of the scenes yes cinematographer said
basically Spielberg directed the entire movie in its entirety which blew me
away because it's so obviously not a Tobay Hooper movie Hooper movie and so
obviously a Steven Spielberg movie I wouldn't call it a Tobay Hooper movie I might
call it a Toby Hooper movie isn't he Tobay no Toby is it Marissa Tome who's
His name is Tobay.
That's not a name.
His name is spelled T -O -B -E.
I thought it was Tobay Hooper.
Tobay Hooper.
I thought, isn't that it?
Oh, I don't know that that's right.
I think it might be Tobay Hooper.
I mean, you can't really look that out.
Listeners, if you know, tweet us about it.
Look it up and if it's got that asterisk, like Beyonce,
I'm definitely right.
But by the way, that is not appropriate for scary stuff,
but I am glad you brought it up
because it was good to hear a final conclusive argument
on that and then he also said
that was no strike against Toby Hooper in saying that it was it had to do with the strike
that was happening and Spielberg couldn't direct it so they had to they basically said
Toby took like a kind of a bullet for Spielberg and put his name on it and just kind of function
as producer right so but hey fuck it man I'm sure the guy made a lot of cash from that flick
I would hope I honestly think Toby Hooper being around is probably what made it so horrific
like a PG Spielberg movie. Spielberg wouldn't have gone as dark.
I agree. I think it wound up all the scarier for him being on set, frankly.
I agree. So, you don't see a squiggle there, do you? Over the E?
I didn't see a squiggle. I wasn't going to mention it, but no, I didn't.
I didn't see a squiggle. You got any plugs?
I don't. I don't. Sorry.
All right. Next week, Kyle Kanane and myself co -headline,
the comedy, I think it's comedy train festival in Amsterdam. It's the only festival with me at
Coyote Linne in Amsterdam with the word train in it so find that. Come see us if you're over there.
It'll be a lot of fun and that's it I guess. Yeah come out to Amsterdam. Let's have a few drinks,
I think smoke some doobes, sure.
Doobie has a MD over here.
All right gang, we will see you,
I would imagine in two weeks,
but keep your eyes peeled.
Thank you for making us feel wanted
and we are excited to return.
That was a hate gun podcast.