And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say, I'll see you in hell, you know I will, I'll see you in hell, you know I will.
Folks, it's We'll See You In Hell, the podcast that talks about movies, movies, movies, and we're here today to review, how does it wear evil lurks or when evil lurks? I can't remember.
I have, I have called it a thousand titles in the last couple of weeks, all of them wrong. I've been saying when evil sleeps, where evil speaks, where evil lurks, when evil lurks, it's not, I assume where, because it's not a time thing.
Yes, it's a bad title. I don't like the title.
What was the name of the, also a Shudder, a Ridge, and also a movie that included extreme violence towards children? Was that called Speak No Evil, the Shudder one that we reviewed? I like that one.
That was called Speak No Evil, because they cut the kids tongues out.
There's See No Evil, there's Hear No Evil, I mean, these have all been movie titles.
There's Gene Wilder's Speak No Evil, Hear No Evil, which covers -
See No Evil, Hear No Evil, yes, exactly.
Um, or see, yeah, see, yeah.
Joe, what's new with you? It's 60 degrees here, so it's a real cold snap in Los Angeles this morning. I woke up feeling like I could, I threw some coal on the fire and I could see my breath.
Pat, to that I would say it's 30 degrees here, so go fuck yourself.
I like that. I miss that. I miss the cold.
I gotta, what's new? I've been home for Thanksgiving, I've been working on the house.
You know, it's, I got a bed coming today, the guest room will be pretty much ready to go by the end of today.
That's kind of all I've been doing. I spent the Thursday with my family. I went out Wednesday with some friends drinking.
And now, and I haven't done anything fun all weekend. I've just been sitting here
putting things together in the house, and then I go on the road next weekend, and I'm thankful to be going on the road, but goddamn, I get,
it's just a lot, man. The traveling, it's, the shows are great, meeting the fans is amazing. It's the traveling part that really, it gets me down.
Yeah.
So, uh, and I gotta go to, to, to three cities later this week, which -
Also getting me down lately is, uh,
the fact that the world is enveloped in complete darkness at 4 .30 p .m. every day.
That's happening. We've jumped into that zone, and now we're on the,
man, you talk about bittersweet every October, November, December. The holiday season is fun,
and can be exciting, and can, can bring a lot of joy for different reasons, but it's also a ticking doomsday clock
as each holiday passes
to, to, you know, that, that stroke of midnight on New Year's Eve might as well be, you know, the, the, the fucking clock and
watchmen going off or whatever. Like, it's like, because you know, you're like, here we go,
three months of dark cold,
and nothing to look forward to. Oh boy, it sucks.
And then I get this feeling
lately with any, whether it's the holidays or whether it's the new year, just any time a year has passed, my birthday,
it's all right around the same time. I'm a January 5th birthday,
and I feel as though I've done nothing since day one of the pandemic. It's not true.
I've actually done quite a bit in completed projects and work jobs and everything,
but I just have this underlying feeling that I'm wasting my life. That might just be my age too,
but yeah, with each passing year, I'm like, what the fuck did you do this year, you loser?
Yeah, I had a good feeling. Who wants that?
Yeah, it's bad.
Yeah, I'm,
I'm, I'm watching, you know, Six Feet Under, which I think is a really, really brilliant show,
especially as it, as it gets past its initial awkwardness.
And yeah, that entire show is about death and how you live your life and the mistakes and the regrets and everything.
I'm watching like three a night.
I'm just, it's too, I feel like I'm a, you know, Citizen Kane looking back on his life, but I'm 40.
I don't know why this is happening to me.
I get that too,
all the time, all the time. I don't think it's
just us, and I don't even think it's, it's the age that we're at. I think it's just,
I just, Pete, we, we, we are not right since that whole lockdown, you know, and then -
Well, we truly did. We all lost time of our lives. There's no question about it.
But the midlife crisis is a real thing, you know, it just, it's something you always think about your dad going through, but we're there.
But everybody I talk to, no matter what age they are, is in this shattered state.
I don't mean to say lockdown meeting just because we were locked down.
I just mean like that period of everything that was happening.
Yeah.
You know, I went, I went to an, uh, uh, a Clippers game the other night. A friend of ours was putting on,
and I never know anymore if it's, if it's me,
uh, or if it's everybody.
But I walk into this thing, it's old friends, it's people I like, it's a fun event, a basketball game.
We got beautiful seats, we got refreshments,
and
I'm just like, why isn't everyone talking about how shitty everything is?
Why isn't everyone talking about how bad life is?
And I think it's because
people don't want to ruin everyone else's night by bringing their shit to the party.
But there's also something about 20 people standing around acting like we're having a good time that is starting to get depressing to me.
But maybe they were all having a good time and maybe I'm just in my
I'll bring my shit to the party. I'll bring my shit to the party. Oh, you and I bring our shit to the party, but
Yeah, it's just like when you're talking with somebody like about like catching up with somebody you haven't seen in a few months
it all just seems like why aren't we talking about
You don't care. I don't care. Like can we get to the heart of the matter?
Yeah, we're dying every second. We're dying
I can't uh, my body's betraying me at this point. My hearing sucks. My my I need to get bifocals finally
Like I have to tap out to that
My bifocals ages you uh 20 years you put those on your face. You're you're 20 years older. Well
If you put them at the end of your nose
Luckily they have ones now
Where it's seamless you can't see that they're bifocals. Okay
And I just need them I don't need two kinds of like lenses
I need I need the top part to be my glasses and the bottom part to be nothing
Because when I have my glasses on I can't see what's up close to me because my glasses are distorting it
So i'm always taking my glasses on and off. So I feel like that's a little bit better
Than needing like a different adjustment lens for the close to to the far. I I can see I can
See regular up close. Yeah, it's just it's just with my my glasses on it's distorted which that didn't
For whatever reason when you're younger that doesn't happen
You can just have your glasses on and look at shit up close and it's fine. I don't understand that but
right
um
My lasik just hit like my 13 year anniversary and I i'm sure i've talked it up on here
But I gotta just highly recommend that
If you're if you're have any
Issues with glasses contacts, whatever it's a literally a one minute procedure
That gave me perfect vision that has lasted me as of right now 13 years. That's pretty fucking good
Forget why I shied away from it. Doesn't it not
Doesn't it only if isn't it only for a certain type of bad vision?
Or no, um, if you have an astigmatism, they won't do it and I think a lot of people do
Okay, but yeah, my vision was 2400 legally blind
What most people see is 20 feet away. I saw it as 400 feet away. So from age
you know second grade on up I had like
A thick sheet of glass like glasses weighed my face down. So I had to switch to contacts at a very young age
And I got sick of them
Very quickly because I have dry eyes as it is so blah blah blah
Wait a minute you saw
Say that again how you saw things from 20 feet something that was 20 feet away. You saw it
Yeah, what 2020 vision means is what what the average person sees as 20 feet away
You also see as 20 feet away. That means you have perfect vision
2400 means what the average person sees is 20 feet away. You see it as 400 feet away, which means like I couldn't see
Anything far away. Oh not meaning I got you not meaning distance
Just meaning like this is as blurry as if it were 400 feet away. Exactly. No, okay
If I was having dinner with kim bassinger at the batman table, I would not be able to see her
In the original batman
Oh the long
Yeah, and what a bummer. I mean, she's a beautiful woman. I'm on a day with her. I would not have been able to see her
I uh
I I speaking of batman always uh last night
I don't know why this happened, but I was in bed and
I I had my ipad open to youtube as I usually do and for some reason I went down a rabbit hole with the
That new flash movie just watching scenes from it
You you're right. It sucks. It completely sucks. Uh, I don't know why I thought on that first watch it was pretty good
Uh, I think I think I was just excited. Have you seen Nicolas cage talking about how he is in that movie and he hates it
No, it's very funny I popped up on tick tock
He's just like, uh, you know, I
Uh, I went there. Uh, I I I definitely
Did not approve of how I was used. I was shocked in the movie theater
Uh, nobody told me it just seemed very angry, but he's he makes me laugh
The perplexing part of it is in this day and age
In this day and age
Yeah
With all they can do
Yeah, why the fuck look complete cgi at this point in my opinion?
Unless it is absolutely necessary meaning guys
I don't know how else we create a 300 foot tentacle monster
Yes
I don't understand the use of it. I'm confused like in this day and age
So so like the the choices they make with all they can do so
I'll give you two examples
And so the second one's going to be the flash but in like
The boba fet tv show. This is a great example of one side of this coin. What was that called boba fat?
The book of boba fat it was called. Okay, the guy that plays boba fat. I forget his name, but he's a
Notable actor. Yeah, you know, he's like
60 now or whatever
He's a 60 year old man. He's got a 60 year old man's body. He's got a gut
You know, he does not doesn't look out of shape, but he looks like a husky older man as you do. Yeah
Boba Fett
In this timeline, they're shooting it in it's like right after return of the jedi. He's he's a svelte guy
and
You're you're like guys you can literally remove a human being's face and put it on another human being's body
Why is this guy walking around in the boba fat suit with a gut
Yeah
Put a different guy in the suit and when he takes the helmet off, it's him. It's the actor
This is so easy to do like you're so able to do this
And my guess is they thought the fans would they would bitch
Not at the fans who are pining for the george lucas era of star wars to come back. Yeah
Where it was all cg. I don't think anybody would have bitched. It's a very confusing choice now
Now here's the other part
Maybe well, maybe the guy said i'll only do it if I can be in the suit. I don't fucking know
Here's the other the other side of it is now is is andy muschietti's flash
Again in this day and age
guys nicolas cage came in
Make it nicolas fucking cage in the movie. Why is it a cgi nicolas cage?
Hey, we want to recreate adam west as batman
His face is covered
Get a guy who physically looks like adam west and alter it slightly with cgi
And have a human being as the adam west batman
This is fucking no brainer shit. I don't understand
Why that that that flash sequence was one. I mean that's sort of
We might be looking at that in 100 years as the end of cinema
That scene where we're just showing you
poorly done cgi renderings of former batman and superman
In a what was the backdrop like a fire cave or something? I don't even remember why we were looking at them
No, he's in the mall. He's at like the crux of the multiverse. So he's looking at all the different timelines and realities
Which is a cool idea
um
But you know, it's like okay guys
I get it. You had to you can't recreate christopher reeve
right
So you got like a cgi christopher. Okay, cool like whatever
Uh, my only guess is is that andy muschietti said guys we're gonna be using so much fucking cgi in this movie
We gotta make it all cgi or the cgi shit's gonna stick out like a sore thumb
I guess that's what it is, but it's like and this is a guy that made it
terrible movie
but this is a guy that made it and and and put uh
Jesus christ, uh the actor that played it. What was his name? I almost said tim conway. I don't know why
uh
Tim curry, you mean no, no, no
That must have been why I must say tim conway. No the new one. Uh, yeah scar bill scars bill scars guard
Doesn't that sound like a fargo name? Yeah, like I was up there talking to bill scars guard on the lake
Yeah, he's bill doesn't fit him as a person
No bill's a guy that works down the street in the in the you know overhead lighting office
Meanwhile
Stellan scars guard is the perfect name for that man
And alexander scars guard is the perfect name for that man and they just tossed bill off to the other one
I think the dad could go as bill scars guard his dad looks like a bill
I'd buy him if he wasn't an actor. I would buy him as bill scars guard. He needed to be stellen
But muschietti in the it movie with scars guard. He did exactly what we're talking about
He took a human being
And then he would alter him with cgi when needed to like make his jaw
Cartoonishly big when his mouth opens or whatever it is
Why would he not use these same techniques?
Why is there a cgi baby at the beginning of the flash when you can literally?
Put a real baby into it and make it look real without endangering the baby cgi baby
Don't you mean a hundred cgi babies? It's so crazy. It's so fucking crazy
Um, what what happens and I don't know why and i've never thought about it until right now
I've never read an article about it
But these guys get obsessed with the tricks the book of tricks
They forget why they came to filmmaking in the first place or they are bored with traditional filmmaking
But you look at a guy like zemeckis
Is maybe the textbook example zemeckis was one of the great
Screenwriters in the history of film he still is even with all his failures over the past 20 years
He's a brilliant screenwriter, but he got obsessed with technology
And stopped caring about story and you see these movies like the witches where it's a bunch of
cgi mice dancing
To 70s disco hits and you're like robert what happened to you?
Uh care, I know you hate cameron cameron went too far down that road and got obsessed with technology
But cameron is the only guy interested in furthering it and advancing it and he does every time out
Say what you want about him. He's advanced the technology. Uh, pretty much every time he stepped out there
You got these guys like
zemeckis
Spielberg to some extent lucas
Where it just becomes about i'm a kid in my sandbox with my tools
And you've forgotten how to connect with audiences emotionally you've forgotten how to tell a story
Um, that's why people are so forgiving of shitty special effects in the 80s
Because you cared if you care about the story, you don't care about a bad special effect
You go along with it. You understand it. You're like god. All right, they they didn't have the money for that
fine
Um because the story and the characters carry you along
I don't know
I don't know. It's it's it's no good
it's really really no good there's uh, it's
I don't know what the
I don't know. I don't know what the next turn of everything is going to be. It's very
You know, I guess it's you know, thank god thank god for major shout outs to to all of these labels and studios that are
That are putting out
You know these these these these collections that we keep buying from, you know, but like scream and and blue horizon and uh,
vinegar syndrome and what thank you guys for curating all of this older stuff
And repackaging it re -releasing it adding stuff to it, uh special features, what have you re
Re -facing it with these 4k transfers or whatever
It's like it's like a dawn a new dawn of cinema of stuff that people never got to see
Or at least lots of people never got to see and I feel like that is the
The sort of answer and saving grace to what's happening now, you know
And as far as new content coming out from the majors is concerned
Yeah, you know joe and I and then I have a few other friends that I always talk to about my
blu -ray purchases and stuff and I got that new video store box set which is trying to kind of recreate the experience of like
renting six
b -movies at the video store
and
so happy to
To support these places because I realize when they show up and me and joe make fun of ourselves and tease each other
About how excited we get about these things or this will fill the hole or this will fix the problem or whatever
The truth is it does kind of fill the hole
I was thinking when it came in the other day that box set and I was like reading the box of each one
You know sitting at my kitchen table big grin on my face
I was like outside of maybe
Little creative breakthroughs I have in my job and in my personal writing and things like that
This is it. That's that's what I look forward to is
vinyl records, uh
Physical media shit, that's it. That's what's bringing me joy at this point. I don't have a relationship
I you know, I have a work a job I enjoy but in terms of like hobbies and satisfaction. That's about it
Did you get the i'm gonna stop shitting on my my
Passion, you know
Did you try to like just own it?
Um, did you get the collector's edition of the enter the video store or just a standard?
What's the diff?
They could they could they could be a little clearer about this
You never talked on the show about your experience with the psycho collection, but they could be clearer sometimes on what you're buying
I'll talk about it right now. Okay, so the limited versions of tremors on 4k arrow has eight versions of tremors
It's insane limited, uh, you know, and then you find out. Okay, this one's forty dollars more
What does it have and it's like lobby cards?
I don't need lobby cards. It's very weird what they consider
another tier
Anyway, go ahead
the the limited edition
It's fun, it's funny how limited edition means the
The special one it sounds like it would be the one that has less. It's a limited set. Uh, but now
uh
the limited edition is um
It's the same movies. However
It comes with now wait this I don't even know if we said this is psycho one two three and four
No, no, no, i'm still on the empire of screams enter the video store. Oh, i'm sorry. Okay. Okay
Uh, so so there was two versions of this so so for those of you
Sorry for those of you at home that don't know what we're talking about. We've got a new arrow and quick pause also
There's also british and american versions confusing things further. Yeah
so
Um, there's an arrow video set
Uh, and these are all blu -rays. These are all blu -ray restorations of the four there's no 4k version of this
um
Of five movies that were put out. I think all originally by full moon
Um, but you've got dungeon master, which is fucking awesome
Uh, that's a really fun fantasy sort of horror movie starring uh, richard mole the late great richard mole
Uh, then you've got dolls, which is stewart gordon great flick
um
Uh about killer dolls and that definitely I think was a full moon
Then you've got cellar dweller not a good movie but a fun movie in that old video store sort of way
Uh alone. I haven't seen any of these movies then you've got arena, which is arena is a
I've never seen it but it's it's about
An intergalactic almost like I think it's like an intergalactic mortal combat style
Fighting championship where humans fight aliens and stuff and then you've got robot jocks and robot jocks is sort of like if if
Rock 'em sock 'em robots was in real life
Uh robot jocks, I think is a is a grittier
version of
What was that?
Um, was that real steel? Yeah. Yeah with hugh jackman with hugh jackman
Which is an adaptation of a richard matheson's steal
Um, anyway, but robot jocks is something along those lines
So they put all five of these into a box set now pad asked the question
What's the difference between the special edition and the regular edition? Well, the special edition is the same five movies
however, it also comes with lobby cards and a really cool book
and and and
in my opinion
Stuff that makes a box set like this
A little more of an experience because as you're watching these wild movies
you can
Kind of read about them learn a thing or two. It just kind of makes it fun. So now mine says special edition
But it doesn't have the lobby cards
That's a that's a shame
I don't care. I I don't use lobby cards for anything, but it's weird to me
well
what what it is weird and what pat was referring to earlier about the um
the uh
Excuse me
um
Psycho set, sorry, I got distracted. Uh the psycho set because I was reading about the uh, the box set to read it to you
Arrow had released
a set of psycho
The psycho movies. Oh, no, all of them, right? It's got the original
1234. Yeah. Yep
uh, and then um, it's got uh, it's got
These it's it's 4k
um
Only british at this point. I think I I got the british version
Well, the reason pat got the british version
uh was because arrow uk was doing a sale and and their 4ks were really like
Chopped heavily down in price
pat
Texted me. He said hey man. Look I got the
psycho
collection 4k
4k is region free. You can get this from their uk site
And it's going to be super cheap. Um, and I said great
so I went and
Purchased it. Uh, I then received it in the mail
And
I'm looking at the back of the box and it's saying
Excuse me. It's saying, you know all four movies in in for the first time ever
In stunning 1080p and i'm like that that's not
Sounds not right like this doesn't have the 4k sticker on it. Like what the fuck is wrong?
so
I text pat sure enough his box set says 4k on it mine says blu -ray
and
Before I was able to confirm that pat certainly had a 4k version of this set and I did not
I was emailing back and forth with customer service at arrow
And I was saying guys
I'm very confused. There is no 4k version of this on your site that I can tell from the pictures
The only page on your webs and and by the way when you're sold out of something you list something as sold out
I'm not seeing a sold out version of the 4k either. I'm just not seeing it
The only page where you can order this box set from is this page I ordered from
The version on that page seems to be identical to the one I am holding right now
Which appears to be blu -ray
yet
The video on the page that's embedded on the page. That's the commercial for this is saying 4k. What is going on?
Guy writes me back. He's like, uh, you got the right version
That that's all he says I go
You're not answering my question that's like a 16 point question
Yeah, I go is this the is this the 4k? Am I just not am I misreading something?
That's the version on the page that you bought
But I understand oh boy
Is there what is this?
Yeah, so at one point I write back and I go
The spines on the 4k are black. These are clear
The back of the 4k box says you there's a uhd sticker on the front of the box. It's not here
I don't understand what is going on
What is happening? Why is the uhd version not even shown on your site anymore?
The guy writes back there is no uhd version. You have the only version
At that point I text pat I go please go over to your bookshelf take a picture of the back of the box and send it
To me I need to compare it to the description of the back of my box to which pat
Responded this is deeply sad, which it was
And that's the kind of thing i'm trying to change
I'm trying to celebrate my obsessions and not shit on them
Um, and sure enough he's got a a 4k version and i'm i'm furious
And I go I don't fucking know man
Maybe you bought that on the on the on the us site and you're just not sure and he goes no
The 4k version isn't available in the us so i'm i'm emailing with at with arrow uk
Arrow uk is customer service
And they're claiming that the only place that offered the 4k never offered the 4k
There was only a blu -ray and they never answered any of my questions about
What is going on which and here's why it's because their customer service is farmed out to wherever
It's not some guy working at arrow. Uh clearly it's tragic
But I think even at your criterions in a lot of these places, you know
It was always deeply obsessed film fanatics that that worked at these places
And you know not just in putting together these dvd packages that obviously have so much love and care
but also just in the customer service departments and I think eventually
They had to just farm that work out like we're doing all across the board and you get people who not only don't
Know what you're talking about. They truly don't care. It's like they don't even get the whole world of dvds. It's it's sad
You're talking to just
You know a standard it person who doesn't care about what you're talking about
Yeah, so
You know, man, I I just
It's just it's it's just it's frustrating it's very frustrating so now i've got this
I don't know. I've got this box set now sitting in my fucking apartment of the psycho movies that I need to return
to
Europe
Yeah, or the uk and uh
You know, I haven't done it yet. I need to do it and I don't know you'll run out of time
That's that's what they're banking on. Can I tell you and I actually haven't even told this to my therapist
I was so ashamed of it. I wanted a cooler to bring to the hollywood bowl
You're allowed to bring in a cooler of drinks and stuff
I ordered it me and my buddy mike brown who you know joe we went to the bowl
We were told our cooler was too large. We snuck it in any way. It was a little too big
I was like, well god damn it
I ordered a smaller cooler
And told myself I was going to send this expensive cooler back
The other cooler showed up. I said well, this is taller than the other one. I had the measurements wrong again
I ordered a third cooler. It showed up. It was too big even though I had measured it
Um now I have three coolers. I didn't return any of them
They're all too big and they're in my garage and I can't return them because I waited too long
Talking like hundreds of dollars of cooling
It's really it's really tough. It's really really really tough
The thought of taking a cooler like to the ups store and and putting a barcode on
I couldn't do it. I was paralyzed by the idea of doing that and I just didn't
I will take uh, I have every monday. I take up like 30
Sales to the post office. That's a nice little feeling of accomplishment. I get each week. I like that
And they stopped being bitches about it I started I sold this daft punk, uh live box set on vinyl
That's awesome. And I used to love to work out to it. I grew out of it
I never listened to it and the vinyl was going for like 600 bucks and I sold it
Uh used opened but I still had all the stickers intact and everything which is big and these dork circles collector circles
Sold it for like five hundred dollars sent it and I was like this person's just gonna pretend they didn't get it
I had gotten so
Discouraged by humanity because I had so many false claims and so many arguments with people
But i'm just making good sales
I'll see the customer message because I got it from this daft punk buyer and i'm like here we go
I didn't get it. So sorry. You have to cover this five hundred dollar loss
Um, and he just said hey man, I wanted to say this is an even better condition than you said
I feel like I made a new purchase and the fact that all the stickers and stuff were in there
Uh, it just like was a real thrill for me. I'm a true fan. I was like, all right
My whole idea of humanity is just shaped by amazon basically
That i'll allow i'll allow how the people are behaving to dictate how I view the world unfortunately and lately they've been nice
It's improving. Um
I'm gonna segue us into the corner, but do I i'd love joe and I to do thanksgiving
Oh, you know
I would just like to share. Uh, i'm not going to review the movie except to say that I saw the first half of it
Quentin Tarantino just reopened the vista theater, which is the closest theater to my home
Um used to be next to where joe lived when he was here
And I go on opening night for thanksgiving with some buddies of mine. We were pumped
And eli roth comes out to introduce it
And he was really funny and charming I liked the guy he had four stars from the movie
Including milo manheim the son of cameron manheim who joe and I know from biblically. That's pretty cool
But they they were so excited for their opening night and they went and sat in the back row right behind me and my friends
They were directly behind me
and
The movie starts with this black friday scene, but it's a black friday like walmart trampling thing
Played both for gore and for laughs
So it's like satirical, but it's just like great gross out bits and gags and this black friday thing
It played so huge
Just like applause and yeah, you know, the director's there and the stars are there
So everybody's kind of pumped and it's la and it's opening night
But man, it was like exhilarating like I hadn't felt that way in a theater in a long time
Everybody's applauding and you felt the high of a director and his cast knowing that their movie is really working and connecting
so
It keeps going and all of a sudden we're missing like every third line of dialogue it drops out
So the brand new vista theater owned by quentin tarantino is having audio issues
So i'm hearing elai roth calling quentin tarantino like hey the audio is fucked up at your theater and it's opening night
um
And the audience would just let out this huge groan every time it would happen
But it was happening every third line the audio would drop out
So elai roth starts shouting out the dialogue and then the actors start shouting out their lines because they know them
And they just edited the movie obviously
So it was a disaster everybody left about halfway through. I still don't know how the movie ends
Joe and I will give it a proper review
but in terms of like cool la movie going experiences
Having the director and the cast yell their lines whenever the audio would drop out was very cool
The vista looks beautiful
it's not like i'm a theater reviewer or something, but i'm sure the
Theater will fix whatever audio problems it had
I'm going there to see napoleon this afternoon
But yeah, I will declare this because I do want you this is why I want you to see it
As of the halfway point when the audio dropped out
Um, I think thanksgiving is one of the great slasher movies i've ever seen
That's high praise for for a half -seen movie having a blast, uh granted it was special circumstances
But it was very funny
Genuinely scary great set pieces blah blah blah. It's very well reviewed
loved it kind of like an 85 percent or something which for a horror slasher is
wild
Yeah, it made me look back at eli ross career and really the only movies of his I love are the hostile movies particularly one obviously
um
I like cabin fever
The rest I can give or take what what is your?
I kind of like i've only liked I got a great admiration for eli as I do for you know, um
Ty west is another guy is it's a similar thing with ty west
I have great admiration for what they do, but I feel there are more misses than hits
But they're guys that take chances and they're passionate and they stick to their thing and I and I love that
I love hostile. I think hostile is one of the great horror movies of modern times. I think cabin fever has its moments
But i'm not overall a big fan of it
um, and and after that
I own all the hostels but two and three is better than two two. I think pretty much it really sucks
Um, i've never seen three i'm gonna have to watch it tonight
And look man me liking three could have just been that I hated two so much
and I have not seen it in a while, so I got to revisit but
um, but um, you know, I
What else did what else has he lied? I'm blanking on what else, you know
We we reviewed his death wish on here with bruce willis and I think we both kind of like that
I did not see clock with the house and its walls the clock. Oh, yeah house and its walls
I guess he's got a lot i haven't seen I never saw green inferno. Maybe he does have more stuff
I like inferno was just struggling so hard to be uh
gross out, you know weirdly
the
The puritan nature of of movie going nowadays
I think that's why thanksgiving was so well reviewed. It's like
It it at least and i've only seen the first half but it made him trim his excesses that I think
Turned too many people off, especially movie critics
Um, you gotta figure most movie critics are like your dad going to a movie or your mom going to a movie
so like some of his
Green inferno where they're ripping hearts out and eating them and you know all that shit
Um, he had to really rein it in and kind of work on his craft. I mean at this thanksgiving
I don't want to oversell it as a movie. But as a slasher, I think
You know, he really obviously gets the genre and does it well
but uh
I will just add on
I'm only going to do two in the corner. But but just yeah me too because I just talked about thanksgiving forever
just a uh
Note on something I rewatched I rewatched big lobowski
and
It's so funny, dude, you know back when that movie first came out and for years. I thought that big lobowski was this
I loved it. I always have loved it. I still do but I thought it was this extraordinarily lengthy indulgent, you know
time commitment of a movie
Epic in length
I rewatched this thing. It's an hour and 50 minutes
That would be like a breeze through the fucking park these days with the length of movies
it's just funny how that's all changed so much and
I still haven't seen flower moon because i'm like jesus christ
I don't want to go in and come out when it's dark outside. I want to see it. But god almighty man, like
You know, you you always want to tell people to go see escorcese in the theater
But it really does I think apple will probably have it in a month
I think they bought the rights and it's it's going to work beautifully as a two -night thing
it just really will as I think the uh,
The irishman does too, frankly. Yeah
I
saw
A picture called the last picture show
Um
The brand new criterion 4k, which I was very excited about because I think the last picture show
Is one of the most beautifully shot movies ever
um
It is shot. It's really it bridges the gap. It came out in 1971
And it's the movie that to me
Probably intentionally by peter bogdanovich the most pretentious man that ever lived also a star of it, too
Directed by andy machete if you'll remember
In uh for for my money the most random and strange cameo in the history of film peter bogdanovich in it, too
but um
the last picture show
Is one of my it's a perfect movie to me. It's one of my favorites. It's it's incredibly sad
And it bridges the gap between the classic
Uh, you know like the misfits carrie grant maryland monroe type movies of the 40s 50s 60s
um with the dark bleak
um
You know taxi driver raging bull all that stuff that was coming in the 70s and early 80s. It's that exact midpoint
Movie is unbelievably depressing
uh
Bogdanovich was banging her at this time
There's a fascinating podcast about the making of this movie. Uh
Mostly through the eyes of poly plat who was the young producer who?
Bogdanovich also dated married to and cheated on
Um, but stayed to produce the film. Anyway, you got jeff bridges and timothy bottoms
Um as two friends who sort of have this young blonde come between them
but the movie structure is
It's especially insane for the early 70s, but it's the structure of like dazed and confused. You're following all kinds of subplots
There's the older people of the town. It's a small texas town
The theater's going out of business much like how boogie nights uses video to talk about the end of an era
um, I would almost guarantee you paul thomas anderson got that from this movie and this
Old movie palace shutting down and decaying and and falling to ruin
Um is probably how bogdanovich looked at the movies of his day, you know, even though he was a young man
He was just a big film snob, but you got chlores leachman
a young
stunningly beautiful, uh ellen burston
um
Ben johnson who won the academy award you got a young completely naked randy quaid
You got clue gallagher garguliger, uh, who I forgot was in this the horror icon
Um, he comes in as one of sybil shepard's dad's
Friends and then bangs her on a pool table. It's a very bleak dark movie about sex
Everybody's cheating on everybody. Everybody's deeply unhappy and unfulfilled
Um, and I think more than anything else this movie contributed to my wanting to leave, uh, missouri
Great movie you ever see it joe never saw it
I'm shocked at how many?
Classic things i've never seen
For that's what I really recommend. It's it's an incredible movie and as an extra on the criteria on 4k
they have
um texasville which was the sequel
That came out in 1990 with jeff bridges and the whole cast back
um
They have it the original version and then a new black and white cut
Of the director's version which has never been released before so a good package from criterion if you care
Uh movies never looked better joe
uh
I watched um
King king on screen
I can't remember if you've talked about this on here or not, but but uh, I didn't because I didn't finish it
Oh, okay. Well, it's you know, it's a documentary about stephen king and the
About the adaptations of stephen king's work being brought to the screen
Uh, I
Found it
It's king is not in it except for some archive footage of his interviews or like maybe like something of him from a lecture hall
There's very little
actual king footage in it
Um, it is mostly interviews with people that have acted in his movies
Uh, and some people like, uh frank
uh
Uh now for god's sakes, what's his face the director darabount, uh who have adapted his movies, um
You know look man
King adaptations at this point. It's like people discussing the beetles. It's it's been discussed ad nauseam
You're not really going to learn much new unless you've never
Ventured into any of this or explored any of it already
but
It's an interesting enough documentary, uh up until it gets to the part where it does shit that almost every documentary
That's meant to praise or celebrate an artist does
Where it starts putting way way too fine a point
on
Uh, you know the the the relevance of of the work
Uh, and of course, it's everybody interpreting it into the way they want to interpret it
This sort of thing really bothers me that this this is this happened
A lot during the the this time period where this movie was made this documentary was made and
Everybody starts comparing the work to being this prophetic telling of trump coming
And it's just like guys
Take a fucking breath
A world existed before you and your trump fears
Did you ever think that maybe steven is writing?
From being influenced during the 60s in the nixon era
do you ever think he's pulling something from the nixon era and talking about that and it's
Almost exactly parallel to the trump stuff and but everybody's like it's fucking incredible
I mean you're talking about a book that came out in 1979 and this guy is calling trump
He's saying it as it's like you mean 10 years after nixon
Maybe he's just talking about nixon. Well, it's so it just it gets very annoying to me. Yeah, um
Um
At one point they're they're they're describing how cell is the movie cell is a prophecy for trump i'm like
Guys I didn't even know they made cell
I neither I neither saw nor read cell. I think cell actually had cusack and sam jackson
Yeah, I never saw it or even heard about it being released
Which is not a good sign even more
Irritating than this is I forget who's saying it
There's a part where somebody's talking about the movie 1408 and going is there anything more terrifying than 14?
Oh, yeah. Yeah, there's tons of stuff
More terrifying hotel room. Yeah than the cgi ghosts that are in
1408 1408 is a fine flick. I enjoy it but it's like guys
Can we just all just please a weird genre of hotel room horror now that I think about it
There was that whole show that the duplass brothers did on hbo. That was a horror anthology setting up one single hotel room
You got room 237. You got the shining you got 1408. You got that movie identity, which was in a hotel or vacancy
No identity
Yeah vacancy also also no country for old men had a lot of hotel room material
I don't know a little observation
Um
And i'll close the corner with an accidental jacobie lordy double feature that I had last saturday
my uh
Buddy brian and I go to the movies and as the second one started we were like we are two
Allegedly heterosexual men sitting here for a jacobie lordy double feature
uh salt burn
And priscilla
Uh jacobie lordy is who the hell is jacobie lordy. I don't even know who that is. Well, he's on euphoria
He's the hard throb of the moment. He's british I guess or australian. He's six foot five. He's very handsome, but
So i'll kind of review them both at the same time because I like them both about equally which is not much
but they both had positive things about them, but
Priscilla is the elvis and priscilla story
That is getting equal or better reviews than elvis the
to me just the
And to joe, I think that just one of the best ways that elvis story could have been told, you know
And I love that movie. I can't wait to watch it again
priscilla
Tells it from priscilla's point of view not that that is unimportant
I'm just saying they did not find a way to make this like a particularly compelling story
Elvis met her when she was 14
That's not really treated as a scandal, you know, he's in his early 20s
But the families are both, you know semi supportive of it, you know
And there's a lot of that's just how it was then kind of vibes
But so it's sophia coppola
And it's the same style of biopic that they did with
Jackie that one about jackie onassis
They they did a couple of those in a row
Um
Where it's like an avant -garde
Biopic of somebody with no real information just kind of vibes
Yeah, that was like the uh, remember the the the david mammott's, uh, phil specter bio. I mean, yeah, jesus
He even starts it with a text that says this is not based on a true story. You're like, what is this?
Right and for a biopic that's always just very weird to me
So what this movie does is elordi is playing elvis i've seen people raving about his performance
I think at a time where we just had austin butler you have to be out of your fucking mind to rave about this guy
Um, maybe it's just jealousy. Maybe I wish I was a six foot five british or australian guy, but
He's just dull to me and has nowhere near the charisma of elvis or austin butler
Um, and the story is basically told through his jackets like when you see him in the comeback special outfit
You're like, oh it must be the 60s
But it's all just these it's told through little arguments between elvis and priscilla backstage
Between elvis being like emotionally distant to her her and her getting her feelings hurt
Um, and it's all vibes, you know, so it was fine. I just don't get what people see in it
Saltburn to me was much more entertaining but ultimately a huge miss in the long run
But it's basically like a talented mr. Ripley or a cruel intentions kind of thing
Barry coigan who's a great actor from banshees of asherin
Meets jacob elordi this hunky guy
And he infiltrates himself into his posh upper crust lifestyle
The movie is a 2006 period piece, which is tough
Um
Tough for a 42 year old man to hear
but um
all the period music now is like block party
And uh, you know arctic monkeys and stuff. That was tough. That was tough. Yeah, sure
Sure, but it's emerald fennel who did promising young woman, which I really liked a lot but
It was a movie that also had its issues and its pacing problems and its tonal problems and a lot of things
but
And this movie has more of them by the way
It felt like that movie took a long time to get to and this one was kind of rushed
But um
I admire it. She's a great she knows how to make things interesting fun
You know shocking great use of music great, you know a lot like copal is like marie antoinette in that way
But again, you're watching a movie that's more about vibes and any sort of compelling story
there's also
I've never heard an audience go more crazy than a scene where when he lordy jacks off in a bathtub he gets out
coigan slurps up
Uh, I don't need to see this
I'm warning you if you go slurps his cum out of the water
That's disgusting and i'm saying like an inch of dirty water mixed with cum
Slurps it up
This theater reacted like it was uh, the shining opening night 1980 it was I myself included it was wild
um
That's what i'm saying. There's something about this emerald fennel that like she knows how to push buttons and and hold your attention
And I admire that to some degree
Uh, and it was certainly more entertaining than briscilla
Neither movie you need to rush out and see but I liked parts of them. All right, joe
Our movie this week
Where evil lurks
Yes
It is where all right, uh, this is a walk us through I believe argentinian
Or is it from mexico? I think it's argentinian
Uh possession film certainly a different take on the possession genre
Uh possession in the movie right off the bat without any explanation is just treated as a thing that's real
A thing that is accepted
And a thing that is a problem
Uh for particularly rural farming communities
In the way a drought or a lack of funding, uh would be
Um
Yeah, this by the way, this is confirmed, uh argentinian and with some funding from the united states, but
What you're describing joe right off. I thought to myself so many
movies in the horror fantasy action, whatever
sci -fi genres could learn from this movie
if you just
Drop us in in the middle of the issue. We will not only will we catch up?
We will appreciate you shaving 20 minutes of boring exposition out of your movie
And letting us catch up and be smart and figure it out
Sure. Yes. So I like that about this movie a lot. Yeah
So so right off the bat there they they identify there's a possession in the in the town
Uh when the possession comes so does the famine and and the craps die and all this stuff
um
the
A person was sent to
Uh
to cure the
To exercise the possessed person because only a certain group of people can do this and they're not priests
The cleaners they're called. Yeah cleaners. Um
It's almost just like a job you have
uh are sent
But the cleaner himself who who comes is is slaughtered
and two
Or three men who live locally who have an interest in saving their farms
Decide to take matters into their own hands to go to the house where the man is possessed to get him out of the town
uh without
Because if you kill him
Then the the spirit will immediately jump or whatever and you can't touch him and all this stuff
It's it's basically just it's like a you know, it's like covet or something. You can't you know, you'll get sick
So it's transmittable so yeah, eventually they overdo it with the rules
It's a lot of rules there. It's very confusing. They also don't really follow them and like, you know
It could have used another whack at that screenplay and shaved it down to three gremlin style
but um
Yeah, I had to I had to read at one point after the movie
This is the only time I read the wikipedia. Yeah for sure
This is the only time i've ever done this and i'll get to this but when I left I was
one of three people in the theater, I went to see it late on a sunday or something
and
The other two people were a couple
I was sitting a few rows behind them and when I left they were still seated
They were doing the sit through the entire credits thing before they leave some people do that
and uh
As I was leaving I said, uh, excuse me
I don't mean to do this but uh
Am I an idiot like i'm confused by the end, right and they were like no that was confusing and we actually had a
a discussion about the movie which I I don't think i've ever done
um, unless I was on like a date or something, but
anyway
You find out they learned quickly that having moved the body
They've now created a bigger problem
Uh, because
I don't know. There's something there's something about like what's happening with this particular
possessed person
Is that there is a a a chance of a re a physical manifestation of the antichrist coming to earth?
And because they've moved this body they have heightened these chances
They've worsened the situation
And they have to go now find this body they have to find it, um, who has to find it well
The
Two men from the beginning that moved the body the third man ends up dying because the
possession spreads to his sheep
And he kills the sheep as his wife begs him not to
uh, and then he
Then she immediately kills him and then she kills herself because you have to stop it or it'll keep spreading
All right, so that'll have that all happens while they're transporting this
Rotten they call it the rotten is um
a big disgusting
Yeah, when they showed this I was like, oh, okay. This is the kind of movie we're talking about here
This was like a big um, like think the fat guy the first death in seven that kind of fat guy
Mixed with like the baron and the original dune
Just like pustules and every time he moves his face like, you know, ooze comes out of his nose and mouth
um, and they're transporting this rotten the rotten gets loose
and uh infects the sheep
so
Basically, this thing is spreading through the town in a pretty original way. I I liked uh, the early stages of this movie
Weirdly, it's like talkie between its maybe we're just used to like relentless action and gore and stuff, but
I found it weirdly kind of like dull in spots and then it would be great
But it kept kind of going back before between those two extremes
well, um, so then yeah you enter into a sort of a
a road movie for for lack of a better way of putting it is
They have to now go find this rotten and wherever he's sort of ended up because now he's a few towns over or something
uh, and
The one guy brings his children with him who are estranged from him. He's been through a terrible divorce
Um
One of his sons or his no, he's got a son and a daughter
uh, his son is
Mentally handicapped this is one of the coolest or he's severely autistic. That's what it is
This is one of the coolest parts of the movie. Like when the demon gets in you you obviously act different
Yeah, and they do a whole thing where the son gets possessed but because the deem this demon is in him
They talk about how like when it gets inside someone who has a mental issue
It the demon gets trapped and it has to like figure out how to control the person like it's a puzzle
I thought that was really cool and very cool. Yes, there's a scene where throughout the entire movie
Which adds tons of tension every time anything is happening. This kid starts grunting and moaning repeatedly
Which really is a great tension builder in the movie
And then all of a sudden there's that scene where he walks in and he's talking to his grandmother and he's totally
Just regular
You're like, holy shit the demons in this kid bad
He figured out how to like unlock this kid or whatever
Um, I realize as i'm explaining this as pat is explaining this if you haven't seen it
It all sounds very convoluted and confusing and people I have to admit
I was a bit confused throughout the entire thing
I know
I just realized we're confused even now on the fucking title. It's called win evil, which it shouldn't be
Me
We're wrong
Oh boy
I I was watching this I couldn't tell why some people that touched
A rotten got possessed why other people didn't they sort of half explain that at one point very passively but not very well
That's the issue from a from a plotting standpoint from a rules standpoint
It's
It's too all over the place that they may remake it and and whittle that down and probably make a more boring movie
I can't be too upset because its craziness is also
kind of its appeal
but like the shocking moments like when the it um
Just like that speak no evil movie
It's relentless towards kids
Like the dog attacks that little girl that was insane a huge like shocking moment and then the little girl lives
But it's because she's possessed right and the demon fixes her right?
So that's another part to this not to cut you off
But that's another part to this is there's a is there's a a thing like almost in the mist
where yeah
he he takes his his survive what he thinks are his surviving kids and
Against his wife's
Will
Basically kidnaps them and takes them away because he knows like there's this evil that's going to spread and we have to get
These kids out of here and she doesn't believe him
And then you know that the wife is back elsewhere with a little girl who she thinks is her little girl
Who's miraculously alive, but the little girl is actually possessed
So, you know that that whole town is going to die
basically this is spreading through the countryside and they have to stop it by locating this original rotten and
Taking care of you know the problem
I think the mist was definitely an influence because it has a real kind of like
Shocking bummer of an ending kind of thing too and it ends with the guy going. No
There's a lot of similarities
but um
I think what it does is what I would have done had I made the mist which is go back and find that the wife has
Turned and him have to battle his wife
I'm surprised they they kept that confrontation out of the movie and I don't know if they kept it out of the short story
I don't remember that is true. So yeah, the wife does eventually show up in this and she's possessed
and eaten
Eating her kids brains like shoveling the kids brains out and just shoving them in her mouth. That was wild
And um, you know also by the end he's like beating the shit out of out of a little girl at one point
You know, there's just a lot of like violence on kids
but um
That's what I liked about it was in its extreme kind of more evil dead crazy gory
Uh, like when he he bashes the big fat guy's head and at the end like that's really shocking and crazy and gross
blah blah blah
Um, I just wish that they had locked down and nailed the story a little bit better
I then I think we might have had a a classic but for for me
I just kind of enjoyed the scares and the gore and sort of shrugged at the rest. I didn't really get it
Yeah, it was
You know, it's funny because we started the review by saying it was cool that they didn't over explain anything
They just jumped right in with this wild premise that possession was just a problem that people face
Just but then as the other side
Yeah
As the movie goes on they start to implement a lot of different rules and it just becomes unfamiliar, you know
So by the time you reach the end of this thing
Um, there's a group of children who are assisting
The possessed person to bring the antichrist child back. You don't really quite understand why that's the case
Again, sometimes if you touch him you get infected. Sometimes you don't
Yeah, I read online that essentially it was supposed to be that this main character was immune to it
Which I didn't pick up while I was watching it
No, uh and the movie basically ends with the reveal that his autistic
son
While he was possessed
ate his mother
His kids grandmother and the main character's mother
uh whole
uh, because you you hear a story that a possessed person does that at one point in the movie and then the autistic son does that
and
Yeah, they pull
The mother's hair out of the mouth
Out of his mouth, which is an odd moment because the mother just suddenly is gone
Like I said, there's that scene where the autistic kid comes in and he's speaking regular and everything and the the grandmother is clearly like
Uh -oh, this is no good
I needed the wikipedia to know what was happening there
Yeah, and then and then you never see the mother again
And then at the end when the husband comes back from this journey that he was on to find the rotten
He picks up the kid and goes home, but they never address
He never says where's my mother or anything, right?
And then all of a sudden the kid coughs up her hair you realize the kid ate her and that's the end of the movie
basically, yeah, um
Practical effects. I give this thing a 10 out of 10
Ball sack I give it a 10 out of 10. You got a lady eating a kid's brains out of its head
Wild shit. Yeah, uh, and then I was terrified this guy's other movie previous movie
No, I haven't either but it's on shutter and i'm definitely gonna check it out. I hear it's great
I'll check it out and then originality. I give it a high score, but but uh overall it was very convoluted. Um
I I suppose i'd watch it again and I suppose if I saw a decent deal
a decent
Look, let's put it this way
We were talking at the beginning of the show of these
Re surfaced
Re -released old movies we get to see that are kind of wild and whatever courtesy of these these labels that put them out
If this thing came out that way and it was something from the 70s and I saw it now for the first time
I'd be like, holy shit. This is crazy. I gotta own this. Yeah, uh given that it's new it has a little less luster to me
But that said it's something I would probably overall add to my collection if I found the right price on it
It's something I I think I would watch again. I'd say my hog is medium
Up for this, uh, not crazy, but but you gotta you gotta tip your hat to something this insane and original
Agreed my my hog is uh semi -up pretty up but um, it's for the visuals the um
The kind of early sam raimi crazy spirit. I would not be surprised at all if this guy's next move
Is a big horror movie or a big action movie or so, you know some franchise or something because he's clearly got the chops
um to make
Great images and stuff. I just I want to see him paired with a little bit better script or a better
A better like like Guillermo del Toro, you know, he needs some help sometimes translating his crazy visions to the screen
But um, I think he'll find that perfect project for him down the line because I really like this move
All right folks, well we'll be back uh with thanksgiving and more next month in the meantime i'm on the road
uh coming up this coming weekend
in uh, denver
In phoenix and in salt lake city
Uh in january, we got the grammar see theater in new york city. Certainly my biggest show ever in new york
and then it's on to uh, well we haven't announced it yet, but
Austin is coming up
I'll be on the jokers
eric andre cruz doing taste buds live and then after that
In february i've got la i've got san diego. I've got san fran
um
And many in nashville, I believe many many more dates. Please go to joe de rosa .com for info and tickets
Happy thanksgiving everybody
Uh, as joe said we'll be back with thanksgiving not sure what else is coming before the end of the year
But rest assured we're thankful for all of you
Thankful for all of you, uh, see you in hell pot on instagram. We got merch on the etsy page
We got a facebook page. Uh, thank you to emily for handling all that reach out to her if you need
um anything at all
Happy holidays everybody. We will see you next month and we will see you in hell