I'll see you in hell.
Folks, we'll see you in hell back to talk about a movie.
This is our final episode for the month of January.
And how better a way to end the month than a movie about the election of a pope.
Every year around this time, we have a few traditions.
The Oscar nominations come out.
Every four years a new president takes office.
And every 30 some years we get a new pope.
That's what's happening is in conclave.
I never thought I'd find a movie about a pope election so riveting, but we'll get to it.
Yeah.
And boy, if you were raised in a Catholic family as I was, as Joe was, this is kind of the
ultimate watch with your parents picture.
I didn't watch it with my parents, but it's a great one for that reason.
And because it could open up all kinds of conversations in the back half.
Lotta inside info.
Yeah.
They were showing like the part of the process of the pope election in this where I was like,
are they allowed to date?
Like was the Vatican applicable and or amicable in giving this info over?
Or I feel like this is sort of secret ceremony shit, but anyway, we'll get to it.
It seemed extremely well researched, but I don't know to be honest with you.
I've never been to the Vatican.
Have you been to the Vatican?
Yes.
Did you go in and all that?
Oh, yeah.
And you go in?
Okay.
Yeah, it's a sight.
I mean, there's a lot to see there.
Well folks, I'd like to start by talking about the top nominations at this year's Academy
Awards.
Please.
Delayed twice due to the raging fires in Southern California, which are still raging,
but I guess now we decided that people have forgotten about them enough that we can go
ahead and have our lavish award ceremony.
What a world.
I do love that the Oscars are going to be hosted by Conan O'Brien.
Conan O'Brien is one of the few people who is like a reason to watch something, whether
it's good, bad, indifferent.
He's going to bring the funny.
And I'll be there.
I'll check it out for best picture.
To me, it still seems shocking how many nominees we have these days for best picture.
That's a very new development that we have like 10 movies.
It was five for 100 years, but the list is Anora, which I loved.
The brutalist, which I liked, but which was way too long, a complete unknown, which was
fine, the Bob Dylan movie.
Today's pictures, so we're very timely, Joe.
Con Clay received a nomination.
Okay.
Duned part two.
Oh, come on.
Come on.
They're just, I don't get this.
Either do it like at the end, like nominate the third Lord of the Rings or whatever, but
you can't take a spot every year for doing the same basic thing.
Duned.
It's the same movie.
I'm sure a lot of nerds are spasming out right now, or whatever the proper word is.
Sorry, I said spas.
Now to me, I'm unable to be outraged about the Dune two nomination because I see that
Amelia Perez received a nomination.
This is the movie with penis, to vagina, which I have seen making the rounds online.
So you've probably seen that clip by now, but are truly bad movie, both politically and
narratively?
I'm still here.
What is that, Joe?
I don't know.
I'm still here.
The Joaquin Phoenix movie.
These titles, you get them confused.
I get them confused.
I have not seen I'm still here and I don't know what it is.
Okay.
It's a foreign film.
All right.
I haven't seen it or heard of it.
Jesus.
Why is, I'm sorry.
And everybody's going to boo me for saying this and I said it about parasite.
No, I get it.
Parasite was a great movie.
There's a foreign language category.
Why are we now in an over bloated category already that doesn't recognize what it should
be recognizing at the time by putting things like doom to end to a slot?
Why are we also taking away a slot with foreign language features when they're supposed to
then get rid of the other category?
This is stupid.
I completely agree and I think anyone trying to make that into a controversial statement
is bending over backwards to do so.
We were America.
This is a, this is awarding our best films.
And then we have a special category honoring films from abroad.
It's a perfect system.
So why are they getting double nominations?
I guarantee I'm still here is also nominated in foreign language.
They also nominate animated movies for best picture, even though we came up with the
best animated feature category to stop that.
It blows them up.
Hold on a minute.
See, I'm still here.
Yes, it is, by the way, the same exact title.
Yeah.
Well, I'm not there.
I'm still here.
Yeah, the Joaquin was called I'm still here.
So is this.
By the way, I'm still here is also nominated for best international feature in this year's
Oscars.
So same with Parasite.
Jesus Christ.
And it's a film in Portuguese.
So nominated is Nickel Boys, a movie that I started, then realized that it was going to
be a movie shot entirely from a weird, awkward camera angle, like from an iPhone, and that
it lasted two and a half hours.
And I said, I can't watch this right now.
Maybe I'll watch it eventually, but I'm not watching a gimmick movie that lasts two
and a half hours.
The substance nominated for best picture.
Okay.
Very interesting.
I mean, it's very rare to see any horror representation.
That's kind of crazy to me.
And then wicked, Joe.
Oh, get the fuck out of here, wicked.
This fucking whole thing, man, I swear to God, this is why I won't watch these fucking
things anymore.
It's also bought and sold such bullshit.
They throw one fucking artistic flick in from Brazil to try to make it look like they've
got their finger on the pulse of cinema.
And this is all such bought and sold fucking bullshit.
Give me a fucking break in a category of best musicals wicked wouldn't make a fucking
nomination.
Yeah.
Yeah, I know.
God, dude.
Unbelievable, man.
Truly unbelievable.
I know.
The moments by an actor, Adrian Brody, the brutalist, Shalame, complete unknown, Coleman
Domingo, sing, sing, Sebastian Stan, the apprentice for doing a okay Donald Trump impression
and Ray Fines for Conclay.
And I love, by the way, I love both the apprentice and a different man received critical acclaim.
I've not seen either.
Neither made a dime anywhere.
But God forbid they won't give it to Stan for a different man.
They've got to give it to him so they can look like see we're being good Democrats and
we're going to give it to him for the Trump.
Give me a fucking break, man.
It's also his whole campaign was nobody even nobody invites me to their academy events
because I played Donald Trump.
So that it's like, dude, that's not happening.
No one thinks you're a Republican because you played Donald Trump.
Well, I just saw an article Sebastian Stan nominated for the Trump movie Nobody Wanted
to See.
Yeah, nobody does this movie.
They make it have to be this thing like, oh, we're this little underdog.
You've been nominated for Oscars now.
So you stop, stop lying.
You're not an underdog.
I also love too that the idea of a great movie.
And I'm just assuming because I haven't seen it, but I just love the idea that a movie
that dares humanized Trump in any way where they're like, yeah, let's portray a person
here.
Yeah.
That's not an archetypal villain, right?
Paper thin with no depth, no motivations, no nothing.
Yeah.
That that that suddenly makes it like, you know, you're carrying water for this man.
Right.
You know, it's just it makes nothing makes sense.
I think it's a fucking dumb.
I've had it.
Supporting actor, you're a Boris off who was great in Anora, Karen Culkin, who was great
in a real pain, even though the movie was average, Edward Norton, who was bad in a complete
unknown bad guy pierced in the brutalist, Jeremy Strong for the apprentice actress in a
leading role, Cynthia Arrivo for wicked, Carla, Sophia, Gascon for Amelia Perez.
Mikey Madison, Anora, Demi Moore, the substance, that's not a supporting role.
Demi Moore leading there.
Yeah, I guess so, but for an and a Torah as I'm still here, supporting actress Monica
Barbara, for a complete unknown, she was good.
Ariana Grande for wicked.
I can admit she was good.
Felicity Jones in the brutalist.
She was not good.
Isabella Russavini from last week's Blue Velvet in Conclave, always great to see
her.
I love Isabella Russavini.
It was great to see her in Conclave.
She does not deserve an Oscar for this.
I agree.
She's got real lines.
I completely agree.
Yes.
And Zoe Saldana in Amelia Perez, who, by the way, did what she could with an unplayable
role in an unwatchable movie that has been nominated for a talk.
The only one of those nominations that excites me is Demi Moore in the substance.
I thought she was tremendous in that movie.
And I have always, especially more so in recent years rooted for Demi Moore.
I just really like her.
She seems like a whole person.
And I listen to her autobiography that she reads and audibles.
It's really, it's not like a, it's a saintly, well-written book, but she's had a fascinating
life.
She's awesome.
And I thought she was great in that.
And that's really cool that she's having this really cool third act in that that she got
nominated for that movie.
For sure.
Directing Sean Baker-Anora, Brady Corbett Brutalist, James Mangold, complete unknown, Jacques
Adyard for Amelia Perez.
That's a French straight man directing the story of a Hispanic trans woman that we are
awarding for best directing, even though we hate that.
So okay.
And then Coralie Farjot for the substance.
Very cool for best director.
Also, and I know we've discussed it.
I think we even did it.
But if you haven't seen her movie that preceded the substance, I prefer it.
It is called Revenge.
And it's probably still on shutter, but my God is it a great movie.
And just every bit is intense as the substance.
And then I'll mention writing quick just because I hate that they never mentioned writing
because nobody cares.
Original screenplay, Anora, the Brutalist, a real pain, September 5th, which I saw last
night, and sucks is so boring.
And the substance again, then writing adapted screenplay.
We have a complete unknown, conclave, Amelia Perez, Nickel Boys, and Sing Sing.
So very coincidentally, we are discussing a very much celebrated and critically lauded
movie this year on this week's episode with conclave.
Joe, what's new with you, old friend?
Well, this is an interesting thing.
I met Bradley Cooper, a star-er-a-met.
And we were hanging out in a mutual setting.
I was not hanging out with him.
He just happened to be where I was and I happened to be where he was.
And we started talking.
I started asking about his she-stake place that he opened or is opening in New York.
And he really lit up.
And I was like, yeah, man, I'm from Philly.
And he was like, no way.
Where are you from?
And we start to talk.
I was like, you know, I was sandwiched up in New York, too.
And he was like, what?
We really bonded over sandwiches and sandwich philosophy and whatever.
It was a very interesting thing.
And he said, give me your number.
I'm going to go real quick before I lose this.
Do you think that Mediterranean business owners bond over falloffalcy?
I mean, just kill the momentum of a story with a hard fucking joke.
Hard.
Go on.
It was a falloffal.
Oh, boy.
The lawfulsy.
All right.
Bill Shakespeare just sat up in his grave and said, I want to sign that boy to a three-year contract.
A falloffalcy.
Go ahead, Joe.
Anyway, he said, give me your number.
I'm going to go to your shop.
I'm like, yeah, cool.
Keep me posted.
The next day he texted me.
He goes, I just got off the plane.
I'm heading to your shop.
What should I get?
I'm like, this is insane.
So.
Yeah, that's really cool.
He went.
And oops, my mic is falling.
Jesus.
Hold on a second.
Uh-oh.
My mic just almost fell.
He went to the shop and I was like, you know, I don't know what to do to like, what if he
doesn't text me or, you know, afterwards, you know, I don't want to follow up and be
like, did you like it?
You know, I didn't want to look needy.
So I was like, you know, a little anxious and lo and behold, the coop, as I'm going to
start calling him, whether he likes it or not, in coop.
He facetimes me from his car.
He's like, I just ate one of the sandwiches.
This is amazing.
It's like, what?
What is going on right now?
Very cool.
It was not rare, a rare positive celeb tale.
He was, he was awesome, man.
He was very, very cool.
And I'm going to, I got to go up north to, uh, to, to handle my, uh, to be with my dad
during this, uh, surgery and stuff.
So I'm going to try to, uh, sneak away for a day or two up to New York and, and I, hopefully
his shop will be up and running by then and, and I'll get to check it out.
But, uh, shout outs to the my show.
Bradley Cooper.
The hungover my strobe himself.
Very weird.
Like, when I was talking to him, I kept picturing the my strobe.
I was like, oh, yeah, he didn't, he did that voice in the,
I can't even imagine him sounding like that right now.
It was, yeah, I was like, oh, yeah, he doesn't sound like that.
I, yeah, I won't, I won't discuss the my strobe while we're speaking positively about
BCL.
I love BCL.
But as I said on here, I, my second viewing of a star is born elevated that from a B
plus to an A plus.
I think that is an amazing fucking movie.
I love it.
Uh, folks, shall we go to the movie corner?
I don't know why I screamed folks out of nowhere.
Let's do it.
Um, yeah, I guess I can start with September 5th, since it got nominated for an
Academy Award for best screenplay.
Um, September 5th is a telling of the exact same story told in Munich.
The story of the 1972 Summer Olympics in Munich, Germany, an American sports
broadcasting team must adapt to live coverage of the Israeli athletes.
As they are held hostage by a terrorist group.
So this is from unlike Munich.
This is from the journalist standpoint.
This is from, you know, it's very much in that all the president's men mode of
a bunch of guys in short sleeve white button up shirts with pit stains, uh, with
black, you know, horn rim glasses.
It's got that Apollo 13 feel of just a bunch of hard work and blue collar men
drinking stale coffee, uh, and trying to get the job done.
But it is so dry and so boring.
And the screen plays a big part of the problem, even though it just got nominated.
There, there's no zip to it.
There's no punch to it.
It's a story we already know.
And we have already seen dramatized by Steven Spielberg, one of our greatest
filmmakers that movie was nominated for tons of awards.
So now to give us a different, much less exciting vantage point on the
Olympics and this, this big national tragedy.
Why?
Why are you giving us a less interesting take on the same material?
It would be like if somebody made Titanic, but it was about like a guy who's
watching it from his telescope.
Like, and you never get on the boat, you know, we just, we're, we're telling you
just the story of a guy watching the Titanic go down.
It's like, no, the whole movie, I don't know why it exists.
Um, it's Peter scar, Peter SARS guard, who is one of my very favorite actors.
You can watch him fucking kill in the Apple TV presumed innocent.
If you haven't seen it, he's so good in that.
Uh, Ben Chaplin, John McGarro, who, uh, was the,
a sort of Cuck boyfriend and our husband in past lives.
He's a good actor.
It's just, it just sits there.
The direction in this thing was really a problem in a movie that's entirely in a
control room.
The camera doesn't move.
So like, you're literally, it's static shots of like Peter, SARS guard going,
give me camera, see, give me camera, see, and then somebody comes in and is like,
if we show camera, see what if what if somebody actually sees blood on the
nightly news, zoom in on Peter, SARS guards face, give me camera, see,
Oh, God.
You know, I just made up that scene, but that could be any scene in this movie.
You know, it is so dull.
And I, if I hadn't seen it with my buddy, Brett, I would have walked out.
It is so dull.
Don't watch this movie.
Um, I think my theme today, along, you know, in regards to Conclave is,
old men movies.
Yes.
And also movies that I'm showing this new lady in my life, because she,
she's never really seen many movies.
And it's, and she's got an enthusiasm to start seeing all the stuff she never saw.
And it's really great as a movie collector to be able to show her stuff.
It's exciting.
So she had never seen grumpy old men.
I was like, I have a feeling you're going to think it's really funny.
And we watched it.
She did.
I watched this movie twice during the holiday season now.
Um, what a wonderful movie.
It's so funny.
Walter Mathau is so funny in it.
Um, it's just awesome.
It's, it's sort of an unofficial sequel to the odd couple.
It was them reprising, not reprising, but, but playing roles again,
where they were had an adversarial position towards one another.
It's, you know, Mathau is the sort of brash, loud one.
Lemon is the more refined, organized one.
It was, it's just a wonderful movie.
Burgess Meredith and Margaret Darrell Hannah, Kevin Pollock.
Do yourself a favor if you haven't seen it.
Watch grumpy old men.
And it's a perfect holiday movie because it spans from Thanksgiving to Christmas.
And then into the spring in, in the film.
So it's worth a watch.
Check it out. Grumpy old men.
I'm a big fan.
And of the sequel, which I have only seen once or twice.
I'm doing a rewatch.
I find the sequel to be almost unwatchable.
Really?
Yeah, they just, it doesn't have any of the spontaneity of the first one.
Like they're just, the story is not interesting.
It's not, it's, it's, it's a, it's sort of just a rehash of the first movie.
Except now Walter Mathau is going to get the woman.
And, yeah, I mean, a step down, but I don't remember it being a huge step, but I'll watch it again.
The jokes aren't, it just doesn't hit in the same way.
There's a lot of moments in that first one where you're like, I think Walter Mathau just rift that.
Right. And it feels organic.
And the second one to me, it all feels very like somebody writing a script, trying to capture the second one
feels like a later episode of a sitcom where you're like, oh, they got new writers.
Will you take a grumpier old man over an out to see?
Yeah, it's 100%.
That's the out to see is I shouldn't say grumpier old men is unwatchable.
It's, it's not that enjoyable out to see is an almost unwatchable movie.
Like it's bad.
I don't even remember it.
Will you take a grumpier old man over an odd couple two?
Well, I'm going to talk about odd couple two today.
So, all right.
Look, I watched sort of an old man movie myself.
I sold my blu-ray copy for a lot of money because I'm, it's a gold rush on Amazon with how much
things are going out of print these days.
But my blu-ray of 10 directed by Blake Edwards, starring Dudley Moore and Bo Devin.
Eric, 10 is an anomaly.
10 is a movie that everyone over 40 knows and no one under 40 knows.
It was a massive commercial hit.
It was a critical hit.
I don't even think people can fathom that there was a time when Dudley Moore was both a
sex symbol and a box office draw.
It makes no sense to me.
And I lived it.
I just don't get it.
But he is funny.
He's charming.
And 10 is one of Blake Edwards many, many midlife crisis movies.
I love his pink Panther stuff, you know, and his slapstick movies with Peter Sellers from back in the
day. They're all a lot of fun.
But as I get older and go through my own midlife crisis and my own divorce and my own
experience of dating younger women and doing this and that and the other and, you know,
things you never think you'll do, but you find yourself doing these midlife crisis movies hit
really hard, you know, they're about, I don't know how he made them for 20 years.
But he was married to Julie Andrews.
It seemed to be a mission of his to show the world how sexy Julie Andrews was.
He was always kind of showing off his wife in a way you might consider perverse or you might
consider cute.
Who knows?
But she's always dressed kind of sexy in this.
An SOB.
He actually had her do nude scenes, Mary Poppins herself.
But this movie is very much Dudley Moore's movie.
Julie Andrews plays his long suffering wife.
He is going through a midlife crisis and suddenly wants to fuck every younger woman he meets.
There across the way through his telescope, he sees a guy living the life he thinks he wants.
He's having nightly orgies with young, beautiful naked women.
And like a lot of guys at this time of life, Dudley Moore starts thinking, is there more?
This is not my beautiful house.
This is not my beautiful wife as David Byrne wants saying, I want to get out and so my wild oats.
And the wild oats are personified by Bo Derrick.
When she is introduced in the movie Tommy Boy, Chris Farley goes, she's like a
10, which is like a very lame, winky in joke.
But she was it.
She was the sex symbol.
They spend a lot of time in this movie with her in slow motion in a see through bikini running down
the beach. And it's time well spent.
She's a beautiful woman.
She's not much of an actress.
The movie is a slapstick romp where in Dudley Moore's attempts to fuck Bo Derrick and cheat on his
marriage.
She's also cheating on her marriage.
He gets in a bunch of hijinks.
He rolls down hills.
He gets stung by a bee.
It's very episodic.
It's very like he keeps meeting wacky characters and he's on this journey.
It's a meet the parents type movie where everything that could go wrong does go wrong.
And it's very, very funny and charming.
And as Dudley Moore is about my age in this and going through a lot of the same stuff.
I'm going through trying to date again and get back out there even though he's cheating on
his wife, which he should not be doing.
I found a lot to relate to.
A lot to laugh at.
Brian Denny. He's in it.
He's great.
The supporting cast is great.
And it's just one of the it came out in 79.
It's one of those that just it's it's L.A.
in the Johnny Carson era.
And that's just an era that I'm fascinated with.
Part of me wishes I was alive then instead of now.
And it's just that big bond L.A.
California late 70s vibe.
If you haven't seen it, check it out.
It's going out of print.
So you got to act fast.
Joe.
After watching the grumpy old men, we then I said, well, now I got to show you the odd couple.
So we watched it.
Again, just a master masterful film, a masterpiece in American comedy.
Mathell and Lemon had worked together before that movie, but this really is where it becomes,
they become the team that we knew them for.
And again, just so funny.
It's astounding.
They have lemon and math.
I both have consistencies in their acting and their performances, whatever through their careers.
But math always truly the same guy for like 60 years on camera, whatever it is.
It's fascinating to me, like just his sense of humor, like the way he riffs things and whatever.
It's all there in the odd couple as much as it is 30 years later in grumpy old men.
And there's not much I can say.
You know the story, a guy gets dumped by his wife.
He's a neat freak.
He moves in with his friend.
His friend is a slob and hilarity ensues as tensions build between the two of them.
It's a wonderful movie.
And it's got a great supporting cast.
Mainly my favorite is the guy that plays Stan on the Golden Girls.
What is that actor's name?
Golden Girls.
I know his name on the show.
Stan's born.
It's all in.
I'll hold on a second.
Crazy.
Golden Girls cast.
Of course, why would why would he be listed in the first 11 people?
He's only one of the main characters of the show.
This is crazy.
He's in the entire cast list on, you know, when you google cast.
Yeah.
He's not there.
Oh, there he is.
Herb Edelman.
He looks like a herb Edelman.
Yeah, he does.
Anyway, the odd couple.
It's a wonderful film.
And it's, what's his face did it?
Jesus Christ.
My brain.
Neil Simon.
Neil Simon at his best.
Neil Simon, sometimes it gets a little too set up punch.
Yeah.
You know, a little too borscht belty.
But when he's on and he's, and he, you know, and he does it right,
it's really, really great.
And this is one where he really hits that mark very perfectly.
But check out the odd.
I'd say if they're cast right and they often were because he was, you know,
he was the hot shit of the 70s.
Like if you get the great cast for his stuff, they really make it sing.
And obviously you can't do much better than lemon.
All right.
Another, I guess on a little bit of a theme today,
talking about movies I sold at a huge profit.
I was going through my movie collection,
which I do when my OCD kind of flares up,
especially because I'm not drinking.
I find other outlets.
So I lost myself in the collection and was basically selling off
anything in the Blu-ray format that had gone up and valued tremendously.
Because you got to assume we're going to get the 4K soon.
They're announcing more and more 4K every day.
So I see my copy of Luca Guadagnino's Suspiria remake,
which Joe and I reviewed on the show in 2018.
And we both really liked, if memory serves.
I bought Suspiria from Amazon in 2018 for $5.
I sold it folks for $69.
Okay.
Pretty impressive.
And it was used.
It wasn't even new.
So before I sent it out, I watched it.
Because I was like, well, hell, if it's going out of print and it never makes it to 4K,
maybe I'll never see it again.
And I loved it again.
Guadagnino, since this time has become one of our biggest directors.
I guess they shut him out for challengers this year, which is crazy.
Because challengers was easily one of my favorites of the year.
They also shut out his movie Queer with Daniel Craig, which I hated.
I get why that was shut out.
But he did, you know, call me by your name, bones and all, numerous other things.
Suspiria is great and it makes me wish you would do more horror.
He's really good at it.
I love the Tom York score.
I love that sometimes it doesn't quite work with the images, which really just makes the movie
even more unsettling.
And when it does link up, it's all the more effective.
The Gore, and this is awesome.
We discussed, you know, Tilda Swinton playing multiple roles in this.
Now that you know the secret, now that the movie's been out for six, seven years or whatever,
she plays many, many roles in this movie, including the fat naked witch, who's like shoving
stuff into her vagina at the end of the movie.
This movie's wild.
It's sexy as hell.
It was turning me on.
I got to admit, it's hot.
It's a bunch of hot dancers dancing and then demons throwing them around the room.
And if that doesn't sound like a good time for you, then then you're maybe
listening to the wrong podcast, folks.
I really enjoy Suspiria.
Had a lot of fun with it.
And that's what I got.
My last movie is, in fact, the odd couple part two, which we then watched.
And these three movies, to me, serve as a sort of perfect little trilogy, even though they're not.
And I'm excluding the sequel to Grumpy Old Men.
But, yes, I would, it's a answered question earlier, Pat.
Yes, I would 100% take the odd couple part two over Grumpy Old Men, 100%.
All right.
It's not...
I only saw it in the theater.
It's not great, but it has plenty of laughs.
And it's a different story.
It's like they're...
They have to drive across country together.
And then it's everything that ensues in that trip.
It's not just they move in together again.
Whereas Grumpy Old Men, too, or Grumpy Old Men, is just...
Now there's a new woman in town in Walter Mathau, who's going to fall in love.
But odd couple two is that the two of them reuniting in...
After I think they say 18 years, they haven't seen each other or something.
They still have the chemistry.
They still have the magic.
And again, Mathau...
Not undercutting lemon.
Lemon does have moments.
And his performance is great.
But Mathau really is what you're there for, because he's just so fucking funny.
And he's really funny in this movie as well.
It's the worst of the three I've talked about, but it's worth a watch.
My only gripe with it is they go too many times for like,
sight gags and things that are just corny, that they don't need to go for.
Because there's so much comedy and humor in just the way they interact with each other.
But what are you going to do?
At this point, they're all in their 80s, I think, when they made this movie.
So, or at least late 70s.
So, you know, you can't expect them to have their finger on the pulse
in the way they all did in the 60s.
But grump...
I'm sorry, odd couple two is a fun enough movie and an enjoyable film.
And it's one I'm glad I own.
So, check it out if you'd like.
And that brings us...
Right?
Or did you have one more?
We just don't think...
Don't forget.
Okay.
That brings us to the old man of the day, of the hour.
The boys of Conclave, the priests and the bishops and the cardinals and the popes of Conclave.
Yes, it is a movie, a thriller, about the process of electing a new pope,
the backstabbing, the behind the scenes, the private chamber's discussions,
the twists and turns that go on, leading up to the election of a new pope.
And the candidates are Ray Fines, who at first does not want to be pope.
But little by little, he impresses people with his actions and becomes a viable candidate.
Stanley Tucci.
As sort of a modern liberal pope candidate.
John Lithgow, as a less liberal candidate.
And then other people who I don't know the actor's names, but you have sort of extreme,
almost fascist candidates.
You have people represent all sorts of spectrums and beliefs and viewpoints within the confines
of the Catholic Church. And Joe, you can take it from there.
It's basically, it's a mix of like, what's the Tom Hanks?
Da Vinci Code type, biblical type thriller.
There's an element of kind of a agatha Christie murder on the Orient Express vibe to it,
even though there's not dead bodies piling up.
There's, it's got kind of that clue feeling.
And because of how hammy Tucci, Lithgow and Fines can be, I would love to see a version of this movie
where they all ham it up about 25% more. And it's like a clues style comedy.
I think that would be a great take on this material because those guys are so good at that.
I love that.
But you watch them all, you know, they all have that twinkle in their eye.
They all know they have good material.
And the performances are kept pretty, pretty straight, you know.
It's a movie that could have become a parody or like a, you know,
eyebrow arched kind of almost like a doctor evil, like, you know, people sneaking around.
And it doesn't go that far, but it still is just a very fun modern mystery to watch
in the way that like knives out is. We just don't get well-written, well-constructed
mysteries like this anymore. So I really enjoyed Conclave, Joseph.
Yeah, I enjoyed it as well.
Yeah, I was having a hard time putting my finger on it, what type of thriller
it mimicked, or not mimicked, but resonated with.
It's, to me, it was a little less of the movies you're talking about and a little more of like
the insider, you know, like a political or newsroom kind of thing.
I loved it. I love movies about this stuff because I grew up in the Catholic church.
And, you know, even though I'm not really a huge fan and I don't practice anymore,
I just find the organization to be fascinating in many ways.
The structure, the corruption, there's a lot to it's like the way people are fascinated with
government. And I find stories that take place in it to be riveting,
especially ones like this that really get into the dirty doings and how corrupt it is and
the politics and all that stuff. Everybody brings their A-game to this. The movie is also a very
fascinating commentary on the masculinity of the church, the patriarchal nature of the church.
And I think it was a very bold move to cast somebody as renowned and respected as Isabella
Rosalini as the primary female character in this movie when the whole point of that character
was for them to show you how ignored the female voice of the church is. And I thought that
in and of itself was a statement, not putting an unknown into that role because it only had three or
four lines. But putting somebody you usually see, you know, blaze across the screen and get to do
all kinds of heavy lifting and emotional, explore emotional depth and all this other stuff to put
her in a very reserved, very quiet role. I thought was a really interesting statement, which is why
I think the nomination for her is kind of crazy because it's like she's good in it, but the whole
point of the character is that she does not get much to do. That's the point. So also a big history
of her mother portraying nuns and the Oscars like to, you know, award that shit history and stuff.
Ingrid Bergman was her mom played a bunch of nuns back in the day. Yeah. So anyway, the,
the, the, the pattern he said the plot, I mean, the plot really hinges though on that at the,
it emits the proceedings or the eve of these proceedings to elect the new pope. A
cardinal, I guess it is, appears suddenly that they had no record of.
And he was a cardinal and Baghdad, but he is from Mexico. And nobody knows where he comes from.
If he's an imposter, if he's legit, if he's not legit, whatever. And that sort of spices things up.
There's a pope from South Africa, who is, or sorry, cardinal from South Africa, who is the
leading candidate to win. He's a black pope. And then some scandalous stuff comes out about him.
And they start to get into the racial elements of that. Like, you know, in fact, one of the cardinals
says at one point, if this guy, if this candidate was white, we would be announcing him right now.
So it doesn't really pull any punches. It kind of gets into the dirty,
icky stuff that none of us want to recognize or talk about when it comes to these sort of processes
about how much does get, how much focus there is put on race and gender and all this stuff.
Instead of it just being an open, even thing, it's quite challenging in that way.
And it's quite rewarding in its storytelling. And then ultimately throughout the film,
this dark horse from Baghdad becomes a real contender in this Pope race.
I mean, I guess we should just say the ending, spoiler alert, if you want to watch it, go watch it.
But this is, and it's a mystery movie. So, so yeah, shut it off if you want to watch it and be
surprised. But it ends with that guy ends up winning. He gets voted in because there are
scandals connected to every other candidate that gets close to the win that come out and get exposed.
Then you think it's going to be Ray Fines. And then it's not Ray Fines. It is actually this Mexican
cardinal that proceeded over the church in, again, Baghdad or something. And he wins. And then
there's a reveal that he was actually born a woman. But he always thought he was a boy.
By the way, he wins because of his, there's a terrorist attack on the church. And he
speaks very eloquently about what the Catholic's position should be during a time of attack like this.
Yes. And it's very beautiful moving. And that's why he wins the election.
Yeah. But yes, then it's revealed to be trans.
Yeah. Well, not true. Not trans.
Yeah. Yeah. So, so he's like, I always thought I was a boy. I always identified as a boy. I
thought out like kind of late in life because I lived in a poor village that I turned out to be a girl.
Yeah. But there was almost a, he called it his condition. There was almost a part where I was like,
wait, is he saying he's like, her mafruitic? Yeah, that's what it was. But, but anyway, he has both.
And that's kind of where the movie ends where it's like, okay, this patriarchal thing just nominated,
just voted in. Yeah. That's terrified of scandal and whatever else just voted in.
Technically, a woman who is identifying as a man as Pope, where does that end up? And of course,
they don't get into it. It just kind of ends there like with posing the question of where might this go?
It leaves you with a great discussion. I can imagine, you know, my dad teaches Catholicism
back in Missouri. I mean, this is a, this is a wet dream for him, this movie. Go out, have a piece of
pie and a coffee and discuss the Catholic church and this movie and what it means and what the ending
means and stuff. It's, it's, it's great in that way. That's why I recommend it with your Catholic
parents. You know, you can actually have a fairly interesting positive discussion about religion
for once in your life. If you watch this movie together and the ending does land. You know,
there's, there's, it walks a fine line because it is sort of a wild twist.
But it does, it walks a fine line and it does land. And, you know, that, that kind of twist would
have literally been, you know, and quite possibly in poor taste, like a fucking sitcom twist.
Yeah, 40 years ago, 40 years ago, 30 years ago, but you know, it's, it doesn't play like that here.
It plays very much like, okay, you know, that is, that is, it just, it lands. I don't know how to say it.
So it does. There's a bit in the end. There's a bit of a feeling of like, and it's a feeling I
don't like where it's almost like you're watching a parable or a Bible story where the symbolism is
so strong that it almost eclipses the fun of the story. And you're just like, okay, we're a little
heavy on the metaphor here, guys. I get it. And I felt like that for a moment at the end. And then
this twist at first, I was like, what are we doing here? And it's like, I think this movie just
wanted to be politically relevant. So they added this twist at the end. But when you step back from
it as Joe's saying, it does work. If you just shut off the part of your brain that's like, you know,
I have, and Joe has it as well, a part of my brain that is looking to be aggravated by things. And
that's how I felt at moments near the end of this movie, like it was jerking me around a bit.
But I want to really admiring it and enjoying it and liking it both for its message and the story
it had to tell. But also for the other elements, the fun and the great acting, it's, there's a reason
that that heavy hitters who could star in their own movie, like Lithgaal, like Tucci are willing to
play like fourth and fifth banana in this movie. It's because you rarely get like a great literate
script like this anymore. And I'm sure they were just pumped to have these great parts.
It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun.
It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It
is fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's
fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun
It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It's fun. It
was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was.
It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was. It was