Welcome to will see you in hell it's the movie show and I am Joe
and I am Patrick Walsh. Welcome everybody to will see you in hell we are
discussing the sketch comedy series I think you should leave on Netflix which
just premiered its second season and abbreviated second season with only six
apps which sort of makes me think that'll be the end of the road usually if
they cut your order it means they're kind of giving you one last hurrah in the
first series only have six apps who's sworn it had eight to ten but maybe I'm
crazy I often am you know oh look it up as you talk oh okay I mean I got it
up it's 12 up you know you're right six and six sorry Joe yeah I thought you
were wrong again well usually you get at least eight on the streaming world but
maybe I mean sketch comedy's tricky to make it maintain anyway we're here we're
talking about that show and I would like to get us if I may on with the show see
I've forgotten how to even do the transition anymore just stumbling through
and at the same time on with the Joe I don't want no scrubs the scrub is a
gotta can get no love from me hanging out the passenger side of his best friends
ride trying to how am I I like that right I like that it's good stuff I'm trying to
bring them back I feel like I did every song so I no scrubs feels new collective
soul I don't know if I've done that one before but hopefully not I don't think so
if you had to listen to one collective soul song for the rest of your life
what which one would it be it'd be the one from varsity blues which goes they've
got a long way to run oh it's it's a pretty song I don't like Sean no I don't like
Sean either but I would go with this song from the jerky voice movies gel
ban it ban it ban it oh let me go make it well yeah that was a good song look
they had some hints you know what if they're still around they're probably out on
those 90s you know gin blossoms tours I just saw next summer rescheduled they're
having at the Greek theater bear naked ladies headline gin blossoms opening and
toad the wet sprocket opening for the bulls that's that's a that's a that's a line up you know that's
horrible well at least with toad the wet sprocket you get they've got a couple tunes I like all
fall down was catchy I mean also sing oh no no no toad the wet sprocket no I'm wrong I was thinking
of cracker no I was pocket does suck actually I think I did do cracker that be with you girl like
being Joe hey hey hey like being Joe I think I did that one once I'm just looking at a picture of
collective soul how they looking I mean they don't they don't look bad they just they just are who
they are and that's what I'm bugging at well it's like the name collect it's what I was just
about to say like when when you're 13 and these songs are coming out you'd ever like think about
the band name but that name is so bad like why don't we make it like you know all of us have a
collective soul like it's a horrible that horrible I just found something called collective souls which
I believe is a collective soul tribute band oh no oh imagine telling somebody you're playing in a
collective soul tribute band oh okay it's just the fan page for collective soul okay are they
still making albums Jim Blossom are still putting out discs latest post 17 hours ago so this
group's going strong wow are they still making albums that I don't I'm gonna see if there's
anything here on the Wikipedia 6 who I always kind of enjoyed as sort of a sub foo fighters the
weasery you know kind of pop punk type band they had some good songs particularly
uh open road song which I love but they the lead singer of Eve 6 has become a huge force on Twitter
he's actually very funny he shared a lot of very revealing stories about his fellow 90s band musicians
he talks a lot of shit about the guy from third eye blind and he's great because he went on all these
big tours these shows with all these 90s bands that are now lost to time and it's worked for him
like the new Eve 6 album is like a bit of an event because he's been really funny and interesting
on Twitter so your career is never dead collective soul going strong 2019 was their last release
an album called blood okay critical reception one of the strongest albums of their career
hey all right good on yet CS rock pit stated blood has plenty in the tank
all music said at this point in their career collective solar acting like veterans playing music
that builds upon their older work music that ignores the present day by going deeper into the
familiar I guess that's negative if blood offers the kind of densely saturated melodies and hooks
that are collective soul trademarks it doesn't feel like a throwback oh nor does it seem like
a nostalgia trip and people are raving about this collective soul record it changed my life five star
what was Eve 6's big song they're big song with I would swell off the ride I would choke on the
right I would let the love will you may have to inside fuck them that's what I'm about to lose
I don't find nothing but faith in nothing I want to put my tenda hard and a blend uh awful
who's saying they're even bigger hit was the prom one uh here's to the times we feel to
life oh suck my dick Eve 6 what was uh they're they're fast punk songs they're gonna quote punk uh
like open road song are good and they they're kind of clever lyricists I don't hate them that much
and the guy's funny onto it you're right tender heart and a blender is lying you rarely hear a lyric
that insightful what was the uh who sang uh I thought they were I'm getting them confused who sang uh
bat bat bat bat down on the floor whatever it was called I was just about to bring them up because uh
I opened for them once local H I like that I like that song I don't know about the rest of it they
were awesome live very intense it was just a guitarist and a drummer and that song is called
bound for the floor but if it had been called copacetic which is how everyone in the world knows it
they'd probably still be around like anytime I've been like oh what's that song and you go to look
everyone's gonna type in copacetic and it doesn't come up right the copacetic they say copacetic
5 ,000 times and bound for the floor once it's like sometimes you try to get too clever with things
it's I always imagine these bands that name their band something that when you search it on Google
it brings up eight million results before your band like you can't call your band friends
there's a great band name friends but why are you calling yourself friends you're stupid
uh it looks like they're still around too look like a local H still around yeah they're playing
papian heriots I saw them on the calendar it looks like their main guy is the Scott Lucas fellow yeah
who is the guitar player and singer and it looks like everybody else kind of rotates in and out
yes they uh they did not speak to me when I was playing with them but they seemed like okay guys
and they were really really good life I gotta say they got a new record I'll call lifeers
2020 the picture I'm looking at of him he's wearing the Nirvana shirt except it says Rihanna and I
like the shirt and I wouldn't mind owning it look at this album features the band working with engineer
Steve Albini that's huge yeah appearances from Juliana Hadfield and John McCauley of deer tick
okay four out of five stars on all music okay album was preceded by a single called Patrick Bateman
and it also features a cover of Motorheads we are the road crew as a B side I gotta check this record out
folks welcome back to Joe and Pat Reed Wikipedia pages for lost 90s bands that's a new podcast
yeah I would recommend going to one of these like summer fest shows with five or six 90s bands even
if you don't like all of them the crowd is drunk as fuck um it's a lot of like women who love sugar
rape back in the day so like it's a lot of like real sloppy you know falling out of their tank top kind
of kind of ladies it's fun it really is fun I don't mean sloppy physically I mean sloppy drunk no I
know it's you mean I know which I was talking to our listeners not huge I know you know I know you
always give me the benefit of the doubt always always yeah what's new in the world of I'd like to start
by you're talking about John Mulaney this really doesn't fit into anything we're talking about but
I have been returning to the stand -up comedy stage I'm going to see Joe out here in a few weeks which I'm
very excited about thank you I saw Mr. Eddie Pepitone Monday night one of my favorite working
stand -ups he did not disappoint although it was definitely sort of an eye opening look at what
flies and what doesn't in LA comedy now because he had an opener who was very much you're like
wearing a sports jersey kind of guy and like his second joke involved in making the jerk -off motion
and the crowd shut down in a way I've I've never quite seen before he had to eventually start talking
about how bad they were but yeah there's just certain things it seems like you're not going to be
able to talk about for a while but Eddie was very funny and then last night I saw John Mulaney who
for the last three weeks has been testing out a new hour at the Trubidor theater here in town
and I assume he'll be putting it up on Netflix or something but it's a much darker John Mulaney as
you can imagine he is recently divorced recently out of rehab he alludes to the divorce a couple
times but doesn't go into it I'm sure he's not allowed to but there is a lot of drug material
this guy you know I think a lot of people were like oh what do you do take a take a couple
adder all every morning or something it's John Mulaney apparently it's a it was a pretty debilitating
co -addiction that required a full intervention from a bunch of comedian friends a big chunk of it
is the intervention and him bragging about how star -studded his intervention was
which is great um but then man he he doesn't care anymore he basically talks about how he's lost
everything everyone that cared about him now doesn't like him he lost almost all of his money
wait why do people not like him I think he was referring more to his wife to his you know he's
like the people that cared for me all right me but yeah I mean I definitely wouldn't spoil anything
about it because he you know he's clearly trying to keep it under wraps but it was a great great hour
plus he did more like 90 it ends with a long thing that might get cut before it airs about how much
he doesn't give a shit about the environment that that was really funny and just really surprising
stuff from such a a buttoned up guy like that I I love this new direction for him being a guy who
was raised goody goody and Irish Catholic and now kind of acts out against it I always wanted to
see that darker side that I think lurks right beneath the surface with Mulaney and he he brought
it out in a big way I look forward to I look forward to seeing it and I'm honestly I knew John when
he started yeah and I used to show them back then it sounds like a return to his roots because
that's what he was like when he started the whole nice guy in the suit thing clean cut like that came
later that came as he became successful but like when he first started he talked a lot about coke
and like right it was still in the Mulaney fashion but you know right but he talked about blacking out
when you drink like it was a lot it was you know it was a lot heavier you know yeah that he almost
it's not like he doesn't use his vocal ticks and style here because it does but he he doesn't it's
way less it's not like he's like so anyway I ruined my marriage you know like he it's a different style
from him but it really worked I'm a obviously a much darker person than most so I dug it some of his
fans might not go with him but I loved it I look forward to seeing it I hope to see it that sounds
great you know the comedy scene here in New York has been pretty great it's been a lot of fun participating
in it again and you know you're seeing quite the opposite of what you described the LA audience
as being I'm finding that New York audiences are are showing a much greater openness
to edgy your stuff or more offensive material yeah and I'm also noticing that if you if you do lose
them on one joke they'll jump right back in with you and go okay you know yeah I saw a lot of that
I went I had to get out of Los Angeles for a bit and he was great but even him and he you know
his fans know what to expect with him but there were some stuff where people would really clam up
but then come right back on the next joke I mean it's interesting it's an interesting time I can't
imagine going out leaving your home after a year inside and not just wanting to laugh and have fun
but there are still people in LA who need to really perform and indicate that they don't approve
of what's being said well there's there's people in New York too I got into it with two of them
yesterday on Twitter but okay as I do you know me Pat I'm always you know I'm you know I'm a
I'm a dangerous kind of guy you know I'm always edgy yeah shoot from the hip sure well you're
always either completely off Twitter or arguing and sometimes it seems like the same hour really
that I don't understand what to do with it anymore you just I don't either I don't post anything
I don't know if I do I delete it yeah I'm like Jesus Christ that I was told yesterday
on Twitter that by a friend that that in a self -admitted communist that my affiliation with a certain
crowd of comedians was problematic and I said you're a communist do you want me to judge you on
only the bad communists right like where is this what is this logic that you have like you can't judge
a group entirely by a few people that's the very definition of prejudice right yeah go
with nowhere it doesn't matter it gives a shit everybody's a fucking moron anyway we made up
that we ended cordially it was fine I'm not gonna name any names I'm not gonna name names what are
my communists anyway literally the only reason I am on Twitter and it's it's it's it's complete
bullshit but in my mind I feel like someday even though it's never happened one of the many famous
people or people I admire or whatever will reach out to me and go hey let's collaborate that's why
it's never happened but that's why I leave it open yeah I feel like I follow Stephen Conrad wrote
the weatherman he's a showrunner now I'm like he follows me I follow him he's got shows going what if
he he would never in a million years DM me on Twitter to ask me to write for one of his shows and yet
that's why I leave it up and also when you leave up Twitter you are leaving yourself susceptible to
if you get a big job or announcement to somebody gone I'm gonna ruin his life and go back to the
twenty eleven days and see what I can dig up it's stupid why don't you have it I only have it I only
rebooted all this stuff because when we started to do taste buds yeah sad was plugging everything
on his stuff and I felt bad I felt like I wasn't carrying my half of the load so I reactivate
the stuff so I could equally plug and that was it and then eventually you get sucked back in yeah
and then the next thing you know it's just it's a shit show you know but so it's very easy for me not
to engage I do a screenshot I pass on to a friend and then it gives me the same effect as like
publicly going after somebody that's fair that's fair I'll give you that wash yeah I get a lot
of screenshots from you I enjoy them oh well thank you yesterday going back and we won't get into
them but holy god yeah losing their fucking minds man it's like what yeah do you have friends that
have lost it over the pandemic I certainly do I talk to them and I'm like you are not the same
well one of the friends that I was arguing with on Twitter yesterday well the only friend I was
arguing with on Twitter yesterday and I said I said we're friends just call me about this right and
they were like I'm not gonna call you and I go okay yeah you're right now let's do it here on
Twitter where it can be exploited right and they said we're friends I haven't talked to you in two
years and I said I'm sorry I haven't talked to you in two years I was wrapped up in a silly pandemic
which of course you make these logical points there none of them are responded to no ignored um and it's
just but yeah I know people that have lost their shit completely um and frankly most of them were
losing it before the pandemic hit the pandemic was just the beautiful icing on the cake I mean it's just
like you know you want to watch somebody finally crack and it's like here here you know but but
but yeah I know a lot of people that have lost their shit people don't know there are people that
just don't know how to interact where it seems we're seeing more and more of women crying and having
tantrums in public online and I'm seeing some of it in public myself in person yeah there's a huge
video that I sent to Joe and then he had a real -life story to share as well but this this lady who's
either she's unwell but she's also at some point clearly starts playing it up because she realizes
she fucked up she takes the swing at a black woman and a victorious secret then once she remembers
oh shit she's filming me she immediately goes into this marital street performance of like sobbing
and she's trying to blame the black lady and then she goes okay this isn't working I'm gonna
act like a completely insane person she starts vibrating on the floor like a fish literally it's
literally a temper tantrum it's a five -year -old it's a literal temper tantrum right it's a 35 -year -old
woman but she's like stop filming me and shaking around on the ground and it's it's scary it's funny
in spots and I watched these videos and Joe what I did not tell you is that they're they're released a
third video the final video and it's the black lady being escorted out of the store are you kidding
no so she'll have the proof she'll be able to say why do they escort her out I well this is
because it's awesome the step here's why I say that the staff I notice is black the girl that's
trying to get the white lady out is also black so I'm yeah my question is I'm not saying this woman
wasn't wrong or something I'm just saying like I wonder if she was escorted out because they were
like we have to defuse this this is insane and you're the only sane one here so let me get you out
of here and we're going to have to bring in the men and the white coats for this other lady yeah
I don't have all the facts I mean but this uh there are white ladies in line who are like just leave
her alone to the black lady they're saying leave the white lady alone she's clearly unwell
but um my my point really is there's all these people in the comments like well why is she filming a
mentally disturbed person and it's like she's filming it because it's all she has if a cop comes in
and says oh there's a disturbance at victorious secret and they see a white lady
following a black lady around the store going stop filming they stop filming they could shoot the
black lady they'd go okay the black lady's the problem that's what black people in america are dealing
with and what they're trying to get people to understand smart people do understand this but um
yeah it was it was very unsettling very unsettling and and the lady I know it was keeping the camera
honored just like look at this lady pulls a gun out of her purse I want it to be on camera you know
because that's the thing we have to treat everyone with respect you can't say crazy anymore you can't
say insane anymore you can I think people still do but that they're trying to make that the new way
and the fact is we don't know if this person is fun crazy or gonna pull a machine gun out of her
purse you know and you have to act like it might be the latter or else you could be risking your
fucking life well I think I think that all of that's true I also do think that some of these
caring videos and I refuse to use the term caring because I think a slur is a slur is a slur and I'm
just I'm not in the practice of it but these videos that come out I think some of them are truly
mentally ill people that are being exploited and I think and then I think some of them are just
awful human beings yeah that are doing terrible things look people it's an unfixable dilemma I
mean it's just you could you could dissect this every which way it doesn't matter it's unfixable it's
unfit we live in an unmanageable country it is unfixable it will never ever ever get better until
there's a major reset which I think is kind of coming soon yeah I'm not sure what form it will
come in but I think we're teetering on it but I feel that way I felt that way for a long time and
these videos I think are even further proof of how fragile this all really is you know it's you
can't even have a logical conversation online with somebody with a differing opinion than you can
or anymore it's impossible it's literally impossible people just want to be awful to one another
yeah no nuance no understanding no nothing no I hadn't thought of it that way I don't agree with you
but that's interesting though those phrases are gone from human vocabulary and you know and it's just
it's just it's just this it's just this terrible thing we've been reduced now and then and then
you you you compile that in with all the years of prejudice and unfairness sexism misogyny
hatred of a class whether it's the rich or the poor class unfair demands on either class it's
it's just the list goes on and on and on and on and on and on and on it's such a complicated deep
conversation you would have to have and we're reduced now to putting each other on display that's
like what we're reduced to whether it's for justice or whether it's for the wrong reasons or whatever
whatever it's for that's what we've been reduced to now is capturing one another and putting one
another on display yeah locating what a person's biggest weakness biggest failure worst thing
they ever said locating that and putting it on display so as to end their life and you know everyone
is doing it everyone has one of those things so then everyone acts out trying to find it in others
almost so that you don't find out what theirs is and it's just gross it's also gross to me it is gross
it is gross and it's only going to get worse because sadly this is a sad truth and I always look
for the balance and everything and I know I know that there are groups of people in this country
and genders of people in this country that have had it far far worse than others I'm not I'm not arguing
any of that but the sad truth at this point is we're at a place where for every video you can see
of a white woman acting disgustingly to a black person that we think justice should be served
because of the incident and we're an agreement on that there's also a video of white people
standing over people eating at a restaurant screaming get your fucking white own business out
of this neighborhood or whatever you know it's so it's like how how could you ever fix these issues
when when both sides of this are that extreme and that irrational and that gross and their behavior
and whatever and it's just it's a fucking it's done we're done we're done so let's talk about movies
one one quick point and then we will get to this movie corner I'll take us right there but this
is a little personal my wife and I Heather well I love very much have been discussing pulling the
goalie and going for a baby and all through the pandemic it was like well we're not going to do it
before we know if the world is going to continue and now that it seems like it might we've got
lingering pandemic stuff we've got this like racial pot just waiting to boil over we've got like
everyone is angry everyone is disgusted nobody's listening all the problems we've just been talking
about and I said to my therapist like we're really at this place of like do we want to bring a kid
into this world with the environment for god's sake I mean they're talking about this being the
hottest summer on record and all sorts of stuff coming our way that's bad in terms of global warming
and the oceans and etc and her point was very simple who will stand up for what's right and good
in the future if good and right people don't have kids and it's the only kid discussion I've had
that ever hit with me you know that that ever connected with me I was like you're right you know
we might be having a kid who will be wiped out in five years by the all incoming plague but if not
you want to have good kids out there good people you want to keep making them however I can't shake
this fear that I'm I'm having a kid who will inherit the road the Cormac McCarthy book you know yeah
I think you've turned this into a terminator scenario where you're potentially birthing John Conner
which is fine I'm not saying I'm saying he's that he's another little warrior in the John Conner army
I'm not saying I'm giving birth to John Conner you never know one of the guys who steps on a school
with a glowing red eye look I'll tell you my take on it I'll tell you my take on it you know I don't
know if you want to hear it or not yeah I know I do I do my we talk very dark about baby in the
South we have a very dark conversation the scrutiny that we are all under by our fellow human beings
these days I can only imagine is amplified 20 ,000 fold when you bring kids into the mix yeah I do not
in any way want to be at the mercy of a system and helicopter parents who think their children
are the most wonderful beautiful things that have ever lived that are unable to do anything on
their own that need to be pampered 100 % and will then come into your life about your parenting style
if they don't agree with it yeah I think it's despicable and disgusting that there are child services
that will come and say we had a report pay us $500 right now or else we're going to potentially
press some sort of charges or whatever I think the school system is in certain states is
being wound back to a time period I don't remember or understand in its close -mindedness
and in other states is so disturbingly woke it's it's teetering on cult a cult and I think
and then the worst of all is what if I have a kid that doesn't see the things the things
the way I do in any way or doesn't agree what if I have a kid that is the person I hate the most
right then what do you do you know so yeah it's always there but yeah but you know so I don't know
you know but I mean the biggest thing for me is in this world
these people are telling you what they think about you and your life and your behavior when you're
talking your these people are trying to get you canceled over a joke from a movie yeah God forbid
God forbid they see you like yell at your kid because you're having a bad day and he's being an
asshole or whatever it is you know like a human behavior you know what I mean and they decide
we're bringing the torches to your place now that scares the shit out of me man
sure I don't think about that much but but yeah it's it's always been scary to have kids even even
in great times but I think now it's like is it worth it you know I don't know to mention not to
mention and it's these are things I would never uh you know obviously they're not interest of
mine or things I would ever act on but like not to mention like I can't even imagine a scenario in
which if I had a teenage daughter like a coming of age teenage daughter like 16 yeah and she's hanging
out with all her 16 year old girlfriends I'd be hard pressed to think of a scenario where it would
be appropriate for me to be in the room with them at this point yeah with with the with the scrutiny
around everything with that they're having a sleepover you think the days of the girls running around
their panties when they're 16 at your house those are fucking long gone and then God forbid
you encounter it accidentally because you get up to take a piss in the middle of the night or whatever it
is yeah that scares the shit out of me it's like it's it's just also well I don't know man I don't know
it would scare me more if we ever heard any news stories about somebody getting in trouble for that
which which we don't I don't so you know I granted you shouldn't have a bunch of 16 year olds
running around the panties at your house but I'm not saying you you're doing you're orchestrating it
I'm saying right right that's what girls do at slumber parties yeah and there was a time where as a
dad you know you could go all right girls take it upstairs and whatever yeah we all know what this
is go upstairs uh and now it's like if I saw one I would have a panic attack I would have a panic
a lot of stuff happens that doesn't go on in the middle doesn't make it a lot of horrible things
happen don't make it true but uh I'm saying you know it was never really acceptable you know but uh it's
I I hear you it's a it's a time where the bar is always shifting and it's it's that that's
sadly that's another reason I stay on Twitter is like I do need to know what is now considered not
cool so that I don't just go out say oh my god my my mailman is crazy and wind up getting
in trouble for saying that you know like I mean well though it's that it's but the other thing too
that's scary I come from a time where if you were to ask all of somebody else's house their parents
could yell at you you couldn't do that now sure you couldn't let's say my kids got a friend who's
a real piece of shit and I yell at the kid yeah now I'm in some kind of school trial
you know I mean it's just all so fucked up like it's just all so fucked up on the flip side my
friend nix mom kissed me full on the mouth once at breakfast it was like good morning she leans in
and gave me an almost lingering I would say more than one second kiss on the lips I loved it you couldn't
do that now no you couldn't you couldn't it was a it was a yeah yeah never mind you fucked you
fucked one of your friends mom said no no no I would have liked to yeah let's take us over to that
movie corner and out of this this thorny ground that we're currently in I saw as anyone who listened to
my my ramble on the solo movie corner knows I've been going through a bit of a time I've not
really had much of an attention span of late so I like to watch these kind of shows lately where you
can be on your phone and not miss anything you know stuff that's not particularly taxing on the mind
and right in that wheelhouse comes a little show called too hot to handle reality show on Netflix
where you bring in insanely hot people with all kinds of sexual chemistry and tell them
you can't fuck you can't kiss you can't touch and every time you do we're going to take $3 ,000 or more
away from the group prize money so everyone's going to split this prize money it's like a hundred
grand or something and every time somebody messes up some of the prize pockets removed the more you mess
the bigger the withdrawal if you kiss I think it's three grand if you fuck it's like 20 grand if you
do a blowjob it's 10 grand whatever this show you know it's almost like a fake 30 rock show it's so ludicrous
I watch season one very quickly I watch season two just as quickly season two is kind of funny because
in season one they're all like guys we can't blow this and everyone's getting horner and horner but
they're all pretty much respectful of the pop and you spank it no oh jeez and they have cameras
everywhere so season two there's cameras in the bathroom when you shit I believe yeah I don't
think they'd ever air it but there's cameras so season two is very much everyone's like I don't
care if I lose this money for everybody every morning they go in and like three of the couples have
fucked they've lost like 60 grand by the end of this thing there's no money left in the pot they
have to redo the rules because these people are fucking so much and both are equally entertaining it's
fun to watch hot people fuck and season one was fun to watch hot people not fuck and look these
reality shows are not gonna not going to win any awards but they're they're very well done
the people are truly hot as shit and stupid and funny and if you're looking for some
mindless entertainment in an exotic locale you could do a lot worse than TH TH too odd to handle
before I say what I saw I want to clarify when I my summer party in the panties
scenario I meant I meant like a like a like a t -shirt with yeah with just I didn't mean like
running around in bras and underwear I don't even know if that happened outside of 80s movies if
10 girls would be running around the house and t -shirts and panties but maybe I never saw it with
my sister and her friends I know a guy I this got planted in my head I knew a guy who told me once
that his 17 -year -old daughter's 17 -year -old friend yeah and he was a very attractive dad
came tried to come on to him and he had to very carefully diffuse it like right because he's
like even in diffusing it you could say the wrong thing and then it flips on and I was like that
Jesus Christ that scared that scares the shit out of me anyway sorry and then you watch
American beauty from from 20 years ago and I remember watching that with a sold out house Kevin
Spacey did I mean another sign of the times changing but Kevin Spacey lusting after this girl who I
believe is 15 in that movie everyone's laugh it played as as broad comedy it was yeah and could
you imagine calling a girl's dad and saying your daughter is trying to have sex with me she needs to
be out of my house do you think that dad's gonna go I believe you absolutely not anyway
I watched I rewatched midnight run all the best what a wonderful film yeah if you haven't seen it
you got to see it I got sad while I was watching it because there was talk for a while that they
were gonna do a sequel with Groden and De Niro obviously it didn't happen and then Groden it's
fun IMDB so it must have made it pretty far down the road yeah Groden's dad it's it's it's it's a shame
because there are two characters that I truly would have liked to have seen like what if these guys
ran into each other again 30 years later whatever it was but it's just a fun buddy it is the it is the
the next to Plains trains and automobiles it is the prototypical like buddy road trip movie
but it plans transit is the comedy and these movies came out and essentially the same year to show you
how good cinema was just not that long ago Plains trains is the comedy version and midnight run it is
just as effective both dramatically and comedically but it throws in the fact that it's an excellent action
movie too it's it's kind of amazing really yeah it's a fun flick it's a fun flick and then
and the great late Dennis Farina hilarious again just steals the show like just John Ashton is hilarious
in that movie the late great yacht that Koto is hilarious in that movie he's great yeah the Joey
Joey pants is hilarious in that movie Ashton on the bed just shoveling to the two cheeseburgers and
fries into his mouth and the guy handcuffs to the radiator like can I at least have some fries
that's how the scene starts it opens and you see Ashton eating on the bed and it cuts away to the
guy handcuffed and he goes can I at least have some fries which is great writing or editing or both
because any I love any joke like that where it sets up you immediately realize the 20 minutes
that preceded it in the conversation right and then Ashton mouthful of food says I already said
no pecker breath and then starts smoking mid meal I mean he's just he's out of fucking control
in that movie he's awesome and De Niro you know it's classic you're this is right around like good
fellas De Niro man you're getting like this is prime time De Niro here like it's crazy how much
De Niro started mugging almost immediately after this like this was you know Brazil's a comedy I
kind of that he was in but this was really his first big like I'm gonna do a comedy movie and he
plays it zero different than he would play a good fellas or any of those movies yeah you get to
analyze this and it's more of like a cartoon a caricature a rocky and bowl winkle or something like
this was really that line where like Groden and De Niro are just playing it completely straight
it is written so perfectly everything plays out great the heart almost sneaks up on you with the
visits to to Groden's daughter and then at the N .C. and the next line the Niro's daughter the Niro's daughter
yeah it's a great film yeah the the what's it called and my favorite sequence is on the bus
because it's so clearly predominantly ad -libbed and like yeah one point like Groden is just going like
why would you do that you know second -hand smoke oh come on why don't you put the cigarette we keep saying
why would you do that yeah and the De Niro at one point starts laughing and you're like they're
ad -libbing this like yeah clearly it's just and then that scene is my favorite line in the movie you
like here's two words for you shut the fuck up incredible yeah yeah the chorizo and eggs run which was
also improvising it's a delicious Mexican sausage it's so good the that's the scene where she goes
what do you have Eddie Groden looks down at the change pile that's all they have left
he goes how much is coffee she goes 85 cents he looks at the change he goes how much is tea
she goes 85 cents looks back at the change all of the tea yeah it's and the litmus test on the money
that whole scene it's just classic after classic moment if you were in the LA area I will be seeing
my co -host Joe do stand up this night but on July 24th I want to say at the arrow theater in Santa
Monica they are showing two Martin Breast films Martin Breast career was killed by Glee but he
also did send a woman another you know eight hours I believe right no Walter Hill no he did Beverly Hills
cop that's what it was sorry and he did midnight run and Martin Breast will be appearing live before
the screenings it's a double feature of Beverly Hills cop and midnight run with Martin Breast an
attendance moderated by Paul Thomas Anderson who is coming down from from his castle wherever
he lives to interview Martin Breast which is awesome so if you're in the LA area I'm sure it's
close to selling out but check her out my second is a great new documentary series on Netflix called
This is pop and it walks you through the history of pop music it starts with boys to men
and I love boys to men I always love boys to men but it talks about basically how their sound
was then taken and blown up to a much more commercially successful
place by your boy bands and it's simply because they were white so all the backstreet boys and in
sink and 98 degrees they're like we carefully studied boys to men and did every single thing that
they did like they fully admit it they're like we were just doing what they did well boys to men were
huge they were huge yes they were huge that's not making it sound like boys to men didn't get any
love they were huge no no no and the the show is extremely well balanced in painting all sides of
this where it's just like yes but these guys took it and really ran with it so it's not it's not
the same as Elvis taking blues music and making five billion dollars while the blues artist died
penniless but you know it's it's a it's a it's a very well balanced well researched documentary about
pop music in the modern day and the boys to men episode is great but my personal favorite was the
episode about Swedish pop and the and how it led to backstreet boys Britney Spears etc.
kicks off with abba and the Eurovision days you get a great little look at abba it goes up through ace
of bass it goes up through again to your to your Britney Spears baby one more time and all these Swedish
producers you see the closet size studio where they would record all this Swedish pop and all these
big stars would fly too Sweden to go to like use their their incredible pop music gifts and they had
they were like how did the five backstreet boys fit in here it's literally like a broom closet but um
look I know everybody doesn't love pop music even the stuff I don't love I'm just a student of
of the history of music I always love this shit I'm halfway through the series it's very well done
check it out if you have any interest at all in the history of music uh I watched um an allen
alde film yeah one old the directed by allen alde the four seasons it's not a good director
Alde uh I enjoyed this film it was very very woody Allen Esk it's about it's about four three
couples that go on vacation together every year uh and they do a different vacation every year and
uh after the you in the four seasons it's a it's a story and four acts that takes place each one
is one of the vacations during one of the seasons and um after the first vacation um the allen
alde's best friend reveals that he's leaving his wife and that their marriage is not working
and then he starts dating a much younger woman and the second vacation is the first time he brings
to the young woman out with them uh and it's about them adjusting to this major change missing the
best friend that was that was his wife uh and learning to eventually accept this new woman he's
dating and realizing it's more than just a midlife crisis like you know he he actually does love this
woman and she does love him and and and that they are being a bit unfair to her because they're angry
about him divorcing the other woman um and they don't paint him as a saint or anything they
they do plenty to point out his flaws and and uh you know the bad stuff about him my my favorite
character in the movie is I forget the actor's name but he's played by the guy that plays the
asshole and the monsters are on maple street and on twilight zone and he also plays the the bar
he's in the barred episode where he summoned Shakespeare to write for him uh for his Hollywood scripts but
that guy's great he and he plays like a hypochondriac dentist Carol Burnett right Carol Burnett plays
Alda's wife she's fantastic in it she's really the funniest person in the entire movie uh there's a
scene where she's fighting with him without Alda and he's like I don't like to get angry I don't like
to yell and she's like well you should try it sometime like does like one of those like Carol Burnett
that's so insane sounding um she's great in it the the woman that plays the younger one you've
seen her in a million she in fact she was in in search of darkness too she was in a sandy dentist right
yeah sandy dentist um she was a diploma actor for a little while there
and the other actor I'm not I don't know his name uh but his wife is portrayed
by the woman from who's afraid of Virginia Woolf uh and that's that's sandy dentist that's sandy dentist
yes the other lady from the diploma uh uh oh wait not diploma I'm wrong I'm not
diploma she's the lady from um now she was on phrasier she played like a newscaster on phrasier
what the hell else was this lady and that's Armstrong from my so -called life I'm looking at the
cast I think that's her yeah I think she missed the mom on my so -called life yeah anyway charming film
starts a little slow but it does get it does get very funny and it's very charming and you know
and I think it's pretty reflective of how like couples are uh you know friendship groups of couples you
know like I thought it was pretty it played that pretty true so okay uh my last one is an all -time
classic that I do to my obsessive love of movies when I was a kid I watched a lot of the the greatest
movies of all time when I was too young to understand them I would watch these you know 50s classics when
I was 10 years old and I often didn't know what was going on so revisiting them as an adult
is a lot of fun for me uh and of course you have the whole new perspective if you watch a movie 10
years after you first see it but uh all about Eve all about Eve with Betty Davis this is the it's
still referenced all the time although I don't know how many people are still watching this movie I think
people referenced it without having seen it but um came out in 1950 and it and it's
basically it one best picture it was it was widely acclaimed at the time one best actress for uh
Betty Davis and the movie is a story that has now become you know one of one of the classic showbiz
stories that you see played out again and again where a young up and coming actress idolizes the older
more established actress and at first it seems very sweet and she loves her and respects her but
little by little you start to realize that she's trying to cut her legs out from under her and become
her uh you see this even when it's not done in Hollywood you see it in a lot of thrillers like
single white female kind of tells the all about Eve story it's a it's a template and usually the
template movies for these the the uh the genres that last for hundreds of years are kind of boring
because the formula has been perfected and done better elsewhere but all about Eve is still really
fucking great the script is just it's one of those fifties movies where every line is a killer uh
the cast knows they've got great material and they're just digging into it it's very very funny
it's very dark it's very bleak it's got a real disgusted look at Hollywood and actors in particular
and aging in Hollywood and how you know you can't trust anyone in Hollywood so obviously this was
right up my alley um I highly recommend that if if you've never seen it it's a it's a real juicy fun
you know it's 220 but but flies by the dialogue is is lightning fast I dug it check out all about
Eve you never saw um I uh oh since you mentioned them I'll close out with this film I wasn't feeling
quite depressed the other night enough wasn't feeling quite in dark enough a place so I put on
boogie nights see if I could just send it right over the edge um it's a masterpiece of a film I mean
there's there's not much to say outside of that it's a brilliant brilliant film every part of it is
absolutely perfect yeah but Jesus Christ dude I just I don't think I remember just how dark it gets
in that second half where it's like for the music it's like bum bum that's the score for like 20
minutes of the movie yeah and you got like Cheatle going into the donut shop you got oh that's
one of the great scenes though what a scene that is yeah you got the roller girl thing in the limo
is brutal uh that's that's tough yeah you got and then and then Walberg Walberg having to jack
off his donkey dick in a van it's just oh my god and when he's just sitting there going do you know
I am I know I am yeah I was like oh god and then the tremendous finale with them going into the
Alfred Molinas house which I never realized until this what I've seen boogie nights many times
this was I felt like I understood the movie more than ever this time because I never real not
that I didn't understand it before but I was just getting it in a way that I hadn't previously got it
and and and and uh that Molinas sequence is so funny like it's and I never realized how funny it was
but like John C. Riley jumping every time that the fireworks go off Walberg's Walberg's like
Nicholson in the shining face when he's just like staring like this is my life now and they're
zooming in on his face that to me is one of the all -time great shots of just like who hasn't been there
if you live an edge of your life like Joe and I do who is who hasn't been there where you're sitting
in a room and just like I need to get my fucking shit together immediately yeah that's uh
Jay Oakerson always points that out of like the the just hanging on his face he's doing that smirk
and then like he just started he starts holding his head like
Walberg really shines in that movie man um it's just the caprio wow and he did Titanic instead
and I think that was the right move I don't think Walberg's a great actor but the you know he's
effective the dumbness that he brings to the part the caprio wouldn't have been able to do he's
truly dumb and so he makes the character work he's better than the caprio he's he's perfect in that
role he's absolutely perfect in that role uh it's it's it's in a it was an amazing astounding debut from
an actor which is why it infuriates me now that they cast him as college professors and things um yeah
but uh you know Bert Reynolds top of his game man like this is like Bert Reynolds you know you're talking
you're talking smoky in the bandit you're talking to the best of Bert Reynolds here uh and um
yeah it's just wild you know that whole end sequence where they all kind of start to go on to do more
you know at the time what would have been called legitimate pursuits you know Amber goes on
Julia and more amazing when she that that scene I mean they her Walberg and Heather grand play
coaked up so convincingly yeah that I'm more is it also a very good at playing coaked up yeah and I'm
like are they on coke right now like I'm just like Jesus Christ man like it is so real well Paul
Thomas Anderson was a million percent on coke throughout this entire 10 year period and if you
listen to the commentary on boogie nights they're all wasted on something they're all drunk and
on something well there yeah when she's pacing around and like yeah walk I don't want to leave this room
neither do I you know like I'm like too many things too many things too many things yeah and then um
but at the end when they all move on to these other pursuits it's it's just perfectly poetic that
pervert Reynolds and Walberg are back where they truly belong which is right doing this movie
you know what my only criticism of the film is this I don't like that in the last monologue he does
of Brock whatever the Chess Rockwell whatever his name is I don't like that in that monologue he's
still being the characters still being misogynistic because because he says he wants to do that when
he first says he wants to do the character he goes I don't want to do that what John Holmes is doing
with that Johnny Wad character he's he's misogynistic and he hits women and whatever which is a weird
reference because this is so derivative of John Holmes's actual life right but anyway um he says that
and then the fall from grace is of course you start to see go to shit and you start to see him playing
the character Walberg playing the character exactly how he said he didn't want to play it where he's
like hitting women and stuff in the movie and being rough and being gross and it upset me that in the
end he doesn't it's a word there's it's a moment of redemption and I just thought like the character
shouldn't still be misogynistic it should be like we've kind of come to our senses here and like we're
doing what we set out to do originally again you know or whatever but that's a tiny criticism and I'm
sure PT Anderson has a very valid reason as to why that is not the case yeah I mean there's so
many movies now that that especially when they're ripping off Scorsese and especially with crime
films you're just like I mean did you guys even try to do anything you're on your on your own did you
even try to take this in a new direction boogie nights is in a way good fellas it is in a way Nashville
Altman's movie it's a combination of the two I mean those influences are are screaming out when they
do the one last thing bit in boogie nights and that's the real dark kind of coked out section
that is good fellas but he puts so much of his own spin and shit on it that it feels completely fresh
and new while honoring those influences if you really want to put a gun in your mouth Paul
Thomas Anderson was 27 when he made boogie nights the dude is is one of the all -time greats and boogie nights
you know look I love there will be blood I love every movie he's made sometimes it takes me a
while to get there but I love them I I think there's a there's a habit now of people dismissing
boogie nights as being like this oh it was just kind of a big stupid a funny movie and then he got
really serious and it's like no no boogie nights is probably his masterpiece in my opinion I agree
I agree and speaking of masterpieces we move on to the newest and absolute greatest sketch show on
comedy television these days as Pat pointed out to me we're texting the other night
it's almost alarming to laugh at something genuinely now yeah and everything is designed to make
you go that's clever like but belly laughs are a thing of the past and this delivers them in spades
yeah I think you should leave by Tim Robinson which I so Tim Robinson was on SNL for a year
of course they got rid of him because he's brilliant not saying that brilliant people don't stay
but they tend to always get rid of since the people they do get rid of always tend to be brilliant
but Andy Sandberg and Tim Hi Decker and some other good people got behind him and
I guess helped him get this show made or at least you know he or at least jumped on board when he did
the comedians and then maybe the comedians came out of this his episode of or I'm sorry the characters
his episode of the characters on Netflix which is a show where six different comedians do their
own half hour episode where they play a character of some kind Tim Robinson's is by far
the highlight they're all very good but his is really just a shining star
yeah his whole thing in the casino his first sketch is super funny super fun yeah he comes into
in the Sinatra like luck be a lady guy and like and then ends up in the bathroom crying
and yes and shitting or something it's something so crazy it ends with this gun store sketch where he
keeps every he every time he try holds a gun he plays a scenario out in front of the gun store clerk
about a guy doing a total paint job on the toilet bowl and then blaming it on him and now he's there
to kill him for revenge and the first season the show came around and it was like it was it was
certainly not a letdown it was it delivered in spades there's amazing amazing sketches
in that first season my favorite of which is when a hot dog car crashes into a store and then
they're like who did that and he's wearing a hot dog suit and he's claiming that his car is not
the hot dog shaped car it's incredible one of my sometimes my favorite stuff doesn't even have
him in it hardly the Tim Heideker sketch where he's playing the way too old boyfriend at the young
people party who's obsessed with jazz it's amazing whoa boy that that sketch a hit home and was just
funny as shit yeah it's amazing it is amazing I've read a lot about him lately because I actually
really thought that he sucked on SNL and I was like he was a part of a bunch of kind of generic
guys that looked sort of alike that were on the show at the time and I was like what did he do
when this happened he was rarely on but he would he would have a few lines and leave and just be the
weird guy or something but every sketch or most of the sketches in season one were SNL rejects
there were sketches that were pitched that lawn Michaels turned down and if if ever there was a more
sort of screaming alert that lawn Michaels should probably not be producing that show anymore
and doesn't have his finger on the pulse of comedy because look at what they put on SNL week after
week right look at all these sketches that have you literally having to pause it sometimes laughing so
hard right it's insane to me that these sketches didn't connect I'm so glad somebody took a chance on
them because generally a guy coming off of SNL after being fired quickly who never got anything on would
not get his own sketch show but it's great that somebody over there recognized just the the brilliance
here because I'm going to disagree with you a little on on the it's a sketch show so it's going
to be spotty you know but season one I thought was by and large every sketch hit or for the most part
they hit and if they didn't they were short non -enough quickly season two holds up the same
standard although I think the last three episodes are way more missed than hit episodes four five and
six I think well so this is for season two now you mean for season two I think there is a slip there's
a there's a very lengthy sketch called Calico pants where he's like thought it was a masterpiece
this sketch with the two the two dots on the khakis or whatever yeah the setup is a guy pisses
on his pants by accident in the bathroom because he doesn't shake he comes out a guy in the office
is making fun of him and then Tim Robinson comes up and says the pants are made like that they have
those spots it's they're called Calico pants right and he shows them a website and then the
and that has these pants and then the twist is that that website is designed for men that get
made fun of when they piss on themselves and you have to donate to the website because now you've
used it to get yourself out of a bind and that right it just goes from there right right I personally
would have made that sketch one minute the sketch is probably 20 minutes and to me it was for diminishing
returns Joe thought Joe thought it was fantastic and that's sort of the beauty of the show is that
in talking about it with friends I was just looking now through a paste magazine ranking of every
sketch that's ever been on the show and several of my favorites are they have ranked at the very
last position I mean it's that kind of show it's the kind of show where you know on SNL if they have
one funny sketch during the week everybody agrees okay they finally got a funny one you know
this show it's so out there and so weird and it really is a good litmus test for people's senses of humor
that everyone completely disagrees on what the best sketches are and what the least funny sketches
are and that's the beauty of it I mean it's a risk taker it takes it reminds me of kids in the hall
more than it does an SNL where it's just a very singular vision they don't really care about whether
you like it or not and that's what makes it so so genius I mean the thing with the thing where he's
doing the the party is bombing and then he's like get my bag I'm gonna live it up to party and then he
just does the blues brothers the blues brothers dance and I was watching and I was laughing because I was
like I remember when they did this and I was like so many people are going to have no fucking clue
what this reference is there's the other reference that killed me where he's got the Carson impersonator
that he that he books at parties he the manages and then the other guy comes in and he goes that's our
George Kennedy I'm like nobody will get that but the people that do will think it's hilarious you know
yeah but um I think he was in a predicament this season because I you know there was a pattern in
the first season of an incredibly uncomfortable situation would get created and then he would flip it
100 % on its ear in the in the most opposite direction you could picture it going in and it got
to a point where you you became familiar with that rhythm and you were waiting for it excitedly
and it was fun I feel like in this season he was like I can't do that again because it's going to
be too predictable right so this sketches in this season a lot of them lean greater on the surreal
than they did in the first season and end in much more abrupt weird ways than the first season did
but everybody I keep talking to keep saying they like the second season better than the first season
I actually thought the first season overall was better but that said I love the second season um the
and I also didn't know this it's called I think you should leave because the hook of the show was
every situation is a situation that a person is desperately trying to get out of yeah and I guess
that is kind of true you know but this season episode one of this season I literally laughed I cried
multiple times I was laughing that hard though the ghost tour sketch where he keeps asking if the ghosts
pull out their cocks and shoot big wads on the and I was crying I was laughing so hard
ghost tours great I you know the blues brother sketch you mentioned for me it became a classic when
he takes off his blues brother's glasses and you see that he's crying that to me was when it took
like I love I love desperation sad especially male desperation sadness frustration and that's
what this show is but um for me the funniest was him and the the old man's suit at the mall doing the
prank show that's where I was really howling and it keeps getting darker and funnier and eventually
he has like a existential crisis and he's just muttering to himself that he doesn't want to be alive
anymore and around I don't want to be around anymore and then the prank show guys like you mean because
of the suit like it was killing me um for me there's no competition I watched the first season one
in one night alone I watched it in a hotel in Ireland with Heather we watched all eight all six episodes
alone howling laughing I watched it a third time Fred Willard playing the piano you know like
the baby of the year sketch with Sam Richardson as the host I thought was
just absolutely incredible and then that guy is also the guy that buff boys right
Sam Richardson is hilarious on these shows and buff boys is the hilarious sketch for sure
just making the guy come up and judge the the in -shaped children cocktail yeah I don't want to do this
I don't want to do the the consistency of season one I mean to me it's the difference between an
A plus and maybe a B plus the highlights of two are high indeed but I did think they kind of
in my mind did not deliver on the last half of the season but yeah people disagree with me
Odin Kirk sketched this season is great brilliant you know and and what I'm playing Odin Kirk
performer yeah Odin's taking it take like a dog with a bone he took that sketch and was like yeah I'll
give you the best it's sad it's like kind of haunting it's an amazing sketch playing the saddest man
of all time this it's so sad and it's like I don't know if they gave him extra crow's feet but
with the way he's smiling and you see like 800 crow's feet appear it's just like man it stays with
yeah then he start yeah that the he's telling the the he's lying he's telling a lot making up a lie
about a wife that he clearly doesn't have who's a super model then he starts getting it she got
sick she's she's she's gone now yeah she was a good woman coffin flop this year was another big hit
for me yeah that's one where it just kept the the the length of it is what makes it funny that there's
no amount of times you can see a naked guy fall out of a coffin that it's not just gonna be hilarious
no explanation why they're naked in the coffin whatsoever no explanation I did sort of
miss and and it's it's not fair it's something they they just happen to pick really really funny people
forte on the plane in season one as the old man is amazing they had amazing guest stars the
Vanessa Bayer sketched where all the women are at brunch shitting on each other is amazing
as I mentioned the Tim Heidegger and Tim Heidegger got a funny one this time out too the Andy
Samberg game show thing with chunky the the guy who comes out and it's like kind of threatening to
them there's so many great ideas well done almost without fail the sketches don't wear out there welcome
there's a couple that do I would say but it's just the best comedy thing of the last several years
in my opinion and the guy deserves a lot of props and he's giving them he only gets them on Twitter
but he's getting the respect that he's had coming for a long time I think I and I'll say it here
I'll say it here and you heard it here first folks I think Tim Robinson has a bright future as a
potentially dramatic actor I think he's a really good actor like he plays sad way too well that I'm
like he could play a good dramatic role I think definitely would be great as a stalker or killer or
something like that I mean he commits a thousand percent to all these parts he's very very good very
funny and he's got a real talent of somehow configuring his face to look as stupid as humanly
possible the whole thing that's the thing where he's on the couch Johnny blaze not Johnny blazes Johnny
whatever that shirt store is called Dan flashes yeah Dan flashes yeah and he's just
he makes himself look so stupid like he just has an ability to do it it's incredible he's just great
he's great I have mentioned on this show before and I'll mention it again if you if you watch
these and you absolutely should watch these sketch shows they are by the way they're not even
full half hours they're like 15 to 20 minutes so it's a quick watch but when you're done with that
circle back to Detroiters which was the Comedy Central sitcom starring and created by
uh Sam Richardson and Tim Robinson it is hilarious it's a little more straightforward of a sitcom but
when they go surreal or go to some of the weirder moments it is so hilarious are they both they're both
in it they're both they're the stars of it it's like the buddy show I guess now you'd watch it on
like the Comedy Central app I mean Comedy Central is basically not even real anymore at this point but
uh that show was great of course they canceled it ahead of its time there is a scene where Tim
Robinson is convinced that he's a great singer and he's trying to record their jingle because they
work at like an advertising agency it it I I never allowed uh when I ran writers rooms people to watch
clips in the room because it just distracts everybody but I remember bringing that clip in and just
it's one that it will kill with any audience he thinks he's an amazing singer and he keeps trying to
sing it every time his voice comes out it's like he's startled by how bad it is like it's not
matching up to how good of a singer he thinks he is and the scene is an a plus plus I'm I'm a big fan
of the guy outside of to see what he does next yeah one more from season one because you said singers the
Johnny Cash fake like the parody of Johnny Cash where he's the side kicks to backup singer yeah
and he keeps coming in with that line about the skeletons in the graveyard and he keeps going they
use their bones for money that's what pays to your list as the number one sketch uh they rank them
they rank all 55 sketch that was uh when I pinkstone watched the show initially before I did and he
and when he told me he goes wait till you get to this number sketch in this episode and I was and I
immediately called him and I was like the bones for money and he was like yeah and I was like
that was so crazy and so funny yeah I couldn't even it's one of those things I was like I don't even
read understand why I'm laughing yeah fully I fully don't even understand it's just funny yeah I mean
Tim Heideker being in this makes a lot of sense because some of the the more like Tim and Eric
it was two things it was either like drug induced disgusting insanity or like really a great sketch
writing and I think this clearly shares that influence of just like you're not quite sure what's
funny about it and you don't have time to ask because you're laughing so hard this one I mentioned with
Joe this there's a trailer for detective crash more which is like a Liam Neeson type movie yeah
and Santa Claus is the lead in it the actual Santa Claus but when they interview him at the press
junket he does the Billy Bob Thornton thing where he's like how the fuck you gonna ask me about
being Santa Claus I'm here to talk about my movie which I would bet every dollar to my name
that's how that started yeah sketch idea started with imagine Santa Claus getting mad like Billy Bob
Thornton did yeah well it's so funny the guy's name I just looked him up the guy's name is Biff Whiff
and he he is an actor he's been on Westworld and other things but I wrote Joe this is even though
he's only in a couple of these sketches I was like this is one of the greatest performances I've ever seen
when they show he's doing all the action movie wisecracks but they're all just a little off
so like he'll kick open the door and shoot a guy and it'd be like what the fuck's wrong with you
you're fucking idiot you know yeah it's hilarious I can't explain it right but this is gonna
fucking suck chief don't leave any cages empty because nobody's gonna be filling them or whatever
the fuck he says yeah all of the wisecracks just aren't quite right they don't quite make sense but
man it just keeps building and then when you hit that press junket scene that guy is unbelievable
yeah performance yeah yeah yeah the thing in the junket where he's going he's going you know what
that's called that's called my rate now they have to pay me that in the next movie it's just
if I don't do a good job they have to pay me $2 million yeah that was a favorite of mine and I also
respect that Tim Robinson when given his own show and his chance to shine after being fucked over
by S &L recognizes when he doesn't belong in a sketch him playing that Santa Claus role it would have
been nowhere near as funny he turns that sketch completely over to a no name guest performer and it
winds up being one of the one of the sketches of the series so he's a generous performer as well
yeah I agree like that and the because he very often gives the best stuff to other people that's very
rare in a sketch performer the woman in it the woman that he was she was in the last season two I
followed her on Instagram she's so funny I'm blanking on her name I think it's Ali something but
she's fantastic too she was the one in the printer that made the Santa Claus joke in the printer sketch
yeah she's awesome she's one of the recurring people like it's just a great show go check
Joe Bob says check it out yeah hogs way up for it I think you should leave and we all need a laugh
and it's a guaranteed delivery no matter what your taste you'll find something funny here I would say
if if my wife had not laughed at it I think I might have looked at her different I'll tell you that
yeah I agree all right folks that's our show we'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell one
quick plug Joe I'm sorry I did want to say in addition to appearing on Scott Weinberg's over hated
podcast discussing Freddie got fingered I am on the TX as in Texas forever podcast discussing an
episode of Friday night lights with two lovely comedians and that you can look for you know search your
podcasts wherever they may be that's dropping shortly I wanted to give them a shout thank you all
very much we don't know what we're doing next but we will be back as always thanks for bearing with
us being a little late we had a little drama a little a Wi -Fi issue etc thank you explained all
that yeah okay good I'm making sure well let's thank you that's a war on gate this quick wrap up
thank you for your outpouring of loves but I we I like to spend a little time saying thanks for
supporting us thank you thank you thank you we keep we the numbers keep going up and that can only
really come from you guys spreading the word and haven't you know we got the greatest fans we love
y 'all and I'm willing quite frankly to spread my legs for it I'll spread more than that baby all right
folks we'll see you next time talking about whole and we'll see you in hell