I'm here for Bett Rivers online casino and sportsbook with poker icon Phil Helmuth.
And now thanks to the excitement of Bett Rivers, I'm also a slots icon.
That's great! And a same game, parlay icon. Cool, cool. A blackjack icon,
a money line icon, a roulette. Take it from Phil Helmuth. If you love games,
Bett Rivers is the place to play in Bett. Bett Rivers. Games on.
Must be 21 plus in present in West Virginia. Void were prohibited. Terms in conditions apply.
gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamber.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fancash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fancash,
guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook, winning hits different here.
Monthly 21 -plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberler, offer not available in those days
terms apply, see Phenatic Sportsbook app.
Hey everybody!
Welcome to we'll see you in hell the podcast that is now a part of the
Fangoria podcast network for more information about the network including
other programs how to follow this show those shows other shows and find
past episodes of all the shows including we'll see you in hell please visit
fangoria .com now on with us patty do you hear that do you hear that do I hear you
talking you hear me talking but you don't just hear me talking you hear me
talking in stereo and in both ears as you are well that I didn't how would I
know I don't even have headphones on we don't need headphones all right and
we're both in stereo do you know why I know there's a supposed to be a format
change of brewing we're shifting the format a little bit on your favorite
podcast we'll see you in hell we decided to go
movie list for a little while, but stick with the theme of hell and seeing you
there and start discussing sinned each week, a different sin. This week we're
going to talk about gluttony. The reason for this is number one, we barely talk
about the movies. Number two, it's a pain in the balls set up. Right. Number three,
you know, we've got to focus on this thing that is just prompting us to have
discussion anyway right and here we are now we're just do you feel this do you
taste that cool crisp freedom right now of us just kind of we're just kind of
sitting facing each other we don't have headphones on there's nothing playing on
the TV well there's just chat here there's eye contact which is always a problem for
me but I can I can do my best with it I'm a lot like a shelter dog who would like
my dad has a shelter dog who I apparently was terribly abused and my dad always says don't
look it in the eye yeah and I feel like I'm sort of like that shelter dog I don't like
looking people in the eye even my girlfriend yeah I'll do it if you need me to do it I'll
do it well here you are we're face to face eye to eye yeah and what you can't see at home
is cheek to cheek as well yeah which is to butt cheeks to butt cheeks well then we wouldn't
be face -to -face. We're turning around over our shoulders, kind of like a
coy little cam girl. So we're also recording this live to the web nude as sort of a
cam girl thing. Yeah, so figured you and I both have the body types that the
single women of America want to see more of. Or the single man. Or the single man
sure. So donate your bitcoins now and see what you can get me to shove up my
asshole on this cam yeah we you know look we wanted to try something different
all things should progress all things should change and we felt that most of
the feedback coming in about the podcast was people enjoying the discussion
aspect significantly more than the movie aspect well there really was no movie
aspect because we were never watching the movies yeah we we we were watching them
they're playing but we didn't pay a lot of attention to by the way do I need to
shut this door. I think so. Cars going by is too much. I think so. We had the door open
here for it because it's a nice breezy night here in LA. There you go. Doors shut. Sorry
for that truck that went by. But the point is if you the listener are going to get essentially
the same thing out of this, whether we're watching the movie or not, why don't we just not
watch the movie and talk about our own lives and how they relate to sin every week. Right
And we can't just freely talk because that's not really a podcast can't be like pat and joke talk
So we got to make it about a sin, but rest assured
We're gonna go off on our old tangents and everything else. That was important to me when Joe asked me about this
I said I'd love to be able to kind of talk about whatever we want we can keep bring it back to that week's sin
Sure, but I want to be able to explore other shit as well. This sin is the movie now the only difference is we don't have to wear headphones
And we don't have to set up a whole god damn thing and stare at a TV. Exactly. Then I said well
We'll only get seven episodes because there's seven deadly sins. Joe says there's tons of sins. I
Googled sin list found a four -page list 130 sins on each page. Right. Baby. We're gonna be here for a while. Yeah, but this week
We're starting with a big one gluttony that you and I both I think suffer from quite a bit. Yeah, whether it's food
booze
drugs, yeah sex, power, it's just we just lead gluttonous lives. Yeah and you
know L .A. is a gluttonous place. It's not because people are eating very
healthy generally, but it's a gluttonous place and that everyone wants more
more more. Yeah. Longer you live here, that becomes your outlook and attitude
as well. And it leads to other sins, your bitterness, your jealousy, your anger.
Yes, and I think that all that we'll deal with in the future. I think that if you're
If you're here and you're not gaining more and more and more
You failed. Yeah, you should kill yourself
That's a little extra killing yourself also a sin is it that's for another week
No, but I mean it is true
We live in this town where we're the the motives of everybody are gluttony is our gluttonists. Excuse me
Yeah, there's also this strange reserve of like well, I don't eat this and I don't do that
And I don't drink this and I don't go there and then it makes a guy like me feel like a big fucking pig
Well until you realize that some people are doing this as well. Just in a closet manner
And that's why like you know, like I'll go home and
somebody will be like
Wow, so like are you guys just drunk all the time there or what happens then you'll find out they're a pill popper or
Some lady will be like oh, you know you drink vodka like on a random weeknight
That's crazy and then she's on her 12th class of wine sure everybody's gluttoness in their own way
Everybody's hypocritical in their own way. I agree. I agree. You want to hear what I did last night? Sure
Oh, there's a big one
Uh, I found a street
Near my new apartment that has a triangle formation of a McDonald's a Burger King and a
KFC slash Taco Bell. Oh boy. And I went, I almost hit all three. It wasn't a, they're
in the same building kind of thing. No, it's a triangle like two Burger King McDonald's
on one side in a perfect triangle point across from them is KFC Taco Bell. I didn't hit
all three. I almost did. But I was like, that's absurd. But I did, I went to KFC. I got three
piecemeal, two sides. My two sides were potato wedges and mashed potatoes with gravy.
Okay. Because I thought a lot of starch there. Going to be dunking the potato wedges into
the mashed potatoes with gravy. Sure. I call that a speed ball. Sort of like dipping a steak
into a chicken. It's more like dipping a chicken into a chicken. Yeah. Right. It's the same
thing. Yeah. Oh, that's true. Or it's like dipping a drumstick into chicken salad.
right right right uh and then I went across from to the Burger King and got a
Whopper Jr. with cheese and a bacon double cheese burger and I ate all of it
except the Whopper with cheese and a few of the potato wedges. Were you drunk? No
no see I would never do that sober. I was having a layaround day it was Sunday it
was a lazy Sunday sure I got a hankering for donuts in the middle of the
afternoon I went out I got three donuts when I went to get the donuts I
I spotted the triforce of these establishments
and then I said at dinner time I think I'm gonna go back
and I went back and did what I had to do.
Did you exercise?
Yesterday?
Yeah.
No, Saturday I did.
Okay, Saturday I walked 12 ,000 steps on Saturday
and I did upper body stuff.
Okay, I don't run, I walk as much as I can.
Right, and I did a, you know,
I jerked off my dick and gizzed some fat out of me. Yeah, that's not necessarily an amazing workout. It's not I
Got to get a new doctor. I'll tell you I have to make a phone call
It's also can be gluttonous as well with jerk off, but I guess that's a difference in problem. I think what yeah
I think what need refers mostly to food and drink food and drink. What's the last see my disgusting
you've had with some food. Well, I, you would never know it to look at me work out at least six days a week and that's the truth. I'll wake up and do it in the morning or I'll do it at night, and it's because my body, be it genetics, whatever else has just decided it's done processing that calories.
It looks to me all you work out is which ice cream you're going to eat that day that's hurtful job. I'm joking
But just kidding as with each year
With each year my body gives up a little more to the point where I
Will work on every day and see no results
I will not eat anything for a week and see no results and it's infuriating
it sounds like you've got some kind of a reverse cancer perhaps perhaps not eating away at you
it's like feeding you so if I'm gonna do like a real gluttonous type thing
it's gonna be maybe a once a month and what it would be would be like I would
have my standard breakfast lunch dinner and then driving home you have that
fourth meal or getting in a lift you get that fourth meal on a night of drinking I
don't do that shit anymore I try not to eat past ten if possible they say
not to eat, you know, four hours before you go to bed. But it becomes more and more
of a struggle and I can't really do it. I used to at least once a month get out, think
of ice cream and eat it, eat all of it. Now, I would say this is my night to do this.
No, hold on, a thing is a very broad measurement with a barrel of ice cream, a wheelbarrow, yes,
yes. I would get, you know, the, the thing, the, the bed and Jerry's, the pipe, no, no,
The bigger one you mean you'd get the gallon of ice cream half gallon, right you'd get the briars like that
Regular rectangular thing eat the whole thing in one night now very often
I would not finish it but that would be a goal and it was once a month and I was much skinnier because I would have
I worked with a guy who was like one day a week you go fucking crazy and the rest of the week you eat perfectly
Okay, I agree with that it worked for me for a bit and then it stopped now if I were to eat that ice cream
I would gain 20 pounds, but while while I was eating it, I would I would gain 20 what flavor would you get by the way?
I love a moose track. I love a birthday cake remix kind of situation. What brand of ice cream are you eating Willy Wonka?
Who makes those tracks as a readily available flavor and actually a bunch of companies make a moose tracks?
It's the most disgusting name for an ice cream flavor. I've ever heard well until I tell you that they're little bits of caramel or peanut butter covered in chocolate
And then they have a fudge ribbon that goes through the ice cream.
Yeah, insinuating that it's mousse shit that's been dropped on the trail.
Oh no, the tracks are like a footprint.
I don't know why that.
They're in the shape of a print.
What's the fudge swirl?
It's just a thick fudge swirl.
Yeah, it's somewhere in that equation is a shit representative.
I don't think so.
What is the track?
Like if you follow deer tracks, you're following deer's feet.
But what brand makes this for?
Every brand at this point because it's become very, very popular.
Who the fuck makes birthday remix?
That you priors any of them.
They all got a birthday cake flavor.
Birthday remix.
You know, there's a whole freezer wall of ice creams.
They gotta, they don't just have chocolate and vanilla, Joe.
See, I only see what's in the little pints
because I'm half civilized.
Sure. Oh, and I haven't done this in three years.
Fine. But I mean, it sounds like when you get
into those bigger portions, they know the emotions
you're dealing with.
And some different flavors come into play.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, so now that I do enjoy the occasional marijuana cigarette, I don't have food in the house
and I certainly don't have this kind of food in the house and if my girlfriend does,
I really just kind of have to block it out. You can't do both. Right. You can't have like,
you know, a wall of cookies in your house and smoked pork. I'll tell you what sucked was last night.
the part of it that sucked, the glutinous meal was tremendous. I enjoyed every bite of it
and you're stoned sober doing this. Stoned sober. And do you feel terrible immediately after
or wait till the morning or not at all? I didn't have a guilt. I just had a bit of a stomach ache
because I over ate a little bit. You don't feel any guilt eating all that. Now because I
ate pretty well all week and I didn't go crazy. Like I ate well all week. So was she kind of like
Okay, whatever.
Um, it was, you know, I didn't care.
But, and I knew today I would go back and, you know, this morning I ate for breakfast
eight, two eggs sliced tomato, a little bit of two pieces of bacon, for lunch eight at
chop salad with no meat in it, like, no dressing, you know, like, I knew I would dinner tonight
eight.
Keenwa vegetable soup, a couple of slices of turkey, I don't get the fuck.
But anyway, my point is this is, uh, I watched the Revenant.
Did you like it?
No.
Seriously, I love it.
Surprisingly, I didn't like it.
It's really, it's a strangely divisive movie,
because I thought it was just a fun action movie
like last -the -mo -week and there's something.
The whole time I was watching it, I was like,
this is precious in the woods.
You mean too miserable for it?
Yeah, it's just somebody at the mercy of their environment
and the environment does not let up on that.
It's just like, your life is gonna be shit.
Almost never had I felt a movie was too miserable.
Maybe that says a little something about the state of mind I live in.
Well, I, you know, we watch precious every Christmas in my family and you get the bucket of chicken.
She steals that bucket of chicken and runs with them.
I remember that part.
Yeah.
That's the saddest part is when she throws it up.
Well, the saddest part is when she gets AIDS at the end on top of every bed.
That would be sadder to me, yeah.
But her vomiting up the chicken is pretty rough.
Yeah.
But the, uh, but I felt like the remnant was the same kind of movie where it was like,
Like it was just thing after thing after it was like for Christ's sakes, right?
One of the things where they all, you know, smoke opium and dance around the campfires.
Even the friend, he makes spoiler alert, if you never saw it, I'm going to ruin something.
He makes friends with the Indian guy that like helps him heal and then they hang the Indian
guy while he's asleep.
You're just like, for God's sakes, give this guy something I rolled with him.
All he has to look forward to is murdering Thomas Hardy and then he doesn't even get to murder Thomas Hardy the Indian guy who yeah
That's suck daughter. They take or whatever
Murder I'll agree that that sucked. I was like why would we watch two and up two hours 45 minutes of a revenge epic to not let him get the revenge
He gets he doesn't get their revenge. Yeah, um, but I mean it was a well -done movie. It's like all that I forget the director's name
But every movie that guy every movie that guy does bird man the red all of them 21 grams
I believe he did yeah, babble which I love yeah, they're all movies where I watch them
I say this is really really nice piece of art. It's very well done
It's it's enjoyable to an extent, but it's they're just not my kind of movies
I think there's just a little two
They're they're dark in a I can't explain it. I'm not against dark movies. It's just there's there's there's somber and I think it kind of
gets me down. I carry. But I'm
bracing. I saw the witch on
Friday. I haven't seen any up
going Wednesday. Wow. Wow.
That's real fucking scary. Real
I've talked to other people who
were like, eh, they're no reaction
at all. Idiots. All right. Idiots.
Only hard movie I've ever been
in where there's a part. Don't
don't say anything as I'm seeing
it in two days. I'm not ruining
anything. There's a scary part
that happens about towards the
the end or three quarters of the way through.
There we go.
This is the only time I've ever seen a human being do this.
It ended, a guy goes, oh my God,
yells it out like loud in the theater.
Okay.
There's an audible laugh because it was such a true
like man being shocked and he got up and walked out.
And I was like, I've never seen somebody walk out
like in almost disgust.
I had, there was a lot of men screaming when I saw
the context in the city.
No.
The contouring and
There was the funniest ever reaction I've ever seen in a movie theater was when I saw
irreversible
Tells that gasp or no movie which has oh
Like literally a 15 -minute unbroken shot anal rape of Monica Baluchi. Oh, yes
I have seen that movie that's brutal and then that fire hydrant beating. That's the most disturbing. They've ever seen him
I'm watching this movie and this old man stands up in the front row
Lord knows why he was there it was 85 years old and he waggles his finger at the screen from like the third row and he goes
And left like it was the 30s Wow, and I was like I agree and that was fantastic
And I stayed and watched the whole fucking move strong now. I also when I saw the river wild with Meryl Streep
Which is an awesome movie actually never saw Kevin Bacon's the villain Curtis Hanson did it LA confidential fan
And at the end, Merrill, spoiler alert, movies, 30 years old, is reaching for a gun out of her raft and can't quite reach it. Pretty standard thriller move. She can't quite get to it.
And this old guy behind me goes, reach Merrill!
And I laughed hysterically. It was his genuine reaction to the movie.
When I saw Rise of the Planet of the Apes, loved it, the part where the ape talks for the first time, a guy behind me went, what?
And I was like, I don't understand what you thought, why are you here right now?
If you didn't know, this is where it was headed.
That was like a nature documentary.
Yeah, I was just like, this is a guy that just likes an ape movie.
Yeah.
Look, I get it.
I'll say this about the witch against not ruining anything it's not scary in the way the conjuring is scary
It's not jumpy scary. It's disturbing. It's bone -chilling. It's like shining exorcist scary. All right
I'd love to talk about it next week because I feel like you're gonna accidentally ruin it. I'm not gonna say anymore
I'm saying but I loved it. I think it's a masterpiece cool 88 minutes. Well, I love that as you would say I do love that
Yeah, I know you do. That's why I'm telling you
what did I see at the theater? I saw Kung Fu Panda 3. Why? I love the first two.
Oh, all right. Well, that's the best answer for that question, I guess. I just
think they're funny and they look beautiful. Nice. It's great animation. You know
and that's that's how I feel about you. Thanks, John. It makes up for that ice cream
coming out. Come on. I was joking. Now my see my gluttony moves are a little
different I would never ever get a full meal someplace and then go get a full meal somewhere else
I might eat way too much in one place or you know like in ordering food like here's here's what I
can't do if me and Heather my girlfriend are going to be like hey let's order a lot of food so we
have food for the weekend like you might do that's not going to fly for me that that food's gone that
night. That's my issue. I have a problem stopping if there's nothing holding me back. But I work
thankfully with people with pretty severe body dysmorphia and they're all pretty fit. Not all
but most. And like it's the kind of room where if you go get a bag of chips, you feel the eyes on
you when you come back to the room. It's not like most riders rooms. Really? So everybody eats healthy.
I eat a salad every morning. I eat a heart healthy breakfast like a cereal with some
Flax seed on it. Okay. I eat a salad for lunch
Sometimes I don't eat dinner or sometimes eat a sensible dinner. So I don't understand my body and I despise my body
Yeah, I find myself doing things like a
Master cleanse once in a while like complete starvation
Because I don't know what else to do
But we both work in these periods of like extreme gluttony extreme raining it in which is very Kaplan. Yes
Yeah, I think I think it's the pendulum swings. Yeah in the Catholic guilt department, but it's you know, I
Don't see my thing is it's not that I need to eat two full meals right at once
Right and I don't I didn't finish all of that stuff. I ate three pieces of chicken and a burger and a burger
I mean and in my defense
A double cheeseburger from Burger King is not
You know, it's two little patties and, you know, whatever.
And then fried chicken pieces, the two thighs and a drumstick are not gargantuan.
It's a lot of food, but it's not insane.
My point is this, I want to know there's more there.
That's the thing I get out of gluttony, I like knowing the safety net is there.
The night's not over, there's food left.
The pang isn't over, there's booze left, sure.
And if I hurt myself to the point where I go home before that runs out, then great.
It was worth the extra cash to know it was there the whole time.
But if you run out before you're ready to run out, that's a sad moment.
But see, so many people and I respect them would be like, like, let's say they're eating a
chicken and rice sort of like I'll do that to chicken broccoli, brown rice, whatever, but
you eat the small portion of it and you're like, man, I'd love to have more food.
There are many people who don't.
they don't even have that thought it's but you know they're pussies and they live in a they live in a
weird world of never going over the line and everything should just be in it's everything in
its right place it's that radio head song you know everything yeah it's it's it's it's come on you
gotta you got it what fun is life if you're not going off the rails a little bit I gotta agree with
that. And if you're not hurting anybody and with this Uber, you're pretty much never hurting anybody.
The drinking, I just, I don't get it. I don't get how people would just never drink. And they're like,
Good, my head's so much clearer in this and that.
Not really.
I've been sober for huge periods of time.
You don't get that much fucking clear.
You're telling yourself things
to make your boring ass life seem better
that there's a reason for doing it.
Now if you're blacking out and fucking bombs under a bridge,
then yeah, get your fucking life together.
What if you're doing that but not blacking out?
Is that bad?
You're just don't sober.
Well, just, you're drunk, but you know what you're doing.
Um, there was a girl who I won't even say where I lived when this happened, but there was a girl who we all went to a party and she started talking up to this homeless guy outside and she went home with them.
You've told me this story and it's real gross. Actually, wait. She went to her home clearly with him. You haven't told me this story. You've told me you took that's I've never heard that story.
I had another friend and we knew a really attractive girl and he told me she got drunk and made out with a homeless guy on the street in front of him
Yeah, and it was like what this was there making out. We were like I don't believe what I'm seeing and then she went home with a guy
Now was it a good -looking homeless man? I mean, yeah, I would say so
But he wasn't like a you could you let me tell you this you could definitely tell he was almost could you smell him and I I didn't get that close
And you hate to be obviously the homeless have been through enough, but it's like there's no chance. He smelled great
You know, there's no chance. I wonder if he had a
You know, was he are we talking like a Mary Poppins homeless kind of guy?
It's like a street urchin like a chimney guy sweeping guy. No, he was pretty good. I'm just saying he was younger like an iron weed
Yeah, exactly. No, he was young. He wasn't like a you know, he wasn't like recently home like a Miley Cyrus homeless guy
No, no, no, I think she has some money actually
No, no, but that remember she brought the homeless guy to the MTV. Oh, right right right like that kind of homeless
He was no you could tell he was homeless like newsies somewhere in the middle there. I'm telling me he was just a homeless guy
Like no, weren't they homeless in newsies Oliver twist like in all over to the street urchins and Oliver twist
Yeah, I portrayed Fagan and Oliver
And Cass is the role of Fagan, the lead role of the Oliver and Oliver twist.
Well, the lead role would be Oliver twist, the lead role other than Oliver.
I thought you said the lead role in Oliver to Fagan is the old man, the mean man, right?
No, well, that's Bill Sykes. Fagan like runs the pickpockets. He's like their king.
Yeah, WC fields played him in the, I got you.
so we're talking fourth grade I walk up to a sign that's posted outside the
drama office okay says in large letters for all to see Patrick Walsh is
Faggen F -A -G -I -N and I saw it it was like oh sweet Lord no and for a kid who was
already not too cool. That did not, uh, do me any favors. Hey,
well, she's faggin, but you went through with the wrong because you're an artist
and you, you're committed to your craft. Just go through with it. I really
sort of changed the game. You lived it. Yeah. You got to pick a pocket or two
boys. You got to pick a pocket or two. There have been few musical slash books,
Slash stories slash movies that I have given less of a rat's ass about than all of a twist
I have never understood the no there's no intrigue. I've never the appeal. I don't get it
He's just an orphan and he wants more food and there's not much that happens really
Yeah, there's that part where he wants a woman who's beaten by our boyfriend
It's depressing, but if it's anything and it's kind of like there's that thing they take from it for the wall
Yeah, yeah, exactly. Pink Floyd's the one. I think they knew what I meant. Well, some might not have I'm clarified. Now we're drinking beer as we record this. Yeah, I mean, that's what I said the Joe and I came over here. So I went, my girlfriend got me tickets to music festival this weekend popped in, popped out.
I had a drink or two each day before we went down to the thing but didn't go crazy.
I'm just like, I just don't feel like drinking anymore.
Then I come over here to do this thing, it's a Monday night, Joe's like, let's have
a couple of beers and I'm like, yep, all right, then afterwards it's going to be eight o 'clock.
Joe's going to be like, hey, you want to go out?
I'm going to go, yep, all right, no, definitely doing that.
That's what I texted you before we did this and said, why don't we go have a couple of
pops tonight?
Yeah.
I mean, you are truly my worst influential friend in terms of that stuff.
I'll fuck you.
I'm not even saying I don't like it about you need a friend like that.
Fuck you.
I'm telling you I like it.
I'm the fucking, uh, you're the worst of my friend.
You feel the role my, you feel the role my buddy in used to feel in that now he's a married
man, but you'll be like, hey man, we're out at the whatever that fuck.
getting wasted like kind of a lot and I'll go okay and usually I'll come out
or was sitting here on a Monday and it's like hey let's go get drunk after this
it wouldn't even be on my mind but you say it and then I'm like yes then you're
like do you want to go get another round here yes you want to go over to this
bar get another round here yes here's what's good you need a friend like that it
makes life fun but many times it's in my best interest to fucking go home you know
you friend of mine, you are the whiny one, the whiny one.
Not even whining about it.
I'm telling you I like it.
Anyone listening to this could tell that I'm telling you I like and appreciate it.
This is where I suggested it tonight is because I have off tomorrow and I know you're not
taping tomorrow.
That's correct.
So I thought, Patty's got a short day.
I have off.
It's a beautiful crisp sweet sweet sweet smelling night here in Los Angeles.
It is.
It's crisp.
Maddie McCarty or dear friend yeah, texted me goes are you doing anything tonight?
I'm at the Virgil love it for hot tub. That means curty brown hollers over there. Yeah, I said patty
We're gonna couple pops after the fucking podcast tonight. It's got some fun
And I'm telling myself now that I'll have a couple beers have a good time at head home, but
A lot of times these nights devolved into me getting home at two o 'clock. We're eating a booze. Hey
you know that's fine. I'm a facilitator. That's right. You're a facility. I make
things happen. Now when I have hated it in the past is when you'll be like let's
also add in this 2 .35 a .m. trip to Del Taco. And then the next morning I'm like
fuck you Joe. I'm feeling like a burrito lounging around my midsection. You're
your own person. I don't twist your arm. I don't pressure you. Let's go to the
video tape. You especially when you're heavily drunk will scream in my face. I
don't do that anymore. Come on you fucking pussy. Have another. Have a shot. Have a
burrito. I don't do that anymore though because you told me that it upset you. So I
stopped doing it. You do it. You're the devil on the shoulder. But I don't do
that anymore. We were out last weekend for our buddy Vince's bachelor party. And
not once did I force you to do a shot. I didn't yell pussy at you one time. That's
And actually the shot you bought me I pawned off on our friend Brent and then there you go
Yeah, they're I really I said bread. I meant Brent
I really try to stay cognizant of when my friends tell me which you have
That you don't like something and you told me before I don't like when you yell in my face
You fucking pussy do the shot with me perhaps didn't need to be told to most but yeah
Yeah, I it worked out better and that night by the way
I had a Red Bull prior which I never do. I drank it such a perfectly even keel with everybody from 4 p .m.
To 2 a .m. I woke up with not a trace of a hangover. I felt amazingly entire night. It was a beautiful evening.
I drank with an even keel that was quite heavy. Yeah.
Till 2 a .m. from 4 .30 did not have a Red Bull beforehand and was
It's immensely hung over the next day, probably because I started eating weed, gummy fish
around 130, as if they were actual food.
I just started eating.
Oh, wow.
And I was like, come on.
Who wants one?
And I was giving them to people.
And like, I ain't like that.
Now, you won't even remember this.
When we were walking to the last bar, which was, as it always is, the goddamn drawing room.
Yeah.
If you're from LA drawing, one of my least favorite bars on Earth.
It is a real hardcore bar, man.
We're walking over there and you were talking to me in advance. You were in great spirits. You were feeling great
Well, I wasn't walking with you if you don't remember then this was the walk to the other bar
Okay, so you were like
Hey, who wants a you know, I got my fish right when I go Joe
I got to tell you I go. I know that sounds a great idea. It's 1 a .m
That's not a great idea. You don't want to do that right now and like this here's a couple real drunk guys telling you
It's not a good idea right now. We're all real drunk. You don't know where that's gonna take you
That's a beginning of the night thing or a no drinking night. It took me baby, and you were like
I guess you're right now. I'm like Joe and you're like, yeah, I go come on man. You don't want to eat this up
All right, I'm putting it back in my pocket and after that you must have started eating them like crazy when I got to the drawing room
Did you just listen when I got to the drawing room? Oh, yeah, you were staring vacantly because the second to last bar
I decided to hang back at for a while just by myself. Yeah, I remember that and I said
I'll just meet you guys and then I walked to the drawing room alone met you guys there and then started eating the gummies
Yeah, and giving them to whoever would take them right and I was
Not in good shape the next day. Yeah, at the end of the night when I left you I said goodbye to your face three or four times
I knew I was not getting
Any sort of register from you mentally or verbally
Well, all right
Yeah, I was in I was in rough. Yeah, it was a bachelor party. What are you gonna do? I tried to release
Is it stave off or scave off stave stave off the guilt the next day
They said, you know, I felt real guilty. I felt terrible the next day, right?
I was like, you know what it was a bachelor party. You go crazy. We weren't crazy
So there's my question you go him
Why are we doing that
one two times a month
Well, why are we not having these like monster 4 p .m. to 2 a .m. hangs?
We honestly we completely should because we're all
A couple years max away from just never doing that again. I mean our bodies won't be able to take it a and b
We'll be married and kids and et cetera aside from our friend getting married. Yeah
There was nothing about that day that made it more unique than we could have made it any other Saturday
No, definitely not we could do that every Saturday. I think all told on the night and I'm buying drinks for Vince
I'm buying drinks. I'm having a good time jukebox here. I'd probably spent 80 bucks
Wow, well, or a hundred bucks. I spent about 500 while you were perhaps
See I didn't go back for the old lap days. I
I looked in my account the next day.
It was just, there were like three debits for like $200 at different places.
I was like, my God, and I had $100 in my pocket when I got there.
What the fuck would I spend all my money on?
See, you were probably, were you doing the gummies pre -strip club?
Because that's a way to lose all your money.
I don't remember.
Well, now that the cat's out of the bag, I didn't know if we were allowed to say that we went to
a strip club.
Oh, I can tell I say I want to strip love and I can also say honestly on the air that I did not get a lap dance
Which I neither did Vince and neither did Vince who's the guy that would you know potentially get in any shit like we would just literally in a strip club for the for the
Symbolism or whatever you want to call it of being in a strip club for a bachelor party. However, I also we were in a bikini bar where there is no
I did get lap dances. I got about 10 in a row, which that's what I was doing when you guys were leaving and I said just go on without me like like we were in Vietnam and I wasn't going to make it.
And I remember going the brown out occurred. I texted you the next day. Things started to go dim during the lap dances. Always bad.
And I think you don't remember something you've spent all this money. I remember walking to the cash machine getting out $200 giving it right to her. Yeah
And then and then walking to the drawing room with with a skip in my step that I can't even explain
Yeah, see what you touched on and I guess it was definitely a Catholic thing as well
But like I think most people they get drunk to wake up with a hangover that like all my head hurts
I know for me. I don't want to speak for you as well. I wake up with all my head hurts and tremendous guilt
And overwhelming shame and most people don't have that Joe's just walked away as I turned to him to chime in on my point
But it is the truth I you know my father told me from when I was five years old
Don't ever have a drink because he was an alcoholic so he had his fun till he was 40 years old
Then he was like you can never have fun so
So, instead of just waking up hung over, I wake up with this guilt and shame.
It's gotten better as time goes by.
And a big part of it is just like, I work really hard, I've done well for myself.
If I want to go out on a Friday night and drink or smoke a joint or whatever, who am I
hurting?
The answer is no one.
The answer is absolutely no one.
Maybe I'm hurting myself a bit.
But within, you know, reach on wood within three years time, I'm probably going to be married
with a little one bouncing on my knee.
Patty, I gotta tell you.
I'm not gonna be able to do this.
Why would I not do it now?
Most people don't get these opportunities.
They get married at 21
and they resent that they never had any fun.
I'm having fun.
I don't think you're anywhere near an alcohol.
I can proof of that is the way you whine like a little fucking baby
whenever I ask you to do a shot with me.
Yeah, I won't do shots.
I mean, it's not really...
I know, I believe me.
I know I'm not an alcoholic.
I can go months at a time without a drink
and not think twice.
It really wouldn't bug me.
But the power of suggestion is key.
I don't have that thing where my hands trembling and I'm eyeing a bottle of whiskey across the room. If I'm home alone
I'm never gonna have a drink
But when somebody's like, hey, do you want to have a drink? That becomes three
When they say, hey, do you want to go to this next place and have three more? I go sure. I'm bad at saying no
My friend Jake Johansson
Very funny comedian. I remember we talked about this at length recently and we were breaking down the like
like, you know, the science of drinks, which one went, where does it turn? And he was
like, if you could somehow master walking away after that third drink, it would be a perfect
night. But the problem is is that third drink is when you're like, well, why not? Here we
are. And that's, that's when you keep going. And here's my, although I can't hardly say
it's an issue, but I really think you hear this upstairs, by the way, it's a relentless,
like a rolling of it's just it's just I'm not I think it's the dog but my
neighbors I believe are playing bachi ball or something up there I don't know
what the there's the shuffle board perhaps happening up there it
literally sounds like a human being version of foosball is having exactly yeah
all right sorry no it's fine I um you were saying one more three three is perfect
if you could ever walk away from after that third drink,
you'd be in, right, which is why I like wine,
because a bottle of wine is roughly four glasses.
Yeah, they're four decent sized glasses,
but it's not crazy.
And that fourth glass, you, that to me when I drink wine,
that fourth glass is when you start going,
I don't think I want any more of this,
like I'm getting tired of this flavor.
It's a lot of sugar.
I've never, I've never opened a second bottle of wine.
No, you have a bottle of wine,
Just take me by myself take a couple of rips off your ball some some mellow weed sure
I did that Friday night. I drank a bottle of white wine
I smoked weed by myself and I listened to these Zappa albums
I bought it in me by that day that were like triple albums now the last time we did this podcast you were saying
I
Just had a bottle of wine smoke some weed
Listen to mega death and play video games this is becoming a bit of a pattern
It was a second time I've done it and I got to tell you it I've always been you know
I'm on a writing gig right now. So it's like when I have to work like during the days and stuff
I'm real big on like we got to tear this town down Friday and Saturday night because I got a work all day
But I got to tell you this it was the first time and I can't remember how long
Where I knew I had to work on Monday and I sat home on a Friday alone and didn't care
I had a really really nice time. I was smiling, I was enjoying the music. I had
conned the dog with me. We had a great time. It can be great and it gets you
out of your head and I've had friends say, because you know, especially the
writers mind, I have an OCD mind, not OCD in terms of light switches but in terms
of human interaction. What did I say? What did I do? Did I bother this person? Did
that, you know, on and on and on. To shut that off, which is where we came into the
picture and alcohols to some degree, it changed my life. And my friends who are sober
all say, well, how do you shut off your brain when it's going crazy? They're either on
antidepressants, which I won't do. Not that I'm judging it at all. But they also will say,
why do meditation? Now, folks, I just ain't going to cut it for me. I'm sorry. I've attempted
You said that's so much like Dennis Miller. It was crazy. Now, folks, that's just not gonna fucking cut it, okay?
That's not gonna get a monster. You want a dolly llama? You're way into a fucking
Reasling babe. How about you go?
You're George W. Bush on the ship of the Titanic and you're saying I won.
How about you contemplate the meaning of getting me a beer, okay?
I'm trying to have a good time. I'm sitting here with the dolly fucking llama.
Babe, it's one of my favorite bad impressions to do. I'm not a fan. I've done a small huge fan
Not a fan of his politics don't agree with this politics, but huge fan of his comedy. All right, I think he's fucking hilarious
I think he's so funny never dug him great great. Didn't let me take when we're gonna dig right let me just digress in this
Let me tell you a couple great Dennis Miller jokes. Oh God. Hey those customers at Walmart aren't getting any slimmer
Are they pretty sure anything under 300 pounds doesn't even trip the automatic door anymore. That's fine. All right
That's a great job. That's fine
Now do you do meditation you do some I used to try to do it anymore. I don't like it
I haven't to be honest. I have not given it a serious try
But when I sit down, I'm like are you fucking kidding me? I know a big part of it is overcoming that but to me it's just like
All right, like I get that it might benefit me to sit quiet, but you know what I do not proud of it
I take a bath. That's my meditation put on music. I sit in the baths up for an hour
I feel great helps me sleep helps me calm down. I guess in a way that is meditation
But in terms of sitting in a room repeating a word to myself. That's that's not gonna work for me
I was you know
I started painting in place of meditation. Yeah, and I and it brought me the same
enjoyment. I'm not really that good at it, but I enjoyed doing it. I'm sure you
know. Well the reason I did that was because my mom's therapist told her about
these things called adult coloring books where they're like can I tell you a
bit quick enraption. The show I write for we do usually the cold open is cat
dennings chewing out a customer for being like somebody had out one of those
You know, the dogs where they're allowed to bring the dog in because they're your companion or whatever service animal
Yeah, it's just we take something in the news and she choose the person out for it at being stupid, you know, it's usually how the show begins
To write the cold open and it was her chewing out a guy
by for doing adult coloring books.
That's crazy that you say that.
Because I researched them and everything.
That's very funny.
Yeah, my mom's therapist turned her onto it
and she was, you know, if you don't know what they are,
I know it sounds kind of silly,
but I researched it as I was writing dialogue
making fun of it.
I was like, I would do this and probably love it.
Well, it's their coloring books, but they're for adults.
So they're very intricate designs
and they take a lot of concentration
because you have to color in a lot of small shapes.
Right, um, it's like it's like it's like the most intricate stained glass design, you know, why doodle all day?
It's the same shit. Right. So I thought I don't really have any desire to fill complete a coloring book
But I like paintings. I have some paintings in my house
Yeah, well, I bet you if you just paint it and paintings great, man
You put on I'll put on like
You know like John Carpenter's lost themes or right or Beck morning phase like something very
cinematic right and just paint and it's great and I haven't been doing it
as I moved into this apartment yeah downsize to save space and I don't it's too
fucking I'm nowhere to put the easel anymore right right I'm actually looking at
a desk cop easel online right now so I can start doing it again it's hard though
because then you got to put the goddamn canvases right and I personally would
so much rather be creative and I I completely get and I would never make
fond of meditation for somebody and working for somebody. But for me, I would so much rather be creating and that's so much more beneficial to me.
Even if it's nothing, nobody will ever see putting your mind to work in that capacity as opposed to just sitting in a room for an hour.
I just, I would be so anxious about wasting that time that I would never be able to relax.
I just, you know, they say, especially with TCM, that there's no transcendental meditation.
Yeah, there's no wrong way to do it right and I you know, there's also my buddy also say that there's no wrong way to eat a Reese's
I agree with
My buddy Sean O 'Connor who's very funny comic and I love him he
We talked about it. I said I can't do it. He goes neither can I don't like it and they go and I said I go they say
There's no wrong way to do it. I know for a fact. I'm doing it wrong if I sit for 20 minutes and all I think about is sex
I'm doing it wrong. Yeah, that's not what I'm supposed to be doing. I'm supposed to be transcending and he was like
He's like no, I agree. He's like I can't my mind can't stay still. I'm distracted. I think a truly funny creative person is always gonna have a
Real struggle with that or else you're not really
I don't want to take my edge off. That's where my comedy lies, you know
I don't mind taking my edge off, but I'm telling you I'm on meds. Sure. I'm on pro -zek. Right. I'm gonna I'm on a hot 40 milligrams a day
right not that much but enough yeah and it I don't feel numb right I just feel
even mm -hmm I just feel even trust me I still have plenty of bouts of unjustified
anger and yelling and traffic and worrying about things like like a Woody Allen
character would or something you know what I mean right I am not I'm not a
Stale brain at this point. Yeah, but I'm a manageable person at this right and I didn't used to be I used to get consumed and
Just something stupid like hearing I didn't get some job. I wanted it was like days of just
Fuck this in this fucking world sucks and everybody's out to get me. It's crazy
It's like that's not none of that's true
You learn when you are around people like that
That's the biggest help for me is when you're around somebody who's like, man, fuck it
There's always a writer in every writer's room or somebody who's like fuck that fuck everything man
This business is so fucking and when you're around that you immediately learn okay
I don't ever want to be this person
Because it can be unbearable to be around. It's like is it everyone's struggling. So you talking about how
shitty life is it not helping anyone out? We're all having issues
We also don't feel need to talk about it day in and my problem was I'd say I never want to be that guy
But then I would still sort of that. I mean, I'm never right. I don't think I've ever been that guy
But I would act more like that guy than I ever wanted to or always ever okay with sure and which brings us full circle
You your frustrations with the world with yourself your shortcomings whatever you then turn to indulge in something
And yeah for me and for you. It sounds like it was food and drink a lot of the time
I am a huge stress eater and when I
When I first came out to Los Angeles, I had a riding partner and it was like, we knew
that we had one week off of work to come out here to LA and basically get an agent and
a job and everything else and I was so terrified and there was this place, there still is this
place called Diddy Reese in Westwood, California and it was two of the best cookies you've ever
eaten and between the cookies was ice cream, delicious ice cream and each sandwich was $1.
dollar. Oh wow. And it was on the UCLA campus over in Westwood. So we had heard it was
good. We go in there and stop. And as I am talking, like, because we met up with all
these agents, and I was like, I hate these people. And is this what people in the lay are going
to be like, and all these agents are douchebags. And I hate it out here. We're not going to
get a job. And I hate these fucking assholes. And at this time, I didn't smoke weed. You
know, like, I had nothing to balance myself. Sure. And while talking, I was almost like
like Bugs Bunny pushing a carrot into his mouth.
I was just jamming this Diddy Rees sandwich
one after another into my mouth,
standing over a trash can on the side of the road,
pounding these Diddy Rees sandwiches until I went,
whoa, and normally, if that sort of thing happens,
it would be alone at home on like a late Saturday night
and I would be like, oh my God, I'm so ashamed.
But this was like someone else saw it.
He took it to the streets.
I was like, Jesus Christ, I gotta get myself in a control.
big stress eater it's a it's a problem of mine but the key is and it always has
been keep the food out of your house for me I live with somebody and it's much
harder to do I'm not a stress eater I'm a depression eater I was a
depression eater okay when I was stressed I don't want to eat usually see when I'm
stressing I don't want to eat because I'm too nervous and I'm convinced that I'm
gonna die or the world's gonna collapse around me so I'm like who can think
about food it's like it's like a death row last meal yeah I'm like I'm gonna
I can't think about eating right now, but depression is when I'm like, fuck everything, and yeah, I'm gonna go get a fucking pizza with everything on it.
I'm just gonna lay here and watch my DVDs and play video, you know, that's how I get.
That's sort of shit, like it's a rare occasion nowadays, but if I really want to just eat something, I'll get like a limited amount of Thai food where I know if I eat all this, I'll be okay.
I would never ever order a large pizza because I would shit can nothing. I can't do that
I can't have that much lying around. It's a problem, but everybody has their problem. I used to do my depression meal used to be the KFC legs and thighs bucket
Which I believe was I would need it all in one sitting, but I believe it was
I think it was 20 pieces or like 15 pieces. It was a lot of chicken
And it would come with that four biscuits and two large sides.
And I would, when I was really deprived, I was living in a studio apartment in Grammar
Sea.
One of my CDs, the closing bit is the story of doing this.
I'm not going to do the bit right now, but when I lived in Grammar Sea, I lived in this
really shitty slum -lord studio apartment, it was horrible, it was gross, and it was cold
and New York, I just didn't have anything going on,
and it was a real dark time.
But I remember I would frequently,
and by frequently, I mean, probably once a week,
once every two weeks, go to KFC,
which was walkable for my apartment.
This tells you something,
I felt lucky that I lived near a good KFC when I moved in.
That was like a perk.
And I'd get the family picnic meal by myself,
and every time without question,
and the guy would kind of look like,
you don't seem to have a family.
You don't seem to be going on a picnic for that.
Exactly, it's 20 degrees outside, you're alone.
I don't see a wedding ring.
It seems that you've been crying.
Now, and I would take it home
and I would just, for like three consecutive meals,
flex of G is on your sweatpants problem.
Yes, yeah, three consecutive meals,
I would just eat it and like, I would eat it
While watching, you know, that was when Netflix and Apple TV was still like sort of a new thing in my life, right, and I'd put on Netflix stuff and I'd eat and pass out on my love seat. I didn't even have a couch because the studio was too small.
Passing on my love seat, wake up, watch a little more, eat again, pass out. Yeah, it was really some real.
So general curts level like fucking pressing mixing sleeping and eating is definitely not
good. Oh, I went through a period like that. Because your body is not burning a thing.
No, I had many phases like that in New York where I would literally where I would get so depressed
because it was such a hard city to live in. Right. And it was, you know, this line of work
is always a hustle and to an extent, a struggle. Yeah. But it's gotten easier over the years
And it's I've gotten to do better things and I've gotten to make more money and things get a little more comfortable
Right, but in New York, we're definitely so far at least the hardest times I've ever had
So I had stretches where I literally would just be sleeping to get to the next meal
Right because I just was so fucking depressed
It was it was horrible. I didn't do anything like you know, not the whole time, but a lot of the time, right
Anyway
way. You get hangovers? Yeah. Every time you drink? No.
50 %? No. If you wake up and you're not, you're like, oh, thank
God. I get about 30. 30 % of the time, I'll go a little too
hard and won't drink enough water or something. Right. And I'll
wake up with a headache. I think that's the only kind of
hangover ever get is the headache. It's never like, oh, I'm
going to throw up. I mean, there were anything like that. I
just, it's just I have a headache. I think I started
to drink when I was 23, which is a good 5, 6, 7 years later than most. And I started smoking
pot occasionally, you know, 5 years ago. I don't ever get it. I'd have to be like going
off the charts. And even then I drink a ton of water before I go to bed. So that's where
you get into kind of a problem area because aside from the guilt, if you wake up and you're
not hung over after drinking heavily, you're kind of like, why wouldn't I just drink heavily
all the time. There's a caloric issue to drinking, of course. And there's, you know, you
don't want to be the asshole who's drunk all the time. But there's a part of me sometimes
that's like, if I could just do this and not get hungover, which is the reason most people
stop, there's a reason Roger Ebert stopped being an alcoholic, but he couldn't handle the hangovers
and do his job. But apparently he was one of the, you know, I watched the documentary
about him, which was great. And he was just like the hangovers eventually stopped that it
was too much. I don't have those. Yeah. And it's not one of those things where I'm like
just always drunk. So I'm never hungover or something. Sure. I could skip a month, come
back in, not get hungover. Well, yeah, when I was your age, what do you
35? Yeah. Yeah. When I was, I'm 38 now, I've been in New York, LA since I was 35 and a half
or something. Right around your age, three years leading up to that, it was like 32 to 35.
I had mastered, I mean, I was drinking pretty heavily in New York.
It was four or five nights a week because I, at that point in time, I had never had a
writing job.
Right.
It was just doing stand -up.
Yeah.
So, there was never a reason to not go out.
All the drink stand -up, I think the big thing keep me from fully embracing that world because
I love it and I think I would have done well.
I do well when I do it now.
But that life is just too much darkness for me with my already built -in darkness for me to be drinking every now
I couldn't do it you can't I'm glad that that's not the case anymore now that I live out here
It's a very different world, but that's I was also depressed as I said, but at that time
That stretch was like all the drinks were free. Yeah the club hooked you up
I'm always made friends good friends with the bartenders not out of any interest in getting free drinks
I just made friendly with bartenders. So I had I got free drinks
And then I also had bars where I would get a buyback every three rounds or whatever. So like buybacks don't happen in a way to my knowledge
No, so I mean it was just
Chaos it was chaos and then I hung out all some of my friends were were industry people
so then they
Fucking comp tabs because they were like it's a write -off. This is work
and it was and we would just it was just night after night of getting shit
face and I just hit a point I remember calling my friends Scott and being like I
don't know what I've done but I don't get hung over at all and I'm really going
after it and he was like that's a fucking miracle why are you questioning it
don't like don't look at the gift horse in the mouth and I'm like yeah I won't and
I'm glad that a that frequency changed because I became happier and healthier but
also be that there is the occasional hangover to remind me like you're not uh yeah that's
why it's there to put you in line. In closing Pat let's wrap this up one gluttony meal
right now what would you do? I feel we've talked about this on the show before you know what
I've been thinking about constantly that I would really love is like an entire box of what
I used to get my mom would let me every year of my birthday pick my birthday meal and
And I got Velvita shells and cheese, which looking back shows you my family might have
been struggling a little bit.
That was the most extravagant meal we could think of.
But I would eat like right now, I would go crazy on some Velvita shells and cheese.
If they still make it, I don't know.
Hey, man, I'm right with you.
Mike let me meal or take a taco kit.
Oh, yeah, we used to get those a lot.
We're the old El Paso taco kit.
So we're both kind of going back to a childhood place.
I still once a month. I'll do a taco night by myself. Yeah, it's exciting. I love getting all the shit and having those tacos. It's great.
What I'm really happy about is my answer always would have used to been like a Ralph's for a grocery store sheet cake.
And now when I think about the think about eating one slice of it, it makes me sick to my stomach because we're getting older and more mature.
You've mentioned the sheet cake fantasy before.
It is a thing like plunging my neck into a sheet cake imagine how good that would feel it's yeah, and then eating it
Folks you've been listening to will see you and how as you could see the
Titles still is appropriate
This is a presentation of the Fangoria podcast network produced by Thomas Defeo executive produced by Ken Hanley a Fangoria entertainment
For press opportunities advertising inquiries and information about will see you and how contact Ken at Fangoria dot com
Let us know what you think of the new format. We hope you like it. We want to try this out for a little while, but where our ears are open and if you're in the Southeast, let's see, March. I'm coming through
many Minneapolis. I'm coming through Wilmington, North Carolina. I'm coming through New Orleans. I'm coming through
So, Hattiesburg, Mrs. Cippy, I'm coming through Greenville, South Carolina, and possibly Atlanta.
So anyway, if you're around, keep your eye out for the Twitter posts, the dates are coming
soon.
Joderosa Comedy on Twitter.
Also if you're at the triangle of KFC, Burger King, and McDonald's, you might see Joe
there as well.
Right.
I am at the Patrick Walsh Twitter Vine Instagram don't really got nothing coming up. I'm just happy to be alive, frankly. Let us know what you think of the new format.
We'll talk to you soon folks.
I have one more plug. Sorry, one more plug.
So I've been recording music since before I did comedy and now then I did comedy. I stopped putting out my music but I started putting out music. I've been writing recording again.
And it's under the band name is Demon Riot, it's on Band Camp.
It's up there for free.
Two EPs for free.
The full album's coming soon.
I'd love to know what you think about that as well.
All right folks, bye.