Music
Hello everybody.
How's everybody doing and hi!
Welcome to, we'll see you in hell, your favorite podcast covering horror sci -fi fantasy
action and sometimes drama and comedy, just about every kind of movie out there because
it got too hard to stay specific.
My name is Joe DeRosa, my name is Patrick Walsh, we're receiving drinks, it's a wonderful
time.
Hello everybody, welcome to New York, it's Taylor Swift once sang, right, yeah.
Did she?
It's a good, welcome to, yeah, no, I don't know the song, I can dream about it, welcome
to New York, right, something like that, good song, Ryan Adams covered it.
By the way Joe, why did you tell Ryan Adams to do what he did, because he's also been canceled.
New York's own, did it, is Taylor Swift her real name, can't be, just blessed with an awesome
name.
Taylor Swift sounds like the new teacher at Hogwarts this year, Taylor, she's like super
fast, like the light comes in or whatever, watch the Taylor Swift documentary which was
called, help me, Swift, Miss Americana I think, entertaining, I got no beef with Taylor, you
know, and then everyone's like, oh well, she's going to be, you know, pro gay or whatever,
you want her to not be, I don't, like she's 20 whatever, like give her a break, I like
Taylor.
Are people coming down under for being pro gay?
They were like, now she's going to say she, now she's going to take a stand politically,
whatever else, she's a pop star, but she ever not pro gay, I mean, that's not like a surprising
twist in Taylor.
No, then she does take a stand politically and everybody's like, you know, shut up and stick
to your music, you can't win, and that's what the documentary is really about, I'm dating
Taylor Swift, she's real unhappy, you can't open, you can't open your mouth anymore, no,
you can't open your mouth, the documentary was no great shakes, but you know, I like watching
what the life of somebody like that is like, if it's an unvarnished, you know, portrayal,
and I felt like this was as close as you can get to somebody like that, I liked it.
I post it, I do, my friends, Jay Okerson and Dan Soder do a radio show called the Bonfire
on Sirius XM, thank you for listening, and I guest host sometimes when Dan's not there,
but I also just guest on the show, and it's a great time, every time we're on, literally
cry to, like, laugh to you, cry, it's the best time, it's so fun.
And I post a video on behalf, to the fans the other night, I post a video, and some guy
writes, skinny jeans and sneakers, good call, they really pull focus from that alcoholic
face.
Oh, wow.
And I'm just like, why is he going bottom to top with the insults, but I'm just like, why would
you say, who benefits from this?
I don't understand.
I'm benefits, I'm enjoying it now, but that's rough.
It's just so, you're like, I posted a nice video that was funny about my friends whose
radio show, you don't even mean, it's got nothing to do, like, I could see if I was going
on there being like, you know kids say no to drugs, and then this guy goes, oh fuck you,
you rank, or whatever, you know what I mean?
You hesitate to share anything at all, at all, any more anywhere.
I deleted my Facebook account, I mean, I'm very fragile, but I used to go into the wonderful
group run by Emily and formerly myself, the Facebook group we'll see you in hell, which
is such a delight, and I used to love reading it, after we'd post a review, I'd be like,
I'll see what everybody said, but it would be 500 things, like this week's episode was so
great, here's my favorite moment, past funny Joe's funny bubble, and then like the 19th comment
down would be like, boy, Pat said something pretty stupid at minute six, and I'm like, what
did you say mother fucker?
Like my whole day is destroyed, I'm driving down the street like, ooh, ooh, I had to get
off, I'm just a bad person, yeah, I really have to try to not respond, because I'm very
obviously a guy that responds, our whole communication now that we live in different cities is me texting
Joe, stop tweeting at that person, take that down now, you're not looking good in this
exchange, stop it, get off well, it's, I really, it's, I mean, you're responding to one
every two months, right, that's how, but you gotta imagine the number I'm dodging in that
two months, and then finally one gets me on the wrong day, you know, I'm like, Starbucks
fuck the order up, and there ain't a lot of them, and then I go on some guys like, you're
cheeks are fat, and I'm like, you mother fucker, cock sucka, I want to tell you a story
about LA, because I'm sure you miss it, but this was crazy, so I eat on every Tuesday at
this place by my house with a friend of mine, and they accidentally gave me back a different
credit card, and I have a very specific design on my credit card, but I didn't notice for
like a week, so I'm charging on this guy's card, he's charging on my card, and it's like
every charge, so we both had the exact same credit card, same design, and it's a very
weird one, so when I finally catch on to this, I'm like, how the hell am I gonna find this
guy, what's the deal, and I look down at the name on the credit card, and I have a picture
over if you wanna see it after, I swear to God, the name of this man, because I was like,
it better not be a common name, or I'll never find him, his name was Bartleby M. Cockcroft
That sounds like a Hogwarts teacher, yeah, exactly, yeah, so I'm like holy shit, so I
Google, I Google Bartleby M. Cockcroft, of course there's one result, and it is somebody
on Twitter who has pulled Bartleby's old Craigslist ad selling a car off of Craigslist, and for
like 30 tweets makes fun of this guy's name, like look at the name I found of this guy on
one, but because his phone number was in the ad, because he's selling a car, I was able
to call him and be like, you have my credit card, so I text him, I've got your credit card,
you've got mine, we've been using it all week for a variety of purchases, he doesn't respond
for three hours, and then he writes back two words, oh shit, end of communication, in my exchange
I'm like, so obviously let's meet up, we can go to that same restaurant if you want, or
I can come to you, whatever, oh shit, so I go, what does that mean?
Can we meet, whatever, and I tell Heather, and she's like cancel the car, he's buying a
car, whatever, so I cancel it, I go down there, he does eventually text me back and he shows
up and we trade cards, and he's like thinking we're going to be pals, I'm sitting there with
my buddy, and there's 800 seats open, sounds like you're meet cute to me, he's next to
me, like sitting right next to me talking about, after we tally up the stuff, he's like, well
I'll just join him with your guy's dinner now, Bartleby M. Cockropt, don't harass this
guy because that is his real name, I'm sure I probably shouldn't be saying it over and over,
and I'm sure he's a nice man, but it was just like, oh god can I get out of this, please
I didn't even need to meet him because I had already gotten my card cancel, but he screwed
me because you know how when a charge is pending the tip isn't included yet, did you know that?
So he's paying me all these pending charges off because he eats out for breakfast dinner and
lunch apparently. What is a man like Bartleby eat? I mean I lost $100 on this deal, easy.
Bartleby's out there having a night in the town, sick of it. I picture a lot of stews for
some reason. He eats a lot of stews, he was British by the way.
Bowls with like steam coming off. He was British. The other story I texted Joe about this, I'm
driving to the AMC, I am an AMC Stubbs A list member, and I'm driving through Burbank,
it's 4 p .m. sunny day 70 degrees on a Tuesday, and down the street as we get to a stoplight I look
over and there's this guy who looks like he's like dozing off, and I'm like okay he's having a rough day
or whatever, but he looked like he was not well. We start driving and as we're driving alongside each
other, I realize he's completely blacked out, gone drunk, 4 p .m. Burbank on a Tuesday. He rolls down
his window, gets it down halfway, vomits, it keeps coming and coming, half in the car, half out,
he starts catching it with his hands and playing with it, because while driving he's fascinated by
his own puke, that's how drunk he is, and throwing up doesn't sober him up at all, and he's driving,
so he's like playing with his puke, he goes like this, there's puke on the side of my car, he flings
it off, and I look over and he's going blue and it keeps churning out of his mouth, and I go sir are you
okay? And he looks up and he goes um fine, like kind of angry, and we kept driving, I should have
called the police, right? But why would you call the cops on your father? My dad hasn't drank since,
well he told me 1981, the truth is 1989, but folks, we're not here, we're not here to split hairs,
this was so insane to me, because I guess I didn't call because once in a while I might have
stepped behind the wheel when I shouldn't have, and it felt like bad karma, but this guy could
have wiped out a school class, what do you do, who would have called the police, let me see a show of
hands? All right, about half an hour, I don't feel that bad anymore. Fuck it, snitches get stitches man.
Guys, not your problem, let him go on his merry way, they throw it in Ireland all the time, nobody
gives his shit, I was in Ireland once, and we got out of an Uber, me in an Irish comic to go to a show,
and the Uber driver was like just rambling the entire time we're in the car, we get out of the car,
and the guy goes, oh man, he was a little fucked, huh? And I go, no, he was just crazy,
or he goes, I'm sorry, no, let me refer to it, I fucked the story up, shit, we get out of the car,
and the Irish comic goes, oh he was a little crazy, right? And I go, I think he was just drunk,
and then the Irish comic goes, oh we don't have that problem here anymore, anymore,
which means very recently, up until that point, Uber drivers were shit faced in Ireland all
the time, which I thought that was such an interesting way to phrase it. I thought he meant
nobody drinks an Ireland anymore. No, no, we were drunk, I think we were, everybody was drunk,
right? By the way, that Irish comic's name, Patti O 'Ferniture.
Folks!
Let's go to the movie corner because we're going to do our first ever celebrity guest's
interview tonight on this show, we've never done that before on this show, and we're going to do
it between the movie corner and the movie review, speaking of which, it's a holiday -themed movie,
does anybody want to take a guess at what it is? Oh yeah, 18 people said, yeah, my bloody
belly. Okay, yeah. Did somebody say cats? Yeah. Is it an international cat net?
I saw cats, by the way. I'm hoping Joe will see this so we can do it on the show, but it's my
lord. It's on its way to DVD already, so I'm not going to say it. You hear, it's the worst
ever, and you finally see something, and you've heard it's not to such an extreme that you're always
a little let down, it's not worse. Even the room, I feel like when you finally see it, I was five
years late seeing the room, and you're like, okay, this is bad, but all right, cats is that bad.
It is, it is that bitch. Cats is something else. I recommend it. All right. Do you want me to
share it? We are doing my bloody Valentine, and in terms of who we're going to be interviewing,
here's the hint, he played Forest Gump. It's not, it's not. It's better. It's better. Well,
Forest Gump on in the theater. There was an off -broadway adaptation of Forest Gump. You know,
movies are projected in theaters, so the joke was, yeah. All right, let's get to the
fucking movie corner, please. Let's get to it. I'm tripping over my words right now. I'll start
us off, Pat, if you don't mind. No, I don't. I have listened. I have listened almost front to back.
I know it's not a movie, but sometimes we veer off, and I want to do something special for you guys.
I have listened almost front to back to Corey Feldman's biography, choreography.
Okay. That was released amidst the time when he was doing all these interviews on talk shows saying
there's a pedophilia ring in Hollywood. I was a victim of it. You know, it's all in my book,
it's all in my book, it's all in my book. So I'm a good ways into the book at this point,
and he talks a lot about Corey Hame having sex with older men. When he was a minor, the part
Corey Feldman never seems to mention in these interviews, and I'm not making this up. Every,
there are several sequences in the book where Corey Hame and him are hanging out and Corey Hame's
like, I'm just so horny, dude. Come on, man. What if we just fucked? And Corey Feldman goes,
I don't want to do that, dude. I'm not into it. But Christ, leave me alone. My shaperones here,
just go fuck him. I think he's into dudes, and Hame goes off and fucks an older man, and then
in the book Feldman will go, I know it was probably wrong. For me to tell Corey Hame at 16 to go
fuck a grown man. So, but he's never mentioned. So I'm waiting for the Feldman talk to interview
where he goes. There's a pedophilia ring in Hollywood that I may or may not have started myself.
Let's just say I agree with the wheel a little bit. This book is outrageous. Yeah, it sounds crazy.
It is outrageous. It's a fascinating, listen, on many levels, one of which him, he tells a story
about going to Disneyland, just him and Michael Jackson. Now he was a vehement Jackson defender
up until recently. But he tells a story in the book about hanging out with Michael Jackson of the two
of them going to Disneyland together, and then deciding to spend the night in the hotel in Disneyland
together, and you can hear him as he's reading the story, anticipating people being like, what the
fuck dude? You were like, forget 14, like that's not. And he goes, so anyway, me and Mike got up to the room,
and there was only one bed. And Mike immediately called downstairs and said, we need a cot,
because that's the kind of guy he was. He got me a cot immediately. And you're like, he didn't get
you a cot. He's Michael fucking Jackson. So where he could only get... They bring the cot up, we start
kissing there for kind of a change of pace. Beds get a little old, so we kind of spice it up a little
bit. That's a, it's book sounds like a living nightmare. It's on Audible, you can download it,
and it is one of these books, and I know you're a fan of this, where he will do the voices of every
character, and you know what? He's pretty good at it. Yeah. He does a great Michael Jackson, he does a
great Corey Hame. He does a great Joel Schumacher. Yeah. He does extensive scenes of Joel Schumacher
yelling at him, because Schumacher directed Lost Boys, right? Yeah. Yeah. He does extensive scenes
of Schumacher screaming at him on the set of Lost Boys, because he's coming in like all
co -kang over. Well, Feldman is, he's like fucking eight. He's stumbling like, Christ,
Joel, I don't got it in me today. Yeah. And Schumacher's like, get off my fucking set, you piece of shit.
It's an interesting book. They didn't pull this shit on the goonies. Yeah. Hey, he talks about
Donner. Okay. Nothing bad. Nothing bad about Schumacher either, except for him screaming
at children. Right. But you know, they're holding up the... I talked on the podcast about the Ronan
Farrow book and his narration, right? Mm -hmm. The Harvey Weinstein book he does voices for everybody,
like as including Rosie Perez talking about sexual assault, Ronan Farrow does an impression of Rosie
Prince. If you haven't heard that audio book, make it a double, a double feature. Insane. I saw a
color out of space. Oh, wow. I want to see that. Starring the Great Nicholas Cage. And I mean
that, the Great Nicholas Cage. He's great in it. It's a very strange, actually kind of, I guess,
unhinged as his norm, hinged performance. But very weird. And he acts out being kind of possessed by
the alien by doing a Trump impression, which is very weird and jarring. I don't know if the director
liked this or not, but it's the director who did the Allen of Dr. Moro, who they made the, or we got
fired off the Allen of Dr. Moro. And can I say that I'm Richard Stanley, I believe. I am so happy
that that guy got another chance. It took 25 years, but yeah. So, if you haven't seen that
documentary about Allen of Dr. Moro, it's great. But he was so hurt by being fired that he signed
up to be an extra on the film he had just gotten fired from so that snuck in as an yes, as an extra,
so that he could be like a part of it still, which is real tragic. But him directing this, it's an
awesome movie. And what a job directing. I feel like it was a blast. The theater loved it,
check it out. It's a kind of like Mandy, but less violent and bad. It's still bad shit.
There's real disturbing shit in it, but great movie. It's the first of a trilogy too.
I'll do Stanley's apparently going to do three Lovecraft movies, which is very cool.
I based off of the juice from choreography, watched a little piece of magic called License to Drive
that I haven't seen. I haven't seen this since it was in the theater. I saw it in the theater
with my best friend, Scott Hoffman, growing, we were 12 years old, and who's late 30s or early 40s?
Just clap. Okay, so if you're, if you just clapped and you were a man,
you wanted to beat, Corey Hame was the coolest kid on planet Earth. You were like, I want to wear
a trench coat with a TLT shirt underneath. He's awesome. And if you're a woman, you probably thought
he was like the hottest dude on planet Earth. Like Corey Hame was the shit. So I want to fuck
Shaperones. Yeah. We saw License driving the theater, I hadn't seen it since, and I was listening
to choreography, and I was like, I really want to watch License to Drive again, and I revisited it,
and God damn did it not deliver on all fronts. Richard Mouser, as Mace, whatever. I say Mouser,
you say Mace or tomato tomato. What's the head of the Screen Actress Guild for some time? Diane Weiss
in license to drive. Corey Feldman. Yeah. A young roller girl. Heather Graham. Heather Graham
Bay. That's the love interest. That's the love interest. Okay. Yeah, yeah, that's the, no, she didn't
play the father. Yeah, she was the love interest. There are other roles. Sorry, you only think a woman
can be the love interest or a father, Joe. Some of us have opened her mind. There's, I mean, it's a
just saying to the girl that he wants to take out on a date. I filled my driver exam. Let's take
a rain check. We're telling his father, I filled my driver exam. Whatever. He just tells lie after
lie, after until he's in a Weinstein level web of deceit, just trying to take this girl out for the
night, and it's insane. It makes no sense. None of it's justified. But God damn it, if it isn't fun,
and it's actually really funny. You're completely turned around there. Yeah. I mean, it's a typical
80s comedy. You know what I mean? It's none of it is truly motivated by anything. There's no real
foundation. They treat getting the drivers like they build this plot up of like, if he doesn't get
the drivers license, he's going to get like laughed out of school. And it's absurd. It's completely
absurd. None of it makes sense. None of it is realistic. But it's a fun movie. And the last, I mean,
for those of you that have seen it the cheer, you'll be able to confirm this or not. I'd say the last
18 minutes of that movie is a car chase with a drunk driver, right? Yeah, like a drunk guy steals their
car. Heather Graham is roofie. No, she's not roofie. She just drinks too much champagne. Oh, by the way,
Heather, I'm glad you mention that. Heather Graham is too drunk because she's dating a man who's
about 42. And she's like a junior in high school. Folks, it was a different time. Not one, not one person
in the movie goes, this is, this is a weird, right? Yeah. Nobody says a goddamn thing. Every,
even Heather Graham's parents in it are like, good for you, sweetie. He's a great guy. I just read
his article about American pie, which came out in 99, not that long ago. A key plot point is
that Shannon Elizabeth, they film her stripping naked without her consent, play it on the internet for
the entire school and it gets her deported. And these were the heroes of the film. And I remember
loving that movie. And I probably would still like it, but it's just crazy. Things have taken a big
change. Yeah, somebody pointed out, oh, who was it? It's a comedian friend of mine on Twitter today,
wrote, I'm sorry, whoever wrote this, it's a friend that I can't remember who it is right now.
But he wrote out about parasite. And he was like, you know, the best thing about all these accolades
of parasite is everybody just seems to be in bond board with a college graduate fucking a 16 -year -old
throughout the entire, nobody says anything. The parents are fine, everybody's fine with nobody
has a fucking, that was a slight gray area. I guess I assume the age of over there is 16, but I don't
know. And he seemed young, I guess. It bugged me, but not to a great degree. It's a little stretch.
It's a little stretch. It's a little stretch. Folks, I saw, speaking of Harvey Weinstein, the assistant,
has anyone seen that? Okay, yes, one person. But it's just a day in the life of a girl who is
assisting, even though they never say him by name, Harvey Weinstein. You never see a documentary or
no. Okay, it's the girl from Ozark, she's a great actress. Laura Lennie? No, the young girl.
What's her name, anybody? No, that's a grown man, but you can look her up. But it's basically like
nothing at all happens in the movie. Everyone that I saw in the theater I saw it in was angry with it.
But it does a great job of portraying what it's like to be an assistant, and especially you can see it
just weighing on her the whole time that she wants her dream. He's not harassing her, but she wants to
achieve her dream. She's in New York, she's in the film business, but just the soul -crushing
effect of working for somebody like that. And it's done almost too subtly, I would say,
to the extent that there's no plots of the movie. But it's worth watching. It creates a great mood
if that's your thing. Speaking of Harvey Weinstein, you've read, I guess, the testimony that the man has
no balls and his intersex. No, but God damn it, I'm going to.
Maybe as soon as this is over. I want to leave right now. Can we end this early?
Well, this woman's up on the stand, and I'm like, oh shoot, this is stupid. Why did they let her say this
because it makes the other people look at their lying? I believe everybody involved with Weinstein's
piece of shit. But she says he had no balls, and he seemed like almost intersex. It seemed like he
did not have generals. And when they say this, Harvey Weinstein's face falls in the courtroom as you
might imagine. But all you've ever heard about this, and meet personal stories I've heard from
people who have worked for him, and also stories that are now being testified about, is that whenever
he was going to meet some girl in a hotel to a solter, he would require his assistant to give him
an injection, and he would inject his generals with the shot. And that lends a lot of credence
to the thought that he might have inverted generals that he is making come out of his butt.
If you haven't checked in with the trial, I'm not making any of this up, but it is fascinating shit,
and the man's evil seems to really note no bounds. And of course you've seen the pictures of him walking
up with the walker. Yes, that man assaulted himself crippled. His tie torn as tie like is messed up,
like he couldn't tie his tie anymore. Yeah, it's a big show. They should throw him in front of a bus.
It's a big show. Yes. That's what Hollywood does. They put on a big show. Next, my final one is,
and we haven't talked about this on the show yet, but we've talked about it privately.
I'm sorry, real quick. Sorry, that was brilliant. Harvey Weinstein's lawyer also this week said,
they asked her if she's ever been sexually assaulted, and she said,
they've never been sexually assaulted because I would never put myself in that position.
And folks, I'm sorry to say this, give it up for Mr. Harvey Weinstein, and his attorney.
He's not. He's our interview tonight. He's going to have a hard time getting up to the stage with the walker.
We should bring them Mike. We'll bring them back down. He comes up with the walker and then does the
interview a magical world. Yeah. My final film is Tessla. Oh, Jesus. I'm on the right side.
This is a movie we've talked about off -air via text. That's the only way we communicate anymore,
people. I know you look at us and you go, look at these pals. The love is gone. This is just a
charade at this point. Yeah. I'm kidding. I miss. I'm joking. It's just a joke. Although I didn't
get anything for Valentine's. You didn't because you don't deserve it. You fucking bitch.
Fine. No. The fanatic starring John Travolta. Oh, yeah. I saw it in the theater, my friends.
I was about halfway into this thing. I was ready to hate watch it. That's what I turned it on. I'm like,
oh, let me laugh at this. I'm sitting there. I got about 40 minutes in. I texted Pat. I go, Pat,
am I crazy? Is John Travolta our finest living actor right now? This is amazing. The movie sucks,
but he's fucking incredible in it. Like his, he, this, he is nailing this. I believed he was this man.
Well, finally, he was directed by someone who met him on his level of talent. Frederick Durst,
the lead singer of Limp Biscuit. Which by the way, he's a fanatic. I know. And if you haven't seen
the movie, there's a full scene in the movie where the dad is with his kid and his dad go, the dad says
the kid, hey man, I used to love this when I was your age and puts on limp biscuit and goes, oh yeah,
now we're rocking. And they just rock out to limp biscuit. And the kids like, I never heard this,
daddy. This is awesome. They play almost the full song. Yeah, almost the full song. I actually
did not think it was a bad movie. I thought what it was was it was like the B movies that everyone
now loves, all the B movies that were made in the 70s, you know, like the trash stuff, people watching,
like, oh, this is actually really fun. This is a cool story. It's how I felt about this. And I think
it's how it'll be looked at in some time. It's trash, but it was really fun. I thought, yeah,
it was fun. I thought it was in his house while he's asleep and then falls asleep next to him.
Like, he's talking him in his house and then he's like, oh, I'm going to sit next to him,
my, the guy I'm talking while I was asleep. And then the next, they both wake up together and he's
like, yeah, gotta get out of here. That's a funny bit, you know. It's a funny bit. It's a crazy movie,
but it's a good. And it was a very tense movie. I felt like with a, with a slight rewrite. And
just a little bit better direction, you know, like, I mean, Fred Durst actually didn't do a terrible
job, but it was just like somebody that had a little bit of a flair for, for texture and,
and genre films a little bit more. I felt like this, I felt like if Elijah Woods company got
their hands on this thing in the beginning stages, it could have turned out to be an amazing movie.
You know what I mean? But it instead just turned out to be a really, really good, like,
made for cinemax thriller was kind of where it topped out. You know what I mean? Do you know why
Fred Durst did the movie? Because he has nothing going on at all on his desperate. I would guess?
No. Well, he did it for the nookie. Oh!
You're a real asshole.
Folks, I also saw the gentleman, which I would halfway through it now was like, is this the most
racist movie I've ever seen in my life? And I googled it, and before I'm done typing the word,
it says, the gentleman racist pops up in Google. And I did not expect that from the gentleman.
What did, like, I haven't seen it. It's a new guy richie movie. It's a new guy richie movie.
And what ways are racist? I mean, it's just all the heroes of the film are all the characters going
parasite shouldn't a one best picture. All the heroes of the film are talking nonstop about either
just being very, very racist with each other. And maybe low life gangsters in the British underworld
would be like that, but it just felt very jarring to me. Like racist about people from England,
people from England, people from other countries, just a lot of, they're all talk, every character is
pretty racist. Colin Farrell is kind of funny in it. Matthew McConaughey is really bad in it,
and he's kind of enjoying the McConaughey results where he's been good in a lot of things, but he's
very bad in it. Playing a villain, which he shouldn't do. I mean, he's a just a likable person
inherently. Has anyone seen the gentleman? Anyone like it? It got good reviews.
I thought it was very enjoyable. It was a little bit racist.
I was saying it was kind of. Yes. Weirdly racist, I felt, and I thought it just kind of hung there
and didn't really do much for me. Oh, well, yeah, he was interesting. Yeah, it wasn't hateable.
It just kind of was a time passer, you know, that's all. Okay. Is it a return to form for
Guy Richie? Does it kind of call back to the snatch days? No. Okay, I didn't think so. But with
those, I don't know. I mean, by return to form, I should say, does it get back to that good picture he
did with Madonna? Is he getting back to that way? No, yeah, I saw Guy Richie stuff. It's that type of
movie, is it not? It's like, yeah, it's sort of faster. It's whatever, you know, but it's a weed heist.
A weed, huh? Okay. So it's half banked, except in England. Yeah. Okay, I got it. I'm with you.
All right. We should do our interview because we've got about a little less than 30 minutes.
Absolutely. So let's do the interview and then get the movie review in and out. Folks, you know him
from such television shows as Living Biblically, I know that much.
You know him from such films as The Santa Claus, Adam's Family Values,
Slums of Beverly Hills. This is the end. Many films. And I'd love, what's that?
Is that called Looking for Kitty? I thought he was in Sidewalks of New York, the Edward Burns. He's in
Bowl. Ladies and gentlemen, one of my favorite characters, and I'm not bullshitting, the great David
Crumholz. Welcome, David. Welcome. So disappointing. Well, like, you know, when comedians go up they say,
you know, I'm from Comedy Central, whatever. What do you want people to say when they introduce you
as you're like credits in the parentheses? What would be the two movies you'd want?
Oh my. You're asking. Slums of Beverly Hills is a good one.
Great movie. David, it's all funny that if you haven't seen Slums of Beverly Hills.
And I appreciate. I like Sausage Party quite a bit. Sure. You played LaVache.
I played the LaVache rap in Sausage Party. That's right. I'm not going to do it.
I didn't ask. No, everyone does. Everyone asks and it's like, dude, not getting paid right now.
You know what I mean? That's how I roll. Yes. You'll only entertain if paid.
I'm one of the worst people any fan could ever meet.
Okay. Yeah. All right. When I met you, I told you we met at living biblically. And I thought,
here's a fan. Yeah. Well, I had the phone finger with your name on it.
No, but I said, the first thing I said to you was, dude, I'm so happy to be working with you.
And that scene where you sing Luck Be a Lady in Slums of Beverly Hills is one of the funniest
things I've ever seen. Oh, yeah. In your dreams. Yeah, that's right.
Now, you were what, 13 when you made that movie? I was, I was actually eight.
Thanks for asking. No, I was 19. 19. Okay. How were you terrified?
Or do you just not care about having to be in your briefs in your teenage years on film?
That would be a nightmare. No, I wasn't. I think my body is funny.
And so I just got a kick out of it. And you know, if you watch the way they shot that,
it's kind of from an, you know, not bad. You can straight up see the outline of my penis.
And it's, it's, it's, it's an entirely disappointing.
Correctly. It starts on your face kind of tight and then pulls out slowly and reveals that
you're in your underwear and you're, and you're snapping. No, that's, that's not.
It's just one lot so it is my head when I close my eyes real tight.
It was in the trailer. I remember that. That's right. It was.
My face has practically been sewn into the great American pop culture quilt
at this point. You know, they just put me up to the plate and I just try to get the bat on the balls.
Folks. No, David, we gave David folks jokes for a living biblical and he killed them.
We didn't give him that one.
I just want to say this has been a wonderful crowd. There's drama in this room.
I just want to say that half of them know what's happening.
I sense tension of a brewing, but I don't know what's going on.
Yeah, there's tension, bro. There's been some, some, some.
But is it just simply like shut up type stuff?
Yeah, shut up type stuff.
Now, David, you played on the CBS drama numbers.
You played detective John Numbers.
That's right. Numbers, Mickey.
Hold on a second. Hold on a second.
Three was with an E.
Yeah, he was a three.
Yeah, right.
The joke Pat, this man, I know you all love him.
He's a dad.
He has made that joke 87 fucking times.
Not for these every day on set.
Now, you played David Numbers, right?
And it's like, Dad, please, every day like this.
My question is, can we talk to John Numbers?
You want me to do Numbers?
Numbers, Mickey?
Yeah, sure.
How are you doing?
Are we doing it?
Is this you?
Is it happening?
A lot of your dialogue in that show was heavy math, right?
Did you ever understand what you were saying?
Most of the time, I didn't, but you know, I...
So, how do you sell that if you don't know what you're talking about?
Well, I didn't learn my lines until like the very, very last second
when the crew was angry at me for getting them wrong.
The first two takes.
And the pressure made you do it.
And then it was like, I am realizing what my lines are as I'm saying them.
And that looked like I was fascinated with my own words.
But really, it was me fascinated that I actually remembered my lines.
That's great.
I'm a lazy shit.
They pay me a lot of money to do very little.
But that's always the story with great stuff, you know?
Like somebody you'll see Ozzy in an interview.
Like, how did you guys write war pigs?
He's like, I don't even fucking remember.
We were coked up.
Right.
I was coked up most of the time I did numbers.
And I, you guys, anybody enjoy fentanyl?
Because I did while I was doing the doose.
Fentanyl?
Most of the doose I was, I was enjoying fentanyl.
You were right in the doose.
I was great in the doose.
What kind of fentanyl?
I give it all, I go out, you know, risk taker.
Daredevil.
What is fentanyl?
Are you doing lollipops?
A lollipop fentanyl?
Yeah.
Fentanyl lollipops.
I don't know what that is, but yeah, I was doing it.
Pretty sure.
That's how I thought people injected it.
Oh, people, oh yeah.
How did you take it?
Is what I'm asking?
I took it, I, I wrote it down.
Oh, see, it's happening.
It's happening.
Thank you.
He's, he's awake again, everybody.
Yeah, hi.
Wait, hold on.
What are fentanyl and his head popped?
What is, what is fentanyl?
Yeah, just before you proceed.
Incredibly dangerous drug
that in being in the very presence of it,
supposedly, can kill a person.
Okay, yeah.
And you're, but I was willing to do that for art.
The character, the new name of his drug deal.
No, I've never done fentanyl.
I've never done fentanyl.
Come on, guys.
But you understand why I might believe you.
I only saw it.
I want to go back to a previous episode.
Yes, I am.
Okay.
What's on your wrist?
I'm on the wrist.
Is it on the wrist?
Oh yeah, that's right.
It is on my Instagram, like every couple of weeks.
The gentleman over here, I just have an issue.
I have many issues with things that come out of your phone.
No, I know.
You text them to me and then you're really something.
Yeah, and then tweet them at me.
And then I write you back and you'll respond.
But perhaps the greatest issue I've taken
is in this previous episode.
I knew you were going to bring this up.
You call
a
Lando Calrissian
Calrissian.
Why would you if you pronounced it like he's Armenian or something?
Why would you do?
Lando Calrissian.
Calrissian.
You sell Calrissian.
You did.
Am I wrong?
I don't think you're going to come at me.
No, I'm not coming at you for that.
Believe me.
I was the guy that you told to shut the fuck up.
Or go fuck yourself.
I was the guy that said, wow.
Are you serious?
Yeah, I was.
I swear to God.
I swear to God after it happened.
I was like, I wonder if I was crumpled.
Yeah, it was, yeah.
You, you, I will.
Whatever, man.
You will write to me.
You wrote to me about the Sonic the Hedgehog,
shit on Instagram.
Because I was making fun of it.
That was ludicrous, yeah.
I was making fun of the trolls who got
we got the redesign done.
Woo, and I'm like, you fucking trolls.
They only redesign it so they can make money, shut up.
And you wrote to me.
I love that this makes you mad.
This is like any other business.
If you have a store and your bread is bad,
you make better bread.
Yeah, so that you can sell more bread.
Yeah, then I grow up business runs in the real world.
Yeah, yeah.
Like how mature people make money.
And then I wrote back to you,
what do you just get out of bed to break my balls
and then you didn't respond?
You have for good reason, right?
What am I going to say to that?
Yes, of course.
You, oh, you're, you're low -hanging fruit for me.
What do you mean?
Are you talking about mine balls now?
No, you're, you're just, you're, you're, you're,
naivete, you know, you're just, you're not a bright guy.
Listen, Patrick, listen.
I know the world in this that comes from
being an Adam's family value.
That's right.
It must be a devastating burden for you to carry around this earth.
That's right, you're right.
Asking about yours is really funny.
Oh, fuck off, Pat.
Yeah.
Fucking kiss ass.
Thanks, Pat.
I'm sorry.
I just, I think the industry like me, please.
Why are you coming after me?
Wow.
I flew out here for this.
I'm breaking balls.
I was hoping I'd cause this trouble.
Oh, you did.
I know.
David, what is your favorite role that you've played?
Wow.
There's so many great ones.
Just one more.
I appreciated my work as Ray Charles and Ray.
I felt that, I felt the black thing really important.
You were in Ray, right?
I am Ray.
He was like, you got a hot sound, Ray.
Yeah, you're going to make it, Ray.
You know, the little Jew that took advantage.
No, I think of all my work.
Yeah, I guess the Duce.
I'm most proud of that.
No one's seen it.
Don't worry.
I saw the first issue.
It was going to be a show on television for three years.
But how many, there's too many fucking shows, man.
Too many shows.
You mentioned 1 ,000 shows to people.
People were like, I've never seen a single one.
I didn't even know that one existed.
I know.
It's fucked up.
You just came back and made it just in time
from shooting the Twilight Zone, correct?
I'm not allowed.
I have an NDA that I'm not.
I'm not a disclosure agreement, but thanks for working with you.
Forget I said anything.
Yeah, no, yeah, I shot the new reboot of Twilight Zone,
season two.
I guess there was a season one I haven't seen it.
It was.
We reviewed it on the show.
Oh, did you?
Yes, you don't want to skip that episode.
Why I've heard things.
But yeah, no, I literally flew in tonight from Vancouver.
So technically, I kind of went, Vancouver, Canada.
So technically, I kind of went to T -Shirt.
Nobody wants to like just giving the shirt to a celebrity.
Well, I wouldn't have taken it because I was a celebrity.
Okay, that's not.
Who's the worst actor you ever won?
I'm not a celebrity.
I'm a celebrity.
You were a fucking celebrity.
I actually know the answer to this question.
Who's the worst person I've ever won?
Worst actor and worst person.
I know it's the same one.
I know the answer.
No.
Deros is actually, Deros is pretty good.
You know?
Oh, thanks, Dave.
Yeah.
I wasn't on that show.
I put that on my resume.
Yeah, Deros is all right.
He's captivating.
You just can't believe a human being like that exists.
You know, it's like shocking.
It's weird, I don't know.
Oh, god.
Anyway, so.
Worst person, worst actor.
Worst actor I've ever, and this is terrible.
This kind of shit gets me in trouble.
I know the answer.
And I don't blame me if you don't want to say it.
So why don't you say it?
You say it.
And then I'll, I'll come in and say it.
I don't want to say it.
I'll make you from numbers.
You told me it was a fucking asshole.
And his name isn't even Rob Mayhew.
What's his name?
Rob Mayhew.
Rob Morrow.
Yeah.
Sorry.
Peter Mayhew was a total fucker.
And she, to switch gears, which we should,
I want to say Peter Mayhew.
I had a funny experience with Peter Mayhew.
You want to hear what happened?
Yeah.
About 20 years ago.
I went to Chicago Comic Con with a friend of mine
who was a budding comic book artist.
And we were outside going in.
And we see fucking Peter Mayhew, who's hard to miss.
He's seven feet tall, smoking a cigarette outside.
Now, they have these very specific rules
that these poor people, well, I don't feel bad for them.
Because at the end of the day, they're assholes.
The celebrities that do autographed comic cons
are fucking assholes, in my opinion.
I did it once.
But why?
Because an autistic child who can't speak walks up to you
and goes, my dad just paid $80 so I could hug you.
And they go, great.
Come get a hug.
Now, where's my 80 bucks?
That's what happens at those kind of person.
But that's pretty much, yeah.
But the fact that you can have them into this thing.
Do you know what I mean?
Like I'm saying, like it's not, what?
I'm saying, you heard what I said.
I'm saying they let all types of people into the thing.
It's not like that.
It's not like they're praying a lot.
They're doing it right.
Nice thing.
They're not praying a lot to people into a public space.
They're not praying on people.
I'm saying they, like, all types of people going.
All types of, you know, earnestly kind people
who are spending money so that they can have a brief interaction
with a half drunk sexual predator,
which is what most actors and wrestlers are, wrestlers.
I've been to these things.
It's like, it's like the kid that played Pico
and fucking Napoleon Dynamite.
Yeah, it's like that kind of, right.
That need to, that, you know, are out of work
and need to make money, which is fine,
but they're making money on off of,
saying I don't think they're all sexual predators.
All right.
The kid that played Pico, the kid that played Pico.
Luke, no, isn't here.
Let him.
Anyway, Peter Mayhew was standing outside.
And so they tell these people, they tell you,
I did it once, which is where
I learned all this shit and I swore it off,
but they tell you, hey, you know,
don't sign any autographs that aren't paid for.
So let's say I go outside for a smoke
or I go walk through the convention and I want,
and somebody, somebody with a kid comes up to me
and goes, please sir, you're so awesome.
Can I just get a picture with you really quick?
I have to say, no, go pay for one.
So I'm outside with my friend and there's Peter Mayhew
and he's smoking a cigarette and we go up to him
and we're like, oh, Mr. Mayhew, is it cool if we get
a picture with you and he goes,
no.
Ah.
Wow.
And we were just like, oh, this is a horrible moment for us.
We look desperate.
He looks tortured.
Right.
He just, you know, you know, yeah.
Fucked up.
Thanks for bringing me on the show.
I bring it out.
I'm trying to enlighten people.
Good, good.
Good.
I wasn't sure.
Can I show you?
Can I grab hold?
We got 10 minutes.
Forget it.
We're going to review the movie.
Thanks, man.
Came in from New Jersey.
Just got back from shooting a show.
Thank you, David, for coming out.
The first guest we've had on the show.
Can we make sure this mic is off?
Just we're not picking up extra mic.
I don't know if Mike if Harrington's in the room.
Thanks.
Ken Hamley, just by the way, Ken Hamley back there.
This podcast would not exist without Ken Hamley, ladies and gentlemen.
Formerly a fangorian magazine.
This is the man that started it all.
While you're clapping, Will Potor, who did the art for tonight's posters and stickers
that you and Joe will get, give away, give away.
All right.
Is anybody else really a single man?
Oh, okay.
Then stay away from will.
That was a perfect set up for like an old -timey Vegas joke.
Are you single, son?
No, my lady's over there.
Oh, must be married.
You know, put it out.
I was like, that's perfect set up.
All right, we got about 10 minutes.
Let's get into tonight's film.
That's all I need to talk about tonight's film, folks.
My bloody Valentine, 1981.
Not the remake, but the original.
The year of my birth.
This is the only time this has happened.
I texted Emily and said,
we're going to do the second show and blah, blah, blah.
And she goes, well, okay, that's great.
Try to do a Valentine's movie, if you could.
And I said, we're not going to have time to watch.
Because it's like Thursday.
And she goes, okay, we'll do it everyone.
Then I call Pat.
And I said, what do you want to do for the second show?
And he goes, well, my bloody Valentine,
the original is on shutter.
It's 80 minutes.
I was like, okay, I can do.
I can hang out 80 minutes.
So then I call back Emily and I go,
hey, we're going to do my bloody Valentine.
I've never seen her so excited in my life.
And I'd never seen it before this.
Me neither.
I'd seen the remake.
This viewing.
But she was so excited.
And then that made me excited to see this thing.
And it sounds like we're already going to have
different opinions via ads on this.
But I got to tell you, my excitement via Emily's excitement
was 100 % spot on.
I love this goddamn movie.
I thought it was a fucking blast, man.
I really enjoyed it.
It is somehow, and he's a very contrarian man,
but his Quentin Tarantino's favorite slasher movie.
Do you believe him when he says that shit?
No, I don't.
I think he likes kind of sticking weird shit.
Psycho 2 is actually better than Psycho 1, you know?
Shut up, Quentin.
Fucking giant head.
He's looking more and more like Frankenstein's
monster every day.
It's he really is.
It's like the next time when he makes movie 10,
he'll be up at the Oscars with the bolts in his neck.
Yeah.
He's got one more step to make the transition.
A full Fred Gwyn with level head at this point.
He's going to start telling people about the pets cemetery.
Right.
But the movie is basically about, you know,
it's real by the numbers slasher.
But as I think we agree, where it steps up is in the way
it's shot.
It has kind of a nice sense of time and place and feel
in a little mining town.
And as I read, it was actually shot in a mine
and the entire cast was like, this was the worst experience
of my entire life.
They went down on a mine and shot it.
But for me, and I looked it up, I was like, every time
there's going to be a kill, they have great setups for kills.
And then to me, nothing, not well executed.
I looked it up and apparently there's 10 minutes cut out
of this for being horrifically violent and graphic
that very few people have seen.
So what do you mean by?
Because there are tons of kills in this.
What do you mean by nothing?
I didn't feel they would like go far enough or like,
you know when the woman is walking, like,
there's a scene where she appears to be killed
by mining uniforms dropping from the ceiling onto her.
Like, they're on these hooks and these things keep falling
and you're like, why is she scared?
They're uniforms.
But then when he discovers her, her boyfriend,
she's hanging from a hook, but you only see her
from the back of her head and like, water is coming out.
So you figure whatever's happening is probably cool and graphic.
But all you see is his reaction, which is this, not well active.
But, and they stay on his face for 30 seconds
that should be on the gore effect and they're not.
I, okay.
So speaking specifically to that sequence,
yeah, I actually liked that they didn't show her
because the movie showcases a lot of really great gore early on.
Makeup effects in this thing for how low budget it is are incredible.
When the lady falls out of the dryer,
as if a dryer would burn you to this extent, it's absurd.
Your clothes would incinerate.
You could also kick the dryer door and get out, I think.
But when she falls out of the dryer, all burned,
the makeup effects were not only great, but disturbing.
So by the time they got to the woman hanging on the hook
in the mine and the sort of visual and situation
was that water was somehow spewing out of her mouth,
like it was being funneled through her neck or something.
I thought it was kind of cool that you didn't get to see that.
I thought that this is the main thing I want to say.
From right off opening shot, right off the bat,
I was hooked because it's very well directed.
It's a very well directed film.
Like I went and looked up the director to see what else he had done.
And it's mostly from Hungary, or Hungary, excuse me.
Hungarian, Hungarian, Hungary?
That'd be Hungary, yeah.
Sorry guys, I've had a couple.
It's a Kiki, Hungarian.
Yeah, Hungarianapolis.
Yeah.
He's hung is what I'm trying to say.
This guy's got a big hog on him.
That's first on his Wikipedia page.
Boy, that were a director.
Could have been the most embarrassing thing
I've ever publicly said.
He's from Hungary.
Yeah.
It wasn't great.
I was telling a story on the radio the other day.
We were talking about embarrassing times when you fall down.
And I go, I was walking one time, and I falled,
and I was like, fell.
Fell, fall, it's not a word.
That's why you want to say in a room full of comedians
who break each other's balls.
Anyway, most of the stuff he has done, it's not even just
that it's overseas stuff.
It's very esoteric overseas stuff.
He did a couple things, I think, in England.
He did some detective movie with Michael Cain, which I couldn't
even believe because the poster for this thing,
when I looked it up, looked like some kind of porno movie
or something.
Let me do my Michael Cain impression real quick.
First, you do the prep stage.
Then you do the double twisty prestige.
Third, you're going to do the double loopy loop prestige.
There you go.
Here's the best prestige reference of all time.
Yes.
Best prestige reference of all time.
I was on Opie and Anthony one time,
and we watched a video on air where a guy put an entire glass jar
up his ass, and then it broke.
And then he had to pull bloody glass out of his own ass.
Yes, disturbing.
Guys, I didn't fucking direct it.
I just watched it.
And as he's pulling the glass out of his ass,
and we're all discussing in the screen with the studio,
Anthony goes, because every magic trick has a tire.
Anyway, this film is very well directed.
The opening shot is that sort of crooked comic book style frame thing
in the mind.
And right off the bat, I was like,
that's a really cool opening shot.
And throughout the movie, I thought he did a really good job
of building suspense during the kill sequences.
And just finding that sequence is great in the bar
when the bartender is telling the ghost story of the town
and the crazy minor who comes back every year to make sure
we're not having a Valentine's Day party.
Who the fuck celebrates Valentine's Day like this?
Very relatable premise for the movie, yeah.
Man, my god, it was so...
We're not celebrating Valentine's Day, are you?
That's an insane premise for a movie.
It was so clearly at the tail end of the Halloween success wave.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Where they're like, what do we got?
What obviously?
Show up.
Nobody's dug out of Valentine's Day boss.
Yeah.
And see the Valentine's Arbor Day.
And let's go about that.
Yeah.
But yeah, the town's going to have a huge party.
It's Valentine's Day.
Town one.
But the bartender's telling the legend of this minor
who comes back to kill every Valentine's Day.
And as he's telling it, it's doing those sort of really quick
flash cutaways to the guys doing the knife game on the table.
And I just...
Like little stuff like that.
I thought it was very well done.
And it was much more than I expected to get out of this.
It's pretty well done.
I remember seeing the remake in 3D.
It was one of the first kind of...
The new batch of 3D movies.
And I remember thinking it was kind of cool.
But pretty average.
Any big fans here?
Love my bloody Valentine.
Okay.
All right.
Is the remake any good?
Yeah, it's okay.
All right.
So there you have it.
We got to get out of here.
Hold on.
We got two minutes.
I want to say this other thing about my bloody Valentine.
Did you notice this about the soundtrack?
This is a weird thing about this movie.
They'll be like a scene where a woman gets like a pickaxe
through her head in a mine.
And you're like, oh, that's upsetting.
And then it literally cuts to guys going to get beer
with like smoky in the bandit banjo play.
So it's like...
Beer, new, new, new, new, new, new, new.
And they're all like, whoa, it's quitting.
That's what they're buying in the shop.
So it's a little totally uneven.
Some transitional problems.
Fair enough.
Yeah.
We are going by the way and we have sort of cleared it.
Although it's going to probably be a little tight in there.
But we're going.
It's kind of having after drink at this barcade around the corner.
Yes.
There's a barcade two blocks away.
Emily, do you know the cross streets?
I think it's on 20.
We're on...
Okay, so we're on 23rd between 7th and 8th.
I think barcade is 24th between 6th and 7th, right?
Google it.
You got phones.
Yeah.
Right around the corner.
But do you guys want to come have a drink with us and say hello?
Okay.
And here's the deal.
We got to get out of this room quick because we have a hard out.
So once we end, please make your way out just respectfully
to the club.
And we will see you over there.
We promise.
And that's what will happen.
And in case we don't tell you there,
I mean, you guys travel for these things
and just blows our mind.
It's so fantastic.
Thank you so much.
It really does.
We talked privately about how much it means to us and how cool it is.
Thank you to all of you who came.
If you're in New York and you came, we appreciate you too.
Just less.
We'll see you at the bar.
We'll see you next time.
And we will see you in hell.
Good night.
Thanks everybody.