We'll see you in hell. We're back for the final episode of July.
Why the final? How appropriate to talk about final destination? Bloodlines. I would say what?
27th movie to be subtitled Bloodlines. Yeah. And the Netflix show called Bloodlines. Kyle
Chandler. See, it's got sort of a double meaning, you know, the bloodlines of a family or a tradition,
but then also the bloodletting of violence. Yes. Yes. There you go. Hellraiser Bloodlines is one of
my favorite hellraiser movies. That's beyond the first, which number is that? Four. Okay. I guess
I've seen it. They only, I only thought one and two were any good, but three kind of sucks because
they turn pin head into like Jason and Freddie. He's run, he comes to Earth and like it's called
Hell on Earth. Yeah. And he's running around making quips and killing everybody and it's stupid. It's
not what the character is. It's just, it's just not, it goes completely against the mythology and
everything. Surprise Clive Barker attaches name to it. But four bloodlines, the reason it's called
that is because it's about the guy that creates the box. Gotcha. And that's back in like, you know,
Victorian times or whatever. And he's a toy maker and he's commissioned to create the box
for a, for a Marquet de Saad type person. And then it jumps into the present day where one of his
descendants is aware of his lineage and is trying to figure out a way to destroy this gateway that
this box can open. And then in the very end, it jumps to the like into space like in the distant
future. Yeah. Then I've seen it. I have the hell razor quartet of torment. Yes.
4K slip case box set kind of thing. Yeah. I'm actually looked. It's gone up in value as a lot of
these things are nowadays. I talk about this a lot on the show. I just talked about it on Matt McCarty's
up and coming podcast. Of course, Joe and I talk about it. But like, it's the time to be buying
physical media. They go out of print immediately. You know, the value is skyrocketing because
there's still collectors. There's just not the the tonnage. So every release now is like a limited
release. Even something like dirty work will have 5 ,000 copies of this three disc dirty work set
that I'm supposed to be getting in the mail this weekend. And obviously, if there's only 5 ,000
or something, it's going to go up in value. So, you know, it's not like buying gold. But it is a
pretty decent investment these days, I think. Yeah. I got that. It's sitting on my porch in Pennsylvania.
I got that Mario Bava box set. It's coming today. Yeah. Yeah. 5 ,000 copies. And a good box set.
It almost hurts you to open the goddamn things. They're becoming like toys where you're like, nope,
don't ever take it out of the box. Well, here's when I had an intervention on myself in my bathroom
mirror. I've had a few of these. But it is such a scratch as an h of depression to buy something and
have something to look forward to coming your way. But I started being like, I guess, I started
getting into these Rhino reserve vinyl Rhino high fidelity. They just they were in the news this week
because they're bringing back their re releasing the Buckingham Knicks debut before they became
Fleetwood Mac. And that's been out of print for ages. So that's a limited release. And I'm like,
should I buy two copies so that I can listen to one and put one on a shell? And I'm like, Pat,
you can't start doing that. But I think about it a lot. I do. I do that. What I'll do, I very rarely
will do that with with a record. But I have some records that are strictly collector's items.
You know, sure. But I did that like like with the Wu Tang. That thing they put out on record
store day was very limited edition. Yeah. Shout outs by the way to forever changes record store
in Phoenixville. Did I tell this story already? I don't believe so. The guy held the guy held the
record. He held one for me, which was really nice. Yeah. And you know, it was like they did this
thing where it was like like every cup cover is slightly different. So there's no two of these
alike. And they only released like again, 5 ,000 or 3 ,000 or something. Yeah. So Sean, my friend
who owns and runs the place, I hit him up and I was like, you know, is there any way you can hold
one of those Wu Tangs for me on record store day? And he held it for me, which was great. And I was like,
okay, my plan is I'm going to buy it. But I will only stream it. Like I'm never going to open this.
Like because this is this will have value. I'll never sell it. I just I'm just like, no,
I this is a this is something I've collected, you know. But I'm like Indiana Jones if there was no
adventure at all to it. And it and it doesn't belong in a museum. It belongs in my collection.
But but Sean, this was very admirable of him. I got I bought that that fucking record three days
after it came out from him. And I go, Sean, listen man, why don't you keep this because
it's already worth $330 on one from 75. Like this is only going to keep going up. And he goes,
I'm not that kind of record seller, man. You want it. And he sold it to me for the for 70 bucks.
He was like, don't dude, I don't roll like that, man. And I was like, wow, that's pretty wild. Thank you.
Nice of you. And nice of him as well. I had two very brief terrible the opposite customer
service experiences all this morning. The first is stub hub now. Well, I used to be a ticket reseller,
you know, I'd buy tickets and find better seats and sell the old ones and stuff at night. You
know, I was always hustling that way. Now it's settled way down. I don't need it to make rent or
whatever, but I used to be kind of obsessive about it. And now they've started cutting off sales
hours before the showtime. They just, so you're just fucked if you have extra tickets and you can't go.
Another new thing they do, I had tickets for a show a month from now, LCD sound system and pulp
to my favorites. And I bought tickets to Thursday and Friday at the bull, assuming that one would fall
out, I get invited to a birthday party. So I go to sell the Friday ticket. And they tell me,
we're hiding your listing because it's not competitive enough. Right. So I look on the lowest
ticket in my section by like $50 lowest price ticket. They're like, you can go lower. You make more money
from the sale. If I, what's wrong with you? So they're like, we're hiding your listing and you have
to like email us to unhide it. They also want you to now send your tickets to a third party.
And then they lose it. That's happened to me twice now. Instead of sending it directly to the buyer
once they buy it, which has worked for 30 years, send it to this weird email address, then neither you
nor the buyer will be able to access it. And I'm like, I don't even see how you're making money off this.
This just seems like you're fucking people over and you're not benefiting. I don't even know what the
end game is. Jesus Christ. It's exhausting. And the other one today, much simpler, but you're equally
annoying. I walk up to ship a sold record that I sold on disc cogs at the post office. I go, hey,
I just want to send this media mail, please, hand her a cardboard box wrapped in, you know, vinyl
record wrapped in a cardboard box, perfectly packaged. She goes, sir, snaps twice in my face.
There's no one at the post office. I said, man, I'm paying attention to you. What do you want?
She goes, can't do this anymore. She's tapping at the box. I go, can't do what? Just an awful
attitude from the jump. Can't do what? She goes, see here how there's a number on the box? There was
a number two on the box that I had xed out with a Sharpie. Can't do that anymore. I go, well,
it's my box and I crossed it out so that there was no confusion as to the address. She goes, yeah,
you can't do that anymore. Now, I will cover it up with a sticker, but that's the first and last time
I'm going to do that because we have to pay for the stickers, too. Well, then, then lady, I'll give
you the money for the damn sticker. What's the issue? Seriously. And what like a postman's going to see
an address label that I made, you know, with all the posting and the address in my home address,
and then go, I wonder if I'm supposed to take it to this number three. What are you talking about?
I just covered it to help you out. I go, is it better to leave it unchecked and she goes, yeah,
just leave the number on it. I go, you know, I start to ask follow -up questions and I'm like,
this isn't going to go anywhere. Let's just drop it. She points to a sign behind me that says,
you can no longer do this. I'm like, okay, got it. I mean, just no offense to the postal workers,
but God almighty, just a system that deserves to disintegrate. You're already like seconds
from drifting into the Pacific Ocean. Like nobody cares, nobody uses you. I sent my father, a
fucking father's day card and a book from Amazon. So, you know, 36 hours later, he's like, I just got
your book. Thanks so much. I really appreciate it. I'm like, okay, no problem. Card should be there
by Sunday, father's day. Sure. He texted me yesterday. Just got your card. LOL. It was really funny.
I'm like, you got it a full month later? It's the post office. State to state, it takes a month now.
It's not, man. It's a sign, it's like a later sign felt bit, but he is a almost scathing thing about
the post office. Like how? Clearly he used Newman as a, as a credulous post office. Yeah, it's like,
yeah, it's, uh, it's kind of harsh for him. But, uh, yeah, man, uh, it's a shame. It's, you know,
I, I see the purpose of it, but it, God almighty, the experience is rough. I, I looked out that
there's a post office near my place in PA that I have to go into sometimes. And it's the first time ever,
I've been in a post office that's not a line out the door. And everybody's lovely. They're all,
they all seem to enjoy it. It's small town, USA shit. It's everybody's beautiful. Like, you know,
they're, their personality. I mean, and, uh, and, uh, it's just, it's just really nice. And I was like,
wow, this is the, I've been looking for this. I've been looking for this post office for 30 years.
You start drinking there at night, hanging out. It's like your local hang.
Um, what else is going on? I got, I don't, I don't, I don't have any too many life updates at the moment.
Yeah, I mean, not much here either. I went to Palm Springs last weekend. It was like 110 degrees,
but otherwise that was fun. You know, I'm doing, uh, boyfriend, girlfriend, shit concerts and movies
and stuff. Having a nice time. We saw Boogie Nights last night in 70 millimeters. She'd never seen it.
I was like, that's one of the best movies I've ever seen. Yeah. You're goddamn right. Yeah. This is one
of these were at one point. Yeah. It's just like, you know, and the crowd was super young too. And
they seemed scandalized by a lot of the sex in it. And I was like, good, that's what used to happen.
And we used to love it. There was this woman next to me, the entire two and a half hour movie.
And I almost said something, but it just eventually became funny because others around us were laughing
at her too. She said, ah, after nearly every moment of Boogie Nights, particularly like, it's like,
oh, like look how young Philip Seymour Hoffman is. Oh, Julian Moore is being nice to
Markey Mark, but you're like, lady, the movie's about hardcore porn and cocaine use. Yeah.
Yeah. Julian Moore, you can come inside me. Oh, seriously? That was what it was. It was a lot of
stuff like that. Like, oh, yeah, I know. That's fucking disturbing. It was less annoying than the guy
who recited Pee Wee. So I let it go. I was on, um, I did, uh, uh, well, wait, no, I do have a
left. How am I talking about this? But my special came out. Yes. I mean, we were talking about it
prior, but not on the air. Yeah. That's my, yeah. So it came out on Monday. Thank you for everybody.
For the support and the love and the my God. What a, what a beautiful first week this has been.
I can't tell you how much I appreciate all the kind words, all the comments, all the views.
Thank you to everybody. Uh, I actually met also too. I met a hellian. Uh, I was in, uh, the bar
at the mothership the other night and, and, and I'm blanking on his name. I apologize, but he came
up to me and he's like, Hey, I'm a hellian. I was like, Oh, good, cool man. Good to meet you.
And, uh, he's like, well, we've met before. You did my Val Kilmer podcast. Oh, yeah. I did it as well.
Yeah. And I was like, Oh, shit. So that was cool. Um, but yeah, it's been a nice week, uh,
wild week. And, and then, uh, and then this happened. This was crazy. So I did Rogan on
when Tuesday and it came out on Wednesday. The first thing
when we sat down, he was like, have you seen this, uh, Hunter Biden clip where he describes crack?
And I was like, no. And he was like, yeah, he goes, it's going to make you want to do crack.
Like, it's, so man's like soliloquy about crack and I, he plays it like a Jesus Christ, man.
You're right. Yeah. Same with heroin. The people who describe it are like, yeah, there's a reason
everybody loves this so much. Like you forget about sex, ever being a thing. And it's, ultimately,
that's not something I want. I'd rather enjoy sex for the remainder of my life. So we're laughing
about it. And, uh, and then, then last night my dad tech, the episode comes out Wednesday. And
then last night was Thursday, my dad techs. Today is Friday, people, if you're picking up the clues.
My dad texts me. And he's like, uh, he's like, you, you made it to Fox news. I'm watching the
Jesse Waters show and they're talking about how Hunter Biden is a crackhead. And they played a clip
of you and Joe Rogan talking about, like, what is mad at him? Yeah. Yeah. Made it. Ma. Yeah.
This is the clips. The news is playing. Uh, uh, that's what weirdly, whenever, uh, I mentioned,
like, when I posted that, uh, I posted about your special that I got a couple of comments that were,
like, I've seen him on, on the Fox news. And it's like, I just, I don't necessarily associate Joe
with Fox news, but okay. I guess he's a regular over there. No, no. I did gut felt a couple of
times and got called a lib tard and, uh, and a fascist. That's nice when you get it from both sites.
You fascist. Who called you, uh, a lib tard? The portions of gut felt's audience called me a lib tard.
And then portions of my own audience called me a fascist. We're going on. I was like, oh, you can't
win. That's pretty much the course now. Uh, I, uh, I had a hellian, and it had been a year,
probably, uh, outside of our live shows, but I had a hellian come up and go, Patrick Walsh,
I went to a double feature at the New Beverly of modern romance, Albert Brooks, and lost in America,
Albert Brooks, just a hilarious three hours of laughs and pain. And, uh, yeah, guy came out,
was a fan of the show. Uh, hello to you. If you were listening, I really appreciated it.
And if you are a hellian and want to approach, please do anytime, especially if I'm with a woman.
Always do it if I'm with a woman. I saw the eyes light up. And does that happen a lot? I was like,
yeah, you know, pretty regular. Pretty, but it never happens. Never happens. But, uh, it makes you feel
like a stud for a minute or two. And that was nice. I appreciate it. Uh, let's go to the, uh,
let's go to the, uh, yeah. I do want to share, uh, quickly, I went, I did, uh,
Pete Holmes, you made it weird podcast and I hadn't seen Pete in a couple of years, really.
But I go in, he gives you that magic mind, which I think is like his version of cocaine.
You know, he sponsors it and I just felt like amped up. And I talked for two plus hours,
you know, it's, that's the thing. It's an over share podcast and you talk for a long time. And, uh,
I had not even posted anything online until this, this week, Joe's show and I'm doing that
commentary and I threw up a few things. And immediately I felt this anxiety return to my body
of being an online guy and having the world know anything about myself. I don't like it anymore.
I used to love it. But I did Joe's podcast, I'm sorry, Pete's podcast. I go home feeling great
about it, a lot of laughs really fun. I wake up at two in the morning having just about a panic
attack about everything I said and I'm emailing his pub is, uh, you know, producer. I'm like,
hey, how much of this can I cut? Have you ever had anybody just pull an entire episode of the show?
How much would I fuck you over if I just pulled the whole episode? And she's like, it's happened,
you know, I would rather you not like, what are your issues? And I'm like, I just,
I don't want everyone to know everything about what's been going on in my life for the last
couple of years. That part of me is so gone that me talking about like things that work for me
mentally and my divorce and, and, you know, trying to get sober and stuff like that. I'm like,
I don't think I want any of this out there anymore. I've just become a different person. So I don't
know if they'll even see the light of day. But, and then there's stuff like him asking me about
the shows I worked on that got out of hand and I'm like, I shouldn't be talking about this.
I don't know. Do you get that when you go on a podcast? Do you immediately panic?
But everything you say and don't ask. I don't give a fuck anymore. I'd love to get to that place.
What are you going to do? Cancel me? I've already been fucking bullied on, I'm not famous enough
to get truly canceled. That's true. And, and, and, uh, I felt arrogance saying famous enough.
I'm not famous. I'm just, you know, I would say I have notoriety of some type of,
something like whatever. And I certainly have fans, but like, I don't like to call them fans,
but you know what I'm saying. Um, supporters. Yeah, sure. But, uh, but, uh, you know, and, and, and,
and I've, I've, I've been through it. I've already been bullied tremendously by the alt -right. It's
happened to, it happened to me years ago before they had a term for it. There was no term yet canceled
through whatever. Yeah. I remember Bert Christchurch telling me he goes, that's the worst I've ever seen
anybody get beaten up on Twitter. Uh, you know, the nurses came after me. I talk about that in the
new special. Right. I bicyclists, the whole bicycling cycling community came after me and tried to
cost me work and whatever. I've lost ads on when we were doing taste buds. We lost ads.
Uh, due to the nursing thing and would, you know, it's like I've been on the websites where they say
I'm a pariah. They fucking review bombed my, my sandwich shop. It's like, go fuck yourselves.
I, I'd rather live in the zone of I'm an open book. You know, so let's talk about it because the
more I try to tread down the road of, you know, and by the way, I know, I know what you're saying is,
is, is a bit different from what I'm saying. Uh, but to speak a little more directly to your thing,
which is personal stuff. I'd rather just live in the zone of I'm an open book because, because for
me personally, I'm not a good liar. Yeah. Uh, and when I can't just be transparent, it gives me
anxiety and whatever I just would rather be like, this is what it is, man. That's it. You know,
I hear you. Yeah. I mean, we, you know, we bonded over bad dads and, and I went in on my dad in a
way. I've never even done on this show to be honest with you. And I just, I picked, I sent him your
special because, you know, he, he likes stand -up a lot. And I figured he would enjoy it. And a second
I did that I regretted it because I'm like, well, this opens him up to YouTube and then it might suggest
Pete's show. And then he goes, oh my God, that's my son. And then he's listening to me for an hour
talk about what a bad daddy is, which I've never said to his face. And, uh, yeah, it just becomes, it's
too draining for me. I was like, I was literally panicking. And then his producer was so sweet.
She was like, it's three weeks till it drops. I'll do whatever you want, man. If you want us to
just pretend it was you and Pete catching up and we didn't record it, we can do that too. But it's,
it's stressful for me. I don't know why I didn't use to be. Yeah. Um, well, let's go, Joe. What do you
got? What have you seen? What have you loved? Well, I, well, oh, wait a minute. Sorry, real quick,
quick rant, uh, for this, whatever, would we call it the rant segment?
I don't know the way. If somebody called it swipes and gripes, I think we had a name years ago.
That sounds familiar to me. Um, I just want to talk about what a fucking moron
Kesha continues to be. I mean, she ever not been a fucking moron. I just saw an interview clip with her.
She's like, for the first 10 years of my career, they owned my voice. Uh -huh. My songs,
my voice, my singing was owned by the company. I didn't own. You mean like how every fucking thing
works ever? You fucking knitwit. You knitwit. I'm glad Jerry Seinfeld didn't hug you on the carpet.
I'm glad you're an idiot. It's just, and she's wearing these fucking dune glasses.
She looks like a fucking moron. Dude, I saw this thing the other day. I have no opinion on Kesha,
but like what, how did she get you this hot? Because, because it's, it's, it's this thing of like,
a person who is extraordinarily famous and extraordinarily rich, victimizing themselves in any way
they possibly can over something that is so normal when you're starting out in the entertainment
business. And I'm not even saying it should be normal. Stop talking about it as if you were
singled out and taken advantage of. It's like, that's how it works. They put up a lot of money to put
your stuff out. So they own the masters. Right. And then you get to a place where you have more weight
and more pull and can make more demands. And then you say, I'm going to own my masters. There's a reason
why musicians throughout time have made a big deal about, I actually own my masters. There's a reason
why Ryan Kugler getting that deal with, with sinners was a big deal. Right. There's a reason why,
because it is not traditionally what happens. Again, not saying it should be that way. But it is.
So for what to just sit there with these fuck, I'm so fucking tired of celebrities that dress like
they live on an alien planet, acting like they don't want to be celebrities. I saw a thing at ASAP,
Rocky walking out of the studio and there's paparazzi everywhere. And he's like, move, man, move, move,
move. And he's, dude, he's literally dressed like George Washington. And I'm like, the audacity of you to
be annoyed. You're doing, you're in the studio and you're calling this much attention to yourself with
just your jacket. Yeah. Their odds are, if you're wearing a hat over your face and a t -shirt and
jeans, nobody's going to have any idea who you are. Chef Rowan's the same way. And I think she's a great
songwriter. But she's always like, they need to be paying us, providing us mental health. They need to
be doing all this for us, watching over. And it's like, you've signed up for this. Did you have
you not seen any movie or read any books about this business? It's going to drain you. And
you're responsible for your own mental health. The record company needs to pay for that.
Then everyone, every boss in the world would have to pay for the mental health of their employees.
Because jobs damage your mental health. It's like, you're not special. You are special, you're a
great songwriter. We're paying you for that. As, as, as, as Mad Men said, that's what the money is for.
You know, at some point, that's why you're making more than everyone else on earth.
Yeah. Shut up. Oh God, dude. God. Are, are, are you your platform for something? You know,
do I need to hear somebody else bitching at me about Israel and Palestine? No, I don't. But I get
celebrity talking about that and using their platform. Don't talk about, whoa, is me? I need better
mental health care. You're a millionaire. Yeah. Well, the, the, the next thing that's coming out of
my mouth is representative only of my opinion. Because that still works in a portion of the business that
I rarely step into. But you know, I'm sorry, man, with this cold bear shit. It's like, hey, dude,
say Steve, you, you want to give them the finger? Why don't you walk? Why don't you fucking walk instead?
I actually agree with you. Yeah. Actually, I agree with you. So you're going to stay on for another
year and, and take more of the blood money. Walk. You're rich. Walk. It's, it's, it's everybody so
full of shit, man. And everybody's going poor Stephen Colbert. It's like guys, guys, if it's
censorship, let's talk about it. If it's, if it's the, if it's politics intervening and, and, and
silencing a certain voice, which I'm sorry, I don't think it is. I think if that was the case,
they would have replaced Stephen Colbert with Greg Gutfeld, not canceled the entire late night slate.
So I'm sorry. I don't think that's what it is. You can agree or disagree with me. But for everybody
that thinks it's that, where the fuck were all of you? And where was your outrage? When John
Stewart lost his show on Apple, because he wouldn't follow suit with what they wanted him to talk about.
Where was your, where was your outrage? When YouTube was demonetizing people for even saying
the word COVID, where it was, it was nowhere. It was absolutely nowhere. This, and, and, and, but let's
just say it is that. Let's just say it is government censorship. That sucks. But can we stop acting like
this guy's going to be out on the street with a tin cup. For the love of God, people, please.
Yeah, I mean, millions a year for this person. And he will continue to work. And now he's got the
martyr thing on his side and, et cetera, et cetera. There is, 15 million a year. Yeah, there is censorship
going on. Just, but it's from Paramount saying, I don't want to keep spending 15 million, 16 million
dollars to, to get Donald Trump off our backs. So there, there is some hush money elements that are,
but South Park still releases their thing, which I haven't seen yet. I've heard it's very funny,
but with major, or with some edits to it, we had an episode of mispact completely pulled. And when
you only get eight episodes, that's pretty rough because they're scared of Trump. It happened.
I'm probably not supposed to say that, but it does, it does happen. Although I don't think it's him
saying you have to pull this, it's them knowing if they want to continue airing critical things.
He's going to not let it go, which is sort of similar, but yeah, I hear you. Yeah. And he's a
fucking cry, baby, which it's like, I don't, I don't disagree with any of that. And I don't disagree,
I don't even disagree that there's not an element of him in this. Yes. I just don't agree with
with the one narrative that seems to be the most outraged fueled. I mean, even John Stewart, he says,
when he talked about on the Daily Show, he says, he goes, where they losing money, sure.
And it's like, but John, he can't just, I agree with you most of the time. You can't just glaze
over that part. That's the point. Yeah, I mean, to keep paying anyone in, in 2025, late night,
$15 million a year is absurd. And these guys, and I was a fan of Colbert, when he did the Colbert
Report, I can't watch anything he does now. But these guys are on there every night doing a whole
monologue about the evils of capitalism. And at some point, you got to look in the mirror and go, I'm
making $15 million a year. And nobody watches my fucking show. And a lot of my jokes are along the lines
of the Cheeto and Chief, you know, our orange leader or whatever. It's like, guys, you know, I don't
know, people have a real blind spot to their own obsession with money. And I'm not saying you got to
give it all back or anything like that. But if you're accepting $15 million a year and your ratings
don't prove that as no one in late night does, when's the last time anyone in your life has said,
do you see that hilarious fallen bit, Kimmel bit, Colbert? I'm not even trying to be personal.
I'm saying all of them are not relevant anymore. And I'll take it a step further.
I have worked at CBS. Same. No, under your leadership. I worked at CBS for about a month.
These are not kind people. These are not good people. These executives. So that's the other part
that bothers me. I was like, hey, Steve, really, your shocked CBS is an upstanding. This is, I hate
this shit. I hate when when the shit hits the fan and the person gets put out on their ass, then they
finally go, they act like, oh my God, I can't believe this. It's like, no, you turned a blind eye and
worked in a disgusting industry. And now it bit you in the ass and now you're going to act like
you're so surprised. You knew all this shit was going on. You know they do this. 100%. You know who I
saw is just signed with WME and is coming back to entertainment. Ellen DeGeneres. Oh great. So she
didn't leave the country. No, she did. I'm not only am I retiring and this is my final special and I'm
fleeing the country. Now I'm going back on all of it within one year. Stand on your fucking
principles. You have enough money. Sit with your mute wife and ride till death together. You ruined
a lot of people's lives. Leave us alone. Let's get to that movie. Yeah, mute wife. Well, yeah,
okay. Well, this is a perfect because that's the way Ellen wants her by the way. She's in the
biggest one of the funniest shows of all time, arrested development. And then we never see her again.
Wonder why? Yeah. And she's the hot one too. I mean, talking about dude shit on Ellen's part.
Hey, baby, sit by the pool and look good. I'll be home at six. Exactly. Spread them. I'll be home
and I'll be hungry. I, well, this is a perfect transition. All I kept saying this week when I would
talk to people about the Colbert thing. I was like, guys, watch the Larry Sanders show. The fifth
season is about how they're they're like, why? And, and I oddly enough, they are saying throughout
the season, why are we paying Larry this much money when John Stewart, we can pay him half? It's
yeah. And it's John Stewart. We can pay him half. And he'll get the same amount of ratings. Like,
yeah, they're always, it's always about how they're thinking about how to just save and make more
money for themselves or whatever. So I already talked about Larry Sanders. Sorry, go ahead.
No, yeah, hacks, hacks, which I really enjoy. It's sort of a, I don't even, I don't even want to say
a lesser Larry Sanders, but you know, it's, it's cut from the same cloth. And they go into a lot of
this as well, you know, the cost of speaking up on your show. And there's a lot of kind of life art
parallels lately. I'm about to do a full Sanders rewatch. You've peaked my interest yet again.
Well, I finished it up and it was great, but I talked about it already in the movie corner,
but it led me to the zen diaries of Gary Shanling, which I've seen, but I was like, let me rewatch this.
Yeah. Part of me. This movie was two part documentary should, should be retitled. The
saddest thing you'll ever watch. I mean, God, damn, I didn't remember how sad it was. Yeah.
Uh, it's brutal. It's, it's a beautiful piece of work. And it's very insightful. And it
gives you a peak peak into Gary's life. I do wonder. Now he and I, this was a Judd Apatel thing. I,
I know that he and Judd were very good friends. I am assuming Judd knew that Gary would not mind
the exposure of these diaries. Or maybe they even say that at the, at the beginning. Like he,
he's, he's okay. He's okay with it or whatever, but I did wonder. I was like, I wonder if Gary
Shanling would be like weirded out by this. I mean, this is really personal shit. The companion book,
which I just bought, uh, yeah, goes into that that Gary was, was okay with it. Okay, good. That's great.
So, um, it's, uh, it's, it's, it's very deep. Uh, it's very funny. It also gets very dark.
Um, but yeah, I was just like, holy shit, man. Like, like, you know, he'll be,
he'll show him like on the tonight show, just killing and then it'll cut to a journal entry.
And he's like, the laughter is not enough anymore. Yeah, I know. Yeah, I mean, well,
the, the reason it's so sad is a lot of people in comedy, myself included in yourself. I'm sure,
including, I just feel that every single day. I was just talking about that. I leave Pete
home, show on a high and then eight hours later, I'm in a dark hole that I cannot get out of. It's,
it's, that's the way it is. Yeah, it's, uh, it's, it's brutal. Uh, so, so on the one hand,
now, now, the optimistic part is you see him
progress in the journey. So as you get further into the documentary, the more zen he becomes,
the more he realizes what is important and, and how to feel fulfilled and all that stuff.
So that's the payoff, which is beautiful. In fact, I took a picture of the screen at one point
and I said, I got to make that my screensaver. So every time I look at my phone, I see this. But
it's an entry that he wrote that says, give more, give what you didn't get. Love more, drop the old
story. And I was like, that's it right there. Man, everything. Yeah, stop sitting there saying,
you know, I didn't get this. So I don't, you know, I don't feel that I can give it or would
fuck all that, man, be your best. Um, so, so, you know, it's great. But even Christ almighty
Seinfeld, they're in the, there's a thing with, we need those comedians and cars. Even Seinfeld is like,
they're talking about David Brenner died. Yeah. In Seinfeld's like, all that material,
guy wrote hours and hours of stuff. What's it mean now? He's dead. Jesus Christ, Jerry.
Yeah. It just goes this, my favorite part though, weirdly, that is what makes me feel better.
The fact that it's all just kind of grist for the mill and the fact that like my girlfriend,
I don't even really have to ask her. I can pretty much guarantee she does not know who Gary
Shandling is or what Larry Sanders is. And like, that's life, you know, and for me, it's a recent thing,
but it's that feeling of no matter what I do, uh, no one will care roughly six months after
my death. And that's the case for almost everybody on earth. And that freeze, I shouldn't say freeze
you up. It frees me up to be a little more bold, a little less panic about every little thing,
knowing that who gives a shit. I guess that's a stoicism thing too, which Seinfeld also talks about
of like, we're all going to die, you know, like, yeah, stop worrying about every little thing.
I nobody's thinking about you. They're thinking about how they're going to die.
Yeah, obviously easier to say when you have half a billion dollar, but yeah, but I agree. I agree.
I his, his takes on that stuff, like his philosophies on life and stuff. I'm often like very like,
and you know what, Jim Carrey too. That's not the really rich guy, but I'm just like,
God damn it. Yeah, I agree with that. You know, but um, my favorite part and the whole thing,
God, it made me laugh so hard. They go to the comedy store together during the day. And, and they're
in the hallway and Gary goes, this place, man, I just never felt comfortable. Like it always just had
a feeling and Gary just goes, Oh, God, it's awful. I was like, dude, I cannot tell you,
comedy store has always been very lovely to me. I always have a great time performing there. I am
prouder than shit that my name is on the wall there. Yeah, but I cannot tell you how many times when
I was like, in a different place before my name was on the wall, that shit walking in there and just
being like, Oh my God, like, yeah, the comedy store has it, it's, it has like the baked in DNA of a lot of
dead comics. Like it feels like death sort of. And there's an edge to it. I mean, I've been to
many a great night of comedy there, but it's, there is like a hopelessness, a despair around it.
Yeah, it's uh, and then laugh factory is Kramer.
Lafactory is Kramer and Lafactory feels terrible for a completely different reason. It feels like,
Oh, God, it silicone implants and it's like, Oh, this is, yeah, I was an improv guy. Not
as a standup, I just mean like if I had to pick in my big standup going days, I'd always pick the
improv just because it's a little more bright, more vibrant. People seem happier for whatever reason.
And the lineups tended to favor my taste, I guess. The store and, excuse me, and this is one of
the things that's cool about it. The store, the vibe in there, it's, it's, it's a weight, there's a weight
to it to the air in there. But I, it feels like a, a very directly related to stand up weight. Yeah,
there's a heaviness that feels like you're in, you're in the, you're in the uh, dirty gym in North
Philadelphia, you know, and like, like, this is where you got to go and there's blood stains on the
mat because this is how you become a, a fighter or whatever. It's that kind of vibe, uh, which at
certain times cannot feel great. And at other times can make, clean up lift your soul. The laugh
factory just feels like, yeah, it's like, oh, this just feels like Hollywood. And not, not,
not the Hollywood, you know, where George Clooney goes. Yeah, exactly. Yeah. Uh, let's get to that
movie corn. We, we arrayed it. I just did the Zen Diaries. Oh, Zen Diaries. There you go. Um,
I went to the Vista Theater, Quentin Tarantino's, uh, theater right by my house. And they released
Kill Bill, the whole bloody affair. Finally, to the public, there's always been talks of private screenings
and it premiered at the Cannes Film Festival. And that's how the movie was originally shown to critics
before he divided into two entities. I've seen Kill Bill numerous times, including opening night and
time square, which is one of the great movie going experiences of my life, just such a blast. I had
split a picture of sangria with this girl some day with and we just had a fucking blast. And then
one of the stuff at the end between carotene and thermon, I find a little needlessly slow and dull,
if I may. But, um, that's always Tarantino. There's a, there, that's the, I always talk about the
pulp fiction scene with the, do I have a pot belly? You know, Bruce Willis's girlfriend and the scene
and the taxi, um, is just endless and could be lifted and not affect the movie in any way. Uh,
Tarantino has sometimes he falls in love too much with his own stuff and could be a little harsher
with the editing stick, but which big director couldn't really. Um, that said, I didn't know how I was
gonna approach Kill Bill the whole bloody affair. I never felt like I needed to see it as one complete
epic. I thought it worked really well as two movies. The first one kind of more action focused,
more fun and the second more meditative, more set piece, heavy, that kind of vibe. And, um,
I'll say I didn't feel that different sewn up together. What they do is they remove the line of
dialogue at the end of Kill Bill one where they inform her, you know, that her, she says, it has a baby.
They cut that. So we're finding that out along with her and that scene really does hit you like a
ton of bricks when she realizes that her baby has been stripped away from her in the hospital, but it's
really intense. Um, but anyone who's there to see the whole bloody affair has seen Kill Bill one and
two. So these tiny little changes like, oh, now we don't know that she's, uh, got a baby out there.
It, we, we do know because we've seen these movies. So to me, if you've always dreamed of someday
seeing this or there were people there who had traveled from out of state to see this kill Bill,
the whole bloody affair, just be aware that a, it'll probably be on 4k within a year or two and
b, it's not that different from just watching the two movies back to back. There's very few differences.
In fact, I heard there's a little bit of length added to the anime sequences, which have always been
really cool, but I didn't notice it as a fan of the movies. The only thing that I did notice and
that I noticed for the entire four hour running time is that the movie has French subtitles because
it's the con cut. So you're watching a movie that already has a lot of subtitles because it's a
globe trotting action movie and that started to get really old to have sometimes multiple sets of
subtitles on screen when you're trying to watch an action movie. Um, that said, for the experience,
for spending four hours at the theater watching these two great American classics, yeah, it was a blast,
but like don't think you need to pay your time and money to go see this whole bloody affair. It's
one of those things that people have been talking up to this extent and people want to say, oh,
there's only been 10 screenings in the world or whatever, which was true, but ultimately it's the
same movies you've always loved with French subtitles. I don't get the point of it. It's like,
just show that, just show both with an intermission. Like who, like, and that's all this what,
this still has the intermission and it still has the credits for one and two, but this is just
credits for two. What is it then? It's only because this was how it first was presented to critics
at the con film festival and people always say it's got to be so different and oh my god,
there's a Tarantino movie that we've never seen, but you've seen it. That's the point of my review.
Great movies, but come on. I don't really have anything else. I just did too. We can move forward.
Yeah, let's move to the review at hand. Final destination, Bloodlines, the highest
rated of the entire franchise. It's rare that you see a part six come in with the highest rating,
but they have done it. It still holds something in the 90s on Rotten Tomatoes with the critic score,
and the audience score is very high as well. And with the Pat score, I mean, I remember two being
a blast because of that opening scene with the logs falling off the truck, which they homage in
this new one. There's a lot of kind of Easter eggs and callbacks to the franchise, which were really
fun and well done. But looking back, searching my memory, and I just, obviously we just watched and
talked about part one. This is the best of the franchise, which never happens. It's the best.
They did a nice job. Guys, we don't need a huge breakdown of the plot here. It's final destination.
It opens with a sequence that takes place in the 1960s, where as all these movies do,
the big disaster happens at the beginning. I would argue they don't really top that opening sequence
because it just keeps going and going. It's why I was laughing with the light clapping my hands,
like a little kid. I loved it. Yeah. You get to see an awful little kid get just demolished. It's
really funny. I was alone watching it and laughing. Yeah. I mean, I watched it a second time,
the movie, and loved it more the second time. That opening sequence plays like one of the all -time classic
like Looney Tunes cartoons. Like just every piece just falls perfectly into place.
The laughs hit, but the laughs are not, you know, the Marvel laughs that we talk a lot of shit about.
They're genuine, dark comedy horror laughs. Yeah. So the sequence, though, takes place in the 60s.
The woman that has the premonition that this disaster is going to strike is there with her
fiancee or about to be fiancee and she's pregnant and it's this beautiful thing where he's proposing
to her and she's going to tell him she's pregnant and blah, blah, blah. And there's a ton of people
because it's the opening of this restaurant in the sky, like this tower experience where you're
way up in the air. So there's tons of people there. She has the premonition. She prevents the entire
thing from happening. So now we jump to the future bloodlines. We're dealing with her granddaughter.
And all we know is the grandmother is still alive. The granddaughter is having these weird recurring
dreams about death and about the experience that her grandmother had in this opening sequence.
And she doesn't know why. She wants to talk to her grandmother about it. The family is trying to
shield her from the grandmother and saying the grandmother's crazy.
Rowan behold, she finally goes to visit the grandmother and the plot is hatched. And I thought
this was brilliant. She's like, look, I prevented a ton of people from dying. And because all those people
were supposed to die that day, none of them did. And now all of their bloodlines are, you know, everybody's
into it makes every movie. That's the thing. It's like, this is where it all started.
Everybody that has died in one of these movies is related to somebody that was in that tower at
the beginning of this. Yeah. It justifies exactly why Tony Todd's character knows so much about all
this stuff. He's got a great cameo in this. And a beautiful send -off to him as a human, right?
Apparently he knew, which I learned from our comments. He knew he was dying on the day and told them
and then they wound up rewriting the scene. Yeah, it is emotional. And this girl is going to try to
stop, you know, this from affecting her family. And the only way to do that is to either die and come
back to life or kill somebody. So, you know, you've sacrificed someone else to your fate.
It's, again, it's fun with us. It's the same plot as all the other movies. It's just, it's just,
this one scores because the deaths are awesome. The characters are fucking great. You like them.
You're sad to see them go. One of the characters, if somebody was saying to me, you know, they were
like, well, you know, who I hated at first, the guy with all the tattoos that, like, you know,
with the lip ring or whatever. And he's like, then I loved him. And I was like, I was the same way.
I thought he was annoying. And then I was like, this guy's my favorite character. And I was sad when he
died. Yeah, he just kept getting funnier as it went. He reminds me of Kyle Galner, who's an actor who's
in Smile and many other dinner in America and stuff. But yeah, he was so funny. Like, that's what really
hit me on the second viewing too was how many just genuine hard laughs I was having at the character
interactions. And then of course, the grim reaper comedy of it all. But I agree. All these people
in this movie are kind of delightful. And you do give a shit about them. And they're not all boiler
plate, you know, I love the dad who gets, eventually gets killed by the lawn mower and all that. But like,
I just liked the guy. I liked his wife and like her dark secret. And there's so much about it that's
just way more clever than it needed to be for this franchise. And I loved it. Big one for the directors
because their filmography, the biggest name is like leprechaun origins. You know, like they,
they were, it was a pretty big deal to get the reins to this and they fucking killed it. And then guy
Bucic, Laurie Evans Taylor wrote it. Bucic has done a lot of what's been good about horror. He did
ready or not. Castle Rock episodes, screams, screams six, Abigail, you know, so fun, decent horror
stuff, you know, he's a good horror writer. But this is his best out of all those movies I just mentioned.
I thought bloodlines was like, again, we're talking about the bar being super low. But this is
easily one of the couple best horror movies of the year. And one of my favorite movies of the year
surprised to be saying it. But I loved it. Wait, so this guy did you already said leprechaun?
No, oh, wait, yeah, leprechaun origins. I thought you meant, um, and then freaks, which I'm unfamiliar with.
Shout out to Dylan Postal, uh, WWE's horn swaggle who played leprechaun and has become a
halamine over the years. He sent me a signed copy of leprechaun origins.
Warwick Davis dropped out or do they just want a new blood? Origins is, that's why I got confused
for a second. And I thought you meant the one that's the direct sequel to the first movie, leprechaun
origins. They tried to go in a new direction. Yeah. And they made the leprechaun more of a monster
that doesn't talk or anything. Gotcha. Um, so it was, it was a fun of that. They were trying to make
it scary. They were, you know, and it was a good idea. But, um, you, yeah, we, you realize when
you take the personality and the talking and stuff away from the leprechaun, that's a big part of it,
you know, it's, it's, you know, but I think what they thought you can infer that he wants his gold,
but it helps to hear it from his mouth. Yeah, they, they, I forget how it unfolds, but, uh,
yeah, they like find gold and then, I don't know, you know, it's leprechaun. They find the golden
and there's problems. Sure. Uh, Brendan Fletcher is in that movie. He was also in, I know, I like
this guy. He was also in, uh, Freddie versus Jason. Uh, and he was my favorite character in that. But
anyway, we're not here to talk leprechaun. Uh, bloodlines. Look, it's a great movie. You're not
gonna be disappointed. Uh, and it has some of the most inventive and creative deaths I've ever
seen, ever in a horror movie. This, uh, oh, that's what I wanted to say. Well, for two things,
that thing with the MRI machine, we're like the magnet. I was like, this is insane. Like, this is,
like, wow, kudos to these guys, whoever wrote this, the guy's name, you said it, but I forgot
you sick. Yeah, I'm using any as a partner, but yes, so many just all -time kills that you're
not expecting this late in the game, you know, like we're, we're so far removed from like the slasher
era where we were always trying to top each other on the kills and stuff. That's kind of gone,
that spirit from these movies. But I'll be damned if everyone in this movie isn't just a banger,
and you think they can outdo the beginning, and maybe they don't, but there's lots of really fun,
cool stuff throughout. Big fan. The, uh, what's it called to, uh, talk about to,
talk about as well, meaning yeah, this thing puts the monkey to shame. Oh yeah, everybody like,
oh my god, the monkey, the deaths were so crazy. Yeah, there were some good deaths in the monkey.
They, they, they can't hold a fucking candle to, to the deaths in this in bloodlines. It can't
come near it, nowhere near it. Repeated gasps on a second viewing from my couch. I was just,
and it'll, it'll be on max. They just announced that I think in about a week, so don't go buy it if
you haven't seen it, but a lot of fun. Yeah, a lot of fun. Um, and I do think we are in what may,
a decade from now, look like a bit of a horror renaissance. Yeah, we're getting lots of different
kinds of horror movies and a lot of them are really good. You know, like we, we talk about all kinds
of movies on this show, but we really never have to veer away from horror. There's always something.
Um, and of course, you know, shutter has a whole nother tear of movies. I never know which ones
are going to be good and which ones were, you know, done in a backyard. But it's just, it's a good time
for low budget horror, big budget horror, violent horror, you know, a 24 cult horror, all kinds
of things are just firing on all cylinders. I thought, yeah, I agree with you. And I think, you know,
not to get on some fucking political stump here, but it's yeah, because horror, because the horror
movies are stopping, they're not agenda agendizing, if that's a word, themselves anymore. It's like,
just make a goddamn great movie. Just make a great movie. There doesn't have to be a social
queue in this. It did. Yeah, make a funny story after when he's like, all right, I'm going to make
this new Eddington, this political movie. He's like, I'll abandon horror. You know, I think people just
are like, leave that out of this. And for the most part, we do. We're not getting, uh,
Trump as of what that stuff's all happening in in bad sci -fi like Mickey 17 or whatever,
where you got Mark Ruffalo going like, beautiful, you know, come on, man, I heard my friend of mine.
Who whose name I will not reveal because he was so scathing about that movie. Oh, that's bad.
He was like, it was the worst fucking thing I've ever seen in my life. He's like, dude, I tried
three times to watch it. I love that guy's other movies. And I was like, I go, I never saw it. I go,
but when you told, when I heard it was that high concept of an idea and the budget was 200 million
dollars, I was like, that's, we're going to have problems here. And you got Ruffalo doing a
Trump impression for the entire runtime. Yeah, I didn't know that. Ruffalo. I love that. One of the
most outspoken anti -Trump guys and is just, just riding that Marvel wave, riding in bed with Disney
all day long. I mean, you'd be making, you can still count on me if old Marvel hadn't come along,
Ruffalo. You'd be making the nickel on on Disney's just Johnson. It's like brother. There is no more
evil institution on planet earth than Disney than Disney. I mean, you are that they're up there
with Amazon. I mean, it's, you know, look, we all use it, but the record show I did not say anything
critical of Disney as they now own 99 % of all entertainer. Thank you.
I think I might told you that you can't pitch a show to Hulu and FX anymore. You have to pick one.
They pick one for you because Disney is that Disney owns them all so they won't waste their time.
They'll say that's more of a Hulu or that's more of an FX. So you've immediately removed,
you know, one more place out of the three that might buy this thing. It's sick. Yeah, it's a little
nuts. Viacom used to do that a little. They're still doing that. Yeah, a little bit. It wasn't,
it wasn't that robust, but there was a little bit of like this might work downstairs. If you go,
if you want to go down to truth, uh, yeah, what the, how are the other Viacom? It was the man channel.
PT. Yeah. I mean, true TV. Viacom still owes me a lot of residuals from the Miss Pat show. And
they're like, well, you know, with everything going on with the merger. It's like, you just paid
the South Park guys a billion dollars and you paid Trump 16 million dollars. And that's just
today's news stories. So pull the other leg. Yeah, fucking liars. You don't have any money,
paramount. And then all the writers go okay. And then our agents go okay. And we never get paid.
My friend Tony Cassias, who's a comic here in Austin, it's like, he told me a story. It's such a simple
story, but it really sums up this business. He goes, yeah, uh, shit, I probably shouldn't have
said his name because it's about his manager. It's fine. Nobody's, his manager is going to hear
this. He goes, yeah, my manager, uh, I got a gig. It was just offered to me. And I told my manager,
I'm, I got this gig on my own. I'm going to go do it. And my manager said, well, well, well, well,
let me call them and get you more money. And he goes, uh, okay. Yeah. He goes, my manager calls
yeah, that's, uh, the offer is what it is. Anyway, uh, I'll add it to the committee commission.
I'll be commissioning it. Yeah, of course. What am I paying you? What are you talking about?
You're commissioning me. Yeah. I, in letting my prior agency go, I was just kind of like,
here's what I'm paying you off of jobs I've gotten myself. And here's what I've made from jobs
you've brought me. And the difference was vast. And I had so many receipts. And the amount
that I had made in five years of this agency was $1 ,500 from them. So I said, I, I'd love to hear
any argument you have here, but like, I'm not going to listen to it. Ultimately, the, the job was
packaging. And when the writers guild did away with packaging, they don't really have much to do
anymore, except take your money. But you quote, need them. So even though every job I get as a friend
calling me and going, Hey, you want a job? It's a great business from top to bottom. Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, it's a lot of fun. Yes. Uh, well, Joe, I know you did a bunch of podcasts this week. Would you
like to tell us where we can see you other than the show? Yeah. Well, the special is out. Please go
watch it. If you haven't, especially is Joe's best. And I just talked to here a few months ago,
about how I listened to everything he's ever done and how hard I laughed. And how I was never bored.
And I was all fantastic. I think this is his best. It's also a, it's got a directorial flair that
Joe's not even mentioning. Is he directed it? But there's a bit of a horror tinge to it. It's got a
vibe that I loved. I love the numbering of the acts. And then just relentlessly funny. And if you're
sick of standups who pretend that the world isn't falling apart, this is the opposite of that for
sure. Thank you, man. That's incredibly sweet. I appreciate it. Um, I really, really do, man. That
means a lot to me. Um, so it's on my YouTube, youtube .com slash at Joe to Rosa comedy. Uh, if you
want to go check out the latest episodes of Stavis world, uh, Risha fears you be tripping, uh, the Joe
Rogan experience, um, Matt and Shane secret podcast and your mom's house. Uh, I am on all of those
this week. Uh, and you can go and I hope enjoy. I hope you watch the special. I hope you enjoy it.
And, uh, and then yeah, next weekend, August 1st and 2nd, I'm in Rhode Island. Four shows at the
Denver. I was supposed to be but a good conflict has come up that is television related. Uh, and I'll
speak more on that later. So I can't be there, but we're going to reschedule those dates. And then I
have some dates through the fall. Go to Joe's in the in the bear spin -off set at his sandwich shop.
You can announce it, Joe. And boy, as he stressed out this week on a new episode. Yeah. Go to, uh,
Joe to Rosa dot com, please. And you will get, uh, you will get, uh, your, your info for your
tour dates and all your bullshit. Uh, oh, and we never said, contribute to final destination.
My log is up. Oh, hell yeah. Log. Get it? Yeah. My, uh, my hog is so up that I'm about to reach my
final destination by which I mean a climax. That's how much I enjoyed this movie. I want to
more out of my log is up. It was great. All right. Go ahead. I'm sorry. It's your turn to plug.
That's it. You know, you know, me where it see you in hell pod. And, and the people asking, what are
we doing for the 10 year anniversary? It is August the 3rd. So we're about a week away. And I think Joe
and I are just kind of Joe's got all this going on and then personal stuff. And, you know, I'm, I'm
have some career things of abruin. And I, we simply don't have an answer, which I feel bad about.
But we will do something to acknowledge the special day. We'll have a special episode. We just
don't know what it is yet. Um, yeah. Of course, you know, we don't ask you for much, uh, you know,
if we can celebrate online and tell people where to find us and how to sign up, that would be great.
You know, we're going to use this opportunity to raise awareness of something that shockingly we've
been doing for 10 fucking years. So yeah. Yeah. Uh, we love all of you. Thank you for the support.
10 years. We'll get, we'll get more into the nostalgia. Yes. And, and all that, uh, uh, when it,
when it's the actual time, but, but as it approaches, it's a great time to say, thank all of you for all of
your support, your love, uh, you know, your consistency. We appreciate it, people. Uh, we will see you
next time. And we will see you in hell.