🎵 I'll see you in hell. I'll see you in hell. And when the sound of your screams becomes the thing of my dreams, you know I'll say. I'll see you in hell. You know I will. I'll see you in hell. You know I will. 🎵
And some other things. I'm Joe DeRosa.
An electric start from Joe.
My name is Patrick Walsh.
What?
Was it too, not enough charge in it?
I mean, no charge. No charge.
Should I do it again?
Let's do it again.
I'll do it again. We'll keep all this in though.
Charge us up. It's Christmas time.
🎵 Ding dong, ding dong, ding dong, ding dong. It's time for we'll see you in hell. Here comes Santa. 🎵
There you go.
How about that?
There it is.
I don't know.
Perfect.
That's my note on that one.
I feel like I maybe need a new, uh, new phrasing for the intro.
Cause I feel like if you're a fan of the show and you hear me do it, you're just like, yeah, we, we know, we, we've heard the.
Yeah.
They know what it is.
They know why they're here.
I mean, we could just, we could start in media res.
In what?
One where it just like in the middle of, in media res means in the middle of the action.
Oh, okay.
We could just come up like mid movie corner and be like, figure it out.
You guys have been supporting us for 10 years.
You don't, we're not, we're not going to hold your hand anymore.
Like a, uh, like a, uh, what's his name?
Like an Aaron Sorkin kind of thing.
You start in the action, you know, picture up their mid -convo.
Yeah.
It's you and me like walking down the hall to the oval office somewhere like mid -convo and they just got to catch up.
One of our, uh, films that we're, that we're discussing.
I mean, we could do, do this right now if you want, do you want to do May, December?
Let's do May, December.
A movie that does start in media res.
It does.
It very much does.
This is a fascinating film.
I'm looking forward to talking about it.
Uh, you know, that'll be in a few.
What a, what a perfect description.
When's the last time you saw a movie that you could say is fascinating, but it definitely is like, I love that.
Well, we'll talk about it later, but it, um, I like a movie that, that lets you do a little bit of the work, but not the usual
indie trap of making you do all the work.
Like we've come up with no story, no nothing, figure it out.
That's not this movie.
This movie gives you a lot of information and you can do with it what you want.
And that's what I really dug about it.
Yeah.
It wasn't like, uh, what was that horror movie?
They came out that they made for like $300 or whatever.
Uh, about a year ago, it was, it was like a Blair Witch, not, not the COVID one.
Uh, but it was like the, man, it was like a paranormal activity, but it was weirder.
And everybody was saying it was super scary and they made it for like 10 grand.
And then I think you saw it and you said, I said, should we do it?
And you said, you're going to hate this.
Don't don't.
Skin of a rink.
Yes.
This wasn't a skin of a rink where you had to do all the work.
Skin of a rink was like 10, 10 minutes scenes, uh, looking at a child's toy.
And then at the end, maybe the toy moves a fraction of an inch.
Uh, it sounds like scat music, skin of a rink, skin of a rink.
Well, what is, what is skin of a rink?
A dinky dink skin of a rinky do.
I love you.
Who was it?
The wiggles Barney.
Oh, that's a thing.
I didn't even know.
Yeah.
Uh, yeah, I didn't even realize that.
Um, Joe, what's new for you?
We're both from the same coast.
I'm in hot Atlanta where it is cold and you were in New York.
Yeah, I'm in New York.
It's freezing.
Uh, I'm just packing some stuff up, uh, getting some more stuff to my house.
Uh, and, uh, gearing up for these holidays.
I'm, I'm hosting, I'm hosting Christmas for my family, which is, uh,
wild Clark Griswold.
Yeah.
I I'm like an antique Griswold.
There will be nothing on the walls.
I'm not excited.
You'll be like a Griswold's dad and that you have a lot of help from
Jack Daniels, I would imagine.
Yeah.
There you go.
And then when I do the big meltdown, holy shit, pass the time, everybody
will go, but he, but he didn't do anything.
This was all takeout food and we brought the food and yeah.
Um, cool.
Yeah.
I am going to Missouri for Christmas down here.
So it's just classic stuff.
They were like, I'll pay your round trip because I obviously don't live in
Atlanta, like, yeah, we'll pay your round trip.
And I'm like, well, I'm going to Missouri, which is like a
50 minute flight for a hundred dollars.
Can I pay that?
And you guys pay my way back to LA for like the two week Christmas break.
They were like, no, one of the other.
So I had to go home.
It's so basically it's like a thousand dollars more to go home for Christmas.
There's, you know, I get it.
I get it.
But I was like, if you're going to pay my flight home anyway, why don't I
just like rent a fucking car and go up there and then you can handle the
rest of the trip, but they won't do it.
They won't.
I don't understand.
They won't because the, because the origin is in Atlanta.
They won't pay one round trip Atlanta to LA and you just got to do it.
How I like, here's what you do.
Oh, that this won't save you anyone.
I was going to say, get the round trip from them from Atlanta to LA.
Just move it up a day or two and then fly to Missouri from LA.
But that's probably the same boat.
Not working.
They run a tight ship over there.
But, uh, you know, we shot, shot the premiere last night, my episode.
It was very fun.
Ms.
Pat always wraps up the taping by asking the audience if anyone
would like to suck my dick.
Oh, um, hands went up last night.
I just didn't take anybody up on it.
It's very embarrassing when she does.
Why didn't you get any of those guys' numbers?
Um, you know, I just, uh, if you're raising your hand to
suck someone's dick at a, at a sitcom taping, I don't know.
I, I, I'd like a little more of a chase than that, to be honest.
I'm like one, like I picture women in their like late sixties, like sitcom,
given the environment.
Like, I feel like there's not a lot of 19 year olds at a sitcom
taping, like, whoo.
Yeah.
No, Ms.
Pat, there is, cause there's nothing to do here.
We're in the middle of nowhere.
So it's like, we, we, it's like a club when we do it.
It's fun.
But, um, yeah, there were some old ladies in the mix as well, for sure.
I would love it.
It's a fun show.
Pat is getting a weekly blow job from a different church lady every week in Atlanta.
That'd be great.
That'd be really great.
The big thing here on the, on the apps is like these women are looking for money.
Like I'm like, Hey, here I am, you know, I'm around, you know, nice little
dating profile, what's up.
And then they'll hit me up.
We talk for a minute.
Oh, this girl's really pretty.
She's cool.
We talk for a second.
And then it's like, um, so yeah, do you want to maybe get together sometime?
And then I'll get like three links to the most expensive restaurants in Atlanta.
One of these three places.
And then I just.
Dematch and leave.
I don't mind, I obviously don't mind paying money for dinner or whatever, but
like, if you're dating to get a free, expensive meal, like fuck off.
That's a, yeah.
That feels like a, that feels like a test.
Yeah, like, you know, like girl, here's what you do.
Well, you know, when he asks for your number, you send these three restaurants
and if he doesn't, you know what I mean?
The, uh, it's a lot of, a lot of that's happening on, on Tik TOK lately.
I see it.
These women who are like in the parking lot, like I'm not going into this
restaurant, I'm a, I'm a, I'm at a different level than this, you know, like
there's just a, a lot of, a lot of class, uh, things happening in the dating world.
Now, I think because no one has money.
They're like, I'm going to view dating as like my way out.
And I know there are men who like that, who like like sponsoring a woman, you
know, like Drake, uh, that does not appeal to me at all.
Like I would, I need to know someone likes me for me and then I'll open the wallet.
Sure.
And, and, and Pat will play as when he picks the woman up and she steps into
the car, he will have Sammy Davis juniors.
I've got to be me playing as a subtle hint that this is what, who he is.
He'll follow that with the Bobby Darin.
Hey world, here I am.
Yes.
And at that point, they're usually out of my car.
That's usually a good test to see when we can dives, dives and
rolls out with Bruce Willis style.
You got to watch that video of the guy.
Hey, it went super viral.
Um, I can't remember the name of it.
I'll find it.
I have it somewhere and send it to you.
But there's the video.
Are you talking the guy who, who takes the girl to cheesecake factory and
she says, Oh, yeah, I saw that.
Yeah.
That was on like national news for some reason.
It's amazing.
It is amazing.
I would know instantly that that relationship was over.
Like I would never take a first day to the cheesecake factory, but I would, I
would love to date the type of girl who would not freak out about it, you know?
Cheesecake factory is great.
It's delicious.
You can order whatever you want.
You can get drinks.
They have food from all across the globe.
Now a first date.
I don't know.
Where did you come down on that?
Would you take a first date?
Where I came down on it.
I was like, I can't believe he's driving her home.
I would have been like, have fun.
You're walking.
Take care of those.
I saw him work.
I took a woman to Starbucks and she was like, so I get all dressed up and you
were taking me to a call.
I do not believe this.
You asked me out on a date.
And then he's like, get out of my car.
Puts the camera on her and he's like, I'll call the police to get you out of
my fucking car.
Let me defend my take because, uh, because I wouldn't take a date to, I, if,
if I said to a woman, do you want to meet for coffee?
Then I've been Steven.
Then I went to Starbucks, but the reason I was, would so harshly have
dismissed this woman is because he says, he's like, wait a minute, wait a minute.
You were an hour late.
I was trying like, I don't understand.
Like you, you, you, you did not seem like you were that enthused about this.
Uh, or into it.
You're an hour late.
I don't know.
I like, you know, I'm basically what I gleaned from him was I'm trying to
figure this out right now.
So, which is very fair.
Um, and her reaction was terrible.
I mean, my favorite reaction videos to it are the ones of like the older or like
middle -aged to older women watching it that are all being, that are all saying
to the guy, they're like, baby, you gotta, this girl's a problem.
Like, you know, like it's, it's so, and then the way she flips and starts to be
like, well, we can still go out.
I'd be like, it is generational.
Like there, it used to be like the, the Beverly Hills housewives, you know, like
where the women that were like, you know, trying to trap a rich man or something
like that, now it seems like that's the goal for about half the dating population.
And the other half is men not wanting, thinking that, that, that dating is
transactional that, Hey, if I spend a hundred, that equals one blow job.
If I spend two 50, that means you're giving me, let's see.
And that's just not how it works either.
All, all of the relationships I have had that worked, all the successful dating
situations, whatever you want to call them that I've had were a level of respect
and like between two people, where if I said, Hey, do you want to go for a walk
on our first date?
It would be like, awesome.
And I think anytime somebody's like, no, what you're going to do is take me to
dinner and drinks and dessert, just stop, stop.
You don't need that.
That's your first, imagine what the rest of your life is going to be like.
I haven't been out with a woman that even wanted to go to dinner.
I can't remember.
Like, it's not really that place.
Most women I go out with are, are like, I don't want to, I don't want to, what?
Like maybe on the fifth date we go get dinner.
I don't want to sit at dinner.
It's awkward.
It's really awkward.
By the way, when Pat said pussy that did not, I did not bleep that.
That was weird.
You said it and it cut out.
It's almost sounded like we edited it.
Oh, maybe that was God.
Yeah.
So you're clear.
I said it nice and clear now.
So people can edit me now.
Thank you for in case.
I mean, if it bleeped out, maybe people thought I said ass.
No, no.
You, you heard the P and then the C that you could tell what you said, but it
sounded like we did like one of those like YouTube edits anyway.
Um, uh, yeah, I, I, I don't understand sitting at dinner on a first
date, I couldn't think of a worse way to get to know outside of a
movie on a first date, I couldn't think of a worse way to get to know somebody.
Then it's so much pressure, man.
Jesus God.
It's so much pressure.
The classic let's get a drink is the standard.
And what I've noticed in Atlanta is if you say, Hey, let's grab a drink.
They immediately push for dinner and drinks and so forth.
I've had that once where I went to drinks with a woman and she was like,
now, you know, you need to buy me a meal, right?
That was back in Los Angeles.
She was like, you know, drinks is not a date, right?
And I was like, Oh, I'm having a really nice time.
I'm not hungry.
I'm sorry.
She's like, you're no, we're going to need to go somewhere else.
You're going to need to buy me dinner.
And I said, Oh, well I'll just say good night.
She's like, excuse me.
I'm like, I'll just say good night.
There's, they're so shocked that you like wouldn't cut your
arm off to have sex with them.
It's like, no, I don't, I don't need this.
I'm not, I'm not.
Yeah.
But, and I want to clarify when Pat says they're so shocked, not all women, women,
this type of woman gets it.
I've talked on this podcast about the numerous lovely relationships I've had
with women, but they're, you know, there there's things brewing out there.
You know, when, when, when a society is, is on the verge of crumbling,
when no one has money, people will resort to crazy shit for money.
And it's like, yeah, I don't think it's, I don't think it's an economics thing.
I think it's just, there are, there are archetypal personalities in the dating
field and this is an archetypal personality, you know, like you said,
there's also the guy that thinks it's all transactional, right?
Right.
There's the guy, here's the thing too.
The, the woman, there's a certain kind of woman that's reacting with
offense as the defense to a man, to a certain type of man who has
taken her to like, you know, like fucking jack in the box or something.
And people, that's the other thing, man, dating people get crazy.
They're scorned, they're hurt, you know, I, you know, when I'm,
when I was kind of broke, my, my defense, not defend, I don't want to say defenses.
I'm not, I wasn't yelling at people, but like my defenses were up on a date
because I felt like, you know, I w was I getting used, you know what I mean?
Like, I don't have the money for this and what, there's a lot, there's a
lot going in and out of it.
Uh, it's complicated, man.
It's not a normal thing.
We're not supposed to be dating, supposed to be like sizing each other up from
across a park or a field and then having sex on the grass and making a baby.
And then, and then, you know, immediately entering different roles for that baby.
Like it's, it's, we're two, someone you like, you bury your nose in their
asshole, see if you like that smell.
And, uh, if so, you know, you go behind a tree and TCOB, you know, is that's
the song that smells that what that's about.
Uh, I remember my dad was giving me a 45 minute lecture.
My dad loves Lynyrd Skynyrd and he was driving me to school or
something and I was like, what is this?
What is that smell?
And it led to a long lecture about the dangers of marijuana, at least in his
mind, I'm not saying he's right, but he says that smell is, uh, marijuana.
But now if you listen to the song, isn't it like the smell of fear, naked
gun, two and a half style.
Let me bring up those lyrics.
Only time I ever loved that song is in Dazed and Confused where they use it
beautifully.
It's the smell of death.
It's the smell of what?
The smell of death.
So this is all about here.
I'll read it real quick.
Whiskey bottles and brand new cars.
Oak tree.
You're in my way.
There's too much Coke and too much smoke.
Look what's going on inside you.
Ooh, that smell.
Can't you smell that smell?
The smell of death surrounds you.
Angel of darkness is upon you, stuck a needle in your arm, so take another
toke, have a blow for your nose and one more drink fool will drown you.
Ooh, that smell.
The smell of death surrounds you.
So it's like a, it's, it is a PSA.
My dad was right.
He wasn't right about the smell being weed, but he was right about
the song being anti -drug.
One of the guys, did they write this in response to who, from what
Lynyrd Skynyrd died?
I think every member of Lynyrd Skynyrd died and then they replaced them all with
their brothers and then all the brothers died, like 25 members of Lynyrd
Skynyrd have died.
It's a, I've never gotten too into Skynyrd.
What about you?
No, I bought one day at Amoeba.
They had every album of theirs in great shape for like a buck a piece.
So I have their entire catalog and sometimes, you know, on like a Saturday,
if you're pre -gaming or something, you throw on that smell, you're going to
have a nice time, but like, you don't want to go with a whole Skynyrd album.
You just want the hits.
The, uh, I just saw a kiss on the, uh, farewell.
I saw the second to last ever kiss show at Madison square garden.
And, uh, my friend, let me ask where the tickets for the last show going for like
substantially more than the second to last.
Well, my friend, Nick Simmons, son of Jean, uh, is a good friend of mine.
And, uh, he got me free tickets on the floor and then, and then he also got me
against the stage at Madison square garden.
Yeah.
So I was literally, I was so close.
I went to put my drink down at one point.
I almost put it on the platform that Jean Simmons descended from the ceiling
on at the beginning of the show.
Uh, it was the, it was the craziest thing I've ever experienced.
I'm not a huge kiss fan, uh, but I liked them and, and it was fun hearing the
song, the song, you know, they opened with Detroit rock city as they came down
from the ceiling with like fire shooting.
It was crazy.
It was awesome.
Um, anyway, it was a lot of fun.
He told me what some of the people paid to be in that area.
I don't even want to repeat it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
More?
Yeah, it was, it was, it was insane.
It was insane.
You know, it was insane and, uh, it was a lot of fun.
Um, uh, and, but then here's the highlight.
This is, this is how this pertains to this episode or the show.
I mean, he said after the show, he goes, let's go backstage and, uh,
man.
So me and my buddy, Paul went backstage with Nick and we were in the green room
and there was Jean and all of his get up.
And I didn't bother him because the guy had been dressed like a demon for six
hours at this point.
I'm like, he probably just wants to go get changed.
Probably that, uh, that leather crotch ain't smelling too sweet either.
Uh, I look over though, who's sitting there, Nick's mom, Jean's wife, miss
Tweed of cinema fame.
Uh, yeah.
And, uh, I go, I go, would it be cool if I said hi to your mom?
He goes, go ahead.
Yeah, of course.
And I go over to her and I go, I go, hi, miss Tweed.
Um, it's very nice to meet you.
I'm a friend of your son's.
I just want to tell you, I love your episode of Frasier because she's
in an awesome episode of Frasier.
I go, I love your episode of Frasier.
And she goes without missing a beat.
She goes, Oh, shut the fuck up.
I started laughing.
I'm like, huh?
She's probably never heard that from her fan base.
Never.
Yeah.
I think she maybe thought I was messing with her and I was like, I'm not joking.
I love the show Frasier.
I was like, I really like your episode.
And she was like, Oh, fuck you.
Come on.
And I was like, I'm serious.
And then we actually started talking for a while.
She was really fun and really funny.
At one point I go, I go, I love Nick.
You raised a really great kid.
So congrats.
And she goes, Oh, fuck off.
Uh, that's pretty much her go -to response.
The, uh, but I saw him like two days later and he's like, my mom loved you.
She thought you were, I was like, Oh, wow.
That's cool.
So, uh, he mentioned at one point, he goes, you know, I'm trying to get my parents
into the onto podcasts, but I was like, well, I will tell you now it is an open
door for either of your parents, uh, to come on, we'll see you in hell, but I
would love to have Shannon tweet on this podcast and talk to her about all the,
the movies of the nineties.
And that'd be fun.
I would have to tell her.
I have only watched her filmography on fast forward and pause.
I have never seen a single plot detail.
I have never seen her act, but when she was, uh, when I was young,
boy, she was something.
My friend, uh, Mike Bello and I used to make up when we were high, uh, cause it
was, you know, we're just coming out of high school, the nineties, we would get
high and we would make up fake, uh, uh, blurbs, like, you know, the back when
like TV guide was a thing, like the descriptor for Shannon tweet movies.
Uh, that would be great.
And it would make us laugh really hard.
So it'd always be like, it'd always be like when a reluctant handyman
moves into the neighborhood,
a reluctant handyman.
Yes.
Yeah.
Uh, an ignored wife starts more than just a little trouble, you know,
like it was always like, no, it would have, it would have to be a, uh, a
carpentry pun for what the wife's getting into an ignored housewife starts,
you know, building a new house of, of lies and betrayal.
That's true.
It was, they were always like, I was thinking like, go ahead.
Sorry, sorry.
I was thinking how crazy it was that your friends with, uh, Jean Simmons
son.
And then I remembered because I don't think of him as this.
I just think of him as my buddy and I should probably be using him for more
things.
I am good friends with Joe Perry's son of Aerosmith, which I'm friends
with one of Joe's sons too, which friend are you, I'm friends with Aaron.
Are you friends friends with not, not Aaron, the other one.
Okay.
Yeah.
There's a couple of kids, Aaron, Aaron is well, I was about to tell
Aaron's biological history.
Who gives a shit?
Uh, they're all very nice kids, but Aaron was shocked by how nice my friend
his name's Tony, but, uh, I met him at a wedding.
He, you know, we were in the same wedding together and I've kept in touch.
He lives in LA, but like crazily nice for growing up in that world, you know,
although maybe Joe Perry's the nicest guy on earth.
Who fucking knows?
We met Joe Perry once.
Uh, he did, uh, cause because of Aaron, Aaron got him on when me and Burr had a
video show, we had Perry on and Perry, just on the phone, we met him a couple
times, Bill got to know him a little bit, but, but he was always very nice.
And we had him on the phone and he was, he was incredibly normal.
It was like, he was just very, very down to earth.
And like, it was funny at one point we, like, he was kind of, he, he just
was so normal at one point, Bill was giving him a little shit about like,
Joe Christ, you sound like you might go walk into traffic or something.
You feeling okay?
And he was just kind of like, ah, you know, man, it's just the same old shit.
And what are you like?
He just sounded like a regular old guy.
Like his job was his job.
It didn't matter what the job was.
Um, I hear that, but there I've now met Nick and I'm blanking on his sister's name.
I've gotten to know Nick very well at this point, but like the
sister, I don't know very well, but they're extraordinarily normal kids.
Like he's got no ego.
He's got like, no, like, do you know who my dad is?
Like none of that shit.
He's just like, you know, who seems normal as fuck is the Osborne kids.
Yes.
I keep seeing them in clips as adults with families.
And I met, um, Kelly, she was doing it.
She was really funny actually doing an improv show that my buddy, damn
black listener to the show put on.
Um, and I'm, I'm just amazed you grow up not only having Ozzy Osborne
as your dad, but then being on a reality show where the entire world
is making fun of your family and they just seem like normal, cool people.
I would not be, I can tell you that much.
I think it's, I think it's why, you know, and then, and then you look at a church
family and their kid is on heroin or whatever, I think it's just the exact
opposite. I think, I think when you're raised around arena rock and roll or
whatever, like you rebel by not doing a lot of that stuff and not thinking it's
that romantic to be on the road and to, to you, even if your dad, even if your
dad, you know, I don't think Joe Perry's a big drinker.
I don't think Gene Simmons drinks at all.
I don't think, um, Sharon Osborne was probably pretty straight and narrow,
but my point is even if your dad isn't the Ozzy who's going wild, your dad's
going to know a few Ozzy's and I think as a kid you see it and you're not like
sure intrigued by it, you know?
Yeah, no, for sure.
It's like the, you know, the parents who deprive their kids of all sweets and
then wind up with a, you know, super overweight kid.
It's like, that's, that's what happens.
If you completely take something out of their diet, they're going to think like,
Oh, I've got to get this, I got to get access to this.
You know, I often wonder if my dad hadn't told me from day one, like never
have a drink boy, never have a drink.
Like if I just wouldn't have grown up and not thought anything of it and had a
normal existence and normal relationship to alcohol, who knows?
Yeah.
It just does not seem like the good way to parent, you know, fear -based.
My dad's whole thing was no, if you have sex, you'll get AIDS.
If you have a drink, you'll die.
If you smoke, you know, it's the classic boomer thing.
We had all the fun.
Now you have no fun.
I think, I got a quick news psycho and I think we should go to the movie corner.
I'm only going to do one in the corner today because it's going to relate to my
news psycho.
Okay.
You just refuse to follow the rules of the corner, don't you, Joe?
Well, I, it's been a busier season than I've expected.
I haven't watched a ton.
I've got three for the next episode though.
Uh, I, um, I guess I'll do the new psycho first.
I find this very interesting.
Uh, the daily wire, which is Ben Shapiro's thing, um, daily wire plus,
which is their streaming service.
They've announced an adult animated comedy series called Mr.
Burcham, uh, which was created by Adam Corolla.
Now, why do I find this interesting?
It's not because I'm surprised that Ben Shapiro has a streaming service or that
that streaming service is doing a cartoon.
Um, I'm, and I'm not surprised that Adam Corolla would be involved because
Adam Corolla certainly leans right.
Um, and I've met him, nice, nice guy, but some of the cast is surprising.
Uh, some of it isn't, it, you Roseanne's on it.
I read this press release.
I was like, okay.
Yeah.
Like that makes sense that Megan Kelly is doing a voice, but yeah, I keep going.
There were some people that I was like, what the fuck?
So, so, well, I, I want to, I want to say, and I don't speak for you obviously.
So I'll just, I'm, you know, with this kind of stuff, I like to
say my opinions are my own.
People get a certain way sometimes about these opinions.
And I don't ever want to speak for Pat when I'm expressing this.
Not that I'm going to say anything crazy, but I was surprised to see, uh,
Rob Riegel's on it Holocaust did not happen ladies and gentlemen, and
Holocaust.
I spell it C O S T because what is the cost?
No, uh, Roseanne, Rob Riegel is on it.
Patrick Warburton is on it.
My, my buddy, Tyler Fisher's on it.
Um, my buddy, Kyle Dunnigan's on it.
Um, I, I look, do I like everything that comes out of Ben Shapiro's mouth?
No.
Do I think that everything he says is wrong?
Uh, I think he makes some valid points and I think he's way off base in other
areas, like most people in on earth.
There are very few people where I'd go.
Everything he says is always wrong.
Um, Alonzo Bowden, a friend of mine, a buddy of mine is on the show.
Um, Jay Moore, a buddy of mine on the show, Danny Trejo on the show.
Um, I, I saw such an, well, I'll get to that anyway.
So, so what I, what I work, what I'm getting to is would I work with Ben
Shapiro?
I don't know if I would, I don't think that I would, I don't think it's on
for me, uh, even as somebody who will do stuff sometimes on Fox, like I think
Ben is probably a little too far in, in, in a certain direction.
That said, uh, I cast no judgment to anybody working on this show.
And I can't believe I'm saying this.
I breathe the sigh of relief when I saw it, because I felt like it was
whether agreed upon, whether agreed with or not to me, it felt like a step
towards we can just do what the fuck we're going to do and work where we're
going to work.
And every single thing isn't an opportunity to judge or present
your politics to people.
Uh, in other words, somebody who's been classically liberal, like, uh, at
least in the public view, like Rob Riggle as part of the daily show can go work on
this and it's not some statement on Rob Riggle's part.
It's Rob Riggle going and working at a place that, you know, let's be honest
people, everybody can get mad about daily wire plus streaming for some of
the content they've put out ethically when it all boils down to it.
They're no fucking worse than Amazon prime or any of these other streamers.
So, I mean, what are we talking about?
But, um, that's my take.
I don't know what your take is Walsh, but I just find it very interesting
that things have seemed to cooled off a little bit, you know?
Uh, my, my take is I hate Ben Shapiro and everything he represents.
I'm not an Adam Garrolla guy.
I don't like Megyn Kelly or a lot of the people involved with the show, but, um,
I think they are wise to be trying to make their own art, you know, if we're
going to keep this separate society, they can't keep letting liberals control
the entirety of film, television, animation, music, et cetera, you know?
So, um, but what do you think, what do you think about, yes, I agree with that.
The thing that's interesting to me is, is like, I don't think Patrick Warburton
is never going to work in a liberally produced project ever again because of this.
So my point is, is like, I think it's finally time that somebody can go do a
job and then go to another area of this business and do a job.
And it's not like, no, no, you're on that team now.
You know what I mean?
Oh, I agree.
My guess is each for each one of these actors, representatives was probably,
they probably had a long conversation.
Like, is this worth the risk?
Is this worth associating yourself with the right?
And that is pretty fucked up.
You know, that the, the, uh, it's just the problem we've been talking
about on the show from day one.
If we keep acting like we're two different countries, we're
never going to get anywhere.
And that's, you know, so I don't know.
I also think too, which, you know, we're w let's not get it too into the heavy
weeds here, but I will say, especially in recent months, I have a lot of friends
in the business who were very classically left, who are getting mad now and going,
I can't do this anymore.
This is great.
Like I can't, this is, you know, and, and, and kind of starting to rebel a little
bit, not picking on the left, but you know what I'm saying?
Um, so I wonder if there's any of that in this of just not necessarily a rebellion,
but, but just a fed up in this of just, I don't give a shit.
You know, like, like Pat and I, another good thing I saw Adam Carolla produces
stand -up shows at the Improvital.
It'll be Adam Carolla and friends.
I've seen Pat and Oswald do those shows.
Yeah.
And I'm like, that's cool.
Patton's classically very, very much out there liberal.
And it's cool to see them doing a show with Adam Carolla.
I, I, I, I'm just relieved to see a little of that happening again.
Um, and I hope that it continues to personally, um, you know, I thought that,
um, Oh man, I forgot what I was going to say.
There was something that this made me.
Oh, I saw, this made me furious.
I saw a review, not a review, but, but an article about the show.
It was from some nonsense website.
You want to talk about sickeningly, sickeningly, sickeningly, sickeningly, pandering.
Uh, the, the guy that wrote the article, I think it was a man, went down the
whole list of, of actors, uh, that are on this thing, took the obvious shots at.
You know, Candace Owens and whatever.
Doesn't mention Alonzo Bowdoin.
And then goes, gets to Danny Trejo and goes, I'm going to give Danny a pass
because he'll do anything anyway.
Oh, fuck you.
Fuck you.
You fucking pandering douche.
Anyway.
Um, so anyway, so, um, so that was an interesting article.
And the one thing I'm going to do in the movie corner, you know, you can go if you
want, but it transitions into this.
Do you want me to just do it?
Go for it.
Uh, I started watching the ranch, the Ashton Kutcher sitcom with Sam Elliott
on Netflix and the disgraced now disgraced Danny Masterson.
It is odd seeing Danny Masterson play a jovial.
We watched as a room on a show I was on.
We watched just the, I go, let's watch the first joke of the ranch.
And, uh, it was, it was Sam Elliott opening the fridge and he goes, almond
milk, how the fuck they get milk out of an almond.
Yeah.
I was like, you know what?
I'm out.
I, you know, I don't need this.
Uh, I will say this about the show.
Uh, there is a, there is, there is a strong character, you know, base there.
Uh, Sam Elliott is quite funny, uh, in it.
Kutcher is funny.
They're, they're all, they're all pretty funny.
You know, um, Masterson understand.
Deborah Winger, right?
Yeah.
Deborah Winger.
It's a great cast.
I love Deborah Winger.
Yeah.
Masterson disappears for obvious reasons.
Uh, in about, I think like episode 12 or something like that.
Uh, or no, it's, it's further down.
I thought he made it longer than that on the show.
They do.
It's four seasons that, but that are cut into two parts and he disappears at
like the top of part three or something.
Um, because then they say that his car, his motorcycle crash, his
body was never found, it gets.
Oh, Alicia Cuthberts in it.
It's a really good cast.
Uh, the, and you know what?
We forget this was this sitcom came out in 2015 or 16.
This thing compared to now, as far as sitcom writing goes, is
like the days of yesteryear.
Like you're like, Oh, remember when sitcoms were like this?
You know what I mean?
Like, so not all Ms.
Pat's a great sitcom, but you know what I mean?
Like we've talked a lot about how watered down at all has sort of become.
Oh yeah.
Um, so I found it, even though it's not being made now refreshing.
Uh, and I liked that I was like, Oh yeah.
There was a time where you could have a liberal character like Ashton
Kutcher's and Deborah Winger's, and you could have a conservative
character like Sam Elliott's and you could like all the characters, even
if you didn't agree with all of them and you couldn't have them have their
conflicts and Sam Elliott isn't just a bad guy and, and you know, as far as
that nuance is concerned, I thought the show was a success.
Uh, I haven't seen all of it yet.
Ethan Embry's in it.
Um, you know, and I liked that they, they're unapologetically like drinkers
and fuck ups and, you know, they have sex.
I don't know.
Uh, so I don't think it's going to be anything that I love, but I read, I, when
I started watching it, I went and looked at an old review of it and it was a good
review and it said, you know, it's a red state sitcom, uh, but it's very funny.
And I was like, again, I was like, man, I hope that those days are coming back
when you can say about something.
Well, you know, it's like a red state thing, but it's good because, you
don't have to go, well, it's red state.
So it's evil.
Um, no, I hear you.
So anyway, and I think, I think the truth is the only way that's going to happen
is if the right starts coming up with better shit, because by and large, look,
I'm a liberal person.
I'm not insane about it, but I'm a liberal person for sure.
They're not making quality entertainment, the right or the left, the right.
Although it's not the left is thriving now either.
I'm just saying whenever there's a, a conservative or right wing project, it's,
it's the worst, whether it be a movie or a show or like, uh, you know, a late
night talk show, whatever it is.
Well, they have to, they have to stop.
I mean, look, the late night talk shows are all playing the game of, you know,
Colbert's all Trump, you know, whatever, right.
Uh, yeah, Gutfeld who's a friend, but they do all Biden stuff.
You know what I mean?
Like, right.
It's, it's, it's a political war on these late night shows to an extent.
Um, as far as, yeah, the content overall goes, the left is winning
in making better content.
The right was, was suffering from exactly what we're talking.
They were making rebellion content all the time.
Well, we're going to make a movie that makes fun of trans people
because that's, they're telling us we can't, you know, whatever it was.
Yeah.
You know, this Shapiro show, oddly enough, sounds like that.
Well, it's a Corolla show.
That's what it is.
It sounds like, you know, it's based on his cranky anchors character.
It sounds like a cartoon you would have seen on Comedy Central.
Right.
So maybe it just is, and maybe, you know, uh, you know, we'll see.
I don't know.
I watched a movie, Joe, that I know you will love.
I give you my highest recommendation.
As I was watching it, I was loving it.
And I was thinking that Joe DeRosa would love this movie.
It is called the Kane Mutiny Court Marshall.
Uh, it is yet another remake of the, of the classic Kane Mutiny
play, famously brought to life by Humphrey Bogart is probably the
most famous version of it.
Um, and this is William Friedkin's last movie.
Yes.
I heard about this.
It's a courtroom drama set 99 .9 % in one room in a Naval courtroom.
There's one or two quick scenes outside of the courtroom, but damn, it was so
good.
It's like, I talked about that anatomy of a fall movie where it was like,
just a solid courtroom drama that's on these top 10 lists all year.
It's because these genres, when they are done well, are the fucking shit
and we never see them anymore.
Um, but this, so Kiefer Sutherland is an actor that I have seen play mostly bad
guys over the course of my life.
I don't think I've ever seen a performance where I would say Kiefer
Sutherland was excellent in that movie, except that maybe Freeway with Reese
Witherspoon, I think he's awesome in that, but this is the best I've ever
seen him.
He's got a supporting role for sure, but he's queeg, which is the big part.
And the, basically the entire trial is there's this captain out on a ship who
everyone just hated.
He was an asshole.
And this young, uh, soldier played by Jake Lacey is like, I've had enough.
And he takes over the ship and the purpose of the trial is, did he do, was
this a mutiny, did he do this without provocation or did he do this because
Kiefer Sutherland is nuts and losing his faculties and Jason Clark, the actor
from 50 % of movies, uh, these days is the lawyer for Jake Lacey.
And he tells him at some point, what we're going to need to do is not prove
that he, he acted crazily out at sea.
We need to show this jury that this man is crazy.
So they like start provoking him and it's like a psychological
thriller in a courtroom.
It's so good.
Um, there's a reason this is like one of the most famous plays of all time.
It's pretty much the, uh, the text, you know, there's not many updates to it.
Lance Reddick plays the guy who's running the proceedings.
He's obviously an incredible actor from the wire.
Um, and there's lots of good character actors throughout, but I highly
recommended it's on Showtime and Paramount Plus, and it's one of the
best movies of the year, easily.
Just a great script, great final bow for Friedkin loved it.
Is it like a, excuse me.
Is it like a, you know, like a mammoth style, Glen Gary, you know, fast talk.
Yes, but it reminded me more of like the, the 90s HB, the made for HBO
movies that you, you always are watching Joe, um, where it's just like,
it's not like people screaming.
It's not people jumping up like I object, there's some of that, you know,
but for the most part, it's just a really solid story.
Very, very well told.
And Kiefer, I gotta say again, I hope he gets nominated for shit.
Cause he was great in him.
Yeah, one of a great one of those, uh, the, the HBO is that you're talking
about is, uh, above suspicion with Gene Hackman, never saw him where he gets
accused, uh, you know, he's a, he's a reputable figure in the town, you know,
they're in like a sort of a Hawaii beach kind of town, something.
Yeah, he gets, uh, he's, he's, I can't remember if he's a politician or
something, but he's the, it's the night of a big gala for him or something.
And he's on his way to it and he's apprehended and brought in under
suspicion of potentially, uh, raping a younger woman.
Okay.
And of course he's saying he didn't do it.
And the whole movie is like him, you know, in the, not interrogation room,
but in like the, the, the chief of police is, you know, whatever office sitting
there, cause it starts with him being like, look, this is probably nothing.
We had to bring you in to talk to you.
And then as they keep talking, it becomes more that he might have
done it, but you're not sure.
Right.
And it starts to become about like, whether if I didn't do this, the
damage done right now is irreparable.
Like, you know, it's it, but the whole movie is them in that room and people
kind of coming in and out and adding details and whatever, it's great.
You need, you need a, a plus script to make that work.
But yeah, I mean, uh, what was that?
There was one called masks, which was, uh, two, two married couples in the
aftermath of a school shooting that came out a couple of years back.
That was excellent too.
It was, I mean, too depressing to really recommend, but, um, yeah,
there's something for that.
I don't mind a film to play if the dialogue is great and you get amazing
actors in it, I know people are like, eh, it's just, they just shot the play.
I'm like, yeah, all right.
Plays are usually well written.
Sorry.
It's called under, no, not under suspicion is above suspicion.
Well, now I'm seeing something called under suspicion.
Oh yeah, that's it from 2000.
Yeah, that's it.
Under suspicion from 2000.
It's Hackman Freeman, uh, Monica Bellucci and Thomas Jane.
Good cat.
I'll watch it.
I'll put it on my list.
Um, I watched on the plane to Atlanta due date, and that is my, my semi pro Joe.
That's one that I saw on theaters.
I saw it as a pathetic plans, trans automobiles ripoff.
I don't know that I laughed once and especially at the time, I really
liked Robert Downey Jr and where his career was headed.
It was kind of the start of his new Ironman career.
And Galifianakis was like the funniest actor on earth.
So I was pumped and very let down by the movie.
Um, watching it again on a plane.
It's a perfect plane movie.
Um, I wasn't slapping my knee, but it was entertaining throughout the
plot is shaggy at best, you know, that the Downey Jr is trying to get home,
uh, for the birth of his kid.
But then there's also some suspicion that Jamie Foxx has fathered his kid.
It's a really weird subplot.
Um, but entertaining, you know, it's a, it's a sea level plans,
trains, but reasonably entertaining.
And there's a scene where Downey Jr punches a eight year old boy in
the stomach as hard as he can.
Give them the shush finger on the way out.
That made me laugh really hard on a plane.
So, um, due date, I apologize.
You're better than I remembered, but still not great.
And my last one, I got a shout out, Tom Petty colon, somewhere you feel free.
Um, it is one of those, Hey, we found a treasure trove of, uh, videos from some
period of an artist's life, and usually that's just a cash grab.
It doesn't hold together as a movie.
I thought this was really sweet, really beautiful.
And mostly because we don't know a great deal about Tom Petty.
The man I read his biography, which was great, but you just don't
see much of him hanging out.
You know, he didn't do a lot of interviews.
We don't know what he was like really.
So this is 90 minutes spent with him making the wildflowers album,
which is his best album by far.
And you know, he's kind of trying to break free from the heartbreakers.
He's working with Rick Rubin.
They have interviews with Rubin and all the heartbreakers present
day to kind of comment on it.
But the real appeal of this is all the footage of Tom Petty writing
and recording wildflowers, um, similar to that, that Beatles get back thing.
You know, if you're into that, how an album is made, how a song gets
constructed, how, you know, a piece of music changes over time, well worth
watching it's free on, uh, Amazon prime.
Nice Joseph.
Let's talk about our movie at hand.
Yep.
May, December, the new film from Todd Haynes, uh, Todd Haynes.
I actually, I had a, uh, professor in college film professor who
was obsessed with Todd Haynes.
So we watched even like his short films and stuff.
And the guy, to be honest, sorta leaves me cold.
I like his more, um, commercial stuff.
I like Carol.
I like far from heaven, but like the more experimental shit is not for me.
This is sort of the perfect mix and he didn't write it, but it's the perfect
mix of an experimental movie and just a classic entertaining story.
Very well told.
Um, the plot is basically this.
I thought of a funny, uh, joke name for the movie would be predator versus
predator as opposed to alien versus predator.
But what it is is Julianne Moore, an actress who I think has been
pretty spotty in recent years.
She is amazing in this movie.
She is awesome in this movie.
Uh, Julianne Moore plays a, you know, a woman in her late fifties.
As the movie starts, we see that she has chill.
What, what appears to be may be, um, a family ranging in age from little kids
on up to, you know, how old is the guy?
25 or something, but you learn that this is like a Mary Kay Latino situation.
The movie was very much influenced by that real life case and she now lives
with and is married to a former student of hers.
She was a teacher.
She had sex with him when he was in seventh grade.
I don't think she was together.
Let me interrupt you.
I don't think she was a teacher.
I think it was just that they worked at that pet store together.
You're right.
I'm sorry.
And she asked, she asked his boss at the pet store.
Um, that's, that's one of the reveals as the movie goes, it's like she wanted
us to hire a young guy, like that.
The plot keeps thickening because she's like, look, I mean, he, he, he
was in control or whatever.
There's a very famous interview with Mary Kay Latino and the kid.
And the interviewer keeps going, Mary Kay, like you, you were in
charge here in the situation.
And she keeps turning to this kid and going, who was in charge?
Tell him who was in charge.
And the boy and the interviewer are like, he was 13.
Yeah.
He wasn't in charge.
And she's like, who was in charge?
Answer the question.
So it really gets into the mind of, and kind of, you know, Julianne Moore
is not judging this character.
Like she is so convincing in her beliefs that you're like, there are
moments in this movie where you sort of buy it like, okay, if they were really
in love and then you're like, God, what am I sick?
You know, that's the beauty of the movie.
Now this, the second thing that, that comes into this is that as the movie
starts, Natalie Portman is playing a narcissistic vein, uh, Hollywood actress.
Who is coming to stay with Julianne Moore and her husband to study Julianne
Moore for an upcoming movie about the situation.
Well, when you, when it, when it first, let me interject if I could, when it,
when you first meet Portman, she's not presented very narcissistically.
She's presented as it's quite gracious.
Yeah.
Uh, when they go and then that's to get in their good graces.
Right.
Exactly.
But then then it's the predator starts to come out and, and as you're watching,
I texted Pat, I go, Portman is demonic in this.
Like, like it's like, like you, you're like, you, you, you, I don't know.
For me personally, as, as Portman's character story unfolded, I found her to
be more off -putting than the woman that married the kid after a while, cause I
was like, well, Christ, this woman does know better.
The other woman, maybe she's, she might be crazier.
I don't know.
There's, there's like, there's, there's a little question mark around why she
did what she did to it, but Portman starts to become portrayed as like, no,
this woman is in full control of what she is doing right now.
Yes.
Um, and, and, and, uh, seriously, we usually just kind of roll with the spoilers,
but if you think you might be interested in this movie, don't listen to this.
Watch the movie.
It's on Netflix and then come back and listen to it.
We're going to be discussing the movie with spoilers, but, um, yeah, it, it,
Portman, like when Joe texted me that I was like, interesting that you're saying
Portman's demonic and not the pedophile, but the truth is Portman.
So Portman eventually fucks Julianne Moore's husband.
She's 36 and so is he, and they start flirting and hitting it off
because they're age appropriate.
Um, so they make much more sense as a couple than him and Julianne Moore.
Also, we see these scenes of Julianne Moore and him, like in the bedroom,
where you realize the insane level of control she has over him.
And she's like fucked up.
Like he gets into bed and she's like that whole scene where she's like,
I smelled the smoke on you.
I what I'd like is for you to shower before you come to bed or whatever.
I was like, oh, that's miserable.
Yeah.
Then she starts crying uncontrollably and then he has to come for her all the
time that the Portman, well, let's, let's backtrack.
Portman starts to get her hooks into this family.
You see her slowly starting to overstep her bounds.
Uh, and at first it's, oh my God, I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to, you know, she's so polite.
She's so, if, if at any point I'm too, it's too much and you need me to stop
asking questions, just tell me what she's very, very manipulative.
There is a scene where everything turns, where she goes and speaks to the local
high school acting class that Julianne Moore's daughter is in.
Yeah.
A kid who's being a smart ass named Cameron in the class immediately
goes, you ever do any sex scenes?
The class laughs, the teacher reprimands the kid and Natalie Portman
immediately goes, yes, I have.
And she starts answering the question in a way that you're like, this is
the perfect way to handle a kid being a smart ass, she's going to now answer
him very maturely and show him like, there's nothing funny about it.
Grow the fuck up.
Right.
But then she starts to talk in way too much detail about too far.
You realize she's got no boundaries.
And then it's just like tar in that way.
They, they, they reveal these things to you very subtly, but you're like, Oh,
so this person's even shittier than I thought.
It's great.
And she says in that scene, you, sometimes you don't know, you forget
that it's just a scene and you go with the rhythm and basically saying like
you and you, the other person might be into you getting off on this, but you're
not sure it's really inappropriate.
And then somebody asked her about playing villains in a movie or
something, and she talks about why, why they're the most interesting characters
because that's the gray area and all that stuff.
And the daughter gets very offended because she's portraying her mother.
Um, that is the scene where it all turns and you start to see the, the
movie now has shifted and everything from that point on that you see Portman
do is something where you're going.
She's it's, it's all the metaphor of getting into the rhythm in the sex
scene, including fucking literally fucking the husband, uh, with a
giant prosthetic penis.
That was very disturbing.
Yeah.
And then he says to her when he's, when he feels used, he says to her, he's
like, I thought we had a connection.
Like, what was this?
And she says, it's just what adults do, which is the condescending
way to say you're a child.
So now she's controlling the child.
Uh, the other scene where, and it's a double whammy of, of learning dark shit
about Portman's character is this quick, beautifully written phone call.
And she's talking to the director of this movie.
She's going to make about Julianne Moore and the son.
And you realize through context clues that she's fucking the
director who was a married man.
So she clearly lives for drama.
And in addition to that, she finds that the boys who are auditioning to play
this 13 year old that she's going to fuck, she doesn't think they're hot enough.
And the director's like, I think we need to wrap this call up.
Like this sleazy Hollywood's director's like, you need to come home.
Like what's wrong with you?
Um, the writing, I looked up the act, the, the writer's name.
Her name is Sammy Birch.
Um, it's a, it's a brilliant script.
I mean, it deserves to win or best original screenplay.
Uh, and the actresses, you know, Portman and Moore are obviously
brilliant actresses, but I haven't seen them this on fire since like 20 years ago.
They bite into these characters so well.
I thought Todd Haynes directed it so well.
There are moments where it's almost like they're doing, they're pushing up against
a parody of a lifetime original movie about this subject, like when at the very
beginning, when Julianne Moore throws open the fridge and she's like, Oh no.
And the music goes, and she's like, we don't have enough hot dogs.
Yeah.
I was like, Oh, okay.
It's doing like a comedy parody type thing, but no, it's a tone all its own.
I think actually that it's Todd Haynes' best movie.
And, uh, I planned to watch it again.
I really loved it.
I loved it too.
Um, in the, in the final, excuse me, in the final act of the movie, uh, the
husband whose name is Joe, uh, he confronts his wife about what it is they have,
what it is they're doing, if they do love one another.
Uh, and in the end of the movie, he, it's the, the climactic, not climactic,
but the, the, the second to last scene is the graduation of the
daughter from high school.
Julianne Moore is in the stands, cheering.
The husband is watching from the sidelines.
Cause you're not sure if they're going to get back together or stay together.
Uh, and, uh, Natalie Portman is also there somewhere.
Natalie Portman and Julianne Moore's characters run into each other one last time.
Julianne Moore reveals this is wild.
Cause the whole movie is, is, you know, the, the stage is set basically that
Portman is slowly manipulating the family and the community to get all she needs
information wise out of them so she can then exploit whatever she can with that.
In the movie, she's portraying Julianne Moore's character in the, in this final
scene when they meet up, one of the things Natalie Portman found out was that
Julianne Moore's character had been, uh, repeatedly molested by her older brothers.
And Julianne Moore's son, who is supposed to be estranged from her tells
Natalie Portman that in secret.
And in this last year, almost the, or another brother tells Natalie
Portman that because he wants the job as a music supervisor.
No, it's Georgie.
It's her son.
It's the kid.
Oh, I thought, I'm sorry.
I thought you were talking about the lead dude.
I get what you're saying.
All right, go on.
Yeah.
The music supervisor is Georgie.
That's the, that's her son.
Yeah.
So who, who earlier in the movie tells Natalie Portland, you know, my mom seems
nice, but she ruined my life and w you know, which is understandable anyway.
Julianne Moore says to Natalie Portman in the scene, she goes, I hope you know
that Georgie was lying to you.
Right.
And Natalie Portman was like, what do you mean?
And she's like, my brother's never molested me.
It was a lie.
Right.
And she goes, it was a lot.
What do you mean it was a lie?
And then Julianne Moore goes, I talk to my son every day.
Uh, I'm secure, insecure people need to do X, Y, and Z, but I'm not insecure.
I'm actually very secure.
I hope you put that in the movie.
And she walks away sort of the winner in the, in the showdown.
And there's this great.
Did you believe her?
Did you believe that she wasn't molested by her brother?
It's supposed to be ambiguous.
I think you're, you're not, you don't get a definitive answer, but what you see is,
is, oh, this woman can play the game too.
And how much of what she has revealed to Natalie Portman was bullshit.
How much of it was smoke?
How much of it was fake?
How much of it was, you know, what was real?
What wasn't, what was genuine?
Was she manipulating Natalie Portman the whole time?
Did she say to her son, Georgie, you're going to meet this woman.
And when you do, I want you to act in a certain way and tell them that we don't
talk who fucking knows who fucking knows.
But see what I, my theory, what my, my take on it is that since you see how
deeply manipulative Julianne Moore has been from day one, and especially when
they go talk to her ex -husband, another great actor in a one scene role or that
pet shop guy, and you find out shit about her, she's a highly manipulative,
very untrustworthy woman.
So you really can't believe anything she says.
So that final reveal doesn't really hit because you're, it leaves
you with so many questions.
But that's my, that's my point though, is that you, you see in the, in this
last scene, there is not somebody, there's not one, one of them is not
steering the ship.
They both have been doing this.
They both have been undermining one another.
And then in the last scene in a great final punchline of, of ambiguity and
more insecurity, they show Natalie Portman on set, portraying the character
in the movie she's been prepping for.
And they do every take when they go reset, you see her get aggravated because
you can tell she doesn't think it's right.
And then the, yeah, the last line of the movie is she says, can we do it
one, they want to move on.
They got it.
And they're like, can we just please do it one more time?
It's becoming more real.
And you realize like, she doesn't, she might not know what the fuck she's even
playing at this point because she's so confused.
So the whole thing was just really, really well done.
A masterclass about an extremely difficult subject where you just feel like
every single piece of the Buffalo was used.
Every single side of the argument was heard from.
Um, and it, it reminded me a lot of tar in that it is a, it makes, it makes
you realize how lazy most movies and shows are.
There's so much to think about and to hold onto and to discuss with this movie.
Um, big fan.
I mean, I'd have to think about if I have any competition, but I would say it's
almost definitely my favorite of the year.
Hogs way up.
Way up.
And we will be back with, uh, a holiday themed slasher by the name of
Thanksgiving, Eli Roth's Thanksgiving.
You can find me on Instagram at the Patrick Walsh Joseph, uh, on tour 2024.
I never promised you a Rose garden starting in Gramercy at the Gramercy
theater here in New York city.
Then onto the comedy mothership in Austin, Texas in January, then onto
the chip face jokers and Eric Andre Cruz to do a taste buds live.
And past that I will be in, I'm coming back to LA, uh, San
Diego, San Francisco, Nashville.
Tons of cities through March at this point, uh, adding new dates, uh, through
the spring, please go get your tickets.
All show info and all that is at Joe DeRosa .com.
And if you're in New York, you want a sandwich and a drink, come on down to the
bar, Joey roses and all our info is at joeyroses .com.
We'll see you next time.
And we'll see you and have.