Summer is here, and Bed MGM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MGM Casino.
Spin on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Land,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help
you make appropriate choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal, durable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
Gambling problem? Call 1 -800 -Gamber.
I say, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
gorya .com. This is Joe DeRosa. I think I'm in your left ear today. And my man, Pat Walsh, Ho Ho,
hello. It's Patrick Walsh on the right side. We're coming to you with a special Christmas
app. We're going to watch Gremlins, which you might have heard some of Noxious Guy in a bar
at some point yelling your face. It's actually a Christmas movie. And so it's die hard because
That's what people our age do. Yeah, you get that with Batman Returns too. Yeah, it's
Batman Returned to Christmas. It's actually Christmas stuff. Yeah, I find we all know that now.
Yeah, we all know. If you do plan on watching along with us today, this is not on Netflix.
We switched over to DVDs because Netflix is getting a little slim pickings and we wanted to make sure
that we did special Christmas movies for the month of December and if we get too
many complaints we'll go back to Netflix but for now we're gonna we're gonna try
this out. We figured also too any horror aficionados that are actually
listening to the commentary along with watching the film it's you know yeah you
don't you own it probably right. Do you own this film? I do I own I think two copies
and I own Grumman's two of the new match.
I refuse to partake in it.
I love it and I'm sure we'll discuss it as we go.
People do love it, key and peeled it a great sketch.
It was incredible.
So get your DVD out at this point, put it into the deck,
as you they say, and get to your menu screen
and get already on the play movie thing
and we'll kind of...
I know, this DVD is like 10 years old.
It looks very chency, the menu, you might have a different one
But hopefully we hit play. We're all rough at the same spot. We'll be at the yeah, we'll be we'll go to get in fact
Here's the easiest way to do it go to your menu screen. Okay. There's no need to do this job
Just stop just go back and just hit play when it's time to do it
Also, we're finding out from people
That they tend to listen in their car. They don't watch a movie. That'd be very dangerous if they want all I was gonna
Say was if you just go to your menu screen to this to scene one then it can all start together
But, you know, there's different menus, Joe.
That's a good point.
You're just a good point.
Actually, complicating it more.
All right.
Should we start?
Yeah, let's fire it up.
Chapter one is called three rules.
And we're going to count it off.
One, two, three.
Play.
Hey, see, and that's a great point.
Scene one, three rules.
That's a smart way to do a horror movie.
Scene one, here are the rules.
Now I just saw a crampus.
They pull out the rules with like five minutes left
to go in the movie.
I've heard, I haven't seen crampus yet,
but I keep hearing complaints
that it sort of doesn't really make sense.
I will agree it doesn't make sense.
I did like it, and I liked it
because I like horror comedies and they never make them. It's very hard to make
tonally. And also because I like Christmas movies. Okay. And it was a slightly
above average Christmas movie and a slightly above average horror
comedy. Now if somebody told me the ending, which infuriated me, not that they
told me the ending, when they told me the ending and I found it finding out that
the ending is what the ending is, maybe very angry. The ending will bother you
much less than other things in the movie. Really? It didn't bother me at all. I just sort of felt like,
it's a complete cop -out but so is the rest of the movie. They don't, they don't really know what
they're doing but it's enjoyable and it was kind of fun. I don't know what else to say. I did text
to my buddy Robert Fee and I said, hey, you know, I didn't hate Krampus. See, he hated him. So,
and then listed like 8 ,000 reasons why it sucked.
And I was like, look, I honestly don't argue
with any of them, but I enjoyed it.
All right, I'm happy to be out of the house.
Fair enough.
Back to Gremlins.
But Cran, you know, Cran, this is the big horror
entry of December.
I think it's okay that I talked about it for a second.
That's okay.
No, no, I wasn't saying that like,
like let's get back to Gremlins.
I'm saying I have a point that I want to make
about Gremlins before we're out of the scene,
sort of backed up against a wall
And I didn't like it. No, no, that's not what I meant. That's all on you, buddy. All right. This is the scene the movie opens
We're inside the shop at this point, but the scene opens with bathroom, buddy. Yeah, with the main characters father
Going to a strange off the beaten track shop
somewhere in Asia, yes, and
he
Follows a young boy to the
To the shop. Yeah a young boy leads him down the stairs
into this shop, which was a different time in the 80s.
Nobody thought anything weird about that.
Nobody said, here's a 55 -year -old man
following an 11 -year -old down dark stairs
in an Asian country.
That's a good point, too.
They're not in Thailand, but yeah.
Boy, that Thailand seems like a pretty rough stuff.
There you are.
You want something, Thailand's got it.
It's a shame.
The bathroom, buddy.
How bad did you want this thing when you were a kid?
I loved bathroom buddy even with all all its faults, you know
It was replaced years later by the talk boy from home alone, which I wanted more than anything in the world
But how was the talk boy?
The talk boy was in home alone too and it's like a handheld device
He uses like record speech it altars his speech it you can oh, that's right people
And when they finally released one it was such a shitty shitty imitation
They just rushed it out because they're like people are going to want this and they didn't do it right but I had
Yeah, cuz in the movie it did makes his voice sound impossible. Yeah, it's just different people that they recorded
Yeah, they're like this is McCullough Cokins voice being altered, right? How hard is it really to fool Rob Schneider?
Rob Schneider is he in with you guys like the the bell hop that's right Kevin keeps fooling you know
It's all blur at this point the home alone
Well, remember who's in what one is just fantastic. I rewatched the other day
It's a great movie tonight plus two is they just really slipped a lot, but it's good
Three is unwatchable. I argue that the end burglar sequence of two is funnier than the end burglar sequence of one
It loses all trace of reality. It's what yeah, it is pretty awesome and it goes on forever
That's the one we're that's when we're Daniel Stern gets electrocuted right and you see his skeleton. Yeah, which is a bit
that they took from John Hughes' own plans transomers.
Yeah, I love it.
It's the end of it is he's throwing bricks onto their heads.
Yeah, and they're just from like 20 floors up.
Yeah, just dropping bricks on their heads.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's really funny, man.
And McCulloch and Colcombe was awesome.
Yeah, but you don't usually get a kid that funny.
The Colcombe, I hope you're well if you're listening.
I hope you're keeping clean, buddy.
Yeah, I think he's doing all right. All right. It seems like he's in good spirits every time I see him speaking of
Keepin clean. It's got Wyland
RIP is anybody surprised I was and I just sort of read it almost like you know
The weather reporter. Yeah, I mean, it was a long time coming. I did think it was crazy
I was just crazy in the sense of like oh, it finally happened right, but I mean it was still like
was one of those things was like yeah just what a waste yeah really that was a
talented singer and I thought like when stunt over pilots were on their game it
was actually pretty great music their third album is excellent their first
three or four are really really good they did some good stuff they lost me
after the third one the fourth one I'm not on board for number four sucks you're
absolutely right yeah but the first three I'm I in Las Vegas Nevada once was
staying at the hard rock and this man come up to me and he was with wife
girlfriend prostitute and she had vomit all over her breast implants
tits were covered in vomit and he goes hey my girl peaked a little early you
want to go see stunt temple pilots front row and I go yeah please that'd be great
and I go how long have they been on for he goes they they strummed the guitar
once and she puked on herself I was like all right so they weren't sure enough on
the first song when I walked in what was it it was I am I am I am all about all
bang all about all I don't I'm beer that's a hell of a hell of an opener that's one of
My favorite so it's don't double pilots on type thing a little rapey perhaps even about rape
I'm not sure I never knew what it was about. I forgot the felb men's in this movie. Yeah, this is my favorite film about Christmas song by the way
It's funny. We talked about this
We took our Christmas songs at work the other day and I said that my favorite was Mariah Carey's all I wanted for Christmas is you
Yeah, which it's embarrassing for me to say it out loud, but I don't care the song fills me with the spirit
I loved it for so long, but it's just too much at this point. It's like especially when I go home to Missouri
It's relentless. Well, this was the this was the contender for first slider the number two
Okay, everybody agreed that those are like these are the top two this song if you're not watching is is the one that
You know, it's the one you two covered Christmas
Maybe please come home. Maybe come home for Christmas. This song was produced by
I convicted murder, Phil Specter.
Yes.
Wall of sound.
Couldn't keep the cops out of your house.
And what's he convicted?
Yes, he was convicted.
OK.
I use it.
Look at this.
Look at him to make a tweet.
Dream team of producers.
Steven Spielberg, Frank Marshall, Kathleen Kennedy.
They did a lot of quality work.
Yeah, Kathleen Kennedy.
Now the head of Lucas films.
Yeah.
Frank Marshall, we're about heavily involved
all the Indiana Jones pictures. We're roughly a week away from the new Star Wars.
I'm beside myself excited and shout out to I'm beside you. That's not possible.
But go on. Shout out to movieweb .com. I read your site every morning. I always
love I think you have your finger on the movie pulse. Better I guess is the
way to phrase it than any other movies that I've been to. But shout out to you
particularly because they had the decency today to say you might the link the
link was for the Star Wars Chinese TV spot released and okay in the
description under the link it said you might want to avoid this shows too much
footage possible spoilers and I was like that's fucking classy that they did
that so you didn't watch it no I didn't watch it you know thousands of people did
and I'm gonna have to hear it before I go.
Nope.
You're not gonna hear shit.
Thousands of people, who do you know
that's watching Chinese trailers besides you and me?
No, they're on movie web,
which I imagine is a pretty big sign.
It is, but I think it's, you know,
I still think it's a nerd site, you know what I mean?
Like meaning like for enthusiasts.
I don't think, I don't think your dad's gonna be like,
you know, I saw that Chinese TV spot.
No, well my dad has never seen any of the Star Wars movies.
So he married my mom in 1977, which means that the two of them were dating,
courting, and still did not find time to go see any of the Star Wars movies.
I was born in that year and I remember my parents taking me barely.
My first memory, my first memory is a young boy.
It was probably when it returned to theaters like a year or two later or whatever,
But I remember the end credits of Star Wars in the movie theater, and I remembered having enjoyed the film very much.
And I remember when my parents took me to see the Empire Strikes Back.
And I was ravaged at the revelation.
The revelation was a hard gut punch.
But the console of cliffhanger of him being frozen at the end of the film. I couldn't even and then I remember when Return of the Jedi came out
It was the most excited I ever was to see a movie in my life
I just watched Return of the Jedi my girlfriend. I are rewatching the
Sexy trilogy whatever it's called
She didn't know which one she'd seen or not. I think Return of the Jedi gets a bad rap. It's pretty fucking great
I like it. I like revenge of the Sith better and it's an argument. I have constantly with people
Well, let's you know if I feel that way. Well, I like it. I like it. This lady. I like this lady in grandma. Mrs. Diggs. Mrs. Diggs.
And I always felt like they probably went out to to Carol Burnett for this role.
Oh, yeah, yeah. And she probably said no for whatever reason that she just played this role in Annie a few years prior.
I think that's why I'm not going to be a tight cast.
And then she didn't work for 25 years. I heard they offered the role of 10 of gizmo to this milk.
Yeah, they offered the role of gizmo to Tim Conway. He was going to do it dwarf style
Remember when he's do that on his knees. I do that would have been a much funnier movie. Yeah
With the with the with the German accent he was gonna do it
Dorf was German
Yeah, like Dorf in houses. I don't remember if it was Germany. He had like yeah, but he had like some kind of Austrian or German accent
I have never set foot in a dad's VHS collection and not spotted at least one
dwarf entry. Look, my dad bought it for me when I was 10 and it was the funniest
thing I'd ever seen in my life. Yeah, you know, this lady is a hot milk.
Really good. Look at that. Really nice piece of change right there. I'd raise
those kids. Yeah, I like that. I wouldn't do a good job. I'm not ready for that
But did I ever tell you about the time that I saw Zach Galligan in the street in New York Joe?
I think you've said it on this podcast twice. I think I have to I think maybe twice. I'll retell it. Oh
Phoebe Kate's baby. I yelled Zach out of me turned around
Frightened don't it again tell the story looked frightened. I thought I just I said I said I'm gonna tell it again
I didn't just slip into it. There's no way this role was not offered to car over in it. There is no way
This is I bet that the role of that dog was offered to Benji as well because Benji was even a bigger draw than Burnett at this time
I heard first they went to Carol Burnett
She said no, then they offered it to Vicki Lawrence to come in now the mama character in this role
Why wouldn't Vicki Lawrence have done this? I'm joking. They didn't
I guess yeah, that would have been great. Let's reimagine Gremlins with the Carol Burnett comedy camp
Yeah, you got Vicki. I want to see Mama play in this lady
sure fair enough she essentially is the sled then you got Conway is Dwarf who
can who can what's his face play Harvey Korman I'll play that guy with the glasses
because he's 16 candles I vote Harvey Korman plays the drunk oh yeah he should
definitely that what's his name plays the guy that's in every movie ever yeah the
Rick Garabra but not Robert Bacana I'll know when I say yeah the guy he's also in
demon night. Yeah, what is his name? Yes, I know. I can't remember, but he always plays
that can picture him. I'll know when I see. Now, Reynolds, two years out of fast times,
playing this tiny, uh, dork role. Well, forget two years out of fast times and playing a tiny
role. He's two years out of fast times. He's playing like a 30 year old banking man. He was
playing a 15 year old two years before this. That's true. I think he was probably much older and
fast times and he's playing a little older in this. Well, I mean, look, they got Zach Galligan in
there as a as a as a stiff working stiff as well. And I mean, I think I can't be more than 19 years
old there, right? I might just be because we are so old because I've noticed now that people who are
anything under like 30 years old look like children to me because I'm getting old. By the way,
How fucking good does this bar look that they're in I would love to hang out at this bar
They give you that mug a mug of beer. Just nice. They are in if you're not watching. I feel sorry for you. They are in
The greatest neighborhood dive bar. I've ever seen in my life would line clearly a set
Mugs of beer obviously fake Phoebe Kate's as the waitress in a little reindeer sweater
Okay, it's also two years out of fast times hugging in all the right places wink, wink
They got video games against the back wall Brooklyn Williamsburg, Brooklyn would spend two million dollars to recreate this bar
Yeah, that's true this week if they could look at that old TV up in the corner. They're playing video games
What is that it's Lana Del Rey?
please. It's about how our boyfriend won't treat her with respect because he keeps
playing his video games. Hey, I got some advice on. I got a game you can play
doll. It's called okay cupid. Find a new guy. It's supposed to feel bad for this
broad. I always like that they add swords on the wall in their house. It's very strange.
In Gremlins not one of the other, you know, and see, there's a little screenwriting
tip if you're gonna have a character just you know yank a sword later in the
movie to fight the grandma as they do here you have them when they come in they
shut the door and the sword falls to the ground the audience is like oh I
bet that sword's gonna come into play these are little touches you can do to make
your movie stand out little touches but they also mask they also mask the sword
foreshadowing very well because you already know the dad is the strange
collector eccentric time see you say you know you probably a couple swords on the
already bought some Samurai so yeah well there those are more like don't
correct me on sorts they're they're they're not really
salmon in my home they're more like we're at Joe's home that's why that's
funny what would you call though there's a like English swords yeah that's
what they're called English swords I'm glad you correct to me with the correct
answer English swords now the mother's preparing dinner this is one of the
things one of my favorite movie tropes ever it's in every movie I've ever seen
in my life. The amount of onion she's chopped up. What are they going to eat? What is she
making? What could they possibly be eating? I tell you, it would be my least favorite food
because I despise onions. This is a trope. It's in every movie. Keep your eye out for it. Anytime
there's a woman, it's always a woman for some reason in the kitchen, chopping things for dinner.
They do two things. Onions are carrots. I've seen more women chop carrots in films in my life.
I've never once been served a dish and had carrots and never once those kind of carrots know you're correct
Yeah, or
They're cutting a cucumber if it's a comedy because then it's like their husband says something to piss them off and they chop into a cucumber
Yeah, like yeah, that's your dick
That's your dick dickless also in every Christmas movie they are watching. It's a wonderful life on TV
I think in every Christmas movie and I love the little homage. It's one of my favorite movies ever made
But pick something else guys
dad comes in with the Gremlin wrapped in paper just no regard for
ex oxygen they don't appear to be any holes poked nothing nothing to the point
where Zach out again shakes it because he thinks it could possibly be a living
thing inside here yeah this movie was written by Chris Columbus who went on to
direct the first few Harry Potter movies and home alone home alone
Uh, Mrs. Dow fire, obviously his worst film and maybe the worst film ever is by
sometimes. He directed the film adaptation of rent. Oh, yeah. Why did he
think he could do that? That's, uh, I think it comes time. I think the musical
itself sucks. I, I, I, I don't know, see it in any capacity. Yeah. I saw when it had
been on Broadway for like 45 years. The, uh, so not exactly as relevant and
vibrant as it was. Little extra movie trivia here. Most people probably know this. But the dad is
played by Hoi Daxton, who's a country singer. Yeah. And I have a, I have a Hoi Daxton album that is
just tremendous. Really? He wrote his own songs. He did. In fact, you and I once were in the car
together right after I bought the CD. Uh -huh. And we, I was listening to, in the back seat, we're
under a sleeping bag. Right. The stars are above us.
Parked out of Joshua Trink. Right. Right. And there is the end,
the endless post a blanket of endless possibilities scrolled
or scrolled out along that road. Uh huh. And we didn't know
where the world would take us or what the night would give us.
They took me to come towns where I took. So I was listening to
this and I remember you saying like, oh, this is pretty cool.
And I was like, yeah, it's this old like country folk album.
Oh my god, and I didn't even know the guy's name because I bought it because I was in
the store and they were playing it and I said, can I just buy this?
Yeah.
And they sold it to me and I just didn't even look at the case.
And later I looked at, oh, Hoi Daxon, I was like, wait a minute, that's the guy from
Gremlins.
Yeah.
And I guess many other movies, but I don't know what he's in.
I've seen him in a lot.
He was like kind of like how the dad on Webster.
Yeah.
You know, that guy was a, oh yeah, that guy was like a football player and then he was on Webster.
Alex carous. Yeah, he was also in blazing saddles. I think they're all dead now
Not all of them probably these two. I mean and the voice of
Gizmo was done by
One how he manned out. Was it noted
Game show host and OCD freak not freak. I did a podcast with him recently. I have
Freaked he killed was he funny. Yeah fucking killed. I was on right after him. It's not my bag
I was on right after him. He was killing with this audience where I was like, oh, it was like nerve -wracking.
Yeah, the guy was like so fast. I was like, why is this guy never in a radio show?
He's still doing the voices, isn't he? No, he was just like the fucking smart ass.
He sure wasn't funny on deal or no deal.
Ever. Well, I don't think it was supposed to be funny. Yeah, just, I mean, if he's this funny,
let the man do what he's got to do, you know? Also, when are they bringing that show back? It's time.
I don't know who gives a shit. They did what NBC always did. They got that a hit and they start running at eight times a week till everyone's sick of it
Yeah, yeah tell me about it lawn water
I'll tell you it gives most adorable, but he's got nothing on this dog. Look at this dog. Look at that dog
It's honestly a little strange that they'd put a cute dog in the mix to compete with gizmo
The cute dog comes in later and protects the mom. I mean, you know, they string him up with Christmas lights is what happens
That's right Jesus
Gizmo is adorable. I think was he stolen by the Furby company sued by the makers of Gremlins and they had to make
I think it was really and then they had to make a Gremlins Furby. I think oh good
I had a gizmo doll when I was a kid and I also had a spike doll. Those are probably worth a ton
Now they're gone now. I had a Furby
No, I had the I had a gizmo stuffed animal and then the spike one was hard plastic. They did a great job
the spike one was really detailed those would be worth a lot if you still have probably I had all the
original Star Wars toys all of them and we were watching I believe it was antiques road show one
day me and my mom and they were talking about how much everything was worth yeah and she called out
to my dad and said quick we got to get our that Star Wars stuff out of storage it's apparently it's
work a lot of money and he said, I threw it all away years ago, so that didn't feel
good. Nope. I told my dad, hey, I collect vinyl now. I have a massive record collection.
You've got all this great old stuff from the 70s and 80s and you don't own a record player.
Do you think I could have all these albums? And he was like, I don't know. I don't know.
I'll give him to you, but not today.
Let me think about it.
So you don't own a record player.
So you can't do anything with him.
Yeah, but I might want to play him again someday.
I knew this would never happen.
So then I said, you know, then if you decide to give him to me,
you're going to have to ship them
and it'll cost a fortune.
Now I can bring them home.
Right.
He's like, I'll think about it and let you know.
Not six months later, I go home.
The records are gone.
I go where are the records?
I gave them away.
Took good will. Oh my god. I was just like, what are you?
It's wrong with you. I mean, it's nicely gave them a good will
But I mean, that still hurts. It's just a man with no regard for his son. I have a similar story. This is a crazy thing here
I have a similar story. My dad also had a bunch of old records. Okay. They were sitting in the basement. He didn't have a player
I said dad can I have these?
He said of course. Yeah
found some gems that I listened to to this day in there. Oh well that's much
nicer now. Turn out for youth. Yeah. That was going somewhere. No that's the
whole story. It was just a father that loved his son giving him the records. You
know what he had in there? No. He had the original in sound from way out the
Beastie boys. The Beastie boys like legally copied the cover. Right. And called their
instrumental collection they're in sound from way out he had the original one from the 60s that's
pretty cool and it's crazy it's called pop music from the future it's fucking nuts okay it's a
nutty album there's zany cuckoo ride gizmo is a lot more life like than say like some of the
star wars star -lac pitch shit they just watched it now do you have the special editions right
I have whatever they put out on Blu -ray and I thought I was watching something without additions and shit
And then at the end they superimposed Hayden Christensen. I kind of liked that they did that
I thought it gave it it gave the six movies a nice unity. He's rumored to have been spotted on the set of episode 8
Really? So I think that's cool. I'd like there to be some tie -ins. I don't want it to be like hey, we're just ignoring that trilogy
Yeah, just take things from it that work and tie it all together. That to me makes the whole experience a little better
Okay, god damn it
I can't wait to see that movie next week terrified my plane's gonna crash my way out to the east coast
Terrified, I'm not gonna get to see it now
So wait in return to the Jedi originally was there that woman singing and dancing with like lips that come out of her face
No, he added that in the special editions, so I was watching a special edition again
You can't get the originals anymore
I have bootlegs of them. Apparently they're coming out. Apparently there's heavy rumors that Disney's finally going to release them.
I thought they had released them on DVD years ago, but then somebody said that they didn't or I don't know.
It's completely ridiculous because you're watching it and there's like that blue snuffle up against looking thing, like nodding its head that looks.
If you don't almost see the fingers of the hand inside its head, and then see Frank
Oz's ball spot reflecting off the lights.
Yeah.
And then up comes this like amazingly detailed CGI graphic of another alien singing in
dancing.
I, uh, well, I look, I, I am one that actually liked a lot of the stuff they added for the
special editions.
I hate that sequence because it's cheesy, but, uh, but I like that they added the stuff
an empire like they made it more visually pleasing they enhance cloud city okay you know
was honest that the empire was great I like the job of seeing added into start with the original one
I don't like the Han shoots first whatever I like that they expanded the moss eyesly stuff you know
that stuff all really worked nicely I thought I just don't like the the song and dance number which
George Lucas quotes said quote, I just thought it'd be really funny to have a song and dance
number in the middle of a Star Wars movie.
Well, I love Lucas.
We're going to miss.
I'm not a Lucas hater, but it does upset me that that sequence is in the film.
Is that alien like playing a harmonica and shins just ridiculous?
Well, that part I don't give a shit about.
It's the, it's the, when it literally stops for a song.
Yeah.
I'm just like, come on, man.
What are you doing?
I didn't hate the Ewoks.
I'm not a big Ewok.
Yeah.
You know, again, very adorable. What I'd like to have one in my home. Yes. Sure. Do I want to watch your movie about them?
No. Have you seen the Ewoks, the Battle for Endor? Of course I've seen it.
Thoughts. You do the fuck do you think you're talking to?
Well, I loved it when I was a kid. Now, you know, nobody from the movies is in it, right?
It's got two children in it that are dressed sort of like they're in flash dance.
Uh -huh. Just these weird headbands. Yeah, sort of tights under loose fitting sweaters.
Now this is what I like when they when they spawn when they just build the water and gizmo and he's popped out all the other gremlins.
Immediately the other gremlins are kind of shitty. Yeah.
So you get the sense of urgency immediately that it's like that old that old man that gave them the gremlins shaking his damn head.
Yeah, the old man that gave them the Gremlin wasn't saying, look, you know, you can't don't get on wet
Because oh, it'll be a nightmare because it's going to be a lot of other Gremlins. He's saying like this is one of the rare good ones, right?
By the way, they have what this man is trying to create. They have these in Vegas
Automated dealers
Jesus, you're right
He was ahead of his time. You're right. He is none of his inventions work. How did they have this big house?
It was the 80s it was a different time. Yeah, you could get anything on credit back then
Layaway people still do layaway. I guess they must there's a layaway. There's a rent a center right near where we live
Oh, yeah, that to me and no offense if you rent it seems so dumb and not just like if you don't have any money
I get it my family didn't have money when I was a kid we never rented something
You're paying more money over time. I don't get it
You know you're paying more money
Wait, I forgot actually rent a center is just renting layaways different. Yeah, you can still do lay away
They keep it and you make payments on it. That makes a little more sense. Yeah
That makes sense to me
You know, that's commitment, too. I think I think this town this country could use a little more layaway. I
I don't know what's going on with with the world at large. We just had a very bizarre service at a local Chinese restaurant
They took, they took a plate, perfectly good plate away, replaced it with a new plate and then brought us third plates out with the food on it.
What are you doing? Just give us a plate of food.
I don't know and then at one point I said could you add broccoli to my meal and the guy stared at me for a good 30 seconds and then said Chinese broccoli or American broccoli.
I said I don't care. Yeah, and then stared at me for another 30 seconds and said I think we can do that
But it'll be $2 when I got the food. There were two pieces of broccoli had been added to it
Buck of broccoli, but I didn't pay for lunch. Old patty war bucks did
Shitching
So I didn't feel so bad about that kind of guy. You're a good guy
I also today, so once in a blue moon, I'll purchase a scratch off ticket usually at the grocery store because I'm trash
and I like them from living in Missouri. So I buy one from the machine and I win
one dollar. The ticket costs a dollar and I win a dollar. So I go to the same grocery store this morning.
I hand the man my ticket. He goes, I don't know if I can do this. I said, why not?
He goes, ah, come with me over here. We walk over to this machine.
Nowhere near where I'm standing. I'm trying to get a dollar and leave.
Right. We go all the way to this machine. He tries to scan it. It won't scan it. See, that's the thing. It doesn't scan.
so I go okay he goes yeah I mean it just it isn't gonna scan I said well you're a lottery
retailer like if I hand you a ticket worth a dollar you have to hand me a dollar right I didn't
say this I'm just kind of staring at him right he goes let me tell you what I can maybe try is I could
maybe try to add in the barcode type out the code and I go okay he goes yeah but I mean as
you can see here and he holds it up to me it's like all those numbers and letters I mean it's just
you know I just stared at him I was like so what do you just should I just not get it not win my prize
he goes no I'll add her I just want you to see it's like gonna take a while my prize I go okay he
types in the letters it takes forever then he types in some other code that goes on forever then he
needs to do a manager code forever he turns me and he goes didn't take that either man I don't
know what to tell you hands me the ticket and walks away so so what if I had one 10 grand this is my
I don't get it because you can't figure the machine out you gotta go to another place he didn't say
Like let me try to get my manager. Let me see what I ate nothing just like peace man. I can't help you out
Look, that's LA, man. Unbelievable. That's LA. The thing is this wasn't some like 20 -year -old surfer named chip
It's it was a 60 -year -old man. Well, guess what?
40 years ago that guy was a 20 -year -old surfer named chip
Any stayed here and that's what happens. That's everything is here customer service. It's a trotious
I've never encountered more customer service people in one concentrated place where they like like they do that
They they tell me they try to explain to you why they can't do the job. It's like I don't give a shit
Right do it or or or be like or have a succinct way of telling me it can't be done right now
Yeah, and they don't offer compensation. They don't offer alternatives. No no alternatives everybody here
like in the service industry has the same attitude that like a pot head sound
man has at a rock club like yeah hey man you know sounds all right to me bro yeah
listen man what do you want for me yeah I don't know maybe you do your job
there is dick dick Miller yes dick Miller yeah it was very annoying jinx that was
weird that was weird it's that same bitch of all now patty here's something I've
never done once on this podcast and I'm gonna ask if you can do it okay can you
take the helm and talk solo for two minutes so I can listen to the voice
mobile that just left me about my dog sure yeah Joe's dogs in danger I'll take
it from here thank you all right I feel like in Wayne's world when Wayne leaves
and then Garth is like but no I'm fine I'll be able to vamp as they call it folks
I saw Gremlins too young it was PG rated it's probably too scary for that and I'm
to tell you a little story while Joe is gone about the two movies that started the PG -13
rating.
Maybe you don't know this.
Maybe I'll blow your mind.
Steven Spielberg was the biggest director there was coming off the hits of ET, produced
poltergeist, Raiders of the Lost Art.
And he's got two movies coming out in the summer of 84, Gremlins and Indiana Jones in the
So because Spielberg is Spielberg, they come back and they're like these movies are really violent like they're kind of intense and they maybe should be rated R and he goes, no, I can't have grandma's, I can't have Indiana Jones be rated R and that's not going to work.
So they eventually because Spielberg was such a big name and carried so much cloud in the industry gave him his PG ratings for both movies but they are incredibly intense for children.
So then when they released the movies and theaters children were horrified by
Grimmlands children were horrified by Temple of Doom and the ripping out the
hearts and Spielberg goes the MPAA he says maybe we should have a rating that
tells parents this is more intense than a PG but it's not gonna have the
nudity and sex and stuff of an R and together they came up with the PG -13
rating because of Grimmlands and Temple of Doom. It's incredible. Temple of Doom was
the first, I believe. Well, all right, thank you. I'd be right, you know. Thank you. Pups
okay. That's good. As a gastronitis, my dog has been vomiting. Ladies and gentlemen, on
and off for, I don't know, a half a week through four days. So, you know, with any dog, you
think, like, well, I probably ate some grass. And then the second day, you think, did he eat
more grass? And then the third day, I'm like, it's got to be his food. So I, I dumbed down
his food and made it less you know made it more bland than he seemed okay for a day and I was
like okay we got it and then he puked again today so I brought him to the vet but they did an
x -ray they sent the x -rays out he doesn't have a blockage thank god uh he's just got a little touch
of a bug and that will probably be $875 yeah yeah for sure I honestly it could be more than that
are you serious yeah I've had friends go in with dog shouldn't it's 13 hundred bucks are you kidding
me I'm not kidding I hope it won't hopefully I'm going high so you'll be my
guess is five honey okay x -ray call me honey x -ray I got some medicines for
them and then I got some some I got some sedatives for when we fly next week
you guys turn into with this movie podcast from me you hear pretty riveting
account of the creation of the PG -13 rating in movies and it's a sink two minutes
And then Joe tells you about his dog puking I'm trying to stay on message here
Well, I thought they would I thought they you know you get up and you say the dog sick and the vet called
I got to leave the podcast for the first time in the recorded history of this show. Yeah, I think you come back
They want to know how's the dog all right dogs fine
Yeah, he's fine and you're concerned
He's overwhelming. He's fine. If you'd come in and been like my boy's dead, I would have given you the appropriate. I
Would I gotta go? I would have the decency to do it
Kastanza style for the sake of the podcast. Just kind of shrug it off. So you're like, yeah, he's dead. Yeah, and then afterward
I would have wept in your arms. He didn't have that long. So yeah, so he's he's okay and I
I can go pick them up. The good news of the whole thing was I had to stay close to home
So I kind of got got a little work from home day today out of it. That's great. You know, that's always nice nice surprise
Yeah, you know expecting right? Yes, not shitting on my job. Just saying it's nice to work from home sometimes
Thank you speaking of Joe gremlins was directed by Joe danti or Dante Dante
I think it's danti. It's not it's Dante
He made inner space, he made some big movies, and then I think the last time I saw him making a splash theatrically
It was like small soldiers when I was
14 and he doesn't direct anymore. I don't get it or he'll do like a direct to the DVD thing or something
Well, let's see what the last thing Dante did was. I love Matt and I. I love the burbs. I love Gremlins
This scene makes me hungry every time. This ham and cheese sandwich with a coke that Zach, Algan's eating
it looks so good. It looks like such a perfect ham and cheese sandwich. I'm gonna
look up Joe. I haven't had a like homemade white bread sandwich in 20 years.
Used to have never done. 20 years? I would say 20 years. I haven't bought white
bread in 20 years. Have you had a wheat bread sandwich since then? I've never had
bread in my home to my knowledge. Not since living in Los Angeles. Really? Yeah. Why?
I don't have an answer for that. You should.
I'm looking up Joe Dante.
All filmography.
Now what do you say to people who are like,
isn't it always after midnight?
Do you tell them to just shut the fuck up
because it's Gremlins
and why do you need to analyze everything?
And most of the movie makes perfect sense
in the world that it's created.
I mean I never have an answer for them
And I never really, I never, I mean, by the way, he comes back with a full platter
of chicken.
Yeah.
Who the hell, why would they have that much chicken left over?
I guess some families don't eat everything in the house has not been my experience.
But it's literally a platter of multiple chickens.
Yeah.
Well, how many chickens did she make?
And if you make it a platter, chicken that big, it's for an event.
I tell you what, she cooks with onions.
the same way she does with chicken. She wants to have more than enough and these
people are broke. They're living on a failed inventor salary. He directs television
now. Directed nine episodes of Hawaii 50. Joe Dancing. Yeah. Is directing some Joe
Legends of tomorrow episode. Well, you know, he's making money. That's good. Look, I
had just a perfect touch. He directed the hole with his last film 2009's The
hole which was fairly well received. He's into porn now. Oh, there you go. The hole.
The crazy thing to know was a prequel to holes with Shilobov. It was a sequel. And it was
they were the other direction. I got you. Yeah. They went the other direction. People think the
sequel always has to be bigger. He went smaller. Okay. One smaller hole. Yeah. One hole in the
sequel. Road warrior poster up there. Yeah. Well, in any case, this, they're also showing
invasion of the body snatchers, which is great because what happens next, the gremlins
are going to go into the pods and then hatch just like invasions of the body snatchers.
Gross pods. Do you know what the origin is of Chris Columbus writing the script? I don't
think so. He was living, I think, in New York at the time. Yeah. And he said his apartment
had a mouse problem and it kept he would lay in bed at night and he said he'd be freaked
out about having his hand dangling over the bed because he was afraid of a mouse would
run by and sweep it or bite it or something and that's how he got the idea for Grimmlands.
All right, I don't like that. Yeah. These pods truly are disgusting if they go into it. Yeah,
they look at the cover and it's not for him. Very alien looking. Yeah. Like I mean like the movie
right looks like that thing on the cover of the original alien box sure it was
influenced I always try to think about that like so grandma's is 84 alien is
79 like so that to us would be like what was the big movie from five years
ago like it's hard to think in that time because we're again old sure but like
2010 so you're talking about like well what came out in 2010 yeah 2010
2010 you had your mission impossible ghost protocol
So yeah, there you go. You had it's like the difference between yet Batman begins
No, I don't think either of those are right
No dark night was 2010
Yes, that does him. Okay, so really the difference between now and dark night is a difference between grandma's and alien
It's like right fresh in people's minds. Okay, I see sometimes I try to think like that
And I realized trying to voice it is not interesting or probably relatable.
I got to be honest with you Pat, I tuned out through the whole set up of whatever that was.
I was completely understand.
All I heard was 2010 and I just scrambled and started trying to think of a movie.
And I think you're wrong on both counts.
I wasn't listening.
I'm sorry.
Ghost Protocol was 2012, Batman Begins, I think, 07.
I suddenly got scared that because I said I got to work from home today.
One of my bosses will eventually listen to this podcast and think that I was playing hooky.
They know that your dog is sick.
You just said that.
I know.
I just got nervous like I for some reason shouldn't have been talking.
Steven Spielberg.
Little Camille.
Where?
He just drove by on a cart.
Oh, he did.
And I was either.
Look at the always at the inventors convention.
Yeah.
Invention.
The invention convention.
I had a movie tweet this morning, I was saying I want to do a Pac -Man movie with Gene
Hackman and Hugh Jackman and the trailer would be Hackman, Jackman, Pac -Man, right?
And Hackman's like his mentor or dad.
so it would start with a young Hugh Jackman and his dad's like quit playing that fucking Pac -Man
and then he starts getting better and better and then his dad becomes like his coach or or he gets so
angry at his son for playing all this Pac -Man that he turns against him and he's the villain and
even when he grows up, Pac -Man is still like, this is what you're doing with your life and he's got to
show him there's good money to be made on the Pac -Man circle. Which they're probably
I got to tell you I admire the fact that you're going to drop an F bomb in a Pac -Man movie.
Oh, it's a hard art. It's a hard art. It's a hard art. So this isn't they go into the
graphic sex. They don't fight the Pac -Man. No, you know what? Because we already had pixels,
okay? And thank God. I ain't making pixels too, baby. All right, so this is. I'm doing a hard
This is essentially Fred Savage's The Wizard, except with a grown -ups and a lot of fucks.
That's right.
I got you.
Maybe you get Savage in there in a cameo.
Uh, okay.
He runs in with the power glove.
Yeah, I think today's audiences would love a wizard reference for sure.
Yeah, why not?
That move is much darker than you think it's going to be, too.
I don't remember.
I saw it at the dollar show when I was a kid.
heavy. I saw when I was a kid too and I was all excited like oh it's an
Nintendo movie. Real heavy stuff going on that movie. Yeah. What is it? I
don't even remember. Like his younger brothers like disturbed or something. Oh
yeah. That's what other turns out to be the wizard. I asked. It's like a Tommy
thing where like you can't talk but he yeah that's true. The game is way too
heavy for what I wanted. All I wanted to see was the Super Mario Brothers 3
footage yeah yeah the power glove that was really shameful to make kids like pay
to see a movie to get footage of a video game like it's amazing they don't do
that shit anymore well they but they tried to make it a real movie at least that's
the part that bothered me more give me a no holds barred style thing right where
there it's just all fluff man that's all I wanted at that age I ask Fred excuse me let
me pick up that name, I dropped Savage if he ever like made out with Jenny Lewis because
she's one of the best looking women in the world. Who the hell was Jenny Lewis? She's
lead singer of Ryleau Kylie. She's a great solo singer on her own right. She was in the
Bill Murray Christmas special on that. Oh, yeah. Well, why would he have made out with her?
Because she was the female lead of the wizard. She was like 14 at the time. Their hormones popping
and he was like, no, she was not interested in me.
So the sav made a try.
Yeah.
The Fred got a little savage.
He said she had a mom who was very involved.
So she was really allowing for that sort of thing.
Can we talk about this Murray Christmas special
for a moment, please?
We can accept, I don't want to lose one thought I had.
Where were we talking about before that?
The Wizard.
Fred Savage.
Oh, I know, okay.
So yeah, Murray Christmas.
was you remembered that, but I gotta ask, or else I'm gonna forget, do you remember
there being a choose your own adventure movie with Christopher Lloyd, briefly released
in theaters where certain seats were equipped with you could choose ABC or D.
No.
This definitely happened, it was an AMC thing and I went, it was like 25 minutes, same ticket
as a movie they were trying to make it catch on like a 3d I might have just
been a test market but it was very annoying and it pretended to tabulate the
votes of the theater and tell you which way you were going. I don't even know
how that'd be possible because it had to change the reels but I went to this
and they tried to pass it off as something that was happening. You went to it. I did
it. I'm gonna Google this. You did it. I'm gonna go. So it was bullshit. They just made
you think you were choosing. Look, as I was talking about it just now, I was like, they would have
had to change the reels. And now they changed the reels all the time in movies. Maybe they just
maybe the reels came, maybe the parts where you chose were at real changes. And they knew like,
okay, that's this real, not that one. Isn't that possible? Yeah. How frequently were you doing the
button every three minutes. Oh, then that's impossible. Yeah, that's impossible.
Yeah, Murray Christmas. What were your thoughts? Look, I love Bill Murray. I didn't like it. I
was laughing a lot at the beginning when he was like miserable. Yeah. And talking about how the
people from Hollywood were at monsters and all that, I thought that stuff was very funny. And then it
just became song after song after song and songs in their entirety and the ones
that weren't with one of the. Yeah, the ones that were supposed to be funny.
It was kind of funny for a little while. And then I was just like, come on, man.
And then it was like real singing and I didn't get to the end.
I couldn't sit through it. I was bored. Is it a dream at the end or something?
No, there is a he hits his head at one point as a dream sequence. That was kind of good.
Miley Cyrus actually sounded great. She sounded great, but I mean, I thought Clooney was
pretty funny popping out from behind that tree. Okay. I don't know. I moved along swiftly
enough that I was interested in. It's just sort of ends. I honestly don't even remember
what happened at the end. It's not long after the Miley Cyrus thing that it ends. It's an
hour alone. So so there's no so the whole thing at the beginning where he's like for some reason
doing a live Christmas special on TV from a hotel like that's never called out as like that was
a fantasy or anything like that. Yeah I mean it he hits his head I think I just watched this I
was very tired. He hits his head but he hits his head and then goes into a fantasy he doesn't hit
said at the beginning, no, well, that's, that's real. They're going to do a show. But nobody can
make it. It's a ridiculous premise. I agree. So then they all sing fairytale in New York. And
then I was watching it with my girlfriend. And I was like, you know, they say the word F -A -G -G -O -T in
the song. I wonder if they're going to do it. They didn't do it. They also, which is probably for
the best, but I was still kind of like, but they say it in the, the wood sense, right? Yeah. They're
the pugs she goes oh it is you scumbag you maggot yet cheap lousy oh really yeah they didn't
sing that part the uh now here's the thing too the other things about me about it because it's
really been on my mind he's got celebrities playing themselves in it then he's got celebrities
playing characters yeah so Amy Poeer walks through the door and it doesn't make any sense and then
Michael Sarah. And then why did Chris Rock show up where that whole thing where he's like I walked on the train rails to get up here
Then he's like I got to go I got to go I'm like what the fuck is happening right now? I honestly don't know
You know what it felt like to me it felt like one of those hipstery things
Where it's like we're gonna make fun of this thing that's been done a million times and by make fun of it
We mean we're just gonna do it exactly as it's been done. Yeah with a with a mild mild
commentary to it it was extremely joke light and then Murray was not singing in
the funny way so it's kind of like oh he was like for real singing yeah it's like I don't want to
hear you sing full songs here Bill you don't have a great voice his voice isn't bad it's fine
it's just like you don't you're not you're not paying to watch Bill you wouldn't go to a Bill Murray
concert I guess I probably would but if it's just like hey no banter I'm just gonna be singing
12 songs I'd be like yeah they kind of never it started the thing at the beginning was really funny
when he's on the phone, he's like, don't you ever try this again.
He's like, my sister, you know, that stuff was funny.
Then they had I thought it was going to be more of like a play on him being
screwed, you know, right?
Well, it was written by Mitch Glazer and Bill Murray, which was a road
scrooge and Sophia Coppola, which is where you wrap this up comes in.
Did she?
Although I did love rodents, suicides and loss of translation.
I love virgin suicides hated loss and translation
But it wanted to see the bling ring. It's all right. It's not great
I actually downgraded from all right to not great and the somewhere is really obnoxious and boring
But what is somewhere with Stephen Dorf? The fuck is somewhere? She directed it. Is that the one where they're sitting on Hollywood boulevard?
No, that's a special about sunset boulevard or something
It's a documentary about sunset.
Yeah, her and Steve.
But what the fuck is somewhere?
I've never been heard of it.
Steven Doerr, if it's like a lonely man in a Hollywood,
and he sits around being lonely.
Aw, poor gorgeous Steven Doerr.
Yeah, my daughter won't talk to me.
All I did was have a coke habit for 20 years in the Doerrr.
That's pretty much what the movie is.
How fuck off, eat me.
And then her other one was Marie Antoinette,
which looked awesome, but I couldn't stay awake.
I had no interest in marine to win it no nor should this scene is particularly intense
This is like a horror movie scene. It's great. They did a great job with this movie where they're trying to kill his mom
So let me tell you real quick
I did not dream this because that's always my fear is that I dream these things mr. Payback an interactive movie mr. Payback
You and your friends choose the action written by and directed by Bob Gale who did that the future came out in 1995
So I would have been 14 sounds exactly right running time 20 to 30 minutes and
I'm going to read very quickly. It's 30 minutes paragraph here. Mr. Payback is an 1995 short film
Designed as an interactive movie. It's 20 to 30 minutes long depending on audience interaction
Requires the audience to vote for various directions the story will take using a joystick attached to the arm of their seats
stars an android who in a number of possible storylines takes action by
humiliating or attacking people who deserve it okay and says Colnebert
despised it I saw that in the theaters it was terrible and it barely worked
didn't really work it didn't really work that doesn't answer my question how
were they doing it unless it was like a video what what what do you mean it
barely worked like you know there wasn't that many people in there and we'd
all be like yelling out a new click it to be like you've chosen C so it was
Rig I think it was probably rigged but Bob Gail's very science oriented. I can't imagine it would have allowed that well
That yeah, that made me that made me second -guess the rigged theory the machinery just didn't well
The uh now that any part does Christopher Lloyd run up to the screen to face the audience and go we need your help
Oh, yeah, I'm sure he doesn't you know five times
They're right. It's gotta be right you make the call right. Oh, we had a request
to do more while we're on impressions.
We had a request to do more
Sam Elliott ordering food.
Well, he was actually ordering food at a bank,
which is at a bank.
That's what we were doing.
Oh, that's gross.
I don't remember what the bit was.
He blew up the ground one in the microwave.
Yeah, I find the blender one to be grosser
when all the guts go out of the wall,
and literally chunks of gremlin fly out of it.
What was, wait, what was the premise?
The bit was, and it was very convoluted,
But basically, Sam Elliott was ordering tacos at the bank because we were just having
more to tacos than I was like, he's at the bank doing this because he's in the scenario.
He's a little nuts.
Okay.
And then we started talking about how the money would be like cheddar and lettuce and they
would sprinkle up shredded.
Oh, that's right.
All right.
I don't really remember the details, but it was a strange bit.
I remember that.
Well, where should he order food from today?
Uh, you know, we just had Chinese, I guess we could do that.
All right, you want to be you can be Sam Elliott first and I'll be the waiter
Now I'm not going to do an accent out of fever. We'll know
Okay, you're gonna be the waiter. I thought we were gonna do dueling Elliott. Well, I'll do the waiter and then I'll do an Elliott one
All right, we can each take a turn
Hi, welcome to
Chinese
He's kingdom. Wow. Wow. You have the easy straight man part where you say hi. I'm a waiter and you've already blown it. Welcome to Chinese Kingdom.
Can I take your order, please?
Yeah. Let me start off with about 3040 of those pork dumplings.
Okay.
Just put them in a pot. Bring them on out.
Okay, I like to do it the bobbin frapple style
Time my hands behind my head and just have that in it now. What would you like the liquid to be that they're bobbing in?
Make it dangerous give me a hot breath
Very good. I want to feel a sizzle in my stash very good
They just use the sword by the way and kill the Gremlin
That's a little rough on the old throat doing Sam Elliott. I think my impression last time was way better. It was it got there at the end though. Sometimes there's a man. Yeah, you gotta do a line. He's actually done. I want to do Sam Elliott ordering
tapestries, tapestries. I thought the bit was Sam Elliott ordering.
Chinese restaurant. Oh, okay. I do break into an insanely offensive Chinese accent.
Do you want to name it for you by the way? Yeah, it's too much fun. You see him doing that Chinese accent
last week? I did not. Oh, God, it was... I can't believe he did it, honestly. It was so insanely
offensive, but it was very fun. Did you see when he created the jacket company that was against Holocaust
cost denial. Yes. Did you see when he had the child locked in a like soundproof chamber
in the same room as like eight people fucking each other? No. That was pretty crazy as
well. I didn't see that. Yeah. Tonight's I'm well tonight at 10 o 'clock at the Vista. They're
doing it for free, which is right around the corner. Nathan for you. The the finale is
I'm not supposed to be incredible. They're just screening it at the Vista. Yeah, but it's
probably going to be one of those things where there's 8 ,000 comedy dorks standing out
there at 10 p .m. You can't get in.
Maybe we go up in front of WGA cards.
Yeah, excuse me, bulls.
All right.
OK, so yeah, I'm just going to.
It's hard not to talk into Chinese accent.
No, no, I want to just pretend we're in a diner then.
No, no, no, we're doing this.
All right.
Mr. Elliott, sorry, I am a fan.
I just call me Sam.
Can I?
I'd love to.
I'm a big fan of yours, Sam.
Um, uh, can I get you started with something?
A water or a, a actually not very hungry?
Okay.
Well, I was interested in purchasing some tapestries.
Um, do you mean like the tapestries on the wall?
That's right.
Me, who, me, you want, which one of my soup films?
Did you like in particular?
Oh, um, I guess I particularly enjoyed your work in mask with
share and Eric Stoltz make me a tapestry with that boy's misshapen face on it okay Sam we don't
make the tapestries here they're just part of the decoration bringing you something that looks like the
boy um we have sort of a misshapen sweet potato in the back I could bring out put it on a tapestry
again we don't make the tapestries here I could I could sell you one and wrap the potato
in it but it won't it will be one that you're looking at on the wall right now
about the original tapestry I'll just take some duck to go okay shall I put it on your bill
thanks gang the podcast you just end there it cuts off right there uh oh right in the water
oh shit stripe just jumped in the water stripe is a real fucking nose to rub it in as well
all right let's do one more okay let's do one more can we both be same
elate this time yeah we'll be two semelates sitting across from each other at
at a screening of gremlins all right oh all right that'll be easy I guess that
would be the obvious thing to do what are we doing here the one with the white
hair reminds me of myself a bit you mean because you're going a little gray up top
I have a mustache similar to Stripe's mohawk, a little snow on the ceiling.
He seems to be multiplying himself in the water's turning green.
I wouldn't mind getting into a little, multiplying myself tonight too, if you know what I mean.
Especially with that Phoebe Cates.
Yeah, what's she up to?
She still look alright?
We had -
We had a different nickname for her on the set of Roadhouse.
or I wouldn't know where she was in Roadhouse. She wasn't, but we all were big fans. We used to call her Curves.
Okay, all right, that's a pretty good one. Patrick Swayze wasn't too shabby himself.
Now, is it true that you and Swayze had a bit of a stormy onsite romance?
You would know better than I would, but yes.
Yes, were you a top as they say or a bottom with Swayze?
When you dance with Swayze, no one's the top.
It's sort of like that thing you do on the end of a baseball bat where you put one hand
on and then the other hand on top and whoever gets to the top of the baseball bat is the
winner.
Only nobody wins.
I always found it in my best interest to let Swayze take the lead.
Yeah, in both dancing and in the boot wall. That's right. I've also fucked Dick Miller, okay?
Now oddly enough, Dick Miller and I were making a clay pot together with me sitting behind
him with him, with him twist my legs. And we did all that. And when I when I hung were
He didn't know how to make a pot.
I said, you're the one who started this pot making love, making great.
When you said Betwixt, it made me think of a Twix and now I'm hungry.
Do you have any mishapen sweet potatoes that I could eat?
Maybe some dumplings.
I'd be happy to make you a tabstry with a Twix bar on it.
What about the boy from Mask's face?
thanks folks all you have to say was you got coming right up and it would have been
the perfect coming right up because Sam Elliott would know what Sam Elliott wants as I
once said to Patrick Swayce coming right up there you go you're but there you go maybe we
it so it sounds like you thought of that. Okay. And the right timeframe. I like the
Dick Miller coat. He's wearing this great. Look at his leather sheerling. There are a lot of
quality 80s coats in this movie that would, you know, the people in our neighborhood here,
Loose Phyllis would jizz themselves over. Yeah. In fact, a man of Dick Miller's age could live in
this neighborhood and still be considered young. Oh, no, in Los
Feelas. I mean, you look like I see plenty of that's what I'm
saying. I see plenty of men in their probably early 60s out here
still dressing as if. Oh, yeah, that is true. A day hasn't passed since
the 12th grade. I mean, look, I got a debt start tattoo on my
arm. I'm in trouble. Yeah, I'm in real. I'm already thinking of
what can I have it change to when I get a little older? You're
doing the you know what most people do when they just get divorced kind of
stuff yeah I mean look if I die young I die young I couldn't care less I don't
want to die tomorrow about me or you about me okay I'd be sad if you don't
thanks I'd be sad if you died thanks Trump I figured that's not what you meant
But there's that just on the spirit
Another Joe Dante film
Trapped ashes. You remember this. I have no idea what that is. I've seen trapped in paradise. I
Do or when the whole came out in theaters. Oh boy
He also directed looney tunes back in action. I did know that and I did see that at the theater
It was a great. You know it has its supporters, but it's not good. It's
You had all the looney tunes who are like hilarious, of course, but then they're bouncing off of Brendan Fraser and
Jenna
Elfman and
Jenna Elfman by the way
Like way after the Jenna Elfman thing had kind of faded away. Yeah, she lands the lead. Yeah in looney tunes back in action
I mean, I think at the time people just because Steve Martin is in that fucking movie. I think people thought
that it was going to be like an Alvin in the chipmunk steal, you know, or it's like just not
something to take seriously, like the road chip. I don't know. I mean, the leads in the last
lunitons movie before that were Michael Jordan and Bill Murray. That's true and Wayne Knight.
Then you go to you go to Jenna Elfman and Brandon Fraser. It's real mad if you say Fraser apparently.
Yeah, by the way, you have acted with that man Joe. That's Jonathan Banks. That's banks. Yeah, star of breaking bad and better call Saul a show that Joe
apparently shit with Jonathan. That's him. Yep. Wow. I was dating this girl. It's different man. Five or so years back. I've seen
Grimmel's a thousand times. We're all watching Breaking Bad. And one of her friends, those of you making the first impression, like meeting her friends. We're all
gonna watch Breaking Bad and this guy goes you know that's the sheriff from
Gremlins and I this is the first thing I say to him I go no it fucking isn't
and we wind up just getting in a huge argument and then he goes bet me $10
like I'll bet you $20 we look it up and he was right I don't know if he ever
likes me again I'm texting old JB right now got his number last time we work
together. Oh, all right. It's as I believe in our growth. It's very impressive. This is a real
name drop right here. Yeah. Oh, it's Joe DeRosa watching Gremlins to celebrate Christmas.
I had no idea you were in it. Muzzle. There you go. Now we'll know how cool Joe is by the speed
with which bands. We're not going to keep track of that. If he responds right away, I will say Joe.
I got to give you props a how do you spell
M a Z EL
You got no Jew in you I
Mean that's not quite how the adoption agency phrased it, but no, I don't
That I know of I don't know I'm adopted. I mean I guess I could yeah
I mean people find it perplexing when I tell them I'm not Jewish. They're like, what are you talking about?
Yeah, that's why I'm asking. They don't understand.
Now this lady, you know, we're back in old Mrs. Degel's, is it?
Degel, yeah. I got to be honest with you. Degel.
Now that she's out of the wig, you're seeing her real hair, she's in a regular face.
You're feeling it. I'd kind of toss it at this lady. Not a bad looking older woman.
Wow. That isn't attractive older woman.
she's okay if you were what is she 65 70 yeah if you were 65 70 and that was
your wife you would not be confined maybe if I was 65 70 sure you would not
that's all I'm saying you would not be complaining you'd say I did all right
man why didn't she need the chair at up and down the stairs but now she's like
running around I bet you she was smoking back in the day I really didn't expect
to take this turn neither did I but here we are what did you just ask she
She's like walking around no problem, but then she's going to take this chair up and down the stairs.
Well, my mom, my mom had certain mobility issues for a little while where she had to, she had to use a chair like that on stairs.
For a certain period of her life, but she could still walk around and stuff.
It's, you know, it's a huge flight of stairs. That's true.
That she would have to climb hence how she dies here in a.
I mean, this is one of the best hard movie deaths ever. It's pretty great.
Does she land on the true hood of the car that the cop now now that I really wish that would have happened
Thanks checking it out. I
Have a sinking feeling that that's not banks. No, I'm a thousand percent. Oh, you're positive. I'm in the credits
Okay. Oh, how embarrassed would you be if it wasn't I just my stomach just dropped it. That's what's gonna happen. Yeah, that's something that I would never forget
Hold on, I'm looking for Mrs. Beagle here on the eagle.
Deagle, excuse me, sorry.
Jesus Christ, I'm deep into the fucking...
I'm deep into the fucking cast list.
She's not even popping up yet.
Do you watch the Fargo program?
I don't, but not because I don't have an interest.
I don't have cable, so...
Kind of still waiting for it to pop up on Netflix or something.
I can loan you season one the first season. I was like starts out and you're like okay
And then by the end I was like this is fucking incredible. It's amazing
Then they throw everything away and start fresh with an entirely new cast and story. I heard and it's perhaps better
I heard the last two episodes of the show are like
There's some of the best you have ever seen in my life. I
Got an old dance and killing it
Patrick Wilson like the first time I ever thought he was better than average I love a Wilson don't you get that guy I call fat
Damon who's in black mass and like every movie that comes out. I love that guy. Yeah, the
She's just a plummence isn't she's not listed
You probably just missed her job. I've gone up and down the list three times calm down breathe
Do a Google search for Gremlins Mrs. Deagle I
I cannot believe she's not listed here on the cast list.
That's insane.
Bank tellers listed.
I think there's all your judge, Reinhold.
Well, they wrote Mrs. Harris, is that?
No.
Maybe they got the name wrong.
Who the hell was Mrs. Harris?
maybe it was the mom with the hot mom I don't know this is looking like Mrs.
Deagle to me except younger well no because no this lady's only 68 now so
that can't be her there she is Ruby Deagle Polly Holiday is her name okay now
let's see some old shots of old Polly holiday oh she was I didn't realize that
She was flow on Alice. Oh, yeah, that checks out. Yeah, but she wanted to kiss my grits kiss my grits
So she was probably a lot of fun. That's sassy. So that
How many got how many times the guys dream about going to a diner and just pick it up that check and bring her home
You know, I mean, yeah, all right partner. I'll drink you under the table
Not bad
Joyous woman. I take back that they offered it to Carol Burnett first because maybe they did just offer it to her flow was big.
I apologize, Polly. I think Polly still doing well 78 looking healthy, vibrant.
And I said she was 65 in this movie for Christ's sake. She's only 78 now. It was 30 years old.
They aged her up. She was 48 in that in this movie.
How the fuck is that possible?
I can't talk about this woman anymore.
I really can't.
I can't do it.
She was born in 1937. This movie was shot in 1984.
How old is that?
50. No.
47, yeah.
How the hell is she only 47?
They aged her up. That's why you thought she looked so much younger
Do you want see she was exactly the age she's supposed to be
So let's talk movies. I said I saw a crampus. What else what else has come out? I saw
There's a segway for you folks. I saw animal Lisa the new Charlie Kaufman movie
You know, I wanted to and then I just thought near I
Tell you it's definitely one that people are gonna be like genius
Yes, genius.
Yes, Charlie Kaufman is certainly a genius.
He's made masterful movies with incredible scripts.
This is a pretty minor deal.
It's like a short story.
It's got a great little moment twist in it
where you're like, oh, that's really cool.
And it's reasonably entertaining,
but there's huge stretches of boredom.
The lead character is off the charts unlikable
and you know you're supposed to see yourself in him but it's kind of like I
I don't even know if I want to go this dark with myself I don't hate myself
this much in what ways is he unlikable he just I mean the just is every single
person in the movie other than him has the exact same voice uh -huh because he's
like everyone who's not him is boring essentially and then he hears a woman
with a different voice and he becomes fixated on her and then I'll stop
Literally they have the same. Yeah, the same actor Tom Newton who was in sounds of lamb huge Tom Newton fan
Does all the voices then he hears a new voice who is Jennifer Jason Lee and then I'll stop there
We don't want to spoil stuff for him. Tom Newton also do the female voices. Yes
Really, so it's like kind of cool the puppets look kind of cool. It's definitely a good movie. I love what he was trying to do
I get what he was trying to do
It'll definitely go over a lot of people's heads and
And I think most people your average Joe's will despise it
Now is there's why I think that kind of movie gets this past because people think they're understanding something that no one else can get
It's uh, you know, it's pretty minor for Charlie Kaufman, but it's a good move. Is there some puppet sex in it?
There's very graphic puppet sex and puppet dick. Are you serious in both flaccid and erect form. I'm dead serious puppet vagina
You're joking. I'm a hundred percent serious
So they literally seriously do the thing that South Park got America did. Yeah, well the South Park. Yeah, team. Oh, these are Tim and Eric. Yeah
Speaking of Tim and Eric watching the Aziz show very funny
Master none. Yeah, it's a good show. Yeah, you came around on it. I didn't like the first episode
But I started with the second one because somebody said no, no go to the second one and then I did and I I think it's really funny
Yeah, it's a very good show particularly enjoying Eric Warheim or yeah very funny very funny very funny solid delivery
Don't know if it would have been as funny with Eric
Stolts in that role, let's say I would say it would not not in the mask makeup just a stulcy hit wood
Now this song is terrible by the way
I mean, it doesn't bother me. It fits the tone of the scene. Like, how much better would
it be if it had some great 80s song? This was a thing that was in the 80s too. There's
a gremlin on a fan, and they turned the fan on high, and the fan like, the fan like
goes so fast that it hurls him off, and he dies. I mean, a ceiling fan, you apply a pound
of weight to it. It snaps. That is true. I mean, the ceiling fan and who's Harry
Crumb holds John Candy. It's my favorite scene in the whole movie. It's
in Crumb. You know, the the cross -eyed Butler. Yeah. He's playing a cross -eyed
Butler on our show this week. Really? He looks pretty much as that of the same
but older and heavier. I was one of the cast that guy is a cross -eyed waiter and he
comes to the table and he's putting everybody's food in front of the wrong
person. Okay. Yeah. And the person goes, no, no, I didn't have the burger. I think you can get
Hollywood to fund that for sure. And then he goes, oh, I'm sorry. But then when he moves it, he
does it wrong. Yeah, it just keeps doing it wrong. Like a Jerry Lewis kind of thing. Yeah. I think
paramount I'll make that for sure. Yeah. Well, the film is called the cross -eyed waiter.
Starring. Starring that. Cross -eyed guy that usually plays the butlers. Right.
it. I also saw a movie we discussed at length in this podcast, The Hateful Eight. We talked
about how I thought it didn't look like it was going to be amazing. And I got to tell
you folks, for me, it's another movie that's going to have huge fans. It's Tarantino's
least successful movie, but I have loved every one of his movies. And I'd still give it
like a B plus. But it's three hours long could have been to dialogues, not as great as
it once was. There's amazing, amazing stuff in it. There's great moments, great scenes.
Samuel Jackson is his best role in a very long time. He's awesome. And he's doing like
Tarantino, Samuel Jack, right? Exactly. Kurt Russell is awesome in it. Jennifer Jason Lee
annoyed me. I usually love her. Walton Goggins has like a lead role in the thing. And I don't
know that he's that kind of guy to know is Walton Goggins. Yeah, with the bug guys who
was on the shield. Uh, he was in Django, he got his dick shut off, I think. I don't
remember. How's my man Bruce Dern? Dern is fine. Imagine. How's
madson? Madson's fine. Doesn't talk much. I don't want to spoil anything for you. I
know Tern. He knows a big deal for people. Rough. How's rough? Fine. I saw it in the
70 millimeter. And the scenes where they're out in the snow are like the best
looking things I've ever seen, but then for two and a half hours of the three hour movie
they're in a cabin.
That's not how you showcase 70 millimetres.
Now you said you like the first half better, uh, I had a, uh, some other people told me
the second half was where it's at.
No, I didn't say I like the first half better.
If I did, I was mistaken.
It gets super violent in the second half.
The first half is slow, but it's got a lot of outdoor snowy western shit and I like that
stuff.
Yeah.
My friend of mine told me that she said it was very similar to Kill Bill. She said it felt a lot like Kill Bill.
I don't know.
First half was the lot of the setup and the build in the second half was all the action.
I wouldn't compare it in any way to Kill Bill, aside from Tarantino.
My least favorite Tarantino movie so far, I've not seen hatefully yet, but my least favorite Tarantino movie so far, I don't count Death Proof.
Right. It would be Death Proof.
But I like that poop when I agree that I gotta say in glorious bastards
See I loved it
Especially off of first viewing man, and I'll watch this again
Maybe it'll pick up but in glorious bastards that first viewing I was like
The man's man's gold. I love and I still love it again when I watch I love huge huge elements of in glorious bastards
But there's a lot in there that I find that I don't care particularly for the storyline of the girl in the movie theater
He's always kind of bored me love it love that girl forgot saying. Yeah, she's
She does a fine job and that David Bowie songs off. It's now here's another thing that I hated about hateful it
It's a tiny little thing
They have an eco more a Kona do the score, which is awesome. It's great
But then Terrence he knows of course known for putting pop music and anachronistic pop music sure in times that don't
like Django and Shane had rap songs and so I'm watching this it's all this
Enacomal Moracone score there's no other music in it and then about an hour
in they start playing the white stripe song Apple Blossom it doesn't apply to
what's going on they play it like while they're driving it's kind of a western
type song and they're driving that's out of they're on a horse and buggy they play
Apple Blossom for 20 seconds then it abruptly cuts off almost like it was an
editing mistake and I was like what the then for the remainder of the movie there are no more songs
that aren't score. So that's one white stripe song. Why would you put that in there?
Quentin Tarantina. He does that you know that he did it there's a thing in he'll do that and it
always kind of bothers me a little bit like he did it in there was a thing in in glorious bastards where
when they show one of the remember the part where they show them rescuing like
the guy from jail. Yeah, to join up. He does like a thing over that with like crazy titles and stuff
suddenly. And you're like, it doesn't, it doesn't, I don't know, he likes putting like those sore
thumb things in there sometimes. I don't know why, but I guess it's to kind of jolt you out out of,
you know, what you're watching, but it doesn't always work and this really didn't work.
But there is great stuff. There's just these huge chunks within this cabin where you're like,
come on man like every word isn't gold you got a shave some and then I don't
know that he changed the script after the script leaked because I heard
everybody love the script and then I heard that he might have changed it up
because of the script leak. Well somebody also was telling me that the way to see
it is the non -70 millimeters so you don't have to do the intermission. Oh I I
loved having an intermission. Alright see I mean that just slows it down. I think the
Well, it's 10 minutes. I think the only movie that I had seen with an intermission was dances with wolves
Tances was wolves had an intermission. Yeah, I don't remember them doing one since them
Titanic. I have one. I think death. I think grindhouse had an intermission
No, because the intermission was trailers for other movies, right? I feel like it had a real intermission though, too
Okay, like like go to the lobby get some snacks, right? Because that's what they would do it at a real grindhouse thing
The other thing I thought about the hateful ate and this might be controversial to some people because it hasn't come out yet people are I think going to love it some people are not but let's say I wrote the hateful ate or you know let's say an aspiring writer wrote the hateful ate and it's the exact same script and they turn this thing in like I want to make this three hour movie from this script it's all set in a cabin right.
There is no way that movie would get made. No, but what does that bother you?
It doesn't bother me, but I think it's it's both cool and also a little annoying because Tantino has
He could have taken a note on this movie, you know
It's like somebody could have definitely given him a couple notes and they would have helped out
I think your better argument is not aspiring writer
I think the better argument is an established writer who's not Tarentino would have had to take notes on the movie
Yeah, that's I guess that's what I was trying to say. Yeah, like it take notes or the movie just does not happen
And then you're like, oh, but I've cast Kurt Russell and Sam jet. They're like, I don't care like those aren't huge names
Channing Tatum is in it. Although he's in none of the previews and it's not a kick
Secret because they put them in the opening credits. I don't know why they're not advertising him
Well, they didn't advertise Jonah Hill and
in in glorious. I mean in Django. Yeah, that was a nice surprise. I take back what I said
now about, you know, like Paul Thomas Anderson. I want him to be able to do whatever he wants.
I also want to guarantee not to be able to do whatever he wants. I don't. Paul Thomas Anderson
needs, but you're going to get you slaps on the wrist these days. Yeah. Look, I don't believe
anyone that says they like inherent advice. I don't believe it. I got to know an argument
at work the other day about it. I don't believe it. It would made me angry, but I also don't
believe anyone that says they like the master I think it's oh I love the master and you can
believe me I don't it's fun to be an impossibly fucking arrogant masteratory film oh it's so much
better riddled with unlike a couple characters oh of course well that what's that saying I I hated
inherent vice and I wanted to love it god I was excited I did too and then I like I'm just like
Martin sure everybody's like every every moment's gonna be a joy brolin though broley always brings it
home. Very funny in it. Yeah, he only part that I liked. I'm pretty acted well.
Then some of the work started saying, well, it's supposed to confuse you. That's
the whole point. And I was like, yeah, but fuck you. You tell me this movie is
supposed to be confusing. I don't want to fucking watch you then. I get stupid.
That's not why I watch movies. Yeah, I read some interview with Paul Tom's
Anderson where it seemed like he didn't really understand it, which is like we're
We're not all doing coke with Robert Altman in the 70s anymore.
Was he doing coke with Robert Altman in the 70s?
Robert Altman was doing coke and then he'd be like, I don't know what those movies about.
But fuck it.
Yeah.
That's how you get some of the terrible, terrible Robert Altman moves.
Although I like Robert.
What are some of the bad ones?
Oh, there's a big string of them in the 80s for sure.
Mr. T and the women.
I fucking hated Dr. T and the woman, thank you.
Oh yeah, sorry.
Okay, that's, hey, girl, come here, girl.
Yeah.
As I said, get it, I'm doing Mr. T and the women.
Oh, I didn't get that at all.
I'm pity to grow.
You don't get it?
I can't believe that wasn't a sketch,
like a mad TV sketch of the time.
Well, did you know anybody besides you
that saw Dr. T and the women?
I truly am.
The only reason I know it exists
is because there's a casting office
I go to where they have the poster of it up.
Yeah.
Um, I hate the latest good, if anything, I just wanted to lower it and go back to the
Altman thing.
What?
What about, yeah.
What about, uh, Ocean Stigs, uh, he made so many movies like, uh, the gingerbread man
is bad.
Grand Canyon.
Grand Canyon was Lawrence Kazan, and I actually really liked that moment.
Did Kazan direct it or just write it?
Both.
I thought, are you sure?
You're thinking of shortcuts.
cuts. Oh, I am. I'm gonna move a similar time here. Shortcuts is pretty great. Okay, so short cuts is good.
Did you get your red man? Isn't that the movie with sequenia? Every Wayne's? No, that's meteor man. Oh, no, that's the glimmer man with Steven Cigal.
No, no, it's not right either. Yes, it is right. Glimmer man is Steven Cigal on keen and I rewinds.
Gingerbread man is Kenneth Branagh, John Grisham adaptation directed by Robert Altman. It's not good. Okay.
he made a prairie home companion based off the worst radio show in the history
of the medium that I can't believe people listen to. I like, I liked that movie.
I enjoyed it. I found it charming. My friend, you, you were, you were, you were
the same. You weren't with us the other night. My friend was on that, was on the radio
show prairie home companion. Yeah. She's a comic, but she was on that show.
what's her name her name is Erica Rhodes congrats Eric yeah well she's on it anymore she's on
anymore like you can not like it it's okay I laughed still that you said you thought it was the
worst radio show that ever made what's it about I never heard this show I just saw the movie where
they're like doing the show it's about this fictional town called Lake Wabigon Tom Sharplin talks about
every week on his podcast, which is my favorite podcast, the best show, other than this one.
But he'll be like, Misha's Pennyworth put out a hot apple pie on the silt, cool.
It's not unlike my Sam Hellian.
Right.
And then it'll be like, little did she know old man Jenkins had a sweet tooth and he was
Passing by that's like what what the show is
So like he'll eat her pie and then she'll be like
Mrs Pennyworth
Suddenly found herself pilots for the big bake shame that's what it is
And there's these jokes where like it's like country story maybe an 80 year old person listening would hear these jokes and be like
Like they'll be kind of joke, but wait. It's like it's just like country stories
yeah it'll be like you know there was a raccoon on the wall and after everyone
ate the pie the raccoon wasn't the only thing that was stuffed like that's
that's the level of jokes like is it ironic or no that you saw Garrison
killer in the movie he thinks he's very funny I met Garrison killer he came
to one of my shows once Erica brought him and then after much she had in
sex with garrison. Oh Jesus Christ Pat. That was the
matter with you. I'm baffled by what I'm hearing. This
girl's skipping around town with garrison Keeler. Oh, she
came to my show and she said garrison really like stand up. I
brought them to your show. Oh, okay. And I said afterwards
probably steal your material. Can you not deface people I'm
trying to say nice things about right now? How about that? You
say you love the guys podcasts and you call call them a joke
thief? I don't love this but I hate no. Wait, you're talking
about Tom Sharpling.
Wait, who's Tom Sharpling?
No.
I'm talking about Garrison Keeler.
I hate his show.
Hurry home companion.
Wait, so, what is Tom Sharpling does?
Tom Sharpling makes...
Does basically what I'm doing now.
He, like, spoofs.
Oh, he spoofs it.
As a recurring bit on his three -hour show each week.
He does it.
Oh.
Is Tom Sharpling the guy does all the voices
and interviews himself and stuff?
No.
Man, we are not going to...
What the hell is Tom Sharpling again?
he uh well he was worked on monk for many years he's a television writer but
for the most part he does this three -hour show each week the best show at
Tom Sharple John Worcester calls in his various characters okay I got it's it's
my favorite thing for one of my shows one of the years he probably has been a
one -year show no monk oh Tony Shalupe yeah okay yeah all right let's get back to
basics here. Garrison Keeler was at one of my shows. Go on. And then my friend
Erica told me she had brought him and then I said to her, I wish you would have
told me I feel embarrassed now because I did all those really dirty sex jokes.
Right. She said he was hysterically laughing and loved it. Yeah, well, it's
probably trying to get in her pants. He is not Pat. He's like a father figure to
this girl. Alright, I guess I don't know the whole story. They work together. You
freak on NPR radio they don't work together in the filthy land of sitcoms like you do
everybody's not trying to bed somebody else all right there's no casting
couch at NPR all right we'll see you know we all know what you had to do to get
your job now yeah I blew Garrison Keelan while this other girl walked I noticed
We're at the end of the gremlins bad blood on his head not to the swift
But he's got you meant between us sad fake blood. Well, we do have bad blood
This is the finale of of gremlins. They're in like a Walmart kind of thing and they're in the sporting good section and
I noticed something about these gremlins. They really take to gadgetry very quickly. Yeah, well
I think they're a little heightened spikes. We don't want to chainsaw around. They figured out how to run the movie projector in the movie theater
They were playing the Star Wars video game and they were good at it. Yeah, Gizmo is now driving a car around, you know, why?
Gizmo
You name something gizmo. They pick up gizmo's quick. Well, they all but they all pick them up quick
And this is what what I do. No, I'm just saying my answer was fine
The lights are going on. Here's the big finale. What we got was frozen over that night
are you doing Sam Elliott or Garrison Kieler right now?
Garrison Kieler. Sam Elliott's more gruff.
Lake Wobigon. What's it? One begun? What the fuck is it called?
Wobigon. Wobigon? Like your woes begun.
Oh God, that's what it means.
Yep. Lake Wobigon.
But my woosh.
Just begun.
Oh, Lake Wobigon.
Wobigon? Wobigon, Kenobi?
Yeah, is that something is this something that's that's a joke they would do they'll be like a guy named
Ernie Kenobi had just come to Lake will be gone the kids all refer to him as will be gun Kenobi that'd
be like a joke then you'd hear like three people in the back of the theater go like it's done in
live audience sometimes yeah who are the fans of the show old people very old
people very old people who have lost all concept of joy and laughter and it is
it's just sort of supposed to be a throwback to like the old days of radio yeah
yeah yeah and then the jokes like little wing there's a cast of characters
okay now who little sushi peppercorn how old is getting down to buy some penny candy
uh garrison kilos probably 140 no I mean because he is old as the audience or is he a younger guy
playing to that oh no he's as old I thought you met him I didn't meet him that's what I'm
telling you it was fun you were too busy making your filthy foul mouth fucking jokes through the
story you didn't hear any of the details I didn't meet him she told you tell me later he thought I
was funny laughing at all your sex no yeah I was embarrassed because I was so dirty in front of him
and she said don't be thought it was very funny just thought you had met him I didn't meet him Pat now
I know that I did not meet him now this is my favorite part in the whole movie grandma's movie I
me. Not very home companion. I mean, Stripe is now in the fountain in this store. He's
multiplying. And yeah, these effects are really great. It's pretty gross when one of
the full -fledged gremlins multiplies because they get slimy green bubbles on their back.
And the bubbles pop up. Stripes are real bastard, man. He's got a gun. He's shooting at people.
He's truly evil.
Now, I don't remember in Gremlins 2, but it's just like Stripes just back, another Stripe pops out.
I don't know if it's another Stripe, or like a bigger Stripe.
And they have all this other Gremlins.
I thought Gremlins 2 is like exactly what you want.
They go bigger, crazier.
It's an insane movie, and it's more of a comedy, but I thought it was pretty awesome.
It's too much of a comedy, and it's too self -effacing.
I don't need to see a scene where Hulk Hogan stands up in the theater and the film stops it's come on
Loved it and then they when they did it on VHS. They replaced it with the tape breaking
Yeah, I know you told me that before and you tried to make it sound like that was like a reason to like the movie
No, I like it for a variety of reasons. God damn it. I own it and love it full
Sorry, that was too harsh. I'm sorry. I didn't mean that fine. I didn't mean that. I'm sorry
Dad seems very hands off like he's like, eh, I know I gave you this gift and it almost
killed us all and your mother, but well, people make mistakes like he's taking no ownership.
You think they give the dad a line in this final scene?
Yeah.
He just comes in and pats them on the back and is making this face like, well, this got this
got a little crazy, didn't it?
They announced Gremlins 3 as being a direct sequel. I don't think it's going to happen.
I think a reboot is probably discussed every day, but they said they won't do it.
They said Columbus won't let it happen.
Look, I'd love a direct sequel. You get Galligan back in there. You get Phoebe back in there.
You get some new fresh face in there. Let's see a sequel.
I think it almost can't be
Galigan in Cates because people don't care about them anymore, and I hate to say it cuz I do I'm saying any studio
That's gonna greenlight this and be like nobody gives a shit about those two. You make him supporting characters
Yeah, that might be best. These fucking studios. It'd probably be like Bill Hader and
Somebody else these studios though. I mean, it's like they're like well, we gotta have people. Does anybody ever give a shit about the supporting cast?
No, do you know what I mean? I do there's one time I do. It's called Star Wars 7 next week
Right when my favorite characters of all time are the supporting cast. Yeah, other than that. I don't give a shit
I mean, I always like the supporting
I don't dislike them. They don't put asses in the seat. I'm saying I don't care. Yeah, like nobody's there going well
We got to we got to be here for this seven minute
it uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh uh
Isn't well who is that guy the guy playing the reporter? Oh, he's the principal from team wolf. Okay. I'm gonna have your ass
So that's a big jump for him in one year's time
That roll to the principal team wolf team wolf was shot before
J. Fox shot back to the future. Okay, it was shot in Canada and I think it was supposed to be a pretty low -budget
It possibly Canada only movie back to the future came out was a huge success.
Michael J. Spock was propelled in the superstar to they released it here smart.
So you know, I don't think this was probably just another gig for this guy.
You know what I mean, I do this might have been a step up from team wolf.
You know, bit part in American movie versus lead role in Canadian movie.
Yeah, I said it.
I'm comparing the markets.
I want to know what our listeners stats are because they were great when we asked a couple of months back, but I want to know where we got fans.
So folks tweeted us and maybe we can find that out, but I want to know if we got fans all over the globe is what I'm saying in Canada, you mean.
I want to yeah, I want to know that we got fans. It can't let us know where you're at and also let us know what movies you want us to do
Because the big suggestion we keep seems to keep resurfacing is people under the stairs. We should do that next because we keep ignoring those requests. I
Don't want to do it. You don't like it. I don't like the film that much, but and I and West Craven just died. So I don't want to
We have done two cravings, we've done two cravings. I don't want to half roast and this person's craving another.
Well, we will do it. We will do it.
But if you have suggestions, I think Pat and I both would agree we're going to make jokes and be idiots anyway.
So send us stuff that you truly want us to do because you want us, because you like the movie versus stuff that you want us just to make fun of.
I don't know. Maybe that guy really does like definitely likes that movie has major fans. I
Thought I'd love to watch it again. I've always seen it once. I
Thought he was saying like I'd love to hear you guys make fun of this. No, I think that people really love that movie
Well, look then we'll do it then if you want to see it again, we'll do it because you know
I just didn't want to go Jacob's ladder. I've been saying I would love to do Jacob's ladder
great. Fantastic movie. We're wrapping up at the smokeless ash tray.
Tail end of grandma's here. He gives him the smokeless ash tray, which you can
already tell us in these lights really makes me feel nostalgic for my youth. You
know, you can't find one Christmas light on a goddamn house in Los Angeles. Oh, I
found a house. I found a house all done up down the street with those kinds of
lights. All right. We're at old school. Well, you can tell me after these people don't
Did you do your house up?
No, because I would have made my house stand out too much.
There's a woman I work with who just bought a great new house that looks very much like a painting.
It is a painting.
They used to do that in the movies, they just put up a painting.
Yeah, just have a guy walk into it.
No, she just bought a house in this really nice neighborhood and in our neighborhood, let's feel it.
And she wants a yellow door on her house.
And I've seen like the spec and it looks awesome and the neighborhood association won't allow it because it would make her stand out
What it's her own home. She's paying upwards of probably two million dollars for
They're not allowing it
So she's like I'm just gonna do it and they're like well then, you know
You're gonna hear from the board and what does that mean? I don't know
But it's your own house. Oh Nikki cats in this from days and a few as a school child
Wait a minute, what?
Nickycat, he just went all the door.
Yeah.
The door, the door.
That's a good three -stugious moment.
Michael Winslow did some Frank Welker,
who's the Joker on the Batman animated series.
No.
No, that's Mark Campbell.
Mark Campbell.
Frank Welker was a Joker in what?
Well, maybe he took over from Mark Campbell.
All right, fine.
Yeah, she can't do this door.
So, like, I could have done lights,
but there's not one house with lights in my neighborhood.
good. So I feel like I would just look stupid. You literally, literally, just said the
thing that's finally made me decide that I will never live here forever. The door thing.
That was it. You can't stand out to it. That's revolting. I get as angry as you do with her
and she's pissed too. She's like, I'm just going to do it. And they're like, you will be
dealt with or something you know I don't think they can sewer but they can do
something. If you're a member of that neighborhood board, fuck you, you soulless fuck.
Sorry Pat, I know you're gonna live there. Jesus Christ. This is Ben, we'll see you
So in hell, a presentation of the Fangoria podcast network produced by Thomas DeFail, executive
produced by Ken Haley of Fangoria Entertainment for press opportunities, advertising, increase
and information about we'll see you in hell contact Ken at Fangoria .com.
Thanks for listening, guys.
We'll hit you in another Christmas episode this month.
Thanks a lot, folks.
Give us those five star reviews, give us those ratings.
I'm at the Patrick Walsh.
Joe is at Joe DeRosa Comedy.
yeah and if you're in New York come see me at Gotham this December 18th and
19th and if you're in LA actually I'll plug those next time it got them 18th
the 19 night folks.