I'm here for Bet Rivers Online Casino and Sportsbook with poker icon Phil Helmuth.
And now thanks to the excitement of Bet Rivers, I'm also a slots icon.
That's great! And a same game, Parley icon.
Cool, cool. A Blackjack icon, a Moneyline icon.
A roulette. Take it from Phil Helmuth.
If you love games, Bet Rivers is the place to play in Bet.
Bet Rivers.
Games on.
Must be 21 plus in present in West Virginia.
Void were prohibited. Terms in conditions apply.
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gambling.
The football season is full of guarantees.
And here's another.
No weather sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October.
If your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning
or winning money back in fan cash. Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 plus. Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gambling.
Offer not available in all states. Terms apply.
See fanatic sportsbook app.
It's a good show.
Welcome, too. We'll see you in hell.
Another January episode in this lovely year of 2019.
Today we discuss phantasm.
And why?
Because that's what we do on this show.
We discuss horror films and fantasy films and sci -fi films.
And sometimes even an action or a drama or comedy.
And eventually we'll get into the Pixar a lot.
But for now, today, still horror.
That horror is phantasm.
I'm Joe DeRosa.
I'm Patrick Walsh. Hello.
Yeah, the Joe Bob Briggs Christmas marathon.
I heard about a week before they were going to be showing all the movies in a franchise.
And I was like, great. Love it.
There's so few horror franchises where I've seen every one.
And I like everyone else thought I was going to be silent night, deadly night.
I've seen the original. I haven't seen any of the other ones.
It's airing on like December 21st.
And I sat down and I got to admit I was in a Christmas mood.
I think everybody there was in a Christmas mood.
And when it was phantasm, I was like, really?
Well, maybe they don't have the rights to silent night, deadly night.
Clearly they didn't.
They're also supposed to show the whole phantasm franchise through
ravager, which I've not, I've only seen the first phantasm now.
But they skipped too.
They skipped too, which is most people's favorites.
And then, you know, he gave some sort of bullshit reason for it,
but I feel like they just didn't get the rights.
What was his reason?
His reason was like,
because it was a different actor playing Tommy or whatever.
Yeah, he did some sort of like thing,
where you know that wasn't the real thing.
But people's favorite of the franchise is phantasm too.
So then many people.
Yeah, you know, I finished one and I was like,
I don't want to watch three and four.
And then he thinks that four is the best or something?
That's a common claim.
I don't agree with it.
But you ever see ravager?
I've seen all of them.
I own all of them.
Yeah.
I'm going to watch them.
I still have them, of course, on my shutter.
I'm a big phantasm fan.
And we can talk about, we can talk about ravager today
in addition to the original, if you like.
The ravager.
But you know, but that's for later, Pat.
In the meantime, it is.
How have you been since the last time we recorded?
Well, it was five minutes ago.
Yeah, but I've been pretty good.
That's a lie, but why drag you into my life?
I got two months more of the show.
I'm at a stress saturation point, you know?
Last night, I went to a lovely dinner party.
I thought I was in a fine mood.
I wake up at 3 .30 a .m.
Sort of panicked, uncomfortable.
I'm up to like nine.
Then I fall asleep to like noon.
This is what my Sundays are, like my nice relaxing Sundays.
Um, but it is what it is.
I'm going to a show tonight.
I was telling Joe.
I don't know if I'm excited or not.
I'm not excited about that show.
A buddy of mine got tickets.
It's a Malibu.
It's a benefit for the Malibu homes that got lost.
Nice cause.
It's a nice cause, but at the same time, you're kind of like,
but everybody in Malibu is rich.
Well, you know, it's, but yeah, it's a nice cause.
The bands I could, you know, I would say Vincent,
who I love and who is a great live performer.
I like saying Vincent.
It's back who is one of my favorite musical artists of all time.
Care less.
Love back.
Don't care.
And, uh, and a band we've discussed at Nausium on the show,
The Red Hat Chili Peppers, who are, I think have a couple of okay albums,
but live, the man's the worst singer that has ever lived and has not improved over a 30 year career.
Well, that's why you got like flea doing back flips and shit.
Yeah, it's, you know, it's kind of you're only, uh, you're only hope.
The appeal is that the Hollywood palladium, which is a pretty small venue,
and it's cool to see him there, but um,
palladium, little fun fact is where they shot the climax of the blues brothers, where they perform.
Uh, I guess that's kind of a fun fact, you know, uh, yeah, sure.
I mean, it's not a bad fact.
Do anything for you?
Nothing.
Con, stop it.
Con's back.
My dog is barking.
Joe brought him back.
He wants his ball.
All right, I'm going to get you the ball.
He figured out where I hid the ball.
Now I have to give him the ball, but we're not playing ball, Con.
So you're going to have to take it over there and just be with your ball.
Joe gets really excited about a ball.
You almost start on the dog.
Jesus Christ.
Have you ever sat on your dog?
I asked.
Uh, no, no.
He almost looked like he was trying to kill himself.
It did.
He jumped right under Joe's ass as it was about to hit the couch.
Yeah, uh, these pants too short.
I don't have to see him in a standing position.
And now it's just getting weird.
But well, no, are they too short?
Because I feel like when I sit, they get too short.
They look the exact right length for standing jeans, but yeah,
they're going to come up a little bit when you sit.
So you don't think they're too short?
I don't know how many different ways I can say it.
No.
We'll say no.
I did.
I said they're a perfect standing size,
but when you have a perfect standing size,
they're going to go up when you sit.
Not too much up though, right?
Of course.
Pat confessed to me before we started recording
in between the podcasts here that uh,
that he's been drinking more than ever before.
Are there, is that how he's raised it?
well, I, you know,
That's something I shouldn't have shared.
Sorry.
Probably not, but I can, I can cut it out of here.
So it's fun.
Mike, my Christmas break, uh,
Christmas is always a heavy drinking time.
I was a mess.
And uh, generally the new year hits
and I'm like, let me turn it off.
But I would say me and my,
my writing staff have been really put
through the ringer.
And we are drinking.
I am drinking.
I, uh, not doing it in the morning.
I'm, you know, I'm not going to work drunk.
But it's the kind of thing where like when I,
when I have a sit like the other night,
um, Heather and I were going to, uh,
the premiere of corporate Comedy Central's corporate.
And while I've got you,
it's my friends Jake Weisman and Mad Angerbretson.
I have some friends on the writing staff.
Saw three episodes.
It's fantastic.
If you're not watching this show, you should.
It's a great show.
But, uh, beforehand, Heather and I go to dinner.
I have a glass of wine.
The second that wine rolls over my tongue.
My eyes open like in a cartoon.
Like when the eyes like pop open.
Like just, I was just like, where's more where I need more?
What's going on?
And I don't like being in that place.
I'm about to maybe do one of my cleanses.
But I'm under too much stress to do it right now.
Uh, yeah, I hear you.
I took, I recently took about an eight day break.
Yeah, I was hoping to do a dry January.
Yeah, I don't know.
See, my problem is is I don't, I've talked about it.
I don't like pot.
So when I dry, that's it, man.
I got nothing.
Yeah.
So I don't know if I'm going to be able to do a dry Jan.
I mean, maybe what I'll do is a, um,
like a once a week or kind of thing.
But as I said to you, well, we talked about booze
because I'm not throwing you out there.
I'll step right out there with you.
Drank yesterday for the first time in a while.
Didn't didn't go nuts at six drinks.
Yeah, throughout the afternoon into the evening.
Uh, and I was like, okay, that's it for the week.
And now today it's like, you know, we're going to wrap this thing up in an hour
and it's, you know, I'm thinking maybe patty and I go wouldn't have a cocktail.
Yeah.
I'm eating bad.
I'm drinking bad.
I'm, I'm weeding.
Do you have to go anywhere right after this?
Not right after now.
Boy, so then there's no, all right.
Well, I think, I mean, I, I keep telling myself I'm going nuts because
in a short amount of time, I'm going to be shutting it all down
and going to, uh, perhaps heading into the child,
you know, fertilizing an egg.
That's a damn it.
God damn it.
But I think we're doing egg storage.
I don't think we're going to have the kid like within the year.
It's terrible news.
But yeah, you know, Heather's like, you might want to tighten things up a little bit
if your jizz is going to be making a baby for us.
I got to tell you.
And maybe this is the first time I'm admitting this publicly.
Yeah.
I'm never happy for a friend when they say they're going to have a kid.
It's fair.
Uh, never, never once have I truly thought that's great.
Uh, you say it.
You say it?
I'm not happy about it.
I did, it bums me out.
It's not happening in 2019.
I know that much, but all right.
Well, there you go.
Uh, this dog is going nuts and pulling on my cord.
Hold on.
I'm going to go lock him in the bedroom with the ball.
And then hope to keep himself busy in there with this.
Well, while you're gone, you hear that bike horn just going incessantly?
Well, yeah, Joe, I do.
Do I hear the bike horn?
That's what it's going to be like when you have a kid because you know,
kids are with the bike horn.
If the kids like me, it'll be chill and just sit and watch people and judge them silently.
And that's fine.
Apparently my entire child that I would just watch people and be like,
look at this fucking loser right here.
And that's still what I do to this day.
Um, let us get on with the show.
If we may.
And at the same time on
with the
this bike horn is fucking killing me.
Listen to this.
Is that a child?
I mean, it's either a child or a man with a mind of one.
Oh, it's a guy selling hold on.
Let me look at this.
He's selling shaved ice for some shit.
He's selling, uh, now it's one of those carts.
You only ever see this in LA, the like Mexican guys that sell the bags of like
fruit.
It's not fruit.
It's those like puff things that look like some sort of weird like funnions.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't know what they are.
That's what he's doing.
He's honking to tell people come out.
I've got the funnions.
He's also appears to have some popsicle sticking out of a garbage bag
and a jug of milk.
That's what it looks like from here.
I can't see.
But that horn is for Christ's.
Oftentimes I go up to a guy who's honking a bike horn on the street
and asks for a glass of milk.
Um, you drink milk with those funnions.
I have no interest.
I always see the fruit guys.
They were, I like the fruit.
I mean, I like all the guys selling stuff in the street,
but that horn's really annoying.
There's this site next door where it's just people bitching about their neighborhood.
It's a great way to kill, kill a little time when Twitter gets to be too oppressive,
but it's just people bitching about things happening in the neighborhood.
And you sign up and you enter your address and then you get all the updates.
So a lot of it's like people are being very noisy and it's 9 p .m.
or whatever, but then sometimes it's super racer shit.
They're like a guy was walking down my street today in broad daylight
wearing a hooded sweatshirt.
Right.
I know we're not supposed to mention their race,
but I think you know what race he was.
And you're like, what are you saying here?
Like are you trying to scare the neighborhood that a man was walking down the street?
Oh boy.
But then there's also funny stuff.
There's people selling stuff.
And that's the kind of thing where like there was a guy
selling fruit near my neighborhood out of a thing.
And for months people were like, he's being deported.
Let's band together and save this man.
And then people are like telling their store, look, he wound up fine.
He didn't get deported, which is great.
But people were like, I still remember the first time I bought a bag of fruit from Manuel.
I had been riding my bike and I was in need of some vitamin C.
And there he was slicing up a honeydew.
I'm like, are you fucking kidding me?
Does everything have to be about you?
People in this town, they can't help it, man.
They can't help it.
There was Manuel with a wedge of watermelon to quench my thirst.
He was wearing a hoodie, which I didn't care for.
Yeah, exactly.
But aside from that, yeah, that's annoying.
Oh, you never got on with the thing.
I interrupted it.
That's how it ended.
I was so annoyed by the bike horn.
Yeah, on with the...
Oh, that's it.
That was the end of that one.
Now, Joe...
That one was crazy.
Do we have anything for screaming in?
I saw this week and I'm going to talk about it in the movie corner,
the movie Green Book, which I found very entertaining.
And I don't know why people hate it, it's a really entertaining movie.
I know why they hate it because there's a big controversy about how
they didn't ask no one, none of the white men who wrote the script,
including Peter Farley of the Farley brothers who directed it and co -wrote it.
None of them consulted the actual black man, whose story it is.
They only talked to the...
What movie are you talking about?
Italian guy, Green Book.
This is Screamin' End.
Wait, what the hell just happened?
Screamin' End is movie news.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I think it's supposed to be horror movie.
I thought you were asking me if I had something and then you started...
I did, I did.
Go run with it.
So Green Book, you know, it's a big controversy that three white men wrote it,
and none of them asked the black guy or his family anything.
They just only went off the white guy's reminiscence.
Right.
And the guy is this guy, Nick Valinoga,
who was actually on the sopranos,
but it's his life story that became Green Book.
Yes, so I saw a tweet today so packed with information
that I had to read it several times.
But you know how when you retweet something,
you can add your own comment to it?
Yes.
So it was like Green Book's Oscar chance is looking bleak
because Nick Valinoga, who co -wrote the movie,
he responded to a Donald Trump tweet, like replied to it.
Yeah.
And was like, I saw the Muslims cheering 9 -11 in Jersey City,
just like you said, Donald.
Right, right.
I'm sure his publicity team was like,
God damn it.
The Oscars are in a month.
You just won the Golden Globe.
Yeah.
And this bike horn just fucking killed me.
I'm sure a listeners can hear it.
Oh my God.
All right, so it says this,
and it's like Oscar chance is looking bleak.
You know, did an anti -Muslim tweet.
Then in the space above it where it says,
you know, like some retweet thing that can add to it,
it says, also Peter Farley admits to flashing his penis
numerous times in the past.
I was like, this movie's going down.
They have everything.
Well, and then they also got in the mortish in hot water
when he said the end bomb at that thing.
Morton.
People got mad.
I realized what he was trying to say.
He was not clearly, he was not being racist.
He was saying like, he was talking about the times.
Yeah, but you don't say the word.
The, uh, I, you know, I've got a problem with the,
this is just, this isn't N word related.
This is any word related.
I think it gets a little crazy when we start to say
in any context, you can never say any word.
And you bet because it, it just keeps bleeding out
to word after word after word after word where it's like,
I understand why the word, for instance,
Kant is offensive.
But the fact that that now has become the C word
as if there is a legacy of bloodshed tied to it,
it's just not, it's just not the, I'm sorry,
it's not the same thing.
You know what I mean?
Like so, you know, retarded is another one where it's like
now even if you say like, this person is mentally retarded
meaning just the condition, you can get in trouble.
Yes.
Like, that's crazy to me.
Like, that's, I understand why people get mad if you use it
in a derogatory sense, but again, that's context, right?
I mean, why not just don't say it, you know?
Well then, but then, you know, but then what?
Then, you know, there's so many other words.
Why don't just then never say fuck again,
only say the F word because it doesn't bother anyone.
You know, oh, that's not true.
There's tons of people fuck bothers.
It's like when a religious person goes,
I say holy cow instead of Jesus Christ because Jesus Christ is offensive.
It's like, what's offensive to?
Holy cow should be offensive to you.
That's the point of, that's the point of that pen and teller made.
That's offensive, technically that's offensive to people
that think the cow is a sacred animal.
Right.
I'm just saying Peter Farley, you know, apparently there was this newsweek profile
and they talked about up here fairly as a prank shows everyone his penis.
And this was like from 1998 and they were like,
when they first met Cameron Diaz or Cammy, if you will,
about something about Mary in the entire interview as Dick was out.
And Cameron Diaz thought it was hilarious and whatever.
And, all right, you know, that was in newsweek
and no one cared for 20 years.
I have heard about numerous writers rooms where people do bits
where their dick is out in a room with men and women.
Beloved people who I won't mention because some of them are dead
have a long history of showing their dicks off in writers rooms.
And it wasn't great then, it's not great now,
but like, are we really going to, why don't we need to bring Peter Farley down
for showing his dick in 1998?
He's doing like this apology tour about showing his dick off so that he can win an Oscar.
And it's like, I've heard nothing about the Farley Bros being the nicest men in all of Hollywood.
You know, I'm just, but here we are.
This is all I'm saying.
I never thought to show, you know, never felt the need to whip my dick out in a meeting.
Neither did I.
I also never felt the need to say certain words in public,
even considering their context, but this is kind of my point.
When we start to let go of situation and what was meant and what is the intention
and how was this being used and what was actually happening.
We start to put all that aside and start to say, nope, across the board,
always this thing can never, ever, ever, ever take place.
I understand that in for some, with some practices and behaviors, that is very good,
obviously murder, et cetera, but then when you start to apply it to everything,
it's like, it's just not how life is.
Like freedom is, there is a certain amount of risk that comes along with freedom.
There is a certain, when you live in a free society, you have to take situations into account
individually and you can't make these blanket things that apply to everything all the time.
In other words, if Cameron Diaz thought it was funny that he pulled his dick out and he knew
that she would think it was funny and they had a chuckle, then that's between Cameron Diaz and
Pharaoh. That's not for anybody else to comment on. It's not the same thing as a guy whipping his
dick out and the person being offended. It's not the same fucking thing. Agreed.
But in any case, people what I'm trying to say is, Donald Trump is trying to make this country
great again. Anyway, it's a complicated time we live in and, Joe, did you watch the Golden Globes?
Pat, I didn't. Did you know that the theme this year was changed?
That it was about you. I kept writing, Joe, the globes this year are all about change because
they said it a million times. And I was mad that I got no laugh on my joke that I texted you.
You texted me that and I wrote the first thing I'd like to change is these hosts. Folks!
That's why I thought you were watching it. No, no, but I didn't get a laugh. I just...
Ha, ha, nothing. I never feel the need to write back, ha, ha. But, uh, yes,
Samberg and oh, together at last, they came out. By the way, where the fuck did these two come
back from? I haven't seen these two in anything in years. They did 10 joke -less or laugh -less minutes.
The audience was uncomfortable. Samberg is doing like, we're gonna really roast the audience,
Ricky Jervais style. And they went to 10 different people and we're like, you're beautiful. You're
funny, like a positive roast. So you're like, okay, fine, got it. Then, Samberg does an extremely
political joke about how the police and the government killed Black Panthers back in the day.
And they cut to the director of Black Panther who was looking like, what the fuck are you doing?
Ha, ha, ha, ha. Like, it was so totally all over the place. We're gonna be the goofy, fun,
cute hosts, but then we're gonna do a really rough joke. You know, like, it was, it was a mess.
The show was a mess. They, here's how stupid the fucking gold, you know, the Golden Globes are
voted on by like 60 people. Yeah. Many of them who are not even from our country. Where are the
Golden Globes? You know, so like, it's a, it's an insane, not the people, you know, you know what I mean?
Not the people not from our country shouldn't be allowed to vote, but it's like, why are we watching
this? Like, it's something important when it's 60 randos from across the globe, picking what they
think. So this year, the winner for best comedy or musical was Green Book, which is a drama about
civil rights. The winner for best drama was Bohemian Rhapsody, which is unquestionably a musical.
Oh, I wouldn't say Bohemian Rhapsody's a musical. I would have put it in drama.
I mean, it's not a comedy by any of you. It's start to finish a musical. How is it a musical?
Because it's wall to wall music from, but a musical means they, the action and it doesn't,
not, not in the context of the Golden Globes. I don't know where Green Book is a comedy. Fair enough,
all right, fair enough. They will put things now in whatever category they think it has the best
chance of winning. You're growing down, you're like, wait a minute, but that movie's a drama. That
everything they had was in the wrong category. These award shows are so fucking stupid. Let me take you
over to Pat's movie corner where I'll talk about Bohemian Rhapsody. Joe loved it. America loved it.
Critics are all talking shit about it. Say it plays like a spoof of biopics, blah, blah, blah.
The movie is unbelievably entertaining from start to finish. The only drawback I had was I was like,
what if you were actually friends with, uh, uh, uh, can I remember the series?
Queen's name. Pretty murk. Because there were times when he was talking to the band where I was like,
oh, I'd fucking hate this guy. Yeah. When he's like, I see things a little differently my, you know,
blah, blah, blah. Yeah, he was annoying at times. Rami Malik was good in the role. I was tremendous.
I think I would have preferred Baron Cohen's take on it because then when I saw Rami Malik accept
best actor, he was every bit as annoying as like the worst moments of Freddie Mercury in the movie.
And just as kind of like smelling his own shit kind of, but, uh, the movie was so entertaining.
I watched it with my mom and her husband. Yes. Loved it. Had a blast. The music is great.
I even liked the corny Mike Myers shit. Yeah. The Bohemian Rhapsody. No teenagers will never bang their
heads to this. I liked it. It was super entertaining. And at about the hour 20 mark, my, uh, stepdad
stops the movie and he goes, boy, you know, I, I didn't know I'd like this star is born so much.
I really enjoy this star is born. I got everybody's been saying it's, and I go, we're not watching a star.
It's just sure it's just a star. He thought the movie. Oh boy. Because the star was born in it. Yeah.
I'd also like to point out that I was sitting on a couch with a giant bullet hole through it because
my stepdad had fired a gun. Yeah. Into the couch. Uh, he goes, uh, well, I go, how did that happen?
He goes, you know, I was cleaning a rifle and it went off. It blew a hole in the couch. It blew a
hole in the fireplace. And it also blew a hole in a box of shredded wheat. I turned to your mother.
I said, Jill, uh, I guess the wheat really was shredded, huh? Oh, man. I said, okay. I see where
you get it from. It's my stepdad. I wouldn't get it from him at all. We're not related. It's just a joke.
But my mom was home. It's like down the hall in a, in a relatively small house could have been shot.
So I'm like, why were you cleaning a gun in the house with my mom here? Like what? Why was it loaded?
Why was exactly. He goes, well, what, I mean, what do you want me to do? Shoot it off the back porch?
We got a school behind us. I go, how about you take it into the woods or somewhere else?
Or how about just clean it in the house without it being loaded? Great point, Jill. Yeah, that's,
that's all you got to do. Uh, maybe you don't clean it in the living room. Yeah. Uh, well, he
met Ramsey as a blast. The dude who played Brian May was awesome. Uh, the Joseph Mozello, the kid
from Jurassic Park playing the bassist. Uh, I love the film. It's super entertaining. It was a very
bizarre choice to have the last 25 minutes. Be a shot for shot. Oh, it was recreation of my
video. But yeah, the last 20 minutes of the movie, it's, it's, it's not, the, it's not 20 minutes
because their whole performance at Live Aid was 20 minutes. And that's not the whole performance.
Oh, I thought it was the whole performance. But their whole performance is going to be available. They
did shoot the entire thing. I just sort of felt like at that point, if you're going to do this,
let us see the real performance. I loved that sequence. Uh, both times I watched it, the second time
was with my mom. We were crying our eyes out. My mom's going, what a loss. You know, uh, it was so
inspirational. By the way, he didn't know he was diagnosed. I know. They flipped a lot of stuff
around like that. But I find that weird as we've discussed before. They flipped a lot of stuff
around time wise. I get that. But I loved the movie. I love Queen. Yes, I knew. Uh, it made me,
it made that watching the movie made me purchase the album, The Works, which was always one of the
later Queen albums that I sort of disregarded. And it is one of the best Queen albums. I can't believe
I didn't never had that one. Um, but um, what's on the works? Radio Gaga. Oh, we
tear it up. It's a hard life. Okay. I want to break free. I want to break free. Um,
nothing but hits robots or or back to humans. I think it's called robot. I can't remember,
but it's a fucking killer record. Anyway, uh, yeah, I love the movie as well. Um, but I've already
stated that I'll do a quick one. I re finished the Kaminsky method. Okay. Love to every minute of
this show ends on a beautiful open note for a potential second season. I hope it happens.
What starts out as a seeming commentary on the business of Hollywood. Uh, and, and something we've
kind of seen a million times quickly, uh, transforms into a very, very sweet story about a very
odd relationship of love between two old best friends. Yeah. These friends do remind me of Pat and
myself. Uh, who are who are you and who I'm on? I'm Douglas and you're Arkin because Arkin is like
married and has a lot of money and did everything right and Douglas is like, you know, a mess.
Yeah, kind of. Yeah. So for me, the stuff that was not working at all and what I couldn't wrap my
head around was I watched the first two, maybe, and they spent 25 minutes of the second episode with
his acting class. And I was like, this is not what this show should be about. Well, that's the problem
with these a lot of these Netflix shows or any of these shows where they release a whole season at
once. It's very obvious that there are places where they're sort of putty filling the cracks. Like,
like, we've got to get 10. If you know guys, if you just stretch it a little more, we can do 10
episodes. Right. And, and so, so there are moments like that that don't work. But overall, I truly,
truly love this thing. Arkin, when Arkin's daughter finally comes back in the series, it's great.
She's played by, uh, character actor, I forget her name, but she was on, she was on an episode of
Frazier. She played a crazy artist. She's the risotto woman from Seinfeld. I feel I feel full when
I eat the risotto. Um, she's great. Uh, she's always great. And she's in this and she plays like this
pillhead addict. And she's really funny and, and crazy in it. Um, Elliot Gould pops up at one point.
Sure. Delightful. Yeah. Uh, I just love the show. I love a show about old people.
Um, sort of discovering new love or whatever late in life that they didn't necessarily know was
there. Right. It's why my favorite love, actually story, is the one about the rock star and his
manager. Yes. It's just a beautiful thing to me. So I love the show. I hope we get more of it. Uh,
you know, it's cliche in, in certain ways, but I really enjoy it. Fair enough. I, uh, let's talk
Green Book. Um, watch that with my dad on the on the other side of the fan. And it's if you're
looking for something, I know the holidays are over. But if you're looking for a good parent movie,
uh, Green Book is a great choice. It felt like a 90s movie. You know, um, people have compared it
to crash because like it does. But what people don't understand is not everything has to be
a super gritty, like rough exploration of something. You know, like, I hate sappy shit.
Green Book, I thought handled sappy material in a non -sappy way. If you're willing, if you want to
like get a deeper look at it, read the actual story of these two men, which is quite a bit darker than
the movie. But if you're just looking at it as a, as a feel good movie, it's unbelievably entertaining.
The story between the two of them is charming and sweet. Maharasha Ali from Moonlight. I probably
pronounced that wrong. And V. Joe Mortensen, I might have pronounced that wrong. You definitely
pronounced that second one. Vigo Mortensen. Yeah. The V. Joe was what I was focused on. V. Joe.
Um, I didn't even know that was him when I would see the trailers. He put on some weight. Yeah.
They're very good in it. His whole bit is that he's eating the entire time. Um, but look, you know,
the fairly brothers even in their most disgusting comedies always had a real big heart going on.
And they bring that heart to this. It's a sweet, entertaining story about race relations. Yes,
race relations at that time. We're not always sweet. But sometimes a spoonful of sugar helps
that medicine go down. And I thought it was a super entertaining picture with great performances by
the two leads. A great performance by Linda Cartelini as his wife back home. I love Linda Cartelini.
I didn't know she was in it. It's really sweet. It's, you know, it's your classic road trip movie where
the two men learn about themselves and learn about each other. And, you know, if you can't let
one of those work its magic on you once in a while, God help you. It was, it was very entertaining.
Best picture? No, but very entertaining. I only do one more because I got to scary stuff I want to
get to. We have time, Joe. Let's do three. I know. I'm going to just do one more because I want to save
my other three for next episode. All right. I watched home coming. I saw the first one which
bored me. How does it go? You know, it's funny. I watched the first one and I was kind of like,
I mean, I was a big fan of the podcast. I was disappointed in the casting of the show. Not because
I don't like the actors that they cast, but I thought the cat podcast was so expertly cast,
particularly with Kathleen Keener, Catherine Keener, and David Schwimmer. I thought they
were really, really excellent. And then Oscar Isaac played the soldier. And I thought I just
thought it was a real good trio of actors that really did a great job in bringing something that I
could only listen to and giving it a visual life. So I was a little sad when I saw that they weren't
playing the parts in this one. But they didn't get any slouches for this. You got Julia Roberts.
You got Bobby Cannon Valley. It was a good show overall. The first episode also kind of bored me.
I wasn't grabbed, but it was shot well enough. And the soundtrack was intriguing enough
and it was acted well enough that I was like, well, let me give this a chance. And then the next
thing you knew I was binging it. And overall I enjoyed it. It was an experience worth worth exploring.
And I actually went out and I did some research on the soundtrack to the show because I thought
the music was so cool. And I learned, interestingly enough, the songs used in the show, very few of them
were original pieces. They were mostly pieces of score pieces taken from old movies from like the 70s.
Yes. To kind of give it that sort of haunting, like I don't know if New York is the right term,
but that sort of 70s thriller kind of feel. And I ended up buying the record store day edition
of the Andromeda strain soundtrack on vinyl because they used scores from other. Yeah.
Because there was a piece in there that got so in my head, I like looked up the episode,
then looked up every song they used in that episode that went to YouTube and listened to every song
and then finally found out, oh, the one song I won is from the Out of Print soundtrack from the
fucking 70s. Of course. But I did manage to get my hands on a copy of it, which I'm happy about. So
yeah, I'll watch it. Heather blasted through it and loved it. I'll get back into it.
I'd like to mention one more if I may. I did two new ones in theaters. I'll do one that's new to video
called searching. This is a movie from last year that I think people really unfairly slept on.
It stars John Cho who is an acquaintance of mine and a very nice man. I didn't know you knew John
Cho. I'm a fan of his. I know. Well, my buddies do the Harold and Kumar pictures. That's right.
He's a super nice guy and in this movie, which is certainly the best showcase I have seen for him as
an actor, it is basically a movie much like unfriended, which was a horror movie that I really had a lot
of love for and sort of kicked myself for. It was a movie that was probably made for 10 grand or
something. Searching is all done online. So for a lot of the movie you're looking at a computer screen.
This is the second movie I've seen that did the extra the third if you want to count cam. And
in all three of these movies, maybe because we spend so much time looking at our screens,
it didn't bother me. It didn't feel claustrophobic or annoying as a gimmick.
Totally loved it. You're looking at a lot of screens, a lot of chats, a lot of videos,
a Facebook pages, etc. But they keep it very entertaining, visually well done, extremely well written.
It's a thriller where a guy is wondering basically where his daughter is. John Cho is wondering where his
daughter is. And it's great. It's like a super small low budget low stakes or not low stakes.
You know, I'm trying to say low. I don't know. I don't know. I'm trying to say so why would you know
what I'm trying to say. But it's super entertaining. Simple film. It's like simple. It's like
taken. But but without all the pyrotechnics and everything. It's got some beautiful twists. It's
extremely well written. I urge you to check it out. It just hit video. All right. DVD or whatever you watch.
All right. Pat, I got a little scary stuff for you. Right. My lovely parents gifted me for Christmas.
The C64 mini, which is the Commodore 60, the mini modern version of the Commodore 64 computer from
the 1980s. The purpose of the C64 mini is exactly that of the purposes for these other minis that have
come out like the Nintendo and such. It is a video game plug and play console. That is HD ready. HDMI
right into the TV set. It contains 64 wink, wink games from the Commodore 64 computer classic.
Many of which have horror and fantasy themes, which is why it fits into this segment here.
It's a very cool looking little piece of equipment. It's beautifully packaged. It's beautifully crafted.
That being said, I haven't had an ounce of fun playing it. These games are the hardest fucking things
I've ever played in my life. I can't get anywhere in any of them. I posted about this on Instagram.
My experience playing it at my mom and dad's was me yelling at the TV as my dad cackled
uncontrollably behind me at me because I kept dying instantly in every single game. I couldn't
get past level one of anything. Okay. But one of the other cool things is it's got a couple USB ports on
it. You can hook up a USB keyboard and actually use it more to the extent of an actual Commodore 64
computer. You're not going to use this thing as an actual computer but you can use the keyboard
for typing purposes and for game playing purposes. It's also got the USB port is also handy
for downloading not only your upgrades to the system but also other games that you can put onto it,
which I did do and found some easier games to play. Still not great at those either. But as an
avid video game guy and if you're a collector out there, I'd say pick one up for yourself. It's
70 bucks. Not too shabby a price. Looks nice on the shelf and hey, you might have some fun with it.
All right.
Our movie of the today. Well, not quite because I wanted to ask you for screaming in.
Did you watch the new trailer for Jordan Peel's us? Yes.
Set the world on fire over Christmas. I think it looks awesome. It looks good. Can't wait to see.
I'm curious to see what happens. Yeah, I don't know what it's about. It looks scary. It looks fun.
I'm excited to see it. It appears to be about some sort of doppelganger monsters. Yeah.
It looks interesting. It looks to be which I like that he's doing this. It looks to be in a similar
thematically similar to get out in the sense of, you know, people not being what they seem they
are. Yes. Were other people possessing people that they shouldn't be possessing. Something along
those lines, you know, the duality of a person or whatever. So I look forward to it. It looks very
good from what I could tell. All right. Great. Now, we're talking on today's show about 1979 film
Phantasm. I had only seen parts of two when I was about 10 years old and found it terrifying. I've
never seen anything in the franchise. I have to pee again. I'm sorry. It's fine. Last episode. I'm
sorry. It's fine. The film has been digitally restored by, of all people, JJ Abrams, who I
guess is a big fan of Phantasm. And the thing, especially for being 1979, the thing looks fucking
incredible. The transfer they've done on this thing. Phantasm is sort of a science fiction fantasy horror
movie. It features one of horror's great villains, the Tallman, Angus, Scrim, also from Poltergeist.
A two, believe I'm right there. Let me check on that real quick. Poltergeist. No, I'm wrong.
I am wrong. That was not him. Some other guy. Okay. Good to know. But yeah, basically it is about
the Tallman, who was an undertaker who turns the dead of Earth into dwarf zombies to be sent to his
planet and used his slaves. That's directly from Wikipedia. I got to be honest. That wasn't
necessarily clear to me from viewing this movie. The movie, to me, works best if taken as sort of a
dream. It's a really, really good sort of replication of a dream state. You always feel like
you're not sure what's going on. You always feel sort of confused and on edge. And that's where you
want to be really for a horror movie. I thought it was great. Visually, it's awesome. There's a very
famous shot where they're kind of floating over a grave and a headstone that is just a really
unsettling shot. And it's a great example of a low budget horror done right. I recommend if you've
never seen it watching it with the Joe Bob Briggs commentary because it was great. I'm eager to watch
the entire franchise and have more to say about this series. But the first one I thought was super
entertaining. I agree. I heard some of what you said. Yes, but I know it was all glowing.
And my take on this film is also all glowing. I think Phantasm is an excellent piece of cinema.
I think it transcends the genre. I think it's a classic film from the 70s that whether you like horror
or not, you should see because it is a lesson in filmmaking. And I think it's very indicative of that
time period of filmmaking. Just really, really, really well done. The transfer as Pat mentioned is
gorgeous, by the way. So you're going to want to get that high death blu -ray, which is pretty
available everywhere. And that's how they stream it now anyway. I got mine digitally and it was
HD. So it looks great. The dream state aspect of the film works very well in the first movie.
The second movie is a little more straightforward. It's a little more of an action horror style of
things. Some people like this better. Some people don't. I love to. I think one is the best of all of
them. I think two is great. And it's a lot of fun. But the dream, sort of, you know, what is real and
what is an aspect of these films? I like that it serves its purpose early on in the franchise.
Later, it sort of gets a little too like, well, I guess they can just do anything they want
because who knows what's real and who knows what is and what isn't. But I guess that's the point.
That being said, I enjoy all of the, I love the entire series. Ravager is disappointing. Don,
it was so raved about. It's okay. It's the budget is the lack of budget is very apparent.
Don Cascarelli, I think is how you say his last name or is it Cascarelli? Yeah. His absence as a
director is noticed. He only produced that one. It's the only one he didn't direct.
And it's also it's the one that gets the craziest as far as like alternate realities and
people kind of not knowing what's actually happening and being sucked from one place in time to
another instantaneously or whatever. Look, it's still as its moments. But it was also compiled
from as far as I understand a series of shorts that were to take place in the Phantasm Universe that
they eventually cobbled together into a full movie. And I think they were web shorts. And again,
you can kind of see that. Like it does have a video quality to it. Which the other ones don't.
It didn't make a great deal of sense to me, which is why I appreciated
Joe Bob Briggs, a horror aficionado and every break was like, now I know there doesn't make
any goddamn sense. The first one are Ravager. I'm talking about the first one. Really the whole
franchise, he was just like, this is all just like a dream. It makes no sense. Don't worry about it.
I was like, good, I don't want to worry about it. Yeah. That's kind of what it is. So like I said,
early on, I appreciate that element a little bit more. Eventually gets to a point where it's like,
well, you can just do anything you want and who cares. But that doesn't ruin it.
Ravager gets the craziest, the fifth one. That one is like, that starts to creep real hard into
like sci -fi. And the first one's kind of, they're all sort of sci -fi -ish. Yeah. But Ravager really
gets into like, to me, like sort of the idea of the post -apocalypse and science fiction and whatever.
But it's, it's a worthy ending and it, it brings some closure to the franchise. And I think
phantasm is one of the few franchises out there where, you know, you could say, hey, if you see
a box set by it, there are very few franchises that you can say that, you know, my parents,
again, for Christmas got me the, you know, God bless my mom. I asked for a wrong turn one to three.
Yeah. Because some fans of ours have said, you got to see two and three. They're great. So I asked
for them for Christmas. I had never seen them. My mom bought me all six. Okay. Wrong turns, which is
awesome. But, you know, I don't think I've ever seen one of the wrong turns. I've never seen any of them.
But then you read up on them and then it was, you know, it's like, yeah. You know, by the time you
hit four, they're like, why are they bothering anymore? You know, I know my mom oddly loved wrong turn.
I've never seen it. You know, and look, I'm a huge nightmare in Elm Street fan. I cannot vouch for
every nightmare in Elm Street film. But franchise speaking, phantasm is a franchise that I would,
and I'm spelling franchise. By the way, the pH. Sure. Fanchise. No, France, no,
France, like phantasm franchise, fanchise. I'm spelling it. Why don't you do that? Because I want to,
all right. Then we can hear the joke as opposed to having to visualize what it would look like on paper.
The joke is, is that I was explaining how in my head I was spelling it. That was the joke. Okay. The,
yeah. It's one of the few you, you can set, you're really set your drink on from start to finish.
It's, it has very, very few weak spots in my opinion. And then also, who doesn't love Reggie?
I mean, Jesus Christ. Guys awesome. I mean, it's got, it's got a real linchian quality to the thing,
you know, like the, the, when they're in sort of the alternate world, it really feels like what you
later see in Twin Peaks, kind of that weird room with a checkerboard floor and stuff. I would
imagine Linch was not influenced by it, but it does a really good job of capturing that dream state,
that sort of creeping dread, which was the name of the course I took in college.
Oh, really about what? Creeping dread was a class we read on writing, the Stephen King book,
but we all had to write uncanny stories like, and that sounds awesome. Short, short horror. And I
wrote a really great one. I wish I could find it because I, I think I could turn it into something.
But, um, yeah, it was all about that, that feeling, the uncanny, the creeping dread that you get when
you make, uh, when you watch a horror movie or read a horror book, strange class, but a really interesting
custom class. Uh, and JJ Abrams, to answer your question, yes, is a huge,
Phantasm fan, which is why the character is a, what's that?
PHAN fan. Yes. Yeah. Yeah. Just doing your own thing. Well, I would say Fran.
He's a huge fan. He, uh, he, uh, that is why the character kept in Phasma exists in Star Wars,
in the new Star Wars movies that he's, okay. Okay. And that's why she's silver. Yeah. That's not
what, that's not why the character exists. He created the character and then they named her Captain
Phasma. Yeah. Because it was based on Phantasm and she was silver and it made him, it reminded him of
the silver ball. Apparently Angus Scrim had a sizable role in, uh, Alias, which was JJ Abrams show
with Jennifer Garner, which I watched a couple seasons of and loved. But, uh, yeah, he's a big fan.
Well, and if for nothing else, that's, to me, that's the reason to see five more than anything,
is it's, it's, it's, I believe Scrim's last performance. Yeah. And it's really cool that they got him
in. Yeah. Before he passed to do this final installation and, and, and officially end the franchise.
I thought that was very cool. And apparently it, uh, barely made an R rating, which is crazy because
nothing here is particularly Dory or disturbing. But apparently it barely made the cut.
Um, I have to go to the bathroom, Joe, I want you to wrap this up. Whoever you see fit.
All right. I'm on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick Walsh and the cool kids is on Friday nights
on Fox as well as Hulu. Joe DeRosa comedy on Instagram. Uh, check out my cooking videos.
I'm not cooking, but my sandwich making videos, Hogi's heroes on my Facebook page.
Joe DeRosa comedian on Facebook. They are there. There's two there now more coming very soon.
Um, I'll be in Vegas and, and, and, and March bonkers comedy club. I will be in, um,
uh, Austin, Texas again in April for the Moon Tower festival. I'll also be in, I think manyapolis
at bonkers for one night at a casino. Uh, and I should be in Pennsylvania as well. And in
April, uh, Valley Forge Casino, uh, one night, one show and then doing a couple of other things
around that in the area. So I hope to see you there for and hell.