Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer, or check out
our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spend on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia only, games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as non -mustrable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided in applicable terms.
Reward subject to expiry.
Gamling problem called 1 -800 -Gamber.
The football season is full of guarantees.
And here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee,
every single game day from now until October.
If your football bet loses, go learn up to $100 back in fancash.
If you bet on football with fanatics,
you're either winning or winning money back in fancash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Monthly 21 -plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberer, offer not available in all states
terms apply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
Hello, everybody. Welcome to We'll see you in hell the podcast brought to you by the
Fangoria Podcast Network, the newly formed Fangoria Podcast Network for more information
about this network, including other programs and how to follow our show and find all the
past episodes of our show and the other shows because there's a bunch of shows, just go
visit Fangoria .com. Please, to my left, Patty Walsh and full beautiful stereo. Hey guys,
It's good to see again. We haven't done this in a very long time, Joe. I know we just released one a couple weeks back
But it's probably been a good month since you and I have
Hoisted the old mics to our lips. I'll tell you it's been hard to stay away with this riveting energy you bring to the table shut the fuck up
Joe and I were in a furious text battle on the way over here
I write he writes when are you gonna be here? I'm thinking about jumping in the shower
Three minutes before I'm supposed to arrive
Like you couldn't think of this early times you're late. Not tonight, baby. I well that and so I go on
I'm rolling down sunset and the corrects it to subset
Like the spelled auto correct. Yeah, Joe was what the fuck is subset?
That's not a street name. I was joking and while he does it
He says fuck you and it comes out fuck your and a boy
I might dig became so hard because while he's chewing me out for an auto correct
there. He hits me back with one of his own. And then folks, he pretended he tried to do it.
I know. I did try to pass it off that I was doing a bit. But I was joking about you two.
Well, baby. You know, I'm not I'm not sharp enough to make a joke that I did. I knew you weren't
smart enough or funny enough. And I jumped all over it. So then at eight o 'clock sharp, I pull up.
I go, you know, he goes, come on in. I go, your dog's going to go nuts. He goes nuts even when Joe
Well, you're leaving it. How were you a writer for television? The details you're leaving out. What am I losing come on in?
I was in disposed and I said just let yourself in and then you said I left out. He's in the shower. Yeah, I didn't want to get you to a rouse
Well, look the reason I'm giving you shit
Probably and it's got to do with our topic for today's law. Yeah
It's a God damn fucking burden and I've said it before and I'll say it again.
Whenever you're coming over to do this, I'm never looking forward to it.
I'm not excited about it.
I'm excited to see you.
I'm excited to see people for some reason want to hear us talk to one another but I mean
something about the phrase have to do.
We have to do a pocket because we do.
got to meet a deadline, whatever else.
When I hear that have to do, I shut down so hard.
And it's the loosest deadline.
I mean, the folks at Fayloria, as you imagine, sir.
They're not corporate.
No, they're not corporate, you know, tyrant.
So, you know, this is a very pretty open -minded
laid -back crew we got over there.
I've never been to the Fangoria offices, but I'd imagine,
you know, there's a lot of like Halloween party style cobwebs,
A lot of fixed spiders maybe a big bubbling cauldron fruit punch. I always pictured a sort of a peely herman style
Yeah decorative thing
There's maybe a talking frightening chair and a bowl of grapes that they tell you as eyeballs. Yeah, and then
Stuff dummy in the corner with one of those rubber Halloween masks on it when you walk by it goes
You know what I mean?
Did a Halloween party when I was a kid and I turned my entire basement into a haunted house. It was incredible
Yeah, and at the end my mom we hit in our giant freezer and she popped up like a living corpse out of this freezer
We cleared all the chicken fingers and shit out of it
It was truly horrifying like all my friends were like you don't expect that it was a lot of like
Oh, here's brains and it was spaghetti and like, you know kids are 10 like you gross
And then at the end when my mom comes flying out of this fucking yeah one of those floor freezer
Yeah with that with the the open it from the top boy people went fucking nuts now
you turned the freezer off before she got in there I assume. No she passed away. She was
frostbite. That was what would scare them. I opened it like mom and then they to like
be face to face with a corpse. This is a dark joke. This is it. My mom is alive and
well and I love her very much, folks. I'll tell you another thing that annoys me about
this podcast. Look at our levels. Now right now we're staring at a computer screen that shows
our levels as we record. Look how much lower than me you are. Every week I read justice.
So I have to, so I don't have to adjust it again and then every week we do this and then it's
you're too low again. I don't understand what is happening. Well, maybe it's that I talk normally
and you scream like a damn banchie. Well, Pat, I'm not a happy man. No, I know. And it's been stated on
here before and I'll say it again. Yeah, I'm not a happy man. We live in a cesspool. We're talking
Today folks about the podcast if you've been away for a few weeks has a new format and it's about
Sin each week's a different sin. It's a loose framework for us to discuss, you know, what's going on in our lives movies
Etc. This week's about sloth easily the most horrifying to me in the film seven
Speaking of things jolting awake that you thought were dead
That really fucked me up. That would probably the scariest scene I've ever seen in a movie. I'll tell you what my experience was with that scene
I my friend Jerry had seen the movie before I did and he was with me when I saw it the first time and the entire
Movie leading up to that he kept like hauntingly
Like warning me out of his own tension because he didn't want to see the scene again
Yeah, how bad this sloth scene was gonna be and I will tell you it delivered on all counts since saying you almost can't set it up too much
I saw it a buddy of mine and I
We bought a ticket for some PG movie and then snuck into seven and I had not seen many
R -rated movies at this time.
I was, I think I was like 14 or something and that scene fucked me up in a really severe
way.
Then later on my dad decided, as I was getting older to start letting me see the occasional
R -rated movie, seven he thought was fine.
There couldn't be any nudity in seven, cut to a ten minute sequence of a guy talking
about being forced to fuck a woman with a knife, but you didn't see it as the point.
Right. Which was probably better to him than me seeing and people for Christ's sake.
Well, that's how all those parents thought back then. But as that scene's coming up,
I'm telling myself, okay, you can't let on to, I can't let on to my dad that I know this scene
is coming. I can't, I have to be just as scared this time out. You know, I was thinking I was going to
have to make myself jump to prove that I hadn't seen it in my life. That would look believable.
Yeah, you know, of course just watching the scene a second time made me shit my pants all over it
I didn't have to act. Yeah, it's that's a rough one speaking of shit. Yeah, that's why I had to get in the shower
Oh Joe
I was getting ready to do the pot here. I sent up the mics everything and I had a feeling come over me, man
I'll tell you I could a I could have fertilized the serengeti with what I did in that toilet
For years, baby
I don't love this
years. It was a real mess in there and I had to get a shower so I apologize.
So, all right. I apologize. What happens if you do that at work? I've never
like taken a show where I was like I need to get a get a shower. What are
people doing? I mean I could have gotten by without a shower but I felt better
getting a shower. We're gonna go out on the town after this tonight as we often do
after our cast. Sure, you got to celebrate another slam dunk. Yeah and I just said I
want to be fresh. I want to be fresh for the ladies that, you know, we're talking about
going to that salsa club that we that just opened. Yeah. Right. I got brought my best
cummerbomb. Now, before we get into sloth, I know we're kind of circling it. Well, actually,
this relates to sloth. One of the things you and I both do is two lazy men is watch a lot
of movies. Yeah, because it doesn't take a lot of effort. It doesn't take a lot of activity.
kind of lay there you watch. I mentioned Pee Wee Herman earlier. I got to talk
about this. I mean, I think it was supposed to be a movie. That new Pee Wee thing
is holy shit. Well, and I respect Paul Rubens. I'm not shitting on the guy. I
respect the people involved with the film. But I mean, my god almighty. I couldn't.
It was one of the most not funny things I've seen a long time. And they added this
whole dark. Why do they make pee? We sort of like sinister all of a sudden and like really selfish
and shitty and yeah there's that running gag to the movie where it goes. I'm gonna let you let
me go now like where he's like really mean to everybody and I'm like what is this and then he kind
of look like looks like he wants to fuck the guy from magic mic a little bit through the whole thing
which that's fine but like it's just it's like all these you throw me too many pee we curveballs right
Now I don't know what to what I don't understand what the it was a lot. I love that wink where
Manginella's like well, have you seen this this have you seen magic mic and I guess you think so wouldn't you
I thought that was funny, but I'm like so you're basically hinting now that Peewee is
Closeted gay man or something which was never really in there before well cuz it's he was a child
I guess the old stage show was more adult. I don't want Peewee being sexual in any way. Yeah at all agreed
Okay, it bothered me on the TV show when, when Miss, Miss Elaine and Miss Avan was holding
the dumbbell and she fell down with it and it, the bar bent to the shape of her tits.
Sure.
I didn't like that.
Right.
Even as a corny kid.
I didn't like that.
Well, it's a big extension of this.
It's a big extension of this.
I think it's supposed to be the takeaway.
Well, in the first movie that that hot piece of
Prejuto, Dottie is trying to bone him.
And he's like, is like making a mockery ever
for being in romantically interesting.
And it was hilarious.
Suddenly in this one, they got that whole thing
where he's making Joe Montana.
What the fuck's the guy saying?
And Janella.
He's making him a milkshake.
I mean, is that enough of a metaphor for you?
Yeah.
I gotta pump the milk.
He's literally like pumping a vanilla.
Yeah, into the. Come on man. Well, look, I saw it probably six months ago. I have not seen
the final new version. That's what you see it. I saw it with our friend Pete and
Appetale and his wife. So you saw this with Pete Holmes. Yeah, our friend, John Appetale
who produced the film, right, who Pete is also working with as a mind. And, and you're writing
on that show now. Well you this has been a long having to pretend you liked something hasn't it?
So you've really trapped me but when I saw it as I said then I don't know what changes they made
but I was like for I thought the opening scene with the alien was hilarious. I love the alien's voice
and then throughout yeah it was no big adventure I thought it was on a par with like a big top
peewee. It was worse than big top peewee which was astounding to me. I saw it no music and was told
the music would help out greatly and I also here's a fun fact for you when I saw it Paul Rubens
came out and talks and he's about 60 and you know he looked like a fit vital 60 years old but he
had a in the film every scene he had a clamp attached to the back of his neck pulling his entire face
skin back and he goes like you're gonna see this weird clamp in my neck were digitally removing it
in post. So every scene when I'm trying to watch and enjoy this movie, his face is being
held back with a metal clamp. So it was very jarring and difficult to enjoy. And I have
not seen the final product. But I'll tell you, I think you saw a better version. I mean,
I would have appreciated a clamp or something, something just something to keep me interested
to watch the whole thing. I tried, man. I tried several times and I picked up where I left
off. And I couldn't get through it, man. It's, it's not. He's also, I hate to say this.
He's not nailing the Pee Wee character. It's not dare. Like, it's, it sounds too much like he's
just talking in this Paul Rubin's voice. There's not enough of the like, well, he's 60. Well,
but there's not enough of that rollercoaster in the pitch. And look, Martin Short is 60. Yeah,
that's true. You see him do Jimmy Glick. It's fucking up and down the, the octave, you know?
Like, yeah, but and I I watched it wanting to love and I also worked on
Pete show before you did.
Yeah, I got to work with Mr.
Abitale, who was was very nice and we had a nice time and I was excited to see it.
I want it to really like this, but I also feel like he's the kind of guy where you
could say like, nah, I didn't like that and he wouldn't be like offended by it.
Yeah.
I think so.
I mean, I don't feel weird.
I win it.
He was big adventures that is a top 20 for me.
I've seen it a thousand times when I was a kid.
and I saw a real temp version.
I'm not even prepared to comment on it,
but I well played, Petty, well played.
This guy knows how to work this town.
Not shitting on the talents of anybody involved.
I just did not care for the film.
And in fact, they did do a sexting in Big Top.
He weaned that bothered me too.
When he bangs that Italian chick from hot shots
and rain, I remember a make out scene, do they fuck?
They make out and then it cuts to a montage
of a train going through a tunnel and a volcano exploding, which they also didn't
top secret in many other movies. I mean, get that out of my Peewee movie. I do agree
with that. It's too much. But the old stage show was really racy as well. Maybe they're
trying to get back to that. It was like wink to the camera racy. It wasn't, we're going
to show a volcano exploding to represent jizz. Valid point. A man child's jizz, which by
By the way, if you met Pee, we heard him in real life, you'd be like, this man has
a, it would be illegal to fuck him.
He would have, you would be a retarded man, you know, you would have a mental condition
of some kind, you know, so you couldn't bang the guy.
If you were, you know, so inclined, well, unless you were, I'm afraid of the more explain
this.
I'm going to get myself in trouble.
But you know what I mean?
I think it's illegal to have sex with a retarded person is what we're trying to get
at.
Yeah.
it is although I shared the story today at work to great acclaim and I'll
share it now it's very brief. When I was in high school I worked the special
Olympics just for the just for the chicks to compete I worked with the special
Olympics and I was assigned a very sweet young girl with Down syndrome and she's
in a sweat suit and she's competing all the events and I'm talking to my buddy
Ryan and all of a sudden he steps back and he goes pat pat pat pat like what I
look down this girl who was probably 12 years old 13 has pulled down both her
pants and underpants revealing a large black bush and is rubbing it. She
I'm probably a senior in high school,
and this girl was 13 or so.
Okay, so you're just young enough
that you can go with it.
I threw my hands in the air.
I waved them around like I did care.
I threw my hands in the air and I'm like,
I go help, help, help, help,
and I'm screaming for any adult and I go, Ryan,
go get somebody, please go get somebody.
So he's looking around and I was so terrified
because I'm like if the wrong person looks over here
and thinks I had anything to do with this, I'm fucked.
And this woman comes over and kind of pulls the girl off me and pulls her pants up.
And I'm like, you have to understand I was talking to my friend, I'm my stuttering and stammering.
And she goes, they're very sexual.
It's okay, they're very sexual.
But I was deeply traumatized.
And I had sort of repressed the memory till yesterday at work and opportunity arose to tell this tale.
right yeah well this is what your response should have been when she went it's
okay you should have went for her baby yeah that should have been your response
I related now I'm hesitant to even bring up that man be Superman do we do that
in another podcast because I feel like you probably want to scream about those for
20 minutes I mean I've said all I needed to say on Twitter it's a fantastic movie
it's the best Batman ever it's the it's it's it's Gene Hackman level Lex
Luther. Uh, I'm just gonna sit back. It's an interesting and it's an interesting
interpretation of Superman, which is front pulled straight from the comics, saying
with Batman. Um, and it was a fine piece of work. I really enjoyed the movie. I thoroughly
enjoyed it. It certainly does not deserve a 29 % on Rotten Tomatoes. No, it deserves a 9%.
Oh, stop it. There was no humor. There was no humor in the other Batman movies. There was
There's no fun in the other Batman movies.
I don't need humor in my movies.
There's a great deal of humor and fun in Batman and Batman returns.
There's way too much in the other two shoe mackerel.
There's no humor in Batman one.
I think there's plenty.
Nicholson is definitely bringing humor.
Let's talk to Nolan ones, which were critically acclaimed.
Now, those did not have humor, but I thought they were, I mean, the dark night everyone loves
the, I don't know why you wouldn't love.
I love the dark night.
I love the no entriology.
But for people to say this wasn't as good and far worse because it didn't have humor and it wasn't fun. I'm saying it's a dark film
It's called a grown -up comic book movie, but I also thought it wasn't exciting or cool to look at
Oh, I thought it was beautifully sure. I didn't care from one minute to the next what happened
It was a frame -by -frame graphic novel. It was beautiful. There was there were there were panels
recreated right out of the Dark Knight Returns. We'll say I'd never read that.
There were, I love that it was super death a superman. I love that it was Batman
Returns, two of my favorite comics of all time, or Dark Knight Returns to my
favorite comics of all time. I love the Doomsday was in it. Lex Luthor, it was a
brilliant, brilliant, especially with the, with the emergence of Martin
Skreli and those types of guys. It was a brilliant interpretation.
I thought he was fantastic and it made total sense. Of course, that's what that guy would
be now. He'd be an upstart guy. And even down to the fact, this is a well written that
part was even down to the fact when they talk about Lex the name Lex Corp and they go, well,
it's nice to meet the Lex in front of the Corp and he goes, oh, no, no, no, my father named
the company. That's his Lex in front of the Corp. It's, that is such a brilliant piece
of writing because of course if that guy started the company, young Lex Luthor, it'd be called
like Shbibo or something like, you know what I mean?
Some modern thing and it's like, well, how do we still keep it named Lex Corp?
But make him a sort of Facebook guy.
Oh, well, we'll say his dad named the company and his dad started and he inherited it and
he's now this like, he's now this like cutting edge technological tech savvy fucking, you know,
what's his face?
The few the very few people I've talked to that thought the movie was okay because I haven't heard anyone
But you think it was better than okay. I thought it was brilliant. I'm not exaggerating
Everyone including those people despised Eisenberg. Oh, well then everybody must be right. I I
Mean if everyone thinks something it doesn't necessarily mean it's right
But it means there might be on to something you're the only person. I know that didn't like the witch and you refused to see the general
perspective on that. Didn't love the witch and I know lots of people who were
very bored by the way. You told me you I went with you told me you didn't like
it. You use those words. Yeah you know it I liked the tone and I liked what it
was kind of going for. I liked it way more than the guy I went with and I know
many people who did you thought ten Cloverfield Lane was better than the
witch which if for anybody listening for anybody listening now you know what I'm
dealing with over here but Joe you're preaching to people who vehemently
disagree with you. No, don't like Batman versus Superman. I guarantee you the
Fanguari audience does not disagree with me on the witch. And perhaps the way I
be willing to bet there are a hell of a lot more open -minded about Batman versus
Superman than you are.
All right, but what the hell do you know about comic? Are you a comic book guy? No, not at all. Well, that's why you didn't it was a movie for comic book
but this is a world full of huge comic book fans and guess what every single huge
kind of a fan I know said it was phenomenal every single one I find that very hard to believe
every single one. Are you in that? I love Batman versus Superman chat room with the exception
of one Andy Levy from Fox News is red. I know Andy Levy. And when I talk to Andy on the phone
about it, I could slowly hear him coming around and going, okay, why didn't think about it like
that. But they had elements of flashpoint paradox in there. Dude, it was fucking amazing.
I don't know what that means. And that's why you didn't like it. All I can say is that
I was excruciatingly bored from the first minute to the last. And that's all I have to
say because that's my opinion of the movie. That's fine. If I'm bored, I can't change it.
That's fine. I started the dose during the fight. The villain was a large turd that couldn't
speak other than Eisenberg. And they're all just kind of throwing each other into things.
Doomsday is made from Kryptonian DNA.
I'm talking as far as when I'm looking at the screen, I'm seeing a third throw around
two guys.
I don't because you don't get it because it starts as a sort of amorphous thing.
And then slowly as he powers up, his bones start popping out and he becomes the Doomsday
from the comic books.
There was it was great.
I couldn't.
I love the sequence.
And he flash.
I love the little Aquaman thing.
I love the Wonder Woman stuff.
I thought it was phenomenal.
Are we getting whole like a whole movie with that that dude as Aquaman and that dude is the flash these are all going to happen the flash
What happened after Justice League Aquaman and Wonder Woman and the solo Batman movie are coming I believe after Suicide Squad when I think of the
60 interesting
$10 million movies that I'm not going to see because of all this horse shit coming out it makes me so depressed I
Don't want to get out of bed if I think about it too much
There's back to our theme when I think about the three hundred one million dollar interesting indie movies that I'm missing
To watch this pile of garbage
Bird throw two people I don't care about around I love by the way. I love this you were bored by it
This guy was glued to the screen ten clover filled lane. It's three people playing cards for 90 minutes
You like ten clover filled like I'm not saying I didn't like it
But I'm just saying like you want to talk about like nothing's happening all I can do is say what I liked
And what I didn't like and then also by the way, we're going to be spoiling these films right now by the way also
You want to talk about you get to the end of the goddamn movie. It's like. Oh, it's exactly what it was supposed to be the whole time
We already talked about 10 John Goat Goodman's evil and and it's aliens. It's it's literally exactly what there's no twist
We already talked about this. We shouldn't go back to it. We're on Batman versus Superman, but I
I thought it was insanely boring. I don't know why every movie has to be 240. I can't wait for the 3 -hour r -rated blu -ray. I'm buying it the day it comes out.
You're watching that all alone.
I don't need you in my life.
Nor why?
I will not be there.
Good.
I wish I was alone now.
As do I, Joe.
Now I'm certain to think maybe the podcast direction we should go and maybe it's not about sin.
and maybe it's us doing like a Cisco and Ebert movie debate.
That's what it always was.
Maybe we need to get back to that.
And every week.
You can't change the format every three weeks.
Do whatever the fuck we want.
It's free.
It is free.
It's free and we don't make it.
We don't make it to time.
And it's free.
We're talking about coming over here, like Joe asked me
to do this podcast.
I was like, yeah, sure.
Then I'm like, why am I doing this?
But it is fun and I like to see the feedback.
I think this is the birth of the new format.
I you know, it's nice to get yelled at by Joe on a microphone as opposed to just face to face. I think this is the birth of a new format
It's we'll see you in hell
But you don't see all the movies like I've seen a lot of movies in the last two weeks. Can I finish my thought maybe before you say
How about I finish my thought
How about I finish my thought Joe if I let you finish your thought this podcast would be me nodding silently while you scream
Oh
Your thought is always in progress
Sometimes I gotta go
Was that I have something to say now. That's are you doing dice clays woman voice when are we gonna watch that dice show?
That's something we can talk about on the podcast. I heard the Adrian Brody episode is a grand slam
Well, I certainly hate Adrian Brody, but I'm I'm excited to see the episode is dice teaching him to how to be a man an
Adrian Boot Brody starts just impersonating Dice and apparently his Dice impression is like off the fucking chain
But can I finish about the podcast finish
Every week we discuss a film or films that fall under the Fangoria umbrella
Doesn't have to necessarily be horror. It could be sci -fi. It could be fantasy. Okay. Yeah
that we agree or disagree on. And we have a Cisco and
Ebert kind of debate about them.
I think that's fine. We've had this format for three weeks.
Yeah. Well, maybe we get through the sins, the seven sins.
We'll get through the seven sins and then we'll switch season three.
For all intents and purposes will be that. Okay.
Because I believe this is now season two of the podcast. That's how I look at it.
all right i've seen a lot of movies since last we talked but i don't think you've
seen any of them so that's why this is fine but my point is i can go to the shelf
over here and i could say patty the vanishing let's go
oh wait you want to watch old movies i'm not saying watch i'm saying discuss
no but i mean you want to discuss old movies and not movies in the theater
because that's not cisco neighborhood all well we can do both doesn't matter
okay why don't we go see a movie or two together each we can talk oh yeah
Yeah, because this isn't a burden enough.
Wouldn't it be rough to see a movie with a friend?
Listen, remember when we were killing two birds with one stone
and watching the movie while doing the podcast?
That was too much.
Now you want to see a movie separately,
then do a podcast about it.
I remember.
We do go to the movies at least once a month.
My point is, is we could just, you know,
here's a movie I'd love to discuss.
We're not getting into it right now, but in the future,
I want to talk about Blade Runner. The movie bores me to piss. I can't get through the fucking thing
I will I completely agrees that'll be a boring episode it wouldn't be a boring episode
Yeah, I would love for us to talk about why we don't like it and I've tried okay
Here's the cut without the Harrison Ford narration. Here's the cut with the narrator
Here's the cut without the unicorn. Here's the cut with no unicorn two unicorns. No Darryl Hannah
Four Daryl Hannes. They have 8 ,000 cuts of this movie and none of them are good
I can't eat the let's save it all right because the movie makes no sense and I've great arguments for that
I think all right
I was really going off patent
I went on a apartment crawl last Saturday where many of our friends had a specialty drink at their apartment
So then you go apartment to apartment have a couple drinks go to the next place. Yeah, very fun
But I mean when we were in the depths of that thing and I mean it got dark people
come six p .m. we started at 12 come six p .m. we were real down in and at that point when we hit
that last bar people were like walking off on their own bumping into walls and yeah it got
real ugly and it went to about 10 p .m. it was over at some point I saw Kurt muttering to himself in
a corner yeah it was it was it was a real long haul yeah but I remember somewhere around the
seven pm are going off about Blade Runner and whoever I was doing a two did not like it.
Well, I thought that was here on the Friday night prior, but maybe you did it.
You know what?
I'm not going to lie to you, Pat.
The Friday night before the pub, the apartment crawl, I was pretty out of my fucking mind
that night too, because I got a new game.
I downloaded a game on PS4 from the network called Zombie and I was excited to put it in
play it for the first time last night and I turned it on and I
apparently put a good 35 minutes into the game. Okay. On that
Friday night that we had no recollection. You were ranting and
raving about Blade Runner that night as well. Well, then
that's what it was. Okay. You know, we ate those weed gummies
and smoked a bunch of weed and drank a ton and as a hell of a
night though, we spun all those records. I feel like I've been
working hard to bring it back to slot, which we have to do for
at least a few minutes. I've been working hard for a long,
long, long time. I usually have a long hiatus. I went from one job to another. I'm tired.
I'm mentally exhausted. And when the weekend comes, it's the freaking weekend, baby. I'm about
to have me some fun. Well, tonight's my Friday. It's Thursday right now, but I switched my Friday.
I switched my Sunday off for Friday this week because we have to shoot on Sunday with the show I'm
writing for. And so now I Friday and Saturday off of this week. Okay. So tonight's my Friday.
We're going as far as my Saturday and Saturday might be my Saturday again, even though I got to work on Sunday. Sunday might be my Saturday too. Yeah, Monday could possibly be my Saturday. Monday is my Thursday. That's a hard rule that I don't change.
But now see we are talking sloth. Sloth essentially means laziness and it's not good to be lazy.
You know in the grand scheme of things Joe you and I are not lazy man. We're just not we're hard workers
We're always working. We're always making money, but is that sloth that what I was at the opposite of sloth
I mean we work to survive. We work to fulfill our dreams, but I'll tell you something man
I mean we're gonna go out tonight. We're gonna have some drinks. We're gonna have some laughs
Maybe a little reef who the hell knows me that's not slow, but hold on a second let me finish the thought pet
You know what a podcast there has to be a give and take there is and you just gave and now I'm taking
Let me finish the sentence
My point is is we're going out for fun tonight. Yeah
If you walked
Wouldn't take much for you to convince me to not get out of this chair is my point. Oh, sure even with a fun night in front of me
But we do that's the thing. I think most people and I mean most and especially when you're talking about the entire nation at large
Are coming home from work every night at six o 'clock eating dinner and then sitting on the couch and watching television until they fall asleep at your
Every single day. I don't blame them for it. I get it
But I am going out a lot or else on the nights where I sit in and watch a movie. I used to not be this way and I miss it
sincerely i work a ton i'm doing what i love but if i sit for five minutes now and i think it's
the phones fucked up or fucking attention span sure i'm sitting there going shouldn't i be writing
something shouldn't i be doing something and i think that keeps me from being slawful because i
can't enjoy being slawful like i used to i used to run six movies on a Friday night come home at five
And watch all six I miss that six movies. Yeah, so you'd go you'd go six p .m. to six a .m.
Yeah, almost every Friday night by yourself. I
Watch usually three with my dad on a Friday and maybe even a Saturday night. It's when you're a kid
You mean when I'm a kid and not always six, you know for whatever, but that was all I did. It's all I look forward to
And I was so happy and so caught up in the movie and now my brain is going every which way
And I'm not truly relaxing or being present or in the moment or whatever you want to call it
I'll tell you one thing I do like about working a day job is that 9 .30 9 .45 hits and I'm
I'm gearing up for bed. Oh sure. I'm under the covers by 10 .15
I'm reading comic books to about 11 my eyes are closing because I'm tired from reading and I'm out and it's a really nice night's sleep
It's good. It's kind of what one is supposed to do, I think. And that's why I think I rebel against it
Like I always sort of force myself to stay up till one. Well, you know, we've always referred to you in Hollywood
Pat is the Zach De La Rocha. Oh, absolutely. Of the TV writing world. Yeah, I am. I am.
That's what was said to me when I first moved here to somebody said, you know, Patty Walsh. I said, no, I don't they said
They said if you ever want to meet the Iggy pop of sitcoms
I pay a guy to walk around behind me with the guitar very quietly going
Yeah, because at any moment when I might strike. What was that word any meowing up?
I sort of got to think you were doing a bit for a second. I was moment with a meow and I wasn't doing a bit
I just came out wrong. Yeah, but I missed a joke is what I'm trying to say
Oh, by the way, I got to died by a rayer today. I
Don't know any of those warriors that dating
Social app for like people in the biz you got denied
They took two weeks to get back to me with they know you have a comedy central special coming out
I have a comedy central special coming out. I've got two behind me. I'm the vet on better call saw
Yeah, I've written for multiple television shows. I've been on Louie. I've been on board did that. What the fuck do you got to do to get on Ray?
Why would they deny that they give you a read? They said listen to how fucking snotty this is you ready for this
Tell people what ray is cuz I barely know it's a dating social app for people in the entertainment and entertainment in shrika and
Not that I am
In any way
Famous, but you feel a little stupid the grand scheme of things you are in the grand scheme of America
But but you feel pretty stupid going on to like an okay -cupid yeah
and possibly running into somebody saying,
oh, I saw you at that, you're, I like your com,
you just feel kind of dumb.
So this ray of thing is supposed to be like,
look, man, you work putting your face out there
in any way, this is for you.
But all my friends are on it.
I'm like, okay, I'm gonna join it.
I join it, they say we're reviewing your application,
we get many applicants, be patient, we'll get back to you.
What do you have to put on this application?
Your credit?
It's just your bullshit, yeah.
No, no. You just write your info, whatever. Then they check like your Instagram or something.
So anyway, weeks go by, weeks. I'm not getting any word. I'm like, I don't know.
I open the app today. It says, our board has carefully
reviewed your application. Our answer is here. And there's a button that you have to press.
Oh, no.
Yeah. And then you press it and it says, you've been put on our waiting list after careful
consideration and it's like that could just mean they have too many people and
they're trying to seem all exclusive and shit it's like when you go to a restaurant
and you're like yeah I got a table for two and there's no one there and they're
like let me look let me see if we have any space it's to make
themselves seem cool it's well I know that's what it is yeah and fuck you well it's
not necessarily a no is what I'm saying but it's fuck you I bet if right
our gasoline applies he gets a straight course our answer is here that's
Pretty fucked up.
You fucking eat me, Ray.
Why would you want to do that?
You don't.
Now I don't wanna do it now.
Is that such a big deal?
You go out on an OKCupid date
and they're like, I think that's all your stand -up special.
Who cares?
It's an interesting job.
My friend, who I texted, I said, got shut down, Ray.
She said, honestly, it's a bunch of models.
You don't have good social skills.
So that makes me feel better.
Yeah.
And it does have a moderately vibe,
like just the layout of the app and everything.
right, you know, it's a lot of fluorescent colors. I think our friend Morgan Murphy is on
Raya. Everybody's on it. She's in your same boat. You're both comedians. You're both semi -known.
Everybody's on it. All right. I can't get on the fucking thing. Yeah. I got friends with no
specials on it. It's, they put a lot of weight on Instagram. They say we're followers. They say like,
We this is for people who live their lives and express themselves to Instagram. That's one of the things that says you want to be in that world
No, I just want to be I just wanted to see if it was like a good dating app
That's it. I just wanted to see. Oh, maybe I'll meet some like fun people in the business
Whatever, maybe you'll meet Rebecca de Mournay like you've been trying to will into it existence
Yeah, that's what I that's what I was thinking
I had my sights set on Rebecca to D
Let that hand rock you know cradle any McDonald lives on my street. I know so come say hello
And she power walks around the neighborhood. She's divorced. I'm praying for the day Marystein virgin and Teddy D split up
Don't have don't say that. I love the couple. I think they're wonderful. She's single
Why would you try to break up Hollywood? We wouldn't try to break them up
But I'll tell you if that Mary if that Mary Steeze ever goes solo. I mean
She is she is dynamite
You have the exact same taste of women as my father.
Steen Birch and Andy McDowell, that's what he loves.
The funniest thing Brent Sullivan has ever said to me, our good friend who's a very funny
comic was, he was telling me about his dad and he goes, his favorite actor is Andy McDowell
and it was one of the funniest things I've ever heard a human being say.
My dad, I may have mentioned this on this podcast before, my dad used to tell my mom when they
were married that he would leave her for Andy McDowell.
Now any any McDonald's divorced, huh? I
Believe so I've never had any particular interest center. I've told my joke about her many times. I don't think she's a strong actress
I love her voice. I like a Southern charm
But yeah, I'd take Steenberg in a thousand times over steam steam Virgin is is could be
On my list above like Marissa tome. No, I find steam Virgin to be ridiculously
ridiculously, ridiculously.
Steam Virgin to me is like another, like,
hella veer in situation, where it's like,
she's gonna be 70 and smoke and hot still.
I think Tomei is the same way.
Tomei is still getting naked.
I love Tomei.
Don't think I don't love Tomei, okay?
I wasn't like the beginning of before the Devil knows your dead.
She's getting railed by Phil Psymore Hoffman.
It's the scene that makes me never watch that movie
with my parents.
Yeah.
Cause I think my parents would really enjoy that film,
but I don't want to sit through that butt -fuck scene.
it makes you feel like it opens on. Maybe, uh, where's the tomato? I'd look my way. She also went
for George Costanza. Yes, you know, this is all fictional, you realize. Oh, really? I thought
those were documentaries. I thought the Seinfeld show was a 99 -part documentary. Yeah, I'm realizing
as we're talking about there. There's no need for sex in these movies. You don't need that. What are
you doing? You don't need that doggy style scene at the top of it before the devil knows you're dead.
I don't get anything out of it I don't get anything out of it
I get something out of the next scene where they're laying in bed going are we that old couple
and all that stuff but I don't need a movie to open on naked Phillips you more often
and fucking maybe in the butt, Marissa Tome.
I think definitely not in the butt.
I loved it.
Why?
Well, A, you got to see her naked,
but it starts your movie off like, here we go.
You know, like it gets your,
you got to get people's attention.
But it doesn't serve a purpose to me.
I think that movie is awesome.
You know what else?
I'm gonna talk.
I love that movie.
Hoffman is great.
There are a million things in that movie
that could have set that movie off.
Yeah.
That sex scene has nothing to do with anything as far as I'm concerned. You're talking like an old man
And I'll tell you what I'll tell you when I didn't feel weird seeing more as a tome naked in a movie
Was in the wrestler because she was a stripper and it made sense wrestler was so fucking great
It's great and it made sense. I'm saying that scene doesn't make any sense to me
Why didn't it could open with them in the bed? I would have still been in I hear you. That's all I'm saying open on them doing drugs together
something I you know, I just
I didn't get it. I didn't get that scene. I'm gonna do a quick a quick shuttle through the movies
I've seen because I've seen a bunch. We're talking Michael Shannon before the Devil knows your dad
I think he's an outstanding actor. I've said time and time again one of the scariest non -harm movie scenes is Michael
Shannon's scene in the Devil knows your dad and that booth. Oh, absolutely. It's a fucking horrifying. He's
Amazing in this movie called Bug that no one has seen with Ashley Judd. Yeah, like a weird fucked up mental horror movie. That is by your boy
Tracy Letz. Well, no. William Freakin. Oh, yeah, directly. Yeah. No, but I was so excited
to see Midnight Special. That guy made a movie called Take Shelter with Michael Shannon.
Some of the best acting I've ever seen in my life. Rent it, watch it, take shelter. It's
amazing. And Midnight Special, I thought it was going to be his jump to the big time, folks.
It's not a good movie didn't like it
It had a great sense of atmosphere. I was into it for like 20 minutes and then it just started just really shit in the bed
And Kirsten Duns and people show up and you're like, oh, I like this person like this person. I'm into it
I'm it and I just went nowhere and then it went to a real stupid place and it felt like a huge let down
I thought it was going to be all compared to close encounters that chance. It's not a great movie. I
Saw hello. My name is Doris
How was that? I liked it. It's okay. My coworker Miss Beth Bears was so good in it. She won't listen to this, so I'm just saying it out from the heart.
I think she should be a romantic comedy star. She's so likable. Sally Field was great, and I don't even like Sally Field.
I worked with Michael Shoewalter right after he completed it, and I would like to see it. I have to say that I think it looks fine.
The trailers don't particularly excite me, but I like Sally Field and I like Michael and I would like to see it
It's a much more interesting and kind of uncomfortable movie than you might think going in and I really enjoy like that
The trailers make it look a bit quirky. Yeah, it's it's pretty intensely uncomfortable in spots
I liked it. Oh great. Okay, uh, that makes me want to see it and our buddy Kumail isn't it in a small role
was very funny. I just saw Camille and hot tub time machine too and I enjoyed
it on the movie. I really thought it was very funny. That's some great jokes on it.
Fuck a dude was my favorite. Yeah. It's good. Rob Cordray yells fuck a dude at
the game show. I mean it was I was beside myself. I loved it. Yeah. Any movie
attempting jokes, you know, and it's my buddy I'm gonna shout. I'm gonna we're
just dropping names that no one knows left and right and I have a buddy Josh
field wrote two co wrote one the man's a super funny writer and I thought it was super
super funny with a lot of great jokes and it's got it's got like a 13 % or something
on right.
Of course it does.
But that's what I was saying about that man so these ratings are unfair.
I never trust critics with comedies.
I feel like these big bloated super hero movies are all kind of the same deal to me personally
but I know you feel different.
You know, one of my favorite comedies ever is, is the watch and it's got like an 11 %.
That's baffling to me too.
I thought that was okay at best.
How can that be one of your favorite comedies ever?
I think it's hilarious.
I think it's like a dirty ghost busters.
You got Vince Vaughn.
Ghost busters.
Yeah, Dan.
We're getting a blowjob from a ghost.
How much dirtier do you need it?
You got Vince Vaughn.
You got Jonah Hill and you got Ben Stiller.
The cast is off the damn all doing the best versions of the guys.
They do Jonah Hills doing the weird like Mama's boy like psycho.
Vince Vaughn is doing the fast -talking hustler guy and Ben
stillers doing the white bread suburban.
It's like it's it's it's awesome.
It's a great movie.
It's really really funny.
Joe, my favorite thing about you is your your passion for things.
I like right now.
I'm like, I guess I'll give the watch another try.
The watch was not good, but I'm gonna watch it again. I'm telling you because I believe in your passion. It's a hilarious movie
Alright, I'll try it again. Deserve better than it got even though I saw it pretty recently. Did we talk about Sloth at all?
We're gonna come back with Sloth when I'm done with the last movie
I saw everybody wants some the quote spiritual sequel to Days and Confused. How was it? Set in 1980. It looks like Fratt boys hanging out
It's it's like a Richard Link later movie man
It's not as good as days confused or boyhood or whatever, but it's like really fun
And I walked out with my buddy and like neither of us had been cracking up the whole time or anything
But we were like I would watch that again right now
He makes these movies that are just really fun hangs
Like all these guys are fracked guys
I wouldn't have probably liked them
But he makes everybody more interesting than they should be there's beautiful
Funny women in it everybody and it's gonna be a star and
I recommend it
I thought it was a great movie no plot at all nothing
Nothing nothing there's not even like a big game. They're trying to get to like you know days and infuse they pretend
There's a plot they wouldn't they got to sign that petition. Sure. There is nothing in this movie. Sure and I loved it
That's why I feel like that you know these people agonizing over story
Comedy it's not always important some of course some densely plotted comedies are fantastic
I like a comedy where you're just hanging out with funny people and they won't make those movies unless you're coming off
Like a best picture nomination. That's the only way you can get make it
He was probably like they can do whatever you want and he's like, yeah, I want to do this script about
People hanging out the only way you can get something like that made it's a shame. Yeah, I know I know it's
He wanted to make a movie about Sloth
Sloth exactly
So Jackie Brown's, you know, a perfect hangout movie and then when the caper starts as fun as an exciting as it is
You're kind of like I kind of missed that first hour where you're like getting high with Bridget fondant and a bikini tub
You know, brown has
Some tremendous lines in it. It's one of my favorite movies ever
Some tremendous lines in it. I love the film when he talks Bridget fondant in the kitchen
She's like, you know, basically says you want and then he goes that hit the spot. Yeah, it's great
James Gray. And then the one of the best acting choices I've literally ever seen in my life
is in that movie with when Samuel Jackson is talking to Robert Forster to get the bail bond or
whenever and Robert Forster he gives he goes what's your address and he gives it to him and then he
goes is that an apartment or a house and Simmons Johnson goes that's a house he's proud of it yeah the
pride in the way he says it because he's got so much to prove yeah as this criminal
And then Jackie Brown gets asked the same question at some point and she's just very like it's an apartment like she doesn't care
Yeah, you know, so many things like that in that movie and I it's on
Cinemax or whatever
Every night essentially and I wind up watching 45 minutes of it like everyone. Yeah, I get very excited every time
I'm leaving LAX and I walk through that colored wall that she runs past at the one point
I love when that seemed between
I mean, well, Pam Greer's incredible,
force was incredible.
And then you'd think they would be huge stars off it,
but no, they were just perfectly cast.
And you don't really wanna see him in other things,
necessarily.
Well, Pam, she had certainly had a research
after that.
And of course she had not as much of one,
but did have one.
But when they're sitting at the breakfast table
and they talk for like 10 minutes,
and they're talking about getting older
and he's talking about,
you know, my hair started falling out.
You know, I did something.
I went and got plugs.
That's like a whole conversation that has nothing
into with the plot, but it tells you everything about them. And then she's talking about getting
old. She's like, I, you know, my ass is getting big. And he goes, done wrong with that. Yeah.
And that's before big asses were in. And he's like wrong with that huge laugh when I saw
them in the theater in Missouri. I got a huge laugh. Yeah. And but the great, the great thing
is that he doesn't say it in a purvy or flirty way. It's the perfect delivery. He says it
like a dad would like yeah nothing wrong with that yeah yeah you know when they kiss at the end
before she leaves I watched it recently with Heather my girlfriend and both of us were like
misting up like I and I had never never had that reaction in the movie before it's a beautiful
feeling like you desperately want them to be together and it's not even really a romance till that last
second. Forster has also another great, he's great through the whole movie, but his other
line delivery that's really fantastic is when they're in the car at the end. He's in
the car with with Sam Jackson at the end. And Sam Jackson goes, you like the blue notes,
whatever I forget what band it is. Yeah. And uh, Robert Forster just goes, they're pretty good.
Delphonics or Delphonics, yeah. When I, uh, I think Samuel Jackson was on Letterman and Letterman,
and you could always tell when Letterman loved
or didn't like a movie.
He didn't like a movie either,
wouldn't talk about it or he'd blatantly make fun of it.
And he's, he will only,
he's talking about Jackie Brown
to the extent where Samuel Jackson's almost like,
can we talk about something else?
But he loves, he's talking about,
you know, Letterman loves Michael Keaton,
he's going on and on about it.
Oh, yeah, Keaton, I forgot.
Yeah, playing the same role as that assigned.
Yeah, but he's talking, and he goes,
he goes, they sent me a clip over Letterman's talking,
he goes, I don't want to show that clip.
Every scene in the movie is great,
But I want to show my favorite scene. So I requested that they send over a different clip
And here it is and they show this clip and it's that clip where
Samuel Jackson sent in the guy out to his car and he goes
All you got to do is push this button. You got to hear a little
And the door is open and he goes don't fuck with my levels now. You can play the stereo
But don't fuck with my levels. Yeah, I got him just where I like them
They cut back and letterman is like clapping and like laughing hysterically like you could tell that he was just so passionate about the movie
Well, I also have the scene between Chris Tucker and Samuel Jackson, the scene where they're
standing over the open trunk. I believe it's fully improved. I mean, it's like they're just,
it's so natural. Chris Tucker, what a waste, man. He's got to come back.
He is. I liked his Netflix special that just came out. Is it good? I didn't watch it. Okay,
I'll watch it. He curses again. Thank God. He got rid of that hole. Like, I'm not going to curse
thing. Right. It was funny. Yeah. It was funny. Uh, well, Pat, this concludes our Jackie
Brown podcast. Yeah. Speaking of what I'm about, I'm about done here. Well,
Sloth is an interesting to talk about. I mean, we checked it off. But frankly, if we talked
about laziness, that's not interesting. Well, the nice thing is as we sort of half -
faster way through this podcast and talked about whatever we felt like and didn't
convince the topic, which is what Sloth is. Yeah. In some ways, uh, you can follow us on Twitter.
I'm at Joe DeRosa Comedy doc or at at Joe DeRosa Comedy excuse me. I am at the Patrick
Walsh. You got anything to plug Joseph? Oh, what am I plug in? I am going to be well look
if you're in Scotland. I'll be in the at the Edinburgh Fringe Festival throughout all
of August of this year. I'll be in Nashville and May for the Wild West Comedy Festival.
Curated. That's still the Vince Vaughan thing? Yeah, produced by one. Awesome. Mr. Vince Vaughan in
Peter Billingsley, yep I believe. So I'll be down there in May and I'll be like I said I'll be in
Edinburgh in August and if this comes out in time I will be at the Moon Tower Comedy Festival in Austin
but I don't know when this is going to drop.
All right, and what else?
Are you plugging anything?
No, I don't really got nothing to plug.
All right, well, you've been listening to,
we'll see you in a little presentation
of the Fangoria Podcast Network,
produced by Tom Stefano, executive produced by Ken Hanley,
a Fangoria Entertainment for press opportunities,
advertising inquiries and information about,
we'll see you in hell contact.
can via his email. It's can at Fangoria .com. I know what I wanted to say. I looked on iTunes
randomly. I hadn't since like the first couple weeks of the podcast. We have tons and
tons of great reviews. And thank you all for doing that. Thank you to those who interact
with us on Twitter. We always love it. Even if we don't necessarily respond, we take your
suggestions and notes and stuff into consideration. Thank you very much. And you helped kind of
Stave off the people who were mad at Joe over as fucking all right. Well, thank you guys. We appreciate you fixing the ratings. Yeah, the ratings are up. Thank you very much. All right guys. Take care