Welcome to We'll See You In Hell, your favorite podcast when you need to get down in that
nasty groove of the genre flicks. We're here to talk to you about the horror, the sci -fi,
the fantasy, the action, sometimes the comedy, sometimes the drama. Yet today really a drama.
We're talking about Martin Scorsese's, hopefully not Swan Song, the Irishman. Hello, I'm Patrick
Walsh. I'm coming in in a very newscastery way, but Joe and I actually haven't seen each
other in about a month. It was a fine, fine how do you do at the door. We embraced Joe's right leg
went up in the back, kind of like that famous photo of the sailor in the Times Square. Yeah,
that the first time I ever saw that happen, I think was on the inch. I think that happens on
the intro to Laverne and Shirley. Yeah, that sounds right. Laverne's leg goes up when she
and I always thought like that was like as a six year old kid, that was like a fantasy. I was like,
I got to make a woman's leg do that one day. But I mean, is that a thing or it's really just that
they're that the guys taller, I think is that they're reaching, but they're also so carried
away by love. I think in The Naked Gun, they cut to their feet and both Priscilla Presley's foot
and Frank Drebben's foot go up. Yeah, that's very, very funny. That's a great joke. I just rewatched
all three of those with a friend of mine. How's three holding up? Three. Look, three is obviously
the worst of the entire run, including the TV show. But it got way more laughs in it than I
thought you have to. Here's the problem with three. You have to get past some real horseshit at the
top. Like, yeah, it basically after it does the untouchable spoof, which was good, which is funny,
it cuts to, you know, the next sequence is basically him in a supermarket is hip to be
square plays. Yes, I remember that. And it's like, I mean, it's like bad sitcom. It was like if
Mr. Mom had been adapted into a sitcom jokes. How's that sperm bank scene holding up? It's
fantastic. Very funny. The sperm bank scene is tremendous. How's Anna Nicole Smith's performance
holding up? She's you know what? She's much she's got much better comedic timing than you think she
would. Yeah, weird. Better than like a Tara Reid or something. Yeah. I remember I've seen Nick Gunn
one and two each. And I'm not exaggerating. Fifty times each. I watched them obsessively when I was
a kid up to the present. Three have maybe seen twice theater and once on video. But I still
remember the line. Yes, like a midget at a urinal. I was going to have to stay on my toes. That is
amazing. Although you can't say midget anymore. I didn't say it. I can't remember exactly how the
gag goes right now. But the the the funniest joke gag, it's a gag. It's not a joke. In Naked Gun
thirty three a third, there is a thing where he's got like a pet parakeet. Yes. And Leslie Nielsen
like, you know, kills it by accident. And then the guy comes in the room and it's like, where's my
pet parakeet? And Leslie like is making me like, I don't know, as like a feather flies out of his
face. Yeah, it's like that bit we talked about with Jared Logan, where his pants button would
knock around the room. If you'll remember, by the way, follow Jared Logan, go see him do stand up.
He's a very funny guy. It's that's the hardest. Well, that might have been the hardest I ever
laughed with you ever. It was pretty funny. And it wasn't at your expense, Jared. It really wasn't.
No, we were high. Not that you're listening to this and supporting us. Yeah, no. Jared had
said at one point that we that he felt his he felt that his pants were tight and he was afraid
that the button was going to break off. And then Pat started riffing in the back of an Uber on the
way to Fu Manchu after several edibles. Yeah. And several drinks on the play out of the button flying
around the room, which capped off with it hits my pet bird. It's a birdcage. Yeah, I come out of the
bathroom. Where's my bird? Yeah, I don't know. Yeah. Good stuff. It's very funny. Real sheepish
looking. But we watched him. We watched him in back in backwards chronological order. We started
to have to with thirty three to third. Yeah, it's like Lord of the Rings. Yeah, we did Star Wars
style. Did you hear that? Somebody's car. They Trump just said he's not cracking down on emissions
anymore. Car can just put out huge clouds of black smoke and it's all good. Oh, man. So we'll be I
mean, why would you ever make that claim? All right. No politics. Let's move on. No politics.
But one thing. Did you see that Biden video? Oh, yeah. We're talking about the hair in his legs and
all that. I mean, that was like a deep fake. I was like, this can't be real. It is real. I mean,
honestly, we're doing the Irishmen. It looks like the Irishmen on that campaign trail. All these
old guys just like not keeping their shit together. And it's what's a wild time. God, man.
When he starts being like, and they'd come and then rub my hair down. I honestly want and it comes to
no point in the end. You don't know how he got there. And am I wrong? Is the point of his speech
to tell black people he relates to what it's like to have their kind of hair? Well, do you remember
what was the story where he was like, yeah, walked in and there was this guy with a knife and
everybody called him Pepper Jack or whatever, whatever it was. But he's telling the story about
like how he fought a pimp for his knife to relate to the black voters. And it's like, dude, you need
to stop. Soda pop was his name. Pepper Jack's from always sunny. So I looked at soda pop and I says,
I mean, it's insane. Wow. Wow. Yeah, he's talking like that speech. He literally sounds like I don't
know if anybody's familiar with this. I know you are, Pat. Go on. Arguably the funniest scene
I've ever seen in anything in my life of all time. The scene in the first season of Eastbound Down,
the Will Ferrell character with the best outtakes of all time, the best outtakes of all time.
I used to watch those as an acting exercise and try not to laugh. Yeah. And the but he could you.
I couldn't get through it. I was like, what if you were in this situation? What would you do?
I mean, no one in the scene, McBride and Craig Ferguson are both not Ferguson Robinson.
It's McBride show and Craig's friends with him. It gives me anxieties. I'm like, what if I was
like the rookie in the scene and you don't even anyway. Yeah. But Biden sounds like the boy watch.
Yeah. He sounds like Will Ferrell. It's incredible. Show me the plums. Yeah.
Take them down to farmers market plums getting a bluish shoe.
If you it is worth paying the five dollars for the Eastbound and Down DVD, which it really is
five on Amazon, the funniest outtakes, they're probably on YouTube. I'm coming off there 100
percent on you. All right. Good. In conjunction with all the anchorman and Ricky Bobby outtake.
Yeah. And the anchorman outtakes are fine, but the Ricky Bobby outtakes are fucking.
They are great. They are great. Yeah.
Carry on. You were saying something completely different.
I was just saying we watched them back with the movies backwards
and then the car went by and screeched. But they are truly best. The movies, in my opinion,
are best to worse. I've said many times here, I think the second one is the best one.
Second one is my favorite moments, but the first one really is the best one.
Two holds my heart. The only thing, the only part of it that I am not thrilled with is that
really kind of slow early section with Ricardo Montalban when he's kind of laying out the plan
and showing you his exotic fish or whatever in the first one, just because that's three sort of dry
minutes without a huge laugh. But one and two are about equal for me. Well, you got that scene's
got the pen behind the back through the red nose. How much of those moments sold just by Leslie
Nielsen? Yeah. Like, I mean, that is a joke where if Jerry Jerry O 'Connell was doing it,
you'd be like, Jesus Christ. But Leslie Nielsen pulls it off. Yeah. And he's doing three suges
ship, but he restrains it just enough that it feels modern. He had him. Yeah. I mean,
I just amazing timing. Me and Big Jay Okerson were laughing on his podcast recently about
the face. I'm so glad my name doesn't contain the word big. Can I just say that?
The they well, your nickname is not much better. It's handsy Pat Warsh.
No, that I'm fine with. That's true. We were laughing really hard about the face he makes
at the Leslie Nielsen makes at the end of part two when he saves the day by unplugging the bomb
because he trips over the extension. Yes, yes. And it cuts him and he literally just goes
like, yeah, no, he has the best faces, just amazing faces.
Anyway, it was enjoyable. That's a little bonus movie corner for you. That wasn't even movie
corner. No. How have you been, Pat? I've been pretty good, Joe. I've got a script in and I'm
waiting to hear and I don't feel the stress. I feel good. I've had a lot of time off work,
which has been so good for me. There's been rain recently, which I enjoy. I just got back from
St. Louis, Missouri, where I went for the Thanksgiving holiday.
Who did you see family or friends or both? You know, I saw them both. And really,
if you're a Walsh, you're always a friend, you know, no family comes together in a more
friendly manner than mine. But it was great. My my wife was really like, I never get to see your
family. I'm really going to make a big effort. Not that she didn't in the past. She's great. But
it was just like she went with my mom to Jazzercise. You know, the two of them made a cake together.
It was it was nice. It was the first time, you know, because when you're married,
you don't live in the same town as your family. It's kind of hard to get that big family feeling
that you get that you would get to say an olive garden.
Well, when you're there. Right. Right. You know, I don't want to seem hallmarky here or something,
but but it was nice. It was a good time. Everybody was on their best behavior,
which is not always the case with my family. And see, my friends was a blast. I want to shout out
fans of the podcast, Mike Curry and Andy Morrison had a big I told Heather they were like,
we're going to have a party on Saturday night. My buddy Ryan Murphy was like, you might want to
tell her we use the word party kind of loosely. So it wound up being just what it was in high
school, which was 10 guys sitting in a small circle, smoking weed, drinking and telling
stories about things that happened years ago. It sounds fun, but it was hilarious. I mean,
we got good stories. No one has changed at all. It was very fun. That's great. I love it. Hate
to be sincere for a moment, but I love it. It makes me happy to hear that. That's an important
part of somebody's life. You need that. You need that getaway to the to the roots. Yes,
it was good. And, you know, St. Louis is always fun. It's a different vibe. We stayed at the
casino again. Nice move. I love it. I didn't do much gambling, but we had a good time.
How was your turkey day? Surprisingly, the same as you're saying.
There was no I did for the first time ever. I had shows around it. Yeah. So for the first time
around the holiday or this kind of holiday, I didn't stay at home. I stayed in a hotel
on the off nights of Thanksgiving. And then on Thanksgiving night, I actually went to my buddy
Dan's after dinner and everything and just stayed with him. OK, and it was the best thing
I ever could have done. It reduced the tension in the house with my folks. We weren't at each
other's throats. Sure. Because of being in two close quarters for too too much time.
You hit an age listeners where you got to do the hotel, in my opinion. Yeah, it made such a
difference, man. Yeah, it made such a difference coming in as a guest to my mom and dad's
Thanksgiving. Yeah. Versus waking up there and being a part of the entire event and the intensity
of like someone running around making a dinner and then yelling at you and everything. Everybody's
in a terrible mood and sweating. And yeah, yeah, exactly. Yeah, we did the same thing. Walked in
like, hi, we're here for food and everybody's happy to see everybody. Yeah, it was awesome,
man. My cousins were in a were in great spirits. I was in great spirits. We had a great time. My
cousin, Will, brought his his new bride, which was lovely. And it was a lot of laughs and a lot
of fun. That was a child bride, you said, right? No, he's no, no, no, she's of age. He's a boy
husband. You never hear about a boy husband. He's yeah, he's he's one of the few. OK, but it was a
great time, man. We had a great time. And then and then aside from you mean child husband.
Well, I thought just boy child bride, child husband. Yeah, I just thought like a little
like boy to me sounds like a little boy. OK, fair. Like Jesse Popp would test. He'll talk
about a boy king. You know, that's funny. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Boy King is funny to me.
Anyway, so. And then around the holiday, I had shows and my friends, though they never listen
to an episode of this podcast, support me incessantly. And to my surprise, as a comedian,
they come out to every fucking show when I'm in the area. So and yet don't listen to the podcast.
No, you get one or the other, I think. All right. I think you're pushing it.
You get one or the other, you know, your podcast friends watch like your TV shows
in the way they watch in the way. No, probably not. You know what I mean? Yeah, like they've
heard it, the pod. But yes, right. Understood. But but anyway, they all came out, but understood.
I'm hurt, too. They all came out to my shows and we went to this really fun bar in Royers Ford
every night called the Toms or Johns. I think it was Tom's Bar. And it was just a fucking blast.
Same thing that you're talking about. Stories drinking. Yeah. You know, Scott, who you know,
my oldest friend in the world, he came out on Friday night. We went back to his house
at like two a .m. He's like the kids at the grandmoms. Let's fucking hang. You know,
stayed up with him to like five playing Miss Pac Man and telling stories. The wife come down
like Manchester by the Sea style. No, his wife, Dana, hung with us for a while and then went to
bed and then never reemerged. But I do have a hilarious video on my phone of him dancing
like like like just elated dancing joyously in his kitchen, shit faced to some Phil Collins song.
OK, and I'm panning back and forth between the two of them. It was an easy lover.
I don't know. It was an easy lover, but I have the camera on him and it starts on him and then
it goes over to her and she is not in the same place. He's in marriage all in a nutshell.
Just stare it out of. It's very funny. But but but she's great. We had we had a great time,
man. We had it. It was it was a really touching, fun stretch home. I ate like a hoagie and a
cheesesteak every day. Oh, you don't show it. I do show it. But you know, well, Joe,
speaking of Phil Collins, let's get on with the show. And at the same time on with the
Joe. Right. That there's a Joe that's been on my mind all the time. Sue, Sue, Sue,
the Joe. There you go. Yeah. All right. That's great. I love it, man. Thank you.
Let's get on with the why don't you take us down? I will. Well, you know what I want to do first,
I want to talk about that. Well, first, well, then the news of the day, the screaming and
there's a bunch of great ones. But first, I need to address. I was telling Joe before this started,
I wake up this morning. I hadn't been on the Facebook page in a while and I get on to see
what the response was to the new podcast. See if there's any shout outs, whatever. This morning
being December 3rd, this is going to come out. Yeah. February. Right. Just so you know. So I
read this thing. It was Lupe who had posted and it sounded so betrayed and so hurt. And she was
crying. And it was like, I thought I knew the guys, blah, blah, blah. And I'm sitting there
reading this thing so terrified thinking what insensitive thing that I say. She's like, we all
know Pat's comment. We all know the comment Pat made. And I'm like, fuck, what did I say? What's
out that Lupe and many, many, many others in the comments thought that we were ending the podcast.
And it's not true. I'm not saying it, when it will or won't, we don't know. We haven't decided,
but it's not ending. And we recorded that episode, I think before even recent ones that you've heard.
So we kind of aired them out of order. That podcast is months old. And at the time, Joe had
just told me he was moving and I was kind of like, yeah, you know, this will probably be the end of
the show. Let's be real. But we don't know that. And I'm sorry to have scared you for God's sake.
We're sticking around. Yeah. Making it work. In fact, I think we both felt that way. We didn't,
you know, up, you know, we didn't know what everything was up in the air. Yeah. A lot of
that is owed to the Patreon. Frankly, it was an experiment that that really worked out. And thank
you all for that. Yeah, we were surprised and we do this on our own, you know, and delighted that
so many fans came over with us to Patreon, because we didn't know if that would be the case.
And we hope more continue to come over. And we hope that, you know, we can continue to deliver
this to you in some form or fashion. And this seems to be working now. Right now, I mean,
you're hearing this in February. Or maybe you're hearing it sooner. I don't know. We record these
and then, you know, whatever. But the point is, is as of this recording, we're basically caught up
February and it's December. So, you know, this new format allows us to get these done when we can
get them done. And, you know, and thankfully, because I've been gone for I haven't seen Pat in
a month over a month. Yeah. So the old way was just not possible, as we've already explained.
It was time to let the old ways die. I think that's the song from Star is Born. I thought it was,
you know, sing that line again and I'll do what I thought it was. And you'll be so shocked at how
well these met. Maybe it's time to let the old ways die. We got tonight. Who needs tomorrow?
That was the theme of my junior prom. We've got tonight. We got tonight like Bob Seeger,
80 years older than everyone in the room. It was crazy. That's a rough and tumble prom theme, man.
Mine was in your eyes, which is hackneyed. But, you know, no, it's a good one. My friend Dan,
who I stayed Thanksgiving night with, he used to do and he still does it when we get drunk. He does
like he meshes all the Aerosmith songs together and he'll scream it at me in bars and it makes
me laugh really hard. But it'll go, it's amazing. Crazy. My age. Yeah, they all just really interlock.
But anyway, but but it's so far so good. It's working out. So, you know, we want to keep doing
this for as long as we can. And speaking of that, I appreciate, as you all do, that Pat's doing the
solo movie corners. I'm going to start dropping in when I'm settled in New York and all set up in
my new place. I'm going to start start dropping in with some solo scary stuffs. Maybe I was even
thinking of doing some solo screaming ends because I seem to get extremely wound up about
entertainment news and then people tell me to shut up. Yeah, if you got a rant, I'm sure people
would love to hear it. You know, so I'm going to start dropping in with some bonus material, too.
There is a video that's going to be posted soon. Emily has it. I have it, too, of me. I'll just get
ahead of it. It's me soliciting sex from an undercover cop. All right. But I begged him not
to share it. I moonlight as a cop. Joe may or may not have been that beat cop making my blunt
or even more extreme, because I should have recognized him. I said and I said to Pat when I
bust him, I said, buddy, it's called beat cop, not beat off cop. Right. And he got the point.
I let him off in a word, even though I knew I was in big trouble. I actually laughed. It was that
good. We've got a video courtesy of Emily Florence that will be coming out soon. She came to the
Come and Take It Festival in Houston and we did the goddamn comedy jam. She recorded me singing
Kickstart My Heart by Motley Crue. OK, so that will be the video that will be going up.
The only Motley Crue song I've ever liked. I love that song and I am not a Motley Crue fan.
I've never liked any of their music and that one gets me like punch in the air. Yeah.
It's a shit movie, but that movie shoot them up. That's what got me into the song.
Yeah. Man, that song is awesome. They had it in the trailer. Yeah.
Anyway, so we're not we're not planning on going anywhere yet. And don't don't don't dry your eyes.
Right. Don't cry. Dry your eyes. A slick Rick once said.
And yeah, you know, we can do a screaming in on the Irishmen. We did talk about how,
you know, Scorsese talking about Marvel became this big ordeal. We talked about that in the last
But now all I'm reading about for the last three days on Twitter is how upset people are
that Anna Paquin doesn't have more lines in the Irishmen as if it's not so clearly
to any idiot that it is a stylistic choice by Scorsese to show you how little involved
De Niro was in his children's life and the sacrifices you make for this life,
which is the entire theme of the film. There was a story where somebody was mad
that his first wife didn't get more recognition in the story. It's not what the story is about.
Would you want it to be longer? It's not what the story is. And then also to
Jesse Plemons, whatever his name is. Yeah, Plemons has like four lines in this thing.
Right. This is what people understand. And he's a big star. Guys, so is Paquin.
Scorsese didn't say, I'm going to write a movie for Anna Paquin and then gave her no lines.
Scorsese had a script written by what's his name? Nick Nicholas. Steven Zalia.
Sorry, Steven Zalia. Did Schindler's List. Yeah.
Everyone in town is begging to be in this thing. I assure you.
And Scorsese is the kind of guy that can get A -listers to do just like Tarantino.
He fills out the smaller parts with awesome actors and then the smaller parts are awesome
instead of you not caring because, you know, because somebody's in there with no lines and
they're acting like somebody with no like, like, you've got Titans filling out every role of this
thing. So that Scorsese says he doesn't think it's a big deal. It was a thematic choice.
De Niro says he doesn't understand what the, I mean, the fact they even have to answer these
questions is insane. But then Anna Paquin says, no, I auditioned for this role knowing what it was.
I was happy to audition 20 years into my career and I was thrilled to have the experience in the
role. And then people are saying people are still going, no, I want to be mad for her.
Yeah, it's it's absurd. It's absurd. And this brings me to a screaming end that I want to talk
about, which is it's somewhat related when a movie like this comes out with this kind of
star power and this these kinds of performances and whatever else. And I don't know what your
thoughts are yet. Let's wait till with the review. But I'm getting these Oscar screeners
for your consideration, as we do every year. I mean, first of all, Avengers endgame. Are you
fucking insane? Followed by followed with, by the way, a Peter Travers review on the front,
of course. I mean, so that comes and then another one is.
For Christ sakes, what is the movie called with the super bad thing, but it's two girls instead
of two kids. Oh, yeah, Booksmart. Guys, these are not Oscar contending films. They're good movies.
You're going to see a couple of nominations for Booksmart. That's nuts. I know it's nuts.
The Rolling Stones, Peter Travers on the cover of the Avengers screener,
which is, by the way, a black and white photo of Robert Downey Jr. caressing the Iron Man mask.
So not pretentious or anything. And then Peter Travers says, sorry, the the movie hits you
like a shot in the heart. Oh, God. Does it? Meanwhile, I know you all like I get a screener
for some like pirate ship movie starring Eddie Redman. What the hell is that? I forget what
it was called. And and Sicily, not Sicily, the girl that was in Rogue One.
And anyway, you know, apparently she was extremely well reviewed in this movie. I've never seen it.
I hadn't heard of it. But that's my point is like, meanwhile, there are these other movies
where women are giving apparently grand slam fucking performances and everybody's going,
we should nominate Booksmart. Yeah. And it's like this. It's like it's like when Ghostbusters came
on, we talked about like the Kristen Wiig stuff that was just completely overlooked,
like these great indie thing. Right. She gets no nods for it. Now we're going, you know, we got to
get we got to get Melissa McCarthy and Oscar for Ghostbusters. The only things that get nominated
are no diss against Melissa McCarthy. It's all the people who who put together enough money
to do the campaign and send out the screeners. You will never see a movie nominated that did
not have screeners sent to the houses. And I think that's terrible because then a little movie that
doesn't have the budget to push forward on something like that never gets noticed or
recognized. They never nominate the right things anyway. I mean, I remember years back,
the Golden Globes nominated The Tourist starring Johnny Depp and Angelina Jolie,
an awful movie that nobody saw. It's an action movie and they nominated it. Not not only did
they nominate it, but they nominated it for Best Musical or Comedy. And in the meantime,
you got a movie like like, for instance, The Babadook, which I was not a huge fan of the movie,
but the woman's performance in it is outstanding. Didn't get a screener for that when that was out.
Or Tony Collette in Hereditary. That's one of the best performances I've ever seen.
Everybody's raving about Nightingale. I want to see it. Nothing. It's good. You know what I mean?
It's like everybody's clear. Stop clamoring around the wrong. Stop worrying about why Anna
Paquin plays a silent character in a movie, which is supposed to be a silent character,
and maybe start championing the other people that are getting overlooked that are doing this
fucking killer work. Agreed. Anyway, that's all I just I just you know,
it's just it's I mean, I don't know why I'm expecting more from the Oscars, but
where were you going with the screaming at? What was it? It was just the the the amount of
news stories surrounding these these movies that, you know, we Robert Downey Jr. refuses to campaign
for the Oscars. It's like he should refuse. He absolutely should. Ridiculous. Right. Agreed.
This is ridiculous. I'm the biggest Vince Vaughn fan in the world. You told me Vince Vaughn was
going to get nominated for swingers part two or whatever. What are you nuts? Agreed. You know,
so anyway, that that was that's all. That's all I had to say. All right. Well, then let me take
you over, if I may, to Pat's movie corner. Now, Joe, am I to assume you're not going to see
Terminator Dark Fate or should we save it for a future episode?
Look, let's sit on it just in case, because I I want to see you know how much I hate
James Cameron. I want to see it. This isn't a Cameron movie. This isn't a movie.
Hey, listen, Tim Miller is saying nothing but Cameron. Oh, I'm sure he's passing the buck.
Don't he is. He said Cameron fucked this entire thing up. Did he really? Well, the big stupid
he said that Cameron, he said he will never work with James Cameron again. OK. And he said that
James, the big argument they had was James Tim Miller saying and I guess this is a spoiler.
I don't know. I haven't seen it. Tim Miller saying, where is the drama in the humans winning?
That doesn't make any sense. Right. And James Cameron was like, where is the drama in the
humans losing? Let the humans win and then let them win again. Right. And Tim Miller was like,
no, no, stop postponing Judgment Day. Yeah, they let a bet. But let the tragedy happen. Right.
Right. And apparently, Cameron, it was also Cameron's idea to and this is news at this point,
but spoiler alert, it was Cameron's idea to kill John Connor in the first 30 seconds of the movie.
He thought that that would be a great way to start the movie off. Uh huh.
Well, Eddie Furlong came out. He's like, I don't know, man, I went in for a day to have a bomb.
They didn't tell me they were going to kill me. I'm going to hold my opinion on this thing. But
that opening scene of Dark Fate used apparently the same technology as Irishmen as they were
trying to age them. And apparently that's actual Eddie Furlong now. Yeah. Which they must have
thinned him out as well. Yeah, they did. Yeah. So. All right. Well, let me take you over
to Pat's movie corner. Now, what I do on my solo movie corner is I've been doing the Oscar picks,
not the Oscar picks, but you know, the the movies of the Oscar season, the ones they're pushing
your uncut gems and that kind of stuff. So I'm still going to do that. And today I'm going to
talk about maybe a few lesser known from the year. I saw Amazing Grace. It's on Hulu. It's like an 80
minute documentary of Aretha Franklin performing gospel music in a church.
It's incredible. It was like the late 60s. Mick Jagger is there in the audience,
but it's basically a church service where the person singing is Aretha Franklin.
She's she is amazing. I mean, if you like her and how could you not? It's one of the most jaw
dropping vocal performances I've ever seen. It's awesome. There's a preacher there who's very funny,
very entertaining, who sings a couple of songs with her as well, but mostly it's just a solo
concert. For some reason, I feel like I've seen so much footage of the Beatles playing of the
Stones playing, but you never really see footage of Aretha Franklin. So this is a great time to
sit with her and see a great concert for an hour and a half. Check it out on Hulu. I saw a great
documentary called Rocket Man, not about Elton John. Oh, I was going to say, Joe, that wasn't a documentary.
It's about a guy who is a flat earther who literally taught himself rocket science and has
had a go fund me or whatever for years, attempting to raise money to build a rocket to launch himself
into space, to take a definitive picture of the earth so he can prove to everybody that the earth
is flat. OK, that's where it starts. So clearly at the beginning of this thing, you're like this guy
is a cook. Yeah. And as you watch it, you realize he actually does understand rocket science. Right.
He does know how to build rockets. He has successfully built rockets that launch.
They don't go high enough, but they fucking launch. Right. Gets scrap metal and shit and he builds
goddamn rockets. OK. And surprisingly, as you go through the journey of this thing,
it's very endearing. You know, I obviously don't agree with the guy that the earth is flat.
But, you know, he and he's a little eccentric, if not Nazi. But it's very endearing and it's
endearing to watch him go on this journey. It's endearing to, you know, you feel bad
for him when he gets down about what people are saying about him on the Internet and stuff like
that. His passion is endearing. But he's also does have a sense of humor about himself. Like
there's footage of him going on Tosh Pointo and Tosh is making fun of him. He's laughing and
he's in on it enough that he's not, you know, right. But it's just a great documentary.
You end up really liking a guy that on paper you would be like, get him away from me. Right. Right.
So I suggest it. It's fun. It's funny. What's it called one more time? Rocket Man. OK.
And it's heartwarming. All right. Sounds good.
What do you got on that? I watched Brittany runs a marathon new to Amazon Prime.
I think that might be another one like some one they might they might be pushing for the Oscars,
which I mean, it's getting great reviews. Yeah, it's you know, the best I could do would be cute.
Best I could say about it would be that it's kind of cute. But it's just a story about, you know,
Gillian Bell, who is their female friend from workaholics, been in a bunch of stuff. 21 Jump
Street. Yeah, she's funny. Very funny actress. She plays a woman who is overweight, big drinker,
big casual sexer, et cetera. She kind of has this rude awakening that she needs to get her
life together. A doctor says you got to lose fifty five pounds or something. And so she starts
training for a marathon, starts eating better, running. She has a love interest. And that is
basically it. I was kind of bored by it, kind of let down by it. Sadly,
it's one of those comedies like so many others. It's an indie comedy that refuses
to put jokes in it. So everything's kind of this like gentle. You know, that said,
it's not all bad. The story is inspiring. If you need a little jump in terms of
getting in shape or something, it might work in that way for you. It's a cute little movie,
but nothing I could say. You got to see. You're not going to watch The Mandalorian,
right? I will at some point, but I don't have Disney Plus. So should I save that
for a potential review? Yeah, that'd be fun. All right, I'll save it. All right.
Well, we're on the Irishman. I rewatched Goodfellas, as did I. So at the east at
midnight. Thirty five millimeter. I watched it on my good old TV. Yeah.
But what can I say? It's a fucking masterpiece. The best. I mean, every time I watch it,
I wonder, will I enjoy this as much as I have every other time I've watched it?
There's going to have to be a drop off at some point. Like the McRib.
You go, there's no way it's going to be as good as I remember it being. Sure. And boy,
does that thing just melt in your mouth. Yeah, every time. Goodfellas is the McRib.
It's do yourself a favor. Revisit that film if you haven't seen it in a while.
Oh, my God. You can't. I mean, it's just it's a masterpiece. It's a fucking masterpiece.
I couldn't agree more about that. I couldn't agree less about the McRib.
But if you're in L .A., the visa does this thing called Secret Movie Club. They put their picks
up. There's a guy that between you and me may go a little long with the intros,
especially when the movies start at midnight. But I go up there pretty regular. They have amazing
35 millimeter prints on the big screen at the theater, which is beautiful. Joe and I and my
lovely wife went and saw four Twilight Zone episodes on Halloween. That was a lot of fun.
But check them out if you're here. They're great.
That's where I saw Goodfellas the other night. Midnight. That's what I'm talking about. That
movie's two and a half hours. Maybe you don't need to do a half hour intro. Just saying.
I didn't. I'm wrong. I didn't watch it on my TV. I watched it on a flight.
OK. And Scorsese would have wanted it. Well, I've seen it regular. Right. But
it just made the flight just fly by. I mean, it's just a perfect movie.
I completely agree. Yeah. An all time favorite. And I was able to take a friend who had never
seen it. So that was great. What was their reaction? Absolutely loved it. I mean, because
it doesn't. You know, he was talking about how movies from that period are edited slower.
They came out in 89 90. They just move slower. They're not with. So a kid seeing it might be
like, oh, God, it's taking forever. But Goodfellas is done like a music video. Scorsese apparently
said when he made it, he wanted it to feel like a two and a half hour coming attraction for the
movie that you're watching. And that's what it is. Oh, well, relentless. That's amazing.
So even a kid watching it now would be like, damn, this thing is fucking moving. That's amazing.
Yeah. The last one I'll mention is a picture called The Laundromat.
This is a movie I was very excited about because it reunited Scott Z. Burns, the writer
who wrote The Informant, which I think is a fantastic movie, and Stephen Soderbergh.
The director of The Informant and many, many great films. This movie is about the Pentagon
papers. It stars Meryl Streep, Antonio Banderas and Gary Oldman play like a Greek chorus type
thing where they're in tuxedos walking along, you know, narrating the film for you. OK, those scenes
do not work and derail the movie in a really big way. I like Oldman. I like Banderas. But man,
they suck. And also adding to the problem, this is a movie told completely out of order
in the style that Soderbergh likes to do a lot. And the Oscar screening I went to showed the
second reel of the movie first. So I enter this thing and I'm like, hey, Soderbergh,
you got to throw me a flag here. I don't know what the fuck's going on. You know, I was completely
lost. And then the credits roll. I look at my phone. It's like 50 minutes in. God damn it.
So then they started from the beginning and then you're watching this thing that's already told
out of order further out of order. So in fairness, I might be judging it a little harshly, but boy,
I haven't talked to anybody who's really passionate about it. They're pushing it for Oscars. I don't
think it's got a chance. Streep is good as always. There's some kind of fun twists and stuff in terms
of the script. And it's an all star cast down to the smallest part. You got David Schwimmer,
Sharon Stone, a lot of people you haven't seen in a while. Will Forte and Chris Parnell have like
two lines a piece. So probably their scene got cut down maybe. Christina Alonzo in the mix.
You know, he always cast comics. Yeah, it's great. Tell your agent he always cast comics.
I will. Your boy Bobby Kelly was in UnSane that Soderbergh did. He was. My buddy Tom Papa is in
Informant. Correct. Patton Oswald. A lot of people are in the. Yeah. All right. That's great.
I'll close with just on topic on theme rather. We also rewatch Casino. In my opinion,
another fucking masterpiece. And you favor it slightly. Yes. No, I don't. I think it's
it's a more raucous watch. I would understand either way. It's it. You see, no, makes me laugh.
Like I watch it like it's a comedy. I mean, yeah, it's hilarious.
But another just, you know, front to back masterpiece.
And the reason I rewatched these movies was because I knew the Irishman was coming out.
And after actually, no, I went back and watched them after I saw the Irishman the first time
because I wanted to, you know, you sort of want to just go back and see,
you know, the stuff that led up to it. And not that I think the Irishman plays like
Goodfellas part three. But if they were going to sell a three pack. Yeah. These movies. And they
will. I assure you. Yeah. These movies would be the three. So not much to say here about Casino
other than in the spirit of this new Scorsese film being out. And if you enjoyed it,
do yourself a favor. Go back and rewatch Casino as well, because it's just another tour de force
just front to back. Sharon Stone, De Niro, Pesci. Yeah. Frank Vincent,
you know, Joe Bob Briggs, Joe Bob Briggs. Yeah.
Jimmy Woods at his sleaziest. Oh, Woods is so great at it. You shut your mouth. Yeah,
you shut your mouth. I'm going to smack your face. Yeah, it's a great movie. Yeah. So rewatch. So
that but that but that brings us to the to the topic at hand. Really? You know, the third and
very loose unofficial trilogy of movies that does not contain any of the same people.
But you can definitely draw a line from Goodfellas to Casino to this. You'll also notice that each
movie is a half hour longer than the one that preceded it. It is impossible not to talk about
The Irishman without discussing the fact that it runs three and a half hours long. Yes. I saw it
the theater up at the Egyptian here in Hollywood and I didn't pee. I sat completely transfixed by
the thing for three and a half hours. And when I looked down, I was like, wow, that moves so fast.
I hadn't looked at my phone. And, you know, usually at a movie, I'm looking at my phone
40 times to see what time it is. Yes. If I don't like it. So for me, it really worked. And I did
a second viewing, which I think gave me a lot more clarity on it at home because there was just
a lot of excitement when I saw it in the theater. So my opinion diminished a little bit in a second
viewing, but not much. And I think the reality lies somewhere in between. But the movie, Joe,
would you like to take us through the story? Yeah, this I was very excited for this film
because I'm a big fan of the story. I love the movie with Jack Nicholson and Danny DeVito.
And I just I really like the tale of and the this guy that was all for the working man
at any cost and was also, you know, to the point of corruption, absolute corruption and
getting in bed with the wrong people and then blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
all the stuff that this movie goes through. So this film takes us through that story,
but through the eyes of Frank Sheeran, who is a mafia hit man and also lifelong teamster
who on his deathbed said confessed that he was the man that killed Jimmy Hoffa
and he knew where the body was or what at least happened to the body.
A book was written about it called I heard you paint houses, which is his confession.
Own it. Haven't read it. Heard it's great. The confession has been,
you know, it's had holes blown through it by many, many Hoffa experts.
It's it's one of the least credible, apparently, according to the experts. However,
whether it's credible or not, it's an amazing story. And the man was the right hand man to
Jimmy Hoffa at the end of the day. So he saw all this stuff up close and personal and was
very involved with the man and was able to shed light on things that nobody else was able to
and also able to shed light on on these mafia titans like Angelo Bruno
and the like that that Bufalino and whoever else that many other people weren't able to.
So this movie takes us through this guy's journey brilliantly, in my opinion,
showing the balance or the way rather that he's torn between three families, his obligation,
his his his obligation to his actual family and his want to protect them.
As that one grows to protect them, he gets in deeper with the actual mob.
As he gets in deep with the actual mob, his loyalty grows. The mob sets him in links him
Jimmy Hoffa connects him to Jimmy Hoffa. Jimmy Hoffa becomes his best friend.
His connection and loyalty to Hoffa grows. And then as all of these three families are
essentially warring against one another silently, you see this man going through the motions of all
of it and being torn between the three that man being De Niro. Yes. And it's a fascinating story.
It's kind of hard to just I think a lot of people think that this movie is just about
how Jimmy Hoffa was killed. And it's much, much, much bigger than that. To me, this this plays a
lot like a raging bull plays in the Scorsese department, at least, because you would never
say about raging bull. Well, it's about when he fought that guy. Right. It's it's not about
it's about the man himself. It's about the life. It's about the flaws. It's about the personal
bullshit. It's about the mistake. It's about all that stuff. And it follows him on a very,
very, very long journey in raging bull as it does in this movie. And I walked away from it.
That's enough of the explanation, the plot. Oh, yeah. Yeah. I walked away from it.
Some would say more than enough. I saw it. I saw the screening with the writer present
for a Q &A afterward at a WGA screening. So I saw it before it was released.
And they did the Q &A afterwards. And I was lucky enough to be called on last,
which felt really good. And Joe goes, Hi, more of a comment than a question.
Though you did. I did say that's not really a question. I just want to tell you some people
hate that. Fuck him. I got an applause break. Oh, good. I said this is I know you got to go.
And I'm last. And I go, this isn't really a question. I just want to say to you,
I just want to say thank you on behalf of all the fans. You gave these guys the gangster send off.
They all deserved. Thank you for hitting this out of the parking park. And the guy was wow.
Thank you, man. And it got a nice applause break. Nicholas Pileggi, who wrote Goodfellas and Casino
executive produced this. So it's got some of the tonality of those films. Anybody who's disappointed
in this movie, I'm seeing the same thing come up. It's boring. It's boring. It's this does not move
like a Goodfellas or a casino. It moves like the Godfather. This is very much a movie about people.
And secondary is the mob stuff. Yeah. Goodfellas and Casino, the mob stuff is first. The people are
second. And this is the opposite. This is about the emotional journey of these people and what they
go through. And, you know, it's it's it's I thought it was a fucking masterpiece. I've seen it three
times now, like 11 hours of your life. Yeah. And it's gotten better for me on each viewing.
I'm noticing things each time I watch it that I hadn't noticed before. It's all it all makes
more coherent sense every time I watch it, you know, because you're picking up on the subtleties
and things and it's answering its own questions. So I loved it. But I mean, let's you know, let's
get into the. Yeah, I mean, I by and large loved it myself. I came out of that first viewing just,
you know, thrilled, really thrilled that Scorsese got the chance, as you were saying to this writer
and the cast got another chance. Pesci had officially retired from acting. So
it is the best I've ever seen Joe Pesci. It's not my favorite performance. I think he's awesome in
it. I think he very well might win the Oscar for it. It's a very different performance from him.
It's like way more reserved and kind of scary and tense. And he doesn't really fall back on
any of his tricks at all. He has an amazing moment where he tries to engage with De Niro's
daughter when she's a little girl. And like you can tell, it hurts him that she's not just doesn't
like him. Yeah. You know, she's like a dog that can sense there's something wrong with him.
And that that was some amazing acting in there when he's just trying to relate to her
and it just is not working. It was crazy. And he plays it so much. I knew guys like when I was
growing up, I had I had guys in my family like not saying they were mobsters, just meaning
older Italian men that I didn't understand that I felt frightening. Right. And just the way he
relates to the kid, it's not it's not my favorite Pesci. My favorite Pesci will always be like,
you motherfucker, you sure. Sure. But it's it's my opinion, the best he's ever been.
Yeah, he was great. Just because it's like that scene where he's like,
do you know why God made this guy so high so the birdies won't hit there when they fly?
Isn't that cute? That's exactly how a guy that doesn't know how to talk to kids talks to kids.
Like it's this terrible joke that he thinks a kid is going to think it's not even really a joke.
And then as soon as the kid doesn't laugh, he's like, do you need anything? Do you need candy?
What can I do anything for you? Yeah. There's that great scene later at Christmas,
too, where he gives her the ice skates. He's like Santa Claus left you something extra in there and
she pulls out a hundred dollar bill. This guy just doesn't understand. Yeah. Yeah.
Um, no, I thought he was great in it. My thinking on the second viewing today, both times,
whether on my on my, you know, Netflix or in the theater, it just moves along. You know,
like I didn't feel the running time at all. Anyone saying it's boring. I mean,
I get why people wouldn't like this movie. Don't get me wrong. I think it has flaws.
But, you know, people are just not trained to watch movies like this anymore.
Yeah, they're, they're expecting nonstop action and fast cutting. And that's honestly what you
expect from Scorsese. We were talking about Goodfellas and Casino. Goodfellas is a movie
that the last half hour, you know, is the super paranoid tense day, but that is shot just as
excitingly probably not a word and glamorously as the beginning. So the first two hours of
Goodfellas is showing you it's also the same structure used by boogie nights, which while
amazing, completely ripped off Goodfellas almost down to the minute. But Goodfellas shows you how
fun this lifestyle is for two hours. For the last half hour, it shows you how stressful it can be.
But even that is so much fun to watch. Then in the last 30 seconds, you see the punishment,
which is he's got to eat bad macaroni in witness protection. But that's saved for the last second
of the movie. And then up comes the sex pistols doing my way. And then you're like, Oh shit,
what an amazing movie. Casino is really the same way. It's three hours. Every single scene
is scored by one of the greatest classic rock songs of all time. Sometimes as in Goodfellas,
there'll be five or six music cues in a minute. And you know, it just goes on and on where the
entire score is this amazing music. Everything's cut like MTV, blah, blah, blah. You get to this
movie and it does take some adjustment. A there's the CGI, which we're going to get to, of course.
But you're watching this thing and it's just edited very slow. Scorsese leaves in a lot of
them stumbling over lines, particularly De Niro. I think that's it's improv. That's a character
choice. OK, I think he's doing he does it so much in the movie. I think I have a feeling he's like
one of those obsessive like, how did he hold his glass? Sure. Yeah. Was this pinky here or that?
You know, I think like I heard he worked in a knife shop for two weeks before the fan. Yeah,
exactly. A fan. I think that's like I think that was a character choice where he's like, this is
how this guy talked. Right. And maybe that's the case. Speaks to why he is so loyal. He's subservient.
It's weird seeing De Niro like that. He's subservient. Like it is cool, though, when you
see the the lion inside of him like, yes, like I'm going to know I'm going to sit there. Yeah.
You're going to sit there. Yeah. Yeah. It's always fun when it comes out, you know,
get in the fucking car and bullshit about your mother. Yeah. Yeah. That. But like what blows me,
this is just a side to speak to the De Niro thing. Yes. Finish. He he's extremely subservient in the
movie. I was watching my admiration for him and Pacino as actors shot through the roof on the
third time I watched this because that was the first time I noticed. I'm like, my God,
they're giving each other so much. There's no ego with these guys. De Niro was sitting like on a
bed quiet. Right. As Pacino was over him going, he's a fucking cocksucker. Yeah. And like it's
not the nose to nose that like that famous heat scene was. It's a lot of like just two guys playing
a scene. Yeah. Not showing off. She knows, you know, doing his thing. But still, Pacino, in my
opinion, should I mean, this is a compliment, should retire after this movie. I'm like, this guy's
found the role that he was born to play. That's it. Like when Pacino is yelling in that scene,
which felt improvised to me, but that scene when he's like, you bunch of fucking idiots
and like he starts talking, he gets so angry, he loses train of thought for a minute
and then comes back to it. That when I saw that theater was laughing so fucking hard
and it seemed like a blooper, they left in and Scorsese has them improvise all the time.
But that scene was so much fun. He is hamming it up. He is overacting a little bit,
but it's so much fun to watch. And which interesting is, is he plays
Hoffa emotionally. I mean, exactly the way Nicholson plays. Yeah. So I'm like, I guess
that's just how Hoffa must be. Did you also see a bit of a homosexual subtext?
No. Because when I looked online, there was a lot of that and I wasn't alone in thinking so.
But his relationship with De Niro and kind of like the leaving his door open thing while he's
sleeping over and all that, people are reading that as homoerotic. And I must say there were
a few moments I kind of did too. No, I think it's always strange to see two, not strange,
now it sounds like, you know what I mean? Yes. I think like you're seeing two men in their 50s
sharing a hotel room. Right. Yeah. You think there must be something romantic happening.
But I really think that that's just that's just how important this guy was to him where he was
like, dude, this is how this has to be. Well, then how do you explain the blow drops?
I mean, the door open thing to me was that all that was to me was I always have my eyes open.
Sure. I always and then De Niro, then you catch it at the end. De Niro does at the very end of
the priest. Right. Father, can you please leave the door? I don't like it closed all the way.
But no, I didn't I didn't get any. I think that that's just how it was back then. Like you had
guys that did everything with you. And that's how the business worked. I felt it way less on
the second viewing. But on the first viewing, I thought it enough that when I looked, others had
the same thought. Anyway, what I was saying, you got Goodfellas, you got Casino and then this,
you're expecting the third in that trilogy. I was Casino is very much to me a sequel to Goodfellas.
Uh, this is it's going so slow. There are way less music cues. If Scorsese was to do what he
did in those movies with music, this movie would have cost five hundred million dollars instead of
two, which is what it did cost. But the music cues are gone. It's replaced by a score that I found
kind of annoying. The harmonica score is not my favorite. I don't think it really works well with
material. It's Robbie Robertson from the band. But I did not love the music in this movie at all.
I think they could have done a much better job with it. That's my issue. There are still there
are still a lot of music cues. It's just clear. It was see, I don't think that that was a I might
be wrong. It was just my opinion. I didn't think that that was a budget choice. I thought that that
was to me that was a filmmaking choice. I think it felt like Scorsese was saying this movie needs
a theme that keeps coming back up. Oh, yeah. And I certain theme song. Yeah, we can't just
he must. I don't think it's him getting older. He's telling a story about men getting older
and was like, let's cut this slower. Let's have a score as opposed to this like super fast cutting
and the crazy music and everything. I do agree. It was a choice. I just don't like the music,
frankly. It grew on me. I didn't I never hated it, but I hear you. It's weird. It's weird.
Anytime you see a Scorsese movie and there's a score instead of like, right, you know,
like 50s rock music playing or whatever. Right. But if I mean, I thought it was,
you know, the story, the half of stuff, it wasn't super, especially on a second viewing,
it wasn't super gripping to me, I must say. But as a as a character study, it reminded me a bit of
The Good Shepherd, which De Niro directed and is a super underrated movie with Matt Damon and
but of just being a very sad, slow character study. And as that I absolutely loved it. The
stuff that I didn't think worked as well was music, as I said, and De Niro's narrating it
the whole time. For me, these little scenes of what you would say are the most clearly linked
to Goodfellas and Casino, these scenes where it's like he put the beer on the hot dogs,
you know, that it was the best hot dog you could find or whatever. All these detours
into what they were eating, what they were drinking, the vodka and the watermelon bit,
you know, they're kind of funny. But to me, in a three and a half hour movie, that's the shit you
got to pare back. And it it was so reminiscent of Goodfellas and Casino where it works so much
better to me because it felt fresher and newer about how they made the pasta in prison or whatever.
I loved all those little details. Seeing it now, it felt like that style doesn't fit with
this story. And it also didn't fit with the very emotional story they're telling. So I didn't care
for those moments. I know they're there to kind of give you more of a full picture of what life
was like. But for me, I've seen it before. I've seen it from Scorsese. I think in this kind of
somber and slower character study, we don't necessarily need to know what the hot dog tasted
like to me. And that's why I think people get frustrated with the length. It's weird, though,
because again, like upon rewatching, all these little things start popping up. They show you
the watermelon and the vodka and the watermelon thing. And the reason the guy does that is because
because Hoffa doesn't let anybody drink around him. So this guy spikes watermelon with
vodka and then so they can eat the watermelon and get drunk and Hoffa won't know. So to me,
that was a nice little moment of Hoffa going when he goes, you boys show like your watermelon.
I was like, oh, he knows exactly what they're doing. They like they're showing how sharp this
guy is. But then as soon as Jimmy gets out of jail, he goes to get some of these chili dogs.
And the first thing he says is, you know, this was this is the first meal this guy wants. See,
the secret is they're they're they're steamed in beer. Right. I think there's some significance
to that. I'm not quite sure what it is that Hoffa is so anti alcohol that he won't let it be around
him. Yet the first meal he wants is this hot dog that's steamed in beer. I think all these little
things have. I think there's probably much more significance to the discussion about the fish
being in the car. Sure. Then I'm realizing right now. And that's what I enjoyed about the third.
By the third rewatch, I started to connect dots on things. I started to understand like this is why
De Niro has to kill Hoffa. Why does De Niro pick the green coffin? Because it's the same color as
Jimmy Hoffa's car. You know what I mean? Like, right. Why is the door open at the end? Oh,
because that's what Hoffa does at the beginning. Yeah. Like, oh, he gets the gold watch at the
ceremony. And he also in the same night gets the fucking gold ring. Right. From Pesci like. And
then in that same setting, he has to which went on first watch. I was like, I don't like that all of
this business is happening at this dinner where Pesci is arguing with Pacino. And then they're
telling De Niro he's got to go kill Pacino, whatever. And then on the third watch, I was like,
oh, no, this is what this whole thing is about. Like, his fucking family is there. He's being
honored by the teamsters. And he's being told by Pesci, you're protected by me forever. Now go
tell your friend we're going to kill him. It all is happening under the same roof. So I don't know
if there is more significance to these little moments. But I will say after the third watch,
I was like, oh shit, like this is all these dots are starting to connect. And on the first watch,
I just thought they were funny. They didn't bother me. But well, and isn't it nice just to
have something to think about after a movie? I mean, this this movie has a lot of little details
that stick with you, make you think and so many great performance moments. The De Niro actually,
the reason I thought De Niro was messing up his lines here and there, it happens maybe six times
in the movie, but they're they're really noticeable. Like he flubs the line. I thought, well, okay,
Scorsese has everybody improvised to death. Maybe these were improvs and Scorsese like the way they
felt. But what I eventually settled on and again, I'm probably wrong, is that in a movie where a lot
of the time we're watching a CGI face, a de -aged or an aged up face that someone messing up their
dialogue feels more lifelike because these faces by nature kind of have that polar express thing
where they look a little off. So I thought he was humanizing these things that could look soulless.
That's interesting. But I could be wrong there, too. Did the aging bother you? It was a little
weird for me on the first viewing for about 15 minutes. Yeah. By the third viewing, I didn't
notice it at all. Pretty much everybody, unless they want to really, you know, just make fun of
this movie. I've heard a lot of people just shit and shit and shit on this movie, and that's fine,
too. But yeah, in the theater, especially the big rosy cheeks of De Niro, when you first see him,
you're like, what is going on? And he's got blue eyes, and you've been seeing De Niro with brown
eyes for 50 years. So it's jarring. It's an adjustment. There's no denying that. And the
scene with the biggest problem is when De Niro in a scene, another scene straight from Goodfell is
when he goes down and tells the postman to stop bringing mail to the house. In this one, De Niro
goes down to beat up this grocer that pushed his daughter. And when De Niro is stopping this guy,
they're doing something digitally that looks terrible. And if you do a fourth watch,
you'll notice, unless you did. I noticed it on the first watch. His arms and legs are curved
in the most unusual way. And I guess De Niro is so old, he can't do that minimal stunt on his own.
But man, it doesn't work. What was interesting, if you watch this roundtable discussion with
Pesci, De Niro, Pacino, and Scorsese, it's on Netflix. If you click on The Irishman,
it's a 20 -minute interview with them having drinks and laughing, and it's great. But
they talk about how somebody came up on Pacino's first day and were like, he's standing up real,
takes him a long time to stand up. And he's supposed to be 49 years old. You got to tell
him to stand up faster. And they were all kind of nervous to approach Pacino and be like,
standing up like an old man because you are an old man. So a lot of it was posture and getting
all that down. Maybe De Niro at his age just can't kick somebody in the head a bunch.
I don't know. It's weird. That's the one scene that stuck out to me as looking odd.
I was confused as to why Scorsese wouldn't shoot around it because Scorsese said they had six
cameras in every scene covering every single thing to make sure that the body movement and
was good. That's the one scene where I was like, why would he not just cut to close up?
But because De Niro can. By the way, he cuts to close up in Goodfellas. When Goodfellas
and when he's stomping Frank Vincent, it's all on De Niro's face. And then it could have been
anyone's boot. So De Niro is, by the way, the body posture, that's just De Niro. If you watch
Goodfellas, he does that. He does this weird thing where he curls his fists up. But he's able to
when he's telling the guy to get in the car, he kicks him. Right. Right. And then like there's
a part where he runs off the rocks like he's able to move around. It's just like there's something
weird in that scene where I feel like they had De Niro stomping. And then they said this is what
I think they did. I think they had him stomping. And then they said, we're going to insert the guy
under you so we can make it look like you're really stepping on his hand. OK. And then when
they did the composite, it just looks goofy. Yeah. It's weird in a movie with so much attention
detail that they wouldn't spend another 20 minutes on fixing that effect because it's bad.
Yeah, that was the that was the only thing in it that when I was like, you know, everything else
was just like the jarring is just is just I'm used to seeing him this way and now I'm seeing
my brain is going to have to just get used to that. But that was the only thing where I was
like, that looks kind of weird to me. It doesn't look right. And it's obvious, too, when when
like when Pacino gets in the there's like four scenes in this where Pacino fights on the ground
and it's clearly not Pacino. Right. Right. Right. So they did it with Pacino.
I don't know why they wouldn't have done it with De Niro, but that's the one thing that stood out
to me that was a little weird. I agree. Didn't really make sense. But but it doesn't ruin it
for me. No, by and large, they did a great job. I was always much happier when they were playing
their current age or older, because, look, you can't help but be thinking about that to some extent
while you're watching a 30 year old Joe Pesci talk on screen. But as they said in the thing,
you know, Scorsese is talking about all these great moments. He goes, Makeup went through
several developments. It was Dustin Hoffman, a little big man where he just looks like a raisin.
Then it was the elephant man where you're like, holy shit, this is amazing makeup. But you feel
John Hurt in there somewhere. Right. And he's like, I just had to look at this like makeup.
You know, we can do it. And Pacino's like, that's the only way I would do it. And Pesci's saying
I wasn't going to do these big dramatic speeches to Bobby De Niro when he's got 20 tennis balls
on his face. We got to find some new way to do it. So it didn't bug me. If it's the only way this
movie got made, I completely get it. But do I prefer Goodfellows where they show 30 years
past by putting two streaks of gray in De Niro's hair? Yeah, I do prefer that. But I get why that
was maybe not feasible for this. Anywho, the movie all builds up, I would say, to its most
effective section, which is the section where it deviates the most from Goodfellows and Casino.
And that would be the last hour where we're tracing just De Niro's very, very sad
realization that he has no family, no friends, really no anyone to be with him in his final days.
And that's the part that I thought made The Irishman feel very special and feel different
from the others. The others even make the downfall look glamorous and exciting and fun.
And you're all coked out and listening to Fleetwood Mac and whatever else. This is like a very sad,
pathetic old man who goes to visit his daughter at the bank and she puts up the next teller sign
and walks off. He can't connect with anybody. He's fucked his life up. And that, to me,
is what made the movie great. And the weird the weird.
I agree with that. I completely agree because I still I get I get very upset and angry in the
last acts of Goodfellows and Casino. I get mad at Henry Hill for fucking everything up. Yeah.
I get mad at Pesci for going too far. And you get that sick feeling when like he starts fucking
Sharon Stone and. Oh, yeah. And it ends so tragically, but both ends so tragically.
And this ends tragically in a different way. But this is the only one where you get you get a
little misty. You get a little teary at the end. It's very emotional. It's very sad.
But also another interesting aspect to this about this to me is when he says like
when the priest is like, did you do you feel for the families of the people you killed?
And he's like, I didn't know the families and he and you can he's not making an excuse.
He's saying flat out, like, I know I didn't know the families.
And it's interesting watching him at the end
because he's got this great rapport with everybody that he talks to in the home.
Yeah. So on the one hand, you're like.
He's alone and this should be sad, but on the other end, you're like,
he seems completely fine with it in a weird way. Right. When the priest is like,
I'll be back after Christmas. And he's like, is it Christmas?
Yeah. And he's like, yeah, almost.
He's like, hey, I'll be here. Like, yeah, it's just such an interesting demise of a man.
Felt to me like he had shut off his emotions to the extent that like he's just kind of
resigned to his life. And so be it. Right. Well, it keeps going back to the war
that keeps getting referenced. The Army was like the war, you know, you did,
you know, and he talks about how they would make them go into the woods and kill those guys.
But he says it's such an important line. And again, the first watch, whatever,
you know, it's going to fly by. But he says when he first meets Pesci and they're talking in the
restaurant, dipping the bread in the wine that when he after he was in the war, he was like,
after this, I don't care. It's nothing matters after. Right. As long as I can live.
And that's the that's the setup for the whole thing. He's like,
whatever I got to do to get by, it's OK. Yeah. Yeah. Pesci in that home stretch when he's
putting the bread in the wine and has trouble chewing it like because you can you can watch
Pesci again in this little 20 minute interview. And he looks you actually never see the real Joe
Pesci in this movie. He's always aged up or age. The real Joe Pesci is not really seen in this.
But when he is trying to eat the bread and like drooling a little bit and old or whatever,
that's the best Joe Pesci has ever been. That's where you're like, I'm watching a 90 year old man
and you see him and he's not that at all. I thought he was just getting up there,
to be honest. But he's he's he captures an old man better than almost anybody.
He's amazing. He came off the bench after. Yeah.
You know, I mean, he did that little shitty love shack. Whatever the fuck it was called.
Yeah, that did with Helen Mirren, you know, a few years back. And I mean,
but I mean, it got bombed. It got terrible reviews. But and I saw it. It sucked. But
I mean, this guy is essentially coming off the bench after 20 years. And dude,
an honest in honesty, more than 20 years, his last stretch of flicks before he retired,
you know, were like gone fishing and all that eight heads in a duffel bag. Yeah.
It's like this guy is coming off the fucking. But between watching these three movies,
stepping back being like, is Joe Pesci our finest American actor?
I mean, he's great. Yeah. And he can do comedy, drama, whatever.
Yeah. But one thing I wonder if the movie needed
and I guess it didn't because I loved it, but or maybe it did.
I wonder if there should have been one scene where Pesci flips.
Just so you knew how fucking dangerous this guy truly was. The writer said they put that scene in
after the fact where he has blood on his shirt. Yeah.
Because they were Scorsese was like, we need a scene where you see that this guy is dangerous.
Like, you know, it can't just be that he's not this nice old man. Yeah.
But I wonder if there should have been one because like I kept thinking of the scene
and made with Peter Falk where he's being like really sweet to John Favreau and then John Favreau
gets like a little defiant about the assignment Peter Falk gives him.
And then like Peter Falk is like, hey, what the fuck do you think you're talking?
What is this a fucking democracy? And like three lines and you're like,
oh shit, this guy, you don't you shouldn't fuck with this guy. He's my boss.
I wonder if there there there should have been one scene where you saw Pesci do that,
just so you knew this guy was by the way.
Maybe, maybe not. But speaking of one scene, significant scenes,
fucking Kytel coming in. Kytel kills it. Kytel is awesome in that scene.
He's fucking awesome. Yeah, looks great, too.
He's awesome. The oh my God. And I loved I thought Sebastian did a great job as Joey
Gallagher. He was fucking great. Jim Norton as Don Rickles.
Yes, Norton as Rickles. I mean, there there's so many just fun little things in this movie.
I think there's so much to recommend about it and people just being like, it sucks.
You know, it's just fucking stupid. You know, like you're just not willing to put the time in
to understand a really good, deep, thoughtful movie. And I at the same time, I get why people
wouldn't like it. I think it is self -indulgent. I think it is at three and a half hours way too
long. There are many times where something is said four times that could have been said two.
And given the same effect. And yet it's like Ebert said, no bad movie can be too short.
No good movie can be too long. Very, very true. When something is great, I can watch it for hours
and not care. And that's how I felt both times watching this. It's a very good movie.
Yes. Two Hogs firmly up. Two Hogs firm and up.
For the Irishman. Our next episode, although I believe we'll probably release these two on
the same day as we've been doing, will be, if you want to do a little homework, Doctor Sleep,
a movie that will probably be available to you on demand and on Blu -ray, et cetera, by the time we
release this. So check it out. Yes, that is, of course, unless we split these apart and release
them at different times. Exactly. Confusing you even further. But the podcast will continue.
Be sure to check us out on Etsy at the hawkhouse .com. If you want some merch,
be sure to check out the Facebook page. Be sure to look out for people on Facebook and Twitter
who don't know we've moved to Patreon. I find myself sliding into some DMs every day and telling
people, hey, just so you know, this is what happened. Now, my question is, are the dick pics
necessary? Not necessary, but I also haven't heard any complaints.
No. So if you see somebody out there still every day, people pop into Facebook and say, hey,
where did the podcast go? Just tell them and don't make them feel stupid. They clearly don't know.
I'm at the Patrick Walsh of Twitter and Instagram. That's all I have to say.
Uh, Joe DeRosa, uh, sorry, Joe DeRosa Comedy at Instagram and Twitter, Joe DeRosa Comedian
on Facebook. That's all I have to say. We'll see you next time.