I'll see you next time!
Hello, hello, hello, hello, everybody.
Welcome to another episode of, we'll see you and hell.
this is Joe DeRosa on one side of your head and I am Patrick Walsh on the
other side of your head. We'll see you in hell. The podcast is now a part of the
Fangoria podcast network for more information about the network including
other programs, how to follow the show, and to find past episodes of we'll see
you in hell. Please visit Fangoria .com now on with the show. For those of you just
tuning in for the first time, the reason we're split on either side of you is
because this is a commentary podcast and if you want to watch the movie along with
what we're about to do, you can kind of just send that up the middle and you
got us on either side just like in real life. If you're watching a movie with Pat
and me, you'd be right between us on this love seat we're sitting on right now.
Maybe I sort of find my hand sliding into your pants, rummaging around,
liking what I see. Maybe the lights go out. Maybe Joe's hand reaches into the other
side of your pants. Which side of the pants were you in? I'm in the right side of
your pants. I'm in the back side. Oh, okay. I go right for the back hole. Wow.
All right. Yeah. Do you lick the fingers or just jam it home after or before? Well,
folks grossed out. These are the jokes you're going to get on this show. We always start
real blue and then smooth out to much more clever stuff. Maybe it's an attention
grabber. Well, that is what it is. It is what it is. Usually in the stand -up
world, they tell you to close with sex. Yeah. We've been opening with it. Sometimes
pedophilia bits. Right. Anyway, here we are in the show. This little preamble time is
the time for you to go to your Netflix account, boot it up, find the movie
scream. That's what we're doing today, and tribute to the late great West Craven.
Yeah. Sad lost to the community. Very sad. I mean, in terms of horror, like, you know,
who better? The guy did minute, well, minimum two masterpieces, I would say.
And I have an Elm Street and I would say scream is definitely a modern horror comedy
masterpiece. I'm going to give a four masterpieces. Keep going. Last house in the
left. The original. Very disturbing. Great film. Sure. They'll have eyes. They'll
realize. Yes. Nightwear in Elm Street. Okay. Scream. That's four. That's fair. And I
think, you know, people were there. Serpent in the rainbow. You know, I've never seen
that. But I heard that Bill Pullman gets a scrotum nailed to a chair. That's
pretty intense movie. You know, some people were tweeting us and that, you know, the tweets,
I think, were probably pretty lighthearted and funny, but it was kind of like, hey, guys,
why are you talking shit about West Craven? He just died. We didn't know that he was going
to die. And all we really did was praise. Nightwear on Elm Street. There might have been
a few quips at his expense. But of course, we love West Craven. We were talking shit
about music at the heart. It's what we were doing. I don't even, were we? Yeah. The
Meryl Streep. That's his one kind of stab, pardon the pun, at drama. I'm not going back
and saying I like music at the heart now. I'm not either guy passed away. I'm terribly
sad. He died. But it doesn't mean I'm going to like music at the heart now. No. And when
I die, I don't want somebody to be like, you know, I'm sorry. I talked shit about pat
shitting his pants at that little league game. He should have talked shit about me shitting
my pants at that little league game. Yeah. And also, you know, I love Sam Remy. When
Sam Remy dies, I'm not going to, I'm not going to praise Oz, the great and powerful.
Oh, no. Now, what a piece of shit that was. Sorry, Sam Remy. Now, where do you think they
went wrong with that movie when they cast James Franco as a wizard? Yeah, just just terrible
casting. I saw it in 3D, which to me, elevates almost any movie. And I just hated it so
much. Was it who was the other one? Mila Kunis was Dorothy? No, Mila Kunis. Dorothy's
not in it. Mila Kunis was the wicked witch of the West. Who there was no Dorothy? No, because
it's before Dorothy came. Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, sort of like a almost like wicked, but nowhere
near as God was bad. My favorite Sam Remy is a simple plan. I think it's one of the most
underrated movies of all time. Well, no. I mean, my favorite Sam Remy is Evil Dead, too,
without question. Love it. Keep it in the genre for this podcast. I don't
have to. You can't tell me what to do. All right. Guys, what we're going to do, and we finally
learn that we're just going to really quickly gloss over this part of the podcast because
it's so insanely boring. Bring up scream on your Netflix instant or even a Blu -ray DVD would
have. They should have done it already. Yeah, or you should have done it already. Yeah.
And basically, you're going to hit play in an immediate pause. Yeah. So everybody in different
load times, then we're going to go one, two, three, play and we all start washing it together.
It's just that easy. It's that easy. So if you've hit play and you're all paused up now,
here we go. Here we go. We've given everybody enough time. Ample. Yeah. And also they could
have paused it if they needed to by now. All right. Here we go. Let your coming around. One,
two, three, play. Now, right here, you should be seeing your mirror max screen, mirror max.
Yeah. Exactly. Everyone mirror max would like make all the good movies. And now they just
make movies where it's like, give me an Oscar. What do they make now? I haven't seen
it. They made like the fucking artist. You know, like they make movies that they get
Oscar whipped into excitement about by saying like, hey, like we got this, you know, like holding
these big expensive screenings and all this shit. And then no one ever remembers them again.
They're movies that don't stand the test of time. And they used to make only movies that
stood the test of time. It's not the same company since the Weinstein's
left. Well, no, do they leave? I think so because yeah, because now they have Harvey Weinstein
is, it's like Weinstein productions. Oh, right. Or whatever. Yeah. I mean, they had, they
had women to beat. Did he beat a woman? No, I've heard, I've heard tales. Let's move past.
I'm trying to work on this business. Let's say we'll say allegedly. Allegedly. Oh, no, it's
truly allegedly because all I do is hear shit. Okay. This is one of, and I'm not, I'm not
just saying horror here. This is one of the greatest opening sequences in the history of
film in my opinion. This is a brutal, brutal sequence. That's what people forget. It's
so fun. You forget how like really disturbing it is. Yeah. When, when, when old ghost face
killer, which by the way, did they name that after the rapper? Did the rapper name himself after
scream? No, his name was ghost face killer. Well, before this, I don't think there was any
tie -in, probably, but I don't know that. The rapper ghost face got his name from like a kung -fu
thing, right? Yeah, yeah, exactly. Okay. Drew Barry. Terrific rapper. Fish scale, one of my favorite
rap albums. Terrific. Yeah. Drew Barrymore in this opening scene here never looked
better. You know, she has truly never looked better. This is an incredible, like there,
I guess there's a bra, but if there is, you, you're not really saying it. I mean, this was,
she was a gem, just unbelievable. Who, who, who, who would have believed she was a crack
addict at six or whatever the hell she was doing? Who would have believed she was hitting the
pipe with ET and a pile of clothes and a closet somewhere? Straightened out. One of my favorite
things I ever saw Bill Murray do was at the SNL, 25th anniversary special. Saw it. When
he went up to her and the audience and he said, we're so glad you cleaned up. Yeah. I remember
that well. And she laughed, which shows that she's cool. Yeah. It's awesome. I think she would
have laughed at my crack bit. I think so too. I think so too. I love her and she never quite
gets the material she deserves. I think, but like, you know, wedding singer, whatever, she's
just a lovable person. She's a dream in wedding singer. Yeah, she's great. In wedding singer,
I mean, I wanted to be my wife, immediately. Sure. Her name was Julia Goolea, which is still
a very funny bit. Julia Goolea. Yeah. No, she's, she goes, her name is Julia and she's
going to be marrying this guy named like Ron Goolea. And then Santa's like, so your name's
going to be Julia Goolea. Oh, it's real fun. My friend Julia spells her name with a G. So
it looks like you should say Goolea, but it's pronounced Julia. Okay. So maybe let's get
around the podcast to discuss that. Maybe when we do a podcast for the name, for the weird
names network, we'll do that. What I love. So I, yeah, I've been reading some feedback today is
some of you are like, talk about the movie, talk more about the movie. And some of you are
like, it's, it's funny hearing you guys riff on shit, whatever. We're really trying to do
a blend. And maybe that's not going to please everybody, but it's pleasing us. And hopefully
the majority of the listeners, we want to podcast. You can listen to in your car on the
way to work. We also want to podcast. If you're alone on a Friday with no date, no friends,
you can watch a movie and feel like you're watching a movie with some pals. That's it. Well,
I agree. This is, this is, this is the conversation that you'd have if you were watching with friends.
It's not, yeah, we're not the fucking directors. You want a real commentary, put the fucking commentary
on your nerd. Just Christ. By the way, you and I could do that. We could talk about various
specific shots, angles, filters, I went to fucking film school. But you know, what you can watch
the commentary on the Blu -ray. You went to film school? Yeah, I went to film school. Because I mean,
I was, you know, we had a small problem with the recorder before the podcast. And Pat didn't even know.
I said, look at track four and tell me what's happening. He's looking at the master output track. What I
did was I went to one of the least prestigious film schools in the country, Webster University. It is
actually a very good film school. But I learned everything basically six minutes before it turned
digital. So I learned how to like, he's two pieces of film together, like I'm film a shoot marker.
I don't know that too. Scorsese editor. I know how to do that too. Okay. I mean, I still know how to
differentiate between track four and the master output. Right. What I, what I do and it's helped me
immeasurably with my obsessive brain is to let go of things I don't need anymore. So when I started
writing, I focused all my energies on writing and learning about the craft of writing and I let go the
audio technical shit that is handled and should be handled by technical professionals. Even if I want
to be a director, I'd rather handle the actors and let some nerd handle the camera. Truly. That was
she's been getting prank called by the the murderer. Yeah. And the prank crawls got more and more
intense and now he's telling her he wanted, well, he just told her he wanted to see what her insights
looked like and she's crying. What do you, what do you think? Real tears? You think these are movie tears.
Probably movie tears. You think she can cry out cute? She might be able to, she's had some darkness.
She's great in the scene. Do you find the voice hearing it now too much or just right or not enough?
What voice? The like, the killer's voice. What do you mean am I hearing it just enough?
I mean, I'm saying do you think it's a little over the top or a little under the top? I never liked
the voice. It's not great. I never liked the killer's voice for two reasons. It sounds
smarmy to me as opposed to like really menacing. Well, also, you know, at the end of the movie when they
reveal who the killer is, I won't give it away in case you haven't seen this film yet. But then he
just speaks through that like dime store voice thing and it just makes his voice like it's ridiculous.
Right. It's not even, there's, there's no technology to this day that could do that. Yeah.
You know, you can change the pitch of your voice, but you can't change the complete like
tamber of the voice. For sure. You can't change the Jeffrey tamber of your voice. How'd you like that
word? Tamber. I liked it in audio school. I recently read a very heavily circulated interview
with Quentin Tarantino, who is of course, one of almost everybody's favorite writer directors.
And I love hearing him talk about movies. I remember I saw him on Charlie Rose, decades ago,
and Charlie Rose was like, what are your favorite movies of the year? And he goes number one,
no question. My best friend's wedding. And I was like, get out of here. What the hell is going on?
He also once said that Psycho 2 is better than Psycho. I mean, just ridiculous shit. But you know
what? I love it. And I always love his like alternate opinions on shit. But he was talking about
scream, like, and this interview came out two days before Wes Craven. And he was talking about how
shitty Wes Craven's direction of scream was. And he's just wrong. Yeah. This is such a tense and
effective sequence. He's let alone the rest of the movie. But like, this movie balances horror and
comedy in a really pretty special way, which is my point about the Quentin Tarantino. I love Quentin
Tarantino's work. But I think he just says things to be inflammatory in interviews. I don't believe
that he really thinks Psycho 2 is better than Psycho. I don't really believe he thought the
lone ranger was one of the best films of 2013. I enjoyed the lone ranger. I didn't get deserve to get
bashed. I didn't say it. But it was not one of the best films of 2013. As an absurd statement.
I disagree. And I think he sees things in a very different way. And I think he
he loves trash as much as high art. And I think that's just I always love reading his opinions on
my best friend's wedding is his favorite film of all time. No, no, that year. But I love the work
of Sam Fuller. And come on, man. Yeah. I just think he has he sees things different. That's all I can
say. I dig what he does. I love reading about his opinions because they're always so weird. Now
the murderer here had Drew Barrymore's boyfriend taped to a chair outside, right?
Boy, if it looked like Frank Whaley, I guess it was not Frank Whaley. It might have been Frank Whaley.
You know, he turns up into some small parts sometimes. Sure. Uh, great actor. I can't believe
this kid was still wearing was still wearing a letterman jacket. Yeah. We came out in 1997,
didn't it? It did. 96 96. Yeah. Um, the kid was really sticking with it. Now, I'll tell you mine
and then you tell me yours. I, because I remember exactly when I first saw this movie, I
had a first date with a young, I won't say her name, but a young woman who became my girlfriend. And
we saw Scramon came in after this sequence. After this, she didn't see the chair get to the window.
She was holding. She was like, I'm not ready. I'm not ready. I'm not ready. I wanted to see it so
bad and I come in basically at the very end of this. This is what everybody talked about. Before I
saw it, everybody I knew that saw it and in the right ups and everything were the opening sequence,
the opening sequence. Yeah. That's why I was infuriated that I missed it. And then also that it drew
Barrymore, you know, who was, who was passed her comeback trail at this point. She was reestablished
as a celebrity at this point. Yeah. And she's just in this opening 15 minutes, whatever it is.
And then gets sliced to pieces. Yeah. I mean, it's a nod to Psycho where you kill off your star right
off the bat. Blonde. This movie was written by Kevin Williamson, who would go on to create Dawson's
Creek, unless he did it before. I don't think he did. Uh, which as a show, I also fucking loved and could
not get enough of. And I love that the lead was obsessed with movies. Dawson, Larry wanted to be
a director. You know, I related to that in high school. I'd watch it every week. If Quentin Tarantino
was here, he'd go, best Kevin Williamson thing, the faculty, uh, the faculty really sucked in.
Well, that that's what the Tarantino would say was the best. You might be right. Uh, I never noticed
this before that she lit or she's, I can't remember she lives in this house or if she's just
house sitting or whatever. I gotta say it doesn't look like they should be living next to that.
Yeah. I didn't. I didn't notice they lived in front of this cornfield. What the hell do you think's
going to happen? And you know, I watched parenthood the other day, which I think is such a fucking great
movie. And we talked about it when we discussed Hannah and her sisters. Uh, but I think it's so great.
And at some point, because it was, it was set in St. Louis, you realize their backyard is like
up against a river. And I never noticed that when I was a kid and that makes no sense either.
You got to look at your surroundings. Isn't there a St. Louis river? Well, the Mississippi is
disgusting, but I don't feel like people are going to live alongside of it, but maybe I'm wrong.
Now here's where Barrymore eats it. I mean, that shed alone, the first stab is pretty brutally.
It comes around the back. You see the knife going and then then he gets on top of her and just starts
stabbing her to death. First it's a shock. Well, the shot of her coming up where she's hanging with her
insides, falling out is real rough. Yeah, I mean, but this, the stabbing in here is so, it's so violent.
It's so, it actually, here's what's disturbing about it. I would imagine it's like if you really had
to stab somebody to death, that's how you'd have to do it. Yeah. It wouldn't be like an easy thing to do.
I mean, there's, well, let's find out. You want to stab me real quick and see.
I thought you'd never ask. Since the day we met, now here's the problem. If you get stabbed
to death, they're going to think I did it. Right. You know, not tonight. 10 years down the line. Whatever.
Here's the thing. Back to the voice of the killer. The device that the killer pulls out at the end
that he shows us his voice distortion device. Yeah. If he actually used the real voice that that
thing gives you, yeah, it's 20 times scarier. It's like this. I agree. We swap monster voice. It's
really freaky. And, you know, in a movie like this, they must have gone over that forever and ever
getting the voice just right, but they didn't get it just right. You know, he sounds almost like a douche.
He's like, hey, it's just not menacing. It sounds very douchey to me. It's a, it's almost like a movie
phone kind of voice or something. Yeah, yeah, yeah. You know, but I mean, look, I guess it works because
everybody really liked it through the whole series that, you know, right, it's stuck. Me and my
friends in high school were obsessed with calling movie phone during the period of time where the
shorts and anger vehicle end of days came out. Right. Because sometimes they'd have the actors record
a little. Here we go. Oh, boy. Is this where Drew's got her guts hanging out? Yeah. Because the mom
just screamed. Oh, yeah, look at that. They're all down her leg. She's hanging from the tree. That's
something movie open. See, I think they should have saved the title card for after she's hanging in
the tree. Joe, I agree. 20 million percent with you. That, that, that screams should have just
bammed into the screen right now. Right. Um, okay. So they used to have stars sometimes record their
own movie phone promos and they had Schwarzenegger do one and it was, if I had a recording of it now,
I would still listen to it five times today. It was so funny. Excuse my subpar impression of Schwarzenegger,
but here's what it was. He would go on November 24th. Get ready. Prepare for the end of days.
And my friends listen to this thing and laugh endlessly. It was so ridiculous and you pictured him
in a recording booth with the headset screaming prepare for the end of days. One of the least scary
movies ever made. And we really had a good time. Now, was he trying to be scarier? Do you think he was
having a laugh? No, I don't think he was having a laugh. Because I think Schwarzenegger is kind of
in on the now, like now. That's a good point. After he was coming. By the way, end of days sucks.
I never, that was the beginning of the end. Yeah. That was, I remember it was end of days and then like
a racer, a racer really sucked, your luggage. And when he shoots the crocodile, yeah. And then, uh,
you know what is kind of an entertaining movie is the one with the collateral damage.
Oh no, what's the one where it's got like a science element?
The sixth man. Oh, okay, with the semi -fowl. Wait, there's the sixth man. The basketball movie where
Marlon Wayne's is like a ghost. I think it is. I'm thinking about the one with Bobby DeVol.
And it's got a science fiction element. And it's Schwarzenegger. I feel like it's called the
something man, though. Uh, the six. Shit. Again, you know, nerds are screaming. It's this. Oh,
wait, I can look it up. I forgot. We're not making fun of you. We're all nerds. I like this. I like
the choices here for, uh, what's this girl's name again? Because she's Nev Campbell. Nev Campbell. I
was called her lift Tyler. Nev Campbell in this 57 year old woman trailer park robe. They got her in.
I love this. Yeah. And then the big poster in her wall is Indigo girls. Well, yeah, exactly.
Because she know how all my school kids, well, you know, going for Indigo girls.
One of the most attractive girls I ever know, I ever knew took me to an Indigo girls concert.
So I don't think that's mutually exclusive. Nev Campbell, for my money, is about as beautiful as you
can do. Yeah, she's, she's a dream. And she still looks pretty much the same. And you know, you couldn't
call her like an amazing actress, but she's very competent. Like you never are like that scene sucked.
She's very charming. Actually, I, she really gained, I always respected her, but she really gained my
acting respect when I saw very good shot here. That movie where she got naked, uh, that James
toe back toe back movie. Yeah. And she played like a real shitty fucking, yeah, I was really rotten in
that. And I liked her quite a bit because I believed her as a shitty person. Yeah. And I love that,
you know, like anytime anybody takes a chance on Nev Campbell, she brings it. The six day, six day,
there you go. And six man is Marlon Wayne's ghost basketball player. Yes. And the sixth sense is we're
Marlon Wayne's as a ghost that Hayley Jolosment can see. Yeah. Exactly. Yeah. Okay. We got it. We figured
it out. Uh, and Drake is running through the six with his was. Yeah. That clears up everything.
I also didn't know this just while I'm on his page. Arnold Schwarzenegger was also apparently in
around the world in 80 days. I think like a thousand people had came as I never saw that. He's in the
Jackie Chan version. Right. His character's name is Prince Happy. Oh my god. And then that was it.
Then it was governor for six years. And then boom, expendable. She's back in action. Sure.
The, what I love now is, uh, in LA, I have a picture of it that I saved. There's a billboard.
Uh, and it has like 80 people on it. And it's the cast of the expendables three. There's so many.
I'm like, am I in the expendals three? I was looking for my own face. The, uh, I like, I never realized
this until as we watch it now. We had, we, you know, skied all rich was just in that scene playing
the Nev Campbell's boyfriend. Never to be seen after, you know, 2000. Who the hell knows where he is. But,
uh, you know, everybody used to make the joke that he was Johnny Depp's carbon copy. Yeah. We talked about
it on the nightmare podcast. And there you go. West Craven breaking in Depp and Ulrich. Yeah.
I mean, this, this movie has some pretty clear nods tonight. We're on Elm Street. Yeah. Well, Nancy
wore a similar, uh, robe or gown that to the one that Nev Campbell was wearing. Nev Campbell has
a bit of a Nancy quality. Very naturally pretty. She's just beautiful. Skied Ulrich, uh, I remember
was in a movie. This, I think is what killed his career. It was called chill factor. And it was him
in Cuba getting junior driving around a ice cream truck that was rigged to explode.
That's an actual movie that got a theatrical release. I saw it and it wasn't. Nobody said this is
just speed. Oh, it was clearly a speed ripoff. It was just such a terrible, terrible movie.
Cuba getting junior, that guy wins an Oscar. Then for the next 10 years, it was like boat trip,
chill factor, snow dogs. Who's ever had a worse agent than Cuba getting junior?
Well, I mean, who knows if it was the agent or maybe it was him just saying, I'll do it, I'll do it,
I'll do it. Yeah, they might have been like, we'll give him five million dollars. That's the thing.
One of the best interviews I ever saw was Samuel Jackson on Letterman. And he goes, you know,
you're in every movie, Sam. You're in every single movie that comes out. It's great. Why do you take
every job that comes down the pipe? Right. And he goes, well, Dave, let me ask you this.
Somebody offers you five million dollars to spend six weeks in Hawaii. Would you take it?
And I was like, Sam, I respect it. I do. Well, that's what IceT said when he came and spoke at my
school. Well, Henry Winks. I love Henry Winkler. I've heard one of the nicest men there is in
all of Hollywood. I've heard that too. I forgot he was in this movie too right now. Yeah. And it just
made me very happy. The IceT came and spoke at my college and he said, he said, I made four movies
this year. They'll be coming out at a liquor store near you. Yeah, that's good. And then everybody
laughed and he goes, look, I know I don't make the greatest movies. But let me, he's like, I'll tell you
something. When you lived in the ghetto and you'd had nothing. Sure. And somebody comes along and
says, we'll give you a couple of million dollars to make a fucking movie. He goes, he did be pretty
fucking ignorant to say no to that. And I was like, all right, I get it. That's some fucking true
ass shit. And then you get some money. And then you can, you know, do your more artistic kind of stuff.
Do whatever you want. I completely agree. Do whatever you want.
You know how they're all the high school kids sitting around a fountain. Not every high school just
had a fountain outside of it. Yeah. My school had like a pit, I think. My school was up against this
place called Bush Wildlife, which was a wildlife reserve where kids would go finger each other.
And I remember we were terrified, much like in scream for about a six month period. Because a
child molester slash murderer named Michael Jackson was on the prowl. And at the time,
everyone was like, oh my god. Can you believe his name is Michael Jackson? Because no one associated
Michael Jackson with pedophilia at all. It was just like, can you imagine how embarrassed Michael
Jackson would be if someone made the suggestion that he was a pedophile. That's how young and you
guys found out it was actually Michael Jackson. Yeah. It was him. He was in the woods. A boom.
Now Matthew Lillard is recently making kind of an indie comeback because I see him in indie trailers
a lot. So I'm glad to see he's still working even though. Yes. And I like Matthew Lillard. I find him
very funny. I thought he was really funny in the Scooby -Doo movies. I didn't see him. Jamie Kennedy.
I'm not complaining that I don't see him everywhere anymore. No, it's fine. I don't do see any more break
dance comedies with Jamie Kennedy. Malibu's most wanted. Is that what you're talking about?
I think so. Yeah. One of those things he did, you know. Rose McGowan's a stone fox to this day.
Truly miss. I truly miss Rose McGowan. Where has she been? I mean, I say this with all due respect.
Maybe the greatest rack I've ever seen in my life. She's the kind of gal I don't know if you could
really handle almost. And as she gets older, she gets better looking and it's almost frightening.
She dated Marilyn Manson. I mean, she's long for a nice. She's in for a ride if you're ready to take
it. Sure. If you're ready to take it. Jawbreaker. Remember that movie? Yeah. I mean, she was kind of a
wrestling movie. Ready to rumble, baby. Which has one of the funniest lines I've ever heard in a movie
ever. Wow, you're blowing my mind now. Now you sound like one Tarantino, but go on.
It's when they find all the replat in the sewer. And don't remember the construction guy that finds him
has a really high pitch voice. He's also in the movie Fatso, which is one of my favorite films of all time.
And he goes, David Arquette goes, where did you find him? And the construction guy goes,
we found him in drain 28. He didn't want to leave. That's that's good. It's hilarious.
It's not enough to make me watch ready to rumble again, but it sounds like a fun thing. Whenever I see
it on, I'll fast forward to that part and watch it. And then I also always watch the part with
what's his name? The distinguished actor that was in the crimes and misdemeanors.
Martin Landau. Martin Landau. That scene is terrific. Also in Baps, Black American Princess,
the star in Hallibar. That's how big a career swing that guy's had. But he's really funny in that
scene where he's the wrestling trainer. Yeah. And they think they killed him and they go, they get
real close to him. And then he goes, and he comes awake like a snake. Yeah. That's always funny.
They do that in the throw mama from the train. Yeah, I remember them. There's a lot of moves.
I used to wonder, like, how did this movie that is like an F minus get like five jokes that are
A pluses? And then you realize it's something I actually do fairly often as you go to movie punchups.
And they get, you know, I'm not trying to do my own horn, but they get really funny writers to
come in for one day and they pay you pretty well. And you add like 15, 20 jokes to a movie script.
And they take them or leave them. And I've been and I'm like, can you get me in on one of the,
I've been trying to, I mean, I've been betraying. I wanted to do that. I think I'd be good at that.
I do them. I'm not allowed to say, you know, which movies and stuff I do them whenever I have free time.
And throw my name in one of those. I absolutely will. I've been in them with the great Pat
and Oswald. Yeah. You know, they get kind of big people. And you know, you're just, you're looking at
a script and you're like, well, this is the worst script I've ever read. Sometimes they're funny,
but you know, a lot of times they're not. And you go in, you just, you throw in these great jokes.
And that's how movies get like amazing jokes sprinkled in with the shit. Well, I guess that
happened with ready to rumble. I can almost guarantee it. A choice for Oliver Platt. Yeah.
Well, I mean, the 90s was a, was a big time for, like, like movies that looked bad and would be
really funny. Like, I remember sugar and spice this cheerleading movie. My buddy and I were like,
you know, bringing all was funny. We'll see sugar and spice. Was that the one where they like robbed
the bank or something? Yeah. And I was just like, holy shit. Like, there's amazing jokes on this.
I think Josie and the pussycats is one of the most subversive funny movies ever made. And it was so
nasty to its target audience. That's great. You almost couldn't believe it. It was shocking. I felt
it was a perfect example, Joe. I thought they were, I thought they were phenomenal. They're really
funny. And like the dark, the, I already mentioned it. I like the first Scooby Doo movie quite a bit.
It was very, you know what? I was very funny. I know James Gunn wrote it, who's a guy I'm a fan of
and who's now a huge director because of Guardians of the Galaxy. Sure. And I'm going to rent it
and watch it because I've never seen it. It's very funny. It's very funny. Great. And there's
actually pot humor in it, which is weird. Well, I thought the cartoon always had an element of that.
My friend made a good point. We saw him in the theater and he turned to me and he goes,
what do you do? They make a joke like, you know, shaggy's like, he meets a girl he loves or something.
And she's like, hi, my name's Mary Jane and the whole theater erupts at the laughter.
And my friend turns to me and he goes, what do you do when your six -year -old says, why is that funny?
Yeah. And I was like, I don't know, man. That made me respect that they put it in there though.
I always wonder that. I worked with a woman who has like an eight -year -old son and he's always
asking her questions and, you know, what does that mean? What is this? And my parents never used
to tell me, which makes it all the more alluring. There's this joke in the naked gun where there's
a really tall guy. Yeah. And he goes, you got something in the corner of your mouth. Yeah, it's
correct. And a half a banana falls out. Right. And to this day, I don't necessarily get it, but I asked
my mom like, why is that funny? And she was so weirdly tight -lipped about it that I assumed it was
some filthy dick joke. But all it is is that the guy's so tall that when he's got something on
the side of his mouth, it's half a banana. I get it. He's still not get that. That's what the joke is.
I just think it's kind of like not worth the squeeze, I guess. It's a hilarious joke.
Because you have something to study about. And then he goes, no, the other side. Yeah.
And then the clump of banana. Yeah, no, it's a decent joke. And I think the naked gun is about as funny
as it gets. But I was always so baffled by it and my mom's refusal to answer me made me think it was
some really disgusting dick joke that it's not. You know what joke I never got in that movie?
Go on. When she's up on the ladder and he goes, nice ankle bracelet. And she goes, oh,
did that slide down there again? I never understood what that meant. That used to make me laugh because you
just picture the bracelet making that journey from her ankle to her from her wrist to her ankle. But
they are really weird jokes that I think probably could have benefited from. You know, give me an
insert shot of her slipping it back to the wrist. Sure. Okay. I mean, they can't all be, you know,
as as classic as nice beaver. Thank you. I just had it stuffed. Which is real good.
Well, now even when I was a kid, I was like, I get that one. To me, the, I mean, one of the funniest
sequences in movie history is a naked gun two and a half, which I might even prefer to the
first or their real close, who lays a much better villain. But I mean, from start to finish that
sequence where he's in the bar drinking because he's all busted up over. Oh, it's great. I mean,
it's just joke after joke. I haven't had this much sex since I was a boy scout leader. I mean,
at the time, I was dating a lot. My aunt took me to see two movies. I was not allowed to see
because there were PG 13 naked gun two and a half and problem child two back -to -back, both hilarious.
I never saw any of the problem childs. Problem child one is great mostly because of
Ritter and Michael Richards and Jack Warden and problem child two is great because it's like really
gross and goes to like really fucked up places. The guy who wrote the guys who wrote Ed Wood,
man on the moon, people versus Larry Flint, they wrote the two problem child movies.
When I was in at the Montreal Just For Last Comedy Festival, I was one of the roasters
for Gilbert Godfrey Roast they did. And my whole closing thing was building up Gilbert like
what an artist he was. And then my example was, let me tell you what an RCS. Not only was he in
problem childs one and two. He was the only cast member to return for problem child three and four.
That's true. Not even the kid eventually said no enough. You know what?
I got other commitments. Yeah. Yeah. Michael Oliver. And then he went on to be in the problem child
TV series. Yeah. Yeah. They were at least as recently as six months ago, still trying to reboot
problem child. But I guess the pilot didn't go. I don't know. What are you gonna do? By the way,
back to the movie. Yeah. We're way off track. We always do.
Neve Campbell Sydney, as she's called, there's the ghost face killers in her house now trying to kill her.
And she just, what is the, did we really miss something? I forgot that she had like some kind of
phone thing on her computer. Yeah. For a deaf caller. Right. Exactly. What's weird to me is,
I recently went to my buddy Ian's bachelor party. And I think he was so adamant about not, you know,
like banging a hooker or something, which is great. But he was so adamant about being good that we wound
up playing it a little too safe. And we spent the Saturday night as bachelor party watching scream too.
And the hotel room suite. But we all had a great time. We kind of provided our own commentary for it
then. Scream one looks so much more modern than scream too, which was one of the most data -looking
movies I've ever seen. Really? It was so, it was 90s to the point where like you were embarrassed for
what you used to wear back in those days. And this looks reasonably modern to me. Scream. Yeah. Now,
it's, well, that's like the nightmare in Austria series too. The first one, more or less, you know,
you can tell it's an older film, but nothing is too out of whack. Yeah. You get into two and three.
I mean, it starts to look real age. Yeah. Our, I just got an email about David, or from David
Arkett or about David Arkett saying, give me work. No, it was a, an email. And, you know, I never know
how I get these things. I guess probably from seeing a concert or something. But it was like two weeks
only at the, like the Burbank Playhouse. David Arkett is Sherlock Holmes. Oh, boy. And I thought,
who's going to sing it? What, what is it? A one man show? It felt there was no other cast members.
I feel like it might be like the, the Holmes monologues starring David Arkett as Sherlock Holmes.
Hey folks, I'd rather see the vagina monologues. And you know how I feel about that? Sure.
I mean, for me, the issue is all about appropriate miking. You know, a lot of times the vagina
gets up on stage and it's not projecting the way you want it. Now has nobody done that as a sketch yet
where they go to see the vagina monologues. It's just women creeping into microphones.
How has that not been made? Maybe they have. But it had, I'm telling you it hasn't. All right,
well, let's do it. Oh my God. Let's get run out of town. All right. Nobody gets to do it. Courtney
Cox still in this highlighter knee on yellow. This, this is the one true 90s thing. I mean,
that's just an absurd dress she's wearing. But I think it's also because she's like this sensationalist
reporter. I think it's, yeah, scream had a lot to say. You know, and I will say it's an oddly
prescient movie with this character in her obsession with not the news, but like the sensationalism
of it. It's a little ahead of its time. Well, it's great to see movies that are entertaining in one
fashion. And then beneath the surface, there's this whole other thing. I mean, it's the
Anchorman to brilliant commentary on news on monitoring news. Yeah, I could just all wrapped up in
this big Will Farrell Joe. So I, I will say, you know, Anchorman to is one of the most curiously
stepped on neglected underrated movies that there is. It's not the first one. But the fact that it
was just kind of brushed aside so easily is very baffling to me because I thought it was really great.
I don't understand why they released the theater version that they did. All that was weird. The alternate
version on Netflix was, was the movie you wanted. And it was 10 times better. And I'm like, why wasn't
this the theatrical version? I own them both. And I couldn't tell you why. I don't, I don't know.
It doesn't make sense. Here's another, you know, I'd say nod to Nightmare and Elm Street. Now you're,
you know, you got the kids in the police station. Yeah. You got the sheriff that's onto, you know,
what the hell's going on around here? Right. I don't want you hanging around with your boyfriend.
This kid might be bad news. What did he do? This is like when Rod gets accused in the first one.
All right. Nightmare and Elm Street, excuse me. I don't remember thinking this at the time,
but I just watched Ulrich deliver that line. And it was bad. Was it? It looked like when you see
an audition tape on a DVD. It was terrible. Look at this face. I mean, look at that face. How do you
say no to that face? Is this guy supposed to be his dad? I look at this guy. They were supposed to
believe this guy birthed. It looks like that guy played bass in like the outfield or the psychedelic
furs or like some, some 80s kind of off the beaten path band. I mean, there is a strange similarity
between him and this guy would be Danny Brad today, playing this role. Is that?
What? It's not the guy who like played, he played meatloaf in the TV movie. And so I haven't,
we're not getting a good look at his face, the cameraman. They made a TV movie about meatloaf. Yeah.
Yeah, they did. What was it called? Let me guess bad out of hell. Yeah, it's pretty meatloaf. I think
it was that it was a VH one kind of deal. What is the story? Who gives a shit? Hey, here's my review.
I would do anything for love, but I won't watch that. Here's my review. Yeah, I'd rather watch a
piece of actual meatloaf. There you go. That's my bid. Look, we both strong. What are we listening to?
My phone over there is buzzing. That's your phone ring. Yeah, it's buzzing. It's a vibration. Oh my god,
that's a fire. They can't hear it. We're there. All right. I hear it very strongly. Yeah,
but you're not, it's not in front of a uni directional mic. I thought your pacemaker had exploded
or something. No, it's really intense. It's so I can feel it in my pocket. So I need a lot of
buzzes. I can't feel it in my pocket. This is where Arquette and Cox met. Am I correct? Yes. And
they are still together? Are they recently divorced? I don't know. They're long divorced.
You never heard all those things on Stern where he said she was having like an emotional affair.
No, I didn't. And all that stuff. That's Cox looking these days. I'm sure fancastic.
Well, I feel like a little bit of a pig saying it like that. I didn't mean it like that. No,
I hate to be an asshole. But I mean, Cox was always, to me, the most attractive of the friends
even over in Aniston. And she went a little far with the plastic surgery. I don't think I'm talking
out of school to say that. But she went a little far with it. And living in this god for second town,
I don't know how women do it really. But she went a little far with them. Aniston was always my top.
I think she's most people's top. And you know, I don't love the kudra always gets left out in the
trash because she's a, I think she's a brilliant comedic actress and the comeback is fantastic.
And she's beautiful too. She'll fantastic and she's a good looking woman.
You know, everybody's got it. Look, I'm sure most people want to bang LeBlanc over everybody
else, but that doesn't mean that Schwimmer isn't a good looking cat. I mean, my, I would hope people's
favorite is Perry. It was clearly the funniest, but maybe girls think otherwise. I don't know.
I, you know, I like a Perry. My favorite. You watch those shows. Chandler is the funniest by a
billion percent. He is. They just kind of ruined him toward the end. He started to get to
Quippy. Yeah. Yeah. What are the rest of the cast of Annie say after you said that, you know,
what I mean, it was right. I hear what you said. There's too much. Cox holding it together.
Body. There's looking terrific. Oh, unquestionably. There's just, yeah, the face is a little wild.
She said some surgery done. And then you, you wonder like, I mean, I talked about as I think I'm on
here before, but like, I never knew that any woman did anything to her face unless she looked like
Joan Rivers. And now I learn that everyone does something, but I also see how you go too far
with it. And you get carried away because as you start to age, you know, it's crazy. Look at
yourself in the mirror. And I'm 34. And you're like, man, I see it happening. Like it's a day to day
thing. Pat, I'll tell you, I have days where I look at the mirror. And I said, when did my father move
in to my face? Yeah, it's tough. It's tough. But it happens to us all. What are you going to do?
I mean, I eat chocolate. And it's on my hips the next day. That's a great big daddy joke,
if I may. What's a movie big daddy? Or is that what you call your father? I call them big daddy,
like in a Tennessee Williams play. No, it's in the movie big daddy. And I'm sound like I was
I tell you, I used to eat anything I wanted. And I had so much fun. Because I tell you,
these days I drink half a milkshake. My ass jiggles for a week. And I laughed because I was 16. And I
thought, ah, that'll never happen to me. But it happens. No, it happens. There's Leo Schreiber.
Oh boy, does it happen? Wait, Leo Schreiber's, he is in this. He's in two. I think he's the killer
in two. Actually, if you don't mind me saying, who is he in this one? I don't think since I was
he's the guy who killed her mom. He killed her mom because they really do that they make it into
a trilogy where like all these movies interconnect. Four, four I didn't love. I think two is a great
sequel. I really do. And Parker Posey's great in it. And I think three is okay. Who's the killer in
four? No recollection. No recollection. Who's the killer in three? I don't remember. I think in two,
it's, I think it's, is it two people on this one? Oh, yeah, it's Lillard. And, ah, well,
there goes for the listener. Stop into it. It's Schreiber, I believe. It's skied all rich in Lillard,
yeah. But liver alone. I mean, I never noticed how much they try to make you or I don't want to say
I never noticed, but I probably, I don't remember that they made. There's Linda Blair from the actresses.
Yes, that's very cool. Yeah. Oh boy. They made, uh, they, they really push you to think it's
all rich the whole time. And then kind of hold you away from it. It's two people. Yeah. But they,
I think before it ends, you're like, oh, it wasn't him. Yeah, I think so. They do a good, they do a good
dance with that whole thing. They do. Here's some, uh, movie insights about the scream film,
the first scream film. Go on. Controversies. I'm reading this off of Wikipedia if you don't mind.
Wasn't there some actual murders with Ghost Faces? It was in the years following the release of
scream. The film had been accused of inspiring copycat crimes and inducing violent acts. In January
98, 16 -year -old Mario Padilla and his 14 -year -old cousin Samuel Ormira stabbed Mario's mother,
Gina Castillo, 45 times killing her. Case became known as the scream murder because it fell in
under intense media scrutiny. After the boys claimed, they were inspired by parts one and two
of the film series. Pair confessed to needing the money acquired from Gina's murder to
fund a killing spree versus two Ghost Faced costumes and a voice changer used to use by the characters
in the film where they talked about the voice changer. Right. So these kids, uh, yeah, they dressed up,
uh, as a, uh, Ghost Faced and, uh, or at least planned on keep, to keep going. They started with
the months. That's disturbing. Uh, during the trial, a psychologist said there were a whole bunch
of reasons why they acted out that way, but did the movie provide a blueprint? Absolutely. That's
ridiculous. It's like saying, yeah, you gotta kill somebody. You're gonna kill somebody.
I remember we saw the boy who could fly when I was a kid. Oh god, I just love that movie.
One of my friends went up on the roof and he was gonna try to do it. Yeah. He was gonna try to fly
and he didn't. We talked him down. We were like, you can't fly, dude. Like, you're gonna hurt yourself.
Was he mentally ill? Uh, he wasn't mentally ill. He was, he was a little slower than us, but like,
you know, he was a normal kid, but he thought he could fly and he went up and he was gonna try it.
The funny part, I mean, now it's funny because everything ended up okay. His little brother who
did not like him was encouraging him to try to fly. Right. So, but uh, it all worked out. We talked
him down. My, my dear friend Fred Savage was in that movie. Uh, as a very young boy.
Speaking your friend Fred Savage. Yeah. I watched, by the way, it was a name drop from Pat everybody. Look,
I'm not above it. Uh, I watched his new movie, the driller, the finisher or TV show, uh,
would write him a new pilot. I saw it on the airplane. They put the pilot on the airplane.
I saw it on an airplane. It was hilarious. Oh good. I can't wait to see it.
Fred Savage was laugh out loud, funny in it. Great. Can't wait. I'm not just saying that. All right.
I, he, it's really funny. I can't wait. And it was, it was, it was, it was relieving to see something
like that. Cause I was like, because that, and I watched grandfathered, which I didn't like
as much, but friends on both of these shows. I will, I will not say anything. It was still funny,
though. I am looking forward to seeing them. I got hope seeing both of them. I was like, it's good
to see network. It's particularly Fred Savage when I was like, it's good to see network TV doing
stuff that's a little off the mark. Sure. You know, sure. But the Savage one, man, he and Rob
Blow both were great in it. The girl from it's always sunny. He's on it. Charlie,
Elizabeth Ellis. Yeah. She's great on it. Yeah. It was funny. She's, I've developed quite a TV
crush on that girl. Oh, she's great. She's really nice and funny. A little more scream controversy
over here. Jesus Christ. Listen to this one. January 17th, 1999, 13 year old Ashley Murray was stabbed
multiple times in the head and back before being left for dead. It's a comedy podcast by his
then friend, Daniel Gill, who was 14. Robert and another guy, Robert, four, who was 15.
Yeah, this is kind of a downer, huh? I don't know that that qualifies as a fun fact. I started,
I didn't mean it as a fun fact. I started reading it because I thought it was going to say
the 13 year old killed people. And then it, yeah. And then I didn't read enough ahead. So I actually
started reading loud. And then it said that the 13 year old got murdered. Right. So sorry about
that guys. I mean, I don't buy that shit. You want you want to kill somebody. You're going to
kill somebody in movies. They might change the style or something. But if you're going to kill
somebody or a nut, you're going to do it. I agree. Bravo's 100 scary movie moments. Opening
scene to scream number 13. Yeah. That feels around right? A five hundred greatest movie quotes.
Do you like scary movies? What is the shirt and hair that Campbell's sporting now? Like,
why do they have a looking so mommush? Uh, I missed her because I was reading the,
the stupid, uh, would you watch the movie? I'm trying to read trivia for the fans and this internet age.
Henry Winkler now is reprimanding kids that are wearing ghost face masks. It's at the school because
they think it's as a prank. And now Henry, I remember seeing the trailer, which I'm sure is on YouTube,
for the third season of the sopranos, which in my opinion, is the best TV season of all time.
I know you don't love the sopranos as much as I do. But in the midst of all this like amazing
shit and like all these crazy action sequences and everybody yelling and going crazy,
there was two people in the scream mask running out of a college. And I remember this was like six
months before the sopranos premiered. And I was like, what the fuck is going on with these
scream masks in the soprano preview? And eventually, uh, it's just two teenagers robbing a jewel concert
at a college, but and it's kind of a funny scene. But I was just like, man, how do the
screen masks factor into the sopranos? I thought they had some weird like new horror element or something.
But the impact of it was pretty far reaching. And this was a huge movie, I remember.
Yeah, it was. I was in high school at the time. It was like this in American pie or everything.
Well, other, you know, some other information I'm seeing here on the Wikipedia page,
and I do remember that this was the case. The horror movie industry was sort of or the genre itself
was sort of slumping. Screen kind of put it back in, yeah, you know, respectful territory again.
And then immediately it started being terrible because I remember this was the age of like
phantoms with Ben Affleck. Uh, you know, a lot of people say phantoms is really good. I've never seen it,
but it's not. There were some good like mimic, uh, Guillermo del Toro did a movie with
Marissa Vena, a dog called mimic. And there was some good horror as we mentioned. The faculty
really sucked. I never saw the faculty. I had no interest. That girl, Christ. That girl, uh, you know,
she's the, she's, you know, this is, they have to have this scene every horror movie when, right?
You know, the, the victim protagonist is in a stall. Yeah, at the high school in the bathroom. And then
there's a bitchy girl that's like, she's a crazy bitch. Can we all agree? There's no worse soap
Spencer than those pink ones that look like sea shells that you push. Like you don't, it always takes
me several minutes to get the soap out and figure out how to use them. They do have never Campbell in a
terrible get up. It's bad. And they hear it like a feathered bangs kind of situation.
I don't mind the bangs. Let's talk about this shirt she's wearing. The shirts, particularly bad.
And I, I get what they're doing. You know, McGowan is always wearing like a, a, a bra.
And they keep her in kind of more tame shit. But, well, they tame is one thing. But, you know,
to make her look like she sells pies she made at home for a living. Yeah, leaving a pie on the
window sill to cool. Teaching Mrs. Tingle. That's one of the other. Wow. Do I remember teaching Mrs.
Tingle. I saw that in a date as well. It was not good. That was sort of like a high school
version of swimming with sharks, right? Like a mean teacher who was, I want to say Helen Miran.
Yep. Okay. And then the kids like to kidnap her in torture or something. Yeah. Yeah. So that's
like swimming with sharks. Except without Kevin Spacey. Yeah. Not as good. And Frank Whaley. And Frank Whaley
once again. So where are these things happen? People keep coming up in these podcasts. Now, here's
my question. I heard that they were making a scream TV series. Yeah. It's on. I haven't seen it,
but it's on TV. It's already been. I didn't know that. I think the whole first season has aired.
And I just never watched a scripted show on MTV. Not, not out of any sort of bias, but I just always
feel like they're for people much younger than me. Maybe it was good. They're gonna keep going
with it too, even though West Craven has passed. Well, he had nothing to do with that show. I
don't think. Except Cash and Jack. I think he was a producer on it. Was he not? Probably. Probably.
You've never seen the show. I've never seen one episode of it. Never saw Scram. Never saw Teen Wolf.
Never saw any of those. I refused to watch Teen Wolf. I refused to watch a show that it takes a movie
that helped mold my childhood and it's turned it into like this, like a real horror thing.
I love real horror, but you don't do that with Teen Wolf. All the fun's gone.
I mean, I can't believe you felt that passionately about Teen Wolf, but who didn't love Teen Wolf?
Did you love Teen Wolf two T -O -O? Unwatchable. It is. Unwatchable. Who knew the stars of both
Teen Wolfs would go on to become big stars? Who knew? Who knew? I mean, you watch Teen Wolf too.
My money was on Bateman bottoming out. Guys, one of the biggest names in Hollywood right now.
Bateman, you know, of course, I always watch them on the Hogan family and all these shows when I was a
kid. But like, I mean, I rest in development. That was a big shock. It's just like, man,
this guy has like the best straight man comedic timing in the fucking game. Yeah, he's fantastic.
And that really does come from working that multi -cam sitcom circuit. If you can do that shit,
you know how to land a fucking joke. You have to know how to land a joke.
He's, in my opinion, the funniest I've ever seen that guy is in that movie
that Mike Judge movie, Extract. Extract was a pretty big lead down for me, but I think he was
pretty solid in it, yes. He's done the funniest thing. He did the funniest things that
movie I've ever seen the guy do. When he's on the phone and he starts pounding it on the desk
because he's so angry. Yeah. It's so, he's just, and then the stuff between him and Ben Affleck
is really funny in it too. I agree. I agree. Yes. Scream TV show. Right out of the loop here,
10 episodes. I didn't even know. Oh, yeah. I mean, I'm sure you can download the season or whatever.
I decide, I never, there's so much TV and so much good TV that someone needs to tell me something's
good at least 10 times before I watch an episode. Or unless it's someone I love and trust,
who's like, you got to see this, it's the best thing ever. I want to look up with ghost face looks
like on the TV show because he does look different. It's a different mask, which I don't get.
You have one of the most recognizable things in horror history at your disposal. Why not use them?
It's scarier looking. Lillard, Staten McAllen in this. Yeah. They established that
like right at the beginning. Oh, Christ. What would you don't believe it? I guess not.
You don't believe Lillard and McAllen? I believe it. All right.
Now they got Winkler put in the mask on. Well, this is the same where you're supposed to think it's
Winkler. Yeah. Is it Winkler? A big story that always gets told in comedy writer's rooms is that
on the set of happy days, he was playing the fauncy, of course. And the fauncy, not the fauncy,
they wrote the fauncy or the fauncy. They wrote into the script this week they had like him saying
correct amundo at some point. And they said he came to the writer's room and he goes,
guys, you keep writing correct amundo and all this. He's like, you don't have to do that.
I know where the amundos go. It was just like a brief period early in his career where he took
himself a little too seriously. But that's a really funny story. Well, and I swear to you,
oh, but the guy in the janitor in the Freddie sweater, who looked like it might have been West Craven,
but I guess maybe we can't rewind it because we got to stay. I keep doing this stupid podcast.
I swear to God, that story is so absurd that if you said to me who said this Henry Winkler or the
Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles, I wouldn't know. Yeah. I wouldn't. I literally, boy, there's,
yeah, I'll tell you what. And I've said this many times in my life, there are some great fucking
jokes in Turtles 1 and 2. I to this date love turtles. One, I hate turtles too. I think I prefer
secret of the use. That's insane. And that's an insane sentence. Here's why. It has, well,
I'm not going to say the vanilla ice came out, but it's got a scene where they're going through
and Raphael is tied up and they're trying to rescue him. And they go, man, it's dark up here.
And they go, yeah, a little too dark. And they go, oh, my God, it's so quiet in here.
And Leonardo's like, yeah, a little too quiet. And they go, oh, my God, it's wrath.
And Leonardo goes, yeah, a little too wrath.
What? When I was a kid, I laughed for five minutes. I don't even get it.
Well, a little too rare. See the difference between you and me.
What the hell is that mean? It's a very funny joke. And then in Turtles 2, I don't get the joke.
What is too rough? Raphael. It's quiet in here. Yeah, a little too quiet. Hey, there's Raphael,
a little too Raphael. What? I don't get it. Well, we disagree. You mean because it doesn't make sense
that he says a little too rough? Yeah. Look, I'm a kid when I see it. Look, God bless. I don't
know. I laughed and my mom laughed. I didn't even thank you, mom, for taking me to both Turtles 1
and Turtles 2, secret of the use. I saw Turtles 1 with my oldest friend in the world, Scott,
who you've met many times, opening night. Yeah, I saw him both opening night with his mom, my folks,
two of us. We went opening night. It was a big deal. And then I wanted pizza afterwards. Part 2 came
out. I was like, don't even bother. Even as a kid, you were a kid. I knew it was going to suck.
And it did. It sucked. It's clearly directed. It's terrible. It's got the first rap song. Look,
that partners in rhyme, first Turtles with turtle power part. That's a part of you.
R. T. Ali. Power. Yeah. But the lyrics to it are wrong. No, I know, but who gives a shit. Raphael,
he's the leader of the group, transformed from the norm by the nuclear. Raphael is not the leader of
the group. I know. So what you never watched one episode of the show and you're going to do a
rap about it. Look, I don't really care about the mistake. It's a superior musical effort. Okay.
And it and Turtles 2. Okay. Doesn't it doesn't have the setup. Casey Jones isn't in it. Look,
would it hold up now? I can almost guarantee no. But oh well. Well, what are you going to do? I would
do Turtles, did you? I tried watching half of it over my class and I couldn't. I couldn't. I mean,
it's fucking terrible. Yeah. Now Turtles 3 Turtles in time is unwatchable too. And a friend of mine at
school had seen it before all the rest of us. And he goes, dude, wait till you see Turtles 3.
They're going to make six Ninja Turtle movies. Go see 3. And you'll see what I mean. Okay.
Somebody Ryan, we go and see Turtles 3. There's nothing that indicates there's going to be six Turtles
movies. He said he saw something in it that was like, you know, there's going to be three more. They
set it up for a whole another trilogy to this day. I don't know what he was talking. Perhaps he was on
drugs. If anything, you go see Turtles 3 and you're like, well, this franchise is over.
Maybe there was this post -credits scene. Maybe. I don't think they're, well, they did do it in
those days. They did it during the post -credits scene. So does Masters of the Universe during
Dolph Lungren, Billy Barty, and Frank Langella? I've seen MOTU or MOTU. What is the post -credits sequence?
Well, he meant to feed Skeletor by throwing him into like a pit of lava. Yeah. And the credits go
and then... Let me guess real quick. Does a bone hand come out of the lava?
Better. Okay. Better. It's actually a pretty cool scene. It's a close -up of the lava and Skeletor's
head pops out. Okay. And says, two camera. I'll be back. But you weren't Skeletor.
Well, they had a sequel planned and then they canceled it. Now, see, I have really strong memories
of my childhood. For example, I remember that I had several birthdays where I would wind up
crying into an alf cake because no one would come. Yeah. You told us that last time. But what I don't
remember is ever enjoying Masters of the Universe. I had a huge Ninja Turtles collection, but I never
remember watching key man or Masters of the Universe. However, there's a photo of me in an orco costume
for Halloween. That's just because you like to put on dresses. But I don't remember ever having a toy
or caring about Masters of the Universe at all. This is a great song by Nick Cave that is also
used in Dumb and Dumber called Red Ride Hand. Really? And Nick Cave, I like to say I'm sorry that
your son died. That's terrible. I'm sure you're listening to this. I'm reading more about the
Scream TV show. And it says... Now, the link that I clicked on said, Scream remake made the weirdest
decision possible. Okay. Go on. Remake me into the TV show. Here's the quote. Please note that I
had been in communication with TWC regarding this and they have informed me that as of now and during
the initial launch, Ghostface is not involved in the new format. They also indicated that because of
this direction it does not mean that Ghostface will not be involved at a later date. So there is still
a question to the question. However, as of now there is no involvement. Further down it says, we believe
Scream is Ghostface and Ghostface is Scream. However, while Ghostface is owned by Fun World,
this is Fun World saying this. The Scream motion picture franchises owned by the Weinstein company
and is their option to film a movie or TV show without Ghostface. I don't know. The plot was already
completely removed from Wes Craven's hit films anyway. So it's pretty disappointing to find that
the MTV version is 100 % in name only cash grab. Okay. So it's just, here's the plot of the show.
You ready? Is this boring? I mean, we're both talking and watching a movie and now you're
reading articles aloud. I just want it. It's like, what's going on? I want to learn about the MTV
generation. I want to learn about the TV Scream show. The Scream TV show. I will watch it at some
point. Well, just read the plot real quick. Go ahead. Real quick. Emma and her best friend Aubrey see
relationships and lives turned upside down when a private video Aubrey's of Aubrey's goes viral and
incites a murder in the teen small town. Okay. Sound like the plot of Unfriended, which was a great
horror movie. Yeah, that's all right. Well, whatever. That's that's your Scream TV show. That's it.
Okay. And that's why it's a different mass because it's not Ghostface, I guess. I don't I don't
know. Why did I do this with these things? I mean, a horror aggravated. There's really been no
successful horror TV shows that I can think of. I literally don't think MTV's ever done anything that
hasn't infuriated me. I can't think of one thing they, well, I like the, the John Stewart show when
he had the talk show. That was 48 years ago. I'm just trying to name good things. I loved you on TV
wraps. I loved to hangers ball. I loved 120 minutes. I mean, it used to have this very like
forbidden feel to me. I never had cable growing up when I would babysit. I would go and be like, I
can't wait to see MTV and I watched the black hole sun video and the weezer buddy Holly video.
And I'd be like, good Lord, these are fucking works of art, these things. And I think most people's
frustration is why does MTV not show any music anymore. It's not my issue really. It's just kind of
like why is nothing on here, particularly good. Well, if you notice out on my DVD shelves,
and I do have quite a vast collection, ladies, yeah, I have a huge, not a huge box set, but like a
four DVD, you know, with each DVD being a double disc or whatever box set of video music directors.
I have the same thing because I have the spike Jones one. I got them all. They're there with two
videos. One of them is amazing. Yeah, they're great when you're having a party just for visuals on
the TV. Sure. You know, spike Jones made, in my opinion, the best music videos there ever were.
Yeah, he was really and now MX fucking amazing movies. He was really good. But yeah, okay, so in the last
20 years, I'd say MTV hasn't done anything that has been infuriated me. That's fair. I didn't see
the recent VMAs, but they're always a real downer. I was at my friends in New York and they put it on
and I literally went and I said, guys, I can't watch this. They said, why? And I said, because it's
making me, it makes me so angry that I'm going to start yelling at your TV. Yeah, nobody wants that.
It makes me furious. I can't even deal with it. I can't deal with it. I miss a lot of, that's one
of cable. I miss, I hate certain aspects of pop culture so much that I don't have cable. And then I
miss tons of shit. Right. You know, I want to watch the goddamn scream show just out of curiosity.
And then I would have been furious. But you know, it's always the thing and I have a very kind of
like I need to finish and I need to complete series and movies and all that kind of stuff. Like if I see
three movies in a franchise, I'm going to watch 12 movies of a franchise. And eventually you're just
wasting hours of your life because they're bad. And that's the way you start a show on MTV and I'm
like, yeah, watch the scream series. But then I find myself having devoted 12 hours to the scream series.
And then I wish I was dead. It's like being in a bad relationship. You just go, this will get
better. And then it just doesn't really. I finally gave up on, and I hate to say it because I'm a
fan of everybody in the show. And I'm a fan of the idea of the show. Yeah. And at moments, the show
is brilliant. But I finally gave up on Bates Motel. I couldn't do it anymore. I did too. It had scenes
that were really like shot in cool ways and like a couple cool ideas. But then more often than not,
you're like, what are you doing? Why is there a whole sub plot about the town selling?
I know. Weed. It's so dumb. Do with anything. I tend to, I tend to need like I said, a lot of
people recommend something or the whole season to have air and people to be like, I tell you,
this whole season was great. Then I'll watch the whole season. By the way, at this point in the film,
if you are watching along with us, they're, they're at a party. Matthew Lillard's character is having a
house party. I've never known a guy like this in my life. I've seen a guy like this in a million
movies about teenagers, never knew a guy like this Matthew Lillard character walking around in a satin
row. No, no good reason. No, just the guy. Well, I had no cool friends growing up, almost to the
present to be honest with you. Sure. I don't like cool people and never had cool friends. But
never went to a party like this. My parties I went to were always like 12 angry guys not getting
laid, sitting in a basement, yelling at MTV. Well, but we had a good time. Pat, we could have been
lifelong chum. Yeah. Yeah. Look, and then you wind up kind of growing up and you kind of missed that,
because now, if me and you were to sit and watch MTV for 12 hours, we'd feel like we were wasting our
lives. Sure. And we'd have other things to go do. Sure. Yeah. At the very least, let's make it a
podcast if we're going to. Exactly. Let's bring in that podcast cash or podcast. Look at this.
Nips. Rose McGowan nips on 10. Now, here's a big question. Do they say, hey, Rose,
we'd love for you to be nip and hardcore on this scene? Or do they just make it real cold in there
and not tell her? What do you think? Do they, do they get it in the contract because it is a form
of nudity? What do you think? I honestly think that it's, for some reason, she probably said, okay,
did not wearing a bra or decided to not wear a bra. And I bet you, at some point, a woman on set
went up and said, hey, just so you know, sweetie, your turkeys are done. And she probably went, oh,
I don't care. Yeah. It was, but she's holding beers up against some of them. I'm fucking the guy that
wrote beautiful people. What do I give a shit? Yeah. She means she wants to be a star. That's
look like she's wearing a bra, though. She is clearly wearing a bra. Those things are rocking through
the bride or else they were fake nipples, which is another weird thing. I know quite a few people
who worked on friends, as we were talking about earlier, and they said, as there became a little
sort of healthy competition amongst the cast and not so much kudro, but Aniston would come into set
for her scenes nip and hard. And you watch, as you move along through friends, you see a lot of Aniston
really aggressively nipping. Then Courtney Cox fearing that she was going to be less desirable
because she wasn't nipping would also start nipping. And the winner was the viewer, of course. Sure.
And then eventually DeCovny started showing his balls on what? I'm joking, Pat. DeCovny.
The reason I didn't get your joke is because I thought you were moved on to the X -Files.
I was like, oh, was that that bit of a joke? Swimmers started showing his balls. Swimmers got the outline
of his balls. Perry comes out with his taint exposed. It was a rough time.
Rosemar Gowan is about to be murdered by Ghostface in the... By a garage door opener. That's my first
voice crack of the podcast. She gets murdered by a garage door opener? Well, they like take her
up in the garage door her body. God, I really remembered nothing. I thought I really remembered this move.
I really haven't seen it in a long time. It's a cool skirt. It draws you into her butt and vagina.
I love McGowan. Just the right shade of pale. You can tell she's got tattoos in all the right places.
There we go. You can tell she probably sidle up to a game of beer pong and talk a lot of shit. Sure.
Where's your drink you pussy? I picture being like one of those kinds of girls. Yeah.
Then she gets drunk and it goes a little too far and then she's embarrassing you in front of your friends.
But you can't stay away. You can't stay away. You tell her you never want to see her again,
you can't stay away. No, you find yourself calling her a couple nights later.
Couple nights, a couple minutes. Oh.
All right, so McGowan just bit it. I remember being very disappointed that she died in the
so I was like, oh, well, I mean, she died. What it why? Did you think you were going to see her naked
eventually? I especially at this age when I'm like 15 years old. That's honestly all I thought about.
Was by the way, I didn't realize how her name is Tatum. Yeah.
Rose McGowan, her name is Tatum. Channing Tatum. One of my favorite jokes I ever wrote for
Pete's show was you talked, you said this in the podcast. I said this already. Yeah. Are you sure? Yeah.
Tatum. God damn it. All right, we've both done this. It's embarrassing, but we've both done it.
I mean, we got to talk for two hours straight in this goddamn thing. I know. I mean, I don't remember
you could tell me where he did an episode about scream. I wouldn't even. We're four episodes in.
I can't remember what the fuck we've talked about already. Yeah. We got to start getting into some
weirder movies so like, you know, yeah, it's making us. Oh, oh, okay, that's fine. Our picture just
went nuts, but then it came back the old as far as this this obsession I have with nudity at the time
because we didn't have the internet in my house until I was in college. I brought a big group of
friends of mine to see the gift and nobody cared to see it speaking of Sam Raimi. And I was so off
the charts excited because I was going to see Katie Holmes naked. Right. And at the time, my
this was pre cruise during Dawson's Creek, I was so beyond obsessed with Katie Holmes. And I just
thought she's the best looking lady in the world. I go to see the gift and I'm like, I heard she's naked
in this and I brought like 10 friends and we're like, okay, here we go. The gift's an okay movie.
It's going going about an hour in. They're all like, when we're going to see this, they pull Katie
Holmes's naked corpse out of a river. And everyone looks down the aisle at me like you fucking son of a
bitch. And I was so distraught that I didn't know what to do. And finally at about the hour 30 mark,
they do a flashback with Holmes and Greg Keneer. And as the flashback begins, I said, thank you,
Jesus. I've got another chance. And she's sure enough. She gets completely toppled on that thing.
And it was as glorious as I'd always dream. And she bangs Keneer. And that movie, she's dating Keneer,
who I think it's her teacher. It's going to say Keneer's like 20 years older than her, isn't he?
Yeah. And that's right around the time he also was banging me on a suvari in real life.
In real life, really? Oh, no, I'm saying in real life.
No, in the very underrated teen movie, loser, with Jason Biggs directed by Amy Heckerlink.
But who did clueless and fast times? I think people get that movie a bad route.
Gift has a lot of weird cast and Kiana Reeves plays like an abusive boyfriend.
Is the loser the one with Jason Schwartzman in it too? No, that's slackers. Slackers, which is okay.
I remember there being a weird cult around that movie, but it doesn't really warrant.
The Schwartz, he brings a cult in. And accepted was the Justin Long. One of those.
I saw accepted in the movie theater by myself. I think I did.
So I was delivering pizzas at the time and I'd get off work at 2 p .m.
And then I still was living at home. And my parents didn't go to a five, so I'd just go to a movie.
Yeah. And spent the afternoon there. And I saw accepted. And that was my introduction to Jonah Hill.
He was funny in that. The part where he's screaming. The part where he's screaming still is the show.
It's amazing. I remember being in the trailer and I was like, man, that's really funny.
And the movie wasn't it, wasn't that funny? It's an art flick. Great bit.
That summer I saw accepted art school confidential.
Oh, I love that movie. And I also love the christ. All by myself.
Also, hilarious. I love darts with confidential. It's a much
meaner nastier movie than ghost world. But I love them both.
It gets dark in ways you're not expecting.
Yeah. Because it starts it starts almost silly.
Yeah, I think it gets like it gets like dark where you're like the end of it. You're like,
Jesus Christ. Yeah. I think that Terry's Wig off is too dark to maybe ever work again,
which is really unfortunate. But like if you look at that track record, crumb ghost world,
art school confidential, bad Santa. And bad Santa came out in, you know, over 10 years ago.
And the guy hasn't made a movie since then we made a lot of money. I have a theory.
He's really difficult to work with is what I've always heard. I have a theory about bad Santa.
Go on. A plus in my opinion. It's a fit. It's a masterpiece. I showed it to my parents
the last Christmas and we had a wonderful time together. We talked about that on this.
I love it.
Right. Jesus Christ. Anyway, did I tell you my theory?
I don't think so. Okay. There's a twilight zone. There's an episode of the twilight zone called
Night of the Meek. The original version of its stars art carny. They remake stars.
The guy from empty nest. I'm blanking on his name. The guy's results. Yeah. Yeah.
And the plot is it's like a heartfelt twilight zone. It's the Christmas episode.
Yeah. And it's about a Santa Claus, a department store Santa Claus who's a complete drunk.
Okay. And you know, gets fired for the department store because he was drinking on his break and more
to, you know, embarrasses himself and is mortified and apologetic and everything. And then actually
becomes Santa Claus. Okay. I was just tapping your arm. Sorry. That's fine.
Actually becomes Santa Claus. That's the twilight zone twist at the end.
Right. He redeems himself by becoming Santa Claus. Okay.
Uh, my theory is that when they were writing that the way the idea for bad Santa Claus was
they were watching that twilight zone and said, well, what if he wasn't embarrassed?
It was just the price of shit. That could that could very well be. I really think that's what it was.
Yeah. How funny would it be if he was just a fucking scumbag like owning this? Yeah.
And then the end he does kind of become Santa Claus at the end of bad Santa. Right.
You know, in a much different way, but, you know, uh, there are some fascinating things about bad
Santa. They're uncredited, but apparently a vast majority of the script was rewritten by the
Cohen brothers, which I love. Yeah. And also obsessively courted and was going to play it till
almost the last minute was Bill Murray. So like, I think Bill Murray would have been amazing.
And yet, I think looking at it now, I love what Billy Bob Thorne did so much. I don't, I don't even
care. I don't need to see Bill Murray play the part. Well, I'll say this and I love Bill.
As much as it saddens me to think I could have seen Bill Murray play that part because he's always
great playing a dirt ball. Yeah. I don't know if I think the great thing that Billy Bob Thorne brought to
it was. He captured a darkness though. I don't know if I would have felt with Bill Murray. I agree.
And Bill Murray is clearly a guy with some fucking demons. Right. But like,
Billy Bob Thorne played that with like, just the, like, no humanity in his eyes even.
And I think that's what makes the movie so special to me. Yeah, the, uh, just like, because, like,
you, I don't think we'll ever again outside of the rawest of indie movies. See a character that,
like, a moral and alcoholic and given up online. That movie blew my fucking mind. Yeah. And it
still does when I watch it. I'm like, this is, this is it. Like, this is the movie that didn't like
make any concessions to anyone. Well, my friend Jim and I often talk about how nobody
curses funnier than Billy Bob Thorne. I agree. I even love the bad news bears remake. Yeah, I was
into it too. Yeah. But he always, his favorite line is Billy Bob Thorne. And I think it's in
intolerable cruelty. Funny movie where he goes. Well, goddamn good to meet you. I think it's his line.
Yeah. And that, and my favorite is always, uh, from, uh, uh, love actually where he walks, he walks
by Hugh Grant's assistant, who's a really hot girl. And Billy Bob Thorne goes, God damn, that's a pretty
son of a bitch. Uh -huh. About a woman. Yeah. God damn, that's a pretty son of a bitch. Yeah,
that guy is, Billy Bob Thorne's fucking hilarious, man. See this, uh, now, this was a word hilarious
than Jamie Kennedy comes on the screen. I mean, is this was, this was a troubling time. Has he ever
made you laugh? Jamie Kennedy's never made a laugh. No, ever. But I know people who love him. So
prank show sucked. Yeah. No, I agree. You know, you get a bad prank show when Ashton Kutcher is
out doing your prank show. I agree. You know, it was a much funnier show that no one ever speaks about
was the anti -dick show. That was on MTV. And that show had some genius sketches on it. Was bent. No,
Ben Salar was Fox. What was the anti -dick show? Anti -dick show was around this time. Like, it feels like
about a 96. And man, he had some amazing characters. He did like a long, sad, dark, Britney Spears
parody episode that was amazing. And it, it fit squarely into that MTV mold, you know, like it,
it was, it was appealing to those kids, but it was really smart and fucked up and funny.
And that is the guy who played me love by the way. It is the guy that played me. Yeah.
Well, what's he up to? Who hasn't had one line of dialogue yet? I don't think. No, he had one.
We were talking through it. He said something to Courtney Cox when they were in the van.
I didn't like how she was yelling at him earlier. Call him a big fat lord. I didn't care for it either.
He's a uncalled for. You know, here's, now here's, look, here's a sort of romantic scene.
Well, man, some bloom. Cox and, or, yeah, our kids. I wonder if they played this at the wedding.
It's where the field during their first dance.
Yeah. They worked their character names into the vows. And when I met my dewey,
and then he goes, when I met my, oh, whoa, how weird was that? What?
I said, when I met my, and she said her name, Gail Weathers, Joe. That was weird. I'm,
yes, it was weird. I'm sorry. I barely noticed it because he yelled so quickly after.
It was kind of amazing. I said, and she said, when my, Gail Weathers, that was kind of a special moment.
I was just, I was just thinking of my vows for him in my head. Sorry.
No, what we would say if you married David, I can't. Where he said it, where he says to her,
luckily, you were in my jurisdiction. You know, something like, right, right, right.
Right, right, right. We started as he looks at the audience. Friends. But eventually, I made you look
at the audience scream in bed because you were, looks at the audience, ready to rumble. Yeah,
right. Perfect. You don't have to be surelock homes to figure out how much our love.
Should we go up right now to like Van Nies, catch the tail end of David, our cat and Sherlock Holmes,
and then hang out with him? Because we're the only two people there. We would be the only people there.
I gotta tell you, why would we not go to that show? If the tickets are more than $7,
there's your answer. If they're less, then yes, I would go. You're making all that TV money.
I am very wealthy. I started a new writing job on Monday. Let's spend some cash and go see this David.
Let's do it. I just terribly curious. He just, he doesn't seem like the right choice, frankly.
I was doing, I can't mock the guy because I was, I was doing a, I remember I, a private corporate gig.
It was in a restaurant. They were having this big dinner in the restaurant. And he was,
I was in the bar waiting to go on and he was there at the bar for his birthday party or birthday
dinner or something and all these people were showing up. And he went off with several good looking
well -to -do people to have a nice birthday party. And then I went in and bombed for an hour in
front of 60 -year -old men that were eating steak. So Dave, you're doing better than I am. What was the
corporate couldn't tell you? No. Never bombed, I mean it just bombing, insulting them because they
weren't laughing. They're heckling me saying we had Sarah, Sarah Silverman once and she was
wonderful. They yelled out a full sentence like we had Sarah Silverman once and you weren't that fun.
They said we had, I said who else has done that? Oh okay you asked. And they said Sarah Silverman
and I said how did she do? And they said oh she was great. Yeah. She was great.
Tell me what she did because this is fucking horrible. Yeah. Figure this out right now.
I, and again, not a brag. I've yet to really bomb at stand -up but I think -
Done it seven times. I think - No, yeah exactly. I haven't done it a lot of times. When I do do it,
when I do bomb, I think that'll be it for me. I don't know that I can handle it.
This is the part in the movie. Oh that's - I was trying to remember how do they make you think it's
not skeet. There you go. There you go. Because skeet gets killed by ghost face.
Definitely - Yes. In front of - The fuck's her name? I was called her Daisy Sidney.
Definitely at this point in the movie I was like oh shit if it's not him who is it and I started
running through my mind and that's you know that I don't think had been done in a horror movie
to that time. It's a great twist. I could have sworn we saw Lillard leave the house too.
Maybe - He ran out with everybody. Everybody ran out of the house. By the way,
hitting him with that door would have had no effect on him. He fell to the ground.
You don't think if you got hit with a big wooden door you wouldn't follow the ground?
It wasn't a big. It was a thin wooden door and it was never Campbell hitting him with it.
Let's test it out, Pat. If you hit me with this door over here I'd go wow what the fuck,
Joe? I want you to go into the other room and run full speed at this door as I slam it into you.
I'd go ow I wouldn't fall to the floor. That puts your money where you're mouth is.
All right I think it'd be more than an owl. Also I mean you got a nitpick here I mean for
Cry 6 it's a you know. No it's just something in movies like you know like when somebody punches a
guy in the face and then his eyes flitter and he falls to the ground and he's unconscious. I'm like
no I don't buy that. What did she just fall on to? She fell off her roof onto a boat.
All right well I conveniently plays to boat. Thank God for that.
Fair enough I'll buy it I'll take it. Lucky break. That could be a boat. Lucky break. Where's people
have boats on the drive one? They do. It's a pain moving that boat every morning when you got to pull
the cars out but it's worth it in the summertime. This has been Pat Walsh from Joe DeRosa for boats.
Are we still believe he's this drunk now? I don't know if Jimmy Kennedy is supposed to be drunk in
the scene or just him being funny I don't know. He's not doing I don't know. He's watching Halloween.
Halloween I watch once a year it's it's it's a it's a perfect movie. It's great I like Halloween
too better. Are you kidding me? No. It's still John Carpenter. See you have a lot more
uncomfortable with quarantine or than you might think. I like Halloween too better. It's it's more
fast paced it gives you more what you want. I could not disagree more. I just couldn't disagree more.
The first picture is very good but it's also slow. It's a very slow bill to the end. Yeah that's
called suspense. I understand but I like the second one. You like H2O? I remember thinking it was okay.
I should go through them all again. That's Kevin Williamson. Yeah that's true. That's a great movie.
We should watch that on here sometime. We will. We should probably watch Halloween. I own them all
recently. I've only watched one and two but I think it's basically like an A plus and a
so you don't four or five six too. I own them all. I'm going to try to watch them. What did you buy
the set? Yeah but the set. The raps aren't too much to me or terrible but yeah it's just like why
why are you punishing us? We're just trying to. It's sorry you trying to make me feel sick. Yeah it's so
much sad and depressed. Yeah that's like a horror movie to me. You know I I don't mind being
scared shitless. I don't mind disturbing but when you start making me sad like what that's not
what I'm here for. The part I don't like is that he there's that like guard in the institution with
them that like kind of takes care of them. Yeah and then he kills the guard too. Now that you're
saying that I remember that very well. It's it we so much it would give so much more of the character
if he didn't kill that guy. Yeah and that was a got that was the eyewitness that was there to tell
the cops like this is what just happened here. You know all those rob zombies are just such like a
just shoving your face in the mud except I did like devil's rejects which kind of had an action
element. It's literally the only one I've never seen because every other one of his movies I
didn't like. Yeah they're not for me. I respect what the guy does like I respect that he's made a
career in making horror movies but you know I was so excited to see lords of Salem. Didn't say that
well. And you know by the third time you're seeing you know burnt face demons jerking off with black
dildos. You're like I get it Rob. Okay everything's good Rob. Everything's to pray I get it. You know
like it's just I don't know by the way for me. I don't even think Rob zombies the guys real name.
I'm going to I'm going to say that now on this podcast. I am tomorrow night. You know what it is. I
actually know what his real name is. What is Brad zombie. Good one Joe. See I'm excited tomorrow
and I'm going to go see the visit the new Shyamalan which comes out tomorrow. I think that looks fantastic
and I if it's I hope it's good. I'm always rooting for Shyamalan. The guy made two masterpieces and
then just an assortment of shockingly terrible movies. I hate signs. I like signs better than the
other ones and I like the first half of the village a lot. The first half of the village is cool.
Lady in the water I was like okay this guy's insane but then you keep thinking he'll get back on
track and he never did. I think the visit looks really cool and I read some article where he was like
I know that this is my last chance. Well after a lady in the water he stopped making horror movies.
That's when he started doing like last airbender and all that stuff. I didn't see that one. The
happening is. Oh no the happening was really almost unwatchable. Yeah the happening sucks.
Signs has some good scares like there's a couple like that video of the yes that's a cool scare.
That's a good scare. Yeah it's signs signs is overall better than the village but I really don't
care for signs. I don't care for. He's just like such a great technical filmmaker like he you know
he needs to let somebody else write his scripts or something at this point although the sixth
incident I'm breakable or almost without flaws but I'm excited about the visit for sure.
I didn't know that open tomorrow. I might go see that tomorrow night because it's going to be at
the Vista right around the corner. Oh it is. I just told all your stalkers where you live. Yeah thanks.
I am trying I'm trying not to have any booze until Saturday so that'll be a thing to do tomorrow night.
Yeah go to the Vista. You're like a werewolf you got to stay off the streets if you want to
like be good. Tell us I'm going to do what I'm a single man on a Friday night you know I'm not going
to a bar what am I going to do. Go take it a movie by myself. Oh it's sabbatroom. Sit behind you and
your girlfriend in the theater. Oh hey guys that's where that you're here too. Poke your head up
between. No that's cool. No no no. Oh really say what do you come on now. All right. No I
mean I guess sit between you. We're nearing the end of the film here. Ghost face is now. Courtney
Cox has fled the scene. Everybody's dead. Ghost face has Neve cornered basically. She's in a truck.
She's locked herself in. We're not I mean we have as always we're not paying the closest of attention
but it doesn't the movie doesn't seem to pack the constant scares I remember it packing.
No it's been it's been pretty steady. I did used to be a lot more of a pussy like when I saw this.
I never found the movie scary. I found it well done. I mean I know these movies don't scare me usually.
Sure. You got to really the exercise used to scare me but because it gets in your head.
The exercise you know especially because my father was one of the only R -rated movies to let me watch
because I could learn about Catholicism. Yeah well she should be watching her pussy. Yeah then
she's masturbating with a crucifix. So we watched it in the next night it's like a full night my dad
takes me to the staircase in St. Louis and he goes this is supposed to be the staircase where this actually
happened where they threw the priest down the stairs and I was like oh so it happened locally.
That's supposed to be based on a true St. Louis story. Okay actually still scares the shit out of
was that it for you with the movie? No I think I watched it fairly recently and I think it's still
terrifying. If you turn the lights out it's gonna fuck you up. Yeah it's scary shit. It's scary
shit. Oh here's where they make you think Jamie Kennedy's the killer. But that you know that one
almost invents a new kind of scary you know like it's still just kind of like unbelievably intense
for today and the fact that audience like you hear audiences passed out in the 70s like yeah I
fully believe that. Yeah it's just it's like a merciless almost like made by a demon kind of movie.
They'll never they'll never come close. I read the book recently about a year ago. I read it when I was a kid
and you read the book when you were a kid how old were you? I used I mean sadly because I couldn't
see these movies I used to read the book. How old were you when you read that book? Probably right
after I watched the movie so I must have been ten or something. Ten. Yeah. You saw her shoving
across in her vagina when you were ten. Yeah and again I couldn't watch the guy I could much any
I read a movie. That part he wasn't like this is a little bit much. I mean I don't remember what we
did at that point I probably left the room but he was big on me learning about Catholicism. Or did he
show you it on like regular TV where maybe that was it? No we watched the real deal because I remember
being like I used to beg my dad to see any already movies and I remember as that movie was going I was
like I might have to leave. I might not be able to watch this but then I might never get to watch
an already movie again so I got to set it out. That's great man. Yeah I remember when my mom finally
let me see it and I was like oh my god it was and I was like oh I get it now I get it now I get
the shit out of me. That was that was embarrassing acting by Jamie Kennedy upon getting shot
like hey Jamie act like you got shot and he can't do that right. What did he do? He goes oh
so this is and look at this with the skeet all rich. Weirdly enough all rich is way better
once he makes the flip than he is is just a normal guy. Yeah I'm still not buying him. I'm buying
Lillard. That's that's a sweater I may have owned in the 90s and I might have worn that necklace too. Look
at Lillard. I'm buying Lillard right now. Look at him. He's yeah he's still great.
Skeets doing like the sinister Lillard on the other hand just looks like a fucking you know
like a like a douchey guy. Yeah I like it. I'm buying it. They should have made T -shirts of that.
See how that that skeet right T -shirt with the two blood. That skeet shirt? Yeah skeet skeet skeet skeet
motherfucker. With the two blood streaks on it. That would have been a marketing marketing move
right there. You saw that T -shirt with the two blood streaks? If it was a little more memorable like you
don't walk out of the mover remembering that shirt. From the back it says scream. Are they I know they're
not doing it overtly but are they implicitly implying that these two are gay lovers? What is this
shot all about? Well Lillard is sort of resting his chin on skeets shoulder. I mean he's giving him
a reach around essentially. Is it is it that kind of like end cold blood? I think there is supposed to be
a certain implication that they have a very intimate relationship. Maybe they're right. It may be
sexual. Yeah look they're they're they murder together. Right. So they remember murder by numbers with
Gosling and Sandy Bullock. Never saw it. That's another kind of like two guys murdering together
and there's a lot of like did they or didn't they kind of shut? Did they put the sting song in it?
They sure did. They sure did. Does it work? No you know what they didn't because they use the
sting song murder by numbers as a major plot point in copycat which is a movie that is so good but was
overshadowed because it came out around the same time as seven. He's in copycat also Sandra Bullock?
No it's Holly Hunter my favorite actress and Sigourney Weaver and they're great together and Harry
Connick Jr. of all people is the villain and he's great in it. And if you have not seen copycat
it was rightfully overshadowed by seven which is a much better movie but copycat is great. It's a
really good solid effort. Really good serial killer movie and deserves better than what it got.
I never had a big serial killer movie. I heard serial killer movie fan. I like
I'll take them over horror movies most of the time. No way. I love them. I love a horror movie.
Sounds a lamb seven. Zodiac. Well boom boom boom. Hold on a second. I don't I'm I was going to say
except for ones like seven or silence of the lambs because they're more they feel more like horror films
to me. Yeah sure. But you know copycat is another you know I never like kiss the girls. Did you say you
have or have not seen copycat. I have it. Come over and watch it. I'm saying that kind of movie. I'm
usually like yeah. Yeah. Kiss the girls with a long came a spider. Okay those aren't great. Those
those kind of thing. Well I like the hitchcock films though and those are always murder mysteries but
yeah. Who do they have taped up here? Kiss the girls isn't awful. Those are used to be the like the
bone collector. There was one of those every week. And they all had jolly and Morgan Freeman.
Yeah. Morgan Freeman was always involved.
Morgan Freeman gives me great hope in this business because he didn't really make it until he was like
53 or something. Yeah. That's what my dad when I was like I really should try and
support me but it's not coming across but I I was trying to be a writer and I was 23 years old
or something which is very reasonable. And he was like you know Pat you got to look at Dennis
Frons. Dennis Frons wasn't a famous actor till he was 52 years old. I'm like yeah I'm a child then.
I'm not like washed up. And I love by the way the bone collector just so you don't think that we mix
up all black actors was Denzel Washington. It was? Yeah. It was Denzel and jolly. I thought that was part
of that Morgan. I thought that was the kisses. Well wait wasn't kisses. Kiss the girl he was playing
the same character and then recently he was played the same character was played by Tyler Perry
who was in all those books but it used to be Morgan Freeman and kiss the girls and along came a spider.
Wait a sec hold on slow down a second. Then there's double jeopardy with Ashley. Kiss the girls
and along came the spider. Morgan Freeman is the same guy. Is it the guy from seven?
No that's its own character. Sevens its own. What move did Tyler Perry play that character in?
I guess the character is called Alex Cross and I believe he played him in Alex Cross.
Okay. I didn't see that one. I heard Tyler Perry stole the show and gone girl.
I disagree but I think people were mostly surprised that he was pretty good in it. I like
gone girl a lot and I like Tyler Perry and it alone. Well he's a good actor. That's the only
Tyler Perry movie I've seen. Yeah bone collector is Denzel and let me make sure Alex Cross is
Freeman. No Alex Cross is. I don't know. No yeah Morgan Freeman played him in along came a spider
and kiss the girls also. And does Denzel play that character in bone collector? Nope.
Different guy. Different guy. Different thing. All right but Morgan Freeman was in training day.
I'm kidding. I love training. It's a fucking awesome movie. Who doesn't like training day?
All right. By the way I think that is top five nudity for me as Ava Mendes in training day
I watched it I rewatched it recently and I about fell off the couch. Do they show her boobs?
Yeah. Really? It's it's really crazy good. All right. And it's brief and you know.
I'll go back into that. Not particularly graphic. It's just really good.
This is why I could never be a murderer because they're now they're doing the thing. They're
at the they're at the part at the end of their killing spree where now they're like we have to make
it look like we are innocent. So we got to stab each other. Right. But but I remember loving
this and being like this is really no it's new shit. It's great. I wouldn't be able to do it though.
That's what I'm saying. If you and I murder somebody I couldn't do that. That was that's the
that's the main thing that would stop me is when you were like okay now we got to stab each other.
When we pushed up on this and go out and kill somebody don't say it like that. But if we get framed
now tonight because I told you before when I said I wanted to stab you if you ever get stabbed
they're going to come to me first now. It's true. Courtney Cox just got knocked out by skied
olrich strangely enough they both have the same haircut. Skied loves those bangs in his eyes man.
I think they popped old scream two out the next year. I think it's how quickly they turn that around.
They went fast with this. They went fast and that scream forward took forever. And Craven was smart
to stick with the franchise because he he left the franchise with nightmare. Yeah. Because he was
against the idea of making a sequel. And he also said and I believe I've said this Christ almighty
shocker before. Yeah. That's what I'm talking about. Look I'm sorry. Guys go back to listen to the
nightmare in Elm Street episode you'll know what I was about to say just then. I didn't say it again
game. So let's say Hollywood comes to you Joe and they say you can remake any horror movie you
want to make. You write it your way. You come in with a cool take on it. What do you do? Whatever you
want to do. Wait say this again. They they come to you and they want you to reboot a horror movie.
They want you to write it. Do your take on it. Your spin on it. Which one do you do?
So like the creep show without without questions. Same stories.
No I would I would want to reboot it and try to get the series going again.
Right. Okay. Like all new stories. But like all new stories based on Stephen King stories.
Yeah. You know and why not just do another a different anthology. Why do you want to make a creep show
well creep shows my favorite horror franchise of all time. Okay. So if somebody came to me and said
what would you want to redo or reboot. I'd want to see more creep shows. Okay fair. You know I love
anthology horror. That or a hell razor but they're already doing that with Clyde Barker is already
apparently doing that so. Directing? It's apparently he's writing directing and producing the remake.
Any stars? Apparently Doug Bradley's coming back as pinhead. That's all I care about. They could
have fucking raccoons running around on the floor. I wouldn't give a shit. But it's the same story?
Like why why wouldn't you? Well it might not be. I'm sure it's going to be a different take. But
but I you know as long as Bradley's in there is pinhead. I mean that's why I watched all the goddamn
sequels. Yeah. And you know they were nothing there. A lot of them were nothing to write home about
right Pat you know what I mean is is it what's one would you do? I mean I think I would want to do
something imperfect like you know like my dream and my kind of thing that I feel I could write
really well would be like a misery. But I don't I couldn't improve on misery. So right well I'm
not by no means saying I could improve on creep show which is why I wouldn't want to remake the old
stories. Right. I would just want to see the thing started up again. Yeah I got you. I think
my dream would have been poltergeist until I saw what they did with poltergeist but maybe we could
pretend that didn't happen. I mean I just you know I don't know that's just who do you think they
would cast if they made by the way Skeetal Rich got just got stabbed with an umbrella. How is that
possible? You know actually you know what? Here's my dream and it's already happening but apparently it's
not going to be what we want it to be is that it remake. I would love a crack of that it remake. Oh yeah
that's a good one. Yeah that'd be good. That by the way the way Skeetal Rich just died head through
the TV and she said in your dreams. Yeah. That's a nod. I believe tonight we're in Street 3. 3. You're
going to be in pictures or a welcome to prime time bitch. Oh right I just watched a little more of that
documentary and the original line was like you finally got your dream to be in television and then
England improvised. Welcome to prime time bitch. I was outside of the Glendale Galleria. Braggar
which is our mall here in beautiful Los Angeles. Yeah and I saw a girl a woman and she looked
very familiar and I couldn't place it for a moment and then I realized who it was and I said you're
from Nymer and I'm Street 3. Wow and it was the TV and she seemed flattered. She was extremely
flattered. I said I want to tell you this you have the best kill in the entire franchise. Yeah
and she said that's so sweet of you lit up smile. She said God bless you. That's great. That was
very nice. You know I I will always recognize like an actor who's been acting a lot and there's
in a lot of shit like I told you about that Richard Reel that actor over at the diner here from office
space and a bunch of movies but like somebody who was in a movie in 1980 I'm not going to recognize
now we had on the show I write for we had on the guy who's named Jonathan Schmock and he played the
snooty guy at the fancy French restaurant in Ferris Bueller with the whole Abe Froman bit. That's great
like the real slick you know it was turned up guy or whatever and they told me the day after we shot
it I had no idea. I think I was really funny on the show. I had no clue and I would like I would
have so loved to ask him about Ferris Bueller but he looked completely different because it's been 30
years. That's amazing. That's amazing. What do you look like? He you you would never would have guessed
but apparently he wrote a lot with this guy Jim Valley who wrote for a rest of development.
He's a big writer and got into much other shit. I took my mom and dad to see a taping of Sullivan and
son. Yep because my mom was a big fan of the show and and Steve Burn got me in and everything and
whatever and but we were we're going in and Steve was taking us around and introducing my parents
to the cast and then he introduced us to the guest star for that week and he's like this is so
and so he was on the nanny and I was like oh holy shit that's like the guy from the nanny.
This girl's son of sea. Yeah it was the guy. Yeah but I didn't remember. Yeah I mean sometimes I
remember like we had Brian Doyle Murray on the show he doesn't look bad different than he did in
fucking. No vacation. No I remembered Brian Doyle. I was on an episode and that was that was
actually one of the greatest things I've ever got to experience in this business was when my parents
were on set it was the week after I taped. Yeah and I introduced them to Brian Doyle Murray and he
said and he tapped me on the shoulder and he said he's a good boy. That's nice. Yeah and there we
have it. Scream. Talked right to you. RIP West Craven of course.
West you're going to be greatly missed man. You did some really terrific work and
very influential shit for sure. You know I say it all the time. Nightmare in Elm Street was my
gateway horror movie. My mom showed it to me when I was 11 and I never turned back so you know I thank
West Craven for that for turning me on to horror for my entire life. Yeah and for me he just reminds me
of being a huge pussy when I was a kid. We talked about shocker a little bit but my friends being
like hey we got to watch Freddie or whatever and just dreading it all day. Things a lot of kids
are like oh sweet I get to watch Freddie. I would just be dreading it the entire day that I had to
watch the scary thing. I couldn't wait to see it man and shocker and all these movies that now are
considered terrible. I was like I can't believe I have to watch this scary. All these movies you're
saying West Craven's movies are considered terrible. Shocker. Oh the movie shocker. Yeah yeah I
read a thing online the other day that said that's a must see West Craven movie. I don't know. I should
rewatch it but I just remember I don't agree with that. They all they all did their job when I was a kid
and they scared the shit out of me and I knew I'm going to watch surfing in the rainbow tonight because I
never seen it. I can't wait to watch it. Craven I'm Craven some Craven. I'm Craven some Craven. We
miss you man and and Godspeed. Pat the people can follow you where? They can follow me on Twitter
Vine Instagram at the Patrick Walsh. If you have comments thoughts on the show you can go through
Fangoria. You can tweet us there. Joe DeRosa Comedy. On Instagram and Twitter and Vine which I
never even said. Please do that. Please you know we've got some couple iTunes reviews but we're
a new podcast so you know if you can review us or whatever you want to do help us stand out from
the pack that would be great. We hope you like us. We hope you have a good time. Those of you tweeting
at us all the time. We really appreciate it. It makes it exciting for us to do it as opposed to yes
you know going through the motions. It's very fun. Thank you for doing that. Leave a nice review if
you would on the iTunes page there. You've been listening to we'll oh and we'll be at the mile
high horror festival. Oh yeah. First week in of October the Sunday of that festival we will be doing
a live details to come. They told us what we're going to be doing but I don't want to confirm.
Yeah I don't have the official okay that we can talk to you. It sounded very cool so we got to make
sure that's the thing. Yeah but it's very very cool and we're doing a live podcast with a movie of
course and something that will make you heart fans quite happy. Denver mile high film festival horror
festival that's Sunday October 4th. Festival is all weekend but our thing is the Sunday. Our thing is
Sunday we'll have time and all that coming soon. You've been listening to we'll see you and how
a presentation of Fangoria podcast network produced by Thomas DeFail and executive produced by Ken
Hanley of Fangoria Entertainment. For press opportunities advertising inquiries and information about
we'll see you in hell contact Ken via his email can at Fangoria .com. Thanks folks we'll see you
next time in hell. Thanks guys.