Well howdy folks, it's will see you in hell and here we are patent
Joe ready to do the show, Joe and Pat ready to make it splat
No one where it's at like two fat cats
How about that
Alan a man I only know from the naked gun, but I assume he was a baseball announcer was that his thing how about that?
It had to be yeah, that was loud. It had to be and that that was I
Mean my god, what a great that's up there with well, that's I
Was a real sucker for when they would take like a thing like that and put it into a slapstick movie like a catch phrase
E thing for the other thing. So like my favorite one ever was
The guy from the Drew Carries Ryan styles war. It's fantastic. Oh
Hatchout's part do yeah, that always killed me by the way
There have been already now doing now doing ED commercials on on Instagram
What are ED erectile dysfunction?
Oh, don't act like you don't know Joe don't act like you don't know
Are they serious commercials or are they like funny Joe? They are quite serious. I talked about it on Lizzie Cooperman's podcast
He like because I just seen one on the way in he like
pops up in your feet and he's like hey
Listen, we've all struggled with it. It's that kind of thing
And I think it's because you and I have said the word blue choo so many times around our phones because we used to advertise for the blue choo products
You can't you can't you're not safe anywhere
No, of course not I mean Ryan's styles is in on the conspiracy
They've gotten everybody it's goddamn invasion of the body snatchers. Yes
For sure. I was just gonna say the the greatest if there's been literally articles written about it
But the greatest slapstick gag of all time is in Hatchout's part do the fact that it's a spoof of a Vietnam movie
It's starring Charlie Sheen his father Martin Sheen was in to tune the greatest of all Vietnam movies
They're passing each other on the boats and a couple apocalypse now
Our apocalypse now I met and Charlie was in platoon. I forgot yeah, and they're passing each other on the boats
And they do I loved you in Wall Street right which
They were both in which was directed by Oliver Stone who also directed platoon, which is considered to be the greatest Vietnam movie by the excitement of the apocalypse
It's it is so insane how good that joke is
there are
In rewatching the hot shots is
They're much more equal than I realized I used to put the original way above
Uh, but they're about equal Hatchout's part two has huge last the joke ratios and these things yeah
Recently as I think I might have said on here I rewatched two and a half with a buddy of mine and one
Naked gun one stands way above two and a half it just does to me, but two and a half has huge art laughs in it. Don't get me wrong
It's like um, I go back and forth one is the better movie. It's the more complete
Substantial film they could get the original
But two might have my more fake more I might have my favorite laughs in it which is a hard
We've talked about it the whole restaurant sequence is just insane. I mean, it's just non -stop man
I haven't had this much sex since I was a boy scout leader. I mean at the time I was dating a lot
Is two is two the one with and where the hell was I?
Yes, yeah walking into no, no, no, that's part one actually that is part worth. Yeah
Uh, yeah, he gets to like that sidewalk turns to hey underneath the speed
Now folks I cannot believe that we have waited this long because I've been sitting on this news talk about ring that scream at end
Now
Because they are remaking the naked gun not doing a new police spoofers or you know something original
They're remaking the naked gun at starring as frank driven
Liam Nison
They're a guy who's done you know one comedy appearance in Atlanta this year where he rift on a story
A news story where he said that once when a friend of his was raped
He walked through the streets looking for any black person to beat
He did a bit about that on Atlanta
Then he comes on Atlanta and does like a funny winking riff on it which was so weird
But then immediately they probably sent that directly over to the naked gun people and we're like hey, here's a real of him doing comedy
So I don't know how he to me
Liam Nison is not it whoever is the new frank driven it is not Liam Nison the writers are
two gentlemen who did
Rescue Rangers chip and Dale movie that everybody seemed to like on Disney plus
I didn't see it, but it's like they've been trying to crack this movie for 10 years and finally when they saw the chip and Dale movie
They said yes, this is this is what we want the naked gun to be
I will say this I will say this naked. Well, I'll say this one thing they did right here
And I do think that they did this right
They they did what they did with the original naked gun which was they went and they got a guy that's known for dramatic roles
That's what Leslie Nielsen was he was not a comedic actor. He had done true airplane. Yeah, but that was the whole point with airplane and with um
With airplane and with
Police squad the whole idea was
That they would do something that
You know with this guy that everybody knew as
As as a dramatic actor and that's why we'll be funny. So I like that they did the same thing with Leslie Nielsen same strategy
Now if it works or not, I can't speak to it. But it's the same strategy
um
And I will say Leslie Nielsen. I mean, I'm sorry uh Liam Neeson when he's
Playing something very dry. That's what happened. Maybe they heard Liam Neeson and they thought it was Leslie Nielsen
Maybe they're right. They got him
When he plays something very dry, it can be quite funny
um
You know the thing the thing he did in uh
Um
Life is too short. Life's too short. Okay. Yeah, it's hilarious. You know, I've got full blown aids like that was really funny man
That's these are really things where he's playing himself true. I think he could he'll
Maybe pull it off the guy uh is one of the lonely island guys and they do this kind of stuff very well
But we'll see we shall see
We shall see Paul
Uh Pat, we shall see. I know I always regret for sir. How many times I've sent Paul my business partner uh the link for the podcast
And he's like, what is this? I'm like, oh sorry
Yeah, I have to know that we all run together Joe just like your women
Oh Jesus, would you stop now folks? I
Last night couldn't sleep
I see somebody on twitter one of these blu -ray accounts I follow go
Holy shit huge maybe accidental question mark 4k sale going on right now at Best Buy
I go to Best Buy and Best Buy is full on doing a black Friday sale
Black Friday's in four weeks
But it says the words on their site black Friday sale and then this list of these 4k's that when
On for like 10 pages
I would have texted Joe but it was 4am where Joe was I was sad that I missed out on this
I said I
Immediately was like I got to buy these now because they're gonna realize the price is wrong bitch
Or you know, I could just wait and hopefully get them on black Friday
But these things sell out immediately so I felt like I was part of this very exciting time
I start checking out and then I go I wonder if Amazon is trying to keep up with them because I always wondered if Amazon changed their prices
By hand or if they had some sort of algorithm
Where if a new price is triggered Amazon changes their price because they're always supposed to be the lowest
So I go over to Amazon and I realized they are attempting in real time to match this crazy Best Buy sale
But they can't really keep up and in the process Amazon is mispricing a lot of shit
So I ordered in a blind
Like just rage so I have so many boxes coming from Amazon this week. It's gonna be Mike Christmas
I'm very excited about it. I need it. I owe it to myself
But I got to show you just the best buy haul I went in today
I everything I'm about to show you cost me around
Between five and ten dollars
And by the way, I'm setting up finally even after I said I wouldn't
A 77 inch 4k TV and a 4k blue ray player. I'm so fucking hard right now
What prompted them to do this sale for two hours at that time of day?
I don't understand. Oh very clearly somebody was working on the ad for Black Friday and accidentally posted it
So when I saw this guy say it on Twitter. I was like oh, it must be a mistake because it said Black Friday sale
We're a month away from Black Friday three weeks away
Here's what I got
Do me a favor pull the mic down to face your mouth a little more. It's like up over
Yeah, there you go. All right
All in glorious 4k in glorious bastards
Okay
Great film it is edge of tomorrow which I believe has changed its name to live die repeat
But if you see in this speaking of Tom Cruise, I'm not a huge yeah, I'm not a I wasn't into it
Yeah, it's a good movie. I just wasn't into it loved it. Monty pythons meaning a life
All right, so far I'm not too mad. I missed this. I know you're gonna like this one Elvis
Oh, okay, 499
five
Wolf of Wall Street, I know you don't like that one either because you're dumb. I've been meaning to revisit Wolf of Wall Street
In my opinion a modern classic the last duel. Oh, yeah, ultimate collector's addition
Jurassic Park said to look absolutely amazing and fork. That's very cool
The Northman
Which I loved don't care
Guy on the way out of Best Buy today look more stone than I've ever been in my life working a shift at Best Buy
And he goes hey, you just get a player
And I go yeah, and he goes you got dune
And I go no, and he goes dude buy fucking dune
He's like, I think it's like 10 bucks. I go. I didn't like dude. He goes just buy it man trust me
So I bought two right here. Do
Oh boy
The untouchable starring noted wife beaters Sean Connery. Joe and I were just watching the hilarious video of Sean Connery
Doubling down on slapping his wife if you haven't seen it
Please
Is on Marvel Walters the fact that he gets the joke out that level of pressure he's under in that moment. Yeah
Barbara Walters at a time when this is the most watched interview on television
He's sitting in the hot seat and she goes you're going to get mail over this and he goes female
The fact that I get some free mail that that joke out the that he's that calm is insane
It's crazy. It's Barbara Walters thinks she's got him
Is it true? Today somebody would say oh, I didn't mean that or that was taken out of context whatever that you said sometimes
It's good to hit your wife and he was like
I don't know about wood. I think sometimes it has to happen
He just immediately laughs like yeah. Yeah, it's a lash. There's what you know
You're like some women they don't know when to stop and sometimes you have to tell them, you know
It's crazy. He's never looked more handsome in his life. He's smirking a little bit
It's wild and then he hits her with a joke at the end and she's clearly flustered but
She's kind of laughing a little bit at what he's saying like it's weird
And Sean Connery was married for 60 years. It's like, you know
The first time I ever made work for him. I don't know for the first time I've ever mentioned in Garafalo
I did a bit about that. I had a show that I produced with Jared Logan
Yeah, and she was on the show and I was so excited
Uh, and I did a bit about that before I brought her on stage and I said I was talking about how like lame like clickbait scandals are
I'm like right Sean Connery said this. I bet you didn't even know because nobody cared which is crazy
Yeah, and then she came on stage and she was like I remember being so excited. She addressed me
She was like Joe
That's a funny bit, but they did care. He got in a lot of trouble for that. And I was like, oh wow. I didn't know that um
I didn't name it in my life. Yeah
Uh, that's a nice way to handle that but he's doing it on the heels by the way
On the heels of doing Indiana Jones three like the guy
Yeah, he's like on a press door. It's crazy
Anyway, go ahead
Uh, I that untouchables hurt. I would have liked if you had gotten me a copy of that, but I don't think he did
Well, I might spend full price on that one wait for a black Friday. It's gonna happen again clearly
And then also amazon is still trying to play catch up so get on there and search some of these things they might be real cheap
This element which I haven't seen since theaters and saying film if I recall
Bigger to recall total recall, which I have always loved and can't wait to see in glorious forecast. Yes, that's a good one
Patriot games 499 haven't seen it since I was a kid
T2. I know you don't like it. Well, that's but it's a good that's a good grab
Ghostbusters the original. Oh, that's cool
Folks, the dark crystal. Oh, I just got that 4k I think and then the one I'm most excited about because I have seen so many nerds
Gizzing about how amazing it looks my favorite horror movie of all time
Polity Geist
This has been like 34 99 since it dropped
I
Got it for 999 a great haul I got more coming from amazon. It's the kind of haul you want to share with a friend rub in his face. I
Thought I'd bought that dark crystal
Well, I got a haul and I got to tell you it's like I'm a little pissed here because
You know screen factory did the big old
I'm trying to find you know here's the thing with screen factory or shout factory
They're one of the great offenders
with
If you don't buy the thing
In your fucking cart. Yes. Oh my god, man. They email you every 10 minutes should be illegal should be illegal
It's invasive and I hate it. Yeah, you left something behind, you know, did you forget? No, I didn't no, I didn't
But on you know, but they did this huge half -off sale in October
They put a big ticker on it you had you had to set 10 days to get in on it or whatever whatever
I got graveyard shift which I'm a sucker for it's not a great movie, but I'm a sucker for graveyard shift
I got tails from the hood finally
I got silver bullet and I got army of darkness which I'm also not a huge fan of
But I was like I'm gonna give it another chance and also for 15 bucks. I'll take it. I only own it on VHS
This fucking thing I ordered these movies on October 8th
The status is still order taken on the website. I emailed saying
Very politely hey guys any update on when these things might ship. It's been a month. They haven't even responded yet
It's like come on. What the fuck? What are you guys doing? You guys aren't like a small little
Just ain't a mom and pop come on and they send out three emails a day
So it's like guys if you need money
I'm here to give you some money. That's my thing lately. It's like
I want to give you money. Why are you making this hard on me?
Yeah, I'm a little irritated with you know Barnes and Noble just did this to me. I finally got into the cure
I
Took me some time
But I'm loving the first four cure albums 17 seconds three something boys
Faith I think is the third
Those three are the ones and then pornography I think was the fourth but those are the three that I really
Incredible live band right up to this day
Yeah, and you know I order these goddamn things and
They go great will ship them out. Here's your expected receivable date whatever all that shit
I get 17 seconds and the other two it's like
They're just not there and it's like they should be there on Monday. Well, it's Monday. It's they're not here
There's no you know, I mean, it's like you gotta tell the person
When they're ordering it hey hey dude like this one's not here right if it says it's in stock
And it says it'll be delivered by that day that means that's what you're supposed to do
I'm sorry is there an influx of people ordering cure vinyl right now on the Barnes and Noble website
Like what the fuck I mean honestly
I think they are so understaffed that when they do like one of these criterion sales they do just don't have like no
Either no one cares or they don't have the manpower anymore
But everywhere is just kind of at the end of their rope and
The customer services is an abomination. I had to stop. I pulled my whole amazon account because
Things were getting stolen so much along the route or not getting delivered and then it just fell on me
To over the whole cost of the item
Meanwhile, they sent me an album. I ordered this week in a plastic bag
Plastic but no bubble wrap
Plastic bag I open it all four corners are bent so you see the vinyl pressing out of the sleeve almost and I'm like well now
I have to take time out of my day
To go get this setup print up a label do all this should take it to the UPS store and everything
And they do it all the time don't send a record in a paper in a plastic bag. You're the number one
Retailer in the world
Yeah, it's that's that's a bummer. That's a real bummer
Shout -outs to vinyl junkies
Which I'd never purchased from
Okay, but and this is also a scary stuff
I got the two dead cross finals from them dead cross is a hardcore band
Red cross but not dead cross dead cross is a is a hardcore band with Dave Lombardo from Slayer
uh
Michael Crane
From a band called retox
Justin Pearson
Who's in a bunch of
Harder edged bands also with from retox and then Mike Pat the great Mike patent from Faith No More and Mr. Bungle whatever
um
And they are definitely a darker
sounding band spooky at times
Anyway, they put a new record out last week
Called dead cross two um, I was excited about it especially because Mike patent bailed on the Faith No More Tour last year
And then revealed he was suffering from agoraphobia
Which was a real bummer and I hope he's okay and and I'm glad to see that he puts something out that he's feeling a little bit better
um
But I got these dead cross records from vinyl junkies because it was like and I had never ordered from vinyl junkies
And it was a place where they had both of the records
And it wasn't like
One's gonna cost 56 dollars and the other one costs seven
You know what I mean? It was like here are the two albums you want. They're both priced at 24 bucks
There you go, right and I bought them. I had them within a week
It's like yeah, thank you
That's all anybody's asking for here man like you know or an email saying sorry we're backed up like I get it
I get it. I own a business. We we get backed up. We hit
We get rushes and and it takes longer to get the food or what I get it like
You don't have to be an asshole to the to the for prider or the supplier
But the supplier should also be like sorry. It's taking a minute. You know what I mean, right? Um
So I don't know. It's just that's that's that's all I'm saying
Sorry
Okay
It's gonna be all right
Is that was that too intense? No, no
I mean, I hear you. It's every it's every encounter. I walked into the post office this morning walk right back out
line of 79 people I'm like
Um in movie news
Yes, you know, I just wish there was more reporting on Hugh Jackman's return as Wolverine. Oh for fuck's sake
Enough already enough when I saw the headline
Hugh Jackman
New the moment he saw Deadpool
That he never should have retired Wolverine. I'm like why
What are the two heaven common Wolverine was a depressed miserable man deadpools a wise cracking carefree
Why would you think that
Hugh Jackman
Because you saw dollar signs. Yeah, exactly because nobody wouldn't saw
Predestination or whatever the fuck that HBO Max original was called that I watched 12 minutes of when I had nothing else to do and couldn't get as the 12 minute mark
I mean by the way
movieweb .com which is you know was for many years my go -to site for movie news
Guys I get you got to put content out every day but articles like
Don't worry darling how to watch from home guys we'll figure it out
Jesus Christ
This is insane I mean like
It's it's listen to this to where is it where is it uh
It was what oh Henry Kaville's eight highest grossing movies
Oh my god, he's only done about 12 movies. That's it. Yeah, so it was Superman mission impossible and then nothing
um
The uh oh great a new Percy Jackson movie because the first one was such a runaway success that movie flopped so bad that they made a joke about it in the trip
In the trip
Wait in the Steve Cougan trip. Yeah Rob what's his name
He go when he got with Steve who goes you do one for them you do one for me. That's how I do
And then he goes he goes does that explain Percy Jackson
I would say the better joke is who who was Percy Jackson for
Oh, that's he might even say that yeah, yeah, but uh I did not see it. I did not uh give a shit
But are you saying they are rebooting it with new kids playing
Yeah, they're making new lightning thieves
Unless it's a sequel to a fucking franchise nobody remembers like that
Everybody smelled that as the Harry Potter ripoff. It was and moved on with their lives
What do you get what's next? We're gonna reboot guardians of ghoul?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, gears of war being turned into a movie because yes
We need more video games being turned into movies it never works and I'm a fan of both genres people
But the where is paper boy the movie where is
Tube and the movie I think I told you this when I was working on a project with rooster teeth
Yes
I went in to have a meeting recently disgraced
Uh conglomerate rooster teeth wait what happened with them
You can look it up. It was a all sorts of allegations. They like went down on a blaze of glory
I think oh jeez that might be speaking out of term because but but look them up
It's not good whatever's happening over there
Well, I went in for a meeting with the this guy Brian who's not there anymore
He now runs Tom sigora's company, but I I said uh
He had to he had a book or whiteboard in his office
Yeah, and it was video game projects were working on for movies whatever
Uh -huh, and one of those was paper boy
I got I looked at him and I go let me just stop you whatever you say
What the fuck could paper boy possibly be about enough? I'd been in that room
I would have walked out with a contract. I would have walked out with a contract
God, but he said it. I guess when I met there. I didn't see the paper boy whiteboard
He was after that. Oh, it was a different it was the Austin location, but uh
Anyway, the Gears of War movie is calling for Dave Batista. Yes, because we don't get enough of him
Oh boy, and then anything that keeps him from from playing a dad to an adorable little girl
Is fine. Just keep him in the action genre and I won't watch it
Um, why are why is everything so bad
Uh, what was the but the reason I had movie web open oh
It's this martin warrants is gonna star in a now you've got my interest
This is interesting a thriller
Go on opposite
Melkovich
Slow down
Call that's gonna be that's gonna be a direct uh
On demand Joe. That's not a real movie. Well, here's the here's the title the title is what
Mind cage
Yeah, that's not getting up the actual release Joe. We're not seeing mind cage on the big screen
It's described here as an exciting game of cat and mouse between two detectives
Oh my god, that is the most generic
Tagline I've ever heard. I thought there was more to it. No, that
We're doomed because all of our movie stars are going this route
To the director on demand route. I had a friend pitch a big comedy at paramount the other day
They said
We're our target audience is Diane Keaton. We're looking for Diane Keaton projects
Diane Keaton should be playing mummies
She's a hundred years old. I love Diane Keaton, but like your target audience
What are you doing
That's really depressing somebody goes into pitch a comedy by the way it was a comedy about two 40 -year -old women
Wasn't like somebody who was pitching American pie 12 was about two 40 -year -old woman they go no
Our target is Diane Keaton and the people who love her meaning to them
100 -year -olds
By the way, there should always be projects made for and about 100 -year -olds don't get me wrong
We love grumpy old men
You know, we love grumpy old men. We love grumpy old men. I'm just saying
I'd like to see
I'd like to see Keaton in that kind of thing. Oh, yeah, yeah, just stop doing body -switching movies for God's sake
Um, I I would like to see Keaton in a grumpy lady
You know, like why does why is it always the men doing that? Oh speaking of which Christ
This fucking Tom Hanks thing like the United States of Gus or whatever the fuck it's called. Oh, yeah as good as it gets watered down
25 times
Jesus Christ
I don't think it is called the truth about Gus, but it might as well be
That's that's a very funny guess. I thought it was maybe stew
I got now I got to know what that movie is called
Oh my god, and it's like it's like they're so afraid to offend anybody now a man called auto
Todd and the poster is
It's Tom Hanks wearing a windbreaker gray hair says a man called auto
That's it. They're not even trying anymore
Try try to get me in the theater
Jesus Christ. I mean
I don't know man. I don't know
It's a it's a guy whose wife died so he's kind of a mild asshole, but not a real asshole because
You know even now as good as it gets you couldn't do it
He's throwing out slurs left and right so they got to make him a little grumpy
That's not a movie. That's not a plot of a movie Tom Hanks is a little grumpy
I
Mean
That's what I'm saying. It's like it's like they're so afraid of offending anybody
like
It's that's it's a mild grump. That's it. That's all it is. You know what I mean? Like you can't do like as good as it gets
Is a true like he's a true asshole in it like he's a damaged guy
And many times it like make yeah, I saw in the theater people get gas like it was watching a horror movie
Like some of the things he would say to people like really rough stuff
And Helen Hunt's damaged in it. She's fucked up like it's it's
But I mean my god almighty man like this this thing. It's like it's like a guy that like doesn't say thank you
And they're like oh can you believe the show you you got to call up the poster and see the face Tom Hanks is making on the poster
What's it called a man called a man called auto
And the tagline folks is fallen love with the grumpiest man in America
Oh god
Look at the face this man is making that's that's as much grump as we can muster
Oh jeez
Is that is that embarrassing?
Looks like a guy that squeezed out is secretly squeezing out a fart. That's a thing. Not that secretly not that secretly
And it's it's by the way, it's a remake of a man called Ove or Ove
Yeah, yeah, yeah, which was from
Did you say this already and I didn't hear you say no
Which is okay good it's a
Which is based on a worldwide bestseller book
And that's got a great tagline. You ready for the tagline which is it's from like Austria or some shit. I don't know somewhere
The tagline on a man called Ove or however you say is misery hates company. That's a good tagline
That is
Doesn't put asses in the seats though
That's also uncomfortably close to the title of the movie. I've been trying to make Missouri loves company
Which I'll read you
Huh, I don't think that's those taglines are no I did. I'm saying. I don't think those taglines are close
This is like that. They did to try to do one of these with Bill Murray. It didn't really work
Um
Uh, just why why
Why
God damn it why do another Meg Ryan movie just do make another god damn Meg Ryan thing
Joe Meg Ryan has gone into hiding
She hasn't been seen since the last time she showed her face and everyone said we hate your face now
I want
And you know, I love movies about old people falling in love. They too
I I would love and not that Tom Hanks and Meg Ryan are old, but they're older people. I'd like to see them
I'd like to see that. I'd like you know, we're talking Diane Keaton. I've said it for years
And by the way, she's still like friends with Woody Allen
So there's nothing stopping this from happening other than the two of them
Make a fucking sequel to Annie Hall where you guys meet again in your in your 80s that that would be an endearing thing to watch to me
Steady's gonna go to Paris to make this fucking
Spy thriller or whatever the fuck he's doing
I hope we get a sequel to riftkins festival before it all blows up
Jesus Christ
Star wall a shaw the only other person will talk to him anymore. I've not heard good things
No, I haven't either I have a riftkins festival
Let's get over to
Oh the movie corner sorry for my cough
I
store
a little
Epic shit called
After son I'd like to start with after son is probably my favorite movie of the year
Knock me out loved it
It is Paul Mescal from normal people which was a show I loved on Hulu
Uh, I think he's a really good actor. He's got that kind of vibe of like a young
Ruff low -hat early on and you can count on me and we always talk about how now he's playing the Hulk and he's giving up
And I hope mescal avoids the
Marvel route because I really like him and he's really talented in this
uh
It is very clearly the director's
recollection
I don't know how autobiographical it is but
uh
Her recollection of a trip with her dad when she was like 11 years old
And her dad is about 30
So Paul Mescal plays her dad they go on a vacation together
And at first you think okay, it's going to be kind of a cutesy little indie
Father daughter flick where they're kind of bonding
And then little by little it just starts getting deeper and deeper and more interesting
But you got to pay attention to it. So like
The dad Mescal is clearly having some personal problems he's separated from the mom
You don't know why or he's divorced from the mom. You don't know why
And then little by little you start to get why like and it's all these great little touches where like
He's sitting with his daughter watching the show at the resort at night
And there's like eight empty giant beer glasses in front of him
You're like, oh, okay, this guy might have a drinking problem that kind of thing
But uh all that shit starts building up and the movie just gets
Deeper more intense
They're acting is so good so natural
They had a great soundtrack to it
It's set in like the early 90s, so it's like blur
REM that kind of stuff
Um, I love the movie. I think we'll probably see a few nominations
I like to talk sometimes like I'm on like good good morning america
I think we'll probably see some nominations
But um I dug it. I really really dug it. It's my favorite movie so far of the year
um
And it's one of those where
You have your own very strong theories, but you're so excited when you get home to like google it and read everybody else's theories
Not that it's that mysterious really. It's just kind of a character study
But they leave so much unsaid that they're it's open to a lot of interpretations
So it's the kind of movie that really rewards a couple of youings I think check it out when it comes out
So as I teased in the last episode
I'm gonna do these these three Woody Allen movies that are
You know three of my favorites if not my three favorites one of them is my damn favorite movie of all time, but
I think these fit into the sort of atomic atomic fall romantic new york comedy thing
And I think they work as an
unofficial trilogy and I've never noticed it before but the first is Annie Hall
You know, it's his seminal whatever you want to call it
You you've probably all seen it
It is a pitch -perfect romantic comedy. It's very funny
You know, it's him and Diane Keaton at their best. It's it's the moment he turned as a filmmaker and started to do things that were more about real people
and less about
You know and less about like exaggerated fantastic situations
And it's it's it's just a great movie
um
It sets the stage though for for what I'm gonna say about the next two when I get to them
He plays a comedy writer. He plays a guy that's obsessed with death and that is painfully neurotic
His partner Tony Roberts
Is pushing him through the entire movie to move to Los Angeles to get a fresh start. He hates LA. He doesn't want to go
Um, he's obsessed with New York
You see how that sort of holds him back in in his life and ways
and
Depending on what lends you watch the movie through he tanks the relationship
Diane Keaton certainly plays somebody with her hang -ups and her neuroses
But he is really the problematic in my opinion more problematic of the two in the relationship
um
And it ends on a on a on a hopeful note where after they break up
They reconvene and they have a great time catching up
But relationships are crazy blah blah blah and that's kind of where the movie ends
um
And when we when I return on my next movie, I'll talk about the second movie
But that sets the stage any off you haven't seen it. I mean god watch it
Uh, unless you hate it what he owns got so much that you can't watch his movies
Then I would say don't but if you if you can stomach the man
It's a it's a wonderful film and that is one of the most Woody Allen of Woody Allen movies because he's in there
He's right in there. He's right in there. It's all everything and it's it's really also too sets the stage for Diane Keaton
It's like for the rest of her career. It's like lovely charming
You know
What's the word?
You know um carefree whimsical Diane Keaton. I mean this is
This is the Diane Keaton. We all know and love, you know, right? And this is kind of where it all begins. I think so
Uh
Joe to rip off an old bandaid. I finally rewatched midsummer
Which many have asked us to do
um
And I'll say this my review the first time I saw it for hereditary. I believe was four and a half out of five
All my letterbox
My review of midsummer was five stars
Seeing it a second time
I think it's more a four and a half star picture
I still feel very highly about it but I can't admit I came down a little bit from my initial you know what happened when I first saw it
And it's much like I always talk about the uh
When I saw the sixth sense I didn't realize I had a hundred and six fever and I was so terrified that I thought I was dying
But I like my brain was being baked and cooked
So when I saw midsummer the credits start and it's got that real sickening music right when you know at the beginning right before you find their parents
With that really really disturbing scene
And the music is so unsettling and weird and there was this massive earthquake in the valley
Which is where I met my buddy to see it at 10 a .m. On the 4th of july
And it rocked the theater and everybody screamed and was running out
And then we calmed down it came back in and like kept watching midsummer
But it was really unsettling and I think that intensified that viewing
I will say are there are there scenes that can get to the point faster? Yes
But I think he's a guy who is clearly a fan of Kubrick fan of a guy who uses a lot of long shots
Um
And you feel midsummer's influence already in the way it looks like I was in smile. There's all these shots where
Uh, they flip the screen. It's going upside down. You know, they do it a bunch of times and smile
And you watch midsummer's just the exact same shot they they not that that that that it was original in midsummer either
But I think it's influenced
Horror a lot for better or worse in recent times, but I think it's made it sort of weirder
maybe a little more interesting
and
It's a super effective all -day light horror movie
To me
You know easily one of the best horror movies of recent years and
Just as the first one is about
Heredity and you know your parents and what you inherit and so forth
And that those themes kind of sink in more as you watch it and you're not as scared on a second and third viewing
midsummer is very much about a relationship toxic relationships bad relationships
And watching it through that lens
You know deep in the movie for me. I think the guy knows what he's doing
I'm a fan of the movie
I stand by it all right. That's cool
Uh
I watched
Second in this trilogy
hand -enters sisters my favorite movie of all time master cut. Yeah
If you haven't seen it it is the most insightful film I've ever seen into the human condition
And how we think about relationships how we deal with rejection and sadness and depression
Why people who have seemingly perfectly happy lives make their lives harder for no apparent reason
Uh the meaningless of life. It hits the existential peak
Of the Woody Allen movies that examine those themes like
It's it's hilariously funny um
It's wild glasses and coats on Michael Cain. Yeah, it's yeah you get great cast
Michael Cain Barbara Hershey me a Farrow
Diane Weiss Max von Seedow
Daniel Stern
Carrie Fisher again
Uh John Cena
John Cena Dave Bautista
Uh
It's just a great and Woody Allen
It's just a great movie uh Woody Allen's storyline of him finding out he might have a brain tumor
And the way that makes him reassess his life it is
The funniest
Version of Woody Allen you'll ever see a guy just having a complete fucking meltdown
Uh
And because it removes the usual discomfort of him romancing someone who's like 40 years younger than him
Yeah, it's it's an inward dilemma, so you like him a lot more because everybody can relate to that
Yeah, yeah exactly so uh Julie Cavner places like assistant in the movie and she's great. Yeah
Uh
Yeah, it's just one of my favorite lines in the movie she goes uh
He he he he he's like why do I have to go get tests if nothing is why do I need to go get if nothing is wrong
Why do I have to go get more tests and she goes to just to rule everything out
Uh, but nothing is wrong and he goes that's just what they tell you because the weaker ones may panic
Uh, that's just so funny because he's just freaking out but anyway um the movie's just amazing um
And it
To me feels like an evolution of the character from Annie Hall because now here he is at a later stage in his life
He's divorced
From me a pharaoh's character in the movie
You find that he can't really have a relationship because he's
Need deep in him in his own bullshit and his own work
He's a more amplified neurotic version of himself than he is in the previous film
Um, and in this he talks about how his stupid writing partner again played by Tony Roberts has moved to LA
And everything he does is a big hit and he's got the greatest life ever
uh, and it is quietly, you know, they don't call this out directly
But it's quietly hurting him that Tony Roberts is also the guy that had to donate sperm to me a pharaoh
So they could have a baby because Woody Allen sperm wasn't strong enough
so um
It's a very interesting evolution thematically of Annie Hall uh and and and and a seemingly again
unofficial evolution of the character he is in that first movie into now who he is in this movie
And it's continued on lastly in the third movie. I'll review
And I'll get to it when I when it's my turn
but hand -enters sisters to me is
The greatest
Woody Allen movie the greatest
The greatest of all New York movies like it's just it just it just hits every note perfectly and an ottoman New York
Yes exactly another yet another ottoman New York
So I
Want I would say definitely my favorite Thanksgiving was one believe it or not where I stayed here and didn't go home
But thanksgiving Eve I went to the arrow theater in Santa Monica, which is a beautiful old theater and they showed hand -enters sisters and plants trans automobiles
Wow, that's killer
Yeah, hand -enters sisters opens and closes on thanksgiving right that's the book and scenes of the movie
And you can wears Waldo's spot yourself a young Sunni around the Thanksgiving table she's in yeah she's in the last uh
It adds an interesting twist
To the watching yeah
I finally found a movie that has been just disgusting Joe for months and I can't say I blame him confess flesh
Directed by Greg Matola, you know, super bad adventure land, you know, he's done good stuff. He's also done really bad stuff
I'm like look
I'm interested every other time this has come up the flesh movie
I know Bill Lawrence who's the Ted Lasso scrubs guy
I know him a bit
He wrote a draft that was like almost got shot with Zach Braff as flesh that wound up not happening
That would have been fucking great that's a flesh that was happening
It was like almost green lit and then they want to pull on the plug on it remember when and not to cut you off
But remember to and now I don't know that Kevin Smith would have been the right director for it
But he was gonna do the Fletcher reboot with Jason Lee Jason Lee would have been a fantastic fucking Fletcher Jason Lee is essentially doing Fletcher
They were gonna do it at one point with Joel McCale who I find a little smug and annoying, but so is Chevy chase and so is the character of how about
How about let's just walk down Dream Street for a minute Ryan Reynolds would have just I mean it would have been a grand
That was happening for at least two three years was Ryan Reynolds was doing a Fletch then he pivoted to clue now he's remaking clue instead
Yeah, but
Sudakis was in the mix
What's interesting is that all of these people
sound like pretty good Fletches and who do they cast a dark horse that no one considered John Hamm
I like a lot of people consider madman one of the all -time great television dramas
And I consider John Hamm's performance
Absolutely amazing nobody else could have played it when I see him in other stuff
Sometimes he doesn't ring true
But as like the asshole and bridesmaids and a little bit part in comedies. I kind of like him
I'd never thought of him as this too smart for the room if anything John Hamm seems kind of dim -witted to me
So he doesn't play
He doesn't do any of the costumes of course. It's not like Fletch lives where you got him in brown face or anything like that
But he also can't commit to any of the voices A because John Hamm is not a master of many voices
But B because at one point they haven't played a gay interior decorator
But he can't do the flamboyant gay caricature anymore. So he just plays it like John Hamm
So there's all these allegedly comedic scenes that don't really make any comedic choices
Not that I need stereotypes to be funny. I just mean if you're gonna build a comedic premise around
This guy is going to play a gay character. You expect something other than what we get in the movie, which is not a choice
Um, Kyle McLaughlin's kind of funny as as a character, you know, there's a bunch of wacky kooky characters in it
I like Roy Wood Jr. a lot as it stand up and he seems like a cool dude
He's kind of charming in it
Marsha gay harden comes in from a completely different movie. She is doing an insane character
But she's like you'll probably wondering why I mean she's literally like doing it like
She's in a movie about Transylvania
Um
It's nuts, you know, it doesn't it doesn't really work
And yet
There's these small character scenes. There's like, you know, John Slattery comes in who was also great on madman and him and ham have him and ham
have a great chemistry
Um, there's occasional comic moments that sort of work the mysteries moderately entertaining
But I don't get why everybody is gizzling about this movie
Because they have to because because because who
I'll tell you to who to their friends you don't have to you don't have to publicly shit on it
But why are you gizzling about it because it's because they're playing the game
This is what it all is anymore everybody knows every every every movie that gets made now and every TV show that gets made now is made by the same 15 fucking people
Yeah, that's true, and it's to a point where it's also corporatized
People don't want to shit anything on anything because Netflix made it and they're scared they'll get blackballed by Netflix
Yeah, it's ridiculous
It's ridiculous. So everybody's got to pretend like it's all fucking great and then quietly talking the shadows about what they really think of it
And that's where the fuck we're at
You know, it's all it's all big fucking conglomerate. How can you shit on a Marvel movie publicly when every one of your god damn
Colleagues is in one you have to just pretend like it's all great
And then it's the six degrees of separation thing well like
Well, he wasn't in that one, but he's friends with the guy from that one and that one's being directed by the guy
I know from that thing and that it's fucking ridiculous
So this is a perfect example of it. You named six people in the in the review
That connect in some way shape or form to everybody in comedy right now. Yeah, that's true
You know, it's just it's not a strong mystery and it's not a strong comedy
So it's not really making big choices in either direction
I'm not saying I remember the mystery of flesh or certainly flesh lives either
But it's the charisma of Chevy chase goes a really long way
On him just simply does not have that kind of light up a room charisma
He's great at playing a very emotionally closed off guarded man
But he's not the guy who walks into a room and charms everybody and buys them around a drinks. That's not yeah
No the vibes are off from the jump and I used to read these flesh books
I know the character and I wouldn't have minded a different take on it
But this is not really a take it's just kind of a very average
Everything kind of movie very white bread blah blah. Yeah, it's um
I just it looked it looked so boring yeah kind of is like it just looked so fucking
Boring where it was just like it's just jar on ham solving a mystery with a little bit of wit
Yeah, yeah
And like he goes to
This woman's house who's like a stoner
So like she's like being a little wacky while he's trying to interrogate her like she's slightly stoned
But the whole thing is played like
You'd do it in a seven like in a threes company where you can't show the joint
It's like guys, isn't this an r -rated movie here like every choice was so vanilla
And boring and that's just where we're at we'll get out of it
We'll get out of maybe maybe my final film
In this
unofficial trilogy is is a movie called anything else which was
Panned by critics, but is one of my absolute favorite Woody Allen movies
Um one of Quentin Tarantino's favorite films
Stars Jason Biggs and Christina Ricci. This is the phase where
Woody Allen sort of casting like a younger person as the Woody Allen character and then he'd play like an older version of it
um
Their comedy writers the joke in the beginning is we're both fledgling comedy writers trying to break into the business
The only difference is I was 21 and he was 60
uh
But in this movie it's it's a romantic comedy again New York City the whole thing
And it's now Woody Allen coaching Jason Biggs who plays a guy named Falk
On why his relationship isn't gonna work why he needs to get out of it and why it's problematic
And in this one Christina Ricci is the more problematic of the two yet they are both problem
But if you put this movie up against Annie Hall
It's kind of like she's playing the amplified
Woody Allen person from Annie Hall with all these crazy neuroses who's controlling the whole thing and and destroying it
And he's playing the more dying Keetney kind of thing who's at a loss
And then you've got Woody Allen who now is playing a guy whose older
Who's quote trying to break into comedy uh
And who's essentially dropped out of life which his character does do in Hannah and her sisters
Uh who's telling a guy
I know you're worried about dying and I know you're worried about the importance of life
And I know you're worried about all these things by the way all these things that his character
Was worried about in the previous movies that I've mentioned all of these things that he talks about
As a character in this movie having previously pined over and been worried about in all these things
Uh, and now he's at a different place where he realizes that life really has no meeting and and this is what it is
Which his character realizes at the end of Hannah and her sisters
And it's almost like a full circle thing where he's coaching Jason Biggs
On how to handle the relationship because he's been there already which we saw him be there in Annie Hall
It's a very very funny movie
Uh
It's got one of my favorite Woody Allen movie jokes ever in it
And Jason Biggs says I have a fear of death and Woody Allen goes that's incredible. I have that my dog has it
It's very common amongst living creatures
Uh
It's a very very funny movie uh
It's it's a fun watch and again. I think these three these are three movies that to me should be in like a little box set together
Um because he never you want
To be a box set maker
Yes, I would like to be a box set maker
That's I don't know how much money is in that especially today, but it's worth a look
I that's a should I should but I should move to a small village in Italy
And be a
Artisan box that's him
Anyway, whittling
And he never really went back. It's funny when you you you you think that every Woody Allen movie is the movies that I'm talking about
Yeah, but when you really look at the whole catalog. There's only a few and these are kind of it
These are the three that really touch you jump into that new york
The plight of romance
existential crisis like he gets into these themes in other movies, but these are the
But even that is more like it's darker. It's not that funny because it's not supposed to be
You know like like like like people always talk about um
Oh god, what's the one where he goes to the festival that everybody always uh
The black and white one where he goes. Oh star dust memories. Star dust memories. People talk about Tentious movie ever
Yeah, like like people talking about Broadway Danny Rose
That those are not these movies like these movies when you step back
These are really the three where he did this in this style and he never did it again
And I wonder he's the kind of guy though. I was talking to my friend about this if you said this to him in an interview
You could literally show him his own notes where you'd be like look
Here's where you wrote down that this was an unofficial sequel and he would just go
I'm people uh, they say that about I think that's great, but I just thought it was funny
He loves to downplay everything so it makes him seem more brilliant, which is annoying
Yeah, he's very annoying
But anyway um those are your those are your goddamn movie. They were they're gonna say you know, I can't control what people say
And that's it right we're on to this movie
That's it
We are on to the movie of the week and one of the biggest horror movies of the year 2022
Which surprised a lot of people I think movie is called smile
Uh
The trailer when I saw it for this thing I was really rolling my eyes. I was like
So that's it like it's the it's a killer smile like when you see someone smile that you like this
It kills you or something. I just thought it looked corny as hell
I've never been creeped out by a smile and it's been done to death the creepy smile
They do it constantly the man who laughs the Joker I agree these are all the things I felt too
But then you saw it and said you got to see this thing and I did take us through the plot wash
The plot is uh
A young woman played by Soci Bacon
That is the daughter of Kevin Bacon and
Hira Sedgwick
Uh who I had not seen in anything. I don't think although I thought she was great in the movie. I she was kind of new to me
Uh, she is a therapist she witnesses a patient commit suicide
The patient is having these like frightening visions of somebody like smiling and advancing
And suddenly she sees Soci Bacon as that
Smiling sort of demon figure coming at her and she kills herself right in front of that's the lady's name Soci Bacon
Daughter of Kevin Bacon
Sedgwick yes
Joe was out of the room folks. He missed them when I just said them. Oh, I well
All right, take it easy. I had to know. I'm just I'm explaining to the public. I'm sorry. All right. Fair enough. The folks
Um, but anyway
Uh, her boss at the hospital is of course
Kumar from here to Kumar white castle which was surprising, but I liked him in the role and uh
I enjoyed seeing he's that's all he's doing now. It's like these little serious
Yeah, and then you can I rewatch and politics. He's he's he's like made an aim for himself in politics
I rewatch channeled in kuma recently and I'm like does he roll his eyes at this thing or is he just like hey, we had fun
But I mean, it's wild that the show now. He's I think they might do another. They're always talking about doing more hell to kuma
Uh, but yeah from there
This soci bacon character
Who is engaged
That is sort of a strange bit of casting. There's a few kind of strange bit of castings the guy
Uh, and her have no real chemistry. She does have a lot of chemistry with Kyle Galner who is her ex who I've known it's seen in a lot of movies lately
Um, I like that kid. I do too. The movie has maybe one too many sub plots. It's maybe a little too long
You could have popped Rebecca Hall right in here and had
Not missed a beat and I bet honestly, Rebecca Hall passed on it and probably regrets it. Well
Becky Becky. Bay Becky. Yeah, hear me out back
This is the kind of hard flick you should be doing doing one that has something happening in it
Like she keeps doing these like things that are like they're she do these horror movies that are like checkoff plays that they had a few jump scares to you
Christ do one of these
Be the Patrick Wilson of the you know what I mean
Yeah, there was this thread going around on Twitter where it said um
There is a filmmaker who made what turned out to be one of the biggest horror movies of the year
Who is writing all these actors and actresses and people who didn't want to work on the movie
To rub it in their face and like rubbing the gross in their face and everything and everybody assumed it was smile
I don't know if that the case it kind of made me laugh, but um
It just made me think this feels sort of like a Rebecca Hall vehicle
but um
The smiling gimmick is there
It's kind of they do creepy things with it, you know, but it's not what the movie is the movie really is about
Trauma it's about like which of most horror movies are these days, but it's about passing
Uh
Can you ever really shake off trauma or are you always living in it?
It follows you around forever that kind of thing. So it is like a curse
But it also works as a metaphor
And I thought a pretty effective metaphor and I thought in the end
That both the story made sense and it made like thematic sense and worked
I was very impressed by it. I thought it was scary
Thanks for cool. It was shot really cool
And the acting was good. I got no real compliance. What do you think Jim?
Excuse me. I agree on all fronts. Uh, I thought
It was very well done. It was very well acted
Uh, it was bleak
Yeah
You know because in the end it's it's got the Manchester by the sea ending, which is you can't beat it
So you're right, you know, right. Yeah, and um
It's you know at the end it's
I
I didn't mind the downer ending. I thought they could have done a little more with the ending
I thought the ending could have here's I mean, look, it's not my job to rewrite things
You know, we're just here to review them, but I will say
What I wanted at the end was because at the beginning of this thing she's this
Doctor and she's treating these patients
And um, you know, there's that guy that she treats her main patient that's like
You know, they're gonna I'm gonna die and all that stuff
You know the guy that that's that's truly paranoid
Right and not doesn't have a thing after her him
Which is why I went, you know, which adds to the drama that when she has a thing after her everybody thinks she's just
You know having delusions and it's not it's real. It's happening
I thought the end should have been that she does kind of beat or seemingly beat this thing
But then she ends up in the hospital being treated
Mm -hmm it goes full circle
And look she's she's she's saved others by defeating this thing by sacrificing herself
Yeah, uh, I thought that would have been a little more weighty than just it just finally gets her in the end
And then it smiles at her ex fiance who's trying to help her beat it
And then you know he's gonna die and it's just gonna keep going right um
But who knows that could be one of those studio note things or you know, you never know
But overall I like the move that was my only note
I thought the movie was great. I thought it was paced very well
I thought it was very well acted um
And they they paid they paid they they hit you with the payoffs and even when you knew something was coming
They did it in a creative way that was great
You know when when they set up like that she's gonna go to her
Nephew's birthday party and you you as soon as
I'm right saying great. Yeah as soon as she says she's going you're like oh no
She's gonna see the smile thing at the party and freak everybody out and whatever
disaster and you're waiting for that to happen and instead
The kid opens this present and there's a dead cat inside of it
That she didn't do the like I guess the monster did it to fuck with her or something yeah
But the point is is like you know the party's gonna be disastrous
You think you know how it's gonna be disastrous and then they take you in a different direction and you're like oh Jesus Christ
And it's awesome. It's fucking awesome like it was yeah it flips your expectations a lot
and
The scares are great
The vibe is great
It seems like you know, it's pretty much unknowns and I think that
The director must have just wanted to put all the money on the screen and it shows
It's a great looking movie on a low budget
I think it's already made like a hundred times its budget. It's a massive hit. They'll be definitely be more smiles
I would say but
I was a big fan my hog is very up for a smile
It was it was one of those
Or what the hell was I just gonna say
Damn it you said the it's a massive hit
It's
Made a bunch of money made a bunch of money oh
No, it doesn't matter. I can't remember
Um
What's the name of that kid again in it that plays your ex fiance Kyle Golner. It's good actor. He is
He's a lot of horror. He was a nightmare in Elm Street remake. That's the first time I ever saw him
Yeah, he's looked the same now for 25 years. Yeah, it's I've looked him. I've googled him before he's like
It's got like a full family. I'm like
How really I'm not as young as I used to or as I think I am
He's some people just have great scumbag
Out of work alcoholic cop energy, but maybe that's not who they are in their real life
Yeah, no, he's uh, he's great. There was some great. Oh, that's what I was gonna say
There was some legitimate the jump scares in it or legitimate jump scares. Yeah, for sure
There's some shocker moments where they cut to like something gruesome that happened to one of the people that died and it's shocking and upsetting
The ways that yeah great ones a lot of really great moments most horror movies
Can't get even two or three of those these days. There's a lot of memorable little moments in there
Yeah, and then like when the ghost smiles at you you eventually kill yourself in front of people in a horrific way
And then and then somebody witnesses it and then they get followed yeah by the ghost um and like the the suicides were really like
You know, they were really creative like they did a they did a good job with all of this and there was just enough
Of the ring
mystery that you know, we talked about the ring recently and I was saying like I wasn't a huge fan of the rings
I felt like it was more of a detective movie than anything else. Yeah, there was just enough of that in this
And you know and look the thing that you talked about last episode that I'm very big on it was all very logical
Everything she did made sense to me. Well, uh -huh. That's what I would do next. Yep. Yep. Yeah
Yeah, that great scene with her therapist that lady's always really good and stuff and I knew that she much she was she probably had a good moment coming up
But when the therapist comes over and like turns into the smile thing starts going crazy
Yeah, I was scared just like everybody really committed and like did a did a really good job with it, you know like
I think oftentimes is just one more draft of the script can make all the difference like
When everything adds up at the end people are much more happy obviously
um
I uh, yeah, I give a solid hog up to this thing same
Two hogs up how about that just when you think we don't like anything we watch
We give two hogs up to a movie. We thought we were gonna hate go see smile
Check her out. We're not sure yet what's coming up
We've discussed some things, but we'll know soon enough
And uh, you know check us out down in St. Petersburg, Florida. Joe one is that December 8th
It's like the 8th or the 7th whatever. I can't remember. I can look it up really quick hold on um
But yeah, I mean I meant the the home listener. I'll look it up though. I think it is the 8th
Upcoming shows December 8th St. Petersburg, Florida
Uh, and I again I well I plugged on the last episode you know where I'm gonna be please come see me
Folks thanks for listening to us. We'll be back. We'll see you next time and we'll see you and how