I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell
And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams
You know I'll say
I'll see you in hell, you know I will
Folks, we'll see you in hell, back at it again
This time with the Banshees of Inisheeran
That almost rhymed, real close, real close
I feel like Inisheeran is right
And I watched the movie, but I watched it a while ago
And I am Irish -ish
Okay
So I do think I'm right
Alright, well, that's fine
What do you think about that, Joe?
It's one of the few things I'm not going to ever argue you on
I don't care enough
We'll get to our feelings on the movie later
But do you feel that this is ultimately how our friendships will end
Yours and mine, with one of us shunning the other
One of us cutting our fingers off despite the other
Talking through mediators, like sending bartenders to deliver messages to the other one
A lot of that stuff at the end
I hope so
I think so
I mean, that's best -case scenario, in my opinion
Murder -suicide is also very much on the table
Yeah, so, you know
Yeah, an interesting film that we will get to shortly
Yeah, I got a new Rex Reed, if you want to do it
Please
You heard of this movie, this musical
Rex and the City, do we ever name this segment?
We named it Mean Old Bitch
Oh, Mean Old Bitch
Rex and the City
There's this new show on Broadway called End Juliet
Okay, is there an ellipsis in there?
Yeah, no, no, it's just End Juliet
Because, you know, let's erase men from everything
Oh, like Romeo and Juliet, I gotcha
Yeah, what if Juliet lived?
Because get it, she's better than he
Anyway, alright, I won't, I'm sorry
I didn't know Rex reviewed Broadway as well, but he does
If you've got something, Rex will come by and tell you what he thinks of it
Headline, review colon, the excruciating End Juliet fails on every level
So we're off to a good start
He's brutal
Set to the music of Max Martin, this moronic new Broadway show asks the question
What if Romeo died, but Juliet didn't kill herself and lived on to bore everybody else to death
Jesus, Jesus Rex, who hurt you?
Rex says, although the moronic new Broadway show End Juliet, at the theater newly named for Stephen Sondheim, who must be turning over in his grave
Rex always mentions somebody turning over in his grave, always
He could freshen up his fucking jokes a little bit too
Although this calls itself a musical, the music, by the way, in quotes, music, is lousy enough to demand a new definition of the word
While everything else on stage adds up to nothing more than two and a half hours of trash
Come on, Rex, come on, Rex
I gave up trying to figure out what motivated Luke Shepard, the director, Max Martin, the book and lyrics
And David West Reed, the book, to pursue the lame idea of fabricating a threadbare narrative like this
It's a stupid idea imported from London, proving we live in a time when garbage litters the theatrical landscape everywhere
Holy shit
Oh my god
Tyrannosaurus Rex
Here's the premise, Anne Hathaway, aka the wife of William Shakespeare, not the actress
Can't settle for the fact that her husband wrote one of the world's tragic masterpieces and nags him mercilessly to change it
Adding new characters, new plot twists that barely contain enough energy to keep the audience from snoring
Lots of sex and a happy ending lace with screaming rock and pop
The Capulets want to lock up Juliet in a convent, but she's an early precursor to the Me Too movement and something of a drum beater for bad taste
So she defies parental authority and heads off on her own to discover sex in songs like
Songs that should only be heard with your fingers in your ears
Come on, Rex
For reasons that make no sense, the action moves to Paris, which has indoor toilets, its own DJ, and is more boring than anyone ever dreamed in the year 1595
So boring, in fact, that Juliet can scarcely find the verve to hang from a chandelier
She almost marries a young boy named Francois, but everything else shifts gears again when Francois kisses a boy named May and falls for his cherry -flavored chapstick
While they sing, I kissed a boy and I liked it
Oh wow, now the show doesn't sound great, I'm gonna be real
The show doesn't sound great
Chapstick in the year 1595, that's odd
Everything fails on every level, the garish vulgar sets look like exploding neon banana splits
Paloma Young's 16th century costumes are eyesores consisting of miniskirts, knee socks, and oversized tennis shoes
Jennifer Weber's alleged choreography, it quotes, repeats the same jerky movements over and over again in every number featuring nothing more than jumping around like spastic penguins
He's so drunk writing this
So drunk
How big is the martini glass?
Just spilling all over the keys
Like Abrams' top secret gag martini
A goblet, yes
Something in The Last Crusade, one of those chalices
What a crime to see that his talent, meaning the...
Who's he talking? I'm trying to...
That doesn't matter
Last paragraph
By the end of two and a half hours from this torture exacerbated by the tumultuous applause of a young audience acting as if they were cheering the World Series from the infield seats at Yankee Stadium, I felt like I was on the verge of a nervous breakdown
And Juliet is quite...
You're old
And Juliet is quite the most excruciating experience I've had on Broadway in decades
Wow
I like this guy
I like it
I mean, imagine getting that upset about it
And it sounds like he's upset other people are enjoying it, frankly
Oh, it's funny stuff, man
It's funny stuff
Let us get now...
You're gonna watch Terrifier 2 and we'll do an episode about it
Please don't let me have sat through that gruesomeness
We're gonna do it, you said?
You wanna do it?
Yeah, I'll do it, I just haven't seen it yet
And I feel bad I haven't seen it yet
But if you did it in the corner right now, I'm not mad at you
But we can also just do it later
I don't care, either way
Let's get to the corner
I'm gonna get to a classic
I rewatched Pulp Fiction on New Year's Eve
It's an all -timer, but to me...
And I can't even believe I'm saying it
But it feels a little amateurish
Compared to even Jackie Brown that came out a few years later
And it confirmed for me
That Jackie Brown is the best Tarantino film
I don't have any doubt in my mind anymore
I always thought Pulp Fiction was in close contention
Now, I really love Pulp Fiction
I think it's a five -star film
I love everybody in it and everything in it
But there's also some stuff
Like some of the performances, some of the dialogue
Tarantino himself, despite the jarring nature of him saying the N -word repeatedly
I think he's funny and believable in the role
I actually don't think that he sucks in this movie
I think he doesn't suck until he starts yelling
He's great until he starts yelling
When he starts going, okay
I'm like, is he being funny?
Because he's not a bad actor
He's appeared in other of his movies and he's fine
The movie really is Sam Jackson and Travolta and Uma Thurman
I think everybody in it's great
Keitel, all the fringe people are great
It gets a little dodgy for me in the section where
Bruce Willis is in the cab
And then he's talking to his girlfriend with the
My pot belly? Do you not like my pot belly?
There's a 30 -minute segment in there with Willis where I'm like
What are we doing?
There's a killing time element to it that the rest of the movie just doesn't have
All the other stuff with Willis is amazing
When he goes in and bails out Ving Rhames and all that shit
The twists and turns of the movie and all that are great
But it's a little shaggier than I remembered
Maybe it was seeing it in 4K as well
And seeing that it actually looks a little closer to something like Reservoir Dogs
Than I realized
It looks more indie than I even remembered
I think it's one of the great screenplays for sure
I love the film so many great memorable moments
But I can officially say for the no one that was waiting for it
That my favorite Tarantino is now officially Jackie Brown
Very good
What's yours Joe?
My favorite Tarantino?
That's a great question
I think Dogs is probably still my favorite
It just holds a special place in my heart
Pulp Fiction I love so much
And I love Jackie Brown
I love them all for different reasons
I love those three movies in the way I love Goodfellas, Casino, and The Irishman
I see Jackie Brown as the Irishman
Where it's a much slower film
It's a much more character focused film
It's not as exciting as the other two
But it's arguably a better movie for it
Because of the depth of the characters
I see Reservoir Dogs as Goodfellas
Where I'm like that's just the one that lays the groundwork
And it's just got everything you need and blah blah blah
And then I see Pulp Fiction kind of as Casino
Where it's like this is the flashiest of the three
And if you're in the mood for that it's great
And if you're not in the mood for that
You might say I'm not enjoying this as much as I would the other two
Yes, sure, except I would lop the Irishman off the list
I would say Reservoir Dogs, Mean Streets, Goodfellas, Pulp Fiction, Jackie Brown, Casino
No, Mean Streets is insane to me to put that above the Irishman
I'm just saying Mean Streets feels like Reservoir Dogs
They seem a cut from the same cloth, baby
Oh, I see what you're saying
They'd make a great double T
I see
I watched, I gotta put my thing up here
I closed my damn document
And I can't remember, something wild speaking
But I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Let me reclaim my time, let me reclaim my time
Are you watching this stuff where they can't confirm this Speaker of the House?
No, I'd rather watch paint dry
I'm not watching footage, but I just read about it
It's like, we are in a shambles right now
And Biden said it's not my problem, did you see that?
Yeah, well, it isn't
Well, I mean, it's kind of the President's problem
I forgot he was even alive
Are we, how are we ranking
Tarantino really is one of the all -time greats
I mean, just banger after banger
How are we ranking Inglorious from the period pieces?
Inglorious, Dejango, Unchained
And what do we want to say?
Hateful Eight or we want to talk about Once Upon a Time?
Because Hateful Eight is going to be the worst of those
Oh, I disagree with that completely
Hateful Eight to me is a masterpiece
How are we ranking Hateful Eight, Inglorious, Bastards, and Django Unchained?
The true period pieces
Inglorious is my absolute least favorite of those three
Interesting
Hateful Eight is my favorite of those three
And I would put Hollywood as a second, which I can't believe I'm saying
No, Django, we're not talking Hollywood
Oh, I'm sorry, Django, I would definitely put Django over Bastards
I could hear, I could understand the argument that Django is better than Hateful Eight
Yeah
I just like Hateful Eight more, why?
Because it's a parallel of Reservoir Dogs
And I really like that kind of thing from him
I think I would go just because of how Christoph Waltz now immediately annoys me
And he was so novel and exciting in that movie
But I don't have the same feeling with him as I used to
So I think I would go Django, number one, followed by Inglorious
Followed in the distance, I gotta say
By Hateful Eight, which I liked but didn't love
And I would say liked quite a bit on recent viewings
But just never clicked into love for me
Didn't do it
Hateful Eight holds a special place in my heart for reasons I already stated
But also, you know, I saw that in the theater with my dad
Right, sure, sure, sure
Which was cool
My dad was so excited by the cinemascope, whatever the fuck it's called, presentation, 70mm
He was like, I can't remember the last time I saw a movie with an intermission
It was a very big bonding film for us
Totally good, totally good
Anyway
Well, how about the Killbills?
Let's go Killbill 1, Killbill 2, Once Upon a Time
Killbills to me aren't even contenders
Really?
Once Upon a Time, absolute gem of a film
Killbill to me are, they're fine
They're, you know
They're fine
I think I would just barely go Once Upon a Time over Killbill 2, over Killbill 1
But
That's insane
The man's made it amazing
Once Upon a Time to me is better than Bastards
I put it over Killbill, I put it number one
No, wait, I thought you just said Once Upon a Time is barely over the Killbills for you
Well, I go Once Upon a Time, then Killbill 2, then Killbill 1
But yeah, I think Killbill 2
Wait a minute, that's your top three Tarantinos?
No, that's me ranking those, just those three movies
I'm saying, well obviously, yeah, Once Upon a Time is the best of those
But I'm saying that's, you're doing, in my opinion, you're doing a disservice to Once Upon a Time
By only comparing it to the Killbills
It's no contest that that's a better movie than those movies, is my opinion
Fair enough, fair enough
But I really love the Killbills
I don't know what you'd, I guess you'd compare them, probably a better comparison would be with Death Proof
Yeah, it's like Killbill 1 and 2 are good
But it's like when he did Death Proof, he was like so up that grindhouse ass of everything
And it's just like, there isn't, to me, there just isn't a lot of weight in Killbill
Like, it's like, it's a fun revenge movie
I think 1 is the ultimate kind of revenge movie
And it's beautiful, and there's amazing action sequences
And the soundtrack kicks ass, and everything's great about it
And then 2 is the heart and soul
They just wait until the second one to give you all that stuff
I thought, I mean, look, just even having that in the world
Like a part 1 and part 2 from him at that time
Was super exciting to me
And I love those movies
I really do, I think they just look awesome
And I think with almost no credit to them
Even though they were very highly influenced by a million other things
But I think they influenced action movies more than almost anything else
So, yeah
Oh, Jesus Christ
You know, I hate to see that, I just got my tax bill
Hold on a second
Property?
Property tax is the ultimate kick in the nuts
No, not property, just what I owe
Oh boy, yeah
It seems to be an insane amount of money
Oh no, oh no
An insane amount of money
This can't be right
Folks, we'd like to announce a spinoff podcast starting immediately
Ay, ay, ay
He was fanning himself like one of the golden girls over here
That's the video element you missed, folks
Alright, over to you
We've somehow talked about the entire career of Quentin Tarantino
This is a number I can't even wrap my head around
Don't say it on camera
I won't, but I can't even
I can't wrap my head around this number
You're schvitzing
Yeah, I literally just started sweating
I don't understand how it's possible
There's usually, you can talk to them, you can figure something out hopefully
Something went wrong, something didn't get taken
Is this like an old trusty account that you've had for a while or a new guy?
No comment
For a while
I mean, do you meet him in an alley or does he have an office?
No, I've worked with him for a long time
I'm just like looking at this number and I'm like
I don't understand how that's possible
Yeah, alright, maybe it isn't
Look on the bright side
Joe's just not going to speak, the rest of it will just be staring into space
Anyway, folks
Yeah, that's intense, nobody wants that bill, for sure
Jesus Christ, okay
Alright
Not since Joe's Dog Shat on the Floor has this podcast seen such drama
Yeah, alright
I forgot about when that happened
It was on the, I guess Emily posted it on the Instagram the other day
I watched Something Wild, which was a conversation with my accountant
Folks, folks
I saw this movie years ago, I hadn't seen it in a long time
I love that movie
Early Jonathan Demme
Criterion
Yeah, I saw it on, I forget what I watched it on
It's a great movie, Jeff Daniels plays a square guy
Who falls in love with a wild spirit played by Melanie Griffith
As he gets roped into her life, her past and aspects of her life
Start to become a threat to him
Mainly in the form of Ray Liotta
In the role that got him Goodfellas
Just playing a lunatic
He's awesome in it
They're all awesome in it
And that forces Jeff Daniels to realize he actually loves Melanie Griffith
And he wants to evolve as a person
And kind of take life by the cojones
Instead of sitting and letting it sort of wash over him
It's a great movie, it's fun
It's Jonathan Demme
Yeah, much more intense than you're expecting it to be
But at its core I'd say it's pretty much a romantic comedy
And it's a fun movie
And an interesting, I can't put my finger on what it is
But it contains, I think there's an interesting racial commentary to it
And I'm not quite sure what it is or how he's doing it
But I noticed on this watch
Throughout the movie, particularly the closing credits
He features scenes with black characters singing
Or performing music in some way, shape or form
The closing credits is, I think it's a Jamaican lady singing that
It's a rendition of some song, whatever, over the closing credits
And that's the closing credits, it's just her singing
I have the soundtrack on vinyl actually
And there's another part where there's a group of black teenagers
Like rapping outside of a gas station
And Ray Liotta, who is the sole antagonist and bad guy in the movie
Is racist
So I was like, there's clearly something there
There's a layer to this there of Jonathan Demme saying something
And I'm not quite sure exactly what it is
Or maybe it's just a means to be like
This makes you dislike Ray Liotta's character even more
Right, well at that time, Jonathan Demme always included that kind of stuff in his movies
Because he did stop making sense
The Talking Heads, probably the best concert documentary of all time
And then he did Married to the Mob
And pretty much all that shit he did in the 80s
Had like musical performances in it or around the fringes on it
Okay
So that was a thing he was doing
But you could be right, there could be more to his commentary
I mean he was a very thoughtful man
I think the guy made just amazing movies for most of his career
Even the ones that didn't quite work were always great
Okay, got it
Jay Demmes, your Philadelphia, which you can't believe I own
But I might throw it on tonight
I might watch an AIDS drama on a Friday night out there
I like Philadelphia, it's just not one I feel you need to
You know, pull off the shelf on date night as well
I understand, I understand
I went through, you know, I feel like my mood has lifted
And I'm on the mend, etc.
But I'm a person who I think like you goes through certain vices when under duress
And this holiday season it was shopping
I was buying some 4Ks
And maybe I don't need Philadelphia and 4K
But doesn't mean I can't buy it
I'm only going to do two, what else do you got?
What else do I got?
Did I even do one?
Yeah, you did Pulp Fiction
We talked about it at length and then ranked every Tarantino movie
I, speaking of 4K, I had heard from Drew McQueenie
Who was a really, I've never met the man but I've long admired him
He started out at Ain't It Cool and now does his own thing
And had his great podcast, 80s all over with my friend Scott Weinberg
And by the way, Joe, Scott Weinberg would love you to do his podcast
About underrated, overhated movies, which I did
If you'd like me to set you up
I don't want to put you on the spot
I'd love to have you on, because I already did it
Me and him did Freddie Godfinger, which I decided was pretty much the right amount of hated when I was watching
I'm into it
Okay, cool, I'll set it up
Drew McQueenie is a guy who writes very passionately about film
And I like him as a film personality and he seems like a cool guy
And he talked about how the 4K of Coraline was incredible
And I remembered enjoying Coraline
But not enough to own the thing
But I thought I'm going to take a chance
Really show off this 4K system and I'll be damned if this movie didn't blow my goddamn mind
And I can't wait to try it in the future
While on acid or something
Because what the 4K really does
I'm learning that is most impressive
Is movies where color is a big part of it
That's where the 4K really makes colors pop and things look amazing
And you kind of gasp at certain scenes, stuff like that
But Coraline as a movie doesn't hold together super well as a story to me
It's sort of a cool little story
And I guess it's based on a Neil Gaiman thing
And he's not really my cup of tea
But the visuals in the movie are incredible
It feels very Tim Burton -y even though I guess it's not
It's Henry Selig who directed Nightmare Before Christmas
And he did James and the Giant Peach and Monkey Bone
And all kinds of kind of weird interesting stuff
But visually I thought Coraline was pretty incredible
And if you're looking for a disc to really show off your 4K
That's one to get
Okay
I watched in its entirety The Comeback
Yes
Which is a TV show about
Masterpiece
Lisa Kudrow
I mean you recommended it on the show to me, on this show
Based on my review of Lucky Numbers
And you said you got to watch The Comeback
So I did
And I binged it in like two days I think
It was over, it was like New Year's Day
It was that period of I'm shaking off the New Year's Eve hangover
And I'm sad
And I need some, I just need to curl up with a TV show
So I chose that one
And man, I loved it
Overall
Initially
I was like, you know, it's a serviceable
It's a serviceable film
Or series, excuse me
It's a serviceable comedy
You know, I did not see it at the time of its release obviously
So it's very hard to judge it fairly
Especially since this came out
Sort of around the time that the British Office came out
And this docu -style thing wasn't done to death yet
You know, by a million different TV shows
It's hard to go back and watch that
And put everything that's come out in the last 15 or 17 years
Whatever it's been, out of your head
Comeback was really mocking the very earliest days of the reality TV boom
If memory serves
Well, the first one
It's making fun of reality TV
But there's no reality TV yet
It's like the real world is the one show they reference
Right, yeah, that's true
And reality TV was a very, very new thing
You know, it was like fear factor was still
It was like that kind of shit was still happening
I think America's Next Top Model maybe had been out or something
Because they do the joke and that's America's Next Top Porn Star or whatever
Yes
So, you know, but once I was able to get over
Like, you know, I was able to get around like
Okay, I can't judge this based on things that did this
Since this, like this became before that
And was able to watch it that way
I found it very funny
Lisa Kudrow's amazing in it
The, the, the
I don't know any other actor's name
But the guy that plays her sidekick, Mickey, is fantastic in it
The guy that plays Pauly G who also plays Bill what's his name on It's Always Sunny
Ponderosa
Yeah, he was great
Lance Barber
Lance Barber, yeah, it's just a great cast of people
The lady that plays Juna who went on
You know, she's now been in A Million Things, The Blonde
She was in the Heartbreak Kid remake
Madeleine Ackerman
Yeah, you know, it's a great cast
Lisa Kudrow plays a TV, a sitcom TV star who's sort of faded from grace
Because the show's been off the air for a long time after its cancellation
And she gets a chance to duly star in a reality show about her comeback
While she stars in a network sitcom
The network, she's painfully desperate
She can't get out of her own way
She has, she's a real person
And she does have a heart and soul
But she compromises that for the wrong reasons at times
In the interest of entertainment and the business
And that's what makes the character interesting
I was expecting her to be, I thought it was going to be like a
You know, way more like an eastbound and down
Where it's like, man, she's just an asshole
And like, she's out to get what she wants
And she's going to get it no matter what
And that's not what it is
She's somebody who is very sympathetically desperate
And wants to be accepted and wants to be liked
And as the show goes on and you get into the second season
Which takes place nine years later
And they shot it nine years later
You find out that that show, that sitcom from the first season has been canceled
The reality show she did ended up kind of disgracing her
And this business that she so wants to be a part of has chewed her up and spit her out yet again
And sure enough, at the beginning of the second season
She gets the opportunity to return to television
Why? Because Pauly G, who created the sitcom from the first season
Who hated her guts has now written a show about a single cam HBO show
About his getting sober from a heroin addiction
His experience in writing this TV show for network
And his experience in hating this woman who starred in it, Lisa Kudrow
Or Melanie Cherish from the show
Valerie, I think it's Valerie Cherish
Yeah, Valerie essentially gets to play an exaggerated version of herself
In this new show on HBO
Second season gets super meta
Because they're talking about like everybody's playing themselves now
Which is like a reference to Curb
Yeah, it's very star -studded when it came back
It was very star -studded
It was kind of a cool thing to be on
Michael Patrick King was doing that at the same time as Broke Girls
So I got to kind of see some of that show coming together and stuff
That's cool
But watching it all at once
I'm sure is a drastically different experience
Because I actually waited ten years between them
So while I like the second season, I consider it a fraction of what season one is
But maybe I'm wrong
Maybe when you watch them back -to -back, it just feels like a seamless transition
I don't know
It felt pretty seamless
I did feel like the second season initially felt forced
Because I was like, well, it's been nine years
They're kind of retreading a lot of the same territory
But then I started and I was like, God, she's just not likable in the second season
And then I realized, oh, that's the point
Because she gets to a place in the second season where she becomes so obsessed
With the age of being part of an HBO show
That she compromises her personal life in every possible way
Yeah
And as the series
Well, her husband is the perfect from Always Sunny as well
The guy who plays the lawyer on that show
No, that's not the same guy
Brian
That's a different
Brian Unger?
That's not Brian Unger
Oh, wait, but he's also on Always Sunny
Hang on
I know that
Isn't Brian Unger on The Comeback Tour?
Or am I crazy?
No
It's all right
It's an easy mistake to make
Who plays the husband?
I forget his name
I met Unger
He's like an indie, mostly indie
I always mistake him for that
But that guy is so good in the role
It's kind of a thankless role
But like, man, you can meet
Even just dating
You meet so many people like this Valerie Cherish out here
And they nail it so perfectly
I mean, Koudreau has, of course, been around so many of these desperate actresses through the years
So
She's a much deeper actress than she gets credit for
Because everyone just thinks she plays dumb
Valerie Cherish is definitely not a dumb character
It's just one of the more interesting characters
I think they've ever done on HBO, really
I love the character
Well, the second season
You know, she
As I said, she becomes so obsessed with the prestige of the whole thing
Yeah
Which does lead to her getting nominated for an Emmy
Jim Burroughs is great
He plays himself on the show
He's sort of the very coarse voice of reason in both seasons for her
And
The second season
There's a B story where Mickey, her best friend and makeup and hair person
Is sick
He's got cancer, but he's going to
He's like, I'll be fine, don't worry
And as the season goes, he gets worse
And it all comes to a head
In this big moment where
She is nominated for an Emmy
She's at the Emmys
Her husband is not there because they have separated
Because he's
There's a great scene where they have this fight
And he's like, where are you? Are you even in there anymore?
Which is how so many of us have felt
In dealing with people in the entertainment business
That we once knew way back when or whatever
And
And, you know, he's not without his flaws and foibles as well
Like, you know
And, you know, she gets a call
And word on the street is that she's going to win the Emmy
And she gets a call in the ceremony
That Mickey, her best friend, has collapsed
And been rushed to the hospital
And this is a really brilliant thing they do
The entire series up till this point
Meaning every episode from the first season and the second season
Is shot as being raw footage that you're watching
From these docu -series things they're putting together
About her life
Every single moment is captured on camera
By somebody following her with the camera
Every single moment
In the moment she gets the call
That Mickey has collapsed
She leaves the Emmys
This thing she wanted so desperately
To rush to the hospital to get to her friend
And in that moment it switches to a single cam sitcom
And that's the first time it's shot that way
Where it's not docu -
And it's so fucking brilliant
Because the documentary shooting is such a
Device through the entire show
That pisses her husband off and causes her so many problems
With her coworkers and all this stuff
And it's just vanity
In that moment it goes away
And it becomes a completely -
It's shot completely differently
And she goes to the hospital
And she chooses the right thing finally
To be with her friend
I started crying, I was bawling my fucking eyes out
It's a beautiful ending to the show
And it justifies the entire two seasons
I would say if you're into
The early Gervais and Merchant stuff
Like Extras
You know, The Office obviously
This is right up your alley
You know, it's a really, really funny show
That becomes more dramatic as it goes
And has just beautifully, beautiful, beautiful moments
Beautifully executed moments in the final episode
Yeah, it's one of my favorite television shows of all time
For sure, easily
Folks, and also by the way
The most accurate portrayal of like life
Behind a super toxic sitcom
It's chilling how -
It's crazy that you didn't remember that scene
To me that's the most chilling scene of the whole thing
Is that guy, the Lance Barber
The really heavy writer guy
Goes to her office
And she's giving him notes on the character
And while she's in the middle of her sentence
He reaches up, points finger gun to her forehead
And goes -
And acts like he's shooting her in the face
Which to me
Is the most chilling moment of the entire series
I remember I was like
Woo, like
And you know
I don't know why that's so severe
But it was just like
Traumatic almost to watch
He's really great
I mean he plays that asshole so well
He plays a great asshole, for sure
You know, some great line
That's a comedy
That's a comedy without the laughs
There's some really really funny jokes
Well early on the Always Sunny guys
Loved the comeback
And Michael Patrick King was one of the first guys to get sent
The Always Sunny pilot
And I think he didn't get back to them
But they used to tell that story
I bet he wishes he got back to them
Anyway
Let us get to the film at hand
Joseph
And that is
The Banshees of Inasherin
Or insurance
The Insurance Banshees
I would definitely watch a movie called The Insurance Banshees
It's like a zombie
Insurance company
And it says we bring bad things to life
Is the tagline we go with
Right?
Wait, say it again?
Oh wait, is it GE?
We bring good things to life?
I don't know, I have no idea
It sounds like it was a good joke
GE's slogan for many years was
We bring good things to life
What is State Farm's slogan?
Like a good neighbor, like a bad neighbor
And then your neighbor is a zombie
Let's drop the project
We are talking about
The Banshees of Inasherin
It is done by
Martin McDonough who did
In Bruges
Which is a really, really great movie
One of the greats, I would say
Of recent years
Starring the exact same couple
Brendan Gleeson and
Colin Farrell
This movie adds
Barry Keoghan to the mix
Oh, he's so good
He is great
Jesus, he's good
And the girl's name is
What, Joe?
Carrie Condon
Which, funny enough
I'm watching and I'm like, I know her
She was on Better Called Saul
We flew home together once
Oh, okay, cool
She's very nice
Irish, right?
Yeah, very nice
Yeah
Really four great performances
These guys are old pros
Martin McDonough writes really interesting stuff
His most famous stuff is like
Four
Whatever that was
Three billboards outside of Ebbing
And, you know
He's a good writer
He's a great writer
Of dialogue
And then sometimes plot is not necessarily
Farrelly
His strong suit, even though I love his stuff
And in this movie
I think it kind of suffers from that
To me, he sets up this
Dilemma, which is
Colin Farrell is kind of a dim -witted guy
It's a period piece in Ireland
I had so many friends who watched this
And didn't know it was a period piece
Because they thought Ireland was this backwards
But, you know, it's like
A village in Ireland
And Colin Farrell meets up with
Brendan Gleason every day at the pub
And they talk and shoot the shit
One day he shows up
And Brendan Gleason does not want to
See him or talk to him
And he doesn't explain it to Colin Farrell
And Colin Farrell is freaking out
For about an hour
I'm done talking to you
And that's too long
That is the dilemma of this movie
It's slow, it's repetitive
It's just kind of
What do you mean you're not going to talk to me?
Well, I'm not talking to you
Tell him I'm not going to talk to him
It goes on for a long time like that
A long time
Then, to kind of up the ante
Brendan Gleason says
I'm going to cut off a finger
Anytime you, what, interrupt me?
No, speak to me
He's saying
I want time to pursue my
Artistic endeavors, which is me
Playing my fiddle
And writing songs
And you
Being a dumb guy who hangs out
And tries to get me drunk
Is not helping me finish my goals
And that's kind of what is revealed to be
The central dilemma
Between the two men, which is sort of
Interesting
But then the larger commentary
Is that they're Irish guys
And they're depressed guys
And this is, you know, every guy in my family
And myself and etc
But they have a hard time
Talking things out
A hard time apologizing
A hard time
Just not
Burying things deep within
So that's what the movie kind of
Turns into, is these guys
Not talking to each other and not working
Their problems out
Really curdles their relationship
And becomes kind of a dangerous
Ripple effect throughout the community
Yes
If I read it correctly
Because my dad, who loves this Irish shit
And me, talked about the movie a little bit
And we both kind of left feeling like
Maybe we missed something
But that's what I took further
I found the movie very interesting
There was a
The backdrop of this thing is there's a civil war
Going on in the mainland as they refer to it
Because they're on an island
And I thought the entire movie
It is
Slow, it's a slow burn
And as I started it
I really hated it
And then as I got into it
I really started to enjoy it
And then by the end of it I was like, this is really good
I felt like the whole thing was a metaphor
For civil war
Where two sides
Or two factions
Who call a place home
Will tear the place apart
And destroy it
In a means to say
That my side of this
Debate is the correct one
And sometimes it seems
Kind of senseless
And I think that that's what
This was
It was a guy saying
For no good reason, I don't like you
Anymore
My side of this doesn't like you
They live in a village of like ten people
So the two of them are almost the only two residents
Of this village
The other guy doesn't understand
And now there's a conflict
And nobody even understands what the fuck the conflict's about
And then Brendan Gleason
Starts to say, I'm going to cut off a finger
Every time you try to talk to me
And in doing that
He's compromising what
The thing he claims he wants to pursue
Which is his musical endeavor
In playing a fiddle
There's a scene where
Colin Farrell's character's
Sister, that character
Goes to Brendan Gleason and says
You're going to cut your fingers off
Then you won't be able to play your fiddle
And he goes, now we're getting somewhere
And to me that was the whole movie
Where he's like, exactly
I will ruin the thing
That I love most in order to prove my point
That's what civil war is
In many ways
At the end of the movie
And then also too
It gets to a point where
Colin Farrell says
He has this pet donkey that he loves very much
Brendan Gleason ends up cutting off all the fingers
On one of his hands
And every time he cuts it off he throws it at
Colin Farrell's door
He ends up throwing four fingers
At one time at Colin Farrell's
Door
Colin Farrell's pet donkey eats the fingers
And chokes and dies
Colin Farrell is devastated
Because his sister now has moved to the mainland
This is his only friend
Again, civil war, what happens?
People flee
The country, people flee everything they know
And other people go, no
We have to ride this out, no matter what
He's alone
He's now lost his only friend, which is this donkey
And he says to
Brendan Gleason, I'm going to burn your
House down tomorrow, that's what's happening
And Brendan Gleason
Despite knowing this
Doesn't leave his house
Again
This is all just
To me, exemplifying this concept
Of what a conflict
Can be
And then in the final scene
You kind of think
They're going to make up and be friends again
And they don't
They basically say, like, we'll both
Continue to live here
And we'll both hate each other
But we will stop
Battling at least
For now
Yeah, yeah, for now
And I thought the movie did a really, really
Good job of showing
That metaphor
Or exploring that metaphor
Through these two characters and their
Conflict
I will admit that I felt it did
Excuse me, feel a bit
More like a play
Than a movie
Yeah, he's written a shitload of plays
But
But I liked it, I really liked it
I thought it was very, very well done
Yeah, it grew on me
And then the four leads are all great
I love these
Actors, they're all good together
And, you know
It just kind of
I think it wasn't what I expected
And maybe
That's usually the type of movie that for me
Grows on me a lot more with a second viewing
Because I thought this was going to be one thing
And it wasn't, so then you wind up adjusting
Your expectations the whole time
And then you don't really get to experience it, blah, blah, blah
Folks, we appreciate you
Wait, was your hog up or down?
Oh, I'm sorry
My hog is up for the Banshees of Anasheeran
Mine's up
Yeah, sturdy
Yeah, I was a little disappointed in
I think everybody wanted an In Bruges sequel
And that was so exciting
At the prospect of that
And that's not what this is
But it still does have some laughs
And they're both great
And I'm a sucker for Colin Farrell playing like a sap
He's good at that, he's really good at that
He's good at everything
I really like when he plays a sort of
Pathetic guy
He just, it's
I think it took me an hour
Into it maybe to realize
And admit that it was not going to be an
In Bruges type thing, and for that reason
I need to give it another shot
But my hog is still up, I thought it was a
Well done movie for sure
We're not really sure
What we'll be doing coming up, but I think
Hopefully, Joe
We'll be talking about a little picture called Megan
If you're willing to go see that one
Because a lot of people are talking about Megan
Alright, I mean it doesn't look that good
To me, but sure
I might see Avatar tomorrow
God fucking help me
Hey, you want to do it, let's do it
I loved it
But we'll be back, you loved it
I'm hearing bad stuff
I'm hearing that the word cuz is used
A lot in it
You're going with the wrong
Mind for this
You're going with your 8 year old mind
You go to the 3D IMAX
I don't care about the 3D
And I think it looks gross
You need to go see it in the 3D IMAX, Joe
Do it
What's that?
Go see it in the 3D IMAX
It was designed for 3D IMAX
I know, but I'm just
I will see it that way if I can
But it's like, my point is
None of that excites me
I won't be like, woo, it's the 3D IMAX
I'm still not going to like it
I mean, maybe I will
Who knows? But why are they saying cuz?
Well, I guess I'll have to get to the bottom of that
Didn't bug me
It's not why I was there
But that doesn't answer the question
Why would the aliens say the word cuz?
Well, they're not aliens
Well, the people
Are they saying it the way we say it?
Like, yo, cuz
There's some of that
They learned from us
The white man goes to their villages
Alright, fair enough
Alright, folks
We'll be back with something
We don't know what, as Pat said
We'll see you next time
And we'll see you in the new year
And we'll see you in hell