🎵 I'll see you in hell. I'll see you in hell. And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say. I'll see you in hell. You know I will. I'll see you in hell. You know I will. 🎵
A hot month. A hot month. With hot movies.
The hottest month, many would say. August.
Yes. Hot like a, hot like a some peck muscles in a sauna. Dripping beads of perspiration down to a stiff bird.
My hands come up behind the pecks. Squeezing them. Encircling them. And you feel my manhood becoming engorged up against your cheeks. Not you, Joe, are talking about this muscle guy that I'm about to fuck in the sauna.
Sorry, just let my mind wander there for a second.
Oh, sure.
Folks, we're here. We're talking about a movie that until four minutes ago, I thought was called Deadpool vs. Wolverine. In fact, it's called Deadpool and Wolverine. Which is odd because the two men are brutally fighting each other for a lot of the runtime. Why not give it a versus?
That is true. I didn't think of that. I, I, I, my assumption would be
that given the poor reception of so many versus movies.
Freddy vs. Jason?
Well, that's not really a renowned, I mean, it might have done well. I don't know, but I'm thinking mostly a Batman.
You don't think a movie where a member of Destiny's Child calls Freddy Krueger a gay slur is a classic?
Does she call Jason or Freddy a slur?
Man, that's funny. I'm sorry. That's just one of the funniest things I've ever heard.
It was a wild choice. This is, by the way, it's after Freddy makes the joke, the play on the first move, the classic Freddy line, how sweet fresh meat.
Yeah.
And in that one, he says, how sweet dark meat.
He says that to her. It's insane.
So look, he set the tone of a combative discussion. It was really Freddy's fault is what you're saying.
I think she might launch with the slur first and he responds. I don't remember which, I don't remember who does what, but it's.
I saw she was, she was in the news. This is how bad the news has gotten, but it was like a seven day news event about a woman at the Cannes Film Festival asking her to move and she yelled at the lady.
And it was like on the news for a week. And the whole time I was like, why is the lady from Freddy versus Jason causing all this uproar?
And I remember she had like a massive career and still acts. She's in like Tyler Perry stuff.
Yeah. Yeah.
Imagine you're in Destiny's Child and you're one of the ones who's not Beyonce. I mean, Jesus Christ.
Well, I was going to say, it's got to be hard to be the Peter Scolari of Destiny's Child where you're like, you know, I'm sorry, you in a mood? Yeah, I'm a little on edge.
Every.
You know what though? Scolari was excellent on Girls. I'm sure it made him a net total of $80 ,000 for all six seasons.
But he was great on that show. He really was R .I .P. Scolari. That's about it. I was I was sad when he passed.
I was like, yeah, between Buzz and Buddies and then Newhart, he was just he was great. He really was a perfect straight man.
And he probably honestly, I doubt they made much bank with Buzz and Buddies, but he probably made his bones on Newhart and it reran and he was a regular.
So he that was probably his career money.
No, that's when he made the big bucks. He had some money.
We had a Julia Duffy on Cool Kids who played his wife on Newhart and she was just awesome.
That's great. I came down. We had, you know, one of our usual reel.
It was it was actually her and the guy from The Nanny, the husband, Charles Shaughnessy, who was even cooler.
They were like both just like we get it. We've been doing this forever.
They show up. They know their lines. They're awesome.
And they did not get involved in any of the drama on set.
But I came up to them at some point.
We had to do a big rewrite of the script and I was like, hey, I'm sorry, we're really struggling here and I'm sorry to give you guys all new lines.
And Julia Duffy was like, honey, I've been doing this for a hundred years.
This is not a problem. This is a one. OK, this is a one.
It's like, thank you. Thank you. I almost embraced her.
That's great. She's she seems awesome and and delightful.
She seems like she's like the you you picture her as your like favorite aunt.
Yeah. Be your favorite. She still pops up and stuff.
She's really good. She's like there's there were few better other than maybe Christine Baranski of playing like that upper crust snob type woman.
Yes. Was she ever on Frazier?
She would have been a great Niles love interest. Duffy. Yeah, I don't think so.
No, not that I remember.
But speaking of Frazier, excuse me, new psycho, more Frazier in the news.
He did just dash. Because they're bringing back some cheers characters in the next season.
Oh, cool. OK, I guess for one episode or whatever, I think Ted Danson's coming back and somebody else.
But he he wants to be a Phil. Yeah, Phil's coming back.
Hey, the audience has no reaction.
The guy in the audience has to be like, we're going to do one more take.
And just so you guys know, that was Phil, ladies and gentlemen, from more silence.
Well, to that point, they did an episode in the original Frazier where Ted Danson does come back.
And the premise is that he's in sex addicts anonymous now.
And he's trying to he's supposed to be marrying a woman played by Taya Leone, who he met in the group.
And he was he had an infidelity and he needs to tell her.
And when he tells her the joke is she's like, I also had a slip.
And her slip is that she fucked everybody at Cheers, which is so funny.
But but the first one is somebody.
And then the second one, she's like, and Phil.
And it gets a huge laugh.
Like, I mean, like, remember, it's a character.
Yeah. What are you watching that up at home?
If you're if you're the guy who played, you know.
Well, the third one is Cliff.
And that's the one that makes Sam, it's it's really pretty wild.
I've actually now that you're describing it, I've never seen that episode of Frazier.
And I'm going to dust it off today and watch it.
It's a great episode. And Danson does like classic dance and she's like Cliff.
And he's like, oh, man.
He's doing like the dance and physical thing that he always does.
And he's going, Cliff, Cliff.
Oh, God, Cliff. Yeah.
It's really funny. It's a really good.
Must be late.
A late episode, because like that when I was in like late high school, I dropped out.
But so there's maybe a few seasons I haven't seen.
Weird that they would do that, though, like have it's almost character
assassination to have Cliff fuck Taylor, even though it cheers is done.
Like that's a weird thing to do, like because Cliff could could never
and would never fuck Taylor.
Well, that's the joke is that she's such an addict that she fucked Cliff.
Like, that's the joke is like, yeah, it's like, look at the bottoms.
I've hit as a sex addict.
I had sex with Cliff like that.
That's what makes me and I guess he ended Cheers a single man, Cliff.
I think he yeah, they actually did
one or two kind of heartbreaking storylines with Cliff were like,
you know, when they finally and they did this on Night Court, too, with Dan
Fielding, where when they finally did get into his personal life and saw
that things didn't really work out for him with a girl he liked or was dating,
whatever, was very sad, very touching, actually.
And those were the moments where they made you care about the character enough
to continue to laugh at him being the most annoying man on earth.
Right. It was well done.
Uh, I wait.
Yeah, I'm sorry. The new psycho.
Sorry. It was that Frazier
said definitively, we're not going back to the bar.
Like, you'll see some characters, but Frazier needs to exist
in this show, in his own world, and he can't like go back to that bar
because then it's just a cheer sequel.
So anyway, that was the point.
That's fair.
I think so, but I think, you know, you do the finale and when you end this one,
you have him go back.
He's in Boston, for Christ's sake.
Why is the fuck is he in Boston then?
I'll say this.
Well, did Frazier ever go to the bar in 11 years?
No, but he was in Seattle.
Yeah. So that's the first reason.
And then the second thing they did do was he goes back to Boston for.
They could have, you know, they could have cut in stock footage
of a plane flying and then he'd be in Boston, right?
It's a sitcom.
Well, they did an episode where he does go back to Boston.
And instead of him going to Cheers.
The airport.
There's a party happening in the airport, and he goes in
and it's Cliff's farewell party, and they're all there.
And it's in an airport bar.
So they just recreate Cheers in a new bar.
And it's a Frazier episode.
Yeah, it's a great episode.
Believe it or not.
Clearly, I haven't seen a lot of Frazier.
I thought I'd seen it all. That's disturbing.
Oh, there's one where Woody comes back.
There's like two where Diane comes back.
Yeah, they they did a lot of like bringing back Cheers stuff.
Kirsty Alley never came back, sadly.
I would have liked to have seen that, but it didn't happen.
She had Veronica's Closet.
Yes. Interesting.
I feel like I actually am siding with with grammar here,
and maybe it's a rights issue, too.
But like you're on the Paramount plus Frazier reboot.
You don't get to go to Cheers.
Sure. You don't.
And I haven't seen the new Frazier.
I, you know, I know you're a true fan.
And if you're if you're saying it's decent,
I'm sure that I'll like it fine.
But you don't get to go to Cheers. Sorry.
The first season was disappointing.
I'd had some laughs.
I he's claiming this is what everybody claims.
But I have my hopes up.
He's claiming that the second season, they found their stride
and it's as funny as anything they've ever done.
And everybody's awesome.
Hopefully, that's the case. We'll see.
Well, there's certainly no reason for him to say that if it's not true, so.
Yes, yes, yes.
I realized the other day I was talking to my team, ladies and gentlemen,
and I realized, no, they weren't calling me to talk about how much shit
I talk about them on my little solo pod.
But my team, my agent manager, were like, Pat, you seem to have like this real
like beyond dark vision of the industry right now.
And I'm like, yeah.
They're like, you just don't seem to feel like there's any hope of anything.
And I'm like, correct.
And neither should you.
Fair enough.
Well, what did they say to that?
Long silence.
I mean, they're all scared as well.
You know, it's a wild time out here, everywhere.
It's it's certainly it certainly is.
Certainly is. What else is going on?
What else is in the news?
I feel like are there any big movies coming out?
Are there any big announcements?
I mean, I I saw the trailers last night before Deadpool and it's, you know.
Remakes, reboots, sequels.
I think that's all we can really expect.
Um, what is well in the news, not trailers, but I have hold on.
I wrote down a couple things.
We got, uh.
Oh, Jesus.
No, I do have a trailer.
Oh, thank God you said trailers.
The Tubi original.
Oh, yeah, you showed me that one.
The Thicket starring.
Wait for it, folks, a Western starring.
Peter Dinklage, fine.
He think James Hetfield from Metallica.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Julia or not.
Sorry, Juliette Lewis.
Lover been in my home.
And Andrew Schultz, a friend of mine, which, you know, it's
I'm happy to see Andrew in a movie.
It's cool that he's getting to do this different thing.
It was kind of odd, you know, but good.
I'm happy for him.
But here's the deal.
Andrew Schultz feels like a guy I would not be able to hide
how much I dislike him if I met him.
He's not even that I know anything about his comedy really per se much,
but just he feels like one of those guys where he would ask me
a minute of the conversation.
What's the what's your deal?
Because now he's looking at him with hate.
He's a nice. No, he's a very likable guy.
He's he's a dude. He's a good dude.
Not a likable guy.
He may be a nice guy, but he doesn't read likable to me at all
because I feel like I would hate him.
You separate the man from the art and now I like separate
the man from the mustache.
I thought that's what you're going to say.
Well, he's been doing that mustache in this haircut for a while.
And then I saw this trailer and I'm like, oh, this is what it was from.
It was for this movie.
I was like, but I guess he just kept it or maybe they're we're doing.
I don't know. Anyway, it's a signature look.
I I'm bothered with anyone who, like, knows who they are, to be honest.
That's fair. I don't like it either. Yeah.
I'm fine with I'm not here, though, to talk about the casting
of James Hetfield and Schultz.
Those two guys in doing a movie makes sense to me in the sense of,
hey, you got an opportunity to do a movie. It's a Western. Do it.
Let's talk about Dinklage and Juliette Lewis,
who you'd think I wouldn't be addressing.
But here is why I will be addressing.
Juliette Lewis is playing a man in the movie, at least in the trailers.
They repeatedly call her Bill and call her a man.
And then I read on Wikipedia the synopsis of the movie
and the character is a man.
Now, maybe there's a reveal, as you said, that it turns out
it's a woman posing as a man.
But I don't think it will be. I just don't think it will be.
I don't know how you how you do that, frankly,
if it's like there were trans people in the Old West.
Great. And honestly, kind of interesting.
I don't know why that's not the story of your movie, but kind of interesting.
They just have Juliette Lewis look like herself and they're they're all calling her Bill.
I think they thought my guess is they think it's a daring casting
and they think they're stirring it up.
And she is a fucking egomaniac.
And she's like, yeah, let's do it.
That's my that's my take on it.
I know you're a fan, but that's my take.
She is not impressed me in her interviews and things with.
I haven't seen much of that.
Do you. Do you think that this started
as a to be original or wound up a to be original?
Nothing starts as a to be original.
I think that's their motto.
Nothing starts as a to be original. Welcome.
Let's talk about the crazier thing in the trailer, though.
Yeah, the serious Western
dinklage.
At one point, goes into a room and does like a John Wick
where he beats up like six guy.
I'm like, guys, come on, please.
I'm not making fun of differently abled or anything.
I'm not. I'm not. But guys, come on.
There is there is no scenario.
At first, he's behind this guy and he gets the drop
and like bashes his face into the table.
And then it's like quick flashes of dinklage, just like throwing
240 pound men through the saloon doors.
And that's just not possible.
He wouldn't have the the strength, ladies and gentlemen,
or the height or anything to get the drop on these people.
I I couldn't care less that the man is a little person.
It's just simply not believable.
That's my point. And I thought it was.
Remember Michael Jeter?
He was on Evening Shade.
He passed away a little.
He was in the Green Mile, a little.
He actually passed of AIDS, but he was a tiny little man.
And he was a sitcom actor and character actor for a while.
You'd know him if you saw him, maybe.
But like Michael Jeter played in Westerns and he'd always be the guy
like polishing the the glass behind the bar or something.
If he all of a sudden shattered that glass over a man's head,
you'd be like, OK, that's the only way he's getting a drop on this guy.
But you'd never believe a frail old man is kicking the shit out of everyone.
It has nothing to do with height or anything else.
It's just simply these two people would not.
Even if he'd been training for years,
even if they cut to a half hour montage of Peter Dinklage
with Robert Carradine doing like killbill shit, breaking boards and stuff,
it's still not believable because all you need is two full sized men to go
to look at each other and go, should we team up?
Yeah, let's do it.
And then beat the shit out of him.
Yes. Yeah, it's it's it's a little crazy.
Now, this was a passion project by Dinklage.
OK, it's based on a novel.
The guy that wrote the novel wrote some other stuff that I've heard of.
He usually does fantasy sci fi stuff.
But this novel apparently is not it's just a Western.
It's a thriller.
But it said that it was Dinklage's passion project forever.
I think that's why it's a to be original.
Yeah, because he probably was like, oh, finally, they'll make it.
And they probably thought, well, this is bigger than anything
we're ever going to do, because Dinklage, here's our chance to step up
into the big leagues. He is a celebrity.
Well, small leagues, but yeah.
But I do think that it's like.
I I'm pontificating now and I don't want to get myself in trouble,
but I have a feeling that if he was shopping this forever,
one of the problems he was running into was people saying,
Pete, we love you, but you can't you can't be the.
Yeah, the John Wick guy in this.
It's it's it's a little crazy.
And I think he was just like, screw you, because Peter Dinklage,
like all celebrities, is probably delusional.
Yeah. Well, it's also it's an easy adjustment to make him an act.
Oh, sorry.
Oh, sneeze coming, not happy when it gets trapped.
I feel like that takes a year off your life.
Doesn't come out.
It's like when you're about to come and then it goes away.
You ever had one of those? All right.
Oh, I'm sorry.
No, I do.
We take the explicit off off this month.
Are we doing a G rated show now?
What is this fucking G?
What was I talking about?
Coming then I sneeze.
Oh, if he was an expert gunslinger,
that's an easy adjustment.
You buy that completely.
He also is in the movie.
They show in the trailer that he's like an expert sniper and stuff.
And it's like, that makes sense.
Like a guy has a disadvantage.
So he becomes excellent at another thing. Right.
Like, like, you know, it's a great example is
what's his face in
Django,
the German guys.
No, no, no. Christoph Waltz. Christoph Waltz.
He's like this short little guy in his 60s.
And they don't make him an ass kicker.
They make it that he is excellent on the draw. Right.
And he's got this contraption that he's made with this gun
where he can like he can take down a room.
It's like, yeah, I'll buy that. Sure.
You know what seemed to make you an expert gunslinger in the Old West?
And it'll be you'll see it, Joe.
I'll just try to describe it for the people at home.
But it seems to be you pull the trigger on your gun and hit your forearm.
You know, they're always bringing like the left arm over and down onto the gun hand.
Maybe they're bringing back the hammer.
No, yeah, it's the hammer.
They pull the hammer back because you can fire more quickly.
So each time when they're doing that, they keep re -cocking it.
Well, I may say cock on a G -rated pocket.
The hammer. That's what would happen if you pulled the trigger.
But pulling the trigger takes much longer.
And that is like they can rapid fire with a pistol.
OK, by just pulling the hammer back repeatedly.
Yeah. Yeah, that's always a cool move.
Looks cool. I always just assumed it was just kind of for style.
I was watching.
I don't know if this counts as a movie corner or not,
but I know it doesn't, because I didn't see the whole thing.
That was Tubi's original slogan was, I don't know if this counts as a movie.
That was going to be their first slogan.
But I was watching The Quick and the Dead.
Cool movie. Caught it randomly.
I've never seen it mid movie, so I didn't see the whole thing.
But I liked it a lot.
I was like, this is like classic Raimi.
Like, this is cool. Yeah, it's fun. It is fun.
And I like that the structure is basically
the same structure as like Mike Tyson's punch out.
It's like, yeah, keep just keep showing down with bigger and bigger dudes.
And Hackman at his best.
Hackman is never better than when he plays a piece of shit in the Old West.
Like, he is great at that, man.
He's always building a house.
I love Gina. Yeah.
And I love coming to my town.
Yeah, it's a lot of that, you know.
Unforgiven, of course.
I love seeing him now.
And everybody, you know, it's always tied to like,
you won't believe what Gene Hackman looks like today.
And they show you a picture
of a guy who looks like every 92 year old man in the world.
Looks like your old grandpa looks like everybody else.
It's like, what, what, guys?
Yeah, they really don't want you to age.
And obviously, it's way worse for women.
But it's just like, you won't believe what's happened.
It's like, well, all right, I believe it.
And it will happen to you as well.
And I love that every picture they get of him
is him walking out of a gas station with a coffee
and like a cigarette filling up his truck himself.
Yeah. And, you know, I'm like, I love that this guy is like, no,
I'm literally living a normal life.
Like, yes, leave me the fuck alone.
The hope is he's on some giant ranch or something.
I don't know what he's up to, but that's the hope.
I'm sure he is.
I'm sure he's made quite a bit of coin and he's, you know,
he's in like Montana or something.
Good. Let's hit that movie corn.
I rewatched The Elephant Man directed by Dave Lynch.
Notorious weirdo.
I've been I'd finally finished that room to dream book
where he goes in all the stories of the movies.
And The Elephant Man is like this weird kind of almost sweet story
from Lynch's career.
Everything else, you know, came to be from him,
you know, having some horrific experience.
Or it's like I was walking.
I was watching a naked woman walk down the street towards me
covered in blood when I was 10 years old.
And it really stuck with me.
His book is full of those stories.
But anyway, this story was basically this guy, Stuart Kornfeld,
who I had lunch with once and was the most fascinating dude.
He is now dead, but he was at Mel Brooks Productions for years.
And I met him when he was at Ben Stiller's production company,
which is where he was for 30 years or something, a long time.
And he saw a racer head and took it to Mel Brooks,
who at the time was just like a 50 year old guy and super funny.
But you don't think of like Mel Brooks and Anne Bancroft
going to a screening of a racer head.
It's deeply troubling even now.
And the movie came out, you know, 45 years ago.
And Brooks, who is an exceptional comedy writer,
but, you know, not necessarily the greatest film craftsman, let's say.
But he absolutely loved it.
He was like, this guy is the perfect guy to do The Elephant Man.
He was looking for somebody to direct it.
Lynch loved the material because it's a freak or an outcast, you know.
They probably would have gone directly to Tim Burton nowadays.
But the movie is fascinating.
It's in black and white.
It looks absolutely beautiful.
It's a 4K transfer, but it's on a Blu -ray.
Not sure why they haven't upgraded it to 4K.
It's a movie that's known for its incredible cinematography.
When I saw it as a kid, it actually had the same sort of effect on me as a racer head,
meaning I was very horrified by it, especially for a PG rated film.
It's PG.
This was before the PG -13 rating.
But they keep you from seeing The Elephant Man's face for about a half hour.
It starts with this surreal, insane sequence
where his mother is trampled by elephants at the circus.
And then it becomes kind of a stiff upper lip British chamber movie.
It's Anthony Hopkins trying to get to know the man behind this insane face that he has.
He has, I believe, elephantitis, which is why he's called The Elephant Man.
But he's got this kind of giant deformed head.
It's hard to look at.
Lynch says that he took multiple swings at creating the makeup himself and his garage.
And every time he would show it to people, they would be like,
no, David, you cannot release a movie where a man looks like this.
They will kill you.
So they found a good balance.
And John Hurt, weirdly, you know how every actor over 50 said,
what actor inspired?
Well, Marlon Brando and Streetcar.
They always pick the same three people.
Lately, the modern actor, the age maybe 32, 50,
they're all picking John Hurt and The Elephant Man
as their favorite performance of all time.
He is really good in it.
I guess they like it because he's able to show you his humanity and personality
despite wearing 20 pounds of makeup.
But he's great.
Hopkins is great.
The story, to me, keeps it from being a Lynch classic.
It really is just Anthony Hopkins trying to get
this elephant man to be more confident, pretty much.
At the end, he's like, I am not an animal.
That's the big famous scene.
It's about how we judge people who look different from us, sure.
But I don't know.
It keeps me at a distance.
It's not a movie that makes me cry, and I feel like it should.
I don't get super emotionally involved in it, but I admire everything about it.
I've never seen it.
It disturbed me greatly as a child, the glimpses I saw.
I'm embarrassed to admit that, truly.
But it did disturb me.
But no, Joe, because it's horror movie makeup.
It's no different.
Sure.
I mean, it's not a real guy with that face or something.
They did a thing on, I think I've mentioned this,
but they did a thing on, Matt Berry had that show.
It was one of the lesser known Matt Berry shows
where he plays like the detective in Elizabethan England.
Okay.
And one of the gags in it is that his informant is the elephant man,
and he goes and gets information from him,
and they make the guy look exactly like the Lynch version.
And then the gag is that he's kind of like Randy,
and he makes jokes and whatever,
and Barry's like, Christ, your fucking head, man, whatever.
It's very funny, but it is sort of disturbing
because it looks like the actual movie.
I've heard from people in recent years that have rewatched it,
they said the makeup doesn't hold up as well.
It looks sort of like plasticky and like whatever,
but I don't know that that would be the case.
I saw an interview once with John Hurt
where he has the makeup with him.
He has the pieces, and he holds them up to his face
and shows how he transforms into the character,
and it's pretty fascinating, but I still haven't seen it.
I didn't notice for a second anything looking fake in terms of his makeup.
I think the black and white actually helps that quite a bit.
It just sort of blends in.
There is, you know, you wonder how they would ever make that movie now.
Would they require somebody who has elephantitis of the face to play that part?
And even though that might sound silly,
there's a movie out right now starring a guy who has elephantitis of the face
and Sebastian Stan.
I'm not sure what that's called.
Who's also in the makeup.
Stan plays, no, no, Stan plays a guy.
Yeah, he's Stan.
Both guys are in it, but Stan plays a guy with the condition
and he is in full makeup.
This is called a different man.
But then the other guy is the guy from Under the Skin.
Right, and see, in that movie,
it is a real person's face sort of used to disturb and shock,
which is questionable, but I mean, I love Under the Skin
and obviously that's one of the more memorable images in it.
This movie, after undergoing surgery for a new start in life,
Edward, a man with neurofibromatosis,
becomes fixated on another man playing him in a stage production
based on his former life.
That sounds complicated.
But there it is.
So do they flip it where Sebastian Stan,
I'm assuming is the guy that gets his face fixed
and then the real guy is playing him in the play?
That's got to be what it is.
Couldn't work the other way around unless the real guy got the surgery done.
A stage production.
Why is this like a word problem based?
No, see, I think Sebastian Stan is a normal guy, Joe.
No, I saw a picture of him in the makeup.
And then there was an article yesterday I saw that said
Nicholas Cage joins the ranks of Sebastian Stan
and somebody else in current movies where they're unrecognizable.
I don't know.
All right.
Well, I always have a fantasy about getting picked
to go into the Criterion closet and I pull the elephant man
and say I'm finally going to watch it.
And that's like my story in the closet.
Anyway, that's where I'm at in life, people.
I'm sitting alone having fantasies about being asked
to go into the Criterion closet.
You do a king of comedy style where you're like in your apartment alone,
but you're like, oh, well, thank you.
Right this way into the closet then?
And then you're talking to yourself, laughing at your own jokes.
Standing in a closet with the door shut.
My theme for the corner will be all rewatches.
All right.
I rewatched Burn After Reading.
Ooh, I love it.
I love it.
It's a fucking masterpiece, man.
How is this not more renowned in the Coen Brothers catalog?
It gets better every time I watch it.
It's amazing.
It's because they set their own bar too high.
It's because when you go see a Coen Brothers movie for the last 20 years,
you can't help but compare it to No Country for Old Men, Fargo.
These like all -time masterpieces.
But Burn After Reading will, just like a serious man has done,
will join the ranks eventually of like their all -time classics.
The final scene of Burn After Reading is maybe my favorite thing
the Coen Brothers ever did.
It's amazing.
Between Rash and JK Simmons.
I love that.
Yeah.
The cutaways where Rash is explaining the situation.
Or I'm sorry, not the cutaways.
The off -camera retorts from Simmons where you don't even see him
and you just hear him going,
Jesus fucking Christ, what the fuck happened here?
It's so funny.
You know what I always forget is in that movie
until he walks away with it is John Malkovich.
Oh, yeah.
He's the best.
His scene where he's like, I have a drinking problem?
Man, I love that scene so much.
Fuck you.
He's incredible in that movie.
You're a Mormon.
Everyone has a drinking problem.
I saw that in the theater and that's the opening scene in the movie.
And I was like, wow, we're off to the races here.
They started strong with this.
But much like Copland, it is a movie where every person is cast
exactly as you want to see them in a movie.
Malkovich is playing a man who's alcoholic,
who's also becoming slowly unglued.
Tilda Swinton plays the most callous,
demonstrative, condescending person ever.
Clooney plays like a daft, arrogant moron.
Pitt plays an airhead.
Frances McDormand plays a woman who's self -obsessed with her body
and is neurotic.
Everybody is playing so hard to their funniest version
of what they're able to play.
It's great.
I'll tell you who I also forget every time.
Dick Jenkins in the mix.
He's amazing in it.
Yeah, Dick Jenkins playing the put -upon.
Nothing's working out.
Every role is pitch perfect.
It's so good.
It's so funny.
Weirdly, and it's probably controversial,
but I hated when George Clooney entered the Coen Brothers universe,
which I guess was Oh Brother, Where Art Thou?
I like that movie.
I feel like you catch him acting in it too much.
He doesn't fall into the performance.
And him and Pitt do these like caricature type performances
that just don't sit well with me.
Although Pitt in this one is very funny
because of how stupid he is and the way he dies,
which is one of my favorite movie deaths in history.
Oh, yeah.
Burning after reading.
Check it out.
The I'd say the two most.
Well, no here.
Who knows?
Here's I won't say the most.
Here's three of the most shocking deaths in movie history
judging by theater audience reaction that I have seen.
Number one, Marty Sheen falling from the top of that building
in The Departed in slow motion.
People were screaming because he did.
He became such a lovable father character in like a few short scenes.
Crazy.
That death scene.
Amazing.
Then you got Brad Pitt getting shot in the face in the closet.
Doubly funny because Brad Pitt was the biggest star in the world at the time.
You don't expect it.
Three, I gotta say out of sight when that big fat guy
running up the stairs trips, falls and blows his head off.
It is so unexpected.
The movie is not violent at all and it's shocking.
But those are the three that come to mind for me
where the audience was like insane for a minute afterwards.
I can't believe your number one isn't also departed when DiCaprio gets shot.
I remember being like, holy shit.
No, I know.
But I guess they're like Marty Sheen comes in and you're like,
oh, I love this sweet old man.
And DiCaprio is a cop who's been double crossing everybody.
So you're at least at least expecting it.
He's going to be in some gunplay.
But you're right.
That was a shocking one as well.
Joe Pesci in Goodfellas probably hit really hard when you saw that theatrically
because the movie that's a big testament to how great that movie is,
is when Pesci goes, the movie doesn't collapse
because he's such a fire plug in that movie.
But he leaves and Scorsese I think wisely knows
now that we've lost our insane engine, Pesci,
we have to make the last 45 minutes of this movie
feel like you're on cocaine, which he does.
So you're so carried away by it.
You don't even miss Pesci.
And the brilliance of that scene is
Leota has the voiceover where he says,
you know, your friend is the one that comes to kill you.
However, I forget how he says it.
Yeah.
And in that Pesci scene and they don't put,
it's almost not noticeable in the Pesci scene.
When he gets killed, it's Paulie's brother.
And you don't even realize it the first couple of times.
And then all of a sudden you're like, oh my God,
that's exactly what Leota was talking about.
And they draw no attention to it.
So it's great.
Anyway, what else you got?
Well, I watched the new Criterion 4K of Risky Business.
I've had a weird history with this movie.
I always was desperate to see it when I was a kid
because I thought it was soft core porn.
That's why I wanted to see every movie when I was a kid.
And it's got some sex in it.
It's a teen sex comedy that is light years above
the teen sex comedies that were being produced at this time.
You know, you've got, as far as that genre goes,
you got the classic PG -13 version.
I'm thinking Can Hardly Wait or PG.
You got 16 Candles, Breakfast Club, whatever, R -rated.
And then you got the sex movies, which are R -rated.
And those are like Porky's, American Pie, et cetera.
Risky Business plays like a very adult drama.
That's kind of funny, but happens to be about teenagers.
I forgot what like a bleak, dark satire of capitalism this movie is.
Perfect timing for Criterion to come out with this
as everyone in the world is talking about capitalism.
But yeah, when you hear the plot, you're expecting one thing.
And that's just not what this movie is.
The plot is Tom Cruise is a very driven, focused young boy.
He looks like a high schooler in this movie.
It's kind of his big break.
And he's Mr. Driven, Mr. Obsessed.
His friends are Curtis Armstrong, Booger from Avenger the Nerds,
and Bronson Pinchot, Balky.
They let Bronson Pinchot and Tom Cruise have like a sweet,
almost like a little boy friendship that I found beautiful.
Because usually in these teenager movies,
it's two teenage guys calling each other slurs.
But they're close friends.
And then Booger is always like, dude, you got to loosen up.
You got to learn to say what the fuck with your life.
That would be more than enough theme for most teenager movies.
That would be more than enough theme for like Superbad, et cetera.
But it's got this whole other movie going on.
He has a sex worker come to his home played by Joe's obsession,
Rebecca DeMornay, never looked better than in this movie.
And she's excellent in it.
And they kind of fall in love.
She convinces him, while your parents are gone,
why don't we turn your house into a brothel?
But then the movie you get is not that movie.
It's not Night Shift.
It's not a bunch of prostitutes running out of a suburban house
in the middle of the night or something.
It's not a sex romp.
It really is about how money rules everything.
There's a scene very early on where Tom Cruise is asking his friends,
they're all like, I'm going to go here.
And I heard you can make like 120 ,000 a year.
And that's all they're talking about.
And he's like, don't any of you want to make a difference
or do anything with your life?
You just cared about money?
And they're all like, yeah, just money.
Money's fine.
Perfect 80s movie.
Way deeper than it gets credit for.
It is very sexy when the sex does come.
Cruise and DeMornay are great.
It's a classic.
I love it.
And it's never looked better.
It looks phenomenal.
All right.
Um, my other entry today is, uh, a terrible movie.
I don't know why I watched it again.
I just did though, um, Lost and Found.
Sure.
There's a few movies called Lost and Found.
I'm talking about the David Spade movie.
I'm such a fan of David Spade.
I don't say this to disparage him.
I'm a massive fan.
I don't know that the guy's ever been in a good movie.
Um, you know, he -
Tommy Boy.
No, he has.
You like Tommy Boy quite a bit.
Tommy Boy is, to me, A plus is, I think that's insane.
If the big Lebowski is an A plus, Tommy Boy can't, it's not -
I'm gonna give Tommy Boy an A, uh, then I'll give it an A.
All right.
Well, for what it's doing, a frat dude comedy, it's the pinnacle.
It's up there with the early Sandlers.
It's up there with, it's funnier than Dirty Work, and I love Dirty Work.
Dirty Work's a terrible movie.
It's a terrible movie.
That's true.
You know, I'm not saying Tommy Boy isn't funny.
Yes.
I'm just saying I don't think it's a good movie.
Well, it doesn't matter.
It's, it's, we can, we can disagree, but it does make me laugh.
And I, that's fine.
I will, I'll give you that.
He's, he's in Tommy Boy.
It's a good movie, but I'm, I also don't count Tommy Boy as it.
Well, I guess he doesn't have a lot of David Spade movies.
Like, it's not like, like Lost and Found is his movie.
Yeah.
For a long time, he was in Reality Bites, which I love, actually.
He was in, um, PCU.
He was just the worm.
He was the guy who was like, uh, are you sure you guys want to do that?
Or he'd be the jerky manager or something, but you don't get a lot of starring Spade.
That's true.
What, um, who was he in Reality Bites?
He was, I want to say the manager at a fast food place that one of them works out.
Okay.
I believe.
Yeah.
All right.
Um, let me look that up.
Now you got me doubting myself, but go ahead.
Well, anyway, but it's a comedic role.
He's not.
Yeah.
He's not playing like a, you know, he's, it's not a serious whatever.
No.
Okay.
He's in one movie where he plays a serious role and he's like a,
he plays like some kind of tycoon or something.
I forget what that's called.
Anyway, he's a, he's the manager during Winona Ryder's job interview at Wienerschnitzel.
Okay.
Got it.
Um, so yeah, it's unfair of me to say he's never been a good, because I'm, I'm, I'm,
he, he, he doesn't usually have his own movie and I'm thinking of,
I'm thinking of, um, you know, like, like grownups and shit like that, you know?
Yeah.
So that's not fair of me.
Uh, fair enough.
Um, anyway, the point that I'm getting at is, uh, Lost and Found is a very bad movie.
Um, it's got a few funny scenes.
The plot is, is he's in love with this woman.
Who's the, who's the love interest?
Some French actress.
I'm not sure what her name is.
Oh yeah, Jeanne Moreau.
But, um, he's in love with her.
She doesn't seem to know he exists outside of the fact that every time her dog gets out,
he finds her dog for her and brings it to her.
And then she's kind of like, thanks, bye.
So he comes up with the plot that he's going to rob.
He's going to kidnap her dog and he's going to say, oh, I couldn't find it this time.
And that's going to keep them interacting.
So then he, you know, it's a classic 90s, create a stalker situation and it'll be a meat cute.
Um, you know, it's, it's just not a great movie.
Uh, does it have some humor?
Yeah.
Uh, the, uh, great Artie Lang is in it.
Artie plays, they do a funny thing.
I mean, this is also very indicative of that time period of comedy where they do a thing
that's completely unbelievable, but it's a, it's satirizing another popular thing.
So they just do it.
So the, what they do in this is Artie Lang is works for David Spade and he like idolizes him.
So they do like a single white female where Artie Lang dyes his hair blonde and feathers it
and starts to dress exactly like David Spade.
That's funny.
It's funny.
It's ridiculous, but it's funny.
Um, but there is a, there is a great scene with John Lovitz where John Lovitz plays
Artie Lang's uncle, who's a vet.
And the dog has swallowed a wedding ring, uh, that David Spade needs to get back.
Yeah.
And they bring him to this vet who's played by John Lovitz and it's classic Lovitz.
I turn to a guy that takes nothing and turns it into gold.
Lovitz has popped in to, he has been so great in one scene in 25 movies.
Yeah.
His peak dramatically, which might, might, might get laughs, but his peak is happiness,
which is about to come out on 4k criteria.
And I'm excited for people to see that scene where he's amazing in it.
He just like breaks your heart.
He kicks off the movie of happiness.
Um, wedding singer.
Yes.
He's awesome in there.
He's going insane and I'm reaping the benefits.
And then he pulls the curtain very slowly across his face.
That's awesome.
A plus, A plus.
Uh, he, uh, he plays this vet in this and he does this gag like,
because David Spade and Artie Lang are dressed exactly the same.
Yeah.
Uh, and have the same haircut.
They walk in the office and John Lovitz looks at them and he goes, he goes,
I see small.
I see large.
Where's medium?
Nah.
And he keeps doing these terrible jokes, but he does that laugh every time.
And he, because it's John Lovitz, it's completely organic and believable
that this guy laughs like that.
And he goes, what did they run out of batter at the cloning factory?
Nah.
Yeah.
I gotta tell you, you're describing a hilarious movie to me.
Maybe I'll watch it again, because.
Well, they also, they also do the, and you get the idea that if,
if Farley were alive, he would have played the Lang part in this.
Yes.
Yeah.
Because they do do a gag that's very similar to a Tommy Boy guy,
where they have to go pick up dog shit from the dog park, like,
bags and bags of dog shit to see if the dog shit out this ring.
And Artie Lang has newspapers on David Spade's bathroom floor,
and he's sifting through the dog shit with rubber gloves.
And he's got like the faintest dot of dog shit on his face.
And his hands are covered and he goes, he goes,
he goes, did I get any on me, boss?
And David Spade goes a little there.
And then of course, Artie Lang wipes it with the shit glove,
makes it way worse.
And he's like, did I get it?
Right.
Yeah.
He's like, yeah, you got it.
These are the only funny parts of the movie.
I mean, you're everything you've said so far makes this one of the all -time
greatest comedies ever made.
Watch it.
It's on surprise.
Tooby.
What's, you know, here's the beautiful thing about Tooby.
It is so hard to find so many movies, even in the streaming era.
They're just not there.
And when you search online, where can I find X streaming?
They don't even mention Tooby half the time.
But when you go to Tooby and search what you're looking for,
be it pornography, be it something that no one has ever heard of.
You can't even find it online.
Be it an art film that's been highly rated by everyone.
You can only find all these things on Tooby.
You have to watch them with commercials.
The commercials will start with no rhyme or reason.
There's no like, okay, here's a good spot to take a break.
Tooby doesn't do that shit, but they do have nearly everything ever made.
It's very impressive.
It's free.
Tooby, like I was saying, my friend Jess described Prime.
Tooby really does feel like, you know, 80s video store.
You know, just kind of like all kinds of, all kinds of like,
they don't even have like a staff to like clean up.
There's just like big piles of tapes everywhere and you figure it out.
I watched, Joe, can I do Quiet Place, the new one?
You're not going to see that, right?
Nope.
All right, do it.
I'm not going to see it.
Quiet Place, day one.
I didn't even really want to see this one.
I really liked the first Quiet Place and I thought the second one was so unmemorable
that I don't know a single thing about it except Jimon Honsu appears
and is shot 10 seconds later.
And I was like, this feels crazily weird and racist for a guy who's had
a 25 year career in Oscar nominations to walk in and get shot or get killed by the aliens.
Anyway, Honsu is back in this one.
I guess somebody probably pointed out to them how horrible that was to do to him.
So he's back, but only very briefly.
We got Lupita Nyong 'o, who is absolutely delightful.
I don't really understand her career.
Um, or what her like management team is doing, what her strategy is, I guess.
But I always am happy to see her.
You know what I mean?
It's like, she always will pop up in something and you're like, oh yeah, Lupita Nyong 'o.
I love her.
But you know what I mean?
She's just like not in the public eye for some reason.
Am I wrong?
Uh, no, I think she is.
I think she just doesn't.
I mean, that's the weird thing nowadays.
When you have a great actor like her, who doesn't completely steer into the curve of
exposure 24 -7, ramming myself down your throats and actually keeps some privacy and
dignity and whatever, it seems like, oh, are they not around?
And it's like, no, they're totally around.
They're just not shoving it in your face.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
Yeah, no, that's true.
I guess I just mean the projects she chooses maybe aren't on my radar.
I just, well, she was in Black Panther, of course.
That's on everybody's radar.
And this is a huge movie too.
I like her.
I love looking at her.
I just think she's captivating and I'm a big fan.
This movie, I gotta say real weirdly, when I looked at my friend's letterboxed on it,
meaning you see what like 20 people you follow thought of a movie, which is fun to do.
I always text my friend, I'll be like, you like that piece of shit?
It's fun.
But all of my friends, for the most part, loved Quiet Place Day One.
Best of the franchise.
Thought it was, you know, excellent.
I don't get it, man.
I was bored.
It was short, 99 minutes.
Kudos for that.
It is done by the guy who did Pig with Nick Cage, which we enjoyed,
but Pig was a three million dollar movie.
This is what we've been talking about.
You get a guy with an interesting little vision, makes an interesting little movie,
and we give him the reins to a 200 million dollar action film,
and then that becomes his career.
I hate it, but it's where we are.
He does, I'll give him a little bit of credit.
He does try to bring a bit of an artsy indie spirit to this big blockbuster.
And I wish there was more of that.
I think like Joker's a good example of that.
But unfortunately, the story is just not good enough.
Nyango has cancer.
There's a big attack, obviously the first attack on Manhattan of these aliens
that would later come to be in the Quiet Place movies.
She meets up with this guy played by, what's that dude's name?
Joseph Quinn.
Okay.
Guess what people like from Stranger Things.
And the two of them basically try to get out of New York, get to safety together.
The other one was about the family.
This one is about the city realizing what's happening, what's about to come, etc.
But there's very little alien action.
There's shockingly little suspense.
Because for all Quiet Places faults, it was packed with suspense.
You remember the set pieces because they were really good and really well done.
This doesn't have that.
It's like, and it's not a shock.
The guy who did Pig is not the guy to deliver you a big suspenseful action packed alien movie.
It's a weird choice.
So it just kind of feels like this little meditation between two people
who are kind of getting to know each other under very dire circumstances.
Much like the Pelican Brief, like it's 1993, there's no romance between the two of them
because how could a hot black woman and a hot white man find love?
There's not even a discussion of romance, which is gross.
They called this shit out when Julia Roberts and Denzel were in a two and a half hour movie
and didn't find each other attractive.
Well, do you think it's that or do you think it's just they're saying
we're not going to do the typical thing where they have to fall in love?
I don't think anybody these days is against an interracial couple on screen.
I mean, that seems to be the.
Yeah, you're right.
I just think if it was two white people, we would definitely deal with a relationship
and it feels weird.
Every aspect of our ways of addressing representation feels weird to me.
And I'm always just trying to figure out what the intent was.
But look, I could be wrong there, too.
Maybe that was the intent.
Maybe both characters were written as white.
I don't know.
And they cast Lupita.
That happens, too.
I could be completely wrong and I'm talking on my ass.
But that would have made the movie much more interesting to me, I guess.
An interracial romance, something because the action wasn't hitting.
It's like we're going to make this character based quiet place movie.
But then they didn't.
They gave Lupita one trait, which is that she has cancer.
And they gave Joseph Quinn one trait, which is that he's nice and like cheering her up.
But this is a franchise that's just very weird to me.
Nobody expected one to be the hit.
It was they rushed to into production and it stunk.
And then I don't think we need to keep going, gang.
Like the they exhausted all the we got to be quiet so they don't attack us stuff.
There's almost none of that in this movie.
And to me, that's why you're doing it.
Otherwise, it's Arcadian.
And look, we liked Arcadian fine.
But this movie is equally as good as Arcadian and it probably cost 50 times more.
Not a disaster.
Passes the time.
It's just kind of like this is already a franchise that feels cooked.
It's that thing where they go so deep into the franchise.
The installments become contradictory of the premise.
You got a movie called A Quiet Place that's not about a quiet place anymore.
It's just about a regular place and aliens attack and everybody's making noise.
So you can't even distinguish whether the aliens are attacking because of the noise or not.
And now it's just an alien movie.
It's exactly it's like the place.
And one of the episodes of Angry Video Game Nerd, he reviewed the video game adaptation
of Street Fighter the movie and he was like, this makes no sense.
He's like, it's a movie.
It's a video game based on a movie about a video game.
So you're so far away from the original IP at that point.
It's odd.
It doesn't make any sense.
So I have zero interest.
If you told me, if you asked me to write A Quiet Place 3, my take on it would be,
all right, if we have to do a prequel, fine, whatever, but just do it 80s style.
The Quiet Place aliens take Manhattan.
We're going to New York.
Now, instead of Krasinski being freaked out because he's underneath a waterfall
that is summoning the aliens because it's causing noise, you start the fucking movie
with a guy jackhammering the street in Manhattan and blood comes up from the ground or something.
New York is the loudest city on earth.
You're doing the Quiet Place movie.
They don't engage with that at all.
There is no like, guys, shut the fuck up.
There's no big New York guy being like, what are you doing?
They don't do anything with the premise of them being in New York.
And in addition, it's so obviously filmed in Vancouver or whatever else
that you don't get any of the New York feel, which is a bummer
because they'll spend $150 million on digital effects,
but they won't spend $500 ,000 to shoot it in New York.
It's probably much more than that, but still.
Well, you just also -
We're all looking fake now.
I hate it.
You just also picked out one of the many inconsistencies of the original film,
which is he's not freaked out about the waterfall.
He goes to the waterfall so he can scream and it covers his voice,
but you're in the loudest place in nature and there's no aliens there.
It's stupid.
I'm not a fan of the franchise.
I won't be seeing it and I'm glad to hear this new one was a disappointment,
so I have no temptation.
Uh, well -made, oddly dull.
That would be my review.
Um, should we move on to, uh, the movie at hand?
Let's do it.
Joe and Pat talking Deadpool and Wolverine.
Um, I will straight away, much to my surprise, say I,
for the most part, I loved this movie.
When I heard a third Deadpool was coming out,
I was like, yeah, cool.
I like the other two.
I wasn't excited.
Um, when they said it was going to be Deadpool and Wolverine, I was intrigued,
but I was also like, Christ, they can't just let any of these characters go.
Hugh Jackman's dead.
Then I saw the trailer and I saw him in the yellow suit and I was like, all right,
you know what?
This looks, this looks fun.
This looks like comic booky.
But then before the release of the movie, it was preceded by a lot of
Reynolds and Hugh Jackman antics, which get annoying and old.
I don't ever want to see the two of them again.
They're a little, they're a little pre movie commercials.
I almost had to leave the theater every time.
But that all said, um, does it seem like there are eight celebrities in the world to you?
Ryan Reynolds, Hugh Jackman, Taylor Swift, Tom Cruise, Margot Robbie.
Um, there's about eight now.
I just said to a buddy of mine, Camille just got cast as a booster gold in, in a DC thing.
And I'm like, he was in Marvel.
Like, why do they just keep shuffling the same, you know, Robert Downey Jr.
is coming back to play Dr. Doom.
Now, granted, there is a storyline where Iron Man becomes Dr. Doom
in one of the Marvel timelines or whatever.
Yeah.
So I guess, yes.
Could you make sense of it?
Sure.
Could it be cool?
Yeah, maybe.
But it's like, guys, it's the same fucking 10 people just being shuffled around,
you know, even in this.
Yeah.
No, that, that you're exactly right.
Obviously Downey Jr. is included in that too.
And I think that's what caused this thought is like, they won't even take a chance on
anybody else anymore.
Like it's getting to like, Marvel is going to have people playing
multiple parts in their little universe.
It's that's sad to me.
And there's this backlash, there's this absolute backlash against fan service
about things catering too much for nostalgia, whatever.
And then you watch the Comic -Con clip and Downey comes out and unveils himself so proudly.
Yeah.
And everybody's going crazy.
And it's like, I'm not saying I don't even get the excitement.
I'm just like, do we want fan service or do we not?
Like, I don't get what we're doing here.
Now, this all said.
I certainly don't want only fan service.
This all said, I will get back to Deadpool.
The new Captain America looked really cool to me.
The trailer was good.
I was like, this looks like a serious goddamn movie for once.
They're not, it's not a Deadpool work works as a comedy because it's supposed to be a
comedy.
That's what Deadpool is.
And that's why it works so well.
I said to my buddy today, we were talking about this.
I said, I'm at a point where I think potentially the DC and Marvel universes are such a mess,
which they make fun of in this movie at length.
The only good superhero movie you could make now is Deadpool Wolverine because it's the
movie that's allowed to piss on the fucking franchises and the universe and make fun of
it and come out of it and call out how ridiculous all of it is.
Anyway, this movie.
Do you know, by the way, and I read, when Jim Carrey made $20 million for Cable Guy,
it was national news for months, 1996 broke records.
It was talk.
We talked about the wastefulness of society, more capitalism talk back then.
Robert Downey Jr.
For playing Dr.
Doom is making the, the thing actually said more than, so who knows how much more than
more than $80 million.
And that's not, that's not somebody, uh, lucking out.
That's not Stallone lucking out and taking 5 % of the gross of Rocky.
And they're like, who gives a shit?
And then he winds up getting rich off it.
That's before the script is probably fucking written on this thing.
They're paying him more than $80 million.
This is a man who definitely has a billion dollars, but it was very eye -opening to me.
I didn't know those salaries were going on.
I thought the $20 million days got under control after Jim Carrey.
And now even your biggest stars were making.
If, if not, if not comparable to that, less than that, I had no idea.
We were doing $80 million paydays.
I mean, that's fucking disgusting.
Oh, Ford still Paris and Ford still pulls like 75 million a movie.
I mean, what, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
What, why work?
I don't get it.
I'm like, hit a place where the money means nothing anymore.
It's like what, go live life or, or go shoot something in your backyard because it's fun.
Like, who the fuck wants to deal with all this shit?
I got to go to fucking, you know, the East end of Canada to shoot something in the winter
because it's, they're going to do it there because New York's too expensive.
And it's cold in Harrison.
It's weird.
It's also like, why not?
Why are we not hearing Harrison Ford just donated $50 million to X?
Maybe he's doing that.
Yes.
But Harrison, baby, what's going on, man?
He does do a lot of, I think charity work.
So does DiCaprio.
I think they just don't like publicize it, but.
Hey, good on them then.
But I hope they do.
Jesus Christ.
$80 million for a six month job.
So anyway, Deadpool Wolverine.
Yes.
Here's the basic plot.
Deadpool wants to join the Avengers.
He is denied the very funny scene with John Favreau, which I really enjoyed.
He gets pulled into the interdimensional headquarters of the guys that run all the
timelines.
So they're making fun of the multiverse.
They're making fun of all the different timelines of Marvel.
And they tell him that the anchor being of his world has died.
And that because of that, his world is fading and everybody he loves will be dead, too.
He realizes he learns the anchor being was Wolverine who died in Logan.
He goes to dig up Wolverine.
Wolverine is in fact dead.
So he has to find an alternate timeline.
Wolverine also played by Hugh Jackman, who was not quite as heroic.
And bring him in to try to save his own universe.
That's the basic plot.
They're fighting against a bad guy or a bad, a baddie, excuse me, woman,
who is the twin sister of Professor Xavier.
And I actually missed that.
The twin sister of Professor Xavier, but she's 100 years younger.
Well, it's multiverse.
So she's one of the rules, right?
Yeah, she's one of the versions of it or whatever.
And in doing this, they have to, and she wants to take over every multiverse and
destroy all of them so she can be the queen of the one remaining universe.
They have to stop her.
They have to save all the multiverses.
And in doing this, they link up with characters from across the Marvel universe
that they hid very well from showing in these trailers.
This is a very, very spoiler heavy review.
I urge you, if you are going to watch this movie, do not listen to this because
there are some really fun surprises.
There's your warning.
And from there it just goes.
It's shitloads of fun cameos from all different Marvel movies that all,
by the way, that all ended poorly.
I thought that was brilliant that they only brought in characters from movie,
franchise, exercises that failed.
They brought in Chris Evans.
You think he's going to be Captain America and it turns out he's Johnny Storm from the
Fantastic Four movies.
They brought in Wesley Snipes.
Blade one and two were awesome.
Blade three was terrible.
Blade three also starred Ryan Reynolds.
Very funny joke there.
Did they mention that they were in that movie together?
I was like, where is that mentioned?
No, they do.
Snipes goes, I don't like you.
And Ryan Reynolds goes, let's be honest, you never did.
They make a joke about that.
If that counts, okay.
They bring in Electra, one of the biggest Marvel bombs ever.
And one of the plot points is they want to join together to fight this villain.
And unfunny they say, we deserve an ending or whatever.
Like, let's bring our own journey to an end here.
And in the movie, it means their personal journey.
And then metaphorically to all of us, it's like, oh yeah, these franchises all tried
to get started and then bombed.
So I thought all of that was awesome.
I thought it was really well done.
There were some jokes in it where you're like, come on, guys, you know, they do a
he's standing right behind me, isn't he thing?
You know, the old lady.
I mean, the old sitcom classic.
He's standing right behind me.
The old lady cursing, the young kid cursing, you know, cliched stuff.
You're like, okay.
But for the most part, it was really, really funny.
The action was awesome.
It was well directed.
And it felt like a super fun comic book.
It felt like I was watching like a really fun one -off graphic novel that I would have
enjoyed very much reading.
I liked it.
I really liked it.
And then in the moments where it was heartfelt, it was truly heartfelt.
I cried a little bit at the end.
I thought it was kind of a beautiful ending and it was endearing.
I really liked it.
Joe, you remain a fascinating human being.
This movie would seemingly be everything you rail against and you have railed
against since day one of this podcast.
It's just cameos.
The story I feel is a very flimsy framework to hang jokes on.
I'll say I only laughed once.
Although I agree with you, it's funny.
Part of that's just me being broken and having written comedy my whole life.
I am more of a guy who goes, that's funny.
I like the spirit of it.
I like exactly what you're saying, that it is an intentional comedy.
And at a time where there are no comedies being made, this is it.
There's something very warm and happy and feel good about going to a movie
with three jokes a minute, whether they are good or not.
A movie that is trying to make you laugh is refreshing.
It's been a while.
The movie at large, the laugh I had, I'll tell you, was the Channing Tatum thing
where he was going to play Gambit at some point.
If that is the character and the voice he was going to use,
that would have been the Morbius of its day.
That would have been the biggest flop of all time.
I didn't know if the character was supposed to be serious or not.
He's throwing cards, which is kind of cool.
And they give him a badass moment.
But then the whole rest of the time, he's talking in this horrible New Orleans accent.
And Ryan Reynolds is making fun of it.
And that stuff, to me, was very funny.
Very funny.
The one time I laughed out loud was, who is your dialect coach?
The Minions?
I laughed so hard at that.
I don't even know anything about the Minions.
I like the delivery.
I like the joke.
It made me laugh.
This is the first comedy I've been to in my entire life,
where I felt like quite a few of the jokes were going over my head
because I don't give a shit about comic books and all that stuff at all.
The thing where Chris Evans became the Human Torch,
that's a joke I got two minutes late.
And I was like, that's very funny.
That's clever.
But it's all in jokes.
And if it were all in jokes and it was $2 .45, like most of these Marvel movies,
I'd be more pissed.
It's a nice two hours, which is appreciated.
Still too long.
But it didn't have that additional half hour where you're like,
I don't know if I'm going to make it to the credits on this bad boy.
He says in the last 20 minutes, he turns to camera and goes,
this is it, guys.
I promise.
Don't worry.
We're wrapping it up here.
I was like, okay, even they know these things go too long.
Deadpool has the attitude of a Beetlejuice or the cartoon character of Beetlejuice.
All the two -camera shit.
He's a cartoon character in a supposedly real world.
To that, I would not have made everybody in this movie funny.
For example, Matthew McFadden, the guy from Succession,
he's playing this with a Muppet movie level of broadness,
the villain in this thing.
And it's like, no, well, this is an R -rated movie.
He should have been normal in my opinion.
Everybody's kind of going for the rafters except Jackman,
who even with all this crazy shit going on just stays in that pocket of like,
I'm a miserable alcoholic.
But Reynolds, look, he's not really for me now.
He annoys the fuck out of me, but he's got that just Bugs Bunny thing where
he keeps stepping up to the plate.
He fucks with everybody.
And at some point you're kind of charmed by it and you're taken away by it.
I thought Deadpool 2, if memory serves, was the funniest of the three by a good margin.
I liked one and two more than three, I will say.
But I liked three.
It just sort of endorsing something like this just feels kind of gross
with everything we rail about on this podcast.
But funny matters.
The fact that it was funny helps and the fact that it was an intentional comedy helps.
Yes, here's why.
Intentional is the key word.
I was watching the Red Letter Media review of this and they liked it.
And Mike from Red Letter Media said,
I don't know if anybody else could get away with this.
I feel like if Star Wars did something like this, their fans would be outraged.
And Jay on Red Letter Media said, yeah, but this is what Deadpool is.
That's why it works because this is what the comics are.
So for that reason, the intent, at every Deadpool, I go in going,
I don't know if I'm even going to like this.
I end up laughing and I go, god damn it, it was funny.
But that's why I said earlier, I feel like it works because it can step outside of itself
and make fun of how absurd all this is and be like, guys, if we're going to do it,
we're going to hang it on its, turn it on its ear and do it like this.
And I loved like, let's bring in the sort of B team of Marvel actors.
That was a great idea, yes.
And I loved seeing Wesley Snipes.
The writers' dicks must have gotten hard when they realized
if we show just the sleeve of Chris Evans' costume, it's also blue.
And you will think he's coming back as Captain America.
And then when he flames on, I was like, I did not see that coming from a mile away.
Like that was so funny.
My favorite joke in the whole thing was when the time cops show up at his birthday party
and he's talking to them because he thinks they're strippers.
He goes, and look at me, big guy, this isn't pretty woman, we're kissing.
I forgot that Deadpool was so homoerotic as well, which I admire.
It's amazing that it's such a big hit with all these incels
because he talks a lot about getting fucked.
I don't have a lot of vaginal sex.
There's a bunch of funny lines in it.
This was the first one where I was like, oh, he flat out is telling us he's gay a lot of the time.
He's not just being funny, like he's saying, no, no, I do this.
I liked it.
I liked all the little quips.
I liked when the female Professor X came out and he's like,
this is not going to go over well with the anti -woke mob.
All of that stuff, I really, really enjoyed it.
The amount of shots at how shitty recent Marvel movies have been felt a little odd to me
because you're not standing in a classic here, Ryan Reynolds.
It's always weird when you're taking shots
because it makes you kind of look at you like, what are you doing?
I disagree.
I think this is a tent pole for Marvel and I think it's a huge success.
And I think, look, I will give you this.
It is a little of the, we're going to call ourselves out on it.
So then you can't make, we called ourselves out so it's okay.
And it's like, well, it's not okay unless you fix all these problems
that you guys are making fun of in your own movie.
But I did like when he tells Wolverine, he's like,
you're coming into the universe at a low point.
All that stuff was very funny to me.
Yeah. Yeah.
I think were I a Marvel fan boy, a superhero guy,
I would have gotten a lot more out of it comedically probably.
But I got a lot of respect for it.
I would honestly, if you were like,
do you want to watch that three hour Avengers movie again, one time?
Or would you rather watch the three Deadpool movies 10 times each?
I'd probably have to give it a lot of thought
because there's always a moment in like those Avengers movies
where I look at my phone and I realize it's been like an hour and 10 minutes
and the run time's 2 58 and I want to kill myself.
Yeah.
And just because this movie didn't give me that feeling at all
and I was genuinely entertained for most of it,
my hog is at least facing forward.
You know, I'm not, it's not pointing at the chin,
but the hog is borderline up for Deadpool versus Wolverine,
even though I think it's the weakest of these films.
My hog is up for Deadpool three times like the claws of Wolverine.
I liked it and I'm happy to admit when I'm wrong.
We'll be back folks with more episodes this month.
Uh, Joe DeRosa comedy on Instagram and whatever.
Uh, and come to those warmup shows.
If you're in the Phoenixville, Pennsylvania area, September 10th and 12th
at the Steel City coffee house.
Um, and I'll be announcing the 2025 tour very soon
and check out Joey roses.
If you're in New York, the Patrick Walsh on Instagram,
see you in hell pod on Instagram.
We will be back.
We will talk to you next time.
And we will see you in hell.