I'm here for BetRivers' online casino and sportsbook with poker icon Phil Helmuth.
And now, thanks to the excitement of BetRivers, I'm also a slots icon.
That's great!
And the same game, Parley icon.
Cool, cool.
A blackjack icon, a moneyline icon.
A roulette icon.
Take it from Phil Helmuth.
If you love games, BetRivers is the place to play in Bet.
BetRivers.
Games on.
Must be 21 plus and President of West Virginia.
Void were prohibited.
Terms and conditions apply.
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -GAMBLING.
The football season is full of guarantees.
And here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the Fanatics Game Day guarantee,
every single game day from now until October,
if your football bet loses,
you'll earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with Fanatics,
you're either winning or winning money back in fan cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to Fanatics Sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 plus gambling problem called 1 -800 -GAMBLER.
Offer not available in all states.
It's Terms Apply.
See Fanatic's fourth book app.
I'll see you when you're gone.
And when the sound of your screams
becomes a thing on my dreams, you know I say, hey, hey, hey.
I'll see you when you're gone.
You know what, I'll see you when you're gone.
You know what, we're gone.
Hello, hello, hello, everybody.
everybody welcome to another episode of we'll see you in hell this is Joe de Rosa on one
side of your head and I am Patrick Walsh on the other side of your head we'll see you
in hell the podcast is now a part of the Fangoria podcast network for more information about
the network including other programs how to follow the show and to find past episodes
of we'll see you in hell please visit Fangoria .com now on with the show for those of you
just tuning in for the first time the reason we're split on either side of you is because
this is a commentary podcast and if you want to watch the movie along with what we're about
to do you can kind of just send that up the middle and you got us on either side just
like in real life if you're watching a movie with Pat and me you'd be right between us on
this love seat we're sitting on right now maybe I sort of find my hand sliding into
your pants rummaging around liking what I see maybe the lights go out maybe Joe's hand
reaches into the other side of your pants which side of the pants are you in I'm in the right
side of your pants I'm in the back side oh okay I go right for the back hole wow alright
yeah do you lick the fingers or just jam at home after or before well folks grossed out
these are the jokes you're gonna get on this show. We always start real blue and then smooth
out to much more clever stuff. Maybe it's an attention grabber. Well it is what it is.
It is what it is. Usually in the stand up world they tell you
to close with sex. Yeah. We've been opening with it.
Sometimes pedophilia bits. Right. Anyway here we are in the show.
This little preamble time is the time for you to go to your Netflix account boot it
up find the movie scream that's what we're doing today and tribute to the late great
West Craven. Yeah, lost to the community. Very. I mean, in terms of horror, like, you
know, who better the guy did men? Well, many of them to masterpieces. I would say Nyver
on Elm Street and I would say Scream is definitely a modern horror comedy masterpiece. I'm going
to give him four masterpieces. Keep going. Last house on the left. The original very
disturbing great film. Sure. Those have eyes. Those have eyes. Yes. Nightmare on
Elm Street scream. That's four. That's fair. And I think you know people were they were
serpent in the rainbow. I've never seen that. But I heard that Bill Pullman gets a scrotum
nailed to a chair. It's pretty intense movie. Yeah. Some people were tweeting us and you
know the tweets I think were probably pretty lighthearted and funny. But it was kind of
like hey guys why are you talking shit about West Craven. He just thought we didn't know
that he was going to die. And all we really did was praise Niver on Elm Street. There
We were talking shit about music at the heart is what we were doing I don't even were we yeah the Meryl Streep
But that's his one kind of stab
Pardon the pun at drama. I'm not going back and saying I like music at the heart now. I'm not either guy passed away
I'm terribly sad he died, but it doesn't mean I'm gonna like music at the heart now
No, and when I die I don't want somebody to be like
you know
I'm sorry. I talked shit about Pat shitting his pants at that little league game
and he should have talked shit about me shitting my pants at that little league. Yeah. And
also you know I love Sam Ray mistakes when Sam Ray me dies. I'm not going to I'm not
going to praise Oz the great and powerful. Oh no man what a piece of shit that was.
Sorry Sam Ray. Now where do you think they went wrong with that movie when they cast
James Franco as a wizard. Yeah just just terrible casting. I saw it in 3D which to me elevates
almost any movie and I just hated it so much was it who was the other one Mila Kunis was
Dorothy no Mila Kunis Dorothy's not in it Mila Kunis was the wicked witch of the West who
there was no Dorothy no because it's before Dorothy came oh yeah yeah yeah sort of like
a almost like wicked but but nowhere near as God my favorite Sam Raimi is a simple plan
I think it's one of the most underrated movies of all time well now my favorite Sam Raimi
is Evil Dead 2 with our question. Love it. We want to keep it in the genre for this podcast.
I don't have to. You can't tell me what to do. All right.
Guys, what we're going to do and we finally learned that we're just going to really quickly
gloss over this part of the podcast because it's so insanely boring. Bring up scream
on your Netflix instant or even a Blu -ray, DVD, whatever.
They should have done it already.
Yeah, or you should have done it already.
And basically, you're going to hit play
and then an immediate pause.
Yeah, so everybody in different load times.
Then we're going to go one, two, three, play,
and we all start washing it together.
It's just that easy.
It's that easy.
So if you've hit play and you're all paused up now,
here we go.
Here we go.
We've given everybody enough time.
Ample.
Yeah.
And also, they could have paused it
if they needed to by now.
All right.
Here we go.
Glad you're coming around.
one two three play now right here uh you should be seeing your Miramax screen
Miramax yeah exactly remember when Miramax would like make all the good
movies and now they just make movies where it's like give me an Oscar what
did they make now I haven't seen they made like the fucking artist you know
like they make movies that they get Oscar whipped into excitement about by
saying like hey like we got this great you know like holding these big expensive
of screenings and all this shit and then no one ever remembers them again.
They're movies that don't stand the test of time and they used to make only movies that
stood the test of time.
It's not the same company since the Weinsteins left.
Well, no.
Did they leave?
I think so.
Because yeah, because now they have Harvey Weinstein.
It's like Weinstein productions.
Oh, right.
Right.
Or whatever.
Yeah.
I mean they had women to beat.
Did he beat a woman?
I've heard tales.
Let's move past it.
I'm trying to work on this business.
We'll say allegedly.
Allegedly.
Oh, no, it's truly allegedly because all I do is hear shit. Okay. This is one of and I'm not I'm not just saying horror here
This is one of the greatest opening sequences in the history of film in my opinion
This is a brutal brutal sequence. That's what people forget. It's so fun
You forget how like really disturbing it is. Yeah when when when old ghostface killer
Which by the way, did they name that after the rapper did the rapper name himself after screen?
No, his name was Ghostface Killa well before this.
I don't think there was any tie -in probably, but I don't know that.
The rapper Ghostface got his name from like a Kung Fu thing, right?
Yeah, exactly.
Okay.
Drew Barrymore.
Terrific rapper.
Fish Scale, one of my favorite rap albums.
Terrific.
Yeah, Drew Barrymore in this opening scene here never looked better.
You know, she has truly never looked better.
This is an incredible, like, I guess there's a bra, but if there is, you're not really
seeing it.
I mean this was she was a gym just unbelievable. Who would have believed she was a crack addict
at six or whatever the hell she was doing. Who would have believed she was hitting the
pipe with E .T. in a pile of clothes in a closet somewhere straightened out. One of my favorite
things I ever saw Bill Murray do was at the SNL 25th anniversary special saw it when he
went up to her in the audience and he said, we're so glad you cleaned up. Yeah. I remember
that well. And she laughed, which shows that she's cool. Yeah, it's awesome. I think she
would have laughed at my crack bit. I think so too. Your E .T. your E .T. tag. I think so
too. I love her and she never quite gets the material she deserves. I think. But like,
you know, wedding singer or whatever, she's just a lovable person. She's a dream in wedding
singer. Yeah, she's great in wedding singer. I mean, I want her to be my wife. Sure.
Her name was Julia, Julia, which is still a very funny bit.
Julia, Julia?
Yeah.
I don't remember that.
No, she goes, her name is Julia, and she's going to be marrying this guy named like Ron
Julia.
And then Santa's like, so your name's going to be Julia, Julia?
It's real fun.
My friend Julia spells her name with a G, so it looks like you should say Julia,
but it's pronounced Julia.
Okay.
So maybe that's...
Let's get her on the podcast to discuss that.
maybe maybe when we do a podcast for the name for the weird names network we'll do that what
I love so I've been reading some feedback today is some of you are like talk about the movie
talk more about the movie and some of you are like it's it's funny hearing you guys
riff on shit whatever we're really trying to do a blend and maybe that's not going to
please everybody but it's pleasing us and hopefully the majority of the listeners we
want to podcast you can listen to in your car in the way to work we also want to
podcast if you're alone on a Friday with no date and no friends you can watch a movie
and and feel like you're watching a movie with some pals that's it I agree this is this
is this is the conversation that you'd have if you were watching with friends it's not
yeah we're not the fucking directors you want a real commentary put the fucking commentary
on your nerd by the way I you and I could do that we could talk about very specific
specific shots angles filters I went to fucking film school but you know what you can watch
the commentary on the blue right you went to film school yeah I went to because I mean
I was you know we had a small problem with the recorder before the podcast and Pat didn't
even know I said look at track four and tell me what's happening he's looking at the master
output track what I did was I went to one of the least prestigious film schools in
the country Webster University it is actually very good films but I learned everything
basically six minutes before it turned digital, so I learned how to like piece
two pieces of film together like I'm Thelma Schoenmarker. I learned all that too.
Scorsese's editor. I know how to do that too. Okay. I mean I still know how to
differentiate between track four and the master output. Right, what I do and
it's helped me immeasurably with my obsessive brain is to let go of things
I don't need anymore so when I started riding I focused all my energies on
writing and learning about the craft of writing and I let go the audio technical shit that
is handled and should be handled by technical professionals even if I want to be a director
I'd rather handle the actors and let some nerd handle the camera.
Truly that was your way of calling me a nerd.
Look I appreciate some nerd is fine now Barrymore.
She's been getting prank called by the the murderer.
Yeah.
And the prank girls got more and more intense and now he's telling everyone well he just
told everyone to see what her insights look like and she's crying. What do you think? Real
tears? You think these are movie tears? Probably movie tears. You think she can cry on cue?
She may be able to. She's had some darkness. She's great in this scene. Do you find the
voice hearing it now too much or just right or not enough? What voice? The like the
killer's voice. What do you mean am I hearing it just enough? I mean I'm saying do you
think it's a little over the top or a little under the top? I never liked the voice.
voice it's not great I never liked the killer's voice for two reasons it sounds smarmy to me
as opposed to like really menacing well also you know at the end of the movie when they
reveal who the killer is I won't give it away in case you haven't seen this film yet but
then he just speaks through that like dime store voice thing and it just makes his voice
like it's ridiculous right it's not even there's there's no technology to this day that
could do that. Yeah. You know you can change the pitch of your voice but you can't change
the complete like timbre of the voice. For sure. You can't change the Jeffrey timbre of
your voice. How'd you like that word. Timbre. I like that audio school.
I recently read a very heavily circulated interview with Quentin Tarantino who is of course one
of almost everybody's favorite writer directors. And I love hearing him talk about movies.
I remember I saw him on Charlie Rose
Decades ago and Charlie Rose like what are your favorite movies of the year and he goes number one. No question my best friend's wedding
And I was like out of here. What the hell is going on? He also once said that psycho too is better than psycho
I mean, it's just ridiculous shit, but you know what I love it
And I always love his like alternate opinions on shit
But he was talking about scream like and this interview came out two days before West Craven died
And he was talking about how shitty West Craven's direction of scream was and he's just wrong
Yeah, this is such a tense and effective
Sequence he's let alone the rest of the movie
But like this movie balances horror and comedy in a really pretty special way which is my point about the Quintin
I love Quintin Tarantino's work, but I think he just says things to be inflammatory in interviews
I don't believe I don't really think psycho 2 is better than psycho
I don't really believe he thought the Lone Ranger was one of the best films of 2013
I enjoyed the Lone Ranger. I didn't deserve to get bashed. I didn't say but it was not
one of the best films of 2013 as an absurd statement. I I disagree and I think he sees
things in a very different way and I think he he loves trash as much as high art and
I think that's just I always love reading his opinions on my best friend's wedding is
his favorite film of all time of that year but it was the work of Sam Fuller and come
Yeah, I just think he has he sees things different. That's all I can say. I I dig what he does
I love reading about his opinions because they're always so weird now
The the murderer here had Drew Barrymore's boyfriend taped to a chair outside, right or if it looked like Frank Whaley
I guess it's not Frank Whaley. It might have been Frank Whaley
You know he turns up in some small parts sometimes sure
I can't believe this kid was still wearing a letterman jacket.
We came out in 1997.
It did.
Ninety six.
My kid was really sticking with it.
Now I'll tell you mine.
And then you tell me yours.
I remember exactly when I first saw this movie.
I had a first date with a young I won't say her name but a young woman who became my
girlfriend and we saw Scramman came in after this sequence. After this she didn't see the
chair get to the window or she was holding she was like I'm not ready I'm not ready I'm
not ready. I wanted to see it so bad and I come in basically at the very end of this.
This is what everybody talked about before I saw it everybody I knew that saw it and
in the write ups and everything were the opening sequence the opening sequence. Yeah that's
I was infuriated that I missed it and then also that it's Drew Barrymore, you know who was who was
Past her comeback trail at this point. She was reestablished as a celebrity at this point
Yeah, and she's just in this opening 15 minutes, whatever it is and then gets sliced to pieces
Yeah, I mean it's a nod to psycho where you kill off your star right off the bat bond
This movie was written by Kevin Williamson who would go on to create Dawson's Creek unless he did it before
I don't think he did
Which as a show I also fucking loved and could not get enough of and I love that the lead was
obsessed with movies Dawson Leary wanted to be a director you know I related to that in
high school I'd watch it every week if Quentin Tarantino is here he'd go best Kevin Williams
and things the faculty of the faculty really sucked in well that that's what the Tarantino
would say was the best you might be right I never noticed this before that she lived
or she's I can't remember she lives in this house or she's just house sitting or whatever
I gotta say it doesn't look like they should be living next to that. Yeah, I didn't notice they lived in front of this corn field
What the hell do you think's gonna happen? And you know I watched
Parenthood the other day, which I think is such a fucking great movie and we talked about it when we discussed Hannah and her sisters
But I think it's so great and at some point because it was it was set in st. Louis
You realize their backyard is like up against a river and and I never noticed that when I was a kid and that makes no sense either
You got to look at your surroundings.
Isn't there a St. Louis River?
Well, the Mississippi is disgusting,
but I don't feel like people are going
to live alongside of it, but maybe I'm wrong.
Now, here's where Barrymore eats it.
I mean, that shot alone, the first stab is pretty brutally.
Comes around the back.
You see the knife go in.
And then he gets on top of her and just starts
stabbing her to death.
He first chokes her.
Well, the shot of her coming up
where she's hanging with her inside
has fallen out is real rough.
yeah I mean but this the stabbing in here is so it's so violent it's so it actually
here's what's disturbing about it it's it I would imagine it's like if you really
had to stab somebody to death that's how you'd have to do it yeah it wouldn't be
like an easy thing to do I mean there's well let's find out you want to stab me
real quick and see I thought you'd never ask since the day we met uh -huh now
Now here's the problem.
If you get stabbed to death, they're going to think I did it, right?
You know, not tonight, 10 years down the line, whatever, you know?
Here's the thing.
Back to the voice of the killer.
The device that the killer pulls out at the end that he shows is his voice distortion
device.
Yeah.
If he actually used the real voice that that thing gives you, it's 20 times scarier.
It's like this gargly swamp monster voice.
It's really freaky and you know in a movie like this
They must have gone over that forever and ever getting the voice just right, but they didn't get it just right
You know he sounds almost like a douche
He's like hey
Has it it's just not menacing it sounds very douchey to me
It's a it's almost like a movie phone kind of voices. Yeah. Yeah, you know
But I mean look I guess it works because everybody really liked it through the whole series that you know, right?
It's stuck me and my friends in high school were obsessed with calling movie phone
During the period of time where the Schwarzenegger vehicle end of days came out right because sometimes they'd have the actors record a little here
We go. Oh
Boy is this where Drew's got her guts hanging out. Yeah, because the mom just screams. Oh, yeah, look at that. They're all down her leg
Just hanging from her opening
That's how the movie opens see I think they should have saved the title card for after she's hanging in the tree
I agree 20 million percent with you that that scream should have just bammed into the screen right now, right?
Okay, so they used to have stars sometimes record their own movie phone promos and they had Schwarzenegger do one and it was
If I had a recording of it now, I would still listen to it five times a day. It was so funny
Excuse my subpar impression of Schwarzenegger, but here's what it was. He would go on November 24th
Get ready
Prepare for the end of days and my friends listen to this thing and laugh endlessly.
It was so ridiculous and you pictured him in a recording booth with the headset screaming
prepare for the end of days one of the least scary movies ever made and we really had
a good time.
Now was he trying to be scary or do you think he was having a laugh.
No I don't think he was having a laugh because I think Schwarzenegger is kind of in on the
The joke like now that's a good point after it was covered by the way and today's sucks
I never that was the beginning of the end. Yeah, that was I remember it was ended days
And then like a racer a racer really suck your luggage and
Shoot the crocodile. Yeah, and then you know what is kind of an entertaining movie is the one with
This collateral damage. Oh, no, what's the one where it's got like a science element?
man. The sixth man. Okay. With the Sen pal. Waiters. The six man basketball movie where
Marlon Wayne is like a ghost. I think it is. I'm I'm thinking I'm thinking about the one
with Bobby DeVall and it's got a science fiction element and it squirts in a year.
I feel like it's called the something man though. The six shit. Again. You know nerds
are screaming. It's this. Oh wait. I can look it up. I forgot. We're not making fun
of you were all men. I like this. I like the choices here for what's this girl's name again
because she's Neve Campbell. Neve Campbell. I was called her Liv Tyler. Neve Campbell
in this 57 year old woman trailer park robe. They got her in. I love this. Yeah. And then
the big poster on her wall is Indigo girls. Well yeah exactly. Because you know how all
the high school kids well you know going for Indigo girls. One of the most attractive
of girls I ever know I ever knew took me to an indigo cut girls concert so I don't
think that's mutually exclusive. Nev Campbell for my money is about as
beautiful as you can do. Yeah she's she's a dream and she still looks pretty much
the same and you know you you couldn't call her like a an amazing actress but
she's very competent like you never are like that scene sucked. She's very
Charming actually I she really gained I always respected her but she really gained my acting
respect when I saw her in good shot here that movie where she got naked that James to back
to that movie yeah and she played like a real shitty fucking yeah I was really rotten in
that night I liked her quite a bit because I believed her as a shitty person yeah and
I love that you know like well anytime anybody takes a chance on Neve Campbell she brings
it. The sixth day. Six day. There you go. And six man is Marlon
Wayne's ghost basketball player. Yes. And the sixth sense is we're Marlon
Wayne's is a ghost that Hayley Joe Osman can see. Yeah. Exactly. Yeah. Okay. We got it.
We figured it out. And Drake is running through the six with
his woes. Yes. I also didn't know this. Just while I'm on
this page. Arnold Schwarzenegger was also apparently in around the world in 80 days.
I think like a thousand people had cameos. I never saw that. He's in the Jackie
Chan version right his character's name is Prince happy. Oh my God. And then that was
it then it was governor for six years and then boom expendables he's back in action.
Sure. What I love now is in LA I have a picture of it that I saved. There's a billboard and
it has like 80 people on it and it's the cast of the expendables three. There's so many
I'm like am I in the expendables three. I was looking for my own face. The I like
I never realized this until as we watch it now we had we you know skeet olrich was just
in that scene playing Neff Campbell's boyfriend never to be seen after you know 2000 who the
hell knows where he is but you know everybody used to make the joke that he was Johnny Depp's
carbon copy yeah we talked about it on the nightmare podcast and there you go West Craven breaking
in depth and olrich yeah I mean this this movie has some pretty clear nods tonight
on Elm Street. Yeah well Nancy wore a similar robe or gown that the one that
Nef Campbell was wearing. Nef Campbell has a bit of a Nancy quality very naturally
pretty. She's just beautiful. Skeet Ulrich I remember was in a movie this I think is
what killed his career it's called Chill Factor and it was him and Cuba Gooding
Jr. driving around a ice cream truck that was rigged to explode. That's an
actual movie that got a theatrical release. I saw it and it wasn't. Nobody said this is
just speed. Oh, it was clearly a speed rip off. It was just such a terrible, terrible
movie. Cuba getting junior. That guy wins an Oscar. Then for the next 10 years, it was
like boat trip, chill factor, snow dogs. Who's ever had a worse agent than Cuba getting
junior? Well, I mean, who knows if it was the Asian or maybe it was him just saying,
and I'll do it, I'll do it, I'll do it.
Yeah, they might've been like,
we'll give him $5 million.
That's the thing.
One of the best interviews they ever saw
was Samuel L. Jackson on Letterman.
And he goes, you know, you're in every movie, Sam.
You're in every single movie that comes out.
It's great.
Why do you take every job that comes down the pipe?
Right.
And he goes, well, Dave, let me ask you this.
Somebody offers you $5 million
to spend six weeks in Hawaii, would you take it?
And I was like, Sam, I respect it.
I do.
too. Well that's what ice tea said when he came and spoke at my school. Yeah Henry Winks
I love Henry Winkler I've heard one of the nicest men there is and in all of Hollywood
I've heard that too I forgot he was in this movie tool right now yeah and it just made
me very happy. The ice tea came and spoke at my college and he said he said I have
I made four movies this year. They'll be coming out at a liquor store near you. Yeah that's
good and then everybody laughed and he goes look I know I don't make the greatest movies
but let me he's like I'll tell you something when you lived in the ghetto and you'd had
nothing sure and somebody comes along and says we'll give you a couple of million dollars
to make a fucking movie he goes you didn't be pretty fucking ignorant to say no to that
and I was like alright I get it that's some fucking true ass shit and then you get some
money and then you can you know do your more artistic kind of stuff but I do whatever
you want I completely agree do whatever you want percent you know how all they're
the high school kids sitting around a fountain you know every high school just
had a fountain outside of it yeah my school had like a pit I think my school
when it was up against this place called bush wildlife which was a wildlife
reserve where kids would go finger each other and I remember we were terrified
much like in scream for about a six month period because a child molester slash
murderer named Michael Jackson was on the prowl and at the time everyone was like oh my god
can you believe his name is Michael Jackson because no one associated Michael Jackson with
pedophilia at all. It was just like can you imagine how embarrassed Michael Jackson would
be if someone made the suggestion that he was a pedophile. That's how young I was found
out it was actually Michael Jackson. Yeah. It was him. He was in the woods a boom.
Now Matthew Lillard is recently making kind of an indie comeback because I see him in indie
trailers a lot. So I'm glad to see he's still working even though I yes and I like Matthew
Lillard. I find him very funny. I thought he was really funny in the Scooby Doo movies.
I didn't see Jamie Kennedy. I'm not complaining that I don't see him everywhere anymore.
No it's fine. I don't do you see any more break dance comedies. No. Jamie Kennedy.
I Malibu's most wanted. Is that what you're talking about. I think so. Yeah. One of those
things he did you know Rose McGowan's a stone fox today I truly miss I truly miss Rose McGowan
where she been I mean I say this without due respect maybe the greatest rack I've ever
seen in my life I don't know that she's the kind of gal I don't know if you could really
handle almost and as she gets older she gets better looking and it's almost frightening
she dated she dated Marilyn Manson I mean she's yeah she's she's she's she's along
for a nice she's in for a ride if you're ready to take it if you're ready to take it
jawbreaker remember that movie yeah I mean she was kind of a shitty heathers but she
was great and the hottest I've ever seen her is in that wrestling movie with ready to rumble
baby which has one of the funniest lines I've ever heard in a movie ever wow you're
blowing my mind now now you sound like one Tarantino but go on it's when they find
and all the replat in the sewer. And I don't remember the the like construction guy that
finds him has a really high pitch voice. He's also in the movie Fatso which is one of my
favorite films of all time. Okay. And he goes David Arquette goes where did you find him
and he and the construction guy goes we found him in drain twenty eight. He didn't want
to leave. It's hilarious. And then it's not enough to make me watch ready to rumble
again but it sounds like a fun whenever I see it on I'll fast forward to that part and watch
it and then I also always watch the part with what's his name the the distinguished actor
that was in the crimes and misdemeanors Martin Landau Martin Landau that scene is terrific
also in baps black American princesses starring Halle Berry that's how big a career swing
that guy's had but he's really funny in that scene where he's the wrestling trainer yeah
And they think they killed him and they go they get real close to him and then he goes
And he like comes awake like a snake. Yeah, that's always funny. I love they do that in the throw mama from the train
Yeah, I remember that dead
There's a lot of moves. I used to wonder like how did this movie that is like an f -minus
Get like five jokes that are a pluses and then you realize it's something
I actually do fairly often as you go to movie punch -ups and they get
You know I'm not trying to do my own horn, but they get really funny riders to come in for one day
And they pay you pretty well, and you add like 15 20 jokes to a movie script, and they take them or leave them
And I've been in them can you get me in on one of the I've been trying to I mean I've been trying
I do that. I think I'd be good at that. I do them. I'm not allowed to say, you know which movies and stuff
I do them whenever I have free time and my name and one of those I absolutely will I've been in them with the
Great Patton Oswald. Yeah, you know they get kind of big people and
And you're just, you're looking at a script and you're like, well, this is the worst script
I've ever read.
Sometimes they're funny, but a lot of times they're not.
And you go in, you throw in these great jokes and that's how movies get amazing jokes sprinkled
in with the ship.
Well, I guess that happened with Reed Rumble.
I can almost guarantee it did.
Odd choice for Oliver Platt.
Yeah.
Yeah well I mean the 90s was a big time for like movies that looked bad and would be
really funny like I remember Sugar and Spice this cheerleading movie my buddy and I were
like you know bring it on was funny we'll see Sugar and Spice wasn't the one where they
like robbed the bank or something yeah and I was just like holy shit like there's amazing
jokes on this I think Josie and the Pussycats is one of the most subversive funny movies
ever made and it was so nasty to its target audience. That's great. You almost couldn't
believe it. It was shocking. I felt that way about both Brady Bunch movies. Oh boy. That's
a perfect example Joe. I thought they were. I thought they were phenomenal. They're really
funny and like dark. The fur I already mentioned it. I like the first Scooby Doo movie quite
a bit. You know what. It was very funny. I know James Gunn Roder who's a guy I'm
a fan of and who's now a huge director because of Guardians of the Galaxy. Sure. And I'm
going to rent it and watch it because I've never seen it.
It's very funny.
Great.
And there's actually pot humor in it which is weird.
Well I thought the cartoon always had an element of that.
My friend made a good point.
We saw him in the theater and he turned to me and he goes what do you do.
They make a joke like you know shaggy's like he meets a girly loves or something and
she's like hi my name's Mary Jane and the whole theater erupts in the laughter.
Then my friend turns to me and he goes what do you do when your six year old
says why is that funny.
me. Yeah. I was like, I don't know man. I made me respect that they put it in there though.
I always wonder that. I work with a woman who has like an eight year old son and he's always
asking her questions and you know, what does that mean? What is this? And my parents never
used to tell me, which makes it all the more alluring. There's this joke in the naked
gun where there's a really tall guy. Yeah. And he goes, you got something in the
corner of your mouth. Yeah, class and a half of banana falls out. Right. And to
this day I don't necessarily get it but I asked my mom like why is that funny and she
was so weirdly tight -lipped about it that I assumed it was some filthy dick joke but
all it is is that the guy's so tall that when he's got something on the side of his
mouth it's half a banana. I guess. How do you still not get that? That's what the
joke is. I just think it's kind of like not worth the squeeze I guess. It's a hilarious
joke. He goes you have something on the side of your mouth and then he goes no the
other side. Yeah. And then the clump of banana. No, it's a decent joke. And I think the naked
gun is about as funny as it gets. But I was always so baffled by it and my mom's refusal
to answer me made me think it was some really disgusting dick joke that it's not.
You know what joke I never got in that movie. Go on. When she's up on the ladder and he
goes nice ankle bracelet and she goes slip down there right down there again. I never
understood what that meant. That used to make me laugh because you just picture the
bracelet making that journey from her ankle or from her wrist to her ankle. But they are
really weird jokes that I think probably could have benefited from, you know, give me an insert
shot of her slipping it back to the wrist. Okay. I mean, they can't all be, you know,
as as classic as nice beaver. Thank you. I just had it stuffed, which is real good.
Well, now, even when I was a kid, I was like, I get that one. To me, the I mean, one
One of the funniest sequences in movie history is a naked gun two and a half, which I might
even prefer to the first or original.
They're real close.
Uh, who lays a much better villain, but I mean, the, the, the, from start to finish
that sequence where he's in the bar drinking because he's all busted up over.
Oh, that's great.
I mean, it's just joke after joke.
I haven't had this much sex since I was a boy scout leader.
I mean, at the time I was dating a lot.
My aunt took me to see two movies
I was not allowed to see because they were PG -13
Make a gun two and a half and problem child to back -to -back both hilarious
I never saw any of the problem child problem. Shall one is great mostly because of Ritter and
Michael Richards and
Jack Warden and problem child two is great because it's like really gross and
Goes to like really fucked up place the guy who wrote the guys who wrote Ed Wood
good man on the moon people versus Larry Flint they wrote the two problem child movies when
I was in at the Montreal just for last comedy festival I was one of the roasters for Gilbert
Godfrey roast they did yeah and my whole closing thing was building up Gilbert like
what an artist he was right and then you know my example was let me tell you what an RCS
is. Not only was he in problem child one and two. He was the only cast member to return
problem child three and four. That's true. Not even the kid eventually said no enough.
You know what this man I got other commitments. Yeah. Yeah. Michael Oliver and then he went
on to be in the problem child TV series. Yeah. Yeah. They were at least as recently as
six months ago still trying to reboot problem child but I guess the pilot didn't go. I don't
know. What are you going to do. By the way back to the movie. Yeah. We're way off track
at this point. We always do. Neve Campbell Sidney as she's called. There's there's the
ghost face killers in her house now trying to kill her. And she just what is the did
we really miss something. I forgot that she had like some kind of phone thing on her
computer yeah a death caller right exact what's weird to me is I recently went to
my buddy Ian's bachelor party and I think he was so adamant about not you know
like banging a hooker or something which is great but he was so adamant about
being good that we wound up playing it a little too safe and we spent the
Saturday night as bachelor party watching scream to in the in the hotel
cell room suite. But we all had a great time. We kind of provided
our own commentary fourth then scream one looks so much more
modern than scream two which was one of the most dated looking
movies I've ever seen. Really. It was so it was 90s to the
point where like you were embarrassed for what you used to
wear back in those days. And this looks reasonably modern to
me. Yeah. No it's. Well that's like the Nightmare in
Elm Street series to the first one more or less you
know, you can tell it's an older film, but nothing is too out of whack. Yeah. You get
into two and three. I mean, it starts to look real. Yeah. Our cat. I just got an email
about David or from David Arquette or about from David Arquette saying, give me work.
No, it's a an email. And, you know, I never know how I get these things. I guess probably
from seeing a concert or something. But it was like two weeks only at the like the Burbank
Playhouse. David Arquette is Sherlock Holmes. Oh boy. And I thought who's going to see it.
What is it a one man show. It felt there was no other cast members. I feel like it might
be like the Holmes monologues starring David Arquette as Sherlock Holmes. Hey folks I'd
I'd rather see the vagina monologues and you know how I feel about that.
Sure.
I mean for me the issue is all about appropriate miking.
You know a lot of times the vagina gets up on stage and it's not projecting the way you
want it.
How has nobody done that as a sketch yet where they go to see the vagina monologues and it's
just women queefing into microphones.
How has that not been maybe they have but it has.
I'm telling you it hasn't.
All right.
Well let's do it.
Oh my god. Let's get run out of town. All right. Nobody gets to do it. Courtney Cox
still in this highlighter neon yellow. This this is the one true 90s thing. I mean that's
just an absurd dress she's wearing. But I think it's also because she is like this
sensationalist reporter. I think it's yeah. Scream had a lot to say. You know and I
will say it's an oddly prescient movie with this character and her obsession with
not the news but like the sensationalism of it. It's a little ahead of its time.
Well it's great to see movies that are entertaining in one fashion and then beneath the surface
there's this whole other thing. You know what I mean. It's the Anchorman to brilliant commentary
on on the news on modern day news. Yeah. But it's just all wrapped up in this big Will
Farrell Joe. I will say you know Anchorman to is one of
the most curiously stepped on neglected underrated movies that there is it's not the first
one but the fact that it was just kind of brushed aside so easily is very baffling to me because
I thought it was really great. I don't understand why they released the theater version that
they did. All that was weird. The alternate version on Netflix was was the movie you wanted
and it was 10 times better and I'm like why wasn't this the theatrical version. I own
them both and I couldn't tell you why I don't I don't know. It doesn't make sense. Here's
You know you got the kids in the police station. Yeah, you got the sheriff that's on to you know
What what the hell's going on around here, right? I don't want you hanging around with your boyfriend
This kid might be bad news. What did he do?
This is like when rod gets accused in the first one
Oh Rick and nightmare no, sir. Excuse me. What's up? I don't remember thinking this at the time
But I just watched Ulrich deliver that line and it was bad
Was it it looked like when you see on on audition tape on a DVD. It was terrible
Look at this face. I'm gonna look at that face. How do you say no to that face? Is this guy supposed to be his dad?
I'm look at this guy. They were supposed to believe this my birth
It looks like that guy played base in like the outfield or the psychedelic furs or like some some 80s
Kind of off the beaten path band. I mean there is a strange similarity between him and this guy would be Danny McBride today
playing this role
Is that uh?
What is that the guy who like play he played meatloaf in the TV movie and so I haven't we're not getting a good look at his face
The cameraman they made a TV movie about meatloaf. Yeah. Yeah, they did. What was it called?
Let me guess bad out of hell. Yeah, it's pretty meatloaf. I think it was that it was a vh1 kind of deal
What is the story who gives a shit? Hey, here's my review. I would do anything for love, but I won't watch that
here's my review. Yeah. I'd rather watch a piece of actual meat
loaf. There you go. Okay. That's my bit. Good. Look we both strong bits. What are we listening
to right. My phone over there is buzzing. That's your that's your phone ring. Yes but
it's buzzing. It's a vibration. Oh my God. That's a vibe. They can't hear it. We're
there. All right. I hear it very strongly. Yeah but you're not. It's not in front
of a unidirectional Mike. Beth I thought your school pacemaker had exploded or something.
No it's it's really intense. It's it's so I can feel it in my pocket so I need a lot
of buzzes. I can't feel it in my pocket. This is where Arquette and Cox met. Am I correct.
Yes. And they are still together. They recently divorced. Oh no they're long divorced.
That you never heard all those things on stern where he said she was having like an emotional
no affair and no I didn't and all that stuff how's Cox looking these days I'm
sure well I feel like a little bit of a pig saying it like that I didn't mean it
like that no I hate to be an asshole but I mean Cox was always to me the most
attractive of the friends even over in Aniston and she went a little far with
the plastic surgery I don't think I'm talking out of school to say that but she
went a little far with it and living in this God forsaken town I don't know
How women do it really but she went a little far with it and it's been was always my top
I think she's most people's top and you know, I don't love the Coudreau always gets left out in this in the
Trash because she's a I think she's a brilliant comedic actress and the comeback is fantastic
Michelle's fantastic, and she's a good -looking woman
You know everybody's got it look
I'm sure most people want to bang Leblanc over everybody else, but that doesn't mean that shimmer isn't a good -looking cat
I
I mean my I I would hope people's favorite is is Perry who's clearly the funniest but
maybe girls think otherwise I don't know I you know I like a Perry my favorite you watch
those shows Chandler is the funniest by a billion percent he is they just kind of ruined
him toward the end he started to get to a quippy yeah yeah what are the rest of the cast of
Annie say after you said that you know what I mean it was right right here it was too
much. Cox holding it together body is looking terrific. Oh unquestionably. There's just
you know the face is a little wild. She's had some surgery done and then you wonder
like I mean I talked about I think I'm on here before but like I never knew that any
woman did anything to her face unless she looked like Joan Rivers and now I learned
that everyone does something but I also see how you go too far with it and you get
carried away because as you start to age, you know, it's crazy.
You look at yourself in the mirror and I'm 34 and you're like, man, I see it happening.
Like it's a day to day thing.
Pat, I'll tell you, I have days where I look in the mirror and I said, I say, when did
my father move in?
To my face.
Yeah.
It's tough.
I can't tell you, Pat.
But it happens to us all.
What are you going to do?
I mean I eat chocolate and it's on my hips the next day.
That's a great big daddy joke if I may what's that is a movie big daddy or is that what you
call your father I call him big daddy like in a Tennessee Williams play now it's in
the movie big daddy Adam Sandler goes I tell you I used to eat anything I wanted and
I had so much fun he goes I tell you these days I I drink half a milkshake my ass jiggles
for a week and I laughed because I was 16 and I thought ah that'll never happen to me but
it happens.
No it happens.
There's Leia Schreiber.
Oh boy does it happen.
Wait Leap.
Leap Schreiber?
Oh yeah that he is in this.
He's in two.
I think he's the killer in two actually if you don't mind me saying.
Who is he in this one?
I haven't seen this one I don't think since I was in college.
He's the guy who killed her mom.
He killed her mom.
Because they really do that they make it into a trilogy where like all these movies
interconnect.
Okay.
Four I didn't love I think two is a great sequel. I really do and Parker Posey's great in it
And I think three is okay. Who's the killer in four?
No recollection
No recollection. Who's the killer in three? I?
Don't remember. I think in two. It's Lee. I think it's is it two people in this one. Oh
Yeah, it's Lillard and
Well, there goes for the listener stop in two. It's Shriver. I believe it's Skeet all rich in and Lillard
it but live her alone. I mean I never noticed how much they try to
make you or I don't want to say I never noticed but I probably I don't remember that they made
there's Linda Blair from the exorcist. Yes that's very cool. Yeah. Oh boy they made
a they they really push you are I think it's all rich the whole time and then kind of
pull you away from it. It's two people. Yeah. But they I think before it ends you
were like oh it wasn't him. Yeah I think they do a good they do a good dance with
that whole thing. Here's some movie insights about the screen film, the first screen film.
Controversies. I'm reading this off of Wikipedia if you don't mind. Wasn't there some actual
murders with the ghost faces? So in the years following the release of screen the film had
been accused of inspiring copycat crimes and inducing violent acts. In January 98, 16
year old Mario Padilla and his 14 year old cousin Samuel Ramirez stabbed Mario's mother
other Gina Castillo 45 times killing her case became known as the screen murder because
it fell in under intense media scrutiny after the boys claimed they were inspired by parts
one and two of the film series.
Pear confessed to needing the money acquired from Gina Gina's murder to fund a killing
spree purchase to ghostface costumes and a voice changer used to cat used by the
characters in the film where he talked to the wishing right.
So these kids, uh, yeah, they dressed up as a ghost base and, uh, or at least planned
on keep, to keep going.
They started with them.
That's, that's disturbing.
Uh, during the trial, a psychologist said there were a whole bunch of reasons why they acted
out that way, but did the movie provide a blueprint?
Absolutely.
That's ridiculous.
It's like saying, yeah, you're going to kill somebody, you're going to kill somebody.
I remember we saw the boy who could fly when I was a kid.
Oh God.
I just love that movie.
One of my friends went up on the roof and he was going to try to do it.
Yeah.
He was going to try to fly.
And he didn't.
We talked him down.
We were like you can't fly dude.
Like you're going to hurt yourself.
Was he mentally ill?
He wasn't mentally ill.
He was he was a little slower than us but like you know he was a normal kid but he
thought he could fly and he went up and he was going to try it.
the funny part I mean now it's funny because everything ended up okay his little brother
who did not like him was was encouraging him to try to fly right but it all worked out we
talked him down my my dear friend Fred Savage was in that movie as a very young boy speaking
to your friend Fred Savage yeah I watched by the way it was a name drop from Pat everybody
buddy. Look I'm not above it. I watched his new movie the
Driller the finisher or TV show with him. You saw the new pilot.
I saw it on the airplane. They put the pilot on the airplane.
I saw it on an airplane. It was hilarious. Oh good. I can't wait
to see it. Was laugh out loud funny in it. Great.
Can't wait to see it. I'm not just saying that. All right.
I it's really funny. I can't wait. And it was it was it
was relieving to see something like this I was like because that and I watched grandfathered
which I didn't like as much friends on both of these shows I will I will not say anything
it was still funny though I am looking forward to seeing them I got hope seeing both of them
I was like it's good to see network it's particularly Fred Savage when I was like it's good to
see network TV doing stuff that's a little off the mark sure you know sure but the
savage one man he and Rob Lowe both were great in it the girl from it's always Sonny's
on it Charlie Elizabeth Ellis yeah she's great on it yeah it was funny she's I've developed
quite a TV crush on that girl she's great she's really nice and funny a little more scream
controversy over here Jesus Christ listen to this one January 17 1999 13 year old Ashley
Murray was stabbed multiple times in the head and back before being left for dead comedy
podcast by his then friend Daniel Gill who was 14 Robert and another guy Robert four
who was 15 yeah this is kind of a downer huh I don't know that that qualifies as a fun fact
I started I didn't mean it as a fun fact I started reading it because I thought it was
going to say the 13 year old killed people and then it yeah and then I didn't read enough
ahead so I actually started reading loud and then it said that the 13 year old got murdered
right. So sorry about that guys. I mean I don't buy that shit you want you got you want to
kill somebody you're going to kill somebody in movies they might change the style or something
but if you're going to kill somebody you're a nut you're going to do it. I agree. Bravo's
hundred scariest movie moments opening scene to scream number 13. Yeah that feels around
right. If I was hundred greatest movie quotes do you like scary movies. What is the shirt
Hair that Campbell sporting now like why do they ever looking so mommish? I
Missed her because I was reading this this stupid
Would you watch the movie? I'm trying to read trivia for the fans and this internet age
Henry Winkler
Now is reprimanding kids that are wearing ghost -faced masks at the school because they think it's as a prank and now Henry I
Remember seeing the trailer, which I'm sure is on YouTube for the third season of the Sopranos
which in my opinion, is the best TV season of all time.
I know you don't love Sopranos as much as I do, but in the midst of all this like amazing
shit and like all these these crazy action sequences and everybody yelling and going
crazy, there was two people in the scream mask running out of a college.
And I remember this was like six months before the Sopranos premier and I was like,
like what the fuck is going on with these screen masks in the soprano preview and eventually
it's just two teenagers robbing a jewel concert at a college but and it's kind of a funny scene
but I was just like man how do the screen masks factor into the sopranos I thought they had
some weird like new horror element or something but the the impact of it was pretty far reaching
and this was a huge movie I remember yeah it was I was in high school at the time
It was like this in American pie or everything well other you know some other information
I'm seeing here on the Wikipedia page and I do remember that this was the case the harm movie
Industry was sort of or the genre itself was sort of slumping
Scream kind of put it back in yeah, you know respectful territory again
We're spending immediately it started being terrible because I remember this was the age of like phantoms with Ben Affleck
You know a lot of people say phantoms is really good. I've never seen it, but it's not there were some good like mimic
Guillermo del Toro did a movie with Mira Sovina and Doug called Mimic and there was some good
hormones.
As we mentioned.
Faculty really sucked.
I never saw the faculty.
I had no interest.
That girl, you know, she's the, you know, they have to have this scene in every horror
movie when, you know, the victim protagonist is in a stall at the high school in the
bathroom and then there's a bitchy girl that's like, she's a crazy bitch.
Can we all agree there's no worse soap dispenser than those pink ones that look like seashells
that you push like you don't it always takes me several minutes to get the soap out and
figure out how to use them.
They do have Neve Campbell in a terrible get up.
It's bad and that hair like a feathered bangs kind of situation.
I don't mind the bangs.
Let's talk about this shirt she's wearing.
The shirts particularly bad and I get what they're doing you know McGowan is always
wearing like a bra and they keep her in kind of more tame shit but they tame is one thing
but you know to make her look like she sells pies she made at home for a living yeah leaving
a pie on the windowsill to cool teaching Mrs. Tangle that's one of the other wow do I remember
teaching Mrs. Tangle I saw that in the data as well it was not good that was sort of
like a high school version of swimming with sharks right like a mean teacher who was I
want to say Helen Mirren yep okay and then the kids like to kidnapper and torture or
something yeah yeah so it's like swimming with sharks except without Kevin Spacey not
as good and Frank Whaley and Frank Whaley once again it's weird how these things happen
people keep coming up in these podcasts now here's my question I had heard that they were
making a screen TV series. Yeah. It's on. I haven't seen it but it's on it's already
but I didn't know that. I think the whole first season has aired and I just it has. I've never
watched a scripted show on MTV. Not not out of any sort of bias but I just always feel
like they're for people much younger than me. Maybe it was good. They're going to
keep going with it to even though West Craven has passed. Well he had nothing to do with
that show. I don't think except Cash and Jack. I think he was a producer on it. Was
You know it probably probably you've never seen the show
I've never seen one episode of it never saw scram never saw Teen Wolf never saw any of us
I refuse to watch Teen Wolf
I refuse to watch a show that it's that takes a movie that
Help mold my childhood and it's turned it into like this like I like a real horror thing
I love real horror, but you don't do that with Teen Wolf
All the funds gone. I mean I can't believe you felt that passionately about Teen Wolf
who didn't love Teen Wolf did you love Teen Wolf to T .O .O. unwatchable it is unwatchable
who knew the stars of both Teen Wolfs would go on to become big stars who knew who knew
Jay Bateman I mean you watch Teen Wolf to I would have my money was on Bateman bottoming
out sure guys were the biggest names in Hollywood right now Bateman you know of course I always
watched him on the Hogan family and all these shows when I was a kid but like I mean a
rest development that was a big shock is just like man this guy has like the best straight
man comedic timing in the fucking game yeah he's fantastic and that that really does come
from working that multi cam sitcom circuit like if you if you can do that shit you
know how to land a fucking joke you have to know how to land a job he's in my opinion
the funniest I've ever seen that guy is in that movie that Mike judge movie extract
extract extract was a pretty big let down for me but I think he was pretty solid in it yes
it's he's done the funniest thing he did the funniest things that move I've ever seen
the guy do when he's on the phone and he starts pounding it on the desk because he's
so angry yeah it's so he's just and then the stuff between him and Ben Affleck is
really funny in it too I agree I agree yes scream TV show right out of the loop here ten
episodes I didn't even know well yeah I mean I'm sure you can download the season
or whatever I decided I never teat there's so much TV and so much good TV
that somebody needs to tell me something's good at least ten times
before I watch an episode or unless it's someone I love and trust who's like
you got to see this is the best thing ever I want to look up with ghost face
looks like on the TV show because he does look different it's a different mass
which I don't get you have one of the most recognizable things in horror
history at your disposal. Why not use them? It's scarier looking. Lillard state in McGowan
in this. Yeah, they established that like right at the beginning. Christ. What? You don't
believe it? I guess not. You don't believe Lillard and McGowan? I believe it. All right.
Now they got Winkler put in the mask on. This is the same where you're supposed to think
it's Winkler. Yeah. Is it Winkler? A big story that always gets told in comedy writers
rooms is that on the set of happy days he was playing the fauncey of course and
the faunce not the fauncey they wrote the fauncey or the faunce they wrote into the
script this week they had like him saying correct a moondo at some point and
they said he came to the writers room and he goes guys you keep writing correct
a moondo and all this he's like you don't have to do that I know where the
a moon does go like it was just like a brief period early in his career where he took himself
a little too seriously but that's a really funny story.
Well and I swear to you oh boy the guy in the janitor in the freddy sweater who looked
like it might have been West Craven but I guess maybe we can't rewind it because we got to
stay keep doing this stupid podcast for you people.
I swear to God that story is so absurd that if you said to me who said this Henry Wrinkler or the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
I wouldn't know yeah, I wouldn't I literally boy
There's yeah, I'll tell you what and I've said this many times in my life
There are some great fucking jokes in turtles one two I
To this day love turtles one. I hate turtles too. I think I prefer secret of the use
is. That's insane. That's an insane sentence. Here's why.
Why? It has well I'm not going to say the vanilla ice came
in but it's got a scene where they're going through and
Raphael is tied up and they're trying to rescue him and they
go man it's it's dark up here. They go yeah a little too
dark. They go oh my god it's so quiet in here. Elena's like
Yeah, a little too quiet and they go. Oh my god. It's wrath
and Leonardo goes. Yeah, a little too wrath
What when I was a kid I laughed for five minutes. I don't even get it
Well, a little too. They're for the swing you and me. How does that mean?
It's a very funny joke and the Ninja Turtles to get what is to wrap
Raphael
It's quiet in here. Yeah a little too quiet. Hey, there's Raphael a little too. Raphael
yeah what I don't get it well we disagree you maybe because it doesn't make sense that
he says a little too rough yeah look I'm a kid when I see it look God bless I don't know
I laughed and my mom left I didn't even thank you mom for taking me to both turtles one and
turtles two secret I saw turtles one with my oldest friend in the world Scott who
you've met many times opening night yeah I saw both opening night with his mom my folks
two of us we went opening night it was a big deal and I wanted pizza afterwards part two
came out I was like don't even bother even as a kid you were as a kid I was gonna suck
and it did it sucked this kid directed it's terrible this kid on the playground rap song
Look that partners in rhyme first turtles with turtle power part. That's a fucking you are T. Ali power
But the lyrics to it are wrong now. I know but who gives a shit
Raphael he's the leader of the group transform from the norm by the nuclear I know Raphael is not the leader of the group
So what you never watched one episode of the show and you're gonna do a rap about it
Look, I don't really care about the mistake.
It's a superior musical effort.
OK.
And Turtles 2 doesn't have the setup.
Casey Jones isn't in it.
Look, would it hold up now?
I can almost guarantee now.
But oh well.
Well, what are you going to do?
I would have liked to seen Feldman return.
That's the other thing.
Turtles 2, no Feldman.
You didn't see the new Turtles, did you?
I tried watching half of it over Pete's house,
and I couldn't I couldn't I mean it's fucking terrible yeah now turtles three
turtles in time is unwatchable too and a friend of mine at school had seen it
before all the rest of us and he goes dude wait till you see turtles three
they're gonna make six Ninja Turtle movies go see three and you'll see what
I mean, okay, buddy Ryan, we go and see turtles three. There's nothing that indicates there's
going to be six turtles. He said he saw something in it that was like, you know, there's going
to be three more. They set it up for a whole nother trilogy. To this day, I don't know
what he was talking about. Perhaps he was on drugs. If anything, you go see turtles three
and you're like, well, this franchise is over. Maybe there was just post credit
it's seen. Maybe. I don't think they're well they did do it in those days.
They did it. There's Bueller as a post credit. So does Masters
of the Universe starring Dolph Lundgren, Billy Barty and Frank Lanjela.
I've seen MOTU or Motu. What is the post credit sequence?
Well he man defeats Skeletor by throwing him into like a pit of lava.
Yeah. And the credits go and then let me guess real quick.
does a bone hand come out of the lava better okay better it's actually pretty
cool scene it's a close -up of the lava and Skeletor's head pops out okay and
says to camera I'll be back but you weren't Skeletor well they had a sequel
planned and they canceled it now see I have really strong memories of my
childhood for example I remember that I had several birthdays where I would
wind up crying into an elf cake because no you told us that last time but what I
don't remember is ever enjoying Masters of the Universe I had a huge Ninja Turtles
collection but I never remember watching He -Man or Masters of the Universe
however there's a photo of me in an Orco costume for Halloween that's just
because you like to put on dresses but I don't remember ever having a toy or
caring about Mash the universe at all. This is a great song by Nick Cave that is also
used in Dumb and Dumber called Red Right Hand really and Nick Cave I like to say I'm sorry
that your son died that's terrible I'm sure you're listening to this I'm reading I'm
reading more about the Scream TV show and it says now the link the link said the link
that I clicked on said scream remake made the weirdest decision possible okay go on remake
me into the TV show here's the quote please note that I had been in communication with
TWC regarding this and they have informed me that as of now and during the initial launch
Ghostface is not involved in the new format they also indicated that because of this direction
it does not mean that Ghostface will not be involved at a later date so there is still
question to the question however as of now there is no involvement further down it says
we believe Scream is Ghostface and Ghostface is Scream however while Ghostface is owned
by Fun World this is Fun World saying this the Scream motion picture franchise is owned
by the Weinstein Company and is their option to film a movie or TV show without Ghostface
I don't know the plot was already completely removed from Wes Ravens hit films anyway so
it's pretty disappointing to find that the MTV version is 100 % in name only cash grab
okay so it's just here's the plot of the show you ready just boring I mean we're both talking
and watching a movie and now you're reading articles aloud I just like what's going
going on. I want to learn about the MTV generation. I want to learn about the TV screen show the
screen TV. I will watch it at some point. I'll just read
the plot real quick. Go ahead real quick. Emma and her best friend Aubrey see relationships
and lives turned upside down when a private video of Aubrey's of Aubrey's goes viral
and incites a murder in the teen small town. Sounds like a plot of unfriended which was
why it's a different mask because it's not Ghostface, I guess.
I don't I don't fucking know.
Why do they do this with these things?
I mean, a horror aggravated.
There's really been no successful horror TV shows
that I can think of.
I literally don't think MTV's ever done anything
that hasn't infuriated me.
I can't think of one thing they do.
Well, I like the John Stuart show when he had the talk show.
That was 48 years ago.
I'm just trying to name good things.
I loved you on TV raps.
I loved hangers ball. I loved hundred twenty minutes. I mean it used to have this very like
Forbidden feel to me. I never had cable growing up when I would babysit
I would go and be like I can't wait to see MTV and I watch the black hole Sun video and the weezer buddy
Holly video and they'd be like good Lord. These are fucking works of art these things and I think most people's frustration is why does
MTV not show any music anymore. It's not my issue really
it's just kind of like why is nothing on here particularly good well if you notice out on
my DVD shelves and I do have quite a vast collection ladies yeah I have a huge box not a huge box
set but like a four DVD you know with each DVD being a double disc or whatever box set
of video music directors I have the same thing because I have the spike Jones one out of
all the guy there are two videos one of them is amazing yeah they're great when you're
having a party just for visuals on the TV sure you know Spike Jones made in my opinion the
best music videos there ever were yeah he was really and now he makes fucking amazing
movies he was really good but yeah okay so in the last 20 years I'd say MTV hasn't done
anything that has an infuriated me that's fair I didn't see the recent VMAs but they're
always a real downer. I was at my friends in New York and they put
it on and I literally one point it's like guys I can't watch
this and I said why and I said because it's making me it makes
me so angry that I'm going to start yelling at your TV. Yeah
nobody wants that. It makes me furious. I can't even deal with
it. I can't deal with it. I miss a lot of that's one of
cable. I miss I hate certain aspects of pop culture so much
that I don't have cable and then I miss tons of shit.
Right. You know I would have watched the goddamn
Scream show just out of curiosity and then I would have been furious, but you know
It's always a thing and I have a very kind of like I need to finish and I need to complete
series and movies and all that kind of stuff like if I see
Three movies in a franchise. I'm gonna watch 12 movies of a franchise and eventually you're just wasting hours of your life
Because they're bad and that's the way you start a show on MTV and I'm like yeah watch the Scream series
But then I find myself having devoted
12 hours to the Scream series and then I wish I was dead. It's like being in a bad relationship.
You just go this will this will get better and then it just doesn't really I finally gave
up on I hate to say it because I'm a fan of everybody in the show and I'm a fan of the
idea of the show. Yeah and at moments the show is brilliant but I finally gave up on Bates
Motel. I couldn't do it anymore. I did too. It had scenes that were really like shot
in cool ways and like a couple cool ideas but then more often than not you're like what are
you doing why is there a whole subplot about the town selling I know weed it's so dumb
deal with anything I tend to I tend to need like I said a lot of people to recommend something
or the whole season to have air and people to be like I tell you this whole season was
great then I'll watch the whole season by the way at this point in the film if you
watching along with us they're they're at a party Matthew Lillard's characters having a house party
I've never known a guy like this in my life I've seen a guy like this in a million movies
about teenagers never knew a guy like this Matthew Lillard character walking around in a satin robe
no no good reason no just the just the guy well I had no cool friends growing up almost to the
present to be honest with you sure I don't like cool people and never had cool friends but
never went to a party like this but parties I went to were always like 12
angry guys not getting laid sitting in a basement yelling at MTV well but we had
a good time Pat we could have been lifelong chums yeah yeah look and then
you wind up kind of growing up and you kind of missed that because now if me
and you were to sit and watch MTV for 12 hours we'd feel like we were wasting
our lives sure we'd have other things to go do sure yeah at the very least let's
make it a podcast if we're going to say exactly things let's bring in that podcast cash or
podcast look at this nips rose McGowan nips on ten now here's a big question do they say
hey rose we'd love for you to be nipping hardcore in this scene or do they just make it real
cold in there and not tell her what do you think do they do they get it in the contract
because it is a form of nudity what do you think it's I honestly think that it's for
some reason she probably said okay to not wearing a bra or decided to not wear a bra
and I bet you at some point a woman on set went up and said hey just so you know sweetie
your turkeys are done right and she probably went oh I don't care yeah well she's holding
beers up against them I'm fucking the guy that wrote beautiful people what do I give
a shit yeah she means she wants to be a star that's like she's wearing a bra though
she is clearly wearing a bra those things are rocking through the bra or else they
were fake nipples which is another weird thing. I know quite a few people who worked on friends
as we were talking about earlier and they said as there became a little sort of healthy competition
amongst the cast and not so much Kudrow but Aniston would come in to set for her scenes
nipping hard and you watch as you as you move along through friends you see a lot of Aniston
and really aggressively nipping.
Then Courtney Cox, fearing that she was going
to be less desirable because she wasn't nipping,
would also start nipping.
And the winner was the viewer, of course.
Sure.
And then eventually DeCuffney started showing us balls.
On what?
I'm joking, Pat.
DeCuffney.
Even Schwimmer.
The reason I didn't get your joke
is because I thought you moved on to the X -files.
I was like, Oh, was that that bit of a joke?
Swimmers started showing his balls.
Swimmers got the outline of his balls.
Perry comes out with his taint exposed.
It was a rough time.
Rose McGowan is about to be murdered by Ghostface in the.
By a garage door opener.
That's my first voice crack of the podcast.
She gets murdered by a garage door opener?
Well, they, you know, they like take her up in the garage
door, her body.
God, I really remember nothing.
I thought I really remembered this move. I really haven't seen it in a long time
It's a cool skirt. I like draws you into her butt and vagina. I
Love McGowan, you know just the right shade of pale
You know you can tell she's got tattoos in all the right places. Mm -hmm. Oh, yeah, here we go. You can tell she probably
Sidel up to a game of beer pong and talk a lot of shit. Sure, you know
Where's your drink you pussy? I picture being like one of those kinds of girl. Yeah
Then she gets drunk and it goes a little too far and then she's embarrassing you in front of your friends
But you can't stay away can't stay away you tell her you never want to see her again
You can't stay away. You find yourself calling her a couple nights later couple nights a couple minutes. Oh
All right, so McGowan just bit it I remember being very disappointed that she died in this I was like, uh
Well, I mean she died what it why did you think you were gonna see her naked eventually?
I especially at this age when I'm like 15 years old. That's all I that's really honestly all I thought about
was
By the way, I didn't realize till now her name is Tatum. Yeah
Rose McGowan her name is Tatum Channing Tatum
One of my favorite jokes ever wrote for Pete show was you talk said this I said this already. Yeah. Are you sure? Yeah taint
We've both done this it's embarrassing, but we've both done it
I mean, we got to talk for two hours straight
and this goddamn thing.
I know.
I mean, I don't remember what the,
you could tell me we already did an episode about Scream.
I wouldn't even, we're four episodes in.
I can't remember what the fuck we've talked about already.
Yeah.
We got to start getting into some weirder movies.
So like, you know, yeah, it's making us.
Oh, uh -oh.
OK, that's fine.
Our picture just went nuts, but then it came back.
The old, as far as this, this obsession
I have with nudity at the time,
because I, we didn't have the internet in my house
until I was in college, I brought a big group of friends of mine to see the gift and nobody
cared to see it speaking of Sam Raimi and I was so off the charts excited because I was
going to see Katie Holmes naked right and at the time my dress was pre cruise during
Dawson's Creek.
I was so beyond obsessed Katie Holmes and I just thought she's the best looking lady
in the world.
I go to see the gift and I'm like I heard she's naked in this and I have her like ten friends
We're like okay here. We got the gifts an okay movie. It's going going about an hour in they're all like when we're gonna see this
They pull Katie Holmes's naked corpse out of a river and
Everyone looks down the aisle at me like you fucking son of a bitch
and I was so distraught that I didn't know what to do and
And finally at about the hour 30 mark they do a flashback with Holmes and Greg Keneer
And as the flashback begins I said thank you Jesus. I've got another chance and sure enough
She gets completely topless in that thing and it was as glorious as I'd always dream
She bangs Keneer in that movie. She's dating Keneer who I think is her teacher
Keneer's like 20 years older than her isn't he? Yeah, and that's right around the time
He also was banging me in a suvary in real life in the in real life really. Oh, no
I'm saying in real life. No in the in the very underrated teen movie loser
Never saw the Jason Biggs directed by Amy Heckerling
But who did clueless and fast times rich my car. Yes, I think people get that movie a bad rap
Gift has a lot of weird cast and Keanu Reeves plays like an abusive boyfriend
Is Lucy the one with Jason Schwartzman in it to know that slackers slackers, which is okay
I remember there being a weird cult around that movie, but it's not doesn't really warrant the Schwartz
He brings a cult in and accepted was the Justin long one of those
I I saw accepted in the movie theater by myself
I think I did I was delivering pizzas at the time and I'd get off of work at 2 p .m.
And then I I still was living at home and my parents didn't go to five
So I just go to a movie yeah and spend the afternoon there and I saw accepted and that was my introduction to Jonah Hill
He was funny in that the part where he screams part where he screams deals the show. It's amazing
I remember the being in the trailer and I was like man
That's really funny and the movie wasn't it wasn't that funny. It's an art play great bit that summer. I saw accepted
Art school confidential. Oh, I love that move and I own it of the Christ
All by myself also hilarious theater. I loved our school confidential
It's a much meaner nastier movie than ghost world
but I love them both. It gets dark in ways you're not expecting because it starts it starts
almost silly. Yeah I think it gets like it gets like dark where you're like the end of
it. You're like Jesus Christ. Yeah I think that Terry's why golf is too dark to maybe
ever work again which is really unfortunate but like if you look at that track record
Crumb Ghost World, Arsenal Confidential, Bad Santa, and Bad Santa came out over ten years
ago and the guy hasn't made a movie since.
That movie made a lot of money.
I think he's really difficult to work with is what I've always heard.
I have a theory about Bad Santa.
Go on.
A -plus in my opinion.
It's a master piece.
I showed it to my parents the last Christmas and we had a wonderful time together.
We talked about that on this podcast.
I love you.
Right.
Jesus Christ.
Anyway.
Did I tell you my theory?
I don't think so.
Okay.
There's a twilight zone.
There's an episode of the twilight zone called Night of the Meek.
The original version of it stars Art Carney.
The remake stars the guy from Empty Nest.
I'm blanking on his name.
The guy that was.
Yeah.
And the plot is it's like a heartfelt twilight zone.
it's the Christmas episode. Yeah. And it's about a Santa Claus, a department store Santa
Claus who's a complete drunk. Okay. And, you know, gets fired from the department store
because he was drinking on his break and more of, you know, embarrasses himself and
is mortified. Right. Apologetic and everything and then actually becomes Santa Claus.
Okay. I was just tapping your own. Sorry. That's fine. Actually becomes Santa Claus.
That's the Twilight Zone twist at the end. Right. Deems himself by becoming Santa
OK my theory is is that when they were writing that the way the idea for bad
Santa came up was they were watching that Twilight Zone and said well what if he
wasn't embarrassed it was just a piece of shit that could that could very well
be I really think that's what it was like yeah how funny would it be if he
was just a fucking scumbag like owning this yeah and then the end he does kind
of become Santa Claus at the end of bad Santa right you know in a in a much
different way but you know there some fascinating things about bad Santa they're uncredited
but apparently a vast majority of the script was rewritten by the Cohen brothers which
I love yeah and also obsessively courted and was going to play it till almost the last
minute was Bill Murray so like I think Bill Murray would have been amazing and yet I think
like looking at it now. I love what Billy Bob Thorne did so much. I don't I don't even care.
I don't need to see Bill Murray play the part. Well I'll say this and I love Bill as much
as it saddens me to think I could have seen Bill Murray play that part because he's always
great playing a dirt ball. Yeah. I don't know if I think the great thing that Billy Bob
Thorne brought to it was he captured a darkness that I don't know if I would have felt with
Bill Murray I agree and Bill Murray is clearly a guy with some fucking demons right but like
Billy Bob Thornton played that with like just that like no humanity in his eyes even and
I think that's what makes the movie so special to me yeah just like because like you I don't
think we'll ever again outside of the rawest of indie movies see a character that like
like a moral and alcoholic and giving up on life that movie blew my fucking mind and it
still does when I watch it I'm like this is this is it like this is the movie that didn't
like make any concessions to anyone well my friend Jim and I often talk about how nobody
curses funnier than Billy Bob Thornton I agree I even love the bad news bears remake yeah
I was into it too yeah but he always his favorite line is Billy Bob Thornton and I think it's
and intolerable cruelty funny movie where he goes well god damn good to meet you I think
it's his life yeah and that and my favorite is always from love actually where he walks
he walks by Hugh Grant's assistant who's a really hot girl and Billy Bob Thornton goes
god damn that's a pretty son of a bitch about a woman yeah god damn that's a pretty son
of a bitch. Yeah that guy is billy about Thornton's fucking hilarious man. See this now this
was a say the word hilarious then Jamie Kennedy comes on the screen. I mean is this was a
troubling time. Has he ever made you laugh. Jamie Kennedy's never made a laugh. No ever
but I know people who love him. So prank show sucked. Yeah. No I agree. You know you
had a prank show when Ashton Kutcher is out doing your prank. I agree. You know it was
a much funnier show that no one ever speaks about was the Andy Dick show that was on MTV
and that show had some genius sketches on it was bent. No. Ben Stiller was Fox. What was
the show? Andy Dick show was around this time. Like it feels like about a ninety six
and man he had some amazing characters. He did like a long sad dark Britney Spears parody
episode that was amazing and it fit squarely into that MTV mold. You know like it.
It was, it was appealing to those kids, but it was really smart and fucked up and funny.
And that is the guy who played meatloaf, by the way.
It is the guy that played meatloaf.
Well, what's he up to?
Who hasn't had one line of dialogue yet.
I don't think.
No, he had one.
We were talking through it.
He said something to Courtney Cox when they were in the van.
I don't like how she was yelling at him earlier, calling him a big fat lard ass.
I didn't care for it either.
You know, here's now here's look, here's a sort of romantic scene romance and bloom
them. Cox and or yeah. I wonder if they played this at the wedding where the feeling during
their first dance. Yeah. They work their character names into the vows and when I met my Dewey
and then he goes when I met my oh whoa how weird was that what I said when I met my and
she said her name Gail Weathers. Joe that was weird. I'm yes it was weird. I'm sorry
I barely noticed it because he yelled so quickly after it was kind of amazing. I said and she said when my neck gale
Weathers that was kind of a special moment. I was just I was just thinking of my vows for him in my head
Sorry, no, what we would say if you married David our cat where he said it where he says to her
Luckily you were in my jurisdiction, you know something like right, right, right?
We started as he looks at the audience friends
audience, but eventually I made you look to the audience scream in bed because you were
looks at the audience ready to rumble. Yeah, great. Perfect. You don't have to be Sherlock
Holmes to figure out how much our love. Should we go up right now to like Van Nye's catch
the tail end of David Arquette and Sherlock Holmes and then hang out with him? Because
were the only two people there. We would be the only people there. I gotta tell you, why would we
not go to that show? If the tickets are more than seven dollars, there's your answer. If they're
less than, yes, I would go. You're making all that TV money. I am very wealthy. I started a new
writing job on Monday. Let's spend some cash and go see this day. Let's do it. I'm just terribly
curious. He just he doesn't seem like the right choice, frankly. I was doing I can't mock the
guy because I was I was doing I remember a private corporate gig oh it was in a
restaurant they were having this big dinner in the restaurant and he was I
was in the bar waiting to go on and he was there at the bar for his birthday
party right for birthday dinner or something and all these people were
showing up and he went off with several good -looking well -to -do people sure
to have a nice birthday party and then I went in and bombed for an hour in
for that 60 year old men that were eating steak.
So, Dave, you're doing better than I am.
What was the corporate?
Couldn't tell you.
Never bombed, I mean just bombing,
insulting them because they weren't laughing.
They're heckling me saying we had Sarah Silverman
once and she was wonderful.
They yelled out a full sentence,
like we had Sarah Silverman once
and you weren't that funny.
They said, I said, who else has done this?
Oh, okay, you asked.
And they said Sarah Silverman and I said,
How did she do and they said, oh, she was great. Yeah, she was great
Tell me what she did cuz I this is fucking horrible. Yeah, figure this out right now. I
Yeah, and again not a break. I've yet to really bomb at stand -up, but I think done it seven times
I think what no. Yeah, exactly. I haven't done a lot of time when I do do it
When I do bomb, I think that'll be it for me. I
the part in the movie. That's I was trying to remember. How do they make you think it's
not Skeet? There you go. There you go. Because Skeet gets killed by Ghostface. Definitely.
Of yes. In front of the fuck's her name. I was called her Daisy Sydney. Definitely at
this point in the movie. I was like, Oh shit, if it's not him, who is it? And I started
running through my mind. And that's, you know, that I don't think had been done
in a horror movie to that time. It's a great twist. I could have sworn we saw
Lillard leave the house to maybe he ran out with everybody everybody ran out of
the house by the way hitting it hitting him with that door would have had no
effect on him he fell to the ground you don't think if you got hit with a big
wooden door you wouldn't fall to the ground it wasn't a big it was a thin
wooden door and it was Nev Campbell hitting him with it let's test it out
that if you hit me with this door over here I'd go what the fuck Joe I want you
Ow I wouldn't fall to the floor that puts your money where your mouth is all right. I think it'd be more than an owl
Also, I mean you got a nitpick here. I mean for Christ's sake, you know
No, it's just something in movies like you know like when somebody punches a guy in the face and then his eyes flitter
And he falls to the ground and he's unconscious
I'm like no, I don't buy that
What did she just fall onto? She fell off a boat onto a boat. All right. Well, then conveniently plays to boat
Fair enough. I'll buy it. I'll take it. Yeah, it could be a boat
Lucky break. Well, where's people have boats on the driveway? They do
It's a pain moving that boat every morning when you got to pull the cars out, but
It's worth it in the summertime
This has been Pat Walsh and Joe de Rosa for boats
Are we supposed to believe he's this drunk now?
I don't know if Jimmy Kennedy is supposed to be drunk in this scene or just him being
funny.
I don't know.
He's not great.
He's watching Halloween.
Halloween.
I watch once a year.
It's a perfect movie.
It's great.
I like Halloween 2 better.
Are you kidding me?
No.
It's still John Carpenter.
So you have a lot more in common with Quentin Tarantino than you might think.
I like Halloween 2 better. It's it's more fast -paced. It gives you more what you want. I I could not disagree more. I
Just couldn't disagree more
I the first picture is very good, but it's also slow
It's a very slow build to the end. Yeah, that's called suspense. I understand
But I like that I like the second one. You like h2o
I remember thinking it was okay. I should go through them all again. I've only
That's Kevin Williamson. Yeah, that's true. That's a great movie
We should watch that on here sometime. We will probably watch Halloween. I own them all recently
I I've only watched one and two but I
Think it's basically like an A -plus and a
So you own four or five six to I own them all I'm gonna try to watch. What did you buy the set?
Yeah, but the set the Rob zombie ones to me are terrible, but
Yeah, it's just like why are you punishing us? We're just trying to it's why are you trying to make me feel?
sick it's yeah it's so sad and depressed yeah that's like a horror movie to me you
know I I don't mind being scared shitless I don't mind disturbing but when
you start making me sad like what that's not what I'm here for the part I don't
like is that he there's that like guard in the institution with him that like
kind of takes care of him yeah and then he kills the guard now that you're
saying that I remember like very well it's it'd be so much it would give so
much one of the character if he didn't kill that guy. Yeah. And that was a guy that was
the eyewitness that was there to tell the cops like this is what just happened here. All those
Rob zombies are just such like a just shoving your face in the mud except I did like Devil's
rejects which kind of had an action. It's literally the only one I've never seen because
every other one of his movies I didn't like. Yeah. They're not for me. I respect what
the guy does like I respect that he's made a career in making horror movies but you
know I was so excited to see lords of Salem didn't say you know by the third
time you're seeing you know burnt -faced demons jerking off with black dildos
you're like I get it Rob okay we're good Rob everything's to pray I get it yeah
you know like it's just I don't know by the way I don't even think Rob zombies
the guy's real name I'm gonna I'm gonna say that now on this podcast I am
tomorrow night. You know what it is. I actually know what his real name is. What is Brad zombie.
Good one Joe. See. I'm excited tomorrow night. I'm going to go see the visit the new Shyamalan
which comes out tomorrow. I think that looks fantastic. And if it's I hope it's good
I'm always written for Shyamalan. The guy made two masterpieces and then just an assortment
of shockingly terrible movies. I hate signs. I like signs better than the other ones and
I like the first half of the village a lot. The first half of the village is cool. Lady
in the water I was like okay this guy is insane but then you keep thinking he'll get back
on track and he never did. I think the visit looks really cool and I read some article
where he was like I know that this is my last chance. Well after a lady in the water
he stopped making horror movies that's when he started doing like Last Airbender and
I didn't see that one but the happening is oh no the happening was really almost unwatchable
Yeah, the happening sucks signs has some good scares like there's a couple like that video of the yes
That's that's a cool scare. That's a good scare. Yeah, it's it's signs signs is overall better than the village
But I really don't care for signs. I don't care for
He's just like such a great technical
Filmmaker like he you know
So he needs to let somebody else write his scripts or something at this point, although
the sixth sense and unbreakable are almost without flaws, but I'm excited about the visit
for sure.
I didn't know that open tomorrow.
I might go see that tomorrow night because I'm trying to be at the Vista right around
the corner.
Oh, it is.
I just told all your stalkers where you live.
Yeah, thanks.
I am trying.
I'm trying not to have any booze until Saturday, so that'll be a thing to do tomorrow night.
Yeah.
Go to the.
You're like a werewolf you got to stay off the streets if you want to
Like be good. How else am I gonna do it a single man on a Friday night? You know, I'm not going to a bar
What am I gonna do go take it a movie by myself? It's sabbatroom sit behind you and your girlfriend in the theater
Oh, hey guys, that's where that you're here to poke your head up between. No, that's cool
No, no, no, oh really sit with you. Come on now. All right. I mean I guess sit between you
We're nearing the end of the film here ghost face is now Courtney Cox has fled the scene
everybody's dead ghost face has Neve cornered basically she's in a truck she's locked herself
in we're not I mean we have as always we're not paying the closest of attention but it
doesn't the movie doesn't seem to pack the constant scares I remember it packing no
it's been it's been pretty steady I did used to be a lot more of a pussy like when I
I never found the movie scary. I found it well done. I mean sure these movies don't scare me usually sure
You got a really the exorcist used to scare me
But because it gets in your head the exorcist, you know
especially because
My father was one of the only R -rated movies to let me watch because I could learn about Catholicism
Yeah, well, she should be watching her pussy. Yeah, then she's masturbating with a crucifix
So we watched it in the next night. It's like a full night and my dad takes me to the staircase in st. Louis
And he goes this is supposed to be the staircase
Where this actually happened where they threw the priests down the stairs and I was like oh so it happened locally
That's supposed to be based on a true st. Louis story
Okay, that's just still scares the shit out of me. I didn't was that it for you with movie?
Yeah, I just think I watched it fairly recently and I think it's still terrifying if you turn the lights out
It's gonna fuck you up. Yeah, it's scary as shit. It's scary as shit
Oh, here's where they make you think Jamie Kennedy is the killer
But that you know that one almost invents a new kind of scary, you know, like it's
It's still just kind of like unbelievably intense for today
And the fact that audience like you hear audiences passed out in the 70s like yeah, I fully believe that yeah
It's just it's like a merciless
almost like made by a demon kind of movie they'll never they'll never come
close I read the book recently about a year ago I read when I was a kid and you
read the book when you were a kid how old were you I use I mean sadly because I
couldn't see these movies I used to read the book how old are you when you
read that book probably right after I watched the movie so I must have been
10 or something 10 yeah you saw her shoving across in a vagina when you
were 10. Yeah. And again, I couldn't watch the guy. I couldn't
watch any other movies. That party wasn't like this is a little
bit much. I mean, I don't remember what we did at that point.
I probably left the room, but he was big on me learning about
Catholic or did he show you it on like regular TV where maybe
that was no. We watched the real deal because I remember
being like I used to beg my dad to see any other movies. And
I remember as that movie was going, I was like, I might
have to leave I might not be able to watch this but then I might never get to watch an
already movie again so I got to set it out that's great man yeah I remember when my mom
finally let me see it and I was like oh my god it was and I was like oh I get it now I
get it now I get why I wasn't allowed to watch this yeah it scared the shit out of me that
was that was embarrassing acting by Jamie Kennedy upon getting shot like hey Jamie act like
he got shot and he can't do that right. What did he do? He goes oh so this is and look
at this with this skeet or it's weirdly enough or it's just way better once he makes the
flip than he is. It's just a normal guy. I'm still not buying him. I'm buying Lillard.
That's that's a sweater I may have owned in the 90s and I might have worn that necklace
Lillard I'm buying Lillard right now. Look at him. He's yeah, he's doing great
Skeet's doing like the I'm sinister
Lillard on the other hand just looks like a fucking, you know, like it like a douchey guy
Yeah, I like it. I'm buying it. All right
They should have made t -shirts of that. See how that that skeet right t -shirt with the two blood t -shirt
Skeet shirt, yeah.
Skeet, skeet, skeet, skeet, motherfucker.
With the two blood streaks on it?
That would have been a marketing move right there.
You saw that teacher with the two blood streaks.
If it was a little more memorable,
like you don't walk out of the movie remembering that shirt.
From the back, it says scream.
Are they? I know they're not doing it overtly,
but are they implicitly implying
that these two are gay lovers?
What is this shot all about?
Well, Lillard is sort of resting his chin on Skeet's shoulder.
I mean, he's giving him a reach around, essentially.
Is it that kind of like in cold blood?
I think there is supposed to be a certain implication
that they have a very intimate relationship.
Maybe it may be sexual.
I mean, look, they murder together.
So there's something.
You remember murder by numbers with Gosling and Sandy Bullock?
Never saw it.
That's another kind of like two guys murdering together and there's a lot of like did they or didn't they kind of shit
Does that put the sting song in it? They sure did. They sure did. Does it work?
No, you know what? They didn't because they used the sting song Murder by Numbers as a major plot point in Copycat
Which is a movie that is so good
But was overshadowed because it came out around the same time as 7. Isn't copy had also Sandra Bullock. No
It's Holly Hunter my favorite actress and Sigourney Weaver and they're great together and Harry Connick, Jr.
Of all people is the villain and he's great in it
Harry Connick's a good actor and if you have not seen copycat
It was rightfully overshadowed by seven which is a much better movie, but copycat is great
It's a really good solid effort really good serial killer movie and deserves better than what it got
I never been a big serial killer movie. I heard serial killer movie fan
I like take them over horror movies most of the time. No way. I love them
I love a horror movie sounds of lamb seven zodiac. Well, boom boom boom. Hold on a second
I don't I was gonna say except for ones like seven or silence of the lambs right because they're more they feel more like horror films to
Me. Yeah, sure, but you know
Copycat is another you know, I never like kiss the girls. Did you see you have or have not seen copy?
I haven't come over and watch it. I own I'm saying that kind of movie. I'm usually like, yeah
Yeah, kiss the girls with along came a spider. Okay, those are those aren't great those
Those kind of thing well, I like the Hitchcock films though and those are always murder mysteries, but yeah
Who do they have taped up here? The girls isn't awful
Those used to be the like the bone collector. There was one of those every week
And they all had joe lee and Morgan Freeman
Morgan Freeman was always involved
Morgan Freeman gives me great hope in this business because he didn't really make it to Lee was like
three or something. Yeah. That's what my dad when I was like I
realized you're trying to support me but it's not coming
across but I was trying to be a writer and I was 23 years old
or something which is very reasonable and he was like
you know Pat you got to look at Dennis Franz. Dennis
Franz wasn't a famous actor until he was 52 years old. I'm
like yeah I'm a child then. I'm not like washed up and I
I love by the way the bone collector just so you don't think that we mix up all black actors was Denzel Washington
It was yeah, it was Denzel and Jillie. I thought that was part of that Morgan
I thought that was the kistis. Well, wait wasn't kistis kiss the girl
He was playing the same character and then recently he was played the same character was played by Tyler Perry
Who was in all those books?
But it used to be Morgan Freeman and kiss the girls and along came a spider
Then there's double jeopardy with Ashley John kiss the girls and along came the spider
or Morgan Freeman's the same guy.
Is it the guy from Seven?
No, that's its own character.
Seven's its own fucked up thing.
What movie did Tyler Perry play that character in?
I guess the character is called Alex Cross
and I believe he played him in Alex Cross.
Okay.
I didn't see that one.
I hear Tyler Perry stole the show in Gone Girl.
I disagree, but I think people were mostly surprised
that he was pretty good in it.
I like Gone Girl a lot
and I like Tyler Perry in it a lot.
He's a good actor.
That's the only telepare movies. Yeah. Yeah. Bone collector is
Denzel and let me make sure Alex Cross is Freeman. No Alex Cross is I
Don't know. No. Yeah, Morgan Freeman played him in along came a spider and kiss the girls also
And does Denzel play that character in bone collector? Nope different guy different guy different thing. All right
But Morgan Freeman was in training day. I'm kidding. I
I love training.
It's a fucking awesome movie.
Who doesn't like training day?
All right.
By the way, I think that is top five nudity for me
as Eva Mendes in training day.
I watched it again.
I rewatched it recently.
And I about fell off the couch.
Do they show her boobs?
Yeah.
Really?
It's really crazy good.
All right.
And it's brief and, you know.
I'll go back into that.
It's not particularly graphic.
It's just really good.
This is why I could never be a murderer
because they're now they're doing the thing they're at the they're at the part at the end of their killing spree
When now they're like we have to make it look like we are innocent. So we got to stab each other, right?
But but I remember loving this and being like this is really no, it's really shit
It's great. I wouldn't be able to do it though. That's what I'm saying if you and I murder somebody and I couldn't yeah
I did that was that's the that's the main thing that would stop me is when you were like, okay
Now we got to stab each other when we pushed up on this and go out and kill somebody
Don't say it like that if we get framed now tonight because I told you before when I said
I wanted to stab you if you ever get stabbed they're gonna come to me first now it's true
Courtney Cox just got knocked out by Skeet Olrich strangely enough they both have the
same haircut Skeet loves those bangs in his eyes man
I think they popped old scream two out the next year I think it's how quickly they turned
that around. They went fast with this. They went fast and
scream forward took forever and Craven was smart to stick with
the franchise because he he left the franchise with
nightmare. Yeah. Because he was against the idea of making
a sequel and he also said and I believe I've said this Christ
almighty chakra before. Yeah. I'm sorry. Guys go back and
listen to the Nightmare on Elm Street episode. You'll know
what I was about to say just then. I didn't say it again. So let's say Hollywood comes
to you, Joe, and they say you can remake any horror movie you want to make. You write it
your way. You come in with a cool take on it. What do you do? Whatever you want to
do. Wait, say this again. They come to you and they want you to reboot a horror movie.
They want you to write it.
Do your take on it, your spin on it.
Which one do you do?
So like a creep show without question.
Same stories?
No, I would want to reboot it and try
to get the series going again.
Right, OK.
Like all new stories.
But like all new stories based on Stephen King stories.
Yeah.
You know, and why not just do another different anthology?
Why do you want to make a creep show review? Well creep shows my favorite horror franchise of all time
Okay, so if somebody came to me and said what would you want to redo or reboot?
I'd want to see more creep shows. Okay there, you know, I love anthology horror that or
Hellraiser, but they're already doing that with
Clyde Barker is already apparently doing that so directing
It's apparently he's writing directing and producing the remake any stars
us. Apparently Doug Bradley's coming back as pinhead. That's all I care about. They could
have fucking raccoons running around on the floor. I wouldn't give a same story. Like why
why wouldn't you. Well it might not be. I'm not sure it's going to be a different take
but right. But I you know as long as Bradley's in there as pinhead. I mean that's why I watched
all the goddamn sequels. Yeah. And you know they were nothing to a lot of them were
nothing to write home about. Right. Pat you know what I mean is it which one would
you do. I mean I think I would want to do something imperfect
like you know like my dream and my kind of thing that I feel I could write really well
would be like a misery but I don't I couldn't improve on misery. So right well I'm not by
no means saying I could improve on creep show which is why I wouldn't want to remake the
old stories right I would just want to see the things started up again. Yeah I got you.
I think my dream would have been poltergeist until I saw what they did with poltergeist
but maybe we could pretend that didn't happen I mean I just you know I don't know that's
just who do you think they would cast if they made by the way skeet or it's got just got
stabbed with an umbrella how is that possible you know actually you know what here's my
dream and it's already happening but apparently it's not going to be what we want it to
is that it remake?
I would love a crack at that it remake.
Oh yeah, that's a good one.
Yeah, that'd be good.
That, by the way, the way Ski Rollins just died,
head through the TV, and she said, in your dreams.
Yeah.
That's a nod, I believe, to that Reno Street 3.
Three.
You're going to be in pictures or what?
Welcome to Primetime, bitch.
Oh, right.
I just watched a little more of that documentary,
and the original line was like,
you finally got your dream to be in television,
and then England improvised.
Welcome to Primetime, bitch.
I was outside of the Glendale Galleria braggart
Which is our mall here. Yep in beautiful Los Angeles. Yeah, and I saw the girl a woman and
She looked very familiar
And I couldn't place it for a moment and then I realized who it was and I said you're
From nightmare and Elm Street 3 Wow, and it was the TV
And she seemed flattered. I said she was extremely flattered. I said I want to tell you this you have the best kill in the entire franchise
Yeah, and she said that's so sweet of you lit up a smile. She said God bless you. That's great
It was very nice, you know
I I will always recognize like an actor who's been acting a lot and has in a lot of shit
Like I told you about that Richard Reel that actor over at the diner here from office space and watch movies
but like somebody who was in a movie in 1980 I'm not gonna recognize now we had
on the show I write for we had on the guy who's named Jonathan Schmock and he
played the snooty guy at the fancy French restaurant in Ferris Bueller with
the whole Abe Froman bit that's great like the real slick nose turned up guy
or whatever and they told me the day after we shot it I had no idea the
guy was really funny on the show I had no clue and I would like I would have
love to ask him about Ferris Fuehler but he looked completely different because it's been
30 years. That's amazing. That's amazing. What do you look like?
He you you never would have guessed but apparently he wrote a lot with this guy Jim Valley who
wrote for the rest of development. He's a big writer and got into a bunch of other
shit. I took my mom and dad to see a taping of Sullivan
and son. Yep.
Because my mom was a big fan of the show and and Steve Byrne got me in and everything
thing and whatever and but we were we're going in and Steve was taking us around and introducing
my parents to the cast and then he introduced us to the guest star for that week and he's
like this is so -and -so he was on the nanny and I was like holy shit that's like the guy
from the nanny Charles Shaughnessy yeah it was the guy yeah but I didn't remember yeah
I mean sometimes I remember like we had Brian Doyle Murray on the show he doesn't look
that different than he did in fucking vacation court.
No, I remember Brian.
Do I was on an episode and that was that was actually one
of the greatest things I've ever got to experience
in this business was when my parents were on set,
it was the week after I taped.
Yeah.
And I introduced them to Brian Duel Murray and he said,
and he tapped me on the shoulder and he said,
he's a good boy.
That was really nice.
Yeah.
And there we have it.
Scream.
Talked right.
RIP West Craven, of course.
Wes, you're going to be greatly missed, man.
You did some really terrific work and very influential shit,
for sure.
I've seen you like hell.
You know what?
I say it all the time.
Nightmare in Elm Street was my gateway horror movie.
My mom showed it to me when I was 11
and I never turned back.
So, you know, I thank Wes Craven for that, for turning me on to horror for my entire life.
Yeah.
And for me, he just reminds me of being a huge pussy when I was a kid.
We talked about shocker a little bit, but my friends being like, hey, we got to watch
Freddie or whatever, and just dreading it all day.
Things a lot of kids are like, oh, sweet, I get to watch Freddie.
I would just be dreading it the entire day that I had to watch the scary thing.
I couldn't wait to see it, man.
And shocker and all these movies that now are considered terrible. I was like I can't believe I have to watch this scary
All these movies you're saying West Craven's movies are considered terrible shocker. Oh the movie shocker
Yeah, yeah, I read a thing online the other day that said that so must see West Craven movie
I should rewatch it, but I don't agree with that
They all they all did their job when I was a kid and they scared the shit out of me
And I knew I'm gonna watch surfing in the rainbow tonight because I've never seen it
I can't wait to watch it. Craven. I'm craving some Craven. I'm craving some Craven. We miss
you man and Godspeed Pat. The people can follow you where they can follow me on Twitter Vine
Instagram at the Patrick Walsh. If you have comments thoughts on the show you can go through
Fangoria. You can tweet us there. Joe's at Joe Derosa comedy on Instagram and Twitter
and Vine which I never even write. Please do that. Please. You know we've got some
couple iTunes reviews but we're a new podcast. So you know if you can review us or whatever
you want to do help us stand out from the pack that would be great. We hope you like
us. Hope you have a good time. Those of you tweeting at us all the time. We really
appreciate it. It makes it exciting for us to do it as opposed to yes you know going through
the motions. It's very fun. Thank you for doing that. Leave a nice
review if you would on the iTunes page there. You've been listening to will. Oh and we'll
be at the mile high horror festival. Yeah. First weekend of October this Sunday of
that festival. We will be doing a live details to come. They told us what we're going to
be doing but I don't want to confirm. Yeah. I don't have the official OK that we
It sounded very cool. So we got to make sure that's a thing.
Yeah. But it's very, very cool. And we're doing a live podcast with a movie, of course,
and something that will make you horror fans quite happy.
Denver Mile High Film Festival, Horror Festival. That's Sunday, October 4th.
Festival's all weekend. But our thing is the Sunday.
Our thing is Sunday. We'll have time and all that coming soon.
You've been listening to We'll See You in Hell, a presentation of Fangoria Podcast
network produced by Thomas DeFeo and executive produced by Ken Hanley of
Vangoria Entertainment for press opportunities advertising inquiries
and information about we'll see you in hell contact Ken via his email Ken
at vangoria .com thanks folks we'll see you next time in hell thanks guys