Summer is here and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer or check out
our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz.
Only available at Bed MDM Casino.
Spin on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp,
Raken Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bed MDM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bed MDM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
Bed MDM game sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bedmgm .com for T's and C's, 21 plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania, and West Virginia
only. Games may vary by market. All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as non -mustrable site credit slash bonus bets unless otherwise provided in
applicable terms. Rewards subject to expiry. Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamber.
The football season is full of guarantees and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good. With the fanatics game day guarantee every single
game day from now until October. If your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan
cash. If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan
cash. Guaranteed. Switch to fanatic sportsbook. Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 plus. Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamber. Offer not available in all states
terms apply. See fanatic sportsbook up.
Starbings on the...
Welcome to Will See You in Hell.
No, it's the podcast you turn to when you need a little bit of the inside info on your
genre, films of preference.
My name is Joe DeRosa, my name's Patrick Walsh, and I don't know the people do come
here for the insider info, but here we are.
We dish the dirt, we do dish the dirt, wouldn't you say, from time to time.
Yeah, what's going on, Joe?
Pat, I mean, I'm much better moved than I was in last time.
Okay.
I'm excited to talk about the movie we're talking about today.
Lightmaster, colon, the littlest rike.
Right.
Life is pretty good.
Okay.
That's all you can ask.
At least for today.
Okay, yet I have an insatiable yearning to go out and immediately drink all day.
You know, I have a drink and sometime, not me, not that long, it's driving over here like
I can have a drink now at 11 o 'clock.
Maybe we have an afternoon cocktail.
Maybe we do.
After the show.
You know, it's fine.
You know, once you get into that zone where you kind of get work done even though you're drinking
sure.
Probably not the best zone to be in, but no, not a bad zone either.
I've written all my best stuff with a drink in me.
Why do you have those pictures out?
What pictures for Joe's movie corner?
What are you saying?
The deep movies, you mean?
Yeah.
I think you meant like literal pictures.
No, I have these out because so I heard from Matt McCarthy, our friend Matt McCarthy and
listen to We Watch Wrestling if you don't already.
It's him and Vince Averill, another dear friend.
He texted me yesterday and he goes watch the movie seconds and I go, yeah, I've been meaning
to.
I have the blue ray and he goes, yeah, I fucking gave it to you.
And I was like, you did because I had a really distinct memory and I still have it of
our friend John coming to the party, Vince and I had at the roost.
John Fulton.
Yeah.
And handing me this, that seems unlikely.
Well, he was at the party.
Yeah.
For some reason, I remembered him giving me this, you might have been drinking.
I was drinking, but it was Matt that gave me it.
I go, I go, Matt, it's weird.
I have this weird memory of my friend John handing me that movie in the middle of a birthday
party we were having at the roost and he goes, it was me.
I handed you the fucking movie at the roost.
He gave it to you like you should watch this and give it back to me or yeah.
No, he gave it to me as a gift.
Okay.
He said he bought it for me.
I think he bought it used because it was unwrapped, which is fine.
I'm not knocking.
And he's checking in to see if you've seen it.
He was like, he was kind of like, have you watched it yet?
I want to talk to you about it.
I own it.
That's a criterion.
Yeah.
If I saw it, I was a child.
I don't know that I've ever seen it.
I've never seen it, but apparently it's pretty great.
And so yesterday that happened.
And also yesterday I was on Doug Benson's food podcast, which you can listen to the episode,
by the way, he talks about food.
Well, it's pretty great.
You get to go to a restaurant and the chef from the restaurant cooks for you.
And you get like an awesome meal for free because you're doing a podcast.
And the restaurant's like shut down for Doug Benson?
They don't shut it down, but he, I guess he tends to go in before they open or whatever.
This place didn't open till five, so we went in at like three.
The podcast is called Dining with D in K, Doug and his friend Karen hosted it, had three
different people tell Doug that I would be perfect for Doug loves movies each time.
You've brought it up many times.
It doesn't go away.
I mean, he'll have some fucking trash on that show, not your boy P. Walsh.
He's my buddy.
I'll talk to him.
I don't need you to talk to him.
Let me see what I can do.
You've already tried.
You can't do anything.
You never seem not open to the idea, but I wouldn't take it personally.
I do.
I take everything personally.
Okay.
Can I finish my story now?
Yes.
I thought surely it was done, but no, no, I didn't know we were talking about your bookings.
No.
Anyway, I'm the best podcast guest.
Nobody ever asked me to be on a podcast.
Well, they tend to usually just ask, you know, stand -ups and actors, I feel like, they get
asked the most.
Never see Rodi's season one episode nine.
And believe it or not, I have it.
No.
I've done both stand -up and acting.
And I'm a Vail.
Tech of a Hell.
Anyway, during the podcast, we were talking about Mel Brooks.
I said, what is your favorite Mel Brooks movie because we were talking about how perfect
young Frankenstein is.
And he said, after young Frankenstein, it's the 12 chairs.
Wow.
And I said, I never saw that one.
And he goes, it's pretty great.
And it's different.
And it's kind of sad and blah, blah, blah, blah.
And I was like, you know what?
I have that on my Blu -ray set.
I'm going to go watch it.
What sold me on watching it is the Dom Delewese is one of the stars.
And I didn't know that.
And in a sad twist, he actually breaks the 11th chair when he sits on it.
That's why they need 12.
He breaks me.
They have to.
You could have had that joke on your podcast, Doug.
I have a longer, thicker Jesus, penis than you.
And also version of that Mel Brooks box set.
And I got it for like 30 bucks on Amazon.
It's got 12 of his movies or something.
Yeah.
Well mine, is yours the Blu -ray one?
It's that, but it's in a bigger case.
Okay.
Yeah.
And I have seen everything on it except the 12 chairs
because you never hear anything about it,
but I'll check it out too.
Apparently as it was explained to me yesterday,
the producers was this huge hit.
Yes.
And the follow up, he decided to do this sort of something different
with the success, which is what a lot of people do.
And then people go, this sucks, dude, do the other thing.
And then you just go back to the other thing.
You just, you do what the strokes did.
Second one you do is the exact same thing.
Third one, you mix it up a little bit.
Third one.
And then you never return to glory ever again.
First one, you're not ready to be like taking huge risks.
You finally, you got in, people like what you're doing.
Give it to him again.
That's my, that's my, well, sometimes it works.
Like people like to kid A.
Well, that wasn't the first one.
It was their ninth album.
Yeah, but I just mean like terrible example.
Well, actually, no, well, then here's a great example.
The bends.
Yeah.
Pablo Honey, nothing like the bent.
True, but Pablo Honey had one hit.
It was not a massive album.
It wasn't like the strokes first album.
Oh, I would say it was bigger than that.
That was pretty fucking big, dude.
A million percent, no.
Really?
Pablo Creep was a big song.
The album itself, not that big.
The bends was getting bigger, and of course, okay, computer even bigger.
I would say they're further down the same path.
Okay.
We don't have to fight about this.
It's not a fight.
I also, I've made several people very angry by admitting I prefer the strokes to radio.
Um, I actually give the strokes, and I love radio.
I give the strokes way more shit than they deserve.
I like the strokes.
I like every one of their albums to be honest.
I even like that last one.
The only thing they put out that I didn't really like was that EP.
Uh, they really liked it, but I hear you.
It was just kind of like, it just felt like this is leftovers, but I'm a little cluttered.
I mean, Casablanca's, at some point, started putting way too much shit on every song.
I love the first half of his first solo album, but the, uh, the voids albums are unlistable.
Yeah.
I don't, I'm not a big fan of those records.
Um, I like, uh, but I got to tell you, I prefer them to radio.
Go ahead.
Radiohead, to me, is okay computer and then a mixtape after that of the other albums.
Like, uh, there is not another radio and album besides okay computer that I will put on
start to finish.
I think Ben's an okay computer or amazing, okay, computer that fitter happier is like a rap
sketch.
You hear it once you never want to hear it again.
I think they should have left it off, fitter happier, prettier.
Uh, I've never not skipped that.
And you know, all the other ones I, I can listen to, but they, they kind of fade more into
background music.
The one that you could pay what you want in rainbows, I think is a great pop album.
I love it.
It's different than their other shit.
In rainbows is another one I would pick up.
I, I have to admit, I'm wrong on that.
Okay.
So in rainbows, and I would also rock the bends pretty much for that, you know, and I'm going
to put these on my amoeba list.
But people who are like, oh, their best work is a moon -shaped pool or whatever, you,
you be in a fucking loser, a moon -shaped pool sucks.
Who says that?
By radiohead standards, by anybody's standards, and it's not like, oh, I miss the guitars,
moon -shaped pool is not a good album, guys.
What a, people say it, people are like, oh, the, you know, the weirder they get the better,
but nobody, nobody should love a moon -shaped.
The one I hated most was that fucking, in the Abneziak or whatever.
Amnesiac ain't great.
It's a, it's a, it's a B -sides of kid A album, basically, but they get, they fight it on
themselves.
You know, they, they just get inducted into the rock and roll hall of fame, and I can't
wait to watch this one.
It's the cure.
It's, you know, radiohead, it's, it's all kinds of great outfits.
Janet Jackson, rocksy music, who I deeply love, and they said they only had the two guys
who aren't Johnny Greenwood and Tom York go to the ceremony, the bassist and the drummer,
or the only two that went, and they had a little interview, and we're like, you know, it's
a difficult band to be in, you know, it's not often a lot of fun, but you could tell they
were just like, guys, we want to fucking go to the rock and roll hall of fame, and Tom
York was like, no love, and snorted a snake into his nose.
And then the other one did some opium, and then passed out, but like, it must suck to
be like the, the, the great, he's a great bassist, the guy in radiohead, but just to be like, guys,
there's always one or two bands are like, we're cool in the rock and roll hall of fame.
Just go.
He's also, the other guy's also a great drummer, and then every other record, York is like,
it's the machine this one may, yeah, you know, exactly.
You could program the box.
Exactly.
God.
Did you see, I saw radiohead live.
I've seen him many times.
With Pete Holmes.
He was opening.
Pete Holmes was opening.
Yeah.
He was in the band.
Okay.
He was sitting.
He was a session pianist.
Okay.
I know.
We saw them live at the, what's the big, what, Bonero is it in, in, yeah, Bonero, the one
in Tennessee.
Bonero?
Yes, Tennessee.
Yeah.
So we're at the Bonero Festival.
We're there to do comedy, Rocky, who kind of orchestrates a huge part of the festival and
is a very close and old friend of mine.
She's able to usually, if you're there performing, get you like super VIP, like, you know, whatever
standing for like the big shows.
Right.
So she gets us into radiohead in this like private little pan area, close to the stage,
standing room still.
We're next to a free, you know, an open bar.
Yeah.
Basically our own bar, right.
And we're watching this thing and we still left early.
It was the best case scenario ever, to ever see any concert we still left early because
it's just like, it's York jerking himself off, you know, he's up there.
He's got the piano facing the opposite direction, like the back of the stage.
He's like looking into a big mirror so you can see his face.
They're doing all this fucking drum machine, horse shit, you know, and then finally, like,
at the end of the set, they play fitter Android, whatever the fuck that song's called Android.
Yeah.
Which is a great tune.
But also isn't out of all the songs of theirs that wouldn't translate as well live as others.
That's one of them.
Yeah.
Because it's such a produce.
There's so much studio shit in that song.
Sure.
And you're just like, oh, fuck this, man, you know, you can't, you can't give me black
star.
Really?
Yeah.
I haven't seen him recently, but I did see him a bunch back in the day, and I honestly
prefer the strokes of the live band, too, and radiohead are great live.
Did you see Robert Smith being interviewed at the Rock and Roll of Fame, one of the greatest
clips?
No.
Now, the cure, I saw them on that last tour live three times.
Each was a three -hour, completely different show.
The cure is a band I've always liked a lot, particularly the singles, but holy shit, they're
amazing.
And if they tour again, you should see them.
But, they're walking out Robert Smith and the cure, Robert Smith at this point is, you
know, 55 or something, just as cranky.
And he comes out, and there's this 25 -year -old perky entertainment report, and she's like,
oh, MG, it's the cure, it does this big intro as they're walking up to her.
And Robert Smith is looking at her like, he's going to punch her in the face.
And she keeps going like, oh, this is such an exciting day.
I love the cure.
He has an eaten in seven minutes, he's hungry.
She goes, are you as excited as me about the cure being ducked into the Rock and Roll
of Fame?
And he is eyes open wide, and he goes, well, judging by that reaction, no, I'm not.
Like with just dripping with disgust, just like, how could anyone ever be that excited?
It's hilarious.
I urge you to see the clip.
I'm sure I messed it up.
Watch the, you should watch this.
So when MTV was new, Zappa did on Halloween night, a live broadcast concert on MTV, because
Zappa's Halloween concerts in New York were legendary, they would do like five nights, right?
It was like crazy.
So MTV, and he just played Monster Mash, right?
Yeah, yeah, the entire time, yeah, yeah, on a glockin' spiel, and so MTV did a
broadcast, live broadcast of the concert one year.
And he's backstage with one of those fucking vapid VJs they had, you know, at one point,
and she's like, I want you to have a good show, Frank.
And man, he gets, because he had just left Warner Brothers and some nasty dispute.
And he's like, can you, and he goes into camera?
Can you believe a person that works for a company owned by Warner Brothers just told me
to have a good show on Halloween?
How dare you?
And she's like, I don't understand why you're mad.
And he's like, bark like a dog, hop up and down on one leg, he gets real like this, to the
point where you're like, why did you agree to do this?
Yeah.
I'm not condoning it, but it is, I just like watching anything where a person is freaking
out and having a meltdown.
Of course.
I enjoy it.
You know, it's, it's gone are the days when you can tell a woman to bark like a dog on
national television.
That's not bring gender into it.
Well, either way, it's not, not great.
No, yeah, those, right, but you, you're saying those were the days.
This is your like opening to all the family.
Those were the day, yeah.
Would you can tell a woman to bark like a dog?
Let's, if I may, get on with the show and at the same time with the Joe, I've been weary.
Were you doing Old Man River?
No.
It's out of like Old Man River.
I said you're right up.
You could have launched into all the family.
Yeah.
I could have done a lot of things.
Pat's staring out a window with a cigarette right now.
Let's talk Pat's movie corner.
Let's get over there.
Let's do it.
I have just an appalling amount.
All right.
Well, do three.
And I'll do three.
Okay.
By the way, I took some freedom this morning.
I'm like shaking right now.
I'm so amped.
There's a lot of pills that do that.
I'm taking something called aja guaya for positive mood, something like that.
Aja guaya guaga.
Is it lined up a bit?
A bit.
But I used to take something called log 9 or something that you're supposed to take it on
an empty stomach and it's kind of like a low level cocaine dose.
That's kind of what creatin is like.
It's like the high without any of the bad part, but I also drink a bunch of cold brew.
I think I may.
There's your mistake.
Yeah.
I'm real jittery right now.
Anyway.
Anyway, I saw a movie that I loved when I was a kid, probably the first like independent movie
I saw when I was a kid called True Stories.
The only film directed by David Byrne, I've been on a real talking heads kick, stop making
sense.
I've always, I mean, since I was a kid, I've been on a talking heads kick, but I was like,
let me see this movie.
It was released on Criterion.
I've clutched onto my out of print DVD for many, many years.
True Stories is a pretty amazing movie.
I don't know how it would appear to a new viewer.
It's like one of the first performances of John Goodman who's got a very large part in
it.
It was written by David Byrne, Beth Henley, and Stephen Tobalowski, who is Ned Ryerson,
also appeared in an episode of Cool Kids.
And to tie it all in, he told me a story about how he is the reason radio head is called
Radio Head, and it involves this movie.
And he's right.
Really?
So, the story is, and that Tobalowski, I'm sure would love this story, he's an amazing
storyteller, being told, but he was dear friends with David Byrne.
David Byrne was like, I want to do this movie called True Stories.
It takes place in a small town in Texas.
It's going to have talking heads, movies.
Here's a bunch of photos, write a script about this.
And he was like, okay, a little confused.
But he eventually, at a party with David Byrne, told him that he can sort of hear people
from beyond.
He can pick up signals from the dead and stuff.
Sure.
And he's like, I don't like to do it.
This is Tobalowski talking.
I don't like to do it, and still, I don't often do it, but once in a while, I'm just
a guy that picks up those frequencies.
And I did it, and I really freaked him out.
And the next day, he came back and played on acoustic guitar, a song he had written about
me called Radio Head.
And the song is prominently featured in True Stories.
I used to obsessively listen to the Talking Head's True Stories soundtrack, which is really
one of their weakest albums, but still great.
And Radio Head is kind of the big rock song.
It's a great one.
All right.
And sure enough, Radio Head was called On a Friday.
They were like, we're not going to go anywhere with On a Friday.
I still say Radio Head would not be a big band if they had kept their name on a Friday.
We would not know about that.
It's a terrible name.
And they were like, let's change it.
Tom York loved this Talking Head's album, Radio Head, called the band Radio Head.
Tobalowski is the inspiration for that song.
Anyway, the movie is a collection of set pieces.
They go to a fashion show and there's people dressed in insane fashions.
Even when I was a little kid, I would show it to my friends and we used to laugh hysterically
at this.
There's a guy in a grass tuxedo.
There's a one with a 40 -foot tall thing in her head, and it's making fun of fashion.
The songs are great.
These little set pieces are very bizarre.
There's one that's like a karaoke bar, but everybody's lip -syncing wild, wild life,
which was a big Talking Head's hit.
I remember that.
Good.
Good, wild, wild life.
Yes.
Goodman is probably like 30.
It's pre -Rozant, even.
He's so sweet and so funny in the movie.
It's like this guy who's just looking for love.
It's kind of about tabloid culture.
It's kind of lightly mocking small -town culture.
I think it was an influence on waiting for Guffman.
I think it was an influence on like Twin Peaks, and I think it's just a pretty incredible
movie.
It's an early 80s independent, like it's 85, 86, a couple years after stop making sense.
I urge you to check it out.
They just released a criterion version, and it's awesome.
It comes with a CD copy of the soundtrack, so there you go.
You reviewing this movie or pitching it.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'll check it out.
Nobody has seen it.
It's a great one to recommend.
It's weird, but it really rewards your attention, and it's got some big laughs in it.
So the video for Wild Wild Life is just an excerpt from that movie, right?
Yes.
Okay.
And there's other things that are, it's kind of like got a UHF structure when they do the songs.
So like in some cases, they have, you mean they're spoofs, right?
No.
Well, they'll have performers do the songs that they, that talking head sing on the album, but
also sometimes they'll just have a music video in the middle of it.
So I hear my two pitches for Weird Al talking head spoofs.
Yes.
My old, my old life.
That's okay.
Or wild, wild wife.
That's probably, it's probably better.
I think the first one is more weird out, where he would sing like about everything just
being like, you know, I've got a mild, mild, yeah, yeah, I think you might be right.
Anyway, I was on an airplane and I watched a documentary called Searching for Igmar Bergman.
Great documentary.
Okay.
Never heard of it.
It's about, as you can imagine, Igmar Bergman.
It's, you know, it's, here's what I liked about it.
It's an analysis of the man and his work.
That's it.
They interview people that worked with him.
They interview people that worked for him.
They interview some of his children and they get right to what you want to hear about.
This is what this movie was and this is what the analysis of this movie is and this is
what this guy has meant to cinema and this is kind of what he was like privately.
They don't waste any time with the boring shit nobody cares about, you know, where he was
born, you know, none of that stuff.
They get right into what you want to hear.
I really, really enjoyed it.
Enjoyed it.
Excuse me.
Right.
I'm embarrassed to say I've never seen an Igmar Bergman movie which I thought I had, but I
guess I'd never have.
So I look forward to perusing his catalog now.
And you know, as you'd expect, he was a complicated guy.
He was very flawed, but he was also very brilliant.
And it was just a fascinating watch and the part that made me cackle out loud on the plane
was he was sitting with two of his children.
He was like one of these guys have like a kid with nine kids, everyone with a different
mom.
And he's sitting with two of his children and he's like, you know, at the end of his life
and he's going, I missed the actors, I miss my actors, I miss my actors.
Right.
Wow.
That's rough.
Yeah, his daughter goes, you know, dad, for once it'd be nice if you just said, I miss my
children and I miss my grandchildren.
And he goes, but I don't holy shit.
That's about right.
Yeah.
It's what, as I said, it's what you'd expect.
But I bought the amazing Igmar Bergman Criterion box set, which is 37 of his movies on Blu -ray
and a giant book.
I'm thinking of buying it.
Is it worth buying?
It looks beautiful, but as you can imagine, I have not watched one movie on it.
Well, I will.
That's why I didn't get it.
Here's the thing.
It's 200 bucks.
It's a steal.
You can get it cheaper, but yeah.
It's 200 bucks for 37 Blu -rays of his, of all of his movies.
And you know, oh, what a deal.
And then you go, then I'm the same way you're, I go, I don't need the whole fucking set.
Buy two and see if you like it and then buy more.
But then you put a buy one and one is 35 dollars.
If you're going to get into Bergman, you buy this, the set, but like it's sitting right next
to my Werner Herzog set, which as I can see, yours is also still wrapped.
Yep.
Unwrapped.
Well, I do, and I have all the time in the world.
I should sit down and like get cracking and I want to.
And next to the Herzog is the Herschel, what's his face?
Herschel, Gordon Lewis.
Yeah.
Watch maybe two of those since I got it.
Had to have it.
Both of those were my two different years.
Both of those things were my big gift for my mom, where it's like, mom, if you, I really
want this box that I have to have it.
But Tower Heist is open.
Tower Heist is no longer my collection.
Oh, okay.
Shamed it out of me at this point.
What was the movie we saw the other day that you told me had the same twist as Tower Heist?
Oh, spoiler alert, dragged across Conqueror.
The end is very similar to the end of Tower Heist.
I'm sure heavily influenced by Tower Heist.
If you want, it's, it's a very similar ending, a poor woman opening a box of gold.
Right.
That was gifted to her by a criminal, you know, all right, Bergman, check out the dock.
I saw, you know, when I saw, I feel pretty.
Oh, God.
It's during Amy Schumer.
No masterpiece, but funny and entertaining.
Really?
I mean, nothing against Amy.
It just looked like a terrible fucking movie.
I thought it looked so misguided, so miscalculated, so mean to overweight women.
And that was really just a bad trailer.
And that's what I basically I saw it on HBO or something, and I was like, I don't know.
And I had heard enough people say, this thing's actually pretty good.
It's pretty funny.
And they're right.
It's, uh, rom comms are essentially not made anymore.
They just don't get made.
So it was kind of nice to see.
The love interest is, uh, Rory Scoville and the picture is stolen.
I would say by Michelle Williams, who I have never seen attempt comedy.
I did not know she was in it.
And she was awesome as like a really vapid, uh, magazine editor.
Okay.
Um, kind of a parody of Gwyneth Paltrow and like, or goop phase.
Well, that's also like how Tilda Swinton was like the funniest person in, in, uh,
train man wreck.
It's very similar.
Yeah.
And, uh, Michelle Williams is great in it.
You know, it's not, uh, it's not amazing, but if you're finding on HBO and you're hungover,
I bet you'll have a nice time.
It's got a good message to, um, I dug it.
I'm going to sneak in one more.
The oath, Ike Baronholz, Tiffany Haddish.
Oh, yeah, that looked funny.
Um, it's okay.
The title is misleading.
That sounds like a real dark like, you know, thriller or something, but it's a, well, it is
a real dark thriller.
It's, it was clearly inspired by the purge, but basically in a Trump -like society, everybody
wants, it's kind of a twilight zone type premise.
Everyone wants, uh, you to sign this oath, pledging your allegiance to the president, which
is something that could very easily happen.
And this is a guy who's on Twitter all day.
He's angry all day.
You definitely know this guy.
You might be this guy.
The Baronholz character who also wrote the movie, his wife, Tiffany Haddish, is more laid
back.
And he's bringing in sort of his, uh, more close -minded family for Thanksgiving.
And it leads to a lot of fights and actually some violence and so forth.
Um, it had a 70s feel like one of those, like, really angry 70s, low budget, comedy satires.
It's not quite there.
It doesn't quite click, but there's a, again, there's enough to recommend it.
I don't like a, uh, what's that movie called with Charles Grodin that Ben Stiller remade?
Heartbreak Kid?
Yeah.
Kind of like a heartbreak kid.
Because that original heartbreak kid is dark, man.
I absolutely love the original heartbreak kid with Grodin.
It's an amazing movie written by Elaine May.
The, um, you know, it's not like that because this is very political.
But I guess my only frustration with it is it was so juicy, you know, like all these
different viewpoints coming home for Thanksgiving and leading to an argument should be a lot sharper,
I guess.
But it's entertaining.
All right.
Uh, I watched, uh, Creed II, finally, cruise control on an airplane, uh, man, I'm a,
I'm a sucker for the Rocky movies, but this movie sucks.
Uh, it's just not good.
It's, it's, I think sucks is too strong, but yeah, it didn't work for me either.
It's just, it's just poorly written.
It's poorly executed.
You've seen the story so many times at this point, um, you know, the fight that the guys
not supposed to take, it's, it's just, it's just so fucking worn at this point.
It needed, this was a time for them to do something like what they did with Rocky V.
I think where you bring a new twist into it.
Yeah.
You know, or mask the idea of him not fighting a little more, um, I just didn't buy the
setup.
I didn't buy that this fight was able to be pulled off.
I didn't buy that he was roped into it so easily, uh, that he was such a sucker for the
game.
Uh, you know, I didn't buy him having the fallout with, with, um, Rocky at the beginning of
the movie.
Yeah.
That's all the Rocky stuff did not work.
I didn't buy any of it, um, yet end of the movie cried like a fucking baby when, when
Rocky shows up at his grand daughter's house.
Yeah.
Cause the whole time I'm like, why do they have him at odds with his son?
Like Rocky Balboa was all about him reuniting with his son, right?
And then his son is in his corner, literally in the corner in the match.
And I'm like, why are they doing this whole he had a falling out?
And then finally at the end of the movie, I'm like, Oh, here's why.
So they could tear jerk these, these, these, the, the, you get me going with the waterworks
and, um, he, they got me him showing on me like, um, you grab, uh, you know, well, I really,
it was really nice, but that was the only part I liked.
The whole premise was flawed to me.
It's like if, I mean, my dad ain't Rocky, but if my dad fought somebody and lost, I wouldn't
then want to beat up his son like everything about it is just kind of not that satisfying.
There was a way, look, there was a way to do it.
I mean, you want to talk perfect timing.
Yeah.
Rocky for was a smash success because we were, it was during the Cold War.
Yes.
And Rocky became a symbol for America and Drago was, was, you know, a symbol for the enemy.
And it was, I mean, people were losing their fucking minds over that movie.
And then the fact that Creed dies in it, like, there was a lot of stuff that made people
love Rocky for.
Talk about a perfect set up.
Spoiler alert.
They start doing this, this offshoot called Creed.
It's time to do a sequel.
What do we do?
Well, we're at odds with Russia again.
Right.
It's exactly 30 years later.
It's like everything was so perfectly set up.
They just didn't execute it right.
Like, they made a lot of wrong turns and twists that just didn't need to be there.
I agree.
Even a very simple point at a point, we're going to Russia, we're going to fight this guy.
We need the money.
It's going to be what makes you like, but here's the thing.
There's a lot to risk here, like, and, you know, but they just, they just really muddied
up.
I think a lot of times they rush the shit.
But we, like, when you got a hit and Creed was a movie where like, they took their time
getting that right and you could tell because that movie works like gangbusters, but sometimes
you try to rush into the second one and you get very diminishing returns.
This did not feel ready to shoot to me personally.
Well, also too, the thing, there was like this, this sort of gag going about how his light
on his house was out.
Right.
Or like, the lamp posted in front of his house was out and he was like, you know, they
keep referencing the light being out and then there's a scene where still owns on the phone
with the city like, oh, it's a jager light bulb.
But again in Rocky Balboa, the woman that he's like befriending has the same problem and he fixes
it.
Yeah.
And it's like this really great moment where you see like Rocky, he's like a guy that gets
his hands dirty and, you know, it just was contradicting so much shit that they had already
set up.
Yeah.
It frustrated me.
But anyway, I'm not upset.
I saw it.
No, I'm glad, you know, but I think it's, it's got to end.
That's it.
Don't do it.
They'll do another one.
My last is I rewatched all that jazz.
Oh, that's one that I've got in the fucking somewhere down there directed by Bob Fawsey.
I just started watching Fawsey Verden, which is the Sam Rockwell, Michelle Williams again.
How is it?
It's super entertaining.
I love all those feud and I love the Hollywood history stuff that Ryan Murphy does a lot.
Rockwell is so great and Williams is so great.
I look forward to seeing that.
It's really entertaining.
It suffers a little bit from that thing of like he'll be talking to somebody and then be
like, but you're Peter Bogdanovich, the biggest director in all of Hollywood.
And you're like, all right.
You have to sort of do that to some extent because the people don't look exactly like them,
of course.
Is there a thing where he'll be like, I'm just stumped.
I have no ideas.
And then somebody goes, go to your favorite place and he goes to Times Square and he sees the
42nd Street side.
And then he hear the, no, that doesn't happen, but might as well.
It's well done.
I've only seen the first one.
I'm excited to watch the second, which is always a good sign.
But I watch Star 80, which I discussed on here, I think.
But to me, a lost masterpiece of the 80s, one of the best films of the 80s, one of the darkest
most disturbing films.
And this Bob Fossy, who I just thought of as a musical guy, clearly had all kinds of issues
and anger and disgust with Hollywood, real true disgust.
And that movie is taking it to its absolute extreme to the point where I don't think a lot
of people would be able to watch the last half hour of Star 80.
It's very intense.
However, all that jazz, which came out in 79, a few years prior, every bit is good, a
best picture nominee, very dark movie.
And he's just telling his own story.
It's about a director played by Rob Scheider, who's clearly Bob Fossy.
He is working on Lenny, the Dustin Hoffman Lenny Bruce story throughout the entire movie,
but they pretend it's not Lenny.
Same thing he doesn't star 80, where he has this guy who's basically Hugh Heffner, this guy
who's basically Bog Donovich.
And it just, by slightly changing them, it's able to just make them into the monsters that
you know they were in real life.
And God, he's got an axe to grind.
In this movie, the axe is a lot at himself, but a lot of it's at the business too.
And he's trying to basically get a Broadway show off the ground and finish editing his movie
while basically having a piled out nervous breakdown drinks too much, does too many pills.
He's got heart troubles.
Roy Scheider is off the charts in this fucking movie.
If you've ever been like, boy, the guy was in jaws and nothing else.
Hey, you're wrong.
But he's incredible in many other things, including this movie.
And maybe his best performance.
To me, the biggest laugh I've had in a long time, and I'm glad my wife is out of town,
and I was home alone, so she didn't see the true darkness of this moment.
But the movie ends spoiler alert.
This is a man making his own story.
The movie ends with Bob Fawsey being zipped up in a body bag.
This is the final scene of the movie.
They basically thump him down on a slab, zip him up in a body bag with just complete
lack of regard for his well -being.
And then the credits roll to, there's no business like show business.
I was howling laughing at how fucking dark that was.
Magic.
And this movie, especially if you're in my mindset of like, fuck this business.
Many people talk in this movie about how fucked up and disgusting the entertainment industry
is.
But this is a man who at the end of his career had so much disgust and hatred in his heart
that these movies really play gangbusters today.
All that jazz is easily one of the best movies of its time, and I urge you to check it out.
All right.
Speaking of pill -induced nervous breakdowns, well, sorry, I am fucking jacked, man.
Well, you're not really bringing the heat on the podcast.
You keep talking about being jacked, but listen, I'm not seeing them.
I'm catering right now in a state of paranoia where I, that kind of talks, not going to do
anything.
No, I'm kidding.
You're doing a lovely job.
I think I need to have a, do you want to, do you want a little taste, do you want a little
pop or something?
Yeah, I do.
Just to slow it down.
Why not?
It's 12 -11.
Well, you want to go do it and I'll do it.
Let me do a couple more.
No, no, no.
I got to last, well, I got to last one.
And I got to scream it in.
We got to get to it.
Get to it.
We still got to review the movie.
I don't got much to say about littlest right from me.
I'll wait to, I'll wait to go get it.
My last movie is I rewatched Raging Bull.
I did too.
Great.
Yeah, well, we talked about it and you said, you know what, I'm going to rewatch that as well.
The honestly, similar to all that jazz, they're both like relentlessly grim portrayals of
men who are not your, your standard hero.
It is, I mean, I always knew this movie was fantastic.
I've seen it a few times, but I watched it with a friend who had never seen it.
Yes.
And she was just like jaw on the ground the whole time, like, oh my God, I was like, yeah,
this movie is pretty, it's fun to watch with somebody that's never seen it because you
forget how shocking it is.
Yeah.
Yeah, arguably Scorsese's finest moment, which is a hard, not to me, but I hear you.
The movie is so simple, it's so beautifully shot.
My favorite aspect of it, and I never really picked up on this before, is the slow motion
shots of every time, everybody that Jake Lamata is looking, every time it's from his perspective
it's shot in slow motion.
And my interpretation of that is, this is a very excitable guy.
Everything sets him off.
So when you see what he sees, it's like he sees every little fucking thing that's happening
and is completely focused on it, and that's why he's kind of a lunatic.
But I mean, just toward the force performances by Kathy Moriarty, Danero, and Pesci.
I mean, it's just they are, they, this is people at the fucking top of their game.
Danero from the jump of this, that first sequence with him and his wife, that's a 20 -minute
scene.
I don't know.
And it does, it hits, every famous part of the movie is in that scene where you need the
steak, bring it here, bring it here.
When he flips the table, that is the whole thing with Pesci where he's like hit me in the face.
That's the same where he's saying, you fuck my wife.
Where do you get the balls to ask me a question like that?
I always find that scene to be amazingly acted, but I can't help but laugh because of the
scene where they audition with that monologue and wait for government.
Do you remember that?
It's the guy playing both parts.
It's this like 60 -year -old like bland white dude and he goes, all right, ready to begin?
You fuck my wife?
What?
Where do you get the balls to ask me a question like that?
And they cut over to like Corkeys St. Clair with his eyes wide open, like hilarious.
The, it's just, you know, my favorite part in the movie is, I don't know if it's my favorite
part, but it made me really howl laughing.
Deniro and Pesci have a falling out and their brothers and then over the, did you fuck my wife
thing?
And then Kathy Moriarty tells Deniro, like, you know, you should call your brother and make
he's your brother.
Make amends and he calls him and Pesci answers and Deniro because he can't express any emotion
outside of rage.
Yeah.
Can't, can't say anything into the phone.
He's just silent and then Pesci thinks it's a prank call and he goes, you think this is funny?
Okay.
Mother fuck.
Your mother sucks.
Big elephant cock.
Yeah.
Pesci is incredible in it.
He's amazing.
Deniro is incredible in it.
I mean, it, so to me, it's fascinating as just a character study.
What I love about it is that it's a biopic of a piece of shit who never accomplished anything.
You never see that.
That in and of itself is very original.
And well, he doesn't come.
He does eventually get the belt, doesn't he?
Yeah, but it's, it's not your traditional, like, it's the story of a man's life where you
feel good about it.
How brutal is that scene where he agrees to take the dive to get the title shot and he's
in the fucking blocker.
What did I do when they, when the old guy starts crying too, that almost got to me.
Oh my god.
And when he's beating up the wall, that scene is almost like he got to leave the room where
he just keeps punching the wall.
That was, that was real upsetting.
Yeah.
But everyone has known a guy like that, every guy at their absolute worst, usually early
on in dating because everything hurts so much.
You don't really know how to handle it.
But like, he does some stuff in this that like every guy has known a girl who's been
a relationship with a guy who's like, you know, some guy comes in and says, how are you?
It gives her a hug, walks on to the next person.
And you see him kind of pull her aside and like, wait, what the fuck was that?
Like I've known guys like that.
I know more of them in Missouri for sure, but man, it's gross and it's uncomfortable for
everybody.
And you know that their home life must be a goddamn nightmare.
Just a guy who is so insecure, so, and honestly, very similar again to star 80, I've just
a guy who's way too jealous, way too obsessed.
And that would make if you want to really destroy a weekend, an amazing double feature.
But Rageable, the way it's shot is absolutely incredible.
The reason it is not to me, like a top three even, I prefer taxi driver, I prefer good
fellas, I prefer can't comedy, I prefer casino, is that it's not necessarily telling
a story.
It really is just like a character study of just things happening.
So for me, I wasn't as involved in it, I wasn't as swept up in it, you're just watching
a man behave badly for two hours.
Generally I love that kind of movie, but we're talking about my favorite director of all
time.
Rageable.
Unquestionably a masterpiece, not one of my favorites, but I mean, it speaks to the
town of De Niro, the fact that he carries that movie with so little to do, yes, there's
no real problem.
But I mean, you know, him at the end, like when he's playing the older, even the way he
captures like what a shitty stand up comic would be like, yeah, you got to push me, make
a comeback.
You know, like I'm like, my god, he's fucking nailing this thing.
But he's incredible.
One thing we've talked about on this podcast before is scariest scenes in non horror movies.
Raging Bulls officially made that list, that scene where he's asking Moriarty if she
fucked his brother, and she starts going, yeah, I fucked him.
I sucked all their cocks, like she finally has had enough.
Dick was bigger than yours.
I'm like, it's gonna kill her.
Yeah.
You're just like Jesus Christ, all fucking mighty, like it's so, it's terrifying because you know
he's a maniac.
But nobody's more convincing at maybe going to hit a woman than Robert De Niro.
You look at Jackie Brown with Bridget Fonda.
You look at him throwing Kathy Moriarty to the ground in those movies, like it feels real
every time.
And I have the one where my favorite De Niro acting, I'm almost gonna punch this lady is in
Casino.
Oh yeah.
When he's when Sharon Stone's just shit face in that restaurant, yeah, I'll fuck you, you
fucking prick.
And he's going, listen to me, you, and he hits the table, and you see him choking the
words back.
You like, oh boy, yeah.
What I also love about raging bull is that the entire time, Pesh, he's like, you're crazy.
You're a maniac.
Yo, how can you talk that way to your wife?
You go home into Pesh, he's housed for one minute, and he's like, it passed me to fucking
barbecue sauce.
What the fuck's the matter screaming at his wife?
But like also judging De Niro, it's, there's a lot of extremely dark comedy in raging
bull.
One, one last thing about it too, and it speaks to the tremendous, the tall, tremendous
Pesh, he truly is an actor.
And I think it, honestly, as far as, as big a fan as his people are, Pesh, I don't think
he gets enough credit for being a great actor.
Like he gets a lot of credit for being the fun, tough guy that we all love.
He's a tremendous fucking actor.
That scene where he's got to make up with Frank, which is a Frank Vincent, because he bashed
his head in a car door, you know, or with a car door, and like the mob boss, who's coached
by the way, from cheers, which is hilarious, and he's making them, and he goes, I want you two
boys, and she can't.
And Pesh, he's laughing like a kid that got in trouble.
It's, I'm like, this guy is fucking amazing, man.
Yeah, he's got this attitude of like, hey, it happened, what are we going to do?
And also, I still beats her ass, and I'm still winning, but I'll take your stupid apology.
Yeah, it's weird seeing coach be like, the fuck's with this guy?
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
Again, another tremendous actor, and you watch him on cheers, he's like, he's doing like
the Woody character.
Right.
Anyway, real quick screaming, and real quick, Star Wars Episode 9 trailer is here, you haven't
seen it.
Oh my God.
What is it?
They, they a long time ago, and then they play the music, and then you see it, you go,
ah, then it's over, no, that's probably it, though.
That's some of it.
A flash of a spaceship, look, I'll tell you the things that lit me up in this trailer.
Right off the bat, as soon as the fucking first frame opens, you, it's got eight, you can
tell that Abrams is back in control of this franchise, he's ending this properly.
It immediately feels like Star Wars.
I can't explain that, it's undefinable, but it didn't feel like that with, with the last
Jedi trailers.
This, as soon as it started, I was like, this feels like Star Wars.
And then the thing kicks in and never lets up.
And the thing that got me, the two things that got me the most were Lando, the shot of Lando,
flying the Millennium, falcon again, and it's Billy D. Williams, and he, and he does the
Lando laugh, you know, and I was like, oh, that's such a great setup, because in solo they
make such a big deal about how it was his ship and, and we knew that, but we never
really knew the story.
So to see like it come full circle now, the last time you see Lando, it's Han is dead and
he's flying the falcon again, and he must just be like, the happiest he's ever been.
That's awesome.
And then at the very, very, and then of course the title reveal rides a Skywalker, which
is awesome.
And then at the very end, the last thing you hear is Luke Skywalker's voice over, he said,
nobody's ever really gone.
And then you hear the emperor laugh, and you know that Palpatine is back.
This fucking thing, I think Abrams, and Abrams has sort of quietly sidesteped, or gracefully
I should say, sidesteped around saying, you know, yeah, Ryan Johnson really fucked up the,
what we were trying to do here, because they're like, did you like last shed on, he's like,
I thought Ryan brought his vision to the screen, and it was interesting to start with nothing
for this movie, you know, like, he just, he was, he's basically saying like, I'm going
to do everything that we were supposed to do in the last movie in this movie, and then
also how I wanted to stand.
Right.
So I think it's going to be awesome.
I'm super excited, it's fun seeing the fans excited.
It's just, it's awesome.
I'm, I'm really, I'm really lit up for this thing.
I'll, I'll watch the trailer, I have not yet seen it.
Set up the little, this right, I'm going to pour us two shots.
If you have anything to mix with it, I'd, I'd rather not have a shot to kick, to kick off
my day.
I got ice.
I'm not a retired police chief.
Sorry, excuse me, a police chief who's about to retire, drop a couple of alka seltzer
in my whiskey in the morning.
But any hoot, we are discussing puppet master, the littlest rike.
It is available on shutter and elsewhere.
I was way more excited about this than I normally would have been because it was written by Craig
Zoller, who we discussed last week at length, as we are huge fans of Bone Tomahawk Brawl
in cell block 99 and his latest, I might use the word masterpiece, dragged across concrete.
This is not that.
This is clearly something that he kind of wrote quickly or wrote to kind of launch.
This is Fangoria Studios, Joe I believe you were saying he has some sort of hand in that.
Or maybe he wrote it years ago and it's just getting made now because of his name.
I don't know the backstory, but I've never seen a puppet master, Joe, you can probably walk
us through the history of the franchise better.
I've never seen one of them.
I recognize some of the puppets from the boxes of the old VHS's.
So you went into this thinking it was a chucky film, correct?
I did.
Yeah.
So you were really off set.
Basically the deal is Thomas Lennon, which is surprise casting, but a man I've always loved
and a man who wrote a great book about screenwriting, like screenwriting to make money, check out
his and his partner's book.
I'm a fan.
It's really terrific and funny and helpful.
I call him Tom Lennon.
You should.
You know.
I met Tom Lennon once, like, stunningly nice guy, but in this, he plays a sad sack who
returns home after a divorce.
He's living with his parents at age, whatever he is, 45, he still looks great.
And he finds an old puppet.
He thinks he can sell it at a convention, sort of a, what do you call it?
Let me, let me back, let me pause you there just to give some backstory setup with the franchise.
So this just sort of functions as a direct sequel to the first film, because the first film
opens with Andres Tudor or whatever the fuck his name as I can't remember, who's played
in that film by William.
Is it Hinkley?
Is that the guy?
It's like, William Hickey.
Hickey.
Yeah.
You couldn't hear a dumb truck driving through a nitro glycerin plant.
The blessing.
Yeah.
Amazing in Christmas vacation.
And Pritzie's on her where he was nominated as well.
And William Hickey, I think we've said this on the podcast before, died when he was like,
I thought he was 90 ,000, he was 68 or something, like, clearly a bit of a smoker.
Anyway, do you know his wife in Christmas vacation, the, hey, is your house on five o 'clock?
May Castell.
She was the voice of Betty Boop.
Oh, really?
In all those old cartoons.
That's great.
She kind of looks like Betty Boop.
She does look like Betty Boop.
All right, carry on.
All right.
So, the original film opens at a hotel.
You learn that Andre has, you know, sort of fled from Germany.
There are some Nazi spies after him.
He's got these puppets that he has somehow animated.
He is then killed.
And the puppets sort of avenge his death.
But he was an evil guy himself, like he's got, he had Nazi ties himself for whatever.
So even going back to the original public master, there's Nazi stuff.
Yeah, it opens in like the late 40s or early 50s.
Interesting.
And then it, then it time jumps to the, okay, I did not.
So this movie takes place 30 years later.
It's the 30th anniversary of the murders that took place at that hotel.
Yeah.
They're having a, this is where the first wrong turn of the movie, they're having a convention.
I mean, it's absurd.
You would never do that.
Sure.
But they're having a convention to, you know, to celebrate, not celebrate, but to commemorate,
I guess, the history of this stuff.
And people from all over the world who have somehow acquired these dolls are showing up to
this thing so they can sell these dolls.
That's sort of muddy and never really quite explained like why these people have these dolls
and how they got them and it's all a bit confusing.
But anyway, they're all now in this hotel and the dolls come to life and start killing
everybody.
And they never explain this, but the guy from human centipede, Udukir, he shows up at the
beginning, all burned up and scarred.
And he is the William Hickey character who is still alive because he's immortal or there's
a lot going on here.
They never really explain that.
They never, you know, it's, it's, it's, look, the biggest, so anyway, that catches you
enough up to speed.
The biggest problem with this movie, and I sent this to Pat when I was watching it.
I said, I think Zahler wrote this thing in 15 minutes while I was taking a dump.
It's like, it's just this thing plays like a, as they call it, a vomit pass of a script.
Like, you know, your vomit draft is when you just throw everything out to get it down.
And then you go back and you start sort of restructuring and whatever.
And it's like, this feels like it never had the second or third pass.
But most importantly, I think what makes this movie fail is the direction of it.
I think Zahler is a guy where when he's directing it, he knows how to bring the right quirkiness
out of it.
He knows what his intentions were.
And when it gets passed off to somebody else, it's not going to translate as well.
But on top of that, this movie is just poorly directed.
And then I look it up, it's directed by a team of guys, there is no fucking excuse
for how bad this thing is directed.
They sunk every penny they had into practical effects to have a bunch of glory, spectacular
deaths with lots of blood and guts.
And then you know what, you don't give a shit about any of it because you only see the character
for the first time then they die.
You don't know who any of these people are, you form no relationship with any of them.
And it's shot poorly from a suspense standpoint, from a lighting standpoint.
The whole thing is, it looks like a hallmark movie, it's bright, it's just a bad, it's just
very, very, very poorly done.
You know, I can't disagree.
Udukeer was not in human centipede, that was Dieter laser who looks exactly like Udukeer.
But you've seen Udukeer in a million movies.
You've seen him in Brawl and Sublock 99 and I think he was in direct, he was in direct
across concrete too.
He was in the, remember the back room of that place and I was like, this is the back room?
Oh, that's right.
Yeah.
Well, and that's exactly what I mean.
Like there's that weird scene in the movie and if you haven't seen it yet, they go into
he goes into a clothing store and in the back room of the clothing store is this like boss
hog office.
Right.
It's all like leather bound and you know, and it's weird.
It doesn't really make sense, but Zoller makes it work somehow because he's there and
he's like, guys, I know how to shoot this, it'll make sense.
You buy that guy's like, all right, I'm gonna, you know, operate back here as like a front,
but I'm not gonna live in squalor.
I'm gonna make it a nice off of the white sugar.
So I mean, this has none of those little details at all.
I will say, from everything I know about the puppet master franchise and little clips I've
seen and stuff.
This appears to have better production value than most.
No, I would, I would know.
No.
The first puppet master, in fact, the first two or three, they're, the first one is a movie.
It's a real movie.
Like if you watched it, I mean, it's not the greatest thing in the world, but you'd be like,
yeah, no, this is a legit movie.
I think it was in theaters, you know?
Yeah.
I think they, I, this is like the critters thing, man, where I'm like, Jesus Christ, how did
you dip off in quality even more than full moon usually does?
You know?
Like this is even for full moon, the quality of this thing.
It looks like a web series.
It looks like we shot an iPhone or something.
It did.
I mean, I will say as a guy who knows nothing about the franchise, it felt like it was over
very quickly.
Oh, it's 90, I think it's 89 minutes.
Yeah.
I mean, it was relatively painless.
And the kills I thought showed a lot of creativity.
Yeah.
And we're like admirably, admirably gross and creative.
Like the puppet blasting into that woman's vagina, then bursting out of her womb, holding
the baby hostage, I was like, okay, that's something I haven't seen before.
Very creative kills.
You know, a lot of heads flying up into the air and shit like that.
To me, if you're looking at it, it's back to my porn argument, my porn horror argument.
It's not enough just to have a money shot.
Like there has to be, you got to be burnt rentals.
In boogie nights, you got to be like, I want you to experience it.
I agree.
You know what all that?
Like, you know?
But looking at it as an homage to the 80s school of horror, I thought it held its own amongst
those.
Well, I think if you keep your expectations pretty low, good.
It had widely mixed reviews.
Some were many were calling it hilarious and unbelievably offensive and outrageous.
I mean, it didn't work like that on me.
I wasn't laughing at it.
There's the guy from the new NBC sitcom Abbeys.
I don't know what his name is, but he's kind of Thomas Lennon's sidekick.
And that guy was kind of funny in it.
I mean, he's like, like they ask him one point, like, why do you want to do this?
And he's like, I got six million reasons why I want to do this.
Some of those, you're like, okay, you know, like, yeah, weird.
The opponents are killing Jewish people.
It's not a good look.
Here's a good, but I think I liked it more than you.
It passed the time.
And I think the kills were frequent enough and creative enough that if that's what
you're looking for in this kind of horror movie, you're going to be satisfied.
Here's the thing.
If you're going to make trash cinema, there's still a quality line there to me.
I'm sorry, there is.
Yes.
You got to either be, you know, John Waters or John Waters, okay?
You got to either go, I'm making pink flamingos.
Yeah.
And it is going to be the craziest fucking thing you've ever seen.
And quality of the film isn't going to be way up there.
But boy, are you going to see a lady eat a piece of dog shit on camera?
It's either got to be that or it's got to be hairspray John Waters where it's like,
Hey, man, I'm making fun of the tropes of movies like this.
Right.
And I'm doing it very well.
And it's I'm kind of turning it on its ear a bit to the doing it so well that, you know,
like my sister could watch hairspray and just think it's an awesome musical.
Right.
When she was 10 years old, like she didn't know to catch any of that, but thought it was really funny.
So here's the thing with this movie.
There's, there's some great gore and blood splatter and all that as we said.
But the humor is not there and the parts that are supposed to be funny just aren't funny.
They're not funny because, oh, that's low brow or that's such a bad joke.
It's they're just not funny.
They're not delivered or executed properly.
The dialogue is, this is what I mean about first pass.
I mean, it's terrible.
Like, you know, Tom Lennon comes into his dad's house and his dad's like, he's like, hi, dad.
And he's like, you're a disappointment.
You work in a comic book.
I mean, it's like, guys, Jesus Christ.
Yeah.
Give it a little finesse, please.
Like, you know, it's just not well done.
The most interesting aspect about this movie is the Craig Zahler connection.
I'm going to look into it and see how he came to write it.
I have a feeling they were looking for a writer.
He's like, guys, I'll write this this weekend.
It has that feel to it.
But, you know, there's a reason he didn't direct it.
I think he was like, yeah, I don't have ownership over this thing, but I can get you a usable
script quickly on the cheap.
And maybe he was a big fan of puppet master.
The guy's clearly a fan of exploitation, cinema.
This definitely does not seem like something that had the care and finesse of his other
three movies.
Oh, Jesus, no.
But, you know, they're also consistency issues.
They're consistency where it's like, okay, so here's a movie that went out of their way to
be able to pull off this kill where, again, a puppet crawls inside a pregnant woman's
vagina, then bursts out of her stomach holding a fetus.
Yeah.
Yet, at the end of the movie, when the main lead female character gets her brains blown
out, you see her brains splatter across a car, and then it cuts back to her and her head
is fully intact.
There's another scene where Thomas Lennon's, his thumb gets cut by the doll, and there's
no blood on his thumb, and it's obvious that it's not there.
It's like, it's little stuff like that where I'm like, guys, what are you doing?
Like, and I love Thomas Lennon, but miscast.
You know, you can't.
It was.
It's the Tim Heidecker thing in us.
It's distracting.
I'm not saying he can't pull it off, but it's distracting.
And the same argument could have been made about Vince Vaughn.
There was a time when you say, when you would have said, who's going to buy Vince Vaughn
as a gritty cop?
Well, guess what, in the cell, we didn't buy it because he was still fast -talking whatever
Vince Vaughn.
Right.
There was a period of time that Vince Vaughn had to go through other types of roles, particularly
Brawl and Cell Blocked on the night, for us to then buy him as a potentially crooked police
officer, whatever.
You can't just drop Thomas Lennon.
The last time we saw the guys, his balls are hanging out of his shorts on the arena.
Thomas Lennon 911, you know, has almost never done a serious role.
And good on him.
I think he's a hilarious performer.
That's a good thing they got David Spade in this drama now, where he's playing like
an oil baron.
And it's like, what do you do it?
That kind of thing can work, but it's like he said, like Soderbergh at some point started
casting comedians in small parts.
The informant, which is an amazing and deeply underrated movie, just about every supporting
role is filled by a comic, but it works and he works with them.
I mean, Tom Lennon, again, you want to know how he wound up in this.
Was he a fan of puppet master?
What made them reach out to him?
They clearly, this is thought of as a horror comedy.
I didn't see that really.
But they made some interesting choices all around.
I was I was glad to have Thomas Lennon as opposed to like, you know, some boring generic pretty
boy.
I'll say that.
There are no jokes.
It's like a lot of that.
It's a lot of that kind of like dialogue that's supposed to be funny, but they're, but it's
not funny, because somebody will say something smart and then Tom Lennon will be just go
like, oh, you're such a joy.
Yeah.
And then that's the button on the scene.
And it's like, it's not really a, you mean, yeah, all of television comedy is that just
like just kind of like, oh, okay, I guess that was an attempt.
But yeah, I liked it a little bit more than Joe.
If you're looking for, you know, fun creative kills, relatively painless, I think you could
do worse, but it's hard to recommend.
Puppet Master, the littlest right folks.
That's our show.
Nice, nice heavy up today.
Go to the Patreon if you like and subscribe, because guess what the episode this month is,
pets and materii extravaganza, babe.
So if you're not a Patreon member, you are missing out, but if you're not a Patreon member,
we still appreciate you.
So don't worry.
But, you know, that's, there's some good stuff going on over there.
We will be talking pet cemetery, the book, pet cemetery, the audio book, pet cemetery,
the 89 movie, pet cemetery, too.
And pet cemetery, 2019.
Yes.
And I will be shaking even harder in the next episode because these pills only seem to
be getting more intense.
And you're adding alcohol.
Well, I thought it would slow me down.
Halfway through the string, I realized tequila is also a stimulant.
Yeah.
I've really fucked up today.
I got a, I got a, anyway, Jota Rosa comedy on Instagram.
This drops Monday.
If you're in the Austin, Texas area, I'm at the Moon Tower Comedy Festival all week starting
Wednesday night at Cap City doing the Dudley and Bob kickoff podcast myself and Ron Bennington
are guests.
So come on out to that.
It's going to be a lot of fun.
And I hope to see you there.
I am at the page of Walsh, occasionally on Twitter, occasionally on Instagram.
And that is it folks.
We will see you next time.
We will see you in health.