Hey folks, it's we'll see you in hell, the podcast you turn to when you want to hear
about movies, movies, movies.
My name is Joe DeRosa across from me is Patrick Walsh, who I'm announcing
because he's got a mouthful of tuna.
He's eating out of a bag at the moment.
Yeah.
It's not a great look.
That's why we're not a video podcast, but if you're just going to spoil it.
Um, yeah, I'm eating some chunk light tuna out of a bag.
They come in a serving size, 70 calories, 17 grams of protein.
I mean, come on, you get them on Amazon, $12, 12 packs.
Yeah.
You think about that and it's fish and they ship it to you with no ice.
Right.
A warm bag.
What are you worried about?
Today's fresh.
I ate steak for dinner with some salad and I had ice cream after which I
shouldn't have done, but I did.
What kind of ice cream?
Jenny's dairy free, uh, some sort of chocolate, something or other, you know,
death by chocolate wasn't that one.
But they all have those names.
Like, you know, what a fiasco, you know, whatever it'll be called sex.
Yeah.
It was good though.
My mom would always get like better than sex desserts.
And I was always like, how bad is this woman's sex life?
That's upsetting to hear.
Yeah.
And especially in a house where the word sex was never uttered, but then you'd
see something like that and be like, Jesus, what's going on here?
Yeah.
That's a, that's a lot to hear.
You don't want to hear about your mom.
Your mom's better than sex.
No, you don't.
Um, Joe, what's new been a while as Stan Stan would sing.
Oh yeah.
Stain.
Uh, what is new?
I think he was just in the news stained old Aaron Lewis.
Cause he said something like, I think he was pro Putin.
It was like, yeah, I'm rooting for Putin.
What is going on with the talk of that?
Like, fuck is Fox really going pro Putin?
Or are they just saying the push to be automatically pro Ukraine is whatever.
Like, are they actually coming out and saying that we're pro Putin?
Uh, I don't watch Fox news, but the clips I have seen are just Tucker
Carlson, just full on saying, I don't know why I shouldn't root for Russia.
I'm rooting for Russia.
Like you just full on says it.
What, what do we, why, why though?
I don't understand.
They, cause they gotta be, they gotta be contrary.
Everybody's gotta disagree.
I can't joke.
Can I give you a tip?
Yeah.
Cause your, your internet is starting to garble a little turn your Netflix off.
Cause that's using your internet and you're in the same room as it.
So that's what I do.
Sometimes it jumps in leaps and bounds.
It's off way better already.
What'd you have back then?
Some old civil war documentary?
Uh, I'm watching, uh, I'll talk about it in the movie corner today.
Andy, Andy Warhol diaries, yet another docu series.
Wow.
Diaries of a dead man who wasn't alive to approve his diaries.
Exploited by this up there with the Shanling diaries and then, you know,
yeah, and, uh, Cobain, they released Cobain's diaries and maybe a year
after he killed himself, I remember buying those still on.
Yeah.
So, um, that's what I was watching.
Uh, I'll get, I'll get to it later.
All right.
But, uh, now, now Courtney love only releases their movies for artistically.
Are there Nirvana songs for really artistically significant pieces of work?
Has she released a new Nirvana song?
Like, like the Batman?
No, the Batman did something in the way, but four times in it.
Oh yeah.
I saw that.
Uh, uh, yeah, we're going to, that's next episode.
We're going to talk about the Batman.
The Batman, a lot of people whispered in that Batman, everybody whispering.
We'll get to it.
We'll get, um, I gotta tell you, Joe, this, uh, lady at work, very funny.
And I, she asked what I like to do.
Cause I told her, what should I do in Atlanta?
I'm going crazy up there at the lake.
What movie?
What movie, Joe?
Shining.
No, it's from Fargo.
Yeah.
Never been a big fan.
That's one of the best movies ever made.
Well, it's, it's, it's a quality film.
I don't think it's a bad film.
I just find it very boring for somebody.
Jesus Christ.
Um, anyway, it's a boring movie.
Yeah.
You want Arby's Dan Dan?
You want Arby's?
So funny looking one had the money.
Dan.
Ugh, shut up.
Yeah.
There's, there's also a plot involving multiple murders, kidnapping.
Whittle it down to Arby's Joe.
I find it so boring.
What do you want?
I, it's fine.
You're entitled.
But I go, um, yeah, you know, she was, what do you like to do?
I said, look, to be honest, uh, I like to smoke weed.
I like to drink, you know, I like to have fun and I've been trying
to go straight out here, but frankly, uh, circumstances in my life have made
it so that I need to get out of my head.
Yeah.
She goes, all right.
Follow me, follow her out to the trunk of her car.
She looks me in the eye and goes, closed mouth.
Don't get fed.
Pops the trunk and gives me something called death by gummy bears, a thousand
milligrams, but that's the whole bag.
They're a hundred, a 10 count, a hundred a piece, like a hundred
was an insane amount.
No, I know.
So, uh, I'm very glad I spoke to her, but I took the slightest nibble of one.
So I'm just warning you that I might just start talking on my ass.
Some books I I've been pretty clean here for a while, but that's all falling apart.
No, no, I think it's been falling apart almost from the
beginning of you getting married.
No, not true.
I drinking sure, but I was trying to do a tolerance break of weed.
But then when you return to it, then it's like, uh, when the truth is
called because it takes you right back to where you were when you left off.
You know, it's like they close in on your eyelid or your, what
it wasn't the pupil dilating.
Yeah.
The, uh, yeah, it makes that noise.
Yeah, exactly.
Um, a close shot of somebody throwing Tums into a glass of water for some reason.
There's always one of those.
It's, uh, that's, well, that's how booze is.
You take a little break and then you return and it's like, Oh dear Lord.
You know, see the thing is when you return, I think the idea is that you're
like, Oh God, I didn't miss this.
But each time I return, I'm like, it's like seeing my mother after we, we had
been stripped apart at childhood or something, and maybe that's a bleak
outlook, but that's how it feels.
Just like arms being thrown around me for the first time in years.
That's, that's what I was going to get at earlier.
When you asked what's new.
Yeah.
I was going to say the oblique, very bleak outlook.
Arguably the bleakest it's ever been.
I don't know what's going on.
I'm real woof, woof.
I got to say, I got an e -bike and I ride it around and it's, it
makes me feel a bit better.
And then you're kind of proud of yourself that you did something physical.
And then you realize all you did was zoom around with a motor.
You didn't do anything.
Oh, it's motorized.
Well, it's an E it's an, it's an electric bike.
So it's got the throttle plus the pedal assist, or you can use it as a regular bike.
Are you in traffic with us?
After all you're complaining.
Sometimes.
Well, my complaining is not a people that ride bikes.
My complaining is the people, the entitlement of people that ride bikes,
which I've found since I started riding this bike in the last few days,
I'm a hundred percent right.
All the places that somebody has almost hit me and been a complete cunt about it.
I now ride in those lanes and notice the places where I almost got hit.
It says in huge letters on the side in the bike lane yield to pedestrian.
So it's very rewarding now.
And then today I was a little out of line and I don't know, I was making
a turn or something and I went into the crosswalk or whatever it was.
And, uh, and I stopped and there was a lady there and I said, Hey, I'm sorry.
And you could see the surprise on her face.
Like, I can't believe this person on a bike just apologized.
Yeah.
She was like, Oh my God, it's, it's okay.
And, you know, there was that glimmer of there is humanity.
It was kind of like the end of I am legend.
There was, there was hope for a second, which is a sequel by the way.
Yeah.
I saw.
And Will Smith coming back, even though he died at the end of the show.
Well, let's see an AI.
Is that what they're doing?
It's not, there's no AI in that universe.
Prequel.
No, it was the last one.
Can't be.
Well, then why are they doing it?
DNA?
I don't know.
Apparently he lived at the end, the alternate ending, which
matches the ending of the novel.
Yeah.
Well, I've seen the Omega man, the Chuck Heston version, which I
liked quite a bit, actually.
I think Omega man is the worst adaptation of the book, not the untruist,
but I, of the three that they've adapted.
There's been four.
Yeah.
One's called I am Omega.
I don't even count that that's by like the, the asylum or something, but
the other three I find last man on earth, uh, starting Vincent Price.
And I love, I am legend.
The movie, even though it's not very faithful to the book, I find
it to be a really fun movie.
Yeah.
It's good.
When that dog dies, it's, it's enough to send you to the Jesus God.
Uh, as Michael B Jordan, it's kind of like, wouldn't it be more interesting
to put a woman in there so they could repopulate the earth or I guess I
don't know what they're doing, but
well, there is a woman from the last one.
Oh, okay.
All right.
So as Michael G B Jordan going to be the new, like Will Smith character
or something, maybe it's just another guy, the ghost of Will Smith advises
him like an Arthur two on the rocks when they brought back John, John
Gilgud, you glued.
My sinuses are also going crazy in ways that they haven't in years.
Uh, I'm constantly know it itchy nose, itchy eyes, sniffling, tearing.
You can hear it in my voice when I'm talking.
Uh, it's horrible.
The texts coming my way from you are, are dire, you know, they seem bleak.
Yours aren't any pick me up either.
I got, I wouldn't say so.
I mean, it's, it's just a real depressing time.
It's just a real depressing time.
There's no other way to say it.
Feel like there's just, we didn't need this world war on top of everything else.
We just didn't need it.
I don't think we're going to get it.
I think it's an, I think it's just, I think it's just a, uh, you know, look,
it's, I'm not saying it's not nerve wracking, but I mean, there, if you
follow even remotely with the news, there's a very clear pattern here of
move on to the next thing to panic about.
Oh, sure.
Sure.
It's incredible how quickly, uh, uh, COVID is, has been dismissed, which
makes you wonder how bad was it to begin with, because you're like, this is weird
guys, you guys, right?
Like I, and I've been following the numbers still, the numbers are still there.
You know, like they're way down, but they're still there.
Well, no, lately they're going up and people keep saying like, it's
beginning again, and it's like, none of you fucking know.
But they are going up.
Uh, I don't, I don't know and don't care.
I welcome it.
I, uh, they keep talking about how, when you, you get it, then it's
affecting people's brains in severe ways, like within a year of getting it.
Couldn't be the trapped inside for two years affecting people.
Yeah.
It's like, how do you know they're saying it causes depression and all
this shit and it's like, or was it everything else causing depression?
Yeah.
Or was it the loss of your life savings?
Might be chipping in on the depression of contributed.
That's a funny premise.
COVID taking all the credit and then, you know, your, your life savings being
like, I feel like I chipped in a little bit here, you know, the other, the other
disastrous things ask you like, like, it's like they didn't throw in on the check.
Like, I saw this, um, uh, meme go, I don't know how long the guy went on,
but I saw the first three and was laughing real hard, but it was, it was
what Billy Crystal's jokes would be at this year's Oscars and they, he was
cutting in old shots of Billy with like the Jufro and everything.
And, uh, one of them was like, oh, it was, uh, it started with like,
don't look up and drive my car.
Not only two of the nominated films, but what all of you said
to your chauffeurs tonight.
And, you know, I hope he went on for a very long time, but it was the kind of
bit where I was like, man, I wish I had stolen that for this, for this show.
But I don't even have the man's name to give him credit, but this is a long way
of saying when I saw Billy Crystal in that, like 1989, you know, hairline,
just starting to recede mode.
It took me back to a simpler time.
It did.
It did like just, just a time where he, even he would come out and make, you
know, off -color jokes and everybody just it's Billy and we were all friends.
You know, there's a reason we were just friends who liked the movies.
There's a reason why as a 44 year old man, one of my primary gifts at
Christmas for my mother was the GI Joe original series box.
I'm desperately seeking a simpler time.
Well, you have been since the day I met you, that that's clear.
And, uh, yes.
And it has been amplified by big, big nostalgia, man, but I get it.
You know, it's like a lot of guys are like that 40 year old
Virgin tapped into that as well.
And they, you know, these are guys who are mocked and women too, who do this.
But I mean, that's where it comes down to.
You're like, when was I last happy?
Oh, right.
25 years ago.
Let's, uh, let's try to recreate that, but it can get sad.
Don't get me wrong.
It can get sad.
It's nice to know.
I'll probably never at this point, be able to afford to buy a house, be
able to afford it because of the inflation and yeah, I mean, Jesus Christ.
It's just one ball kick after the next.
I mean, my God, there will be a housing crash and, uh, you just gotta wait for
that and wait for the next collapse of the world.
Yeah.
Pray on somebody else's misfortune.
That is the way to get ahead.
It is the only one.
I was just down at, uh, South by Southwest, which I had a great time at.
Yeah.
I love the festival.
We did a thing called the sandwich summit where I did a roundtable
discussion with, uh, some sandwich makers from around Austin.
We had the Joey Rose's sandwiches overnight and gave them out to the crowd.
It was really fun.
Eddie Pepitone and Blair Saki sat in as quick quick question though.
Sorry.
You said roundtable was the table shaped like a sandwich.
No, no round figurative roundtable.
Okay.
Carrie.
Uh, yeah.
Pepitone was really funny because you know, the talk is sandwiches.
It's like, you know, what made you want to get into making, right?
Why do you make all your sandwiches on biscuits versus whatever, you know?
Yeah.
And then Eddie would be like, I'm here for truth.
Uh, I want to expo.
We're here to get to the bottom of reality.
The banks are taking over.
He would just interject these insane things.
It was really, really funny.
I love that he's vegan as well.
Like the perfect piece of the puzzle, you know, he got a lot of shit for that.
Cause he did try one of my sandwiches and we're like, Oh, how vegan of you.
Yeah.
Uh, we made fun of him a lot for that.
He was a great, it's like, they always talk about how it like levels out your
mood and you know, you don't have these personality spikes and stuff.
And then you got a mad man screaming on a corner.
I went through, he was the last person I introduced.
I brought everybody out at once on stage, but I went around the table and
announced to each person wasn't like why they were there.
Right.
So this guy, Mo has a company called Jew boy burgers.
He's Jewish guy, obviously.
That was a lot of fun too.
Like being, he'd be like, sometimes people find the name weird.
And I was like, and you're not even Jewish makes it extra problematic.
Right.
I don't like it.
It was a really fun time.
Anyway, I went around the table and I was like, well, I was here
because he makes burgers, uh, Derek is here because he does traditional
deli sandwiches and I went all the way around.
And then when I got to Eddie and I was like, and Eddie Pepitone is here.
Cause sometimes you need the opinion of a stupid asshole.
And we laughed.
Good.
We laughed.
Shout, shout outs to Liz.
We'll see you on how Liz, uh, big fees or yeah.
Big, uh, techs, uh, Stoney, Austin, Austinian, Austin, whatever it,
however the hell you say.
Anyway, Liz came out.
That was nice to see Liz.
Um, well, boy.
Yeah.
That was that.
Oh, that's what I was going to say.
So, uh, now I love South by Southwest.
That's a great time.
Did you hit the Austin bar scene?
Yes, I did.
Did your country line dance?
Didn't country line dance.
Instead I drank and took Adderall every night, which is sort of
like country line dancing, but my one night on Adderall and drinking out.
Oh, I hated it.
Hated it.
Keeps me going.
Sometimes anyway.
That's what the alcohol is for.
This is the one thing that I want to say.
I'm saying it with a little hesitation because I love South by Southwest
and I'm going to go back, but I do find it funny.
I do find it funny that such a liberally spirited festival, uh, that
would be very critical of, you know, let's say a big industry that
unfair wages to its workers, like Amazon, you know, or something like that
relies so much on volunteer help.
I just find that to be curious.
That's all, you know, it is curious.
Well, Amazon makes a lot more money.
Come on.
South by is making, they're doing all right.
Yeah.
They're always told.
I've never been the, the, the, the lanyards this year said HBO max on them.
I mean, they're doing all right.
Are they just straight back to, uh, packing people into clubs?
No masks down there or no baby.
It was, it's back, baby.
Where it was, it was regular old.
The fist is the first time I ever did this ever.
Austin during South by Southwest was the first time I gotten into an Uber
and the guy said, do you have a mask?
And I was like, no, uh -huh.
Nobody's making us do this anymore.
Why are you even, you know, like where I kind of got an attitude about it.
And I wasn't a Dick, but like, that was the first time I ever even wasn't
like falling over myself and be like, I'm so sorry.
I forgot whatever, right.
Because it was so just like, and the guy's like, you're supposed to have one.
I was like, buddy, I'm not disagreeing with you.
I'm just telling you, man, like they, they've, they've passed the mandates gone.
Like you don't have to do it anywhere.
So like, you're going to keep running into this man.
Like, I'm sorry, if you have one, I'll put it on.
I just don't have one.
Because it was, it was, but that is, that's everywhere.
New York, we don't, you don't have to show vaccination anymore in New York.
Done.
I believe LA is there too, or at least close to it, which I found shocking.
I mean, Atlanta has been a complete free for all.
That's where I am currently folks, but, uh, yeah, you rarely see a mask.
I look forward to watching LA continue with the individuals and the entertainment
business in LA continue to insist on, uh, distance hangs and using COVID
continually for the next two years is an excuse to be flaky.
That's going to be fun to watch.
I can't, I love seeing that.
Well, and every little mental issue people blame on COVID.
And it's like, we all did it.
Henny.
Yeah.
I've been kind of trashing the Ayahuasca thing on stage lately.
And particularly, particularly people in LA where I'm like, I'm like these
self -centered narcissists is just toxic personalities that are completely fucked
up, go out into the woods with a shaman and trip their balls off and then come
back and go, look how mellow I am.
I'm fixed.
And I'm like, you're fixed.
You're on an extreme come down.
You tripped.
Yeah.
This can't make up for years of mood stabilizers.
Like you're fucked up.
You know what I mean?
But like the audacity of that, the audacity of like, I had a psychedelic
experience and I'm fixed, like, what are you nuts?
I've heard it from a lot of people exclusively in the city of Los Angeles.
As you can imagine.
But, uh, yeah, it's, um, I, you know, I do it.
I know Mr.
Like, who was it?
Neil Brennan always talks about it.
Um, I don't know if that's an endorsement, but I don't know the man.
I personally would do anything.
If somebody said this might make you happy and it's not going to kill you, I'd
give it a shot, you know?
Hey, sure.
I'm not against the idea of doing it.
But the idea of it fixed me in one night is like, I took a shot, you throw up
100 % of the time, everybody throws up.
So that, that right there, like a community throw up or while crazy high
has me not super pumped to, uh, to do this, but you know, if you know, you
see shit, especially now that I'm kind of doing this inner child bullshit.
Like maybe if it helps you connect that in an even more real way or some, maybe,
I don't know, nothing works.
The truth is nothing works.
You start doing something and you're like, I think, I think this is better.
I think I'm getting better.
And then you're like, no, I actually feel worse today than I
may have ever done in my life.
I'm going to try to today.
It's just that office space thing of every day you see me.
That is the worst day of my life.
That's how I feel lately.
I'm going to try micro dosing.
If I can get it through my insurance.
Surely you can't get that through your insurance.
Can you use?
Yes.
Some insurances, it is a thing now.
Like you can get it through.
Here's the thing.
If you can't, it's $1 ,200 a dose.
Yeah.
They make it.
What a shit country.
This is God almighty.
Wait, $1 ,200 a micro dose.
Yeah.
They make it, they do that.
It's not worth that obviously, but like they do that.
So it's, it's unattainable.
That's a, that's a big Pharma Joe.
Why don't you stop out of competitors?
Right.
Because then, because that bag of mushrooms from a comedian for
60 bucks and travel is not because that's not a, that's not a micro
dose like, and then there's no way of measuring it out.
These are, you know, here's all that is, is big Pharma's way of saying,
if you can't, if we, if we figure out a way corporately to make this
insanely unaffordable for you, then you will be forced to use our medication.
Right.
And you'll stick with the Prozac or whatever it is that you're on,
which those things are great too.
But it's shitty.
The guy I used to text when I wanted mushrooms, uh, I, I texted him this
past year and then realized two days later when he didn't respond that
he had killed himself and I forgot.
Not that I forgot, I didn't know him at all.
I just remember hearing that and I was like, Jesus Christ.
Um, now, Joe, I want to say it didn't help when they didn't help when they
found his body, the endless voicemails of you going, what'd you kill yourself?
Call me back.
You're supposed to be dealing me a legal drugs.
Yeah.
You're, you're David, uh, who's the guy for mr.
Saturday night, David Tamer is David Tamer is number one customer.
I've started seeing Paymer and more and more things actually.
But, um, I don't know.
I like, he's an awesome tales from the crypt.
Yeah.
He was, he was always nominated back in the day, had kind of a career.
Now, Joe, the other day you said the payoff and I'll stick around by the
foo fighters might be your favorite rock song payoff of all time.
And I meant to ask, were you talking about stick around, stick around.
Okay.
It only does that once.
And it's the end of the song.
I mean, it's like, you're, you're like, you're ready to that.
That could make me jump off a roof.
It gets me so excited.
It's great.
Well, I thought you were talking about, this is a call, which ends with that
guitar, like a battle at the end, like, and then on headphones, it goes back and
forth through the channels, which sounds awesome.
Um, and then monkey wrench, which I used to perform in my car all the time to
get my teenage rage out of the cage.
But monkey wrench ends maybe better than all of them.
They're doing what he's like hell of a band.
You're talking about when he's like,
yeah, no, that's a great one too.
I used to do it in the one breath in my car.
Um, and believe it or not, lost my virginity late still, even though I was
doing that, um, I told Joe and I'd like to share with you all too, I guess this
might even be a scream and end because it made me scream out loud, but I was
sent and I w I guess I won't go into the studio making it, but a very big, well
known comedy studio and they're looking for a writer to do a reboot of our list.
Our list starring Robert.
Now our list and it's like this, what me and Joe always say, like just do an
original story who today is going to be excited about the name our list, make a
show about a sports agent and save yourself a million dollars.
It's so crazy.
Now, do you think wall comes back like force awakened style to pass the
baton to young artists?
I think, I think we'll play as the dad.
Yes, for sure.
Um, Jesus Christ, it's so nuts.
I get a shocking.
I got to scream at end for you.
Yeah.
So there was all this hubbub hubbub hubbub hubbub, whatever you call it.
West side story star, Rachel Ziegler.
Oh God.
I've been reading about this all week.
Yeah.
She got nominated.
Hey, I didn't, I didn't get invited to parties a lot either.
Sweetheart.
I didn't take it to Twitter.
He got nominated for West side golden globe, but it was her first movie ever.
She did not get nominated.
The film did.
I thought, no, I think she got nominated for best actress in a, no,
they'd have to invite her if she was nominated for best actors.
No, no.
Golden globe, not Oscar.
Okay.
All right.
Is the movie nominated for an Oscar?
West side stories nominated for several, but not best actors.
Well, anyway, she didn't get invited.
Uh, well that, that makes her not getting invited.
Make a little less sense to me.
I just was like, who cares?
You didn't get invited anyway.
She made it just the amount of time I've been reading about it.
Like, Jesus Christ, they're going to invite her now.
Like, well, that's the story.
Yeah.
Not only is she invited now, she's now a presenter.
There we go.
I mean, she'll do a one joke, one very tame joke about it.
So now, you know, if you want to be a presenter at the Oscars, just complain
about not being able to pretend that.
I mean, seriously, does anybody, this is like goddamn, what's that movie?
The invitation with Seth, uh, Seth, uh, Rogan.
Yeah, this is like the invitation.
It's like guys called the invitation.
That's the conversation, the interview.
The interview conversation is Jane Hackman.
Yes, that's right.
It's like the interview.
It's like, guys, the, if you despise the thing, despise it just because you get
invited, doesn't mean now you have to go to it.
Yeah.
I can't stand this shit.
Nobody stands for anything.
Everybody bitches about the, the, the cool kids table until they
get invited to the cool kids table.
It's like, turn it down, be a fucking gangster.
No, you didn't invite me.
Fuck you.
I'm not crying.
I mean, Jesus Christ in the seventies, you heard it all the time.
Like, uh, when, when Annie Hall won, somebody had to accept the Oscar for
Woody Allen is that he was playing clarinet with his jazz band that he just
didn't go exactly like, and I'm not saying Woody Allen's a role model.
I'm just saying, doesn't anybody do that kind of shit anymore?
Like Brando sending the American Indian lady out to take the award.
He's like, I'm not, I'm not showing up.
Like I think anybody just make a stand anymore.
Well, I think people are too needed to needing to do that.
They need the fame too much.
Fame has become too important, but I think when it starts to be attempted
now, it's it's by people who are so dumb that it doesn't connect.
Like when Joaquin Phoenix walks up there on Oxycontin and goes, Hey, we
got to talk about the farming in this country, you know, and the cows are
being milked and that, you know, like that's the cause now is some idiot
getting his minute deciding I'm going to use this for good and choosing
to make that issue cows, you know, that that's how stupid this generation is.
And he's a brilliant actor, but come on, man.
He comes from a family where everyone's name is leaf river.
Joaquin.
It does say a lot.
I mean, they were hippie folk, you know, people of the earth or whatever,
but it's like, that's great.
And at the same time, there's bigger issues.
Like I don't need everybody to go up there and talk about the issues, but
if you're going to do it and you choose cows, I do have an issue because
you're being stupid and selfish.
Well, I just my whole thing is, is.
You know, we it's nothing new to say, oh, you know, this sort of victimization
thing has has spun out of control.
We've heard people say that ad nauseam, but my God almighty, at this point,
it's like now victimizing the fact that you didn't get invited to a fucking
stupid bullshit with the world at war award ceremony, like, and turning the
fact that you were the lead in this movie and you did get nominated in other
places, this is now you're caught.
Like it's, it's, it's like, you have to spend everything now, every opportunity
into some form of unfairness.
And it's so odd.
Jesus everything is an injustice or a slight with the world at war.
Yeah.
Could I play one of those got like, I wouldn't be like Kenneth Branagh or
whatever in the lead, but could I play one of those guys who like pounds the
table and goes, the world's at war, man.
Why not?
Why couldn't I have kind of that like middle -aged Irish character actor look?
Uh, yeah.
Maybe I'll go to that.
I'll be a guy who pounds giant mahogany desks or orders people out of my
office.
I always love to play a chief, a chief who's tired of all the bullshit of police.
You mean, or do you mean Indian chief?
No.
I always thought I wanted to pitch this.
I never really found a way to make it interesting beyond a sketch, but I
thought it would be funny to have a movie where like the hot, sexy young cops
come in and the chief choose them out.
Like you guys are just being, you know, you're all over the place.
You're dragging my name through the mud, but then instead of following the
hotshot, sexy cops, we go home with the fat chief and he's complaining to his
wife about these hot shots at work, but it's more like a character study of him.
I think that's great, but it was just a sketch though.
You know what I mean?
You wouldn't watch that.
I don't think, I think you could actually get into a pretty interesting
character study and possibly drama.
That's something that starts very funny, but then gets into this guy's life.
Maybe a funny comeback role for Reginald bell Johnson.
Yeah, there you go.
See Danny Glover be good in this role.
Yeah, sure.
I think, uh, I think a funny sketch would be an Indian tribe where the
chief is yelling at two hotshot Indians like that.
Yes.
You speared the trout.
Yeah.
Oh, I told you to wait.
Run.
I told you to crouch in the woods and wait, but you had the spirit.
Just cause you're running, it's going to get your kid.
You think you're running everything.
Get out of here, chief.
I'm sorry.
And the Indian chief, even though it's like in the like 1700s, he's
chain smoking Marlboro's black coffee.
Chain smoking, peace pipes.
I mean, how offensive are we going to make this thing?
Taking, yeah.
Taking the piece by putting it out defiantly in the, in the ashtray.
I'll tell you what I am here.
And it's some sitting bulls**t and see even this people could declare
offensive Joe, the fact that we're doing the last year old native
American last part, I'll say completely authentic.
Love the native American.
Yes.
Completely authentic setting in the teepee, except there's a coffee
machine and a Maylocks bottle in the corner.
Yeah.
Over like a, a fire that's smoking off of rocks.
All right.
That's like a funny, like naked gun kind of gag.
I think it's funny.
Mad TV back on the horn.
All right, let's go to the movie corner.
Yeah.
I've seen some movies I've been watching.
I've been seeing, and I'd like to start with a film called.
Actually haven't watched as much as I thought, but let's start with fresh.
Fresh is a, I guess you could almost call it a horror romantic comedy type thing.
Um, directed by Mimi cave.
It is new to Hulu.
It's a Hulu original and it stars Daisy Edgar Jones, the lead from normal
people, which was my, probably my favorite show of last year.
Excuse me.
Two years ago.
Uh, I love her.
She's beautiful.
She's great actress.
She's funny.
I like her a lot.
Oh yeah.
Daisy.
Yeah.
She's great.
I didn't know.
I didn't know who it was when you said it, but, uh, yes, she's very good.
She brought me in.
Uh, Sebastian Stan is not an actor.
I get the appeal of he bores me.
Uh, he's in everything.
Now I just finished watching him in this Pam and Tommy, which was a big let down.
And now he's in this, um, the movie is basically a human centipede type thing.
And I'm, you know, I'm just going to spoil it for you because all the
marketing is covered in blood.
So they do that anyway, but basically it's a romantic comedy, you know, young
couple meets cute in a supermarket.
And then at about the 30 minute mark, they go away for the weekend.
And you realize that he is harvesting young women for their meat and sending
their flesh to rich people who want to eat the flesh of beautiful young women.
You know, no spoilers beyond that, but that's kind of the end of act one.
It's one of these movies.
I saw two movies this week where the credits opening credits started at the
40 minute mark, like trying to beat the departed, you know, I remember in the
department when they did that in the theater, like it was such an exciting
thing, like it was crazy.
I don't know.
I don't know why it was so crazy, but it just really was.
It felt like I remember insane and the whole place commented on it.
Everyone was talking.
Uh, so to have to fresh.
And then my next movie, drive my car, both did this 40 minutes in had the
credits start, but it really does feel like two different movies.
I get why they did that.
It's directed with a ton of style by this director, Mimi cave, who I am not
familiar with and look, it ain't perfect at all, but it's kind of a fun.
Horror movie.
Some of the stuff with the grinding and eating of women really grossed me out.
And I'm not easily grossed out these days, but I think when you're
in just a bummed out place, sometimes gross stuff takes you to a really dark
place and I found this kind of needlessly depraved considering they
were also trying to make it funny.
Um, so I don't know what to say.
It's a, it's an average horror movie.
I didn't like Sebastian Stan yet again in it.
I did like Daisy Edgar Jones a lot in it.
And I think it's got some kind of fun twists and turns, but a very imperfect film.
All right.
I mentioned, uh, Oh God, I'm going to sneeze.
I mentioned the, Oh boy.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
I mentioned the Andy Warhol diaries earlier.
God almighty.
I've never had allergies.
I always had allergies.
They have not been this bad.
And I've never had them, never had an issue.
Anyway, uh, Andy Warhol diaries on Netflix.
It's a six part series, uh, again, where they go into his diaries to reveal to
you a bit of the real Andy Warhol because he was such a character and created a
persona that sort of shielded his private life from the media.
There's a lot of mystery surrounding him.
For instance, people knew he was gay, but they didn't know if he was asexual.
He often claimed to be, um, they didn't know how deep his personal relationships
went and blah, blah, blah, all that sort of stuff.
So they created the series now to ruin everything he worked so hard to
create publicly for himself.
I didn't ruin the soup cans.
Did they, Joe, not the soup can.
He talks at length about them in the diary.
I'll tell you the frightening thing about this thing.
Andy Warhol narrates it because they created an AI program that mimics his voice.
And he narrates the movie.
And if you didn't know that from them telling you at the beginning, yeah, you
would think Andy Warhol was narrating the movie.
So wait, they write dialogue for the AI and he says it, or it's his actual words.
He reads the passages from the diary.
Oh, okay.
That correspond and they use that as narration for what you're watching.
Gotcha.
Um, but that's pretty crazy.
This is the same thing they did for Val Kilmer, which is going to let
Val like speak in films again.
Um, but like the show, I was interested, you know, I find that
era of New York city fascinating.
Uh, I live in the neighborhood where it all took place.
Um, I love this neighborhood, the Lower East Side.
It's where, uh, I opened my place, Joey Roses.
I have a great affinity for the neighborhood and its history.
And, uh, so I am, I was interested and I do find Andy Warhol interesting,
but the show itself is kind of boring.
They strangely, and I say strangely because it's not anything we don't know
already, they keep hammering, oh, like almost ad nauseam, the fact that he was
gay and he was ahead of his time as a gay man and that you couldn't talk about
that stuff back then.
And it's like, yeah, we know.
Like, so mention it, but they keep coming back to it over and over.
And I'm like, that's a new thing in documentaries, the overspelling out of
this shit and I don't get it.
Um, I'm on the episode now, which is towards the end where it's, the episode
is called Andy and Basquiat, which is the one I was most interested in because
that's Basquiat's a very interesting fellow and a great artist.
And, um, and I liked the movie Basquiat, but everybody always says the movie
didn't really tell the story accurately.
So, um, I'm curious to see where this unfold, how this unfolds, but
I'm halfway through it.
And look, overall, it's a cool little docu -series, Debra Harry's in it, uh,
Fab five Freddie's in it.
I'm a big fan of and countless other people for some reason, Rob Lowe
repeatedly interviewed in this thing.
I it's weird.
What is his connection to Andy Warhol?
I must've missed it.
I don't know.
I thought they would have named, I thought they would have presented that
immediately, but they don't.
So I'm like, I guess buried in some episodes somewhere, he finally brings
up what his connection is, but he talks as if he knew him, but who knows?
You know, that's, that's nothing new.
Like you watch any documentary now and I'll have like, you know, like
Pat and Oswald being like, that was the thing in the twenties though.
You couldn't get a breakout.
Like, that's like everybody just talks.
Like they were there.
Yeah.
A lot of the people in like that Superdave documentary, you're, you
realize that they're just fans of Superdave, right?
It's like technically a documentary to have people rave about something, but
that's what a lot of them are these days.
Yeah.
Um, but it's an interesting story.
Interesting enough.
Um, I don't know if he would have approved of it at times.
You're like, yeah, he would have cause he was obsessed with celebrity.
At other times you're like, no, we kept all this private for reason.
It's weird.
At one point they're interviewing a guy and the guy's title is president
of Andy Warhol enterprises.
And you're like, what, what is this?
And then the other weird thing is like, it's like, he'll talk about, like
going to studio 54 for Liz Taylor's birthday party in like 1980 or whatever.
Yeah.
And, and he's like, I thought it'd be like 20 people, but there were
hundreds of people, yeah.
And they're showing like snapshots at the birthday party.
And it's just like, you, you, it's such a, it's like that thing when they talk
about like the Bilderberg group or the Illuminati or whatever, and you go,
it doesn't matter if it's the Clintons or the Bush family or, or, or Trump's
when they're all in it, they're all there.
They're all in the, the Jeffrey Epstein jet together.
Oh yeah.
It's, it's that kind of thing, except with famous people, because they're
like showing snapshots of this thing.
And it's like Diana Ross, Tom Smothers, Jimmy Buffett.
You're like, it makes no sense.
Other than they're all just wildly famous at that time.
Right, right.
You know?
So like, you know, they're in the club and you're not basically, um,
tail as old as time.
Yeah.
So, but, uh, you gotta stop tapping on your desk.
Sorry.
I know it's a sensitive mic.
It's driving me crazy.
And I can only imagine what it's doing to the listeners.
You're driving me crazy with that low cut top you're wearing.
Well, from driving me crazy folks to Academy award nominee for best
picture drive my car.
How about that NPR style transition?
I haven't even heard of this movie.
Look, I want to just briefly, and I liked the movie, but I want to briefly
speak about something here.
I did online Sundance at the beginning of last year.
I went up to, yeah, I got it as a gift and I watched a bunch of movies.
So I was reading a bunch of these articles that must, must see movies at
that's cause they're not out.
There's no buzz on them.
So you don't know anything about them.
So I read a few critics articles, what to look for.
And none of them mentioned drive my car.
I read a lot of daily Sundance reviews of the festival.
And a lot of people said, boring, endless, way too long.
Don't watch drive my car cut to a full year later.
The movie comes out in normal release and it's nominated for best picture.
It's one of the most acclaimed movies of the year.
I don't know what happened between those two points or who paid off who,
or what went on.
Sure.
But the hype on this thing is that it is one of the great movies of all time.
I mean, it's, it's for, we just had it with parasite.
So, you know, it does happen.
But the fact that this movie that's up for best foreign language film is also
up for best picture is a really rare thing.
I don't know.
I don't, I don't know what the love is for it.
I do know that it's a very, very niche audience and that most people would
never finish this movie.
I would say 90 % of viewers would never get to the end of this movie.
Uh, and that doesn't mean I'm, I'm better than them or anything else.
I just mean, I watched it in seven segments.
It took me seven full days.
How long is it?
Three hours long.
Good.
It is a really powerful and interesting story about a man who.
Doesn't really know his wife as well as he thinks and is worried basically that
if he asks her for more, he'll lose her or something.
He it's about how people's perceptions of one another, keep them from truly
knowing one another is the theme of the movie and it had really powerful and
interesting things to say as well acted, but 45 minutes of this movie is a
production of uncle Vanya, the checkoff play.
Oh my gosh.
You're watching long chunks of uncle Vanya, which is syncs up with the
narrative, believe it or not, Joe.
So it's like a throw mama from the train situation.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Believe it or not, what's happening in the play kind of syncs up with
what's happening in real life.
This sounds unbearable.
It's a guy, he goes home.
Uh, he seems to have a very, very happy marriage.
And one day he goes home and his wife is cheating on him.
And it spirals him out.
It's a movie about grief and about how, you know, like I said, it's
about how can you never really know somebody?
And there's a lot of heavy shit that I enjoyed musing on thinking about.
I read several articles after I watched it to kind of see if my
opinion linked up with them.
It's that kind of movie.
But you're watching a lot of checkoff play on stage and you're watching a
lot of people driving around in silence, just driving, driving and driving.
So if I hadn't watched it in seven days, which probably means 20 minute
chunks or something, I probably would have despised this movie, but I
found the ending very moving.
I got what it was trying to do.
I think the themes of the movie are very unique and kind of special.
And yet the delivery system, and I'm sure the director would say, well,
I, we had to do it this way.
The only way you could understand the pain, the man was going through
whatever and fine, that's what art's all about.
I'm just saying your average person is not going to sit through three
hours of people driving around and then a checkoff play to get to a
really interesting story, they're just not going to do it and they shouldn't
have to.
And yet I liked it, folks, I get the love.
It's something very points.
There's something kind of beautiful about it.
You know, like whenever they call a movie meditative, you know, it's
going to be the most boring piece of shit you've ever seen.
Yeah.
And this movie ever review says meditative, but maybe because now I
am really trying to meditate and do this.
My therapist, when I think when he realized I was far too far past the
point of no return, he started talking to me about what's called the fertile
void, meaning you're in a void.
You can't get out of it.
You will someday, but you're not going to now you've got to find a way to
make that void creative and fertile at as depressing as that sounds.
That's what helps me write day to day and kind of just like, I have to kind
of get into this weird zone and this movie, I met it on that zone at times.
And when I did, I understood how a meditative movie can be cool.
If you're open to it, you know what I'm saying?
It sounds torturous.
I think the edible might be hitting the way I'm talking, but, uh, no, it's a,
it's a movie that I think, you know, it's a conversation piece.
I like the movie and yet I think there was a lot of shitty stuff about it.
Uh, okay.
I'm going to stick with doc you as a, my theme today, uh, last night,
I binged bad vegan.
Should I watch it or not?
I keep telling people, keep telling me yes and no.
Well, it's a docu -series, but people did tiger King.
So it's an equally crazy story.
Yeah.
It's equally as insane and funny.
And then also tragic, um, and crazy.
Remember how maybe you don't, but I was so excited with it's the first,
it's the closest I've come to a snow day was when the pandemic started.
We didn't know what was coming.
Tiger King dropped.
I watched all 10 hours and like 24 hours curled up with a bunch of pillows
and blankets on the couch drinking.
And I was like, this pandemic thing's kind of fun.
Did you have a vibe like that when this all started?
No, no.
You knew from the beginning that it was bad news.
It wasn't that I knew it was bad news.
I just was depressed every waking moment, uh, in the beginning.
It wasn't until they said, you know, you can walk around with drinks outside.
If you want, that's what I was like, Oh, this is so bad.
Yeah.
Uh, sorry.
I interrupted you go.
Um, it's a, it's a docu -series about a woman that, that ran the most,
I guess successful and exclusive raw food, vegan restaurant in New York City.
It was called pure food wine.
Uh, which I already have a problem with because you're eating uncooked
vegetables and you're paying like, you know, and you're paying like Gordon
Ramsey, whatever price this is like.
I'm like, come on guys, it's fucking vegetable, but who knows?
Maybe they made it.
Maybe they did something magical.
I don't know.
It's closed now, but, um, uh, she has a very successful business.
It becomes a hotspot for celebrities.
Uh, and eventually she meets a guy sort of through Alec Baldwin, uh, who
she falls in love with and then begins to sell her a bill of goods, uh, that
she goes down a very bad road for following, uh, basically loses everything.
Uh, I don't want to say too much, but.
Oh, she follows this guy based on the premise that he tells her.
Has the secret to immortality and that he knows how to make
her and her dog immortal.
Okay.
Do you get to see the guy?
He's not in it because he refused.
Yeah.
But you see pictures of him and stuff.
Like he's out, like he's out of, he's like walking the streets.
He's not like in prison or anything.
Yeah.
Um, and you know, of course in the end, none of it is her fault.
Um, you know, all the highly illegal shit she did the entire time, it was all
because she was under the trance of this man telling her he could make her immortal.
So, you know, look, there's definitely some, some validity to, to the, to, to
what she's saying about, like, you don't understand, like he, he was so.
Hypnotic and all that.
I get that.
I get that, but it does get to a point where you're like, come on lady, Jesus
Christ, this is ridiculous.
And then when they're saying to her, like, well, that's how I felt about the,
the Tinder swindlers victims, which like, you know, there's, there's red flags
and then there's like a hundred red flags.
And I think the, the, the subtle theme of that documentary, the Tinder swindler,
which I don't, I didn't even think that I should talk about on here because of
how lame I thought it was, but the whole point was like, people are so starved to
find a human being that they can tolerate that they will just put up with
thing after thing after thing after thing.
It's very true.
And I hate to slam my own gender, but I think women have it a billion times
worse, you know, and because guys are just not, especially once the app game started.
Sure.
It was like, there's a lot of guys who were just out there to game the system.
They're not looking and he takes sure.
And he takes full advantage of that.
They meet on Twitter, you know, and he takes full advantage.
He's creating accounts and pretending to be other people who are talking to her
and advising her to trust him and all this stuff.
He's a wild, insane lunatic of a human being and just a toxic person.
But it does get to a point where you're like, Jesus Christ, lady, come on.
Like you're stealing from your employees, you know, like repeatedly
because, and here's why it's suspect.
You hear phone calls like that were recorded for whatever reason, where
she's saying to him, like, well, then give me my fucking money back because I'm not
giving you another fucking dime.
And then, and then it's like, so right after that call, I went with him to France
and you're like, what are you doing?
So it's a little weird.
Um, it's like that.
I just read this newspaper article and it was so fucking disgusting, but it was like
a policeman or a sheriff or something in a small town who was, you know, clearly into
some weird child porn stuff.
And he had his wife who was a school teacher, put his semen and cupcakes that
she baked for the kids and feed it to them.
Yeah.
I saw that.
And now, you know, if you watch any movie, you know how these plea deals work, but
the woman gets completely off on this because she's like, he manipulated me into
doing it or whatever.
And it's like, no, there were many off ramps for you not to feed these.
Yeah, those fucking cupcakes.
Why don't you, why don't you buy a batch of cupcakes, throw
those in the trash and feed them the non -jizzed ones and tell your husband
you did it even like with the, even it's the baby in the woods routine
thing from good fellows.
And in that scenario, you can, you know, you know, Karen, you know, that
guy is the actual FBI agent that dealt with Henry Hill, but I mean, you know
what I mean?
It's like, at least in that situation, you can go, well, Christ, it's the mob.
She might've been scared.
They were going to kill her if she left, you know?
But even with that on the table, you're still like, Oh, come on, Karen, stop it.
You know what I mean?
Like, so is it worth your time?
I, you know, like I, I enjoyed it, uh, but I think you could read the entire
story in five minutes on the internet and not spend six hours watching it.
Uh, I looked up some stuff afterwards.
The most interesting of which was, see, this is the other thing too.
They, they had to, um, scrutinize her text messages when she went to trial
for all this, and they found that she had a sexual relationship with
her lawyer happening, uh, and Louis CK might've given her VD.
Those were some of the texts that were unearthed text between her and
Louie were like, she was like, you gave me a venereal disease.
It seems that they're talking about, um, what's the one that, that women get
that, that guys don't know if they have HPV HPV as soon as you're
talking about HPV and she's like, you, you're, you're, are you not clean?
Whatever.
And he's like, and he, I'm not defending, but he does say, he says, he
goes, look, I told you before we had sex, I didn't know if I was clean.
That's hard for guys to know if they have that, but you said that that was okay.
You might've given it to me.
I don't know.
Yeah.
And then he's just like, it's fine.
Don't worry.
You know, and he's, he's, he doesn't come off great, but at the same time
you're like, no, but you can sort of see that there's this like, I'm
sure he saw that newspaper headline.
I was like, uh, damn it starts with disgraced comedian.
Louis CK might've given vegan, uh, fraudster.
When I, when I briefly did stand up, I had this whole thing about Lou
Perlman and I was, remember, remember Lou Perlman?
I was like, really?
My, the whole goal of my life is to avoid my, my, uh, obituary
containing the phrase disgraced former boy band Empress Sario, which
was his whole thing that he was this guy who fucked all the boy band candidates.
But yeah, you don't want, you don't want disgraced in there.
But I will say there's a bit of a pattern.
You can kind of see with her where it's like you choose very poor situations
for yourself and don't take any responsibility in the fact that you
chose them, like there is no, like, I get it, you're pissed.
He might've given you whatever, but there is no part where you're saying
I'm a fucking moron for having trusted you, right?
You know what I mean?
You got to have that part.
You got to have the part where you go, I'm a fucking idiot.
I, I have nothing but that part.
Yeah.
So, um, and then also it's weird that you're banging your defense attorney.
Sure.
You know, like when that usually happens in like erotic thrillers, but there's
all, you always read newspaper articles about that and stuff.
It's like, how hard is it to not fuck your lawyer?
Like this stuff happens all the time.
How are people fucking?
I don't even understand.
I've never understood it.
I feel like it must be you, you get to a place where you feel like it's the
only person in the world you can trust that has your back and it doesn't help.
It doesn't hurt that she's smoking hot, right?
You know, like I've been in situations where I've been sitting with someone.
I, you know, obviously decades ago, I wanted to fuck them.
I felt 99 % sure they wanted to fuck me.
And then I went home.
I just don't have the gene of like, Hey baby, you want to come back to my
place?
I never did.
Yeah.
Well, you're probably better off.
No, Matt.
I don't have HPV.
Maybe I do.
I wouldn't know who the hell I saw another Hulu original because I
think they realized that would have lost some money on it.
Theatrically deep water, deep water directed by Adrian line.
How many fucking movies are going to be called deep water?
I mean, there was dark water.
There was dark waters there.
Well, dark water with Jen Connelly was a remake of a Korean horror movie
called dark water.
And then they did a Mark Ruffalo, Aaron Brockovich type picture called dark
waters, right?
And then there's a deep water.
The one with the kids, with the sharks swimming around them the whole time.
That's no, you mean that?
Oh, that real indie movie.
Yeah.
That might be called deep water.
Then there was dark deep blue sea starring LL Cool.
J deep impact, deep impact.
Uh, anyway, deep water, boring water, water for chocolate.
Sorry.
Water for chocolate.
Yes.
Uh, water world, of course.
Uh, deep water was directed by Adrian line or Lynn who directed fatal
attraction, Jacob's ladder on faithful indecent proposal, flash dance, nine
and a half weeks.
That guy had what you call it as a brand.
Yeah.
I mean, he did like, kind of like MTV, early MTV movies, kind of like
erotic, hot, but mainstream movies.
He had a lot of hits and then he kind of vanished for a while.
And this was his attempt at a comeback and he's got a huge stars, Ben Affleck
and Anna de Armas while they were banging.
And their chemistry is kind of the reason to watch it.
Anna de Armas is very attractive.
I don't know if you're allowed to say that, but she is.
That's the reason people are watching this thing.
She is naked.
Yes.
Um, the movie is basically like cocks the motion picture.
It's Ben Affleck as a cuck.
He has an arrangement with his wife where it's like, if you don't leave us, me
and the daughter, you can fuck whoever you want, but then people, her
lovers start winding up dead.
So this is an erotic thriller, which is a genre that I really miss, but it is,
if this has come out in 1994, I mean, this would have been laughed off the screen.
Erotic thrillers used to be really good movies.
Fatal attraction is a perfect example.
This movie is unfaithful, hot stuff.
Unfaithful is great and hot stuff and a good movie.
Um, this isn't good.
The whole kind of cuck thing is sort of interesting for a minute.
Um, it seems like it's kind of walking a line where it doesn't know if it
wants to be really serious or it wants to be like a campy wild things type of
movie, but it doesn't commit to either.
And it's just not very good.
And I'm, I would say I regret watching it.
It's not a very good movie.
And honestly, Ben Affleck is so powerful and so rich that probably he had this
movie buried because JLo was like, I don't want this movie coming out where
you're fucking your ex -girlfriend.
This needs to be buried.
Put it on Hulu.
I bet that's what happened because they're huge and rich and they probably
paid somebody a million dollars and were like, just bury the thing.
Um, my last one, uh, and this is the only movie that I saw at
South by Southwest, sorry, the kids in the hall comedy punks, uh, uh,
new documentary about the kids in the hall.
They were all there, which was really cool.
Uh, I got to chat a bit with Scott Thompson, which was really nice.
I'm a big fan of his.
I got to chat a bit with Dave Foley, which was really cool.
Drame has to, um, when to see the movie.
It's a documentary about the kids in the hall.
I mean, there's nothing really more to say.
It's awesome.
It gets you incredibly excited for the new season.
They say in it, Kevin McDonald says in it, we don't see the new season as a reboot.
We see it as the sixth season of the kids in the hall, which is awesome.
Um, I'm inclined to believe him, but everybody says that every time
sure never is, but I think I, they, in my opinion, they don't make bad work.
Uh, uh, you know, I, I love that show very, very much.
And I'm excited to watch they, uh, you know, it's interesting to see their roots.
It's interesting to see all this never before seen footage of them starting out.
It's interesting to hear the stories of how they met.
The two most interesting and intriguing parts were when they talk about doing
brain candy, I always knew they had some sort of weird riff with Dave Foley.
I didn't know what it was.
And it started with him getting news radio and Kevin McDonald telling him
not to shoot the pilot because it would mean them having to cancel a live
appearance and Dave Foley is like, I told Kevin, I'm not going to not shoot
the pilot because that's insane.
Uh, and he shoots the pilot and the, they start to work on brain candy.
And, uh, you know, it gets really ugly.
Lawsuits get involved.
They're not, none of them are talk there.
None of them are talking Dave Foley.
He's the outcast.
Uh, I always thought it was that he was like, I'm too good for this at this point.
I'm a big TV star now and it's not.
It's like he was supposed to be involved in that.
And it got so ugly that he got to a point where he's like, okay, guys,
I can't do this with you.
Yeah.
So like, I'll show up and do my part in the, in the, in the movie, but whatever.
And, um, he, uh, there's, there's, there's footage behind the scenes from that.
That's wild where there it's so tense.
And like Kevin McDonald turns to Cameron, he's like, you know, what's funny.
This is the first bad day we've had.
I'm kidding.
Of course they've all been horrible.
It's yeah, I mean, I, I read, I read the kids in the hall, one dumb guy by Paul
Myers, who was Mike Myers' brother.
I read that last year.
It's an excellent biography of the kids in the hall that I felt covered.
Everything you could want to know.
They go real deep into Beran Canyon stuff.
So I, I assume that this is like a sister movie to it.
I'm dying to see it.
That guy was there that wrote the book, um, or at least, well, I don't
know if it's that book or not.
There was a guy there that wrote a book.
He collaborated with the guy that made the movie.
Guy with a horrible haircut, gray hair, gray hair.
Can't remember if the haircut was better or not.
Mike Myers is all through the documentary.
Yeah.
Like saying, like, I'm, I was so jealous of them.
Like they were, they were good doing things I never would be able to do.
Like, which is astounding because Mike Myers is fucking hilarious.
The director of, of Wayne's world too, was, uh, this guy, Steven
Surgic, who had only done kids in the hall and then never directed another
movie for some reason, but yeah, I know Mike Myers loved them.
My favorite part of the movie is they talk about like how they start to
rekindle their relationship and it starts to get better and they become friends
again, and then they, they do same guys, different dresses, and that's
like the official reunion and they're, and they've been together ever since.
And they talk about when they do death comes to town and Scott Thompson has
cancer and I didn't know this, he was supposed to die.
It was like really serious and Dave Bruce McCullough tells a story.
I was weeping like a, if you see him tell this story, you don't cry.
You're dead in your fucking heart, but about like a tough day they had with
Scott Thompson breaking down because he was like, he was like, I think I'm going
to die, you know, like, and it's, it was beautiful.
It was beautiful.
And to see the movie come through that and then end with the anticipation
of the, of the new series and like, it was fucking awesome, man.
It was so, so wonderful to see.
And then like, and then just also seeing some of the old clips like that.
I forgot about, you know, like, or they hadn't seen in a while seeing citizen
Kane, you know, like, uh, you know, they're not showing the whole sketches,
but they're showing parts of sketches.
And, uh, it's really, really funny, man.
It's it was great.
It was great.
It was a great movie.
And there it's, what's interesting is, is they're really serious in the
interviews, like they're not, not, not, they're not being like, they're
not taking themselves seriously.
They're just not trying to make fun of anything.
They're just, they're just talking normally, which was really interesting.
Um, but Dave Foley has a great line when he goes, when they sued you, did you,
did it feel like a certain type of betrayal?
And Dave Foley goes, it didn't feel like a betrayal so much as it was a betrayal.
Yeah.
I mean, it was no surprise to me reading the book, but they're clearly such like.
Bitter, like angry guys, you know, at their core who, who have grown up a lot.
I'm sure, but it's just like, I, I know a lot of guys like that.
A lot of my friends are like that.
Like, it's just like, they can't let anything go.
And they had five of them, five guys, the same age who had all that, that shit.
So yeah, I'm sure it was tough, but I'm glad we still get them.
I'm excited to see the new show.
I had a great moment where I was backstage at a standup show that Scott
Thompson was on at South by Southwest.
We have the same manager.
And, uh, so we kind of like, you know, new sort of knew each other
from that, but does it, but anyway, I, I hadn't
spoken to him and, uh, he came backstage and I was talking to Rich Voss.
Uh, about when I went on Joe Rogan and called Anthony Cooley, a racist
and like everything that happened after that, and Scott Thompson walked
in as I was telling that story and sat down on the couch next to me to
like go back over his notes and, uh, and we, you know, we said hi.
And I was like, I was like, excuse me, Scott, I'm sorry.
I'm in the middle of the story.
And I was just like, nice to meet you.
But, and I went back to the story and I go to rich, I go.
In hindsight, I probably shouldn't have called him a racist on Joe Rogan.
And I looked over at Scott Thompson and Scott Thompson goes, Oh no.
He didn't even know what I was talking about.
He just was like commenting on like, why would you do that to yourself?
It was really funny.
It was really, really funny.
Yeah.
I saw him do a bunch of monologues as the buddy love character at the lyric
theater, which is a two minute walk from my home.
And it was awesome.
They're still great performers.
Go check them out if you can.
And an underrated film, the wrong guy starring Dave Foley.
Very funny.
You should check it out.
And kids in the hall is now on Amazon prime Amazon.
Yeah.
And you should check that out too.
If you've never seen it, it's an amazing.
I'm going to repurchase brain candy.
I had it on like, it's about to come out on Blu ray.
Never been.
Oh, like scream factory.
One of them, but it's about to come out on Blu ray.
It's never been out.
So make sure you wait.
Or if it's out by that, by that one, it's an awesome movie.
That's a cool part too.
When they talk about meeting Lauren Michaels for the first time.
Yeah.
And they go, whoever knows Lauren Michaels has a Lauren Michaels.
I think Mike Meyer says that.
Right.
And then they go through all the kids doing their Lauren Michaels impression.
But when it gets to Mark McKinney, it's exciting.
Cause you're like, that's the boss and brain candy.
He's doing awesome brain candy.
Like it was, it was, it was just really fun, man.
It was really cool to see.
I can't wait to see it.
And now you might notice we've been talking for an hour and we
haven't gotten to the film at hand.
That's because at least I know I have nothing to say about this movie.
It is called the cursed.
And again, uh, that Sundance from last year, they'd had this midnight
movies part of the Sundance where it was like each night they would have a
couple like horror movies or really fucked up shit or whatever.
And they had that prisoners of the ghost land, that terrible Nicholas Cage
movie and a bunch of others censor was one of them, but I stayed up because
I thought the curse sounded cool.
I like a period piece, horror.
It said practical effects, which I always enjoy.
Gory, gory where I watched it.
And I remember just being so disinterested, so bored in the
events that nothing stuck.
Now my, and I chalk that up to, I watched a bunch of movies in the
same weekend for Sundance, I guess.
But it was not one that stuck with me.
So when I went up to the AMC to watch the cursed for this podcast, it took 45
minutes for me to go, have I seen this?
And I bring out my phone, look on Wikipedia and realized it was at
Sundance and I did watch it.
I had rated it on letterbox, letterboxed again, helping me out,
letting me know what I've seen.
But it was a traumatizing moment.
I've never forgotten.
I've seen a movie before, so it made me wonder about my mind and getting old.
But it also made me, especially when I watched it in its entirety for a second
time, say, I cut myself some slack because this is one of the least
memorable movies ever made.
It sucks.
So, well, it doesn't, I don't think it sucks.
I think, uh, walk us through the plot.
If, if you even know, well, I can't remember.
Yeah.
It's in a period and there's wolves.
Uh, a kid, there's a, there's a, there's a wealthy, it's the father of a family
who's also the sort of patriarch of the town, uh, is a wealthy landowner.
There are gypsies living on the land.
They want the gypsies to stop, uh, squatting, if you will, on the land.
The gypsies won't leave.
So they burn and murder the gypsies.
You find out, and then the gypsies put a curse on the land.
You find out later that the gypsies in fact own that land and the greedy
patriarch just didn't want to give it back to them.
Uh, and that was the justification for the curse, uh, and why he
was extra wrong in killing them.
Uh, and that curse is, is that the werewolf will rise.
So, uh, a kid becomes a werewolf and bites another kid and then
that kid becomes a werewolf.
It all sort of comes down on the son of the patriarch, uh, who eventually
turns into a werewolf and is killing everybody in the town.
Um, they don't know it's their son.
They just know there's a monster on the loose and they have to fight it.
As Pat said, it's got all the right elements of what turns me on about horror.
It's, it's, it's almost like a modern day, you know, hammer type film.
England, right?
England.
It wasn't England, right?
I think everybody was English.
I think I came away from a second view.
And yeah, it was England.
It was England.
Yeah.
Um, England period piece, Gothic horror werewolves, practical effects, the clip
they were on the stooms, fancy lads muskets.
Yeah.
They released a great clip online of like them cutting a werewolf corpse
open and then like, uh, one of its victims, like trying to birth out of
its stomach and that's the cool part.
That's what was awesome.
Yeah.
And I was like, man, this, this is right up my alley.
Like, this is so, I can't wait to see this, man.
But then you watch it.
I left the theater saying that was pretty good, but I got to admit it
was a little distance down a little time.
It's like, it's like seeing like if Ipsen wrote a horror movie or something like
that, like, uh, like you watch a doll's house and you go, I know this is good, I
guess, but Christ almighty.
I'm bored shitless right now.
It felt like that to me.
It felt like, I didn't even think it was good.
I mean, there was nothing fresh or innovative about it to the fact that they
got a budget to do like a period piece, a historical costume drama with this
story boggles the mind to me.
I thought the story was interesting and I thought the ideas were cool.
And I don't think they did anything wrong.
Yeah.
It just wasn't interesting.
It was a lot, in fact, quite frankly, and I might get shit from this for
sure, first from certain people for this fruit from certain people, but it was
a lot like some of the hammer movies where you're like, you're like, I get,
yeah, it's, it gets, got all the ingredients, but Christ, I'm bored right
now, man, you know, like, uh, all those movies have great spots and then really
boring spots.
It's just the nature of the beast.
And they're all, they're always like 70 minutes, you know, the hammer
movies I love in theory.
And sometimes when I'm sitting through one, I'm like, Jesus Christ.
You know, but yeah, it is what it is when you're making movies for five
grand, sometimes they're not going to be great.
This, um, I, I, I, did any of the cast ring any bells with it?
I don't, I didn't know who anybody was.
Nobody left a mark.
I don't remember any of the performances, nothing about it, but was
anybody, were you familiar with any of them?
I guess I should.
No, no, me neither.
I didn't know who, not one stinking person in this thing was.
No.
Um, I also didn't like that.
Oh, another really cool element where you're like, that can't go wrong.
Do the scarecrow that comes to life.
That's always scary.
Yeah.
But in this, it just didn't matter.
They even blew a talking scarecrow.
I didn't like that.
The werewolf wasn't really a werewolf.
It was like a were wolfie being, you know, it was sort of a quadro.
What is that called?
A quad ped quadro ped.
Uh, uh, what's that called when it's like, it's like an
animal that's a bit human.
I have no clue.
Quadra ped.
Well, biped is you walk on two feet, right?
Okay.
So all fours, I guess would be like called like a quadro ped, I would think.
I'll take you at your word.
Like it was a bit, it was like a humanoid kind of thing.
You know what I mean?
It wasn't really like a werewolf.
I wanted a werewolf.
I also would have liked a werewolf transformation proper.
Yeah.
They didn't give you one.
They showed like the beginning stages where they were like rabbit
and their eyes look crazy.
Yeah.
But you never really got to see them transforming in a movie with practical
effects.
I don't know.
I guess a werewolf transformation costs a lot of money and it is a
big strain on your budget, but I would have liked to have seen that.
Um, but yeah, I got to say, even as I was text arguing with you after, as I
was leaving the theater saying like, no, I thought it was pretty good.
And you were shitting on it.
As I was writing to you, I was like, I would never buy this.
And that's always my mark of, yeah.
If I can't, if I can't imagine owning it, I'm like, uh, you know, or if I
owned it, I would never put it on.
You know what I mean?
Like, I guess it wasn't that good.
It's probably the, the, the movie.
I've liked the least that I have seen twice.
I watched it entirely by accident twice, but just, I mean, the fact that
nothing sticks with me about it.
Just the hog is down.
The hog is taped to the balls at this point.
My hog is falling.
My hog is, is silence of the lamb style wedged between my meaty thighs.
My hog is soft orgasm falling where you go.
I guess I was into it, but God, this is depressing.
Like a ruined orgasm.
Oh, you just mean, you know, when you have an orgasm, but you're
like not fully erect, you have like a soft, I mean, I guess it's happened,
but yeah, it's always been a bad time.
Yeah.
That's what I'm saying.
It's one of those.
Like I had the orgasm, but it wasn't good.
Anyway, we'll be back next time with the Batman.
Uh, and until then, uh, Joe DeRosa comedy on Instagram and Twitter.
Come to Joey roses in the lower on the lower oath on the lower side
in the lower side of Manhattan, one seven four, Rivington street.
Go to Joey roses, NYC .com for all information.
Please come see us for a sandwich or a drink.
Um, and then, uh, I'll be on the road.
I'm not on the road again until may, but I'll be in Austin and may
Creek and cave, uh, so go to Joe DeRosa info .com to get tickets.
Please come out for that.
The Patrick Walsh Twitter and Instagram, uh, we will be back in five
minutes with a review of Robert Pattinson is the Batman Emily Florence for all you
do the only thing I ever repeated was the Batman Joe.
Uh, thank you, Emily Florence.
Sorry, Joe talked over my thanks to you.
We are working on a live show.
No details confirmed as of yet, but we are working on
getting some live shows popping.
See you when hell pod is the show's Instagram.
Uh, we love you all.
Thank you for supporting us.
Talk soon.