I'll see you in the podcast that talks about the movies you love.
We love you hate we hate. That's it. Oh, okay. It wasn't really the end of a sentence or a
thought, so I didn't know. Um, you know, I like to keep it, uh, I like to keep it open. Okay.
And mysterious. Right. Joe, what do you think is the worst, the best album with the worst cover?
Uh, for me, Fleetwood Max Tusk ranks pretty high with the Polaroid photo of a dog, the beige background,
it's terrible cover. There's a band that I like quite a bit called a giant dog.
Isn't even the band. I love them too. Joe, we like the same music. Where'd you hear them?
Uh, I don't know. I heard them first in a record store in Echo Park. That's what I,
so I got turned on to them. I'm a fan. But I am too. And I find that all of their album covers don't do
their art pieces and their interesting art pieces, but they're very misleading. Like if you saw,
to me, their album cover, your and then also the band's name, a giant dog. Sure. Your head isn't
going to this like cool pseudo T rex. Yeah. Like power, glam pop thing that they deal. That's so cool and
so unique and interesting. It just doesn't look like that to me. It looks very, it looks like the
out kind of album cover that, uh, what's that band? Um, uh, who's the band that sounds like Paul Simon
that everybody says is good, but they suck. Well, you're talking about vampire weekend, but yeah,
yeah, looks like a vampire weekend record. I mean, they have the worst album covers I've ever seen,
but their music also sucks. I love them. And I like their record covers, but the giant dog
covers are, are almost horror pieces. Kind of a little unsettling. I don't care. Aliens and dogs
and beasts. They're, it's, they're all like claymationy things or stuff. Right. It's weird. It's just
not what you're, it's not what you'd expect. Yeah. It might be scaring off new fans also.
Um, Pat, let me take a minute here to talk about what a pile of shit blank gym is.
Blink gym. Blink gym is a chain of gyms. I don't know if they're just in New York or if they're
a national chain, but I want to just talk real quick about what scum they are. Uh, they have called
me repeatedly now to say, Hey, during the pandemic, by the way, for the last year, to say, Hey,
your, uh, your gym membership is, um, we, we can't process the payments on it anymore. Uh,
I go, yeah, cause I'm not a member anymore. Yeah. And they go, well, you, you never, uh, you never
stopped coming. And I go, no, no, there's a pandemic. So I stopped coming. I'm not a member of your
gym anymore. So just cancel the membership. And they go, yeah, the only way we can do that is if you
come into a location or send us a letter, right, via the post office. And I've said to them, at least
10 times on 10 different phone calls now, it's a pandemic. Yeah. Your gym branches are closed.
Even if they weren't, when they were temporarily open, I am not going into a gym during a pandemic.
I'm not going to the post office during a pandemic. Two of the most crowded, slow moving plate,
you know what I mean? Just like just asking for trouble, cancel the membership.
Can't do it. You got to send a letter, hard letter, snail mail letter, or you got to go into
a location. It, and I go, it's a pandemic, make an exception. Uh -huh. And they're like, we can't,
you're just going to have to do. And I go, okay, I'm never paying you. I don't know what to tell you
then. Yeah, you're never getting the money. Right. Well, we'll send it to collection. Have at it. I don't
care. You got to the point the other day, I said to the guy on the phone, I go, do you like what you do,
sir? And he goes, what do you mean? And I go, how do you, how do you sleep at night with this? Do you
like, are you proud of yourself? You're disgusting. And they said something and they said, go fuck
yourself. And then I go, now hang up because the big scary man said the F word.
So I'm sure they're, uh, they're going to look out for you. Yeah. And then he said, is there
anything you, I can do for you, sir, trying to take the high road. And I said, yeah, you can do me a
favor. You can go fuck yourself. Do you think you can handle that? Do you think you could figure out how
to go fuck yourself right now? And then I mean, blockbuster used to do that shit. You will get a bill
from a collection agency. Now, hopefully you can just argue that it was a pandemic, but you might have to
go to a courtroom. Who knows? Is it worth it to you? It's $85. So they're wanting you to basically
sign back in so that they can get money from you and then quit. No. If I sign back in, I still can't
quit unless I go into a branch or send a hard copy letter. And I keep saying to them, just cancel
the membership. It's a pandemic. These things are not viable options right now. And they won't do
it. How many times you go to that gym? I actually went quite a bit in the beginning. Okay. Uh, now,
nowadays. Well, yeah, I mean, I can't, I can't imagine. They're opening them in Boston. Now,
gyms again. It's like, who wants to go into a gym and put your hand on a metal pole where 40 of
the other guys who have just walked out of the bathroom, where they've been taking vial creatine
shits, you know, spraying their, uh, protein powder all over the seat, not washing their hands. They come
out lift weights. These are the kind of people that are in a gym during a pandemic. So you know, they
don't care or believe that it's real. And now you're supposed to touch the same pole they touch.
I mean, and you can forget about those steam room orgies. I mean, look, I'll have my phone where I want,
but, um, no, it's, that's crazy. Uh, I get letters either to my DMs or publicly, about two,
three a week from people furious with me for the same exact reason, because they think that I am the
president of New York sports clubs, who I guess is named Patrick Walsh. So they take to Twitter,
find any Patrick Walsh who's verified, I guess, and just send them the nastiest shit. And I've written
back a few of them, you know, for the most part, people are like, oh my god, I'm sorry. But this one woman
went, well, so I guess, uh, the head of New York sports clubs just has the same name as you question mark,
question mark, question mark. I'm like, yeah, bitch. That's how nice work. Yeah. So names work.
Well, she think we're each a snowflake. And, and the only person with your name is you?
Well, that's, that's how these damn kids were raised, Pat. By the way, I have that snowflake, like, like,
snow, not like the new usage of snowflake. That's what, that's what the new usage is.
I, yeah, now that makes sense. Yes. But it's sometimes it's the perfect term.
Sometimes it's the perfect term. Sometimes Cuck is a good term. Sure. You know, you can't just say the
word is always bad. Right. I want to hit you with a quick news psycho. Yeah. Because it pertains
exactly to what we were talking about last episode. And I, in between recordings, we take a brief break.
And I went on movie web .com and found this story that just came up today. Disney Plus blocks kids
from Peter Pan, Dumbo, and more because of negative stereotypes. Meaning like your parents have to
log you in? Yeah. You're now, if you're in like the kids, if you, if you have the kid filter on Disney
plus folks, I thought Disney plus was the kid filter. But what are, what are the issues with those
g -rated films? Peter Pan in quotes portrays native people in a stereotypical manner that reflects
neither the diversity of native peoples nor their authentic cultural traditions. It shows them
speaking in an unintelligible language and repeatedly refers to them as redskins and offensive term.
All right. The redskins thing very valid. Peter and the boys in this part, driving nuts. Peter and
the boys engage in dancing, wearing headdresses and other exaggerated strobe tropes, a form of mockery
and appropriation. They're accusing Peter Pan in the lost voice of the property. So we're,
I would buy up all the westerns you can because we're not going to have westerns anymore either.
You better hop to it, folks. I've been, I've told you on here already. I've been buying them.
I got 30 days of Sodom in the closet. I can't buy them all up right now. And it's like,
Joe's devoted a lot of his life to, you know, arguing passionately for free speech and so forth.
I don't want to be a spokesperson for these things. I don't want to be talking about this every week.
I'm not that guy. And yet you hear it and you're like, God, they're just wrong. That's just wrong.
Unless all it is is they're putting a little warning up top. Then I don't think kids are fun.
No, the, in a rather bold move, the movie web dot com reports and a rather bold move,
Disney plus has pulled several classic movies from children's profiles.
Oh, they're controversy. They pulled them, but they're still on the site. You need like a parent
permission. Yeah, that's what I'm saying. Dumbo because of, um, Dumbo is one hour.
It includes a drug stuff. No, it includes crow characters. Oh, yeah, who pay homage to racist
minstrel show where white performers with black and faces and tattered clothing,
imitated and ridiculed enslaved Africans on Southern plantations. The leader of the group is
done. Dumbo is named Jim Crow, who shares the name of the law as an enforced racial segregation in the
United States. But aren't they bad guys? Aren't the crow's bad guys in Dumbo?
I mean, I don't remember, but I mean, if they're representing these black guys and they're bad guys,
that's not any better. No, no, they're saying the crows are paying homage to the racist troop,
troop. Oh, I see. So I'm saying, if the crows are bad guys though, isn't that the point like that
they're not good guys? I don't know. Is song of the south on Disney plus? That's been long taken off.
Yeah. Well, they had it up though. Let me see here. I'm just curious. I thought that wasn't
possible to even find anymore. No, no, it never went on there. Upon hearing of Dumbo's plight,
the crows become the baby elephants mentors and father figures and insist him in the rescue of his,
oh, jeez, okay. All right. Well, they got Dumbo looking up to a budget racist crows. I had no idea.
Some of these cases, it's warranted. Yeah. And speaking of war, it's pet. Yeah. Am I under arrest?
No, I was trying to think of somebody that did something. I couldn't think anybody.
There was another couple. Well, there's army hammer, of course. Yeah. Why did you tell army hammer to
do what he did? Do you read that stuff? Finally, I didn't. I'm still confused as to I know I didn't
read it. I mean, it sounds some of it sounds. I don't understand. What did he do? He said, I want to
eat your heart to somebody or something. Well, he has, according to him, eaten a deer heart,
a, you know, I'm taking a big bite out of like a just out of the ribcage deer heart. But then you
wonder, what are these things or fantasy? What are not? And who knows? I don't think anybody cares
enough about army hammer to really lean into this. But I read tons and tons of the DMs and texts
and everything else. I felt bad doing it. But I was like, all right, the man seems unbalanced.
He has an obsession with cannibalism clearly. And then none of that's illegal. However, there seems
to be some instances of him breaking pre -agreed upon sexual boundaries and then just like ghosting
the girl afterwards, leaving her there. So mentally, it doesn't look much different than an actual
sexual assault, even though you kind of agreed to terms ahead of time. I'm not into this world,
you know, it seems like a sexual assault world. That's not your thing. I'm not into the like,
let's agree on a safe word. You know, that's, that's not my thing, but it seems like dangerous ground,
especially on this day and age. I listen, I like a bit of freaky sex myself. I find that if you need
to establish a safe word, that's a, you're going into a place. I don't want to go to right now. Exactly
what I'm saying. But I will say the reason I didn't read any of it was because by the time I found
out about it, there was already claims that a lot of these messages were had been doctored and were fake
and you couldn't tell which were real and which weren't. And with given the way of the press these days
with how much fake stuff gets reported, it's like, I was just like, what am I going to do? I'm going to
read something. I'm not even going to know if it's accurate or not. And then I'm going to get all worked
up. And who knows what I'm even reading, you know, like worked up. I mean, aroused by the idea of
army hammer fighting me. Well, and the, and the main girls case are the one who had the most messages
that I read. She had deleted all of her responses. So you're just truly reading a one -sided conversation.
And it's like, look, I don't know. It seems like he's very unbalanced. He's a drug addict. He's
a Instagram account where he's like documenting even weirder and darker shit because he just can't
just close fucking Instagram even after an instance like this.
Got kids too. It's like dude. Got kids. Yeah. I mean, he seems unwell. I think if we never got an army
hammer movie again, I can't imagine anyone in the world giving a fuck. Find another Nazi looking guy.
Oh boy. They're out there. Oh boy. He looks like a Nazi.
He's a Nazi. He is a Nazi. No, he's a good Nazi cast. Yeah, it's a good casting.
By the way, today's film is anything for Jackson. Yes. The Jermaine Jackson story.
Yeah, definitely that family would bend over backwards to do anything for Jermaine Jackson. He was
definitely the the favorite son. You ever watched that Jackson's an American dream?
Just Joe Jackson beaten the shit over and over again. I've seen it so many times. Seriously.
Yeah, it's the guy. It's Freddie Boom Boom, Washington plays from Welcome Back Outer, plays Joe Jackson.
And it's upsetting seeing him play such a prick. But that's a great movie, man. That's an awesome movie.
Well, I'm not awesome. But for for what it is, like one of those TV late 80s mini series,
it's really good. I saw that one and then the Beach Boys won.
They were both good. These were put more more more time into those back and the Beach Boys won.
You know, they go into a little into the abuse Brian Wilson put up with not anywhere close to what he
actually put up with based on his autobiography. But his dad used to like watch him take shits.
Oh, man, they didn't put that in the in the John Kusek one either.
No, it's just something people don't want to say. I don't think I wouldn't see. I would
like to see that. I mean, give me the give me the juice, man. Like this is what we're here for.
Show me why this guy is damaged. Sure. Sure.
All right. Why don't we oh, there was one other thing. Oh, did you see the another new psycho? The trailer
affirmatively released for Godzilla versus Kong? I didn't watch the trailer. I watching everyone
get excited about it. I'm like, you were also excited about the last Godzilla and the Godzilla before
that and those had great trailers and then they sucked. So why are you excited about the third one?
I hated the first Godzilla. The trailer for the second one did not excite me and I never saw it.
I was surprised that the trailer for this one got me as excited as it did.
It's been a while since that's happened. I mean, primarily because when they finally face off
for the first time in the trailer, it begins with King Kong punching Godzilla in the face.
They know what we want to see here. Right. And I was like, all right, this looks like it could be a lot
of fun. And it plays rap music as they're fighting. It's kind of exciting. What song are they playing?
Please, Hammer, don't hurt him. I don't know this song, but it's one of those like,
you got to get your weight up. It's time. You know, one of those like real like, you know, like
call to arms, like rap songs, like it's really, it gets you excited. Well, they're dumping it on
HBO Max, which I am after Wonder Woman and the little things starting to just think they, that's where
they're putting their turds when they know they got a turd. But we'll see. I'm excited to see
this little things. Something else, man. You, you really have talked about, well, let's not talk about
anymore. I don't want to ruin it if we're going to review it. It's getting good reviews, though.
No, I have seen one good review. The poster said it was a good movie. Well,
then it was Peter Travers involved. I don't know. I'm just, I'm being funny, but I was walking
home from the grocery store and I saw that it said that it was a good movie on the subway poster.
Okay. You want to, why don't you take us over the movie corner, Pat?
Joe, I'd be glad to. I watched the 40 -year -old version.
Oh, how was that? I have the screener. I haven't watched it yet.
Yeah, Rada Blank, who was unknown to me. It is a black and white film. It is about a 40 -year -old woman
who basically is a teacher. She feels like she has not been doing what she wanted with her life.
So she decides to kind of take control and become, she's a rapper in her free time. So she does
some recordings with a guy who becomes kind of a love interest and she also wants to put a play
together. The material with her kind of going up against the evil white producer, all feels very
real. It feels like this woman has been trying to get her plays made for a very long time and there's
always some rich white producer who's like, don't we need a white lead to kind of help bring the
white audience into the show? And, you know, just really wants to dumb things down, simple,
simplify things. These are things you would say frequently on the set
of living biblically to everybody. That's true. And I would say, Pat, the whole cast is white.
And you'd say, it's not enough. You'd usually reply with. We had Tony Rock. We had Carla.
Yeah, that is true. That is true.
You know, those scenes are funny. The guy who plays the producer is kind of funny and her dealing
with them is great. You know, he's just like, he wants the show to be wider. He wants the,
they like, it's not called torture porn, but it's called like, there's a new term for it. Black
misery porn or something like that where anytime you have a story about a black person, they're not
falling in love. They're not saving the day. They're always in pain. It's always precious. You
know, I've read a lot of articles about that lately. And this has a lot to say about that. Like, no,
I want to make this about my experience. I'm telling you, this is my authentic truth and this guy saying,
yeah, but people don't want to see that. So, you know, it's not reinventing the wheel. Spike Lee's
been doing this stuff for a long time. The way this movie is shot in black and white with a lot of kind of
like little almost like documentary pieces scattered throughout and little man on the street
interview scattered throughout. It feels very much a companion piece to like she's got to have it.
Spike Lee's earlier stuff. Also a similar, similar vibe to Hollywood shuffle Robert Townsend's great
movie about what he went through as a as a young black actor in the industry. So there's some great
stuff. There's some great observations mixed in with some stuff that feels a little like I've
seen this before. That wasn't handled as well as I've seen it handled elsewhere. But that's part of
being a first time filmmaker. The woman's got a lot of talent. She's funny. I like her vibe. I like
her wraps. There's enough to recommend about it. It's not a classic, you know, but it's a solid
first effort from Rod of Blank. All right. I'm going to do some movies. I always wanted to see
that I never watched until recently. I'll start with Victor Frankenstein. Never saw it. Always was
curious. Didn't think it would be very good. So I never watched it. And then last night I said,
what the hell? I'm going to watch it. Not at all an unenjoyable film. Interesting fun performances
from Daniel Radcliffe and James McAvoy. It's a new telling of the Frankenstein tale that centers
around him and Igor being partners and Igor also being a brilliant scientist. I enjoyed it. I
thought, you know, overall it kept me intrigued. I wanted to see where it was going when they finally
get to making the monster at the end of the film. It's a cool looking Frankenstein's monster,
which you don't get often. A lot of the time you get De Niro with stitches on his face.
This actually looked like a crazy monster. And he was a superman, like a modern Prometheus in
this version, like he has two sets of lungs and two hearts and all this stuff. So it was fun, man.
I also like that earlier on. They showed the first experiments with creating life and they are
their abominations, they're upsetting. They're like hybrid monkey tiger things,
lame stuff. And I thought that was really cool too. Watching him sew together parts from dead animals
to make these like weird mutated beings. It was quirky. Played a little bit like late Arab
Burton, which I know is not a, you know, it's not really a great. It's not an accolade. I understand.
I'm actually surprised him. Burton didn't direct this. It seems like it must have been pitched to him.
But overall it ends with the birth of the monster than the rest of it is like trying to build the monster.
It's it opens with Igor who is a hunchback in a circus who was abused by the circus and
but at the circuits, he moon lights as their doctor. And eventually Frankenstein comes in and
saves him from the circus. He's like you're being wasted here and these people are abusing you.
And he sort of springs him from the circus. But in the process of doing so, the circus people
because they're trying to like keep him there, they end up killing some of their staff in the process
and then they frame the murders on Frankenstein and Igor. And then so then there comes in this police
investigation where they're looking for this guy but in the meantime Frankenstein curious Igor of his
hunchback, hunchbackedness, whatever you would say. And then the experiments, whatever the police
commissioner has played by I'm blanking on something Scott. Willard Scott. Willard.
He's played by the guy that plays Moriarty in Sherlock who I think is one of the best new actors
on the scene. I think he's the new like Mark Rufalo. He's amazing. But you're not talking about Martin
Freeman, who's this? Or Moriarty. Martin Freeman plays Watson. I haven't seen him.
He's great. He's an Irish actor. I'm blanking on his name, but he's tremendous.
Anyway, it's a fun little film. I mean, any more for me,
half of what I'm looking for is logical storytelling, which we'll get into with today's film.
And look, man, this this this followed through with everything it set up.
It gave you a payoff with a monster. It had some interesting grotesque scenes and it was well
acted in fun and hammy and the ways it was supposed to be. You know, is it going to change your life?
No, but you know, is it something that's a fun Sunday afternoon watch? Yeah, totally.
Okay, okay. I saw a movie called The Vast of Night, which is on Amazon Prime, and it's something
I've just seen a lot of raves about both from friends, from critics, etc. It seemingly came
straight to Amazon. Maybe it had a little release window that I missed, but I think it was straight
to Amazon. And it is basically small town 50s. Two radio obsessed teens discover a strange
frequency over the airwaves and what becomes the most important lot night of their lives. So what
this is is kind of your standard would be alien invasion type thriller. I will say, you know,
I guess it's just because of the small budget. It doesn't really go anywhere at all.
It was so meticulously crafted. There's like these, it opens up with a five minute,
easily five minute tracking shot. That's amazing through a high school gym.
Then after that, there's like 20 minutes of like alt men ask, you know, jumping from character to
character in this gym. And then you're kind of like, oh, wait, maybe they only had the budget for the gym.
Because you're like, I'm spending a whole time just wandering around a gym and I'm not really
that into it. Then there's a tracking shot in the middle of it that goes from the gym all across town.
That is one of the most insane shots I've ever seen in a movie. It has to have it has to have had
cuts in it somewhere that I missed. But kind of like this, this 1917 vibe of like a camera just going
all throughout the town in and out windows and buildings. It's an amazing shot. So really,
you're 45 minutes in before we even get to this mysterious sound that they hear over the where the
air waves. And it's like, is this an alien? What's going on? And then it turns into this sort of like
a podcast. There's people calling in. They let them have like five minute calls on the air where you're
just like listening to someone listen to them talk. Oh boy. So it's like, it's like a supernatural
pump up the volume. Exactly. Or talk radio or whatever. The two the two child actors are young actors.
I guess they're in their teens are both excellent. Their newcomers obviously. The look feel of the film
is excellent. As far as tracking shots go, if you're a fan of them, like, you know, most people
really love and respect the good fellow shot or touch of evil or the beginning of the player,
this kind of blows them away with its use of tracking shots. But what it felt like to me is that
this guy was like, look, we have a story that's not all there. We don't have the budget to pull off
an alien invasion movie. So let's take the money we do have and put it into creating amazing shots that
will have people hire me to direct bigger movies. And I guarantee that will happen. This guy will be doing
Marvel movies in probably a month. And so be it. That's the way Hollywood works now. So yeah, worth
watching. If you're just if you just acknowledge going in that it's never going to get exciting. It's
never going to build to this climax that they keep promising. Just enjoy it for what it is, which is
like a first time director with no money being like, check out what I can do. And it's a success in
that regard. The movie itself kind of a dud. All right. I finally saw Charlie Wilson's war.
Okay. I never saw it. I was one years ago. Yeah. Yeah. He's working again.
I loved it, man. Yeah, it's good. I didn't know it was sorkin. It's Mike Nichol's final film as a director.
I loved it, man. I loved every minute of this thing. It's just, you know, Hank's and Philip
Seymour Hoffman playing two guys alive at a time when guys like that could be alive. You know, just
getting just drinking around the fucking clock. You know, Philip Seymour off and chain smoking.
Yeah, that's that scene where he's in his boss's office. And he's like, he's like go fuck yourself
for you. He's screaming at him. And then the guy's there fixing the window. And he's like, I'm
going to use the hand even. I was like, I'm going to need you here for a second. And he takes a hammer
and breaks the window. And he's like, you go fuck yourself. You're fucking child. Like I'm like, this
is back when it was when it was a job, man. Like this is this is fun stuff. I really like the movie.
I thought it was interesting. One disappointing thing was I as I read about it, you know, some of
the backstory with the production was this was initially supposed to end. So it's about the US,
excuse me, it's about the US helping army Afghanistan during the Cold War against the Russian
attacks. And Afghanistan eventually defeated Russia. But what happened after the fact was after
this this had transpired, the United States kind of didn't do anything to help out Afghanistan
to develop its country or rebuild anything that had been destroyed by the Russians. So they never
went in and rebuilt schools or anything like that. So it kind of became the wild west in Afghanistan
after this, even though we had helped them, we didn't help them for long enough. And it's what
essentially allowed bin Laden to take power and come into power and then eventually led to the
events of 9 -11. So it's an incredibly interesting story with a lot of twists and turns to it.
The play or the screenplay originally was supposed to be I guess in its original form was much more
like a doctor strange love for modern times. And a very comical but deadly serious satirical look at
war. And it certain this movie certainly is not that what it is though is a very very interesting
story and a very riveting one that's impeccably acted. It was fun seeing Tom Hanks be funny again.
Like he's funny in it. I haven't seen him be funny in forever. And I know this movie's very old
at this point, but it was just fun to see him be funny. It was awesome like seeing Philip,
seeing where Hoppin play that kind of character. Like it's a very mammoth -esque character.
You know, and Julia Roberts is in it. I guess she had no effect on you at all. I was getting I was getting
her. She's wonderful in it. She's absolutely wonderful in it. And she plays
like this, this, this, like far right wing debutant. Yeah. Which that was interesting to me to see
a story about a liberal senator or congressman whose dear friends and in many ways in love with
a far right wing debutant. And they stand for the same causes. And it's not like one some
pinco bleeding heart and the other some evil fucking fascist. It's like
their people that have similar interests and want to help people and want to help liberate
these people that are being attacked and all this stuff. I thought it was a very interesting story.
I thought it was very enjoyable. The only strike against it is it kind of just ends
with this sort of modeling shot of Tom Hanks receiving an award for his work in the liberation of
Afghanistan. And it doesn't really make sense because the scene right before the ending is
Philip Seymour Hoppin saying the crazies are coming in. We've done good, but we haven't done
enough. And then you hear jets flying over as he says it, which is obviously alluding to 9 -11.
And the movie was supposed to end with the 9 -11 attacks. And Tom Hanks said that he didn't feel
comfortable with that so they changed it. I think that's a shame. I think there there was a much
bigger commentary to be had with a good deed that eventually goes wrong because it's not a good
enough of a deed for lack of a better way of putting it. That said, totally worth a watch.
I love any Hollywood movie where there's blowout in the fucking open. You know, they're drinking
all day long. 10 a .m. just pouring whiskey. Yeah. It's awesome. Awesome. Chain smoking. I love the whole
thing. I should watch it again. I bought it for like three bucks and all I really remember about it is
is Phil Seymour Hoppin being very funny in it. But the ending, you know, what you're not mentioning
is that they replaced the 9 -11 planes with a hot air balloon. And to me, just a real head scratcher
of a choice. Right. And the fact that they put balloon boy in it. Yeah. And the reason the balloon
hits the World Trade Center is because it gets blown off course. It's not even. Yeah.
Who was balloon boy? Eliant Gonzalez was the kid who like sailed across the world by himself
herself. Balloon boy. What the hell are you talking about? Remember balloon boy? It was 2009.
The Jail and Hall movie bubble boy. Is that was bubble boy? No. It was the balloon boy hoax. 2009,
a homemade helium filled gas balloon shaped to resemble a flying saucer was released into the atmosphere
above Fort Collins, Colorado. And they claimed their six -year -old son Falcon was trapped inside it.
You don't remember this? You're asking for trouble. You name the kid Falcon. I mean, clearly they were
insane. They were just looking for attention. Oh, wait, that's right. Wasn't this a hoax?
Joe, I've said the balloon boy hoax three times. Oh, you have? Sorry. I don't want to listen to much
when you talk. I know. I know. That's good for a podcast. I find a two person podcast podcast.
This is a dog show. Okay, I'm going to give you a choose your own adventure. You want me to do the
kid detective or on the rocks? You could do either because I'm not going to listen because I'm going
to get a cigarette. But you can do the kid detective. What is that? It's a very popular film of the
year, Joe. It stars Adam Brody. That's not what I want it to be. I wanted it to be like a Disney
plus adventure film. No, it's a great setup. It sounds similar to like the Crane Boys that you
mentioned on that Frazier episode. But it's a guy who was like a cute kid detective when he was
nine. And now he's grown up and he's trying to cash in on that fame. But he's like a he does blow
in the film. He's an alcoholic. But in movies, he was a kid detective or in real life. He was a
child in real life. He was a child detective who like swept the town. It's like a real life
Nancy Drew or something like that. That's very funny. And then now grown up, he has kind of refused
to grow up. He refused to grow up. He stays in the mindset of this kid. He's very immature. He lives
with his parents. He's very angry. And through the course of the movie, he winds up sort
of getting a new case. But the case turns out to be a very disturbing and adult case
that causes him to grow up, if you will. So it's fairly simple. It's it's your standard
you know, mystery along the lines of like a long goodbye. Or they used to make these movies all the
time, just a little film noir. But it's got a hint of comedy about it as well. Until the end,
at the end, it really, and I'm not spoiling anything, it really does become a serious adult
mystery that throws you the viewer by surprise, but it also throws our kid detective by surprise.
All of his starts funny though, it starts comedian. It does. So and then it winds up kind of having
something to say about how it's hard to grow up where the cases get a lot more disturbing when you're
an adult, whether you're a detective or not, you know, you hear about shit and you're like, God,
so it's about a loss of innocence. The mystery actually turns out being really good. It's a very good
well done mystery, which you don't often get in these things. This makes me happy because I've
felt that for a long time we've needed a movie that tackles the struggles of a child detective.
Much like the child superstar in Hollywood, you know, they never talk about the dark side of it.
They just show you how nice it is and they're in the fame and the glitz, but
I'm glad that something's tackling this. It's not showing you how how kid detectives have to
grow up. I know I'm kidding. It's showing us how we all have to grow up in a way and how things get
darker and sicker as you get older. Now, does the case he's on involve a kid criminal mastermind
that was once his adversary who's also grown up now? You know, if the movie had made any money,
I think we would have been treated to a lot of these films. I think we could have had a lot of
fun with him getting cases or like what you're describing with his old nemesis would have been great.
They don't do that here. It is just a very short, quick breezy movie, but I really enjoyed it. It's
people have been going nuts about it. I think in the way that people go maybe a little two nuts when
they discover a movie that nobody else has seen and then they, you know, rave a little too hard perhaps,
but it's really well done. It's effective. I look forward to seeing what the writer director does next
and Adam Brody who is also has a very small role in promising young woman is great. I always like
seeing him and stuff going way back to the OC. He's in thank you for smoking. So you just remember
him being very funny in that movie as well. Is he the assistant to Rob Lowe and thank you for
smoking? Yeah. He's great in that. Oh my god. Yeah. He's an ails it. You were like this. I've met this
guy a thousand times. Yes. And he was in ready or not, Jennifer's body. He's got some horror
ties. He's just always good. And I don't know why they never bumped him up to that big star status.
I, unless it's coming, but they have him in the kid detective. He plays a 31 year old and you
don't bat an eye. I looked him up and he's 42. I mean, he could be a big star if they'd let him. He's
so much more charismatic than most of these big actors. But the director is this guy Evan Morgan
who also wrote the movie. I would watch for him kid detectives a lot of fun, especially if you like
mysteries. I just rewatched this isn't my last one, but I just rewatched Austin Powers 2.
Yeah. It's by your shag me and you had asked me, is it doesn't hold up? I'd say the first one front
to back is still a better movie. Yes. The laughs are much bigger in part two, even if they're not
as consistent. The Doctor Evil and Fat Bastard scenes in part two are front to like their impeccable,
it's it's brilliance. Agreed. It's it's absolute brilliance. The anyway, my last one is a film
called Tenure starring Luke Wilson and David Keckner saying and Gretchen Moll. Again,
this is a movie I'd passed by a million times on Hulu or Amazon Prime. I don't remember what I watched
on. And I was wanting to watch it because I was like, I love Luke Wilson. I really love Luke Wilson.
He's a charming guy and he plays a defeated man very well. Like he's very, very funny in that type of
role. And I had a feeling that's kind of what this would be. And sure enough, I was right.
You know, look, this is one of those movies. It's an indie comedy. If this had come out in 1996,
it would have been nominated for Academy Awards probably, but like, you know, it's just a little too
late for this type of thing to have gets it was poorly reviewed because I think it was just something
we had seen too many times by the time it came out. That said, it's a cute little movie about
professor trying to get tenure at his college and being in competition with a Yale professor
played by Gretchen Moll that comes in and the potential love story being hinted at there. They're
always very funny. Uh, it's a cute film. And again, it's just fun, it's fun watching Luke Wilson
with his back against the wall like he's very good. I don't understand why he's not a bigger.
He had more than enough time in the sun for his level of talent. Well, he was an everything for a while.
He's kind of, he is a little, he's able to do that one thing. I mean, as far as I know, he's very good
at being the guy that's just like, ah, geez, man, come on. You know, like, yeah, he whispers a lot.
I noticed he's very good at whispering and getting a lot of cross for the whisperer. Sure.
He's just fun to watch, man. I'm a big fan of that guy. I like him. I like him more in the old.
Heckly good looking film. Ten of bombs days. Yeah. He's not as funny as Owen, which holds him up.
I think he's funny in a different way. Yeah. Yeah. He's a straight man.
Basically. Yeah. Yeah. Which back in the day, they were the higher pay to the two.
Right. Do I got another one here? Another pick? Yeah, you're done. That's it. That's it. It's now it's
time to get on to the, it's time to get on to the movie. Yeah, the show of the hour.
So the hat just came off and the hair's looking wild. The hair's looking real wild.
What do I got? Who am I impressing these days? It looked like you just picked your head
up out of an ash tray. Today's film, anything for Jackson, new shutter, original horror film,
about two grand parents, male and female, the male of which is a paternity doctor.
And they kidnapped one of the doctor's patients who was soon expecting a baby
in the hopes of conducting a satanic ritual that will bring their grandson back into the world.
That's pretty much the plot, right? Sort of a reverse exorcism where they are going to
put the spirit of their dead grandson into the woman's stomach so that they can have their their
kid back again. Yeah. So overall, well -directed, low budget, they did a lot with the budget they had,
well -acted. Yeah. This is the only movie I've ever seen that doesn't have a Wikipedia page. So
clearly, A, shutter's not doing their job and B, this must be even more low budget than I imagine.
Yeah, I looked for one as well because it was one of those movies where the ending didn't make a lot
of sense to me and I was like, wait, what was that? Same. So it's well -acted, it's well done, it's well
spooky, spooky moments and some very cool looking monsters that appear as they conduct this day's
long process of repossessing this baby or whatever. That said, I had a lot of logic issues with this movie
and I'm starting to notice with, this is a very well -reviewed movie. It's got a 98 % on Rotten Tomatoes
from Critics. Yeah. I'm noticing that something is happening now with horror that was happening with
comedy about 10, 12 years ago, started happening where you'd see a movie like Cold Souls starring Paul
Giamati, which is everything, you know, everything but one step short of like a mellow drama, this thing,
hated that movie. I hated it. But you picked up the box at Blockbuster because I was back
when Blockbuster was still around and it would say things like gut bustingly funny,
uproariously hilarious. You know, it's like kind of like when transparent was winning like best comedy
and you're like, what the fuck are you guys talking about? This is deadly serious. I'm noticing this now
with horror where horror movies are getting astounding reviews and you're just seeing they're going
so, so what? Just because it's horror, there has to be no regard for logic at all. Like there's
major, major plot problems with this thing. Like there's critters for a horror movie to not resolve
itself and to be sort of vague about the details. That's the horror they prefer for whatever reason.
I'm fine with that. I'm fine with vague about details. I'm fine with not resolving itself. That's not
what I mean. I have a problem with the film that number one after they kidnap a pregnant woman
and the first thing they do, they kidnap this woman five minutes into the movie. I mean, this is the
whole movie. Yeah. As soon as they kidnap her, the first thing they do is make a fairly big production
out of we've got to run the test and the husband goes outside, the woman is screaming her head off because
she's been kidnapped and they and he calls his wife on the phone who's in the room with the woman
and he says, I can't hear anything. It worked and she goes, can you really hear nothing or can you
kind of hear a little something and he goes, no, I hear nothing out here. Yeah. And then you
cuts back to the wife in the room with the pregnant woman, as she's screaming and the wife says,
stop screaming. Nobody can hear you. We have soundproofed the room. Now, the way a soundproofed room
works is you can't hear anything from outside that room. You also can't hear anything inside the room.
That's how soundproofing works. Yes. Throughout the movie, they continue to communicate with this woman
from another room with the door shut. Yeah. They've got a guy who comes to clean the snow out of
their driveway, who for some reason is the most eager driveway cleaning man that's ever existed.
They're constantly worried about him running a snow blower in the driveway that he's going to somehow
hear this woman who's in a soundproof room. This kind of shit drives me crazy, man. It's like,
then don't make it a soundproof. Just take that element out and now we've got a suspenseful thing
where we got to get this guy off the property because he could hear her. That's all you got to do.
Why are you establishing a thing to only contradict it over and over and over again and not even in a
way of like shit, the soundproofing didn't work. I was wrong. Just like no, we're just going to ignore
that we ever said that. Don't worry about it. This happens a lot on this show. Whereas what you're
mad about, I didn't notice or care. While I don't disagree with what you're saying. I guess I'm
just willing to sort of put up with more too as long as the rest is fairly involving to me. In the
first half, I really liked it. A, I liked that his name is Henry Walsh. Julian Rishings and Sheila
McCarthy play the older couple. I know I've seen the old guy and some stuff. I don't know what
offhand, but he looked familiar. The wife did not. They both get very strong performances. It's
directed really well. And I think what a lot of critics liked about it is that you've got a built -in
story in that the writer and director have only done Hallmark Christmas movies. They've made like
that was cool. A hundred Hallmark Christmas movies together. Like to pay the and the whole time
they're like trying to just kind of keep the lights on so they can do their own project. I love that.
I love it too. Soundproofing, it seems like the kind of thing they'd go, you know, maybe that was a
studio note. What if you sound print and you wind up doing something even though you don't quite get it
or they just made a mistake? It does, now that you mention it, yeah, that doesn't make any sense to me.
But let me just say, it's not even just that it doesn't make sense once. Yes. Well, that's kind of,
it wouldn't be. It is repeatedly contradicted. Yes. Like guys, you slap me across the face with
this detail. They go on and on in scene after scene where the wife is going, we went over this and
we've covered every base and we need to keep up appearances and you have to go to work and we have
to act normal. Yet then a scene later, the snowblower guy comes and the guy's like,
it's like, guys, why are you establishing these things only to just completely contradict them
and then have no payoff with the contradiction? If you're going to have the husband contradicting the
plan. Oh, if the point is the husband's not good at keeping up appearances and that's what gets them
caught, then have them get caught. Have it create some tension. It doesn't do any of that. It ditched
just literally a guy being a bumbling idiot and there's no, there's no consequence for that.
Yeah. When that dude shows up, I mean, I, and for whatever reason, it just didn't, it didn't cross
my mind. But it's like, yeah, if you don't want this guy to hear, it does you more of a service to
not have the room be soundproofed than you just have a suspenseful scene. There's no reason to do it.
I spent the whole movie or at least the first half wishing that woman would stop screaming.
So I thought that they would say, hey, the room soundproofed, it makes no point of you to sing and maybe
they were making it up. But then Joe reminded me, they did the test. So it is this weird detail of it.
Joe, you're a man who once one of those details hit, you can't get back into the picture.
I get it. Well, that's right or wrong. This wasn't the only detail.
Okay. Now, that's an old couple in their early 70s, I suppose, late 60s. You wonder, how do they
get into this satanic thing? I mean, these aren't, these aren't your typical Satanists. Uh -huh.
They get into the satanic rituals because there's a Satan's group that meets at the community center.
Uh -huh. They go to the community recreation center and go into what looks like an AA meeting
and all put in broad daylight, by the way. They're not sneaking it at night and we're talking
two o 'clock in the afternoon. Yeah. Kids down the hall playing dodgeball or whatever. Yeah.
And put on hoods and have a satanic mask. Guys, for Christ's takes, man, come on. I mean, look,
let's be honest here, I think it's super cool that some guys that did hallmark movies to pay the bills
or whatever had a dream to or guys and women, I don't know who they are, but that the people that made
these hallmark Christmas movies had a dream to make a horror movie and they finally, I think that's
cool. But you know what? This is written like a god damn hallmark movie. This is written like a
hallmark. That's a hallmark movie thing that you would see and you'd make fun of it endlessly.
You're like, oh, for god's sakes, the wife, Satan group meets at the community center. This is absurd.
I, I would bet if you asked those guys, they have a little bit of a sense of humor about that,
that taking place at that location. I don't know, but there's nothing funny about it. That's true.
They don't really put it, you know, push it into a satirical level or a comedy level.
I mean, even even when they finally conduct the ritual and she paints a pentagram on the ground,
it's like, how many fucking things do we, I mean, there's been several mainstream movies made at this
point that contradict that the pentagram is something evil. It's like, this is like paint by numbers
shit to me where it's like, guys, a pentagram. Come on, man, like Google something, Google one thing.
I had just watched all the night stocker documentary and he favored a pentagram and he was certainly
very evil. So all right, fair enough. That's great. By the way, the Netflix night stocker thing.
It's fucking awesome. I watched it in one night. But yeah, it's, it's not, it's not a perfect film.
What I will say, I loved about it is a the old couple. I liked that it starts immediately.
Like they're having a conversation about pancakes or something and then they're just kidnapping
this woman off the street violently. That part was cool. Right off the bat. I'm like, wow,
that's an exciting arresting opening. At some point, it does kind of the hell razor thing of
in addition to what they tried to bring back from hell. They're bringing back other creatures
from hell. They've crossed over into our plane. And that to me is when the movie was really in the
sweet spot in the zone, especially the second man, the guy who's like body contorts and he's got kind
of this weird like almost like a skull mouth, a skeleton mouth and that creature was very, very creepy
and very well done on again, a very low budget. Yeah, I thought the, I thought the demon spirits were
cool. I thought the ghost coming back look cool. Yeah, what I didn't like was. Yes, sorry,
am I cutting your off? I mean, that's really all I have to say about it. It's in that kind of
sweet spot there and you're like, okay, it's building to like where everything comes over from hell
and we have this big battle, but you're kind of in the back of your mind like, well, they don't have
the budget for that. And they don't. It just sort of, it does kind of end rather abruptly. It doesn't
necessarily do what you'd hoped it would do with its intriguing premise. It doesn't do much of
anything. So weirdly, both movies that we're talking about this week, this and Hansel and Gretel,
I, I liked a lot. I liked certain aspects of it a lot. And I just wish that they had stuck the
landing and they didn't either one in my opinion. This one, I, when the devil comes up and it's like
by the bed, you know, I love that shit. I love the kind of on the cheap world they created, but I would
like to see them, you know, put more into the script. And for me, it wasn't an issue with logic.
For me, when I'm going into a movie about bringing things back from the other world, I can kind of
suspend logic. I just wish the story had been better. I think it's completely lazy writing to,
because this to me is of the school of thought of like, oh, you had a problem with the soundproof room,
but you believe demons come back. It's like, now those are two different logic arguments.
We're talking about a fantastic premise here, but there are real world elements in that within
that premise that need to make sense. And I think it's completely lazy writing. I think the demons
coming back in, and as a matter of fact, was completely lazy writing, because when they finally
explained why that was happening, they said, every go when you open this portal, every ghost in
purgatory is going to try to run for the open window and come back into this world. It's like,
why is your dead three year old grandson in purgatory? It doesn't make any sense. That's very true.
What could he have possibly done that would not get him the head? Nothing. It's lazy writing.
It's just, well, wouldn't it be cool if it was this? It's like, yeah, it'd be cool, but you have to
justify it. Make up something. Oh, when a child goes to the other side, sometimes he can end up in
the wrong place. I mean, these are like tiny, tiny, simple, simple fixes that take five minutes of
thinking or debating or whatever. On the top of my head, they could be like, wait, your son was
baptized, wasn't he? And they're like, no, there you go. Oh, well shit. Now you're, there are easy
fixes to these things. They don't cost any money either. Every single soul that comes back from
purgatory has ample opportunity to hurt the people in the house, whether it's the pregnant woman
who's been kidnapped or the old couple. None of them ever do. Yeah. Yet at the end of this thing,
the guy that's on their side, this red head that they bring in to conduct this ritual for them
is the only guy that gets taken away by one of these people. It's like, well, why suddenly was he
able to be taken away, especially when he was the guy that knew how to protect himself from these
monsters? You know, there's a thing at the end where there's a thing throughout the entire movie where
everybody that comes to the house, the driveway man, the cop that thinks they've kidnapped this woman
and confirms they do. For some reason, when they come near the house, they kill themselves. I'm
the kid that you're bringing over to conduct the ritual would kill himself. Then you guys would kill
yourself. Like, why is anybody killing themselves? Again, these are like two sentence justifications.
It's funny. We talked about thank you for smoking in the last episode, but there's that scene
where Rob Lowe plays the agent who's going to make the movie with the cigarette ad with the cigarette
product placement. Right. And he goes in space and they're smoking and then Aaron Eckhart goes,
well, space they would they would let they would be incinerated because of the oxygen or whatever
the fuck. And Rob Lowe goes, that's an easy fix. It's one one line of dialogue. Thank God they made the
whatever the thing. You know, it's like, it's like, yeah, dude, like,
that's a dumb shit big time Hollywood agent character, like doing a joke about how easy it is to fix
these dumb little logic issues. And yet they didn't even do that much in this movie.
Make some rules follow the rules. I'm very big on that. I didn't understand why why at the end,
when the pregnant woman is running away, like the the the the drive way man that had killed himself
is is mistakenly thinking he's she's his wife that cheated on him. I'm like, nobody,
what the fuck is going on here? It just it was all just a lot of things done to be like,
well, be scary if this happened. And it's like, well, yeah, I guess so, but like I don't why is that
happening? It doesn't make it it hasn't happened before. Why is it happening now? And the last thing
I'll say critically is I really hate. I'm I'm so tired of this thing where it's like they're
satanic, but they're against swearing, you know, like, you know, like they do this thing throughout
the movie where the where the old lady is like, we don't curse in this house. And we think sex is dirt.
It's like, you're doing a satanic ritual where you're going to murder a stop it. This is come stop.
Well, that's some political commentary. They're they're talking about I would assume about how
the Republicans act like they're pissed about language while they kill us all. I get sure, but it's
been done a zillion times at this point. Yeah. It's like, just do something a little bit different.
I, you know, I'm not going to mention anything plot wise about the little things, but I do think
where you and I differ on this kind of stuff is like when the little things was was playing out the
Denzel movie, I was standing up going, what the fuck that you can't do that? What the it piss me off
and I'm yelling. And for some reason with horror, I tend to just always let it go. And it's not
because, okay, it's a it's fantasy world. So anything goes. I just sort of feel like
I'd rather that they had had and explain this better. I'd rather there was a reason for it. That
wasn't just scary things happening, but also horror can be just scary things happening. It's not
going to be a classics, not going to be an ultimate great movie for me. But if a movie is scary things
happening and they're done well and they're pretty scary. And I like what I like what I'm seeing.
I tend to be a lot more forgiving than when it's a thriller set in the real world. That's where I'm
coming in with this one. I thought it was a, you know, an average horror movie with some above
average moments. I admire these guys for working in the in the in the coal mines for so long of
hallmark, Christmas movies, and then doing something like this. And I look forward to what they do next,
but I understand your grievances. The movie could have been a lot tighter and made more so.
I would, I am, I will willingly see what they do next. I'm curious to see what they do next.
Because that's where the, you know, the proof is always in the pudding, right? If they do another
thing and it makes perfect sense, then you can go, this clearly somebody stepped in and
fucked this up or whatever. What I don't get is the rave reviews about something like this.
Really come on guys. Like you will, the same critics will rip a movie like once upon a time in
Hollywood to shreds. Yeah. Because of plot holes or something. And it's like come on, man. Like,
don't, this is, come on. So, uh, you know, it had great moments. I think there was a real knowledge of
of the genre here. But I think they made some work, would I consider to be some rookie mistakes
in in in the logic department? And here's the thing. You know, if you want to make a fever dream
of a horror movie, then go make a fucking Argento horror movie. Yeah. All right. But I'll tell you
this. You see some of that later, Argento shit. And you start to realize here's a guy that may or
may not have really known what he was doing. Okay. And it's, and then especially when you read about
his process where he'd have a dream and then walk downstairs in the morning and tell it to a writer.
And when they had enough of these assembled, they would make a movie. Yeah. It's like you see some of
that later error, Argento stuff. And you're like, I don't think he knows what he's doing. Like,
I think he just had a great crew, you know, and I mean, and the right people around him that helped him
execute these really beautiful, mystical, metaphorical visions of his. And so it's like, look, if you want
to do that kind of thing, then great. But you can't, you can't present me with so many points of logic.
And then just have no regard for that logic, you know, we're going to think even even one 24 -hour
pass on this script, you could have fixed all these issues with ease or just like shown it to a buddy.
And they go, what about this? You know, it did, there were a few moments like that that, you know,
sticking your car on more than mine. But I get them. I think it's a slightly better than average movie,
mostly because of its visuals. But that said, I will give it a sideways hog. I'm not down,
but a sideways. My hog is one of those where it's not straight out in front of me, but it's about half
up. It's also not pointing up to my chin by any means. Right. Okay. All right, fair enough. That's our show,
folks. It's, yeah, we'll see you in our podcast. You know the plugs we did in the last episode.
Thanks for joining us. Thank you to everybody that's sticking with us.
Uh, uh, whether it's just listening to the back catalog or subscribing on patron of these new
episodes, thank you to all the new subscribers. People are really coming in and the, the, the,
the subscriber ship is growing. Thank you to all the new subscribers. Them too. And you can listen
to us naked, by the way. It's, it's your choice. We're not going to judge you for that.
Yeah, I love you. Good to see you. Same to you, Jill. Love you as well. Uh, happy.
Groundhog. When did they get this end of the month? No, they get this on the, this is exactly February
1st February 1st. Happy Groundhog day. Yeah, right before Valentine's day. Happy Gallantines.
We, I'm not going to say exactly when, but in the coming months, I think it's safe to say that we
will be doing both promising young woman. And we will also be doing the little things on HBO Max.
Um, keep, uh, keep your love coming. Emily sends us your guys comments and stuff. We do see them
sometimes on the Facebook, even though we don't have accounts. Thank you all for sharing with people
that we are on patron. I still a year in, more than a year in get, you know, what happened to
the podcast, you know, I get it all the time. So, um, if you see someone lost out there in the
wilderness, tell them where we are. Thank you. We're at 701 patrons. Patrons. That's the most beautiful.
We've ever been at. Thank you guys for listening and subscribing. And we hope you're enjoying the show.
Yes. Uh, and I will have, uh, as I have throughout quarantine, a very special lengthy edition of
that, so a movie corner coming up shortly. Thank you all. We will see you next time and we'll see you in hell.