Welcome to We'll See You in Hell. This is your favorite podcast discussing genre films.
Reviewing genre films. Sometimes doing commentary on genre films, though we don't do that much
anymore. Quite frankly, it's a pain in the fucking ass. But we'll do some here. I want to start this
episode because there was, if all went as planned, according to the last episode, some audience votes
will have come in about a disagreement pattern I had. But regardless of who won, I want to apologize.
My voice gets very loud and it sounds like I'm yelling and that was not my intention.
It was my father all over again.
It's very sad to me, and I say this for myself, that I can only express this
eye to eye and openly when the mic is recording.
That's fair.
I tried in between episodes today to say, hey, sorry, it's not like I was mean to.
And it was it was almost like when you when you're giving the hooker the money after.
There was no apology necessary. It was a friendly diversion discussion.
I got to go get more. My kratom went bad. I got to get some good kratom. I'll be right back.
What's a kratom?
Kratom or it's like energy pills.
And it went bad.
Well, I left I left the container open by accident while I was gone.
And the coloration of them does.
I'll just take.
Wild start to the show.
Oh, no, that doesn't taste right.
Your pill dissolved in your hand and you're trying to eat it.
No, it didn't.
What do you mean?
It's plastic. They're capsules.
Then you take them with water.
You don't taste it anyway.
No, that's when I put it in my mouth, the plastic tasted weird.
And I was like, I think something is not right.
All right.
Listen, we just had a nice makeup.
Let's not start with the criticism.
I think you got to up your meds.
I think you're losing it.
I'm down.
I'm down to 10 milligrams a day.
It might be the issue.
The ish.
And we pump it up.
I'm coming right back.
Folks.
Hello.
We are talking today about the third season of the beloved Netflix franchise, Stranger Things.
And we'll get there.
Don't worry.
But what's going on in the world?
Joe and I were just discussing.
They're apparently officially now finally going to impeach Trump.
It's September now.
You're probably hearing this in December.
I'm going to go ahead and guess they haven't done it yet.
Other than that, there's not much going on in the world.
You know, I am working on things that I'm not at liberty to discuss.
Jesus Christ.
This is like it's like when they tell the guy at Woodstock.
Go out and stretch.
Daltries passed out.
I assume you were coming right back in.
And I'm also still troubled by this.
This pill thing.
Cranium.
It's an all natural energy booster.
OK.
Pete Holmes recommend that to you?
No.
OK.
But my homes did.
Sherlock.
By the way, you watched Holmes and Watson and told me to watch it.
Yeah.
The only person I've ever heard say anything good about it.
It was just as bad as everyone says it was.
It's it's it's not as bad as people say.
It was so bad.
It's not a good movie, but it does.
I would argue can't be watched in one sitting.
It has it has some funny parts.
Oh, you didn't think the part was funny when he does.
He let me jump ahead of it.
No, he can't rap.
He can't comprehend that the woman is a doctor.
That part's funny.
And he's going he's going, my God, the grief has scrambled.
Your brains.
She's like, no, I'm a doctor.
And then he goes, D .O .C .T .O .R.
I thought that part was really funny.
I wasn't laughing.
I thought it was.
I mean, look, it was one of those things where like, you know,
when a comedy goes real bad, like even if something funny happens,
you're too far gone.
That's how I felt.
The opening of the film is unforgivable.
Yeah.
But my first laugh was, I got to say, was almost at the top.
At the opening, I was like, this is terrible.
But then when he's sucking the tear back into his eye and they go,
what is he doing?
And they go, he's un -crying.
It made me laugh.
I was going to do it on the movie corner, but we.
The Trump jokes were so humiliating.
The Trump jokes were awful.
Look, it's also like, know your base, Will Ferrell.
Like, do you really think you don't have Trump people
supporting your movies at this point?
Again, I don't think it was a great movie.
I don't think it was a good movie.
I would go as far as as far as say it was a bad movie.
Yes.
But it was not a zero percent movie.
It was like I was like, all right, I laughed at like
fucking six scenes in this.
That was enough to to make me go, I don't hate it.
I would never buy it.
I don't even know that I would watch it again, but I wasn't mad at it.
I guess that's the best way.
Now, when I say make similar sentiments.
There's anger.
There's not anger.
What what you say similarly, but here's the difference.
You will say Zach and Mary bought a dildo to the wedding
or whatever fucking movie, you know, it is with Zach Efron or whatever.
That was it.
Yeah.
You'll go, I considered a good comedy because there were three laugh out loud moments.
But I mean the same.
I mean, like, you know, you're using completely different words.
I don't mean a good comedy as in like, you know, a fine piece of work.
I mean, like it passed my time.
All right.
Well, that's had you said that I never would have argued it.
Yeah.
Well, all right.
I got to be more precise with my words.
Listen, you don't got to do anything you don't want to do.
And I want you to feel safe here.
I just walk out.
You hear you hear the mic.
You hear my car start outside.
The Simpsons joke they went to like 30 times that I always loved is Marge would be like,
oh, man, you did remember our anniversary.
Like, of course, Marge.
And you hear.
They're all just sitting there in silence listening to it.
Always made me laugh.
That's very funny.
And, you know, it's still fresh after 68 seasons on the air.
You want to go right to the movie corner because I'd like to do a scary stuff today.
Yeah.
I'd like to do a news psycho.
You want to start with a news psycho?
Let's start with a news psycho.
I want to talk about the controversy around Joker.
This Joker picture coming out.
These are big news stories in the movie news world.
Two things.
The first is Joaquin Phoenix walked out of a press conference because a reporter actually
asked him, don't you think it might be dangerous to make a movie like this that
the violence might influence people?
He walked out as I believe he should have.
Did he say something or just stand up?
He literally stood up, walked out, talked to some executives from the studio, then came back.
It was like, next question.
Clearly a man that's like, I have to do a thing right now so I don't throw water at this man.
Sure.
And that'd be bad.
So I'm just going to go talk to the studio people and have them tell me what to say.
Plus, the reporter asking the question was in the full Nicholson Joker make up,
which I thought was just crazy.
Somebody had some tweet the other day and they were like, Jared Leto, when he's the Joker,
sends rats to his coworkers, like loses his mind.
Joaquin Phoenix loses 50 pounds, nearly loses his mind.
Heath Ledger goes completely insane and then it cuts back to Cesar Romero.
That's like so uncommitted to the role that he paints the clown makeup over his mustache.
And they have a picture of him where you see the man's actual mustache through the makeup.
He told me it wouldn't do the part if he had to shave his mustache.
Love it, love it.
So that happened and now they said that the movie will not be played at the theater where
there was the infamous Batman shooting when Dark Knight Rises came out.
Fine, but I mean, could we send any more of the wrong message to these fucking lunatics
that do these horrendous things?
You frightened us.
That's what that says.
Yeah.
That's all that says.
Everybody thinks that they're going to create somehow an incident -free environment in this
country and you're not going to.
And by making the, look, make the right attempts, background checks, sure.
Filtration for people that buy firearms, sure.
I get all that shit.
I get it.
But for Christ sakes, guys, when you go, we're not going to show this Joker movie
at the place where the shooting was with the Batman movie
because we're afraid that that might inspire somebody else to come in shooting.
Well, guess what?
By not showing it there, you just did that anyway.
Yeah, I mean, you did the same fucking thing.
You put the message out to the world that it's on your mind
and that's what these lunatics prey on.
People would do well at this point to just avoid that theater on opening weekend.
Yeah, yeah, I agree.
But, you know, it didn't bother me at all.
I'm sure the people in the town probably wanted there to not be the Joker
in that theater, and they have a right to that as well.
What bothers me is this.
I can't believe we're going to release this thing from the left.
And don't you think this is going to inspire more people to murder, et cetera, et cetera?
Why do we decide which ones are fine and which ones aren't?
Because they are never going to reveal that movie.
What's it called?
The Hunt.
That movie is never going to be released
because Trump and a few others grumbled for like way less amount than the Joker.
They pulled it.
The Joker, I guess, has so much money behind it that they're like,
yeah, we're not going to do it.
Who's making the decision?
Listen, here's at the end of the day, for me, this is what it all is.
The press are disgusting.
Of course.
They're disgusting people that perpetuate a 24 hour news cycle, hence the name of this segment.
And they need their story and they need an evergreen story
because an evergreen story makes money.
And they will get it at any fucking cost, no matter what.
And this is just more of the press stirring up shit.
So they have something to fucking write about.
They're disgusting people.
They have no ethics.
They have no morals.
They don't care about you.
It's a corporate fucking job.
They don't give any more of a fuck about you than the manager at the bank does.
I think what happens, too, is that especially if you're on Twitter, which is always a mistake,
they know that anything Joker related gets hits.
So anytime you get on Twitter, it seems like the only thing
everyone in America is talking about is the Joker.
And it's not true, but it starts to become like
there's nothing else going on in the world but the release of this superhero movie.
And it's and it's and it creates it helps fuel panic.
It helps fuel confusion.
It's fear versus consumption.
It's all this shit going on now with the stupid fucking impossible meat everywhere.
They scare the shit out of you with all this bullshit about red meat.
That's not true.
And then they come out with the solution.
We've got a fake thing that bleeds.
And then you flip it over in the supermarket and read the ingredients.
It's got God knows fucking what in it.
Well, they'll be proven harmful in two years.
Much like, OK, we've got a healthy alternative to smoking, vaping two years later.
Oh, shit. Everybody who vape is now going to die.
And it's why any anytime anyone jumps on a fad, I'm like, you don't want to wait a minute.
You know, like the people who would be dying from cell phones aren't dying yet.
But we're all going to carry these things next to our balls all day.
Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, it's just it's just so crazy to me.
The value and the stake that people put in what the fucking press is saying.
And look, just because Donald Trump hates the press
doesn't mean you have to like the press.
OK, just because he hates them doesn't mean you have to like them.
They sucked before him.
They always sucked. Yes.
All right. And it's just he's utilizing it as a target for his constituents to get by.
Who cares? It doesn't change.
They suck. They're terrible.
It's just, you know, and they flan these fucking.
Look, I got a lot of I got a lot of people actually way more support me than get mad at me.
But people got mad at me.
There were people who got mad at me when I took a stance on Twitter with saying,
like, fuck you if you think somebody should be fired for a joke.
And not one of these people complaining about Dave Chappelle.
We'll talk about the charity of any did for shooting victims for free last week and all that stuff.
And people come back and go, you know, oh, no, this is a
comics should be criticizing one another.
You know, and I got these comedians.
Of course, every one of them, L .A. based, not one fucking New York comic had a problem with it.
But L .A. comics going, oh, yeah, comics should criticize each other, Joe.
You don't the fuck you're talking about.
It's like, don't you fucking moron see and you know who you are.
You're probably not even going to hear this.
But if you do hear it, you know who you are.
What you fucking moron see that this is exactly how fucking Tupac and Biggie and all that shit
happened because the fucking press comes in fanning the fucking flames.
Can you believe what they're talking about in their music?
So and so said this in his song.
Can you believe that person said that in their song?
Do you feel this inspires violence?
And then two people get fucking killed and they go, why did that happen?
We don't get it.
How did that happen?
You know, they follow Britney Spears with cameras and boom mics all over town.
They literally report her location place to fucking place.
And then she collapses from anxiety and exhaustion in a hair salon or whatever.
And they go, how did this happen?
These people are fucking trash.
They're trash.
Anchorman two, strangely enough, depicts the press accurately for the trash that they are.
So fuck you press people.
Fuck your take on violence.
If you're one of these people, I'm not saying everybody is awful.
There's exceptions to every role.
But if you're one of these fucking morons trying to get people stirred up
because you think the Joker movie is going to cause violence, which you don't.
You just know it's going to get you clicks and attention.
You fucking leech.
Fuck you.
All right, I'm done.
Sorry.
And they don't care.
I mean, they well, that's the thing is that they don't care.
I don't agree with everything you said there.
But what I do agree with is that these people definitely don't care about the Joker
and what it's going to do.
And they're the same people who jizzed all over Heath Ledger in The Dark Knight,
which was a great performance.
But it's like it's just whatever way the wind is blowing that day.
I'm so tired of it, man.
I mean, what do you know?
Look, I obviously get pretty amped about this stuff.
Yes.
What do you do?
What are the options?
It's either you cut it all out of your fucking brain completely
and you have no access to the outside world.
You completely cut the tether.
Or you look at this shit every day because there is no kind of look at it sometimes.
There isn't.
There just isn't a way to do that.
You either look at it or you don't.
You were off Twitter a good long while and seemingly much happier.
Then you came back.
I came back because I had a good amount of followers
and I know that in this sick fucking industry that matters to certain people.
But I got to tell you, I'm clearly drifting away towards more independent ventures.
I don't think that's any big surprise given the stuff I say on here about Hollywood
and how I feel about the sort of mainstream part of this industry.
So I probably don't need it.
Or then maybe I need it even more because then I don't have any publicity machine
to help me get my stuff out.
I don't fucking know, dude.
It's like I want to exist in the society we live in.
I want to be a part of it to an extent.
But it just seems like with every passing day to be a part of it,
you have to submit yourself to more maddening shit.
And it's just not fucking healthy.
I mean, my God Almighty, it's like you go on Google News
and you'll see headlines like, you know, Guy Fieri tweets
for the first time in a month or something like that.
You know, and you're like, what is happening?
Or, you know, Justin Bieber liked a post that Selena Gomez put on Instagram.
It's like that shouldn't be a news story if you're in junior high school.
But that's where we're at.
It's it's it's I mean, because I'd love to get off Twitter.
But then where would you get your news?
Like L .A. News is the same thing.
L .A. News is.
Look, it was spotted in Beverly Hills today will be like the third story.
I mean, people always say, you know, look, I'm not trying to change shit at all ever.
Yeah.
But, you know, just to use the to reference the expression,
people say the best way to change the system is from the inside of it.
So I look at it this way.
I'm a newsman.
Yeah, I'm going to become a newsman.
This this is I am launching a 24 hour news network.
But I you know, the way that applies to my life as a stand up is, OK,
well, the best way to criticize everything is from the inside.
I can't criticize it from the outside.
I have to criticize it from the inside.
I have to understand it if I'm going to write material about it.
And, you know, you it's fucking maddening.
It's fucking maddening, man.
It's yeah.
Google News, CNN, Fox, they read like Twitter now.
Yeah. Outrageous.
And Twitter is viewed as a news source.
Like, you know, somebody tweeting something is usually one of the big stories of the day.
And really, the president's pushing us in that direction because a lot of his policy
is tweeted and his attacks on people.
And, you know, you know about all that.
I do. But I never had thought about I never thought of it that way.
Like, he's actually I think he's he's a big part of it
because they have to go to Twitter every day to see what he said.
Folks, take me away, Calgon.
Let's go over to Pat's movie corner.
I saw.
I was very intrigued by this film on Hulu.
The amazing Jonathan documentary and Joe, you had put on Instagram or something
that your buddy Steve Byrne had done an amazing Jonathan document.
My buddy Steve Byrne did the real documentary and this fucking hack came along with his.
Because this one is obviously way flashier and more attention getting
because it's full of hooks and gimmicks.
Yeah.
And it's not a traditional documentary.
Yeah, it's full of tons and hooks and gimmicks.
And then he also tries to paint Steve in it as somehow his competitor or enemy.
But Steve's not seen in the movie, is he?
I watched it.
Well, we I'm not talking out of school.
Steve talked about us about this on the bonfire completely to me
and Jay Okerson when I was cohosting.
But Steve, Steve said they showed up and there was another, you know,
they were shooting and there was another crew and it was kind of obviously an awkward moment.
But they got along very well.
They stayed out of each other's way.
And he said that this guy came to him and said, I want to put you in the documentary.
And Steve said, listen, I don't want to be in your documentary.
I'm here to make my movie about my friend, Jonathan.
That's all I want to do.
I won't get in your way.
Like, I just really want to make a movie about my friend
because he's sick and I want to capture and blah, blah, blah, blah.
This guy said, don't you think you kind of owe me?
I've been I mean, I've been doing this longer than you have,
meaning directing documentaries, I guess.
And he was like, dude, I'm really asking you, man, like, please, like, do I have your word?
Yeah.
And they shook on it.
And he said that was the end of it.
And then Steve said when his documentary premiered at a film festival, this guy was there.
Right.
And he's like, what are you doing here?
And he goes, the guy was like, oh, I just wanted to come support and whatever.
Lo and behold, this guy's documentary comes out and he shapes the entire thing
as if Steve is trying to undermine him.
And then he's got to make his finale going to see Steve's premiere or whatever.
Well, and he got his out like about two weeks before Steve Burns,
which not only makes his not as relevant, but it also adds confusion.
You know, Steve's was out first.
Oh, was that Steve's out first?
And congrats to Steve for it.
I didn't hear about it till after I saw this.
Steve had about five hundred thousand views before this guy's even got one.
We'll get it.
So I'm glad that Steve's is doing well.
But yeah, this guy is I refuse.
I've read about it and I've read the synopsis and I've watched clips here and there,
but I refuse to watch it on Hulu because I'm not giving the guy the fucking watch.
Yeah, I mean, he really does paint it as though he's the hero.
And I watched it the entire time thinking this guy who did it.
Oh, man, he's getting fucked.
I watched it like a Man of La Mancha type thing where I'm like,
this poor director can't catch a break.
So to hear that other side of it is certainly interesting.
Who knew The Amazing Jonathan would be the biggest subject of films?
Who knew?
But for what it is, it's on Hulu and it's it's entertaining.
The first half is like a documentary and then it becomes like it's almost like that.
The movie Catfish where you're not sure if what you're watching is fake or real or what's going on.
And the truth of what it all is when it when you finally comes out is not that exciting.
But I thought it was worth a look and go see Steve Burns as well.
Compare and contrast.
I watched Steve's is available for free on YouTube.
So check that out.
I watched all that jazz, which I hadn't seen since I was a kid.
I was on an airplane flying back to the city of a fine city of ours.
And excuse me, excuse me.
I'm on JetBlue.
JetBlue has got a number of classic titles unedited.
OK, hats off to them for that.
Delta has started to really edit their films.
We're at least show edited versions.
But I thought, you know.
I want a Fosse kick.
Let me watch them all that jazz.
And what better screen than the built into the back of a seat airplane?
What did you want me to do?
Play with my balls?
Well, I saw it at the Egyptian theater a couple of weeks ago.
Oh, well, you're better than me.
Cabaret Fosse night.
I I loved watching the movie again.
I hadn't seen it in forever.
I barely remembered anything about it.
It's just a tremendous film.
It is so mirrored to Fosse's life.
I'm confused as to why he even bothered changing the names.
Yeah.
I mean, he had his most recent ex girlfriend.
And ranking.
Yeah. Play his current girlfriend in the movie.
I mean, it's.
He's cutting a movie about Lenny Bruce in the movie.
But it's somehow not Lenny Bruce.
But it's not. They never call him Lenny Bruce.
He's directing a musical that's basically Chicago, right?
It's not Chicago.
His wife, ex wife is clearly supposed to be Gwen Verde.
You know, it's it's it's his life
to the point where when I was watching it, I was like,
there's stuff in Fosse Verden Verden that.
Did they take it from this?
Or was it just this was that close to the real thing that that it
it was that close to the real thing, but they had books.
There are very detailed biographies of Bob Fosse they use.
But all that jazz helps.
I mean, it's very similar.
Like there's a and there's a point where I was like,
is Sam Rockwell's Fosse based more on Rob Scheider's?
Portrayal of Joe Gideon,
because they're eerily similar at times.
I think it contributed, but there's so much Fosse footage.
I'm sure Scheider did the same research that.
Well, Fosse was directing Scheider.
Rockwell did. Yeah, but yeah.
But I mean, I tried to look up Fosse footage after I watched the.
I couldn't find much. I couldn't find much interview footage.
I mean, there's got to be some.
I mean, there's interviews on the all that jazz and cabaret DVDs.
You know, like there's stuff out there.
OK, anyway, I loved it.
For some reason, I remembered it being in black and white and in color,
and it's not. It's just in color.
Great performance from Alf's dad in a supporting role.
Oh, dude, he's off.
He clearly Fosse was like, I want you to go as big as human.
Huge. Yeah.
He's a crackhead now. That's sad.
He's dead.
He died. Yeah.
OK, he died about a month ago.
Crack will do it.
It'll do it.
And then also Ben Vereen is off the fucking charts in this thing.
He is. Ben Vereen's always scared me because of he's creepy.
Zubali Zoo. Yeah.
Which I watched when I was a kid.
He's he's creepy in this movie.
That finality finale where they do bye bye life is fucking creepy.
It is. Agreed.
70s musicals are creepy.
There's a reason I own the whiz.
There's a reason I own whiz is creepy.
Jesus Christ superstar creepy weird.
So it's an awesome movie.
I would I think I would like to get a blu ray of all that jazz criterion.
Oh, really?
Scoop it up. It's great.
I'll scope, baby. I'll scope.
I saw all that jazz and cabaret at the Egyptian theater
and cabaret is a hell of a picture, too, by the way, better than I recalled.
But I also saw Godfather one and two, which is always a treat.
If you can go to the theater and see it in 35 millimeter, I mean, six hours,
but it flies right by.
Then I came home and watched a little picture that I hadn't seen in 25 years.
Godfather part three.
It's a movie that I have long defended off of a viewing when I was like 13.
I'll be like, it's not as bad as people say.
And Sophia Coppola is not as bad as people say.
And this and that this movie sucks.
And Sophia Coppola is not giving a performance.
It's it's embarrassing.
I like the picture.
They talk in there about how Winona Ryder was supposed to do it
and dropped out due to exhaustion, which is usually Hollywood talk for drug addiction.
But they talk, you know, Julia Roberts was supposed to do it, fell out,
and they couldn't get anybody in there.
But it's like your Francis Ford Coppola making the Godfather three.
He could have gotten anyone in Hollywood.
He acted like, you know, I had no options.
She dropped out at the last minute.
Nobody was available.
Bridget Fonda has four lines in the thing.
Slide her over.
She's a great actress.
Right.
I mean, I really like Sophia Coppola as a director.
Some of her movies.
I was appalled by this.
I don't know.
I don't know how I've been defending this movie for so long.
The Joey Zaza stuff.
And, you know, Andy Garcia is decent in it, but the story just kind of lurches around.
The Catholic Church stuff doesn't really work.
He does talk.
I listen to a little bit of the commentary and he had a movie planned with DiCaprio
as a young sonny, you know, James Conn from the first.
And it was going to be dealing with like much like Godfather two flashbacks to DiCaprio
as a young sonny.
And then the present day, Andy Garcia mixing it up and they couldn't get financing,
I guess, because nobody's going to build a movie around Garcia now.
But DiCaprio would get it made.
So maybe it'll happen.
I doubt it'll ever happen.
And by the time they does happen, they'll be like, we have to age DiCaprio 30 years.
For sure.
I I like the movie.
I know that knowing the backstory of it made me like it more.
You know, Coppola and Putzo went to the studio and said,
we want to do a Michael Corleone epilogue.
And it's called The Death of Michael Corleone.
It is not The Godfather Part Three.
It's about how this man's life finally ends.
And he said the studio insisted and insisted it has to be Godfather three.
And then the more it moved in that direction, the more it fell into the shadow of the first two,
which is exactly what they didn't want to do.
So when you look at it along those lines, I do think it brings closure to the story.
I think it is a beautifully poetic moment at the end that he does die
legitimate but completely alone.
Yes, and he is his his lust for legitimacy comes literally at the cost of his entire
everybody he's ever loved.
And it was supposed to be the opposite of that.
I think that's an awesome, awesome ending.
But I hear you.
It's not the most exciting film.
Coppola is supposed to be putting out, you know, because now nobody will let him make a movie.
He goes back and makes money off all his old movies.
So I really like the new Apocalypse Now cut.
I saw it twice, the theater.
He's doing Godfather three, a recut that's supposed to be like 45 minutes shorter.
And there is enough good stuff in the Godfather three that you're like,
that's a pretty good mob movie is how I felt about it.
Yeah, of course, it's in the shadow of two of the best movies ever made.
But 45 minutes out of this thing would make all the difference in the world.
I mean, there are there are scenes where you're like, why was this here?
I guess they probably wanted it to be three hours like the others.
They didn't have three hours worth of material here.
The other tough part of it, too, is Pacino at that point
had gone through such a physical and vocal transformation.
Yeah, it's hard to connect him to the original character, right?
He sounds and looks like a different human being completely.
So that's tough.
Is it worth I have them over there and I've never even cracked them,
but I have the Coppola restoration of the trilogy.
Is that worth hanging on to or do I or should I just get like the blue rays?
You have to get the blur.
I mean, they're they're incredible and they're like insanely cheap.
You can get the trilogy with this amazing disk of extras with like
everybody's audition tapes from the Godfather.
You have to get it.
All right. And it's cheap.
But yeah, I mean, three, you know, it's just not something.
There's something missing from it.
It just doesn't move you in the way the others do or something.
Well, a lot's missing.
The Duval said no because he was pissed about the pay gap between him and Pacino.
Yes. So then you got.
George Hamilton, George Hamilton in there.
Holy shit.
I mean, these are not good replacements.
You can't replace Winona Ryder with Sophia Coppola.
Also, too, there are odd story elements that that throw you off guard.
The diabetes thing is unnecessary.
Yeah, I don't know why they're doing that.
It would be just as interesting and far less distracting to just see
an old man starting to have nervous panic attacks over his past.
The incestual thing with the cousins is weird.
They never really explain why I wondered that is when Winona Ryder dropped out.
Julia Roberts dropped out.
All these people dropped out when I was watching it again.
I was like, maybe they dropped out because their agent were like,
you want to do a movie where you're fucking your cousin?
Like, especially at that time, I just saying,
I just didn't get it.
I do think it's a great debut for Garcia.
He's very good.
And I love I love Montaigne.
I just he's always he's when I love when Montaigne plays a prick.
It makes me laugh.
I like it.
Tim is always bored me.
I don't know why he's a little bit odd.
He's a kind of an odd guy.
Like, and he's got a, you know, he's got a strange sort of timber to his voice.
Yeah.
But sort of a Romano vibe.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
But anyway, I'll just do one more because Holmes and Watson was going to be my other one for this.
But I on the same theme, I watched rewatched Young Sherlock Holmes.
Never seen it.
Hadn't seen it since I was a kid, man.
And it's if you haven't seen it, watch it.
It is 110 percent super fun.
Spielberg produced popcorn adventure movie for young people from the late 80s.
It's got one of the first ever CGI significant CGI sequences in it where stain a night, a stain,
a stained glass picture of a night comes to life and actually sword fights a guy.
And it looks really fucking cool, especially for the time.
It's a really fun Sherlock Holmes adventure.
The kid who plays Sherlock is great.
The kid who plays Watson is great.
It's just it's it's got that Goonies vibe to it.
You know, it's a lot, a lot, a lot of fun directed by I'm blanking.
But, you know, one of the guys you would think it was directed by,
like fucking Richard Donner or somebody like that.
Young Sherlock, who did direct it?
I'm really blanking.
I just watched three o 'clock high.
Chris Columbus might have written it.
Yeah.
Directed by Barry Levinson.
Barry Levinson, three o 'clock.
Levinson was still doing like big, big kind of movies.
Spielberg had taken his name off of when he saw the film.
He pulled this guy out of film school, Phil Joannou, who did State of Grace and
U2 Rattle and Hum.
And he was like, your first movie is going to be an Amblin three o 'clock high.
You can rewrite the script.
He gives his like 23 year old kid full full reign, sees the movie and is like,
you made a Scorsese movie for teens.
I wanted you to make a John Hughes movie and pulled his name off.
Three o 'clock high is an awesome movie.
It's a very cool movie.
Yeah.
So Spielberg is a strange, strange character.
And probably has some very, very large skeletons in a very deep closet.
Yeah.
I mean, I guess I'll do three o 'clock high for mine.
I mean, I got the Shout Factory Blu -ray and, you know, the biggest
is Jeffrey Tambor.
It's a Casey Sizemasko who was around the sort of brat pack, but was never a crucial part.
And three o 'clock high weirdly is one of those because I used to rent anything that
wasn't rated R over and over and over again.
And it's one that I had seen and didn't have that big a memory of.
But it's memorable only because of the way it's shot.
I mean, Spielberg was completely wrong.
If they had done the story straight, no one would be talking about three o 'clock
high.
And instead you got the Shout Factory with all these great interviews and stuff on it.
And the thing is shot like it was shot by the other Barry, Barry Sonnenfeld,
who did Men in Black and was the DP on some of the coolest looking movies ever made.
Evil Dead 2, he did Raising Arizona.
You know, all those shots were like the cameras on the end of a
board running through the woods and all that.
That's like Barry Sonnenfeld style.
So in my in my opinion, it would have been an extremely forgettable teen
bully movie without all the crazy camera work that Spielberg had some big problem with.
If you haven't seen it, check it out.
It's very fun.
I got a scary stuff before we do the movie.
All right.
Now, I pulled the DVDs from the shelf while I do my scary stuff.
Do me a favor.
You look over the back of that.
It sounds like this might be worth keeping.
I don't know because you're going to have zero interest in my scary stuff.
Go on.
The Legend of Zelda Link's Awakening is out.
By the time you hear this, it's been out for a while.
But gang, what more can I say other than if you are a fan of the Legend of Zelda series
in the traditional games, not the Breath of the Wild open world style, you need.
Well, I guess they're all sort of open world in their own way.
But you know what I mean.
Go get this game.
It is fucking beautiful.
The graphic design is insane.
It looks like little plastic.
Literally looks like you're controlling little plastic figurines.
It's crazy how good this thing looks.
And it's just an incredible.
Some people are like, well, I played Link's Awakening
when it came out on the Game Boy in 1989 or whatever it was.
It's like, this is not that game.
This is a this is a complete remake of that game.
It's not just an HD upgrade.
There's all these like Super Mario style levels that turn into side scroll and
and the Mario characters are in it.
And it's awesome.
It's such an awesome game and plenty of monsters.
So that qualifies it for scary stuff.
So go check that out.
That you are certainly correct that I had no interest.
Do you think I should keep this?
To me, the difference between Blu Ray and DVD is night and day.
I think Blu Rays are as good as movies can look.
And it does have a lot more extras, but will it sit on your shelf like this one did for years?
Does does the Coppola Restoration exist on Blu Ray?
Yeah.
Oh, it does.
Oh, OK.
I'll sell it then.
But they're not going to give you any money for it.
I might get five bucks for this.
OK, maybe two.
I take that 50 percent.
Take the stickers off.
If you got that one guy, I don't even go up to that one guy anymore.
And maybe I walk my stuff right back out to the car.
Which guy?
He's like a 50 year old black guy with like grayish black hair.
Uh huh.
He's the one who shook his head and disgust when he saw you walking up.
I think he's the one who will like look through a bag of 200 things and go,
I can give you like a dollar.
Otherwise, just no.
Then the other guy will pay you full price for things.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, if you see him, don't don't bring it up.
He won't help.
Uh, folks, let's get to the task at hand, which is stranger things.
Season three, the gang's back sheriff, whatever Winona, the kids.
Uma Thurman's daughter and Ethan Hawke's daughter is now in it.
And I thought was fine.
I am in love with her and I want to marry her.
OK, I think she's 15.
No, she's 21.
I will.
OK, still.
Uh, she's.
One of the most wonderful human beings I've ever seen exist.
Well, I was completely indifferent to her.
I love that.
I thought she talked exactly like her mom, which she does.
She reminded me of girls I went to high school with.
OK, a lot of girls I went to high school with.
And I think that just kind of stirred something up in old Joe.
OK, that being said, I'll probably never even meet her.
No.
Uh, yeah, she's new.
There's a unbelievably annoying new character, the girl who likes ice cream a lot.
Oh, which is about as bad as television gets.
I mean, folks, you want to we'll get to the overall story in a second,
but you want to talk about.
Just a step backwards in the evolution of entertainment and diversity and all this thing.
I mean, this couldn't be worse.
They got they were they got a they got a 10 year old black girl in this thing
who's clearly been written by a 50 year old white man, you know, and she like.
It's it's she she somehow magically knows everything about like science,
like they'll be in a bind and she'll start spouting out all the and like.
But there's no hint that she's like a bookworm or anything.
And then she's like sassy and she curses, which, by the way,
I know all of you were clamoring for this.
The the little black kid that's in Halloween, the new Halloween movie,
he's coming back, they announced to Halloween for Halloween kills.
OK, for the scene, he was the best part of Halloween.
It's just such a hack stock, frankly, racist fucking character.
We're going to write in a little black kid and he's going to be super sassy
and act like he's 40 years old and he's going to curse.
It's like how many times they're going to write that fucking character.
And I felt like that's what this little girl was.
I mean, what made it worse is that you could feel the sweat on it
of how much they wanted her to be like a breakout character.
And you just she didn't catch on at all.
She was very annoying, not the actress's fault.
No, but you work with what you're fucking handed, man.
Yeah, it's it remains a very white show.
A lot of shows get to just keep doing that.
No one says anything about them.
It all depends on which ones they decide they're upset with.
But yeah, Stranger Things is essentially entirely white,
which made this kind of egregious character stand out all the more.
But it's not like they don't introduce other new characters.
Like, you know, it's Modine.
And then who's the guy who looks exactly like Modine?
Matthew Modine and then carry a rider.
Oh, Carrie Elwes gets added to the cast like,
let's get a guy who not only is another middle edged white dude,
but looks identical to Matthew Modine.
And also to can somebody get a shot at something?
What do you mean?
Can well, I shouldn't say this.
This show has introduced a lot of new faces to people I shouldn't come.
But I'm just like sitting there scratching my head like.
You're stunt casting Carrie Elway.
Well, I guess because he's from the 80s,
but, you know, it's it doesn't really.
Nobody remembers.
Every bit is offensive.
And it's weird that this is the season they chose to like make these weird errors
because Winona Ryder is given absolutely nothing to do.
She was when this show started, my number one reason for watching.
I've always loved Winona Ryder.
This season, she is literally running behind the sheriff, David Harbour,
going like, come on, come on.
She has one line of scene that's like, but are you sure?
Well, he does everything.
She's given nothing to play.
And I honestly think that sucks.
Winona is great.
You shouldn't have done that to her.
Should have done it like that.
Let's let's let's real quick.
Just give a quick synopsis of the show.
That'll have to be you because I don't want anybody to be lost
in this small town in Michigan where everybody thought all the weird shit had stopped.
It's still going on.
There's your fucking synopsis.
Strange things.
Things are still coming through the vagina in the wall.
Yeah, that that for from the other dimension.
Real quick.
Why is the portal to another dimension always a vagina in it to the deadlight thing?
You're looking into a vagina with teeth.
It looks like they modeled it on a vagina.
And they do the same exact thing and stranger things.
Yeah, yeah.
It's because the nerds who make this shit are scared of pussy.
Well, that's probably.
Anyway, so they're there.
So wait, what's happening now?
They're OK.
So there's the bad shit isn't gone from the town.
And then and then David Harbor finds that the sheriff finds out that the bad shit's
not gone from Winona Ryder and acts like she's crazy.
You think after you've dealt with this twice now, you'd be like, oh, really?
It's still going on for Christ sakes.
All right, here we go again.
You know, but those kind of resets don't ever work for me on a TV show.
No, it's one.
And I love these down and down, but it's one of the reasons why eventually I had to tune
out because I was like, you're hitting reset every season with this guy.
Let him learn one thing, one thing.
Well, I mean, that's a show I deeply care about.
They would give him a step forward from time to time with that.
Well, yeah, but then they would reset.
That's true.
Like it's always sunny.
I like that they made Matt Gay and there is some sort of new insight he has because of
that.
It's not the most he's still an awful person on the show, but it's something.
So in a show where you fought fucking intergalactic or interdimensional aliens or
whatever the fuck they're called for two years, maybe the third time it comes around,
you don't go, oh, horse shit.
And it's just kind of the same aliens and the same set pieces and the same drama.
It's the line that drove me crazy in Crystal Skull.
And I'm not even a Crystal Skull hater.
But the line that drove me crazy is like when he's when Indiana Jones is like telling
the legend to Shia LaBeouf.
Yeah.
And he goes, so you said the city's made out of gold or whatever.
And he's like, I don't know.
It's just a story, kid.
It's like you have seen things, you know, it's possible.
Yeah.
Don't talk like that.
Right, right.
Anyway, so that's the basic story.
And this time, the way it's taking or trying to take over this town, which God only knows
why it gives a fuck about this town, it's it's turning citizens.
It's like possessing citizens and then turning them into sludge that then helps form a giant
monster.
And the leader of these possessed citizens and the only one who never gets turned into
is bad boy Billy from season two, who for some reason at the top of this season with
zero explanation, Mike's mom tries to fuck.
Yeah, they never hint that they're that she's unhappy in the marriage.
They never hint that she's like, you know, I was the hot lady and now I'm a housewife
and I feel that there's no motivation for it.
Right.
And then it just makes you hate her for the rest of the season.
They really threw her down the river.
Yeah, for sure.
I mean, for me, some of those possession scenes were well done.
The one at the family dinner table.
Yeah, that was cool.
Was effective.
I loved hearing the Never Ending Story theme song performed, which is an amazing.
That song was ridiculous.
That's I love the song.
Yeah.
And it made me happy to see that little kid singing it.
Yeah, that's all I'm saying.
But yeah, but I mean, this fucking thing, they literally do a full acapella version
of the Never Ending Story in the finale of the season.
And you're sitting there going, this is literally just there to get you excited
about the song that it doesn't tie into anything.
No, not not one part of this movie is related or the season relates to the Never Ending Story.
They keep doing the back to the future things.
And I'm like, are they going to get into something about plutonium here?
What the kid with the teeth remains the highlight.
But this what I mean, season three, we should have been given something new,
something that shakes things up a little more than this one did.
I will say it remains extremely watchable.
Heather and I watched this thing in two nights, four hours a night.
Didn't bat an eye, but it just left you feeling empty.
We didn't discuss any of the episodes when they were over.
We didn't discuss the season when it was over.
We were just like, now we watch that.
I was very excited at the beginning of this thing.
I was enjoying it.
I was like, all right, this one's a lot more jovial.
This one is clearly more of an adventure.
It's way this is playing way more like they live a lot of cussing.
I know. Yeah.
Which was new for them.
Pinkstone pointed out he was like, you know, the new Stranger Things was
it was basically Red Dawn with Monsters, which I agreed with.
Yeah, they were clearly doing a different take on a different 80s genre,
which I thought was interesting.
But it was just a better show when it was a spooky small town story.
This thing now, you're going to have to do your own thing and create your own story.
You can't just keep doing little riffs on others shot others shot ship.
Well, also, too, they keep making it bigger and bigger and bigger.
And now they're into a thing where the Russians are there.
Yeah. And you've got a 14 year old and an 18 year old kid
somehow outsmarting Russians in the in a Russian fortress.
It's like, guys, this is getting a little fucking ridiculous.
Like, come on while like learning how to fall in love and other things.
You know, it's yeah, it's a lot to believe that it remains to me
entertaining when the next season comes around.
I'm going to put it on, but it's time to introduce something new,
raise the stakes, give us some other dynamic between Harbor and Rider
because clearly they had nothing for them to do this year.
Harbor just kind of runs around being a dick.
You know, I had issues with it.
And then they do the thing.
And this is one of my least favorite writing tropes you could ever do.
They do the thing where they play out a cliche
and then to get away with playing out the cliche,
they have a character in the scene call out the cliche.
Yeah. So it's like they'll they do this thing where
it's clear that Harbor and Rider want to fuck the whole time.
And and, you know, and then there's a scene where they're fighting
and it's like that classic scene where
if they weren't driving a car while they were fighting, they would like start kissing.
You know what I mean?
And then like in the middle of the scene.
What's that kid's name?
Who's 40, but looks like he's 68.
Brett Gellman. Oh, yeah.
Gellman's in the backseat and he goes and he goes,
Can you two get it over with and just have sex?
And you're like the only thing worse than you guys
steering into the curve of Harbor and Winona Rider being in love.
Yeah, is now having another is then playing it out right through like the bickering
and then on top of it, having this guy yell out the thing like,
Oh, it's so obvious.
And it's like, guys, that doesn't make it a better story.
Yeah, the Harbors overprotectiveness of his daughter
were real thin as well.
After a certain point, watching those kids make out
was getting a little weird after it was gross.
It was gross.
And Millie Bobby Brown, we talked about in the it chapter.
Or was it today?
What was today when you were talking about Julianne more over emoting?
Yeah, yeah.
Was that this episode or the it?
No, it was it was the previous one.
Okay.
But I mean, again, Millie Bobby Brown, it's like I can't.
I can't watch her breathe heavily and weep anymore.
She weeps all through Godzilla, King of the Monsters.
Yeah, I'm just bored with it.
And it was my I'm not bringing up Midsummer to bring it up.
I'm just saying it was one of the things I didn't like about Midsummer.
I'm like, all right, you can cry.
I get it.
But let's get like, well, Joe, I mean, you've been face to face
with women crying your whole life.
You know, and I always say the same thing.
It's triggering for I say the same thing, baby.
You knew I had to go from the beginning.
Don't give me the waterworks.
And then you press play on free bird on a little boombox
and take your motorcycle out of town.
Because this bird, you cannot change.
In all fairness, when I say this bird, I do point to my crotch.
Yeah, which leads to more crying.
You don't know when to quit.
So, yeah, folks, Stranger Things is kind of more of the same.
It's it'll pass the time.
I'm sure you've seen it by now.
Well, oddly, though, I mean, oddly, it's it's I understand why you would say that.
But I almost think it's not more of the same.
And that's some.
And then it but it's also not any.
It's worse.
Yeah. You know, like more of the same would have been bad, too.
But this was not any.
This to me felt like I felt it needed a new jolt that I was not getting.
And then Sean Astin gave me that jolt in season two.
But this season was missing that.
And it was an ice cream girl.
You know, the show's in trouble when the most exciting moment is is a Paul Reiser cameo.
That's true.
At the end of it.
Well, when they when they cut to Sean Astin in this one, I was like, oh, right.
He's not around this season.
And that really sucks because to me, he really his emotional story really pulled me through to.
So I don't know.
I hope they come back strong for four.
And I hope it doesn't go on forever because they're clearly already kind of running low on ideas.
I think they said they're going to do five.
I thought sounds right.
I thought two was a push.
And I thought they pulled it off.
I love to.
Yeah, this now.
And it's also at that point in the series where we're like in all like movie franchises
that are fantastic and hits this point where the characters start just being like,
OK, how did she just do that?
And then one other character goes, she's got superpowers.
OK, you're all caught up.
Right.
And then they're just they're just going, OK, because obviously it's born to the viewer
to go through the exposition or show somebody in disbelief.
But I'm sorry, there's a way that you have to do that.
It can't just be everybody just accepts everything right from the beginning.
Right.
Because we don't have time to get into it again.
I just don't think there's anything left in the tank.
Nobody wants to see these kids running around with pubes.
And that's what's happening now.
And it's weird.
Well, in these as they're not showing us the pubes, at least as these characters.
Right.
Look, in another year, if they're not banging each other, it's going to be weird.
Somebody's going to lose their virginity and then it's going to be like Buffy,
the vampire slayer.
Yeah.
And nobody wants to see that.
Folks are our next show.
I can almost guarantee you will be Joker.
I'm sure you'll all see that.
What else is coming out?
Well, Doctor Sleep would be a good one.
We should definitely do the Shining sequel.
Yeah.
So those are both coming out.
I'm seeing The Shining on Thursday with Miss Kilgara for my wife.
Oh, thanks for the invite.
You're not here.
I know.
But it would have been nice anyway.
Jesus.
Can I just get an invite?
It would have been nice for you to invite me even though I won't be here.
I know.
I'm just kidding.
God damn it.
I'm kidding.
So look for Joker and Doctor Sleep probably on the December app.
And if you want to see this.
Well, no, I'm forgetting about the timeline.
Those are both November movies.
So you'll have seen them by now.
I am on Twitter and Instagram.
Jokers out this weekend, isn't it?
Next weekend.
OK.
Oh, sorry.
I stepped on your plug.
Sorry.
No, that's it.
Jotaro's a comedy, Instagram and Twitter.
Jotaro's a comedian on Facebook.
Jotaro's info for show dates and whatever.
I'll be at the Come and Take It Fest, November 6th and 7th.
So look for me there in Houston, Texas.
Take care.
See you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.