Hey everyone, welcome to a new episode of We'll See You In Hell,
the podcast where we watch movies and talk about them while we watch them
and then give you the chance to either listen along while you watch or just
listen to us. It's up to you. Sounds like a lot of fun to me.
That's Pat Walsh. Hey guys, I'm Joe DeRosa.
This is now a part of the Fangoria podcast network for more information about
the network, including other programs, how to follow the show, and find past
episodes of We'll See You In Hell, or episodes of any show for that matter.
Please visit Fangoria .com. Now let's get down to it today. We are watching.
We have chosen, I want to say Pat has chosen Leopardcon.
Warwick Davis, Jen Aniston, I guess, is that pre -friends?
Yeah, this is pre... Yes, it would have to be us, I suppose, yeah.
Yeah, Jennifer Aniston didn't ask for a release from friends to shoot Leopardcon.
Sure. This is the original, as Pat has mentioned,
Warwick by the cast, Warwick Davis, Jen Aniston.
This is not the remake, which somehow managed to be worse than the original.
I don't know how the fuck they pulled that off, but God bless them, they did.
Anyway, you know the deal if you've listened to the show before.
If you don't, now's the time to go to your Netflix and find the movie itself.
If you are watching, we will give you a moment here to pause and do that.
So go ahead and hit pause.
Okay, you got the movie.
It's a three -step process.
Right now what you're going to do is you're going to hit play.
In the second, you see frame one of the movie.
We need you to pause it again.
Second, you see frame one of the movie.
Why do we do this?
Because everybody has different load times on their Apple TVs or whatever their
devices are that they're watching.
We're waiting for ours to load now.
It's a matter of fact, we've got a spinning wheel here today.
Okay, we're paused.
You got a black screen on pause.
And I guess we're going to go one, two, three, then play.
So we can start together.
Black screen on pause.
Was that brief enough this time?
It was.
I wasn't near as annoyed as I was the other two times.
All right, one, two, three, play.
We're rolling.
I'd like to start by congratulating the lovely Jan Anderson
on her recent marriage to Justin Thoreau.
They got married because I'm sure she's listening to this.
They did get married.
Long time coming for Jen, she said a hard road to hoe.
Road to hoe?
Road to hoe.
Or rope?
Road line to hoe?
Okay.
I heard it was splitsville.
Corners have been looking at us weekly.
Yeah, the Corners is when the checkout line.
Did it have the tear mark down the center of their photo?
Yeah, it was the tear mark.
I like when there's the tear mark.
I do too.
I think that's a nice effect.
Every like erotic thriller of the 90s also had that like a family photo
with a big crack down the center.
Like hand the rocks the cradle and that kind of shit.
Yes.
Now, if you've never seen the movie leprechaun,
you know already by our conversation how much you need to pay attention to anything.
We're just completely ignoring the opening of the film.
It does open with the instant reveal of the leprechaun himself.
It's the first thing you see in the movie.
Zero mystery.
Yeah, I got to tell you it.
Now, if I'm sitting down to write leprechaun where it says in the description,
there's a mysterious leprechaun living in their basement.
Look at this.
Warwick Davis top billing over Jennifer Aniston.
This was a different time.
But wow, that's a cheap graphic there too.
Mysterious leprechaun, they don't start by having a family move in and there's a strange knock
or they find a gold de balloon in the microwave or something like that and go, what is this?
They show you a leprechaun.
Immediately.
Counting gold.
Very dumb.
I bet that was a producer with a big cigar and he was like, the picture is called leprechaun.
You got to show him a leprechaun.
First five minutes, baby.
So now we got we're in Ireland, I assume, because the guy just pounded a bottle of James
and as he got out of his limousine and then threw it on the ground.
I haven't drank in a couple of weeks and when I saw that, James and bottle,
I started to salivate.
It always looks delicious on screen, doesn't it?
It really does.
When you see a guy guzzling whiskey on screen,
you see a handsome, successful guy like this.
He's wearing a nice, uh, Colonel Sanders suit, a beautiful hair piece.
Arrives in a limousine to this shack on the Irish countryside as a butler or limo driver.
Maybe both.
The guy seems to be doing everything.
Sure.
I would dare say that this guy has found some of the leprechaun's gold.
Right.
And that's our setup here.
How is she not recoiling from his breath?
Because they're Irish.
That's, you know, that's that's Jameson is like toothpaste.
That's true.
Sent.
Anytime you see an Irish, not just an any guy, guzzling the whiskey,
you know, there's always those scenes in like movies where they go up into like the executive's office
and he's got the the glass to canner things.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And yet they pour it out and have a drink.
It always looks like it's like what tastes like iced tea.
Peach snapple.
Well, they're definitely drinking iced tea.
Yeah, never tastes like that when you get it at old J's bar.
I think there's a rule in film and television that you can't actually be drinking alcohol.
Because I remember that final drunken interview with the cast of cheers.
They said they were never drinking actual beer because they weren't allowed to.
But they were drunk in the final interview.
The final interview, which I hope you can find on YouTube,
it's Leno trying desperately to control like 14 blackout drunk actors.
On the set of and cheers are on the tonight show.
He does the interview on the set of cheers and they are so messed up and I guarantee
that they've probably tried to scrub it from the internet, but I hope it's still out there.
Well, Kelsey Grammer has claimed publicly that he doesn't even remember shooting the final episode.
He was so drunk.
I love that.
That makes me happy.
Now, I love it too. What made you take a drinking break?
Well, you and I are similar in that we drink too much sometimes and also I'm very Catholic,
which there's a lot of punishment to yourself that goes on, a lot of guilt, a lot of self -loathing.
Right.
And when I hit one of those pockets, I usually abandon all drinking.
I eat incredibly healthy.
Just clean things up for about a month.
I do feel much better, but I'd be lying if I said I didn't crave the occasional alkybeth.
I think I'm approaching one of those breaks myself as we were discussing before.
We almost didn't do the podcast today, folks.
I was in quite a mood.
But I got to tell you, I'm happy that we're doing it.
It's always great to see Pat Walsh's face.
Oh, thanks.
And he picks leprechaun, which I love.
I'm already feeling great. We're laughing.
We're having a good time.
There's a voice coming out of a suitcase right now on the screen.
And I'm not sure if that's the leprechaun's evil magic or if they're just drunk.
No, that's what they're hearing a voice come out of a suitcase.
I watch this on VHS. I guess I must have been 12, 13.
I have no real recollection of it.
Probably remember the aforementioned drinking.
Well, I remember when I saw this.
I remember seeing trailers for it when it was in the theater.
I wanted to see it desperately.
Wow.
I liked at the age.
I don't know. I was probably 11 when this came out.
12 something like that.
At that age, I loved any hard thing that had to do with a little goblin shirt or a doll that came
to life. Anything small. I like tiny horror in those days.
And I didn't get to the theater.
I think because my mom wouldn't take me or something.
And then I remember going to the West Coast video in my neighborhood.
And they had the dry erase board behind the counter to let you know what was coming out soon.
And I remember seeing leprechaun on there like a month before it came out.
I counted the days.
Rented it.
Reserved it.
Rented at the day came out.
Watched it.
Don't think I got even 25 minutes into it before I turned it off.
You didn't finish it?
I finished it in like in like sections.
Oh, okay.
I just even at that age, I was like, this is not a really a great movie.
I'm always very committed to finishing a movie regardless of how shitty it is.
I have a twin Javoc D with that.
And I'll watch a movie for two and a half hours, even if I hate every second of it,
because I got to get to the end of it.
So I can say I've seen that movie.
I fast what I do is now is I'll fast forward.
Sure.
And I'll get the gist of each scene at the top of it and then fast forward and go,
okay, I know what's happening.
Yeah.
And then I just go to the end.
I watched Bicentennial Man in like five -minute increments over the course of maybe six months.
It was one of the hardest movies I've ever had to sit through.
I, you know, I attest that's tougher to get through than awakenings.
Oh, I love awakenings.
I love awakenings.
I'm saying for different reasons, you find that a sad movie.
That's a hard break.
I find Bicentennial Man more heartbreaking and gut -wrenching or awakening.
No, it's pretty pain.
Now, if you are watching the guy,
what's this guy's name?
Colonel Sanders.
Shameless, probably.
Shameless McSanders is trying to kill the leprechaun with a gun.
But he's holding up now a four -leaf clover.
Which...
Massaging the lady's head.
Because the leprechaun murdered the guy's wife.
Yeah.
And now he's rubbing her head as she's dead to be like,
I murdered your wife.
So he, you know, it's taunting, demon taunts, as they say.
But the four -leaf clover is what repels the leprechaun.
But now his gun heard it.
Which I haven't seen this movie in a while.
You'd think something with magic.
Usually the gun is useless against whatever villain you're trying to kill in a horror movie.
I remember this. He puts the four -leaf clover, he puts the leprechaun in a crate,
and then puts the four -leaf clover on top of the crate, and the leprechaun can't fight it.
Is she the size of that clover?
It's a big old clove.
It's a big clover.
I used to spend to give you a little taste of how exhilarating my childhood was.
I would spend hours and hours looking for four -leaf clover.
I would try finding them too as a child.
And now, I don't think kids even go outside.
It was a simpler day.
Did you find any?
I think I found one once.
I would always find a three with a little brown chunk on it of dirt and pretend that I had found one
and my mom and I was like, yeah, that looks really good, Pat.
Right, right.
Even your mom couldn't be bothered with your bullshit.
I had nothing to do.
I worked at Blockbuster Video for many years.
I hate to brag.
And I was there during the leprechaun in the Hood days.
Oh, yeah.
Have you seen that one?
I've seen all of them.
Okay, does he talk in a hip -hop petois?
Not in this one.
Well, no, in any other...
Oh, in leprechaun, no.
No, he still talks like the leprechaun.
He doesn't make any like rap jokes or like...
I'm picturing some vaguely racist things.
Leprechaun in the Hood is sort of like sort of a comedy.
Okay.
It hopes on us.
I think that's back.
No, snoops out.
And the iced tea is in it.
Oh, sure.
Or is that the second one?
One, there's leprechaun back to the Hood and leprechaun in the Hood.
One of them has iced tea in it and it's a sort of like a comedy.
Okay.
Now, this is what kills me.
The guy does all this trouble to get the thing into the crate, puts the four leaf clover on the crate
so it can't escape.
Then he's going to burn the crate.
Why can't the leprechaun escape because of the four leaf clover?
Yeah.
I thought leprechaun's loved four leaf clover.
This is real simple writing, Pat.
Like you said, the executive said you got to show him a leprechaun in the first 30 seconds.
What's his weakness?
Well, it's got to be a four leaf clover.
Okay.
I mean, you look in the lucky charms box.
It's a leprechaun holding a four leaf clover.
I agree.
I think it's a bad move.
I think it's like if you made a my little pony movie and you said the weakness was rainbows.
Yeah, I mean, you'd think a leprechaun's weakness would be like silver or something,
like the opposite of gold.
Silver bullets or rain because he loves rainbows.
Yeah, let's role play.
I'll be the executive and you pitch me ways.
Better ideas for the leprechaun to be weakened, you know, it's weaknesses.
And I'll be the executive.
Okay.
So I'm thinking maybe because, you know, we know leprechaun's love gold.
I'm thinking that silver is his weakness.
Let me ask you something, Walsh.
Are we making a vampire movie?
Oh, are we making a werewolf movie?
We're making a leprechaun movie.
I'm sorry, that's a good point.
Mr. Weinstock.
Bold move.
Patrick.
Well, some Jewish.
He's a studio executive.
This guy is matching his truck, which is a cool move.
The look at the shirt is the exact same color as the truck.
For a second there, I couldn't tell if you were talking about the executive
that you'd created.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Or the guy on screen.
You're talking about the guy on screen.
Yeah.
Yes, he matched his shirt to his truck.
Aniston dating a significantly older man.
It's her father.
This is her father in the movie.
Well, you know, this is not, she's not dating.
We do live in the city of angels.
Joe, lipstick city.
Yeah, but this is not, this doesn't take place in the cities of angels.
It takes place in Ireland.
This take, are they in Ireland?
She was just driving through the Irish countryside with like,
oh, that's, well, this is the shack.
This is where a shame has just died.
Now they're taking it over.
Okay.
Boy, Aniston's.
Good looking gal.
I don't know if I'm the first to say that.
This was, what was she, had she been on the edge?
Do you remember the fox sketch showed the edge?
I don't, Pat.
I got out of the house once in a while as a child.
I did too.
But I looked for a four -leaf clover by myself and then I went back inside.
And this is the guy that said it was sad.
I counted the days to leprechaun came out on video.
Now there was a sketch show with
Julie Brown, but not downtown Julie Brown.
Oh, I know. The other Julie Brown.
Yeah.
And the goofy, we're talking goofy Julie Brown,
not sassy Julie Brown.
And I think maybe Wayne Knight or something.
I used to love it.
It was a bad sketch show.
It was on around the same time as Ben Stiller's show.
I love Ben Stiller's show.
Of course you do.
I own every episode.
Who was Wayne Knight?
Wait, wait, oh, Wayne Knight,
the new man.
He might not have been on it.
I'm going to talk about my answer.
I think he was on the Kelsey Grammar
green screen sketch show.
Remember that?
The one with Paul of Tompkins and Caitlin Olson?
I think so.
It's always something fun of him.
I wasn't Wayne Knight on that.
That sounds right to me.
That sounds right.
Was that show funny?
I never saw it.
I love Kelsey Grammar, so God damn much.
I always want him to be phrasier though.
It's terrific and boss,
but I just want him to be dainty -free.
Did you watch all of boss?
No, okay.
I watched some of it.
It's a good show.
It was a little over my head.
It's very political.
I mean, I can't even keep up with Veep.
No, I feel the same way.
It's too deep.
I feel the same way.
I don't know what the fuck they're talking about aftertaste.
I love Veep, and I laugh a lot,
but there's times where I'm like,
what?
I know nothing about the government or politics.
Yeah, West Wing kind of threw me.
I don't care.
I'm bothered with that word.
And here's what I think,
and this is a terrible attitude to have.
I always feel like whatever I think about politics,
whatever I do about politics,
it will have zero effect on what happens.
I agree.
That's the most apathetic, terrible attitude to have.
It's what they worry about the young people having.
But my vote doesn't matter.
My nothing matters.
Like whoever's going to be president is going to be president,
whoever's going to be city comptroller is going to be
city comptroller.
Patti, I get the same exact take.
I do vote.
And I thought I never voted.
The difference between you and me is,
I thought it would be well received
to express that to Janine Garafalo a week ago.
Oh, no.
Yeah, that's not the person to say that too.
We had a great discussion afterwards,
and I learned a lot during the discussion,
and I actually thanked her after,
but I didn't realize as it was coming out of my mouth.
Yeah, this was not the right person to say that too.
You know, why I vote is I feel like,
okay, like when I'm at a concert
and there's a thousand people applauding at the end of each song,
it doesn't matter if I applaud, you know,
and I feel the same way about voting.
But I do applaud because I'm not an asshole
and I want to feel part of the event.
And that's why I vote too.
The argument that I don't vote,
the argument is always,
well, what if everybody felt that way?
Well, but they don't,
and that's when I retort to that.
Exactly.
Now, this is a little movie trivia here.
We're now into the scene
if you're watching along where
Jen has met the hunk.
I love how we're on a Jen basis.
Yeah, well, I feel like if I met her,
she'd say, call me Jen.
Yeah, I've met Kudro.
She was lovely.
She's the only other friends I've met.
She's the only of the friends?
Yeah, I thought you said the only other friends.
The only of the friends that I have met.
I'll tell you what, I could go for a Met La Blanc once in a while.
I'd like to meet him.
He was always my least favorite of the friends.
He just seems like a fun guy in real life, though.
Yeah, I don't know.
I've never seen the episodes or whatever.
I haven't followed his career outside of it.
I think he's had the least luck movie -wise, definitely.
But he's had one of the better careers.
He had to spit off and now he's on his,
that show, that show episode.
I just said that.
But I mean, it's been going strong.
Yeah, I mean, he gets not many for Emmys every year,
even though not one person in the world has ever seen
an episode of episodes.
Did you just, you said episodes before I said episodes?
I said it maybe 20 seconds before,
and I'm starting to feel unheard and unrestricted.
I didn't hear you, and I do respect you, and I do listen.
Now, is this guy gardening in a grimace -colored vest?
Oh, it's a guy from Peeley's Big Adventure.
Yeah, would you still chew and gum?
Is that a nod?
It's great because I'm glad my movie trivia thing's got
pushed back to this scene because I forgot this guy was in it.
Is that a nod to Peeley, him chewing gum?
No, he plays a borderline retarded man in this movie.
I bet it was a nod to Peeley, and I don't like you just dismissing it.
I don't think it was.
He's supposed to be like a man with a child's mind sort of,
like, I think, you know?
And that's the kid from what?
Well, that's the kid, I don't know.
That kid always played a kid that looks like white trash, though.
Yeah, I've seen him before.
I've never seen that kid cleaned up with it.
Always a smart one.
With a respectable haircut.
He looks like the kid from Poltergeist, but it can't be because this is 10 years later.
Wait, is it the kid from Poltergeist?
No, I just said, you know, it's 82, and now he's the same age of 93.
Is this from 93?
Yeah.
This movie's from 93?
I was older than 12 when this came out.
Oh god, I was 12 when this came out.
I was 14 when this came out.
Uh, okay.
The guy that we just saw, the purple -shirted gardener hunk.
Yeah, that's the guy from summer school, Mark Harman.
No, that's not Mark Harman.
No, no, no.
I'm saying the movie summer school with Mark Harman.
Oh, I love summer school with Mark Harman and Kirstie Alley.
Yeah, that guy is from summer school.
What if you say that's the guy from summer school, Mark Harman?
No, I was saying that's the guy.
I mean, obviously, I know that's not Mark Harman.
Okay, that's the kid that sleeps in the cot during class because he strips it night.
Yeah, yeah, that's right.
So he's he's gardening in that lavender vest, uh,
at a home that an abandoned shack that Aniston's moving into.
It's not a lavender vest, first of all, for those who aren't watching.
It's a purple shirt that he's cut the sleeves off of.
Oh, pardon me.
Now, maybe no, no, I was talking to Tommy Hilfiger over here.
Maybe that's a nod to summer school.
No, I was talking to Jay Crue over here.
You know, maybe they're like, this is what a stripper would wear on stage.
Right, you chewed the gum.
They're not and everybody's other movies.
It might be an Aniston is on edge because of the leprechaun.
And she was coming hot off the scary looks in the crate.
Did you see that?
I saw she is ice.
That was scary.
Does Aniston pop the top in this one or no?
She never pops the top.
Well, now people say like Sandy Bullock never popped the top.
But there is that movie called like fire on the Amazon that nobody knows about where she popped the top.
Well, I don't think Aniston, she briefed Nip on Aniston in the good girl.
Yeah, I remember that.
When Jill and Hall is a man,
Aston's like 22 and after.
This is also a pre -nosed job, Aniston.
Yeah, you can tell she had a little bit of work done.
I mean, she's still gorgeous in this one.
Well, now you see her and she still looks great,
but you can tell there's, it looks like maybe like a mattress cushion in her face.
Her cheeks look real puffed out.
I think she's getting a little of the tux.
She's getting something.
I mean, a little bow.
See now, this is a crazy thing.
I work with very wealthy people and they talk some about plastic surgery here and there.
I never knew that anyone had plastic surgery unless they looked like John Rivers or something.
I assume that everyone else was just aging beautifully.
Oh, my sweet, my sweet boy.
And then people started saying like, and I'm talking like very recently, like two, three years ago,
people were like, no, everyone has it.
Everybody's had it.
Everybody's getting it.
I had no idea.
What work have you had done, Pat?
I had my penis shortened.
Come on.
That's somebody's bit.
I was frightening people.
I had my taint laser.
Why did you have that done?
So there's no hair on it?
Yeah, it looks great, but it was covered by hair.
I like to showcase my taint.
And then I had my eyes switched.
I put the right and the left socket, the left and the right socket.
Okay, because I just wanted to kind of mix it up and no one really notices.
See, this is why you're good.
I can throw you a premise.
You run with it.
You criticize me immediately.
I know I wasn't criticizing.
I was saying I appreciate that about you.
That I can throw you a loose.
No, you said that's somebody's bit.
You accused me of stealing a bit.
No, somebody's doing a dick shortening bit.
The dick shortening bit, I think I've heard.
But the other ones are really right.
Oh, waiting for Anthony talks about how he got his dick short.
Yes, there you go.
One of the fun I've ever met.
Hey, if you're going to steal steel from the best patty.
Pretty willard.
That's what I say.
Yeah, no, I've never had anything done.
I've never had anything done either.
I'm not above it.
No, I'm not above a lipo one day,
which I don't think is out of the realm of possibility.
Well, now they're freezing that off.
Is the thing now.
How does that work?
You like squeeze a clump of fat and then they freeze it off your fucking body.
And it's like very expensive and a lot of people do it apparently.
Is it painful?
I believe it's pretty painful.
Wait a minute, doesn't it take your skin off?
Look, I truly don't know how it works,
but it's called cyber -sino -siro, something like that.
Sounds terrible.
I heard it discussed at work, so I'm going to reason I know about it.
That sounds terrible.
My dermatologist does...
I go to a dermatologist once in a while.
You know, you want to make sure that thing on your knee is in cancer.
And are we human?
He's dead.
How are we seeing it, sir?
See the slow man just pushed the shamrock off the...
Right, off the thing.
He's going to get gone.
But he does...
He does lipon -plastic surgery and he has had so much work done.
It's insane.
Your dermatologist?
Yes.
Now, what does he look like?
Does he look like a Martin Short character or what?
It's not absurd, but he's had a lot of work done.
I shouldn't say it.
The leprechauns had like four facelifts, it looks like.
The leprechauns are doing well.
He's eating a bug off his arm.
For some reason.
Now, Warwick played the leprecha...
Well, I guess there aren't that many roles open to what is the word?
Little people?
Little people.
How is little people better than Midgets?
Yeah, I don't even want to touch it, Pat.
All right.
I don't know.
That's why I don't want to touch it.
I'm afraid I'll say something wrong.
Yeah, you're wrong.
It'll be a blog up tomorrow.
Let's blow past it.
Like, he did Willow and he's the star of this multi -multimillion dollar action movie.
And now, five years later, he's in this bargain basement.
Well, I mean, was this considered kind of a bigger title at the time?
The first two were three were theatrical releases.
They made a lot of money.
And then they had a long run.
I mean, look, it did well enough that they felt the need to reboot the franchise.
Yeah, that's true.
So, I mean, I didn't even hear about that.
That was the theatrical release or DVD release?
Straight to VOD, as it's called these days.
It's terrible.
Yeah.
They took away the leprechaun's personality.
That's the thing.
I was always like, if they would have made this movie correctly,
this would have been a really scary movie.
Like, where were Davis's legitimately scary in that costume?
Right.
He's a good actor.
It's a cool idea for a movie monster.
But they just made the movie shitty.
Yeah.
You know, whereas the new one, they kind of made the movie half decently.
But the leprechaun is just like this literally like almost like faceless monster.
Who's portraying the leprechaun?
The guy from WWE.
I want to say his name's Fizzy Wig, but that's not his name.
Who is the guy first?
Yeah.
Fizzy Wig's got from Christmas character.
Yeah, I know.
Fizzy Wig's the guy from Muppet Christmas character.
Yeah.
And yes, Pat, it's a little person.
They don't have the Undertaker playing leprechaun in the WWE.
Because WWE produced it.
The WWE films.
That's weird.
What's that guy's name?
Hornswaggle.
Okay.
Now, here's the thing.
I was on the Opian Anthony show years ago, one day with Ricky Jervase.
Yeah.
Came in.
It's the only time I've ever met Ricky Jervase.
I think you mentioned this on the last one.
Did that we talk that I mentioned leprechaun to?
Yeah.
Or maybe that was just me and you shooting the show.
Why would I mention it on the,
we were probably just shooting the show.
Okay.
Well, yeah, I asked him because they were doing that life's too short show.
Yeah.
And I said, after we went off the air, I said,
there's a lot of fun.
I got to ask you a question.
It goes anything.
I go, why didn't you do a shit on leprechaun?
Yeah.
And life's too short.
I go, it's, I mean, I would just think it was a treasure trove.
Sure.
You've shit on everything else that I did.
Yeah.
And he goes, he goes, oh, I don't remember.
He goes, I think we probably did.
And it just got cut out.
Right.
So there's your answer.
He said it, of course, and we're Ricky.
I think I thought.
I like that show a lot.
I really liked the finale.
Like the movie wrap up.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Have you watched Derek?
Oh, yeah.
How's Derek?
I like it.
It's, it's a little,
it looks like I wouldn't be able to take it.
No, it's good.
It's, it is a good show.
It's a little schmaltzy at times.
Yeah.
It's a little too melodramatic at times.
But like I, I like it though.
I think it's a very good show.
I like the low ladies too.
I like everything those guys do.
I love the low ladies.
Yeah.
And obviously the office and then extras were both fantastic.
Extras is my favorite.
I think it's a masterpiece from start to finish.
I completely loved it, but I love the office much more, I would say.
The finale of extras makes me cry without fail every time I watch it.
It is great.
I can't, I can't get through without crying.
Now, how did the guy, Francis from Peewee's Big Adventure,
how did he get away from the leprechaun?
Because he's, I noticed now as we drift lazily back to the film.
He's still running around in one piece.
Look at that.
A rainbow just went up,
which is the doing of the leprechaun.
Oh, because he's got to find his gold.
So that's the, the golds at the end of the rainbow.
Right.
They're really,
we've got a really low body count already for a horror movie.
Well, I'm saying you could have killed the, the Francis from Peewee
right off the bat.
They didn't kill him.
Right.
Now I wrote, I hate even saying this publicly, but I wrote a,
movie for the sci -fi channel before I became a known writer.
I'd be bragging about it left and right.
I think that's such a good credit.
It's a, it's so bad, but I co -wrote it.
We wrote a draft that was, like, tremors.
It had a great sense of humor and it was, it was scary.
And they have a rule there where you have to have a kill every 10 pages.
You know, like that.
And we pitched this movie The Moth Man and wrote it.
I think 15 grand or something, which at the time was much needed.
Sure.
And they were like, guys, this is great.
This would be the best movie we've made here at the sci -fi channel.
But we don't make movies with any humor.
We follow a very strict policy of just kill, kill, kill, kill, kill.
No jokes, no tongue in cheek.
That's what our audience wants.
So it stripped it away.
It was unwatchable, like, beyond unwatchable.
I would never recommend anyone watched it.
It has nothing of me in it.
It's a terrible movie.
What was it called?
Moth Man.
Just Moth Man.
And they're in the sci -fi channel.
And now their whole brand has changed.
And they're doing Sharknado, just five short years later.
Well, here's what I propose.
Repitch it.
You repitch it.
And you reboot Moth Man.
I don't think I need to go back there at the stage of the game.
But it was kind of fun to write.
I mean, I would love to make movies like that.
Yeah.
Well, it's just like you're like, oh, well, it's a sci -fi channel.
They're paying me 15 grand.
Obviously, I can have fun and do whatever the hell I want to do.
It's got no budget.
And then sure enough, even they have network people
who are like, no, can't do it, can't do it, can't do it.
That sucks.
And it winds up being a terrible product.
Now, do the listeners a favor,
because you've told me this before,
tell them the final line of that film
when they kill the Moth Man.
Oh, well, yeah, that survived.
So yeah, he goes, he holds up.
I don't know what the truth is.
I don't know if this was in the movie.
It might have just been in the script.
I think it was in the movie.
But he blows the Moth Man up with fire.
And then this crazy old man goes,
like a Moth to a flame.
And that was kind of cool to see that.
But we were like, let's get Gary Busey.
Like, let's get some star power in there.
And then when they came back,
we can't get Gary Busey.
We don't have the money.
Right.
I was like, okay, this is going to be real bad.
Who'd they get?
It was all nobody's.
There was a girl named Jewel State who's a beautiful actress
who has been in like, firefly and stuff.
But nobody else.
Are you telling me the cast of leprechaun had a higher profile
than the cast of Moth Man?
I'm 100 % telling you that.
Wow.
But it's amazing.
Moth Man wasn't a theatrical release.
Well, that's fine.
But I mean, you could have got one of those other people.
Maybe get the guy that played change song
from summer school.
I had no say in casting or any,
or really even in the script.
I was just sort of forced at gunpoint
to turn in exactly what they wanted.
And this is why I don't have a big movie career.
Because I think the writer gets to pick the actor.
Sure, sure.
Well, for a while, you know, I read 8 million comedy scripts
when I came out here.
TV pilots and stuff to try to get a job.
And every pilot for at least five, six, seven years said,
enter Jimmy.
parentheses.
A Vince Vaughn type.
Right.
It's like, that's all anyone was going for.
Sure.
And now Vaughn's comedy career has died.
And then I was like,
oh, it's very smart move for him going to the drama with his true detective.
And boy, that was a swing in the mess.
Although I liked it more than most.
I liked the sex party episode.
I was entertained throughout.
Sometimes buy how bad it was,
but I always had a good time with it.
I still find Vince Vaughn very funny.
I fucking love Vince Vaughn.
I mean, who doesn't love Vince Vaughn?
He's just not not getting the projects he deserves.
Do I ever tell you about the time I met him?
You did, but you can share it with our listeners.
Let's share it with the listeners.
All right.
Because I'm working on a script with a friend of mine.
Steve Burn.
Okay.
And we will meet over it,
their production company.
Not Steve and Vince's.
Which, I mean, Vince Vaughn's production company.
Their production company is behind my parking spot at my job.
Yeah, Wild West.
Yeah.
Picture show.
So anyway, I just would go over and go to some
ambiguous boardroom and just meet Steve.
And we'd sit there and write.
And that was kind of that.
Right.
And then I got to meet Peter Billingsley,
which was very cool.
Sure.
Because I'm a huge Christmas story fan.
Well, who was him?
And you know,
that's a piece of my childhood.
I'm meeting this guy in real life and swell guy.
Hell of a guy.
Very nice guy.
By the way, we're changing the name of the podcast to name droppers.
It's just me and Joe dropping names.
You're going to hear stories about the sci -fi network.
My, the names I'm dropping are like the head of the sci -fi channel.
Well, you said you met Koo Dro and she was nice.
She was great.
Yeah.
Anyway, one day I show up.
I said I'm here to meet Steve and the person
at reception said he's playing video games with Vince
in his office.
And I immediately collected myself and said, okay,
I'm about to meet a guy that I've watched in a million movies.
Sure.
That I think is really funny.
That I also really want to like me.
Yeah.
Don't, you know, so don't act like a 16 year old teenager right now.
And, but anyway, I went into the room.
They're playing hockey on PlayStation.
And it was literally the scene from swingers.
Yeah.
They're playing hockey video games.
And Vince Vaughn is just, he's almost doing the lines
from the actual movie.
Right.
And I was like, they, whoever found this guy was just like,
just put a camera on him and just let him be himself.
That's so many things.
The sad thing is that's almost 20 years later.
I mean, it's amazing.
His, his system came in at one point and said,
you have a call in line one.
And he said, I don't need attitude from you.
There's a nice way to do that.
I was like, I've seen him do that.
In actual movies.
Yeah.
It was really funny.
My, my boss is Michael Patrick King who did Sex in the City.
And he, Vince Vaughn, I guess, was in Sex in the City on a show.
He was on an episode.
And he tells the story.
What does he?
Yeah.
So he tells the story about Vince Vaughn came in and he reads the lines and then he goes,
all right, now we're going to do a couple takes my way.
If that's cool, I'm going to just kind of have fun with it kind of mess around with the material.
And they all kind of look at him.
And he goes, wouldn't it suck if I was that guy?
Maybe like him as well.
Why wouldn't you let him improv?
He's a very fun guy.
That's really great.
Wait, wait, are you sure it was Sex in the City?
Yeah.
I mean, they, they had the big stars pop in.
No, it definitely wasn't the comeback.
They had, they had McConaughey on there and Vince Vaughn and
I mean, I own the pink velvet cheese box set of Sex in the City that complete series.
My mommy bought it for Christmas for me four years ago.
Wow.
But I've never seen that episode.
But then again, I haven't gotten deep into four and five yet.
Seasons four and five.
That would have been when the show was at its hottest and when he would have come on.
Well, then I got to check it out.
I watched them all when I moved to New York.
So I've seen them all, but never since.
I got to, I was like, this is what New York's going to be like.
And then proceeded to not have sex for several years.
I had a very sex in the city experience in New York, which is why I got into the show.
When I lived in New York, I wasn't that into it.
I'd never really watched it until the very end of my stay.
I started to watch it.
Turned on season six on HBO on demand as a goof.
Yeah.
Because I had only seen the movies at that point.
Sure.
All I had seen was Sex in the City one and two in the theaters and I did not like them.
What's the highlight one?
But then I said, let me watch season six as a goof.
Hooked immediately.
Asked for the box set for Christmas.
God, it started watching it from the beginning.
Watch the first three seasons pretty rapidly.
Yeah, it's super entertaining.
It really is.
It's a younger golden girl.
It's a younger golden girls.
It's an older girls.
Yeah, it's almost the same age, hot and Cleveland.
Yeah, exactly.
All these shows have connections.
There's a thread here.
It's a slightly older female entourage.
This guy, I thought was Booger, but he's not Booger.
It's not Booger.
Booger does show up on think.
My favorite role that Booger ever played was the lawyer on moon lighting.
Sure.
Remember?
I remember my parents love moon lighting,
but I never was allowed to watch it or anything.
My mom loved moon lighting.
She would make me watch it with her.
Oh, okay.
She entrusted it was funny.
I was too young to get any of it.
I didn't get the nuances of a romantic comedy at 11.
Sure.
But a lot of will they or won't they kind of material rent?
Yeah, but Bruce Willis is apparently potentially
championing a moon lighting movie.
Really?
I've heard he's exceptionally difficult person to work with,
which I can't even believe, but I guess it's true.
It bums me out because I love Bruce Willis so much.
But yeah, you listed those Kevin Smith podcasts
about when they were doing cop out.
It's horrible.
I guess that's really only who I've heard it from,
so maybe he's nice to others.
And cop out was so bad, maybe he was just depressed.
Well, let's think about it.
Tarantino worked with him.
Did, but he never went back to the well?
Well, that again, there's a lot of guys Tarantino never had back.
It doesn't mean they're difficult.
Let me say this to you.
I just saw a trailer for the hateful eight.
Can't wait.
Nice rhyme.
I was very excited about the,
I'm excited for any quantum cinema.
The man makes amazing movies.
But I saw the trailer and I was like,
you know, haven't we kind of been down this road before?
With what?
With everything.
It's like he just did the western with Django and Shane,
which was, I had a lot of western elements.
And then I'm like, he's worked with all these people.
Like, when I'm looking at mad cinema,
and I'm looking at, and I like them.
I like the love Kurt Ross.
I love Sam O 'Jaxon, but I'm like,
same way I feel about Scorsese making every movie with DiCaprio.
I'm like, I just want to see him work with other people.
Well, this is why I'm excited about the movie.
Tarantino's last few movies kill Bill, volume one and two.
Yeah, uma, uma was in that, but you know,
he didn't have a lot of his usual players in it.
Well, Madsen and others were in there,
but yeah, that's true.
Yeah, Madsen's in it, but it's not a huge role, right?
Yeah.
In glorious bastards,
not a lot of his usual suspects.
I would argue Brad Pitt does not do a good job in a glorious bastard.
I loved him in it.
I thought he was way too cartoony for that part.
I love the movie.
It was incredible and he was fine.
I just sometimes I was like, you're not quite good enough to be doing this,
this over -the -top character.
Like, I'm not quite buying.
I thought that was the point.
I kind of thought that was Tarantino's sort of like graphic novel approach.
Perhaps we might have been directed into that.
Anyway, I just, if I could finish my point, Pat,
before you want to critique everybody's performance.
I feel passionately about this.
Django and Shane, none of his usual players.
Well, Sam allow him.
Oh, Sam, yeah.
Yes.
Okay, let me rephrase, I'm not saying this correctly.
First off, Walt's had just been in glory.
Right.
We haven't seen his usual players doing the Tarantino thing in a while.
Samuel Jackson played against the Tarantino type in that way.
I'm excited about that.
Samuel Jackson stole Django and Shane.
He's amazing in it, but he doesn't play the Samuel Jackson guy.
We all know and love from the earlier Tarantino.
That is true.
He played the ultimate uncle Tom.
Exactly.
So I'm excited about the hateful late because I personally feel like
this is Tarantino saying I'm going back to the roots.
Original script about a bunch of criminals stuck in a cabin.
It's very reservoir dogs.
And it looks like they're all doing like the snappy Tarantino dialogue.
So I'm like, I think this is kind of a gift to his fans.
I wasn't going to make this because it leaked, but come on guys.
This is too fucking cool.
And he did bring Jennifer Jason Lee into the mix who I love.
And she looks like she's crazy and fun on it.
She looks great in it.
I'm excited.
D 'Roth back on screen.
Yeah.
See, like, Roth doing like a little like
snidely whiplash, like mustache character.
I'm like, I don't know.
I just always am like Tarantino can get whoever he wants.
What the hell is a whiplash mustache character?
Snidely whiplash is like a...
Oh, snide.
I thought you meant doing a snide.
No, he was saying he was doing a snide.
You mean the character snidely whiplash?
His line in the trailer was like,
oh, we're going to have quite a bit of fun on Tweet or something like that.
It's like, come on.
I don't know.
I just, I...
It's just coming from the guy that wrote moth, man.
Don't hold it against me now.
I couldn't be more excited to see it.
And I will see it before opening day
because I will seek out advanced screenings of it.
I'm saying I wish he would expand his casting a little bit.
But I think...
Pull fiction, everyone in that, it's like,
wow, you never expected to see any of these people.
And it was very exciting.
I think he did.
I think he had, he had yet another breakout,
like hit star actor with, with Kristoff Waltz,
just like he did with, with, uh, with, uh,
in Jackie Brown, uh, what's the latest name of Jackie Brown again?
Pam Greer.
Just like he did with Travolta.
You know, he's done it consistently for his entire career.
I think this movie is simply a gift to his fans.
Sure.
I think this is...
I mean, they all are.
They're all a gift to anyone who enjoys this.
But I mean, like, I don't think this is him saying, like,
hey guys, look what I did this time.
I think this is him saying, like,
I'm gonna give you something you're gonna really enjoy.
Yeah, okay.
Like he did with Grindhouse.
Oh, I love Grindhouse.
I love them all.
But that, you know, that also sounds like it the way you're talking.
I love them all and I love all the Scorsese movies.
My point is, when I see, oh, like,
Scorsese is making another movie now with DiCaprio.
And I like DiCaprio.
But I want to see him work with other people.
That's all I'm saying.
I want to see him work with De Niro again.
And I don't think they're ever gonna make that Irishman movie.
No, that's not gonna happen.
I'd love to see Tarantino work with De Niro again,
because De Niro and Jackie Brown is off the charts good.
He's great.
Everyone, Jackie Brown.
That's a fantastic movie.
That's my friend Jim's favorite Tarantino movie.
I'd put it very close to Pulp Fiction.
Yeah, Pulp Fiction is my favorite.
Resort Dogs is my second favorite.
I'll put Jackie Brown third.
Yeah, I mean, look, they're all great moves.
It's also like, when Scorsese or Tarantino is working in the past,
a Western genre like, you know,
or like when Scorsese does coon dune,
or he's doing some movie about monks right now that's gonna come out.
Like, I'm just like, uh, and, you know,
I understand these people don't want to do the same thing over and over,
but it's like, Tarantino, just make an LA crime movie
because we'd all fucking love the shit out of it.
I wish, I hope that at one point he does what Scorsese does,
which is every 10 years go back and make a gangster movie again.
Yeah, I hope Tarantino does his departed or something.
That would be awesome.
Or his good fellows.
Yeah, Scorsese's most successful film.
Most praise film.
Good for their movie of all time.
Yeah, I mean, it's, you know, and it was done during the period
where he was trying to resist going back to that sort of stuff.
Joe, what is your favorite movie of all time?
It was Goodfellas.
It was taken out by Glen Gary Glen Ross,
which was taken out by Hannah and her sisters.
Oh, all right.
That's my absolute favorite movie of all time.
Followed very close second place by Glen Gary,
very close third place by Goodfellas.
Now, I'll take crimes and misdemeanors,
misdemeanors over Hannah and her sisters,
but I love Hannah's.
Crimes and misdemeanors are wonderful film.
The reason Hannah and her sisters is my favorite
is because it's got my favorite Woody Allen jokes I've ever heard in it.
I love the characters, and it's the most insightful film I've ever seen.
I've never watched a movie where so many characters say things
that I've thought almost word for word in my head.
Like when she talks about how her date shed and her chest.
Yeah, that because I've done it and received it.
And I've had that conversation on both ends.
Yeah, so I know what that's all about.
I watched parenthood again last night, which I think is an amazing movie.
The original, okay, I was going to ask the movie,
the original series or the new series.
I've never seen the series any either of them.
I love the movie.
I really, I've always loved the movie.
I think it's fantastic.
And I watched the interview with the writers afterwards
and they talked about how they were completely inspired by Hannah and her sisters.
Really?
Yeah.
How it was like four separate, very legitimate stories.
And it was the hardest thing they ever wrote.
They wrangled them all together,
but they were like, they walked out of Hannah and sisters
and were like, let's do a movie about having kids like this.
It's great.
That's great.
Parenthood's a great movie.
It is.
L .A. story.
Also, Diane Weiss brought her over from Hannah.
She's a great actress.
Love Diane.
Do you think?
Now, look.
Not being mean.
But do you think she's an attractive woman?
Yeah.
I kind of think so.
Yeah, well, I'm not currently attracted to her.
She's, all right.
Don't.
I'm not being mean.
I'm just saying, I'm just saying like, you know,
but when she was, you know, in her 30s, 40s, 50s, yeah.
Uh, she's still, how old is she now?
Oh, she's 70.
I'm not.
She reminds me a little bit of my mom now in her older age,
which is where the attraction disappeared.
But Hannah and her sisters, she's like smoking hot.
Yeah.
You know, talking about plastic surgery,
that what annoys me so much,
and I hear it way, way, way more in Los Angeles,
but people being like, oh, do you see her?
She looks so old.
And it's, they're talking about like surely McLean,
who's 90.
It's like, she, she's supposed to look old,
and you will look old.
Surely McLean 90?
I don't know.
She's 80, 80.
Just like this whole thing.
I'm like, do you see how old, uh, you know,
so and so looked like Bruce Dern?
I'm like, Bruce Dern is 79 years old.
You are going to look old too.
People get old.
Real quick, back to the movie for a second.
Bruce Dern's in hate play, it also.
Carry out.
Yeah.
I mean, what the hell are you complaining about with this movie?
All right, I'm not, I'm not.
This, uh, they're, we're in a diner scene.
We're, the, we, the keeps jumping back to this diner scene
between Aniston and the dancer from summer school.
He's eating some kind of meatloaf dinner.
It looks delicious.
I thought it was like a Thanksgiving meal,
which is something I used to always order at restaurants and diners.
I'd get, they have a Thanksgiving special.
Most diners have it.
I love it.
You get some turkey, some stuffing, some whatever.
It's great.
That's a meatloaf and mashed potatoes with gravy.
And then he's got a bowl of peas and carrots there.
It looks fantastic.
It looks so good.
Jennifer's character is turning her nose to it,
saying it looks disgusting.
I don't understand why, but.
Well, she's a snob.
I think she's the, her character in the movie is from LA.
Okay.
Did you notice that that cop just pulled over
the leprechaun in his tiny car and was just casually addressing him?
Like, it was a normal situation,
and that he was a normal person he was talking to be.
I didn't.
I haven't been paying attention to the film.
I, the cops dead, though.
I saw him kill the guys dead.
That was the box of lucky charms.
Was that supposed to be a little jump?
Probably.
But I mean, here's the, I think he pulls it out and scales at it.
Lucky clovers couldn't get the endorsement.
So this is where he eats it and he spits it out and says it's disgusting.
Come on, let him have a little fun with the character.
But I'm saying you pull over a guy who looks like that in a tiny car
than the cops going to be like,
Hey, you think you're going a little fast?
Wait, give me a break.
Who's in the tiny car?
It just happened to, I mean, we've been talking.
Was the leprechaun in driving the car?
Yeah, he was driving a tiny car.
No, he was not.
Yes, he was, Joe.
Have you not been looking at the screen at all?
I got real wrapped up in whatever the hell we were just talking about.
Wait a minute, the leprechaun was driving a car
unless I hallucinated.
Are you sure it wasn't the paint that the Francis guy and the little kid?
Joe, the cop pulled him over and then he like tried to rip his face out.
That's why the cop was bloody and ran into the woods.
Holy shit.
Yeah, I missed that.
Why is, I don't think we're in Ireland by the way.
Nobody is an Irish accent.
They only did it at the beginning.
But I think she drove for the Irish show said,
why do you think this is an Ireland is probably because
they don't have the budget to be filming an Ireland.
They're probably filming in Burbank.
Well, but nobody has an Irish accent.
I think it's a beginning.
That guy is from Ireland and he's coming home from a trip to that
to Ireland when he's down to pot of gold.
I think that's the plot of this.
And these green rolling hills that she was driving through,
I mean, that could be Northern California for Christ's six.
But why in a movie like this, would you have
shots of her driving through lush Irish countryside
and not have it be Ireland?
That's your question about this movie.
Well, that's the decision that you're questioning about this movie.
I have many questions.
When did he get hit in paint?
Who the hell knows?
I didn't even notice the leprechaun driving a little car.
Yeah, we should probably glance at the movie once in a while.
You know?
And now Aniston is perplexed by the shoes on the table.
The leprechaun for some reason piled a bunch of shoes on the kitchen table
and they're trying to figure out why it happened or how it happened.
Where with Davis?
No, Bruce Dern.
That's who I actually want to talk about.
Okay.
Back to Bruce Dern.
What's your favorite Bruce Dern quote from a movie ever?
Because I know I have mine.
Bruce Dern quote, I mean, I used to obsessively know movie quotes
and then eventually I had to force them out of my brain
to make room for more necessary things.
I don't know.
I live when he screams in coming home, which is insane.
I never saw coming home.
Oh, what's that about?
Look at the war, surely.
Coming home from Vietnam.
It's a 70s movie.
It was, I believe it was definitely nominated for best picture.
Jane Fonda sounds like a rough, rough ride.
It's a great movie, but he's, she, let me try to remember.
Oh, it's John Voight in a wheelchair.
And Jane Fonda falls in love with them and it's like
screwing him and cheating on Bruce Dern.
At some point Bruce Dern goes insane and starts screaming at her
and it's some of the craziest acting I've ever seen, but I love it.
So Jane Fonda is cheating on her husband with a man in a wheelchair.
Pretty sure that's the case, yes.
Why would she be doing that?
It would should be the other way around, shouldn't it?
Like, I lost my legs and you didn't you cheat on me?
I think that's what the thing is, is that not only is it
emasculating but you're choosing to go with this guy in a wheelchair.
But he can still bone down.
No, he can, he goes down in her.
Very upsetting scene in board of the 4th of July when they go to the
whorehouse and is it willing to foe?
Like, like freaks out because the hookers make in front of him.
Oh, yeah, yeah, sure because he can't get it up.
Yeah, I remember that.
That's rough stuff, man.
That's rough stuff.
I was the time when they'd give Oliver Stone $60 million a year to make a Vietnam movie.
With a lot of slides and clips throughout the whole thing.
He was, I mean, he was in a, I can't even say is anymore.
He was an amazing filmmaker for quite a while.
JFK.
Well, you told me that you liked that last one he did.
I liked savages, but it was hot trash, but I like hot trash.
But was the point that to make it hot, did he try to make it hot trash on purpose?
Probably not, probably not.
I don't know, fair enough.
Fair enough.
My favorite Bruce Durin quote is from the Burbs, which is also my favorite.
Oh, all the Burbs.
Favorite horror comedy.
I believe Fangoria tweeted out the other day what's your favorite horror comedy?
I responded to the Burbs, hands down.
That's a great, great movie.
When he, when Bruce Durin, when they go to the neighbor's house and Bruce Durin goes,
all right, cut the shit clopec.
What's the goddamn goofy noise you got coming out of your basement?
And as he's marching toward him, yeah, the guy is just fucking great, man.
What's his relation to Laura Durn?
Father.
Father?
Not brother.
Oh, he's 30 at least over at least the murder.
Bruce Durin and her mother is Diane Ladd.
And Diane Ladd?
Okay, yes, Diane Ladd.
He played her mom in Wild at Heart and other things.
I sometimes get Diane Ladd and Barbara Hershey mixed up.
That's fair.
And also too, Deborah Winger all mixed into there.
Oh, I love Deborah Winger.
Now, I pitched this to you the other day, my ideal movie.
Sure.
I want to do a comedy expendables.
You said that, well, yeah, we're texting about that.
Yeah, you said expendables.
Well, let's get to the beginning of it.
I want to make a movie with Dabney Coleman.
Okay, Howard Hesman.
Yeah.
And I figured out the perfect third guy.
Uh, uh, coach Craig T Nelson.
Yeah, that is not the perfect guy.
Yes, it is.
He's not even a comedian.
He's not funny.
Craig T Nelson's hilarious.
No, he's just plays it straight.
He's coach.
No, you had a better person in the set.
I said John Lithgale, but I think John Lithgale is not really comedy either.
Well, third rock from the set.
He's hilarious.
Okay, Kelsey Grammer.
We can get him all.
The expendables has 18 people in the cast.
And then you said,
also if you're going to get Howard Hesman, you got to get Martin Moll.
I want Martin Moll.
My point is is I want to get every funny guy that reminds me in some way of my dad.
Sure.
Into a movie again.
Yeah, I get that.
Being funny again.
You mean like a guy with kind of a short fuse.
Bowling boxish.
Yeah, has had a mustache or does have a mustache.
Right.
I mean, Dabney Coleman is spearheading it.
He's my Stallone.
And as I told you, this movie would make maybe $60 ,000.
What's we could do it as a straight to VOD?
Yeah, that those always make some money from what I hear.
Yeah.
Why not?
Like you're you're picturing a trailer where it's like Coleman Moll.
Like no one's going to see this movie.
It's not really like that.
A little more lighthearted.
It'd be a comedy.
Okay.
Well, Coleman Moll, but they're slipping on banana peels in the action.
Yeah.
What are they doing?
Are they doing a heist?
No, it's just a comedy.
All right.
I have no plot idea for it.
I just I just want to get these.
The 10 of them like sharing a box of donuts and like black coffee.
Maybe they're maybe here's a pitch.
By the way, Dabney Coleman's breath always smells like coffee.
That's a guarantee.
I would go as far as to say the same for Martin Moll.
Well, pretty much all those guys.
The breath smells like coffee.
How about this for a plot?
They're they're all gangsters.
They're all mob guys.
Okay.
That have gotten that are all that have all been in the witness protection program for the last
30 years. They're now so old.
They're facing forms of dementia.
And forgetfulness and all this stuff.
The government or the fitness protection program knows this could be a problem
because these guys might start leaking their mob secrets.
So they have an old man home just for guys that live too long in the witness protection program.
And another actor who will name in a minute
pretends to have dementia to get put into that home to get all their secrets.
There you go.
And that's where you bring in your Ben Stiller, your younger face.
That's going to be your younger face.
And that's your star.
This could probably be a movie that we just shout out.
It's better than it's better than most movie ideas that I hear on the regular basis.
I think it's a really good idea.
It's not bad at all.
A guy pretending to have dementia and he goes in and he's like,
hey, tell me your secrets.
Now, because he's going to write a book.
Right. Now 10 old men with amnesia and
Alzheimer's doesn't necessarily make for a great comedic premise,
but we could work with that.
Well, we don't have to use the term Alzheimer's.
Yeah, they're getting a little spotty.
We just kind of foggy.
Yeah, we just say like they got to go to this place because who knows what they'll blur it out in
a conversation.
Yeah, my dad's only 67 and I mean, half the shit he says.
I mean, he's at a point where he's leaking secrets like he's bragging to me about things.
I don't even know what he's talking about.
Right.
Yeah, I like that.
Yeah, we call it whittlest protection.
Now that was the, I think it was the layer of the cable guy movie.
Was it?
I think it was, actually.
I was going to make a point in what we called witness erection.
Okay, that's not bad.
I just thought of it just now.
But it gives it more credit if you say I always want it to.
If you lie.
It makes it sound like you really had that idea perk in in there for a little while.
Did you see my new tattoo, by the way?
No, what is it?
That is a vector graphic rendition of the Death Star from the Star Wars video game from the 80s.
Oh my god.
Pretty cool, right?
So that's a huge tattoo.
Yes.
Do you, how much thoughts do you get that you wake up and go, you know what I want?
I've been wanting something on the other side of this for a while
because this always looked too plain and stamped.
Is that the Ghostbusters logo?
Can somebody not make that joke one time?
It's not a joke.
What is it if it's not the Ghostbusters?
It's a no sign.
No, what?
No.
That's my personality.
You have to ask that question.
Your personality is no.
Am I a guy that goes with the flow?
No.
By the way, my favorite line in straight out of the Compton.
Why do you always got to try to fuck that guy's girls?
And DJ Yellow goes, why not?
Yeah, it was such a, it's such a good line.
Why not?
I love Compton so much.
And I think, you know, we're spacing these pockets out so much
that we're going to be talking about movies that are like a month old when they hear it.
But straight out of Compton, on our time came out yesterday.
We both saw it for some reason not together.
I went in the day.
I went about five o 'clock.
I loved it so much and it was long and I didn't care.
And I'll tell you.
I knew a lot of the story already because I was such a fan of that music as it was
coming out.
Yeah.
And I was very obsessed with all that West Coast rap that was coming out in the late 80s
or 80s through the 90s and everything.
So I knew a lot of the story, but I will tell you, it was
unbelievably comprehensive.
Yeah.
I couldn't believe, I love that they put in like
the DOC story that he got in the car accident and his voice box got crushed.
And that ruined his rapping career.
And it wasn't the stuff I didn't think they would put in there.
I thought it was really just going to focus on NWA.
Right.
Yeah.
It wasn't done in that way that like walk hard made fun of so good of like
Tupac, what are you doing here?
No.
Like, you know, these people were in it and
they didn't need to touch on everybody but like every time they brought in like
Snoop or whatever you'd be like, awesome.
Yeah, the audience, when I saw the audience was applauding.
Yeah.
They were cheering at times like Tupac they were cheering like
I just got chills.
It was really fun.
Tupac looks a lot more accurate than the Snoop, but Snoop sounded like Snoop.
I saw the film with Matt McCarthy and his lovely wife Glennis.
Yes.
We walked out of the theater and met words where
how the fuck did they get Tupac to play Tupac?
Yeah.
I thought maybe they hired, they signed the hologram.
That guy was from Coachella.
It was unsettling how much he looked like.
Yeah.
Almost.
Sounded like him, yeah?
Yeah.
And his cute son looks exactly like it.
Like, cube.
Yeah.
They did, you know, wipe out all the
severe beatings of women that went on.
But I'm okay with it.
They did.
Like Dr. Dre beating the shit out of D -Barns.
They cut that out.
Probably should have been in the film, but I'm sure Dr. Dre was like,
they made Dr. Dre look like he was a pussycat in the movie.
And Dr. Dre is not a pussycat.
They made easy look kind of like a pussycat.
Yeah.
It's like this guy seems like a great guy.
Yeah, it was a little cleaned up.
I also liked when he said, I also really like the line when they're at the party,
the wet and wild pool party.
Sure.
And easy he says, are we done here?
And Jerry Heller goes, yeah, he goes, okay, I am going to fuck now.
Yeah.
I was like, I love this guy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I love this guy.
The guy who played easy, I think stole the show, actually.
He was tremendous in it.
Yeah.
Now did you, by the way, the leprechaun just got his hand cut off.
Yeah, let's at least look at this movie.
It's crawling up up.
What powers does a leprechaun not have?
The fucking four leaf clover?
That's the only thing that can stop him.
Can crawl and then regenerate on its own?
Watch, he's going to reattach his fucking hand because he has a hand in the other movies.
Anyway, the, the, what's it called?
Oh, a geomoddy.
Love geomoddy in it.
Is he never not good playing that guy?
He's, I loved him in the Brian Wilson movie too.
Somebody had a great tweet today, I don't know who, but it was like,
so what I'm gathering from every movie released lately is that Paul
Geomoddy ruins music.
He just shows up at ruined the Beach Boys, ruins the WWE.
But yeah, he was really great in it.
And I also loved how even though I knew the story,
for like the first half, you're kind of like, this guy is all right.
You know, he didn't play it like, you know, the stupid white guy who doesn't get the music.
He seemed to genuinely be a fan,
genuinely like what they were saying.
But just be, you know, some people who do those shitty business practices can't stop.
I read an interview with F Gary Gray and they said,
why we were surprised you didn't give it to Jerry Heller Harder.
Yeah.
And he was like, well, he's a boy.
We didn't, we weren't trying to paint him out to be like a demon man.
Yeah.
He's like, you know, we wanted to portray the guy with some fairness.
But you know like,
F Gary Gray is a name that if you asked 100 people,
one person would know that name.
Right.
He's directed Friday?
Yeah.
The Italian job, which was like a massive hit.
Yep.
He directed, set it off, which is a great movie.
He did the negotiator, which is a great movie.
He didn't know that.
Did he do the, did he do belly?
No, that was hype Williams.
Okay.
But it's like, how many great moves this guy have to make before somebody,
this is the one that's going to get him the recognition.
Yeah, this is being, this is being very talked about.
And his name, it was shot awesome.
This is not like,
he was a hired gun director to direct the movie and get a job done.
This is like, he'd develop this with Dr. Dre.
Yeah.
Like, you know, his name is all over this thing.
Like, this is, he's going to finally get his,
get his moment from this.
He should.
He's been a, he's been a great director since,
Friday was 1995.
Like his movies always have a lot of energy.
They're always shot really cool.
I love the guy.
I also really spoil our alert.
If you don't want to hear this,
cover yours for a second.
I always really, I also really enjoyed the closing credits of the film.
Yeah.
When they were cheering,
everybody in the theater was cheering,
like when they were showing the real clips.
Oh, yeah.
Then you'd see the scene from Friday.
Yeah.
And the day.
And then like, the Dr. Dre beats transaction
and Evan M.
and 50 cent being like,
we'd be nothing without Dr. Dre.
It was just really a cool movie, man.
Very inspiring too.
Back when musicians were actually rebellious.
Yeah.
You know?
Yeah, I mean, Q being that sort of politically aware
was very cool.
I didn't really know that aspect of it.
No, you know, from his lyrics,
but it's kind of like,
I didn't realize him.
Like that interview was such a funny scene
with that what we were talking about earlier,
the Jewish defamation league.
Yeah, it was, uh, yeah.
The, uh, yeah, when he goes to shake the guy's hand,
and he goes,
what did he say?
What's your name?
Fuck, get the fuck out of my house.
Whatever I don't know.
Eat a dick. Get out of my mind.
Get the fuck out of here.
Yeah, it was, uh, it was a great movie.
Yeah.
It was a great movie.
I, uh, back to leprechaun though.
Yeah.
I mean, uh, no, they're all still alive.
But there's been, uh, they, they, they, they, they,
they brought in needless, there was clearly a decision made
to bring in auxiliary characters to kill.
So this core group could stay alive.
Right.
I guess because they thought maybe all these people
would be in the sequel.
None of them are in the sequel.
Yeah.
Literally none of them.
I mean, Aniston, the very next year was the
one of the biggest stars in the world.
Aniston, uh, do you think that she maybe
in her contract was supposed to come back for the sequel
and there was some heavy negotiations
that had to go on?
No.
Okay.
Sometimes they do that.
No, I don't think so.
I think she, they probably didn't.
You know, I think she probably saw this as a very
obvious stepping stone at one point.
Yeah.
And, uh, and then got a gig and said,
yeah, I would never do the sequel to that movie.
So many of our biggest actresses got their
start in terrible horror movies.
It's crazy.
Yeah, we're reading it online last episode.
All those people that started in the
children of the corn sequels.
Yeah.
By the way, I told you I had final sacrifice
the part two.
Yeah.
On DVD as a bonus movie, uh,
with storm of the century.
Right.
I finally watched it the other day.
I mean, it's, I couldn't believe how
fucking bad it was.
And it's only the second one.
I mean, it was like, so imagine
what the fifth one was like.
Oh, man, the leprechaun just appeared.
So wait, if he can teleport, he appeared,
but he appeared in like some sort of
electromagnetic way.
What?
He can also, he also has telekinesis.
But wait a second.
If he can disappear and reappear, why don't you just
disappear when the guy was trying to shoot him earlier?
There doesn't, there don't seem to be any rules and regulations here.
That's what ever grade horror movie needs.
What gremlins understands very well.
You need clear rules.
Yep.
I agree.
Clear rule or else the audience is like, what?
Like you got to know what kills it.
What strengthens it?
Whatever else?
Exactly.
Establish what the weaknesses are.
Establish what its limitations are.
That's the most important part.
Yeah.
I mean, gremlins' limitations are.
Gremlins' me is the cleanest version of that
because that guy, the Chinese guy, literally says it.
He says the three rules as it fades to black
and then comes up on the credits.
Yeah.
Like you're like, okay, got it.
Let's do it, gremlins.
And then it's amazing.
Never, never get it wet.
Never give it daylight.
Never feed it after midnight.
That's the big one, too.
And no matter what you do, never, never feed it after midnight.
That would always kind of bothered me because it's always
after midnight somewhere.
But there's a lot of people.
Never bothered me until somebody said it to me.
And honestly when the person said it to me,
I wanted to punch them in the face because I was like,
you have a brain that then that isn't good for movies.
And sometimes people really bug me with that shit,
just coming at like with a purely logic way to like some movie
I've loved my entire life and it's such a bummer.
But I get it.
I understand.
I just don't, it's a weird rule,
especially when they're coming from China.
That means when you're feeding it in America,
it's after midnight.
China, that is true.
So that bugs me a little bit.
It also kind of bugs me that one of them somehow knows
that it'll morph into this demonic Gremlin.
If it eats after midnight, so it purposely,
purposefully choose the clock wire to trick Zach Galligan.
One of the Gremlins knows.
Yeah, stripe.
Well, there's the, yeah, stripe was established.
That's a very smart mischievous Gremlin.
But what a, my question is this a dog.
Like a dog or not a dog,
but a caterpillar has no concept of its own evolution.
It doesn't know like I got to get in that cocoons
so I can turn a little butterfly.
It's just what it does.
But the Gremlins, I think,
were painted as being fairly intelligent.
That's all I'm going to say.
All right.
Did I ever tell you the time I saw that Zach Galligan guy?
That's his name, right?
How did you know?
Is he still looking at the sun?
He lived in my neighborhood in New York.
Okay.
Two times I met him.
The second, the first time I met him at just a light
and I said I love wax work.
Really?
I said thank you.
It's one of my favorite horror movies.
Okay.
You should do it on here.
It's on in demand on Netflix.
All right.
Is wax work like wax figures that come to life?
It's a wax muse.
Well, let's save it for the wax work episode.
All right.
But essentially.
Anyway, that was the first time.
And it was very whatever.
The second time I was standing on my front stoop,
he walked by.
I realized it was him.
I jogged down the stairs.
By the time I got down the stairs,
he was like half a block away.
And I yelled,
Zach turns around looks horrified.
Didn't know what was going on.
And he looks at me with this expression like,
do I know you?
Yeah.
And I go, I love Gramlins.
And he goes, oh, I'm sorry.
I thought I knew you for a second because you yelled my name.
And I said, no.
And he goes, well, thanks a lot, man.
Yeah.
And he just walked home, I guess.
I'm assuming walked home.
Does he still act or is he like an accountant now?
I bet he's like a writer or producer
or like a TV director.
Those guys all see you going to like,
Andrew McCarthy does a lot of TV directing now.
Fred Savage,
directs from Fred Savage.
Fred Savage, Fred Savage.
He's also still an actor.
Starring in a new sitcom.
I hear it's great.
I got a lot of friends working on it.
Oh, really?
Success.
Who else is in it?
Rob Lowe.
And is it a one,
a single camera or is it like a live audience thing?
It's a single camera.
It's called The Grindr.
It's about a guy who's been playing a TV lawyer
for many years and then he goes home
and thinks he has the skills to be an actual lawyer
with his actual lawyer brother.
I love it.
Fred Savage is one of the best guys in the world.
And yet another name drum.
I want to meet Fred Savage.
I'm pissed you've never introduced me to the guy.
Well, you can come to one of my poker nights.
He usually plays.
We also get lunch a lot.
I could bring you now.
Would he mind if I came to a poker night
and narrated it?
A lot.
Daniel Stern.
He's got a pretty good sense of humor about those things.
He might tell you to shut up at some point.
I'm kidding, Pat.
I'm not really going to do that.
I just thought maybe it'd make us laugh right now.
Yeah, well, just wait a minute.
Well, I know.
Be good.
That was the night I won
in $26.
I mean, I wouldn't go.
Hey, Fred, I love little monsters.
No, I'm going straight to the wizard on that one.
Okay.
Fred, the wizard.
You mean, monsters scared these shit out of me when I was a kid?
What do you want?
Which is why I didn't watch a lot of horror movies.
That was wrong with you.
Sorry.
It scared me.
That's how we mandale monster movie scared you.
My pet monster scared me the cartoon.
Are you joking?
No, I was a pussy.
I'm not going to argue that.
That's beyond pussy.
Yeah.
That's like emotional damage or something.
Yeah, I had a lot of severe emotional damage
that I'm still dealing with.
Okay, sorry.
Take it back then.
It's a rocky road to hell.
They've broken yet another rule in this leprechaun movie.
They shot him and he jumped right back up again.
I mean, at the beginning of the film, the guy shot him
and he was knocked out long enough that he could pick up,
walk to the leprechaun, pick him up, throw him into the crate.
Look, I'm starting to think they didn't put a lot of work
into the screenplay of leprechaun.
Yeah, I'm starting to feel that way too, Pat.
I hate to say it.
See, they keep shooting him.
Yeah.
And then he just is going to get right up again.
See?
The phone's ringing.
I had that phone.
We all had that phone.
Yeah.
I had to answer the phone.
Hello, Walsh residents, Patrick speaking.
Don't wonder you were scared of my pet monster.
Yeah, you know.
Jesus.
Sounds like it was a metaphor for your family.
My pet monster had chains.
I had metaphorical chains as well.
Yeah, yeah, the constraints.
Yeah, the constraints put on you by
parents that wanted you to act too cordially.
It is crazy.
What is this now, Joe?
That was a complete rip of nightmare on Elm Street.
Yeah, for those of you who are not watching.
That also wasn't his hand.
For those of you not watching,
Jennifer asked to answer the phone which was the leprechaun
because he can just magically make the phone ring
and be on the phone somehow without using another phone.
And then his hand came through the phone
to a tiny doll hand.
Yeah, so we can also minimize his body parts, apparently.
Is it, is it that he's making them hallucinate these things?
No, I don't think so.
How do you do that?
I think that kid was in like three ninjas or something.
How do you do the time check without stopping the movie?
With the Apple TV?
Hit the arrow?
No, I wouldn't do that.
Why?
Get us off track with the loser.
No, you hit the down arrow.
I wouldn't do it.
I don't know.
I need to know how much is left in this movie.
I don't trust the Apple TV remote.
I have lost it one million times in the cushions of the couch.
Pete Homes tapes his to a piece of a big piece of cardboard
which is sensible, but it makes it look sterling white trash.
Yeah, I've been over there and I'm like,
you guys got to find a like they'll throw it to the side of the couch or something
that nobody can see.
He's got it like a gas station bathroom key.
Yeah, it's real trashy looking.
Pete, if you're listening, your house is trashy.
I need to know how much time is left in this film.
This is our 3rd episode.
It's the first time I've felt tortured mildly.
I agree. This is not a good film.
It's a terrible film.
Aniston is kind of caring me.
I like that they have her in a pair of shorts.
My favorite Aniston scene is when she walks naked through the apartment and the break up.
Sure.
Great stuff.
Oh, God.
And doesn't she get a wax right before?
Yes.
God, damn it.
I love her in that movie with that German girl.
She's perfection in that movie.
I love her so much in that movie.
I agree with her side of the arguments.
Yeah, no, I get mad at Vince Bond.
I'm like, why doesn't he get up and help her do the damn dishes right now?
I agree.
And he's so like,
you know, so indifferent to her.
And when she finally walks away, it's like, yeah,
which is kind of the beauty of the movie because you see yourself in it.
Whenever you look back at a relationship,
you're like, why didn't I do this or why didn't I do that?
That's what the movie kind of makes you feel like.
You know, in my head, they got back together.
They run into each other.
Maybe they did.
The movie and they had that really nice smile in exchange
at Christmas time.
And I'm saying, by new years, they were humping again.
I wouldn't be surprised.
They both look back at each other.
They did.
They did. He changed.
You know, what's the fuck?
So now the leprechaun just reappeared on the back of their truck.
By the way, the last time he was roller skater.
Last time he appeared, it was blue light.
This time it was green light.
No, it was green last time too.
No, it was green when he moved the bag of gold.
But it was blue when he came back.
Did you see what just happened, Pat?
He's on a roller skater.
That's looney tune shit right there.
They're doing looney tune shit.
Here's and he went through a fence
into the shape of the leprechaun is the hole.
Yeah, in the fence.
Now here's my question.
If this fucking guy can disappear and reappear,
did a Benny Hill tape speed up?
They did. He just skated off all fast.
If this guy can disappear and reappear,
why doesn't he just disappear and reappear in the car
instead of riding on the back of it,
like Michael J. Foxx and back to the future?
Thousand percent.
Also, when he lost the car and crashed in the fence,
why is he skating to get back of it to do it
and not just disappearing and reappearing where she is?
Two thousand percent, agree.
The hell is going on.
Somebody just wasn't given the proper notes on the script.
I mean, these to me are clearly executive notes.
The old security guard asleep bit.
I just can't imagine any writer would be like,
this is a good idea.
Well, it's probably the writer director was like,
well, we should look him up.
You know, maybe he made a horrible, successful horror movie prior.
I'm going to look him up.
But narrate what's happening here
because I believe what's going on is she is going to now find
the Irish guy that trapped him at the beginning of the movie.
That owned this house before they lived in it.
It's 10 years later, he's now in a nursing home or something.
So let the people know what's going on.
So we don't have dead air while I look up.
This show reminds me of that great scene
and Exorcist 3, which you showed me,
which was a horrifying scene.
With the the shears.
Yeah, when that nurse comes running out,
that was.
Exorcist 3 is one of the scariest movies I've ever seen.
It was great.
That was one of our first hangs, Joe.
It was our first hang.
Yeah.
We got breakfast at a diner.
Yes.
I had some kind of goddamn egg plate with beans
that annoyed the shit out of me.
I remember giving you a very critical.
I had a Mexican.
We're in like this Philly style diner.
It's like, clearly you get the pancakes.
Yeah, I don't know.
I have the way post ran chair.
I tried to not eat like a loaf of bread in the morning.
All right.
I'm looking.
Mark Jones wrote and directed this.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, that's not a good sign.
No.
Maybe these were his ideas.
And maybe he did the others.
I don't know.
Oh, and he did.
He did all of them.
Anything else?
Okay.
So this is just a guy that excited.
He was just going to go down a road and not get off of it.
I'll say, Joe.
46 writing credits.
46.
Yeah, leprecha, all the leprecha.
Don't read them all.
Just read what the names are.
All the leprecha, movies.
Ripple, stilt skin, which is essentially.
That was also world Davis, right?
I don't think so.
Okay.
It's a variation of it.
It's it's leprecha.
It is leprecha.
Basically the same thing.
So she found the old guy.
So obviously this guy has his back to us.
Is this going to be the leprecha?
Yeah.
So where's the guy?
Yeah, where's he?
Where's O 'Grady?
Did he kill O 'Grady?
I would assume.
Why don't you teleport to her side and slither throat, leprecha?
He's not chasing her in a wheelchair.
Yeah.
Like he's in a wheelchair.
The slowest means of.
And they're doing the Benny Hill thing again.
Yeah, speeding it up.
This movie is a lump of shit, man.
I'm sorry.
I don't like to criticize other people's art.
Art.
Yeah, I don't.
I really don't like to do that.
What had he done prior to leprecha?
Was there a hit that enabled him to write and direct us?
Well, a lot of TV work.
A couple episodes are rip tied.
Rip tied.
What's that about?
You don't remember rip tied?
No.
Was it like sequestia SV?
It was like a boat show with cops.
Boat cops?
Two Vietnam vets now work as private eyes
in sunny Southern California.
Oh, that sounds good.
Nick and Cody are the muscles
and Murray is the computer wizard.
All right, that sounds great, actually.
Yeah, it was like one of those like, you know,
scarecrow and Mrs. King kind of thing.
Sure.
You know, a lot of fun.
A lot of fun.
Yeah, a lot of laughs.
Eight episodes of the 18.
Okay.
Two episodes of Hunter.
All right, we're good for him.
My grandpa was obsessed with Hunter.
I loved Hunter as a kid.
Hunters that like a bold
Fred dryer.
Fred again.
There's another guy.
We'll get our football player.
Yeah, another guy that looked just like my dad.
Yeah.
My grandpa, I think loved Hunter
because he kind of looked like Hunter.
Rodan episode of Alph.
The animated series.
Oh.
Rodan episode of police academy.
The animated series.
Wasn't it weird that there was a police academy cartoon?
That movie was like all tits and bush.
Yeah.
Well, there's less nudity than you think
and the other ones don't have any really.
But the running gag through the first three
is Leslie.
I forget that lady's name.
The big blonde.
Getting like tossed repeatedly into pools.
Yeah, oh yeah.
And her tits showing through her t -shirt.
Yeah, I remember some early jerking to those movies.
I don't think I've ever told you this.
When I was an NBC page at 30 Rock in New York,
I gave tours of the studios.
And one morning, I was like so hung over
like every blink kind of hurt.
And I had a eight, I think at 8 AM tour.
And I was taking this tour group around 30 Rock.
We get to the control center.
And they show you on like 20 TVs
what's being aired currently on NBC.
Right.
And I look in there and there was a talk show.
And I've looked it up.
I know I wasn't dreaming it.
It actually happened.
It was an Alph talk show.
Oh yeah, I remember that.
It was Alph conducting a legitimate,
seemingly serious interview with Dennis Frons
about his craft.
And for two minutes, there was no jokes.
And Alph's just like, so now what brought you to NYPD blue?
Was it the script?
Yeah, I was blown away.
And I laughed so hard at this.
Because I was so hung over.
That Alph was like basically like Charlie Rose.
Alph's always really hit my funny bound
from when I was a little kid.
One of my early bits was this was true
that I turned off an episode of the Cosmos
hosted by Carl Sagan.
To because during a commercial break,
I stumbled upon the Alph talk show.
And the bit was this is why I will never achieve anything in my life.
Like I was more interested in the puppet alien.
I wouldn't be too.
There's a picture of me to go back
to my emotionally damaging childhood.
My birthday is January 5th.
And every year I would invite a bunch of people to my party.
And it would get snowed out every year.
And my family wouldn't come.
My friends wouldn't come.
No one would come because of the snow.
And just ring after ring after ring on the phone.
My mom would answer it.
Look over at me sadly and be like,
oh, it looks like he's not going to make it either.
It looks like grandma and grandpa are going to come either.
So just one after the next.
Oh.
And there's a picture of me crying into an Alph cake.
That my parents have.
Did they at least get you presents?
Yeah, they got me, I mean, they did their best and got me presents.
But like there's a full Alph cake with not one slice cut out of it.
And I'm crying with my head in my hands at about age seven.
Which is really that picture.
If I can track it down is my childhood in a nutshell.
Me crying into an Alph cake.
Would they risk it?
By the way, the leprechaun just got shot again.
And now he's out this time.
Now he's out.
He's dead.
He's out.
But I don't know if he's dead, but he's out.
They did find out that they need to get a four leaf clover to stop him.
She heard that from the guy.
So the leprechaun kills him, hangs him from an elevator shaft.
And he's like, hey, you should find a four leaf clover.
He's still alive.
The leprechaun doesn't finish the job.
With his dying breath.
You've got to find a clover.
Laddie.
Lassie, probably.
Lassie.
Yeah.
So now they're in the field looking for four leaf clover's
to stop the leprechaun.
Like much like a scene from patch childhood.
What is this guy up to?
Buckston.
Francis.
I let him up the other day too.
Actually, coincidentally, I was like, I was wondering what.
Francis.
I was wondering what was happening to him and what happened to the guy
that played, uh, uh, in Beetlejuice.
Oh, the fact guy.
Ortha.
Yeah, he died.
Did you know that?
They didn't know that one.
Yeah.
He died because he had some mobility issues.
It's very steady fell in his house and hit his head and died.
Yeah, that sucks.
I love that guy.
Yeah, I loved him.
I love Captain O 'Hara in the movie and Jeffrey Jones.
Everybody in the movie.
It's a home run.
It's a grand slam, I would say.
It really is.
Tour de force, but every movie was just like inventing shit.
Like that was like one of the craziest performances of all time.
Jeffrey Jones.
Ortha was arrested for child pornography.
Yeah, he was.
And the guy can still make me laugh.
Yeah.
Ferris Bueller's day off and Beetlejuice.
That's how funny the one guy is.
I feel bad even saying that out loud.
Now Jones, it'd be a controversial pick,
but he'd fit right into our movie because I guarantee his breath smells like coffee
and he has a mustache.
I agree.
And he was funny in the 80s.
Let's get him on board.
I agree.
We'll make him promise not to look at any child porn while he's filming our movie.
The look again.
This is the third podcast now where we've discussed child porn.
Didn't didn't think we could get it in, but here we are.
I didn't even realize we were doing it.
Yeah.
Mark Holton is the man who played Pete Francis.
Okay.
He was also in Teen Wolf, if you remember.
I do indeed.
He also played Gacy in the John Wayne Gacy movie.
Oh, I bet that's horrifying.
Our friend Vince Avril.
Yeah.
Good friend of ours.
Love Vince.
He is very frightened of horror films.
He does not care for them.
I want to get him on the podcast just to watch how scared he gets.
Okay.
I've had him leave my house when I put on something scary before
because he couldn't handle it.
I was, I, I've, I've respect that.
But he said the last time he looked at anything horror related,
he goes, I turned on Showtime.
There was that movie Gacy on and that fat guy from Peewee's big adventure played.
There you go.
And he goes, he's trying to push this child's head into a bear trap.
It disturbed me.
That sounds really disturbing.
Yeah.
You know what I don't think is fair, frankly?
What's that?
Is that when you go see a comedy, like I saw a train wreck,
you go and you're forced to watch three,
four really horrifying horror movie trailers.
I don't think that's fair to people who don't want to see that, you know?
I, I usually find that the genres of the trailers reflect the genre of the film.
This is not always the case, though.
Really?
It's not always the case.
And when I saw vacation,
I saw one of the scariest horror movie trailers I've ever seen.
I don't, I wish I remember what it was called, but it was really freaky.
What was the trailer?
You know, it was just like a real tortury kind of vibe.
And it was very intense.
It had a red band instead of a green band at the beginning.
Really?
In front of vacation?
Yeah, and it was a horror movie trailer.
And I was like, well, what about the people who came to see this family comedy?
It's not a family comedy.
It's a comedy about a family.
It's a r -rated comedy.
Comedy about a family.
Family comedy.
This is the credit on actor Mark Holton's IMDB that I'm most intrigued by.
Okay.
By the way, they slingshot it at Fort Leif Clover
into the Lepricon's mouth and he's melting it.
Now he's turned pink lights and some green.
Very reminiscent of the Gremlins death here.
Yeah, when Spike falls into the pond.
Or no, in the daylight.
Except somehow Gremlins filmed 10 years earlier
had better special effects.
This is the actor, the credit I want to see,
Francis from Peewe's Big Adventure.
And he was on Tim and Eric's awesome show, Great Job.
Played a character.
One episode, his character name was BM Farts.
No, I don't remember that.
Well, I don't remember either.
I want to see it though.
Sounds funny.
Yeah, well, I guess he still works occasionally.
That's probably a guy who had to find another career.
Now he's 2008, up till 2008, looks like steady work.
All right.
That's kind of cool makeup effects there.
It looks like, well, again, it looks like the Gremlins effect.
It's the exact same effect.
It looks kind of like, remember that fruit and vegetable Gremlins and Gremlins too?
I hate Gremlins too.
I fucking love Gremlins too.
You're out of your fucking mind.
You know, it's hailed as like a lost classic now.
It's got a whole lot of respect these days and I have always loved it.
Explained to me.
I mean, I get that it's a...
Well, it's a satire.
I mean, it's a comedy.
It's kind of like a loony tunes type deal.
Yeah, but why did they go that route?
And they're making front of Trump 25 years ahead of its time.
Why did they go that route with it though?
I think Joe Danty, who was a great director.
I like Danty.
What is he directly lately?
A lot of like straight to the EOD shut.
But I really loved him for that 10 -year stretch.
I loved all his movies.
And I think he kind of leans more towards comedy.
You know, like I think he wants his movies to be kind of fun.
Well, I mean, it was certainly a bold choice for a sequel.
I just wanted another Gremlins though.
I also love that the projector broke when you saw it in the theater
because the Gremlins were fucking with it.
And it felt really real and was really cool.
And then when you rented it,
they shot a different version where it seemed like your VCR tape was being torn up.
Now that was pretty cool.
In the version with the videotape being ripped up,
does Hogan still jump up somehow?
Yes.
That's pretty cool.
Hogan's in there.
Yeah, I remember that.
What people sure got over that Hogan scandal quick.
These things flare up now for like 30 seconds.
Everyone's like, oh,
fuck Hulk Hogan.
Like they ever gave a shit about Hulk Hogan to begin with.
Because he said, what did he say?
I'm not going to say what he said,
but he said some pretty outlandishly racist stuff.
I mean, I get it.
It's just I'm kind of like,
why are you allowing yourself to get so upset about Hulk Hogan?
But wait a second.
He has no effect on your life.
Why?
That tape came out eight years ago.
And nobody said anything.
Did that part not come out?
I think it was part of maybe his divorce hearings.
This came out or something.
I don't know.
Oh, yeah, okay.
I think I heard that.
I've never been so relieved.
By the way, the credits have been rolling for about 20 seconds.
Yeah, that we were paying no attention.
And yet you just felt that you wanted the movie to be over.
Thank you.
It was really bad.
This guy's name is John Overacker.
Can we make a pact right now?
Yeah.
No more leprechaun movies on the podcast.
Yeah, obviously, Joe.
None of them.
No, but here's the thing.
A few months goes by.
You think, I'll be funny like we thought today
it'll be funny to watch it because it's not that great.
Yeah, no.
Well, he had one and a half stars from the very,
very loose standards of Netflix viewers.
So that tells you that.
Yeah, well, anyway, Patty,
I still had a nice time, Joe, as I always do.
And I hope our listeners did as well.
I had a great time.
It's always nice to sit on a love seat with you and watch your film.
You've been listening to We'll See You In Hell.
It's been a presentation of the Fangoria podcast network.
Produced by Thomas DeFail, an executive produced by Ken Haley
of Fangoria Entertainment.
For press opportunities, advertising, inquiries,
and information about We'll See You In Hell.
Please contact Ken via email.
His address is kenatfangoria .com
K -E -N at Fangoria .com.
Thanks a lot, guys.
We'll see you next time in Hell.