All right, welcome to we'll see you in hell it's the podcast you turned to when you want to talk about those
John reflects in TV shows I'm Joe DeRosa and I'm Patrick Walsh I love everybody house
things Joe just just great Pat yeah we live in a great world overthrow of the
government yeah I mean right now in the next week let's say
everyone is almost a hundred percent certain that there will be another terrorist attack
here on US soil and no one is doing anything and that's reassuring no it's uh it's an
interesting time where you are living in right now no one is speaking to us it reminds me of like
when my parents used to scream at each other for like four hours and then they would just kind of
come downstairs and just not mention it like no we heard it something needs to be said to us so
that we know if we're gonna be okay here or not yeah you kids want to go to pizza and uh okay you
know watch me and your mother sitting in icy silence while we drink from those big red see -through
plastic cups uh you know aside all that aside though Walsh aside from a doomed country aside from
honestly I don't know if we're making it out of 2021 frankly I'm surprised we made it out of 2020
this this year's will be worse than last year yeah it is for decades maybe this year will be
worse than the last yeah despite your cute memes you know where it's like speedy Gonzalez
in the one side and it says 2020 and then it says 2021 on the other side and it's like the dust of him
when he ran away okay you know that that'd be like one of those dumb memes you'd say it's like yeah no
you're uh but he's running into the open mouth of Sylvester the cat yeah uh I had a friend uh who was
in town uh and we were speaking yesterday and she told me that she it was the first time she had been
into the city since way before any of this started happening because she lives out of state okay she
said that uh she said she was walking through unions like not through union square but through like
both the streets but the area below union square to go up to the strand bookstore and she burst
into tears because she said it was the first time she had seen what everybody in New York was talking
about like the like the destruction of the city like the fall of every business and whatever yeah he
was like it never it was never crystallized until that moment and she said it was so sad to see and
I was like yeah it sounds about right and that's when I realized that's what I'm living in every day and uh
God knows what emotions are swirling around in me right now I only want to think about it yeah
I mean everyone's gonna have really severe stuff I think whether you want to call it PTSD or whatever
else that will pop up in new and strange ways throughout the rest of our lives but like I'm feeling it
you know I feel like I don't want to get out of bed every day and I want to go to sleep at 8 p .m.
and etc and I've never had that so I have to wonder what the crazy people are doing throughout this
situation they must just be getting crazier and crazier and waiting to strike which will happen and
is happening my only hope is that we're crazier way crazier than we think we are so then like if
if we're staying sort of we are by the way yeah then like it will be that much worse but um I don't
know man uh anyway today's show is Cobra Kai
Cobra Kai um on a serious note folks uh let's get serious for a second forget all that fluff at the
top on a serious note um stay alive don't I they're the the the uh the COVID sickness and the
suicides are getting closer and closer to me closer and closer to uh my friends you know so like
just keep your wits about you call up a friend I I know you guys still got the Facebook page at least
you got these hellions hop on talk movies whatever listen to an old episode or do something that
doesn't involve me in Joe to to benefit your mental health you'll probably be better off
but uh I would go as far as saying this at this point if you're getting into such a dark place that
you might do something harmful to yourself uh whatever to whatever degree if it's between that
and going out and hanging out with some friends go hang out with the friends don't worry about the
you shouldn't do that because of COVID or what that's my advice I'd rather see you I'd rather see you
get a flu than uh you know like something's got to give here at some point I'm not telling you to be
careless I'm not saying go spread it around but I'm saying like you know a lot of people are like
destroying their mental state yeah it's like you'd I'd rather see you just maybe go be a little risky
and hang out with a couple of friends and have some drinks hang out and have drinks in a park you know
like be safe about it you can do both um hop on a passing box car train
ride the rails a bit yeah drink with like like a hobo you know yeah there's something you could do here
sure um what else is going on Joe I mean uh my my I got nothing my creativity is dried up
supposed to be like pitching things and I'm like everyone on this call is just gonna be cool acting
like this isn't happening uh it is a weird time for that I had a I had a really good meeting this
week with somebody that uh it was a relief it was a relief it was the first meeting I'd had in a
while with somebody in the industry to talk about a project and we laughed a lot and I didn't know
this person but as soon as we started talking at the top of the call she just goes how you doing nice
to meet you how are you and I go oh just fucking great I mean it's just isn't this amazing
started laughing and she's like I know right it's fucking sucks and we just uh it was it was it was
honestly like one of the most therapeutic things I've done through this entire thing was like to have
a work call that was that like lacks and candid and just it was nice but it and I bring it up for not
the reason to say I had a good call I bring it up to say it was a relief because had it gone in the
other direction mm -hmm which some of them that I've had have as you're talking about where people are
just talking as if yeah nothing's happening it's just odd man it's just very uh which by the way
is Hollywood just open I'm just seeing production after production coming out they don't even throw up
the covid uh disclaimer anymore of like this was shot with testing or or before or what the new
hell's kitchen season just came out Gordon Ramsay and it takes place in Vegas which is like the Wild West
I think they just shot the fucking thing like yeah I mean there's a chance these things
sat on the shelf but probably not I think that you know like I iced teas on I love iced tea of course
but he's on he's one of one of the funniest people on Twitter yeah but um you know he's super like
hey you fucking idiots wear a mask stay inside whatever then somebody asked the status of his new like
CW crime show or something oh yeah we're in production we're shooting right now you know I think
there's this complete disconnect that people have with like yeah everyone should be doing this but
I'm I I don't have to obviously I'm safe well there's that new Netflix show now I'm sure they're
taking I'm I'm assuming they're taking and I'm not shitting on the show my friend fortune uh
feemsters on it yeah uh and David spade hosted and I watched it last night yeah and like I want it to be
I wanted to do well because I'm fans of them but I mean they're they're again no disclaimer they're
out there spades making covid jokes in front of a full audience I was like you can just do this now
they bring out a Elizabeth shoe she hugs 14 -age children she hugs them they had the funny thing was
they had macho and spotka on on a zoom screen clearly like you guys are just at that age where
we're gonna keep you in another room yeah exactly teetering on 60 yeah they got um you know I
think I sent this to you job but we had the we we take these curative tests I don't know if that's
the same test they take in New York but that's our sort of covid test and they announced this week
that it basically doesn't work yeah you send me this is what everyone's been using as as a test uh and
they said not only that but the 25 year old who they who they gave the money to to like provide
a bit provide these tests has no medical experience um they gave this huge contract to a completely
unreliable person uh and now that's becoming a big scandal so we're alone we're just alone yeah
the 25 year old the good news is he's got a million followers on tick -tock that's what they looked at
actually yeah uh so yeah hit no here it is it's I mean uh the city is paying curative $115
for every test not reimbursed by insurance collecting nearly 65 million to date this is a scandal of
shocking proportions painful to think how many angelinos received a false negative from a curative test
when they were actually positive so LA seems to be I mean the the corruption that it goes we might
as well be doing a fucking Chinatown sequel yeah this uh I mean look at the bright side
aside from the constant suit in the air and the zero good restaurants lack of culture
uh lack of real diversity uh utter rampaging selfishness uh town built on vanity
mm -hmm I'm sorry I was trying to think of a positive you're also taunting from the point of
you of someone who just described his own city as as falling into the sewer to start the show
um I'm not saying I'm in a much better place but I yeah at least our test work I think I think I don't
know who knows well the things those tests they do like at SNL there's a lot of talk about them not
working where they just pop it onto your forehead and tell your temperature but I don't think anybody
knows I went and got a rapid test recently and the waiting room of the clinic was in violation of
COVID whatever the protocol like there was like 20 people in the waiting room and like the ladies
behind the desk are screaming at people it's because they're like wandering around and it was a fucking
shit show yeah and here's the worst part it was a privatized clinic that went public that got bought
by a public thing and I know there's a lot of bad with privatized health care and I know there's
a lot of good with public health care but my god almighty you want to see two systems that don't work
either way you know what I mean or at least some proof that there's a little bit good on either side
potentially right this thing went from like a military fucking operation to like a zoo it was just
ridiculous dude it was it was chaos in there yeah like the day after it got absorbed into the
public chain and I was just like yeah look man I've benefited from from non -privatized health care
greatly like I'm for it but guys well there's there's some there's some bad stuff here like there's
some stuff that needs to be tended to and then also you know it's not so bad all the time when you
can go into a clinic that only takes some insurance and I mean and I'm saying that from a place
that usually don't take my insurance right I'm not saying that selfishly but I don't know what
the answer is so fucking in fairness you did buy your insurance from one of the bacon egg and cheese
on a roll guys yeah I'm the street no it was in a bodega it was inside but yeah it was
yeah that's my my first car insurance I got in the back of a of a food for less the one by your
your last apartment here in LA it's a beautiful parking lot to wander through yeah I googled like
cheapest car insurance possible because I had this thousand dollar car and they sent me to this
place and I'm walking around the food for less parking lot like hey where is the insurance building
here like oh no it's a it's a small insurance company inside the food for less but you know they
insured my car sometimes I wonder why do I pay for like a state farm they all pay out unless that's
the issue is that when you actually have an accident they they're not at food for less anymore
they all vanish into the sewers I'm currently with Geico and it is dirt cheap okay dirt cheap crazy
cheap like it was hundreds of dollars less than any of the other quotes I got now I want to ask you
something on air yeah it's not not even remotely scandalous but so this week and our friend Matt
sent us both this link to get the hammer box set it's like a bunch of hammer film 20 hammer films
on Blu -ray for like 20 bucks it was discounted from a hundred dollars Matt McCarthy of we watch wrestling
yes tune into that show yes so I get on the the website I'm like shit there's lots great deals here
I buy six items six Blu -ray is at a massive a deep discount if you will and I'm like well great
this will be in my new place this will be in my new place I want to give these Amazon Fox any money
48 hours later I have six emails from deep discount DVD I'm like sweet I guess it's it's shipped baby
it each email is an individual cancellation for each of the six items that I ordered with
you know the hammer box set all of them are not coming to me yeah oh god damn it wait a minute I
assumed my email from deep discount was a confirmation let me check my ass Matt he said he's got a
confirmation it just seems like I got a shipping confirmation here god damn it uh Matt said something
that made me laugh I was racing to meet my friend when I got the text from him uh for the hammer box
yeah and I was like there's no time to think about this I have to get this right now
and I should have done that and I did it so fast and all I was thinking was I just got scammed something
this there's no way this was real I just got scammed and I texted Matt and I go I never ordered
something so fast in my life and he said I ordered it with the speed of a man that was certain he made
a mistake and I was like yeah yeah that's exactly I'm glad you felt that way okay we're good uh and I
think it's legit I'm assuming it's just gonna be one of those deals where they got a case of like promo
copies right to them and they can resell you know the for dollar each or whatever and they can
resell them at 20 bucks but it's a set I'd been looking at for a while but I was not gonna pull the
trigger on because I like I like the hammer stuff but not enough to spend a hundred plus dollars on
more blue rights of it and I had some of the movies already but to 20 bucks for that collection is
pretty insane it's insane it's a dollar movie and uh pop market is another it's the sort of the
vinyl equivalent of deep discount DVD and I've got some great deals on there that seem too good
to be true and then one day they just started canceling every order so who knows I think that they're
not like Amazon in that they have to give you a price if it's up they're basically just saying fuck
you but it's fun yeah in any case thank you Matt for bringing that to our attention yes uh thank
you both for buying an extra one and sending it to me I texted you as soon as I got it I don't know
why you didn't hop on it because I thought I'd give them even more money and they didn't want any
of it that's what I don't get all of them sold out I every one of the six items I was ordering
and you're positive that's the case HIV oh boy oh boy all right well I want to tell you about
before we move into the movie corner yeah wait did I have a hold on I'm trying to forget if I have
scary stuff give me a second here I do have a couple scary stuff but something I want to talk about
more than that oh news psycho they announced a Rubik's Cube movie is coming out
what are your thoughts on that I mean I don't have any it's like the problem is like
you know we've been talking for years about how there's no comedy anymore and how comedy is
getting worse and worse but the truth is there's nothing to lampoon there's nothing to satirize it's
it's done they're making a goddamn Rubik's Cube movie it's like when I heard they were making a Tetris
movie a few years ago which I believe is still coming Tetris is at that very least falling blocks I mean
I can't imagine what the movie would be but at least you have to dodge blocks a Rubik's Cube is a
as you well know a cube you twist with your hands what is the plot I'm sure it will be
uh you know some alien device that once it is solved it can go home or
fixes some galactic dilemma or something like that that's my guess so like the need to do it like
okay so like we always talk about hey when you're making a movie out of my three sons which nobody
remembers from the 1950s why do you have to call it my three sons just make a movie about a guy and
his kids this is a hypothetical that movie doesn't exist but why do you need the Rubik's Cube name
is it like they're just trying to sell more of the items I don't know in what fucking analog
you know in this digital landscape what what analog purist they think wants to see a Rubik's Cube movie
or they think it's even still playing with a Rubik's Cube the only thing I could think of is there's a new
Rubik's I'm guessing perhaps there's a new like LCD screen Rubik's Cube coming out where it's a it's the
square it's all screens and then there's the digital representation of the color squares on the screens
and because it's screens that you can do different configurations of the cube or whatever and it'll be
the new Rubik's Cube or whatever the fuck I don't know which I guess would be kind of cool but
that's the only way I could think of it you could update this thing to where people would still
who the fuck is sitting there like a psycho I mean with these things I hate it when before there was
a game or anything like that we had one of my parents house you know and we had nothing to do there
but the only time I ever used it was like when I was just needed something to do with my hands while
I was watching TV that wasn't masturbating you know I my dad would take the cube once in a while
and take it apart and reassemble it and you know the original form with all the solved
and that blew me away and then I and then in five minutes it would be mixed up again and I wouldn't
be able to figure out how to get get it anywhere near back normal right the last time I remember
a movie coming out to move a product was the power glove with the wizard the Fred Savage vehicle
right but that's even even with that though it was called the wizard right and it was about
basically an autistic kid who was graded video games and like they're we it's actually kind of a
a drama oh I saw it that yeah but I mean it's like it and yeah there was product placement
and obviously with the power glove and it's where they announced Super Mario Brothers 3 and all that
stuff which is cool but like it wasn't called power glove it would be right now it would be called
power glove I mean it's this movie may never see the light of day there was supposed to be a candy
land movie with Will Smith a few years ago that never came to pass you know I think sometimes they
just look in the mirror and they're like let's just both plug in this horse shit uh not not often
but at least with candy man visually you could imagine it would be pretty crazy and trippy yeah
but I guess I'm gonna be like a willy wonka I watched the speed cubers documentary on Netflix which is
about the very low stakes world of uh who can do it the fastest and they had all these you know I would
say 99 % of them were on the spectrum but they had all these kids uh who could do them in like six
seconds do these Rubik's cubes and it was actually a great little documentary it's only 45 minutes
it's on Netflix the kids they focus on are very sweet but like yeah and I don't know what it would be
I don't know what it would be um it's a dark time did you watch that thing I sent you with trailers for
30 new Netflix movies yeah it's a three minute trailer for 27 different movies that are coming to
Netflix they're they're excitedly announcing that they're gonna have a movie every week in 2021
and there isn't one of these projects that looked good or he'd find it it looks that bad it looks
terrible I mean it's it's quick clips of stuff but like it's like it's they also have their talent
announcing it so it's like linman well on a zoom and then he he says something at the same time as
Halle Berry and he's like I can't believe this I just had a jinx with Cal with Halle Berry so there's
like written material as well that makes you want to die but then the clips the there's a superhero
movie with Melissa McCarthy and Ma who's Ma Octavia Spencer they play superheroes like they look
like a hundred million dollars they are the superheroes yes what is it a comedy I would so I would hope
I mean she's in a movie now where it's her partnered with James Corden as a robot on HBO Max
these things she's got a movie every couple weeks oh well voiced by James Corden well
yeah I was trying to tell you the other day like Johnny Carson the legend you know the he held
that seat forever probably the best to ever do it Johnny Carson wasn't on the weekend you know
doing Oklahoma he wasn't you know the star of the godfather part two or some why is James Corden doing
five movies a year and hosting a nightly talk show because he's James Corden you answered your own
question and kids don't like it was like I don't seem to like him yeah Carson was like I don't need
to do that shit I'm Johnny fucking Carson yeah I'm gonna go get drunk with McMahon it's Saturday I
bet he never got drunk with McMahon no they used to get shit can together oh yeah I always got
the vibe like he wouldn't hang out with him outside of no there's stories of Carson like getting into bar
fights and shit he was apparently wild drunk I have his biography I haven't read it yeah do you ever see
the clip of McMahon drunk on the show he was always drunk on the show I just I didn't know that they
were friendly outside I always thought it was a Paul and Dave situation where they never interacted
no there's a Dave Letterman did have had his cameo and cabin boy it's not like he didn't act
as well but remember that was funny part of the entire movie it's incredible I disagree with you but
it's a very funny part let me rephrase that I think the movie is funny up until that scene ends and
then they're on the boat and I don't care anymore boy I hate them fancy that yeah yeah have the
London broil yeah yeah anyway I let's kick off the movie corner with something I want to talk
about that I downloaded then immediately returned to the audible store last night great yes I I'll
start with what I just watched which was this so there's two movies coming out that are for my
consideration for and for yours promising young woman which I hear is great and is a I believe a
rape revenge movie starring Carrie Mulligan that I have heard is just awesome and then a movie called
Pieces of a woman so of course I get these confused all the time but Pieces of a woman stars Vanessa
Kirby Ellen Burston of the actresses fame and Shyla Buff who has been dropped from all market talked
about this last week what you talked about this already I mentioned he was pulled from the marketing
but I didn't oh oh oh I just watched the book I'm sorry I'm sorry okay so I finally watched it
it's you know there's all these articles now like did Shyacost Vanessa Kirby her Oscar would
like imagine sitting in your imagine caring Joe imagine caring even Vanessa Kirby shouldn't give
a fucking shit but these people like at variety like what does this mean for Kirby's Oscar chip
get the fuck over yourself um the movie is not is not good it starts with a 30 minute
on one one shot unbroken take of a woman having a painful horrible home birth
um just a constantly roving camera in a small apartment while Shyla both goes like what the fuck's
going on and she's like and uh you know she moans and groans and has this horrible birth for 30 minutes
um spoiler alert baby dies 30 minutes in and then the rest of the movie is her dealing with the
horrible pain of having lost a child and they drop this mid -pandem it is you know I get it is
well acted you know it's probably the last time we're gonna see LaBouffe in a movie um gets
as dung out for the occasion all right but um you know everyone thinks they're making such
fucking art in this thing the only person who actually comes off with with some dignity is burst
in everyone else it literally might as well just be wearing a sash that says award me an Oscar
please I lost my fake fictional baby uh didn't care for the film all right I download it sometimes we
do books on the movie corner I download it last night uh I've been I've been
I've been incessantly watching and rewatching Seinfelds because they take me out of and I'm
because I've exhausted the show four or five times over at this point but I just keep going back
and watching them again because they're just such an escape from all the shit um so last night I
download is this anything Jerry Seinfelds new audio book I've got it haven't listened to it
it documents all of his material basically from from the beginning of his career up through present day
okay like you know that it's some of it is stuff that made it into a special hero there's a lot of
it is stuff that didn't and it's just kind of like the this is a representation of all the jokes I
kept in this accordion folder over the years right with each decade he does like an intro chapter
explaining where he was at at that time and that sort of thing uh I bought it I went to sleep
listening to it I heard a lot of it because I was having trouble sleeping I immediately returned
it this morning it's the most insane thing I've ever heard in my life really uh I would net and I
don't say that to shit on him I'm sure it's a fun read yeah doesn't work as an audio book because this
literally is just joke for joke for joke it's not like he's formed these jokes into some sort of narrative
it's just jokes yeah and he's got an English woman announcing each joke so she'll go
she'll go going into the city and then he'll go when I was a kid you lived on Long Island you went
in to the city you got on the train then you got off the train then you got in a cab what do you do
with Uber you take an Uber pop pop thoughts but I was a kid that's the entire book it's
lunacy it makes no sense it just now again it probably worked really well as a book
because you could just read the material like on the toilet or something and you just have a few
chuckles after you read a few pages put it away this format they've tried to do with this audio book
it just does not work man at all see I thought I'd much rather listen to him that's what I do it
and read it that's what I thought and then because he's in a studio recording the bits the bits where
he's clearly supposed to be screaming he's doing this fake scream okay I'll be like hope you like
you know like I'll just do a line from the show because I can't remember one of the jokes but
hopefully like a like relationship ends like a band -aid you got to pull it right off like he like
does this like throat scream it's very weird his rhythm and tone and inflections are different because
he's doing an audio version of this audio book right not just stand up I was very disappointed because
I thought I had found six more hours of Seinfeld to just kind of delve into yeah escape from the hell
on earth right now and it just doesn't it just does not work as an audio book it just doesn't work
some of the bits it's crazy because like it'll be like four different versions of the same joke
and he'll separate them or like it'll be like five things that go together in his act but he'll
separate them all as five different jokes instead of just clumping them together uh -huh
so it's just so stop start stop start stop start and this English lady keeps coming in and titling
everything it's it's so weird it doesn't make any sense I have a few things to say here first this
isn't a movie it's a book no but you've done audio books in the movie corner before I don't think
that's true yeah I simply wouldn't have done that yeah yeah well go to the listeners on that I might
have done them as a scary stuff it doesn't matter as I said at the top of this sometimes we do
books and don't I don't need I don't we don't I mean I you always had your issues with me and the
scary stuff but I mean I think the rules to this one are a billion percent clearer and you get to your
other point what's your other you have fucked it over um also last night I watched the one where they
drew on Uncle Leo's eyebrows yeah and I was like a this one is never aired I haven't seen this one
in 10 years be it's insane I forgot how insane that show gets by the end of it I mean just not
they got Newman in a in a back room with like a hot lamp on his face sweating and crazy stuff um yeah
that's one of my favorite endings in the episode that's the one with Wilford Brimley is the attorney
general the or the or the postmaster general where he well he wasn't in it unless I missed him but I
know I know he's in one of them I remember him being I think that's the same one with Newman getting
because it's where they because Newman knows that Kramer is I don't know maybe I'm talking
out of my it's easy to mix them up yeah um and it's a TV show so it has no place in past movie
corner just like audio books I watched well that's not we've done TV shows in the movie
many many times but go watch shithouse shithouse shithouse it is it's a 2020 movie it is an
indie movie I had just heard and seen so many people love this thing you know it's I was already
kind of rolling my eyes it's it was made by a like a 22 -year -old 23 -year -old it was made for like
$15 ,000 there's a duploss amongst the producers who helped out and the title is shithouse with the like
the percent sign and the ampersand you know because they can't say shit on the poster so everything
about it looks terrible sounds terrible it's a it was just a fantastic movie it's it's along the lines
of a before sunrise where it's just a guy who's I've you know it's a familiar story to everyone who
goes away to college I commuted but you know nobody wants to talk about how lonely you are and how
it's just like where are my friends and I miss my family and I don't know what you know this first
time away from home so it's this guy just doing a there he does not care how bad he looks how
nerdy he looks how awkward he looks how pathetic he looks it's the guy you know wrote directed and stars
in it but he just kind of it's a comedy about basically how bad an awkward and comfortable college is
for half the running time I would say and then he hooks up with this girl to party played by Dylan
Galula who was great actress and the two of them have this kind of fun wacky night together at college
gets a little serious here and there but by and large it's just a very funny little indie movie the
kind of movie they made all the time in the 90s just like young people hanging out having fun
and I hope they make a lot more like it knowing that this thing cost $15 ,000 makes me feel like I've
wasted my life I should be doing this I won't do it though I know I won't do it but it's it really
really is a good little movie I recommend checking it out it's gonna be free probably in two weeks
that's been $5 to rent for like three months check it out I finally sat down in front of back watch
pet cemetery too we've discussed it on the show before I've I think you have consecutively said like
I've seen parts of it I you know you know I was never a fan or where I maybe I had watched it but
wasn't paying terribly close attention because I didn't like it but I finally sat down said I'm
gonna watch this thing start to finish it's garnered a cold following it's been 20 odd years since it's
released there are almost 30 years since it's released I want to see what I was missing
director Mary I always want to say Hartman it's not Mary Hartman Mary Hartman Lambert Mary Lambert
returned to direct this picture I believe she co -wrote it as well I have this to say
not only did Mary Lambert not work again well she did but in much on much lesser plateaus
well you know not quite high a ground you know she continued on not only did that happen not only
what she somewhat shuffled out of the Hollywood fold she deserved to be this film is atrocious
on every level it is made by somebody who doesn't know how to make a movie look no further than the dream
sequence seen where the wavy line effects come over the scream so you know that Anthony Edwards is
having a dream it's a terrible movie it is not in any way consistent with Stephen King's original
source material that could be the studio's fault I don't know I don't know that there was a way to
make this movie good but I do think that there was a way to at least convey the material in
some sort of intriguing manner and this thing is I mean you've mentioned this before on the show
the end the end credit sequence the scene right before it they're driving off in a car and there's
the faces of people are like coming up in little dissolve circles on the or wipe circles rather
on the screen like like the end of a fucking little house on the prairie episode this is somebody
that doesn't know how to make a movie this is terrible yeah it's like in in the muppet show when like
Charles growd and it'd be singing in a bubble in the corner and miss piggy be looking up at him or
something it's like the plot of the movie basically is clancy brown dies and gets buried in the
pet cemetery for some reason even though he's an asshole and his stepson hates him and he's
abusive and he wants to be rid of him and and the stepson is not in any way at fault for his dad
stepdad dying yet the step kid that hates him says we got it we're going to get in trouble and we need
which makes no sense so they bury him in the pet cemetery and the effect as on clancy brown is it
makes him zany this is the plot of the movie clancy brown comes back as a zany zombie who
if I remember correctly there's a zany rape attempt isn't there it's a full -on rape yeah of his wife
yes but played sort of wacky if I remember correctly there's a bit of a wackiness to it and and
not only comes back as a kind of quirky zombie continues to function as the sheriff of the town
puts on a sheriff clothes every day and goes to work nobody notices that he's a rotting man walking
around this is it's it's the movie it's fucking crazy and not in a fun way in a way that makes no sense
god bless you Lambert I really love the first movie but I'm sorry to say it and you know it's
it this struck me as somebody that doesn't know what they're doing behind the camera whoever wrote
this should have also been ostracized I would like to see that Eddie fur along rightfully so
another guy just rightfully channeled out a Hollywood shortly after this I mean the head was just a
terrible actor uh he was I mean the the puberty he was going through in terminare to I've never
anyone else would have just recast it's it's it's almost too much but um this was not
co -written by Mary Lambert was right by Richard out and I think pet cemetery is a very well -directed
movie from what it looks like here Lambert wanted to do it about Ellie Ellie Creed as the central
character who was the only survivor Paramount did not want to make the lead a teenage girl so they
rewrote it and probably it was rushed into production as this is the vibe I get and that problem with
these situations is now her career is essentially done because she's directed this movie that you know
people just don't like although looking at the reviews here variety says it's 50 % better than its
predecessor I mean this is just insane yeah it's just insane now here's here's there's the the
the completely sexist double standard of Hollywood James out and who wrote this piece of shit
or Richard out and excuse me Richard wrote this piece of shit gets to then go on
uh well he wrote boy you wrote for the adventures of brisco county junior all right let's not
I used to love that show uh but then he gets to he gets to write the uh in out in the original
screenplay was acquired for the basis of journey to the center of the earth he subsequently wrote
the sequel journey two uh those are certainly much higher profile projects in my opinion that he
deserves Steven Spielberg selected into a rewrite of gremlins two although he didn't receive credit
on it it led to an exclusive multi -year writing deal at Warner Brothers during which he penned several
screenplays including an unproduced sequel to the goonies I mean you know look I don't mean to be hard
on Lambert I'm being half facetious here but like you you I assume you get what I'm saying where it's
like I get it the script is terrible it's not going to be a great movie but she's doing things behind
the camera here where I'm just like you've got to be kidding me like yeah you you feel us they feel
twin peaks influenced they feel like she's going for a weirdness that that you can't mimic the people
have tried to mimic David Lynch and you wind up looking really stupid maybe that's what it is maybe it
is supposed to just be this yeah that's a good call because there is something twin peak -ish to the
Clancy Brown character yeah Clancy Brown who usually is an excellent actor slipping in and out of this
absurd fucking New England accent the entire time literally like it sounds like he's doing like
it sounds like he's telling you a joke at the at a party about the peppered farm man you know what I
mean and he's just he's just trying to get through that guy's lines so you know who's you know he's
doing in the bit right it's a terrible terrible terrible terrible movie but I still respect it more than
that shit house fucking remake that came out two years ago yeah it's way better than the remake and
don't it's way better I respect it oh sorry how it's way better than that hashtag s h asterix
t house all right my third is a documentary called feels good man this is also available for like
two three bucks and all the streaming services so it'll probably be free very shortly feels good
man is a very interesting documentary very depressing documentary about the very cool very
you know funny friendly loving cartoonist who created amongst many other characters this character
peppy the frog and peppy the frog became the unofficial official face of the alt -right movement
so he basically made this comic book kind of like a ghost world type thing sort of an underground
comic book that was pretty successful and doing well with his friends and it was basically about
four animals that live together and the strips you see of his work the the animation looks really cool
that the jokes are funny it's just a guy who like wanted to make people laugh and do drawings and he's a
family man and has a you know daughter and a wife and just tries to get through the day and be happy
and now has to live with this horrible guilt that this frog that he created is now the representative for
hate in America basically and he tried for a little bit to kind of get it back you know but instead
it's like you google now peppy the frog and his name comes up you know he's associated with
this alt -right like not just right wing we're talking like alt -right psychos so
it's very very sad it's it's just basically kind of a encapsulation of why the internet is so horrible
how horribly it can go wrong um you know this guy now can't make any money off his most famous
successful character and you know it's it's a it's a small scale story about that guy and the
situation but it's also does a nice job of kind of painting a picture of how horribly fucked the
internet is and also a really good look at those Q and on alt -right type chat rooms and what's the
place not read it but what's the other place where they go in and
type chat for chat yeah a lot of I didn't know anything about that world so I'm you know it's kind
of the world you don't necessarily want to be an expert on but the movie does a good job of
showing you all that if that's a topic that interests you you know it's a very interesting
documentary I think just as effective as the social dilemma and showing how
the internet can be used for bad as as if you didn't know that but you know it's it's well done I
recommend it I'll close us out with a documentary called For the Love of Spock okay which was made by
Leonard Nimoy's son and it's a documentary about Leonard Nimoy and more more specifically his
portrayal of Spock and what Spock has meant to the culture and how the character reflected the man
and the man reflected the character nothing terribly moving but a very sweet sentimental documentary
and nothing you know terribly new that you don't already kind of you know it's not like you're
gonna see this crazy behind the scenes bonus footage that you've never seen before or you know
tons of exclusive interviews or anything like that it just kind of tells the story through Leonard
Nimoy's own words and through the words of his son and and friends and colleagues of the actor
himself and it's just a very touching little film you know if you're a Star Trek fan I recommend watching
it that's really but yeah I mean it's you know it's it's it's a nice little just kind of again escape
okay just watch something where people are saying nice thing my biggest takeaway was that he he
was a good just solid drinker well and do his fifties really yeah no that was about Nimoy neither did I
but he went into a rehab in like his early fifties and I was like okay it's time anyway our show today
coberkai season three we've already discussed seasons one and season two Pat and I are both fans
season three dropped nice and early in 2021 on Netflix
uh we've both watched the season in its entirety and we're here to talk about it there's gonna be a lot
of spoilers in this so if you haven't seen it yet you're gonna want to turn the channel now
and otherwise full disclosure I'm glad I liked it but I actually said to Joe last night I was like oh
I don't know if I want to do this because uh the three guys who do coberkai are three of my closest
friends Josh healed John her with Haydnish lost bird I see these guys all the time they're great
so you know I'm just I'm just being honest with you but uh and I'm very close with Ralph Machio
and the lady that plays his mom yes I'm actually friends good friends with Dana Deut and uh
and uh Brett Ernst or his friend and they played the car salesman Brett oh yeah I saw
Brett new stand -up once and it was very funny yeah I don't know the other guy
um the guy that like you know his like right hand man did the deal right yeah okay um yeah I'm a
fan of the show these guys for a little context John and Haydn are writing partners who did the
Harold and Kumar movies they did the fourth American pie where they go to the reunion um and they've
you know been associated with a bunch of comedy films Josh Heel did the hot tub time machine movies
which are both super funny and uh you know they're just guys that have hung in doing the work uh for
years and then finally they've been friends forever they teamed up to do this but they've been talking
about doing this since I met them in 2007 this has been a a true dream of theirs to do and they'd
explain it to me and I was like yeah it sounds really cool but like it's weird because you think okay
who's gonna green light a show with Ralph Machio and William Zabka you know you're just like those names
mean nothing to anybody and it's been such a treat to watch like even kids at like fucking love
this and also go back and love the karate kid it's become a huge hit for Netflix and I'm very happy for
but uh yeah I'm I'm happy Netflix finally got a break you know well yeah it's like YouTube I would
assume is kicking themselves but the truth is the show wouldn't have become a hit on YouTube because
nobody watched television shows well it was a huge hit on YouTube that's why I went to Netflix
well it might have been good done well for them but nothing like what it became when it went
to Netflix it might have done well for YouTube but it like I think the I would disagree with the only
because the anticipation for season three I think said it all it was that popular already and I think
the Netflix let it you know kind of sell over the fence they put seasons one on two on Netflix I
think that's where they got a lot of people I forgot they they kind of prepped them for them.
All right uh if you walk us through the the arc well season three picks up where as you could imagine
season two left off uh which was a season that picked up where season one had left off um but you're
basic uh in and out of the or synopsies of the story here is uh you're catching up with Daniel
Larusso and Johnny uh 40 years 35 years whatever it is after the events of the first karate kid film
Johnny has fallen on hard times he is not the hometown hero anymore he is a guy that is having a
rough go of it whereas Ralph Macho is elevated to be a very uh profitable uh or successful rather uh
businessman with a car dealership and a beautiful family he has everything that Johnny had in the
original movie that Ralph didn't and now Johnny is in the Ralph Macho position uh and it goes
from there as they explore you know the duality of both characters how neither of them were
wholly bad or wholly good uh it dances around for two or see the first two seasons of their potential
reconciliation Johnny relaunches Cobra Kai which brings crease the original Cobra Kai dojo uh
sensei back into the mix uh they have a falling out which is when you really start to see that Johnny's
a good guy uh and karate begins to plague the town which is where last season ended all the high
school kids are either Cobra Kai or Miyagi Doe which is Daniels Dojo uh and they have a all -out school
brawl that leaves one of the kids uh paralyzed and in a coma uh and that's where things end
and this season finds us uh with finds Johnny incredibly regretful uh lower than he's ever been
because this kid that got hurt and is now in a coma uh was basically like a son to him because his own
son wants nothing to do with him um his own son at this point has gone over to Cobra Kai so is
essentially now being pitted against his own father because Johnny is now knows as with Cobra Kai
Daniel's daughter is sort of seemingly in love with both of these boys
who will she pick Daniel is forged a relationship with Johnny's son uh and wants to try to help the kid
but Johnny's son now hates Daniel as well because he feels betrayed by Daniel uh because Daniel turned
him into the authorities after the high school brawl because he was trying to do the right thing for him
and the kid resents him now for it and creases built a tougher meaner more evil than ever Cobra Kai
uh Johnny has nothing Daniel has Miyagi Doh what will happen next uh and that's that's kind of where we're at
when the when the season opens and or in some of that stuff transpires in the first episode um this
one starts to bring in a little more of the mythology of karate kid 2 it ends on a cliffhanger
that nods to karate kid 3 uh and i would say overall we oh also we also see the return of Elizabeth
Shoe is Ali she swoops in for an episode or two and is charming and breathtaking and wonderful and
they did it really in the right way in my opinion like it was like they didn't have her come in to fall
back in love with Johnny or or you know disrupt everything she kind of comes in like this voice from
the past that that's there when Johnny and Daniel need to hear it most so they can get some sort of
leverage uh and perspective and then she's gone and i think it was perfectly done yeah i agree it's uh
and just bring some class and star power to the proceedings you know because this the next season will be
the first with netflix money behind it and i think the show is gonna take us a step up i would
imagine but um you know it's kind of got this real low budget kind of under the radar feel cobra
guy so to get a star like Elizabeth Shoe i know she's not as big as she was back in the day or something
but she really comes in and and and lifts it and i agree they used her perfectly um the uses of
the characters from karate kid 2 sort that was sort of a dead spot in the season for me but that's
just because i'm not familiar with two i saw it i've seen one a bunch two once when i was a kid
and three maybe half of that when i was a kid uh and then the swank one of course i watch but um
i think you know what what really appealed to me this time around on the show a it is a show about
zappka's character macho i like macho's care i like all i like the kids fine but to me i'm waiting for
the next time i can see zappka they've they've done him really well uh he's kind of a man out of time
a man kind of frozen in the eighties the the scene where he's trying to plan out how to respond to her
facebook message and then eventually just decides on not much you i was a big lol for me i thought
that was super funny um and it's believable that that that's what a guy who is like trying to kind
of date and stuck in the eighties and all that would would be like in zappka plays it really really well
uh the the karate sort of taking over the town aspect to me is just becoming funnier and funnier
like when i don't even i could ask i know they always found this to be funny but i don't think
the show plays like a comedy really at all um with you know some funny little moments of course but like
it's when all the kids were fighting at the end of season two that was a big change kind of in
the direction of the show it's a 20 -minute karate scene basically where they're just
getting together i didn't like that i loved it i was just like holy shit like i didn't expect this
they really went for it and then they do it again in three it ends with a big in -home battle a kid
gets thrown through a glass window you know at that point i was like shit man like i like i like
when it goes to those crazy heights um but for me i think it kind of needs to go a little deeper
at some at some point soon like i think it was circling all these areas maybe it's just the time it came
out but there's a really great sort of uh parallel to be had here between the the warring dojos being
democrats republicans and then this guy crease starting the alt -right essentially he's taking
obra kai too far into like okay your principles are are are fine and and and rooted in some sort of
history but you're going too far and now you're killing people maybe they intended that maybe they
didn't i can text him and ask but i i think that there's some really interesting stuff to explore there
because watching it the week where we have this coup that's what i was thinking about the whole time
well there's uh there's a lot of parallels you could draw it it mimics many or reflects rather many
of the themes of classic kung fu movies uh you know the masters in the warring dojos and all that
it's very very reminiscent of classic mythological stories there's heavy star wars type themes in
this you know you could see creases the emperor Johnny's Darth Vader the misunderstood villain uh
Daniel's Luke Skywalker who for the most part does everything right but it's kind of a goody goody
i love all that stuff i love the epic scope of it all uh and i love how well -defined and complicated
these characters are they they they come off like real people to me with real problems and real emotions
and and real reactions to things which is why i don't like it when it goes i don't
mind that they're having these brawls i mind the settings that they're having the brawls in
you can't have a 30 -kid karate brawl in a high school and there's no teachers around at all to sure
it's it's a little absurd so that for me if that's done intentionally to prove a point or to give a nod
to something that i'm unfamiliar with then i'm i'm definitely all years to it that's the only aspect
of it i don't like for the reason that the karate kid one is such a wonderful film because it's a rocky
story written by the same writer or no i'm sorry same director by the same director the same sorry the same
director stormy old adults and sorry it's very much that it's not a it's not just like
raki's on a movie about boxing karate kids on a movie about karate so movie about
relationships and and and childhood and and being lost and coming into your own and on all these things
coming of age rather um and then the second two become way too much about karate
uh particularly the third one which turns into like it's it's it's almost like it's like crazy
it's like almost like this miss it's almost like a missing in action or you know like a big a bad
stalone movie or something uh uh and this this show at the end of season two in my opinion started to
reflect the lesser aspects of the franchise now i think it's very cool that they're tying in
elements of two and three i like when they pull a universe together but i don't like that all of a
sudden these things that were very very criticized in the in the later installments of the film series
are now being really celebrated in the series itself because i felt like the first season of this
show rated all the missteps of the sequels of karate kid and i think for the most part seasons two
and three continue to do that like it's awesome when Daniel goes to japan and reconnects with the
nemesis whose life he spared and that guy teaches him the secret technique right that he later he
needs to use that stuff is all awesome because it's so human and it's so personal i don't need
a 30 -kid karate brawl in Daniel LaRusso's home where multiple kids are getting thrown through playclass
windows and it's just a little too much and if you're gonna do it guys just have them meet behind a
dingy supermarket have them meet behind that food for less in the food for less yeah i mean that's
all i'm saying like don't do it in a setting that's like come on guys like neighbors would hear this
this is crazy right i'm different from you and that because it is such a sort of small scale meat and
potatoes kind of show and very you know like at a time when every show looks like it was directed by
Paul Thomas Anderson you know you know a much lesser version but all these shows are just throwing
so much at you in camera tricks and and all and and this is a simple show so i like when it kind of
lets its flag fly a little bit and goes nuts and and it's the culmination of a season's worth of
tension i think also sure what i picked up watching this on the on season three is Heather my wife
is not watching she walked in and was like oh this is a show for kids yeah it's very much for
this you know what it is yeah yeah yeah so like i think the reason my guess is that the reason that
karate kid two and three lean more into karate is because kids were becoming obsessed with fucking
karate from the karate kid so now i think you're getting that again karate kids and families this is
a true show that kids and parents like equally which again it's it's so smart of my i'm proud of
my friends for pulling this off because they've got like one of the biggest shows on Netflix but it
respects yeah completely respects the the source material um to the extent that i'm like holy shit
they're they're carrying over arcs from the karate kid part two like i don't even remember who these
people are i should rewatch them i guess but they're clearly trying to make people happy in that
regard but i think also thinking back to being dark teen let's say i would be sitting just like
you're we're sitting in home alone rocking a new chair like give me those traps baby give me those
traps i think kids are like give me an on all -out karate brawl and they're getting they're giving them
exactly what they want all right that's a great point i dug it i like the show i like the kind of
aspect of it i think that it is um just super well done it's the kind of fan service
that i'd love to see more of and i think if they brought this kind of fan service to your big
franchises your wonder woman's your star wars whatever else people would be much much happier
well i think it's uh i also respect i also say too i love that it's a show that lets kids be kids yes
well they're cussing a lot more season three i noticed yeah but it's not and which is great
because that's what you do when you're that you you know you they're drinking beers and shit yeah
it's like they're doing kid shit and i like that it even gets into like the way kids in high school would
manipulate the current uh uh safe space language of you know like the boat like when hawk the bull one of
the bullies is like she she violated my safe space and i felt triggered like and and he's doing that
so he can get out of trouble like i'm like i love that i love that they're all doing things that
kids would a lot of kids would do i love that they're just kids being kids i love that it's not kids
getting into the heavy it's not kids talking politics which is what so many kids are portrayed as
doing these days and it's like they're it's letting young people be young people parents aren't having
conniption fits because they were their their kids got into a fist fight they're not happy about it
right they're angry about it they're upset about it but they're not bringing the police into it or
trying to get kids expelled or whatever there's an element of oh god these are the growing pains
uh when you're this age and whenever and i like that i think that's awesome uh i i really do
i really i really like the show for that reason and you know you you've you've changed my mind on the
something that somebody in that demographic would like to see so they get to see it um
it's a great show and and you're absolutely right in the sense that you can sit with this you can
sit and watch this with anybody and your family and for the most part it's fine um you know there's
you're not there there's not like suddenly like a bush and tits on screen or some guys balls or
something right um the violence is at times you know um drastic but you know again you're not seeing
eyeballs shoot out or or bones piercing through skin or anything um it's a great show
my hog is up congrats to kobra kai i'm thrilled to see Ralph macho and zabka back in the mix i really
am like and i hope that they now get to do obviously the kids on the show are going to go on to do all kinds
of stuff i'm sure but i hope that way i hope now we get to see like a little resurgence of macho and
zabkin and some movies you know i was all i always enjoyed to me williams bobka is the arguably the
greatest eighties movie bully of all time i would love to see him and more stuff and i always lit up
when i saw macho and anything and it had been like since fucking weekend at bernie's you know i mean
not i'm sorry not weekend at my cousin Vinnie uh you know it had been a while so i'm i'm just happy
to see him back and kai looks amazing zoder bergs they both look great soda bergs the kind of dude that
would throw zabkin to like a a leading role in a movie like he loves doing stuff like that um yeah
so i hope that happens too and and i again i mean i i anyone who watches the show and doesn't
re -fall in love with Elizabeth shoe i don't know what you're thinking i mean she's she looks like she
did she looks better than the leaving lost bagus days for christ's sake and also doesn't look like she
had the Nicole kibben shit done i don't know what's going on but she just congratulations she took
good care of herself or something i don't know what she did she right she floats into the show like
it like a breath of fresh air like you know everybody everybody is just like in love with her and you
completely see why she's great in the show um so yeah hogs up and uh that's all we got i'm i'm the
Patrick wall shit twitter and instagram each day i consider leaving both so someday you might wake up
and i'll be gone um and uh thank you for all the by the way i've seen a lot of them thank you so
much for the great response on the Oliver Stone episode it really broke my spirit on New Year's Eve
to have to record that hour plus thing twice uh it it it broke my spirit quite frankly but i think
it's something i'm going to do again and thank you thank you to those who sent me all the happy
birthday messages uh it's January 5th we spoke on the day but i didn't even know it was your birthday
i'm so sorry happy birthday buddy oh it was it was last week um but thank you for all those
messages right now it's fine job please um and that's it we uh well joe's got his plugs of course as
well but we'll be back with the very special Friday the 13th episode next yeah no segments on the
next one we'll just going to get right into the whole franchise uh uh uh yeah the joderos
a comedy on twitter and instagram i also could be gone at any second uh joderos a comedian on facebook
quick announcement i am no longer doing without a country uh Corinne Fisher will be carrying on the show
without me um i decided it was time to go uh and focus a little more on the podcasts like this and
taste buds with salvo kano on myself which you can catch on no -press network on youtube um i just
didn't want to talk about the news anymore and i know we got it got a little bit into the dark times
at the top of this episode but what can i say folks i i am i'm trying to use entertainment uh
and my professional involvement in it from here on out as a means of escape uh i have no desire any
i've been ranting and raving for 20 fucking years and i'm tired and i just don't want to do it anymore
i just want to talk about shit that i like to talk about uh you know uh you'll find and you'll
find other political podcasts there there there i know that there was jose and karenne's but i think
there's one other one too that you could probably download yeah so uh that's about it for me that's
it for me uh we'll talk to you next time folks see you now