folks it's another hot episode of we'll see you in hell here in the back half of july
our final two for this month oh boy do we got one for you we're talking opus
today opus the new a24 joint starring a .o edabiri and johnny malkovich and in
in an almost non -existent role juliet lewis i have no idea why she would sign on to this movie
because her part was non -existent but she's in it the whole time she just kind of runs
around in the background the uh usually yeah it's who the whole thing there's a lot to talk
about with opus but um we'll get there well we will get there but i'm i'm i'm gonna go a little
bit there now only out of necessity so we can start this thing on the right foot um and it's
going to be something that's never been done as far as i know on on this podcast but uh
you
as you know our 28 years later discussion folks uh was was like the old days it got very heated
both on and off camera uh sometimes a movie just stirs us up like that and brings us to a place
where pat and i are almost having to re -re -commit our vows to one another
afterwards yeah we're going to the madonna inn this weekend to hopefully fuck the pain away
uh but i barbs
i uh i sent pat a voice note yesterday uh after i watched opus and i will say all this to you now
folks we'll get to the review but after watching opus i retract everything i said about 28 years
later i i might not have liked the movie that much i might have found a derivative but jesus
christ it was a movie that was a movie that was a movie that was a movie that was a movie that was
a movie it was it was put together it was constructed well it was well acted it was
well directed it was well written yeah uh whether i liked it or not i'm realizing is secondary
you put that you butt that thing right up against this opus i was like i should be on my knees
thanking god for a movie like 28 years later the holy jesus i i'm taking i'm retracting my take
i now i'm saying uh my hog's up for 28 years later
literally based on the fact that i momentarily forgot where we had gone to in the world of
cinema how far we had fallen in the world of cinema and to see a man like danny boyle
still making something of quality that he clearly cares about is a beautiful thing because jesus
christ almighty joe i respect the hell out of it there's been nothing more difficult for me
in my life up till the last year and a half i've been doing this for a long time i've been doing this
for a year or so than admitting defeat admitting i was perhaps too hasty and judging something it's
not easy to do but yeah we're we're at a time where the bar um is buried they've buried the
bar so you know i hate to grade in a curve i hate it when something comes out you know there was a
lot of these during the pandemic bill and ted the third one is one i really remember where everyone's
like okay we can all agree this is an undisputed masterpiece and i'm saying i'm not going to
y 'all been locked in the house too long we haven't had a new movie in a year you've lost your mind
and i hate that that fake judging on the curve but we're coming to a point now where if we want
to talk honestly about the movies that are coming out you got to really do that i mean we're getting
largely season below c c's and below is what i'm trying to say well it's it's shocking um because
when you put the uh reins of the
carriage in the hands of uh a gq editor you'd think the gq editor who's never directed anything
or written anything you'd think that's the guy to put at the helm of a john malkovich a24
horror movie i as i always do you know when a movie is particularly striking visually like
the ugly stepsister 10 minutes in i'm i'm pausing it i'm on wikipedia finding out who the creative
team is you know did they make a show or did they make a show or did they make a show or did they
make a short that was that was considered cool and that got them there you know how'd they get
here um and i do that also when something's really bad because i wonder how did this person get
10 million dollars to make a movie this is this is uh ludicrous and in this case i looked and i
was just disgusted a guy with seemingly no background at all in film an editor of a
magazine this is one of the most this is clearly one of these cobbled together
this is what's so sad about cinema now uh or or one of the things that's so sad about cinema now
um these things a lot of the time are are cobbled together they're dinner parties
yes they're plucking people that they are friendly with that they think are interesting that should
all work together because it would be so fun it'd be so wouldn't it be so cute if we all work
together and it sucks it sucks the the by the way it would suck as a dinner party too you would not
have fun by the way yeah and also this is the upside down fucking world we're living in the
one lady in this um stephanie something i think her name's stephanie something actress yeah i i
looked her up she's got a million plus followers on instagram there and no wikipedia page there it
is who who exactly it's like what are we doing guys it's like
she's she's so not notable as a performer no no it's okay i'm not knocking that you don't have
a wikipedia page but my point is this it's like you'd think if you're gonna steer into the curve
of let's let's uh cast a film based only on notoriety and clicks that we can get out of our
cast members let's put that first you'd think you'd want somebody that steers into the curve
of notoriety where they have a wikipedia
page and the public knows who they are whatever they're not even doing that right anymore
they're just looking at followers this woman worked for the kardashians yeah wait which one
was she i don't remember she was the lady who type in this movie i mean spoiler alert we'll
get to it later but she's the lady who eventually gets like poisoned and her face all swells up
oh yeah yeah okay yeah we're talking about amber mid thunder is that who we're talking about no
like stephanie oh she i see yeah um not even in the main cast oh stephanie sugna suganami yeah okay
yeah so she but i mean they're not even stunt casting properly they're not even doing their
homework to stunt cast properly it's so crazy take the extra step of of trying to see if these
are real followers like that's what i'm saying yeah five hundred thousand followers for probably
i don't know how much it is but it ain't that much yeah you'd think somebody
on the staff somewhere would have been smart enough to go uh guys i know we want to put her in
because you know we think she's got this big following and she's an influencer and stuff but
i can't really find her on the internet outside of her instagram are we sure we want to do this
she worked behind the camera for kanye and kim and now she's acting what are we doing like there's
christ almighty let's put john madden in this role it'll get more eyes on it you know what i mean like
yeah yeah no that's nuts it's it's crazy but but this is like this is oh jesus that was my my
alarm to wake up but i've been up for hours i don't know why i even set an alarm i'm always awake
yeah the internal clock which is a a nice way to say uh pulsating anxiety yeah i hear you i did the
same thing i went to bed at 3 a .m and i was like i'm gonna sleep all all the way to 10 a .m because
we got to record at 11 and yeah it was like 10 a .m and i was like i'm gonna sleep all the way to 10 a .m
up at 8 15 yeah that's the only thing i haven't quite straightened out i mean i i will say this
sobriety has been absolutely fantastic for every problem i was having except my sleep has just
never quite gotten right i was waking up at 3 a .m every night and that i was hating because i can
never go back to sleep right now i just now it's a little better i'll do like an 11 to 6 but then
when i'm up at 6 i'm just like what am i doing what are you doing but
it's a good night anyway i do have a sty in my eye i look like paul dano uh after hugh jackman
gets done with him in prisoners um what what is a sty is it is it like pink eye did you did i
touch myself with a dirty hand what happened uh i've never understood what a sty is uh i've never
i don't know what causes them i think it's like a pimple i think it's like some form of pimple
on your eye on your eyelid under the skin does it hurt it hurts very badly yeah and then they the
only advice they have is to hold a hot washcloth on it for a half hour which intensified it if
anything i also have i you know i have not been white knuckling not drinking it's it's for the
first time ever i've had i have no desire anymore but i did get these drinks at the whole foods that
are like a they're called hyo
and they were delicious watermelon mint or whatever and they got the they kind of give
you a high feeling because there's those mushrooms in them now it's nowhere near being high or drunk
but that's a new market social cocktails for the the non -drinker or whatever so i was having one a
night and uh they have ashwagandha which i've mentioned and been mocked for on the show before
but they it mellows you out and gets you ready for bed and makes you feel kind of nice and relaxed
but i was noticing
my piss was on fire as the kings of leon once sang and i did not know what was going on i thought
did my girlfriend cheat on me what's happening here and then i google it hyo drinks honestly
expecting to find nothing hyo drinks urethra and boy lots of people have this issue yes it's it
strongly irritates your urethra i'm like can i have one of those drinks i'm like i don't have one of
one thing yeah you could have one thing you can have it but you turned your back on it baby
yeah no and yeah i'll tell you that tequila never made my pp burn it might have led to things that
made my pp burn but it never made my pp pure it's honest whiskey just pure pure uh i'm uh i'm i yeah
as always you know god knows what tomorrow will bring but um i'm enjoying my time
free for you
from it free from its icy grip i uh yeah i got the blood work done yesterday i'm
fucking terrified what that's gonna look like what have you been doing drinking a lot
i've just been i'm coming out of it a little bit um you know it was it was thank you by the way
there are some people that have reached out and said how's your family and all that stuff
things are the dust is settling with that
oh good
my mom
still has the health stuff going on but but but but it's evening out at least to a place where
there's not more happening what was happening for a while was more things kept happening
on top of the baseline issue we seem to be back to just dealing with the baseline issue i hope
so that's that's you know that's calmed down you know i'm through the breakup it's i've accepted it
it's over whatever um you know saw her last night
i was i was you know what are you gonna do just ran into her randomly yeah uh you know but it's
well that was that's how a couple of times i was threw my Monet allow me to just think
fine we're on good terms it's just you know so i'm getting distance from these things
that were really intense for a moment and i was there were other things happening too
i don't need to get into all the details but i was extraordinarily self -medicating
just drinking drinking way too much uh and uh and just eating whatever
yeah
so i'm getting distance from these things and i was really intense for a moment and
know i started gaining weight and you know i'm not exercising whatever so i'm coming out of it
and i'm starting to get back on track with diet and all this stuff and i'm gonna have to slow the
drinking down a bit too but it's awfully hard to not it's just so hard not to drink when you go
and do so like i'll go to the mothership and i'll do these shows and they're awesome
and then every night at 11 p .m they the bar closes to the public and it's just for the
comedians right it's it's really hard to just go i'm just gonna go home sit alone you can't
just celebrate with a half a can of high y 'all my dick's got your piss up for the next week of your
life so um it's it's super fun but i'm gonna have to just
slow down
down the fun a little bit uh which is a good problem to have but anyway i had to you know i
had to get i was due with i work with this clinician with my supplements and all this
stuff and i had to get my blood work done and i i called her and i was like look i'm not gonna lie
to you uh i've been on one uh my numbers might be a little off here she was like just go get it go
get an honest reading let's see where you're at so i'm just like they take your blood test and
it's like the thing
where they're like the the wires like spaz out of it i'll touch it i'll tell you one thing i
start i'm very i'm disappointed myself not only did i start smoking again a few months back or
probably six months back i'm i'm like full -on smoking again like i'm like yeah half a pack a
day you can hear it in my voice uh it's just like god that's that's the one thing i need you to just
cut that's so good you can't be mad at me you can't be mad at me you can't be mad at me you can't be
doing that shit i i don't know i don't think i ever told this on the pod but the last time i got
my blood work done i did it and then immediately had to go to atlanta uh for months and i'm in
atlanta and i get the results and lady breaks it down for me she's like everything's good you know
the every this this really improved this is great i was like oh all right awesome and then she goes
i do wonder though uh you know i know you wanted a full sti panel why didn't we get your urine
and i said well i urinated
in a cup and put it where the nurse told me to put it sealed with my name on it she's like huh
well let me look into that days later she's like so look i'm not happy about this but we can't find
it um can you just come in and do it again i said no i'm in atlanta now and now i'm worried about my
sexual health which was the whole reason i came to you you know i wasn't giving her that hard a
time but it's like how do you lose a cup of piss as a doctor
the system is the system is batshit it's it's you you go into i tried to write
i never did it but i tried to write a joke about this you go in you pee and then they just tell
you to leave it in a basket yeah exactly that's what this was they leave it to you though they're
like go pee in this and then down the hall is a basket on a little table yeah put it there like
shouldn't somebody be taking this from me whatever the lady when i did it last time she goes i go how
she goes i need you to pee in this i go okay well how much and she goes i don't know maybe that much
i'm like it's not a cooking show tell me give me a pinch of your yeah draw a line on the cup and say
go to that line like what do you gotta do it like salt bay where you put your hand in the stream and
then like splash it on her yeah i yelled bam when i dropped the cup off yeah um i do have a quick
scary stuff just because i'll forget it
if i don't say it i saw this this is the last thing i saw last night before i went to bed and
i was like that's a cool story that i'd like to share it's very brief but uh joe dante and i never
know if it's dante or dante and i've said it both ways uh he just sold i didn't even know he had
this but he had the original citizen kane rosebud sled that he had bought at auction
and apparently he puts it in his movies as like an easter egg it's in a lot of his movies he
uses it and he's had it for you know the entirety of his career he sold it last week for just shy of
15 million dollars jesus christ which i can almost guarantee is more money than he had in the bank
from his film career his 40 -year film career it's really kind of amazing um and mazel tov you know
i would have sold it long before then he's got to be 80 85 years old like just i would have been
second i heard a two million dollar offer
yeah here's the sled enjoy isn't it surprising that um it's kind of surprising that there's any
that there's somebody alive who would still be willing to pay that much money for a movie
artifact that old you'd think at this point anybody that would have paid that would be dead
yeah well i guess that it's it's because it's still considered the best i mean it's probably
just some film nerd but yeah 15 mil for an old chunk of wood i mean
you got wood deteriorates also i don't know how they how they kept it pristine but it looked nice
did i uh well did i well we got it we got a new psycho too that we should i don't know why we
haven't done this yet i can't believe we haven't done this yet the the teaser trailer for the new
space balls came out oh really any footage from the film or no no no i just mean the one the one
you and i watched and we were texting oh okay yeah yeah
about it but uh the casting uh hey well gad is apparently taking over i guess he's going to be
the son of is it ralph barf barf sorry yeah he's of course by the way i'm sorry to interrupt did
you think when john candy was eating that it was when i was a kid it made me so sick did you think
he was eating barf in the movie i don't know i don't know i don't know i don't know i don't know
dog food never even occurred to me i'm like he's he's named barf that the the cauldron he's eating
out of if memory serves has the word barf written on it and as a kid the thought of someone eating
barf made me nearly throw up and it's part of the reason i never got into space balls i don't know
why they called him barf that was always confusing me but no it's his dog dish so it says barf like
a dog and it's wet it's wet dog food and he's dipping the biscuits in it believe it or not i
look kind of appetizing but but um you know gad and in in the least startling move of all time
has cast himself in the most self -aggrandizing role in the film of course stepping into the
shoes of john candy um i thought he was going to be the son of dark helmet which which would
have also been just as ego driven but uh but bill pullman and daphne zuniga are
coming back so is mel brooks um i think that's it from the original cast because everybody else
has passed but then they've got and i'm sorry this just seems weirdly racist to me that they
have kiki palmer taking over the joan rivers part because the whole point of the joan rivers robot
was like attitude and whatever and it's like the only
moment in this movie you're making her do the part that let's we but we all know it's going to
be her being like uh -uh honey you know what i mean like it's like guys what are you doing and if they
don't do that my hat's off to them but it's like yeah we'll we'll see what it looks like when it
when the time comes i don't know what she's doing in this movie i can't imagine kiki palmer loves
baseballs i i wish i was her manager because i i really do love her and i just don't feel like
she's being used right at all
i only saw her in uh nope but i won't hold that against her yeah no i mean for me it's just her
own her own personality her own talk show when i see her interviewed when i see her talk to i i
love her vibe and everything about her but the project she chooses are not on point i hope we
haven't discussed that natasha leone is playing joan rivers in a upcoming biopic which is actually
kind of interesting casting i would say that is interesting casting and i would like to see that
and natasha leone would i i i say this in defense of kiki palmer and i hope that they don't do this
to her but it can i found that casting a little strange i was like this seems this seems like an
old hollywood uh racial hiccup uh but we'll see hopefully they don't go that route with it um
the uh the movie looks well there's nothing to see yet who knows but there's i mean jesus christ
a cast and crew of writers uh the likes of hollywood has never seen couldn't make the
history of the world sequel viable now now they also didn't need to do 10 it should have been a
fucking movie and it would have been great the four funny sketches would have been great yeah
i'm uh i think space balls will have to be better than that almost but uh have i'd have we discussed
the upcoming larry david barack obama's
sketch show mocking american history larry you you did the best sitcom in american history for my
for my money i agree then you leave you create something equally wonderful innovative hilarious
occasionally it shows its age but for the most part we had a decade and a half of just pure
magic maybe two decades at this point
it is time to fucking retire these people why do you not care about your legacy presidents care
about their legacy don't don't you're not going to hit it again this isn't going to work it's
fascinating to me that that larry david doesn't see that it's a lose -lose for him and it's a no
loss for obama nobody cares if obama bombs in the sketch comedy world obama doesn't care what's he
give a shit it's pure fun for obama
yeah larry david is great obama isn't as funny as i thought he was how funny did you really think he
was you know um it looks like a bad idea yeah we'll see but but speaking of bad ideas and there's
a little more on this mel a little more in this mel brooks stone a little more blood to squeeze
out of this one they've also announced jesus fucking christ on his goddamn christ aj
jay jesus fucking christ and his god you know what pat if this keeps going with this shit they
were i'm gonna start saying you're gonna see me turn on the sopranos i'm gonna turn my whole thing
over now you know nothing would make me happier than that joe by the way uh and i'll get to what
i was gonna bring up uh shout outs to not today pal the podcast starring uh starring the two kids
from the sopranos uh who are delightful i i gotta listen to your episode because i i love
watching them enjoy each other they never really enjoyed each other on the show maybe that's part
of it but i just i love them they seem really funny and grounded and down to earth they're
really great uh robert and jamie lynn uh they're they're she's one of the sweetest human beings i've
ever met and robert is one of the nicest guys i've ever met like they're they're really wonderful
people but
i'm shouting them out right now because when big jay was on they talked about the sopranos
yeah jay was like yeah man who doesn't like that show and they were like i will tell you who
fucking joe to russ and i was like oh i've arrived like this is i've made it asked actually
is referencing me yeah well i re i re re re re re re re re re re re re re re re re re re re
re yeah
of course as pesci's kind of sidekick and for the first time ever in my life instead of watching
sopranos and going oh there's christopher there's because they used a whole bunch of
the cast from goodfellas um but i said oh oh right frank vincent from the sopranos
I started going the other way because at this point I've probably seen Sopranos more.
But Vincent's best role is on The Sopranos.
Because I forgot what a almost assistant he is in that movie.
He's the boss.
He's such a powerful force in The Sopranos that seeing him as like Pesci's lackey was really jarring to me.
I'm like, wait, Frank Vincent, you don't have to take that.
Why aren't you beating the shit out of this guy?
Me and a few of my friends text back and forth.
I don't know if they're GIFs or GIFs, whatever they're called.
But the posts on Instagram where it'll be like a clip from a movie and then somebody writes a caption on it.
When you say you're only going to have one drink and you have 10.
There was a casino one yesterday that, Jesus Christ, it took me apart at the seams.
The caption was, after you go on a two -day bender with your boy.
And it's just the clip of Pesci going, what the fuck happened to you?
What the fuck?
And then De Niro's going, what the fuck happened to you?
You lost control.
You're out of control.
And then Pesci goes, I'm out of control.
Look at you.
You're in a bathrobe with a fucking cigarette holder.
Fucking John Barrymore with a cigarette holder.
Yeah, that is.
And then under the idea that they've been on a two -day bender.
It's so funny, man.
That is one of the more realistic male fights in movie history.
You know, Cassavetes nailed it, of course.
But Scorsese gets, I think he just lets him improv is obviously how you get there.
But man, it feels real.
And oh, really?
I did this.
You did that.
Like it's, I mean, we just had one of those jokes.
Yeah, it does.
It felt very, very real to me.
And Sharon Stone in that fucking movie is so amazing.
But this is the first time.
And this this shows you now.
Now, I am a divorced man and I had a difficult divorce.
And I thought I was going to watch this hating Sharon Stone even more.
But I'll tell you what.
She tells De Niro from the very first minute that she does not love him.
Yeah.
He brings all of that pain on himself because he wants to fuck her.
I mean, that's basically it.
And he's so controlled.
I mean, that movie is the best.
Dramatization of how a woman can can take everything from me.
I'm not talking about myself.
I'm talking about that movie.
It's like he just followed his dick a hundred percent of the time.
You know, she she again and again and again and again fucks him over and he takes her back.
She ties her daughter up.
She ties his daughter up and they do that.
Then Pesci can't can't resist.
Now he's hooked on her.
He's down.
I really fucked up with this broad man.
I never should have started with this broad.
There's a there's a my dad is at a point now where he's like, I will never let a woman
enter my life again.
Not that my dad was beating them off.
He had, you know, two wives.
But it is true.
It's like there's a reason people are scared of love.
It throws off everything else, you know, because your hormones are out of whack.
Your emotions are out of whack.
You're not thinking clearly.
And Casino, that's how I viewed it this time.
It's almost I almost saw it as a story about a man and a woman as opposed to the birth
of Las Vegas.
No, it's very much.
It's very much a strangely a small movie about relationships.
And De Niro, the more you watch it, the more you realize it's it's the driving the engine
in that movie is De Niro's character, Ace, Ace Rothstein.
His is that it's his hubris.
Yeah, it's his it's he's a control freak.
It's it's it's why he's such a vital tool.
Both for the mob at the beginning and why he's able to, you know, the whole thing at
the top when Pesci's like he'd find out what would they used in the baseboards for the
basketball game.
So he knew how the balls would bounce, like like he's talking about how he knows how to
call the bets and all this stuff to win the to win in the gambling stuff with the gambling
stuff.
And he continues to and then he says it to Alan King when Alan King wants him to run
the casino.
He's like, if I do it, I got to do it my way.
And there's the great blueberry muffin scene.
I want it.
There's an equal amount of blueberries and the guy is trying to orchestrate every part
of his life.
So it is fully organized and controlled down to his wife.
And then the wife ends up being the thing because you can't that's it's so interesting.
The one thing he can't control is another human being.
Yeah.
And then you can't.
Because he has no emotion.
Yeah.
And then that is the undoing of everything.
Imagine now, especially in this world where.
By the way, from all I'm hearing, I thought it was just Netflix, but apparently AI notes
are the norm across all networks and streamers.
You're getting they insist that you feed scripts into AI to give notes, in which case, why
do we have executives?
But if we're wondering why movies are seeming more samey, it's because we're literally trying
to recreate the movies of the past.
We're giving them notes that match because that's all AI has been fed scripts and that's
all it knows.
So it goes, it should be more like this thing, which is going to eventually destroy all of
the originality.
But well, how do you think in this day and age where AI is given notes that that blueberry
muffin scene remains in a three hour film?
No, no.
So many of the details in that movie, so much of the repetition of that movie and he, you
know, he's got the Devo pumping in the background to increase your paranoia and everything.
But there are moments where you're like, we've seen this scene before, kind of, but the repetition
is what.
Makes you paranoid.
And, and puts you in the mindset of this guy.
Like all his tactics would just be, uh, shunned now you would allow all those people, all
those little things get cut.
There's that scene in the Irishman.
This is another thing that would get pulled where they're talking about the fish when
they're on, literally on the way to kill Hoffa.
Yes.
And they have that favorite scene of the Irishman insane conversation with the fish.
So if you read about it, he literally did pick up a fish that day.
That was amazing.
That's a real thing that happened.
And then Scorsese turns it into this moment in the movie where you're like, even though
they're on the way to a hit, they're still going to have small talk.
Like this is how this works.
Yeah.
And it's so crazy, but so telling of how casual the murder is, uh, because they're talking
about fish, fish, and then he gets killed and that gets cut.
You know, AI is like, well, what does this have to do with anything?
Casino is apparently like 99 % true.
Like, like crazy things.
You think had to have been invented is almost totally true.
I urge you if you're on letterbox, he doesn't, he never posts there anymore, but, uh, Stavros
Halkias has a hilarious, very long review of casino.
He got thrown off for the content of one of his reviews.
So when he comes back, he's like, well, I certainly wouldn't say that this is something
I, the whole reviews from that point of view, like, I don't want to get kicked off again.
So I wouldn't tell you that I love the violence and the, you know, it's very, very funny.
I urge you to check her out.
Um, oh wait.
See, no.
Oh shit.
Sorry.
Good.
No, just the other scene that I talked about with, with McCarthy the other day is when
he was Pesci hits Rickles with the phone and he falls face down on the floor and you're
like, oh geez.
Cause it's Rickles and it's an old man.
But I think that test audiences must have thought Rickles was dead because Scorsese
includes this scene that always makes me laugh where Rickles flips over with his tongue hanging
out.
Yeah.
Like those kids are like birds of different birds.
And it clearly Scorsese was like, just act dead.
We won't use it.
And he did, but they all laughed and then they wound up having to use it to prove that
he didn't die.
That it looks so bad.
It's terrible.
They're there.
Say, I think does stuff like that to fuck with us.
I don't even, you know, that's what Matt said.
I was talking about how the 4k really makes it obvious that the, the mannequin that they
replaced the Nero with right before the car blows up and, and Matt thinks that Scorsese
does that to be like, we're making a movie here.
and i'm like i don't think so i don't know you know the big the big one is obviously that it's
the one everybody talks about is the irishman de niro kicking the guy on the sidewalk scene
yeah and i'm like scorsese knows enough obviously about movies to look at that and say this looks
awkward yeah there's something there's a reason for it i don't know what it is i don't know if
it's him saying it's yeah we're letting everybody know that clearly we're using the de -aging thing
this is a wink to camera i don't know but um well there's good felt you know paul sorvino has that
scene where he's like it's like putting a silk hat in a pig with that guy you know and hit the
cigar appears and disappears from his hand like 10 times and it's very distracting and very annoying
and they've asked him and and thelma schoonmaker his longtime editor about those kind of mistakes
and they're like you're 99 .999 percent of people will never
ever noticed that and if we're doing our job you're not going to notice a cigar comes and goes
we're all about the feeling it gives we'll we'll do a hundred edits and have a cup
appear and disappear 10 times it doesn't matter but to you know as a guy who's watched these
movies a bunch of times it does become annoying and a distraction because you're like this is
perfect why did you let that slide i yeah interesting when i did when i did louis he he
was like he he was like we were we would be shooting and like like in between takes the
background and he was nice about it but people be like guys that was over there whatever and he'd be
like guys guys guys it's okay thank you let's just go let's just nobody's gonna care about any of
that like let's just keep moving and i was like oh this is really nice and you get done in four
hours right instead of you know 16 hours to shoot three pages because every five minutes i get like
i get fucking aggravated not not to anybody like i don't out i don't put it outward
in very internal i hide it well yeah or at least i think i do but i get aggravated man when i'm
and it's just people just doing their job they're doing their job so they don't get any shit it's
i'm not discrediting that or discouraging that but you know you're about to go and like the
person's running up to you and touching your hair and and you know what i'm like
nobody is going to notice like like it it's it's distracting you know like yeah and again it's
people doing their job god bless them i'm not knocking them but it's it's i wish more directors
had the attitude of guys from the jump we're not going to worry about these little things
so let's keep moving all right well that what you're describing exactly pretty much described
how my good friend fred savage got the boot from hollywood it was like he's preparing for a scene
and he's trying to get his lines down and someone comes up and starts brushing dandruff off his jacket
which is already kind of embarrassing in addition to everything else and he like
puts his hand up and winds up kind of their their arms smack each other you know and there's a sound
and everyone gasps and it's like that that was all it took uh which is not great but um and and
there may have been other things he's a friend and i shouldn't speak on it i guess but it's
it's these things happen i mean i i've had to say to actors like hey you know you're you're
right arm needs to be here instead of here and you can just see on their face they're like you
know everything all this pressure i'm fucking under and remembering these lines and it does
suck the continuity aspect of it gets real old real fast by the way also too the pressure on
the actor because most people would probably think oh the fucking ego -driven arrogant egotistical
whatever actor the pressure on the actor is i don't know how many takes i get to do of this
and if i don't fucking land the plane i'm gonna look bad
and then i don't work i have to do my job you know what i mean and it's hard over and over and
over again to to make this line funny or to make this be funny or to to to it's it's you know
whatever so so that's that's a little thing in in in defense of the actor as well but um
but anyway real quick uh we really digressed but that's fine we did uh
uh
and that's the other thing one more casino thing do you ever see the outtakes with uh
rickles oh yeah did i talk about this already on here that probably would have been the funniest
set of all time as my guess it's so great when he's just sitting there you with all your breathing
and bullshit learn the goddamn line so we can get out of here have you seen him uh at the whatever
afi event about robert de niro where he gives the talk yeah it's amazing yeah um the other thing i
was going to say is i was going to say i was going to say i was going to say i was going to say
the mel brooks thing and folks i didn't even read the story on this the headline disgusted me so
much but they're making a tv series called very young frankenstein
now is this a pre i guess it's a prequel
it has to be yeah or is it a no it's a sequel it i did read a little bit it's a sequel to the movie
and now it's some new kid who is going to try to replicate or emulate the the work of his
father or grandfather who is the gene wilder character in the okay
not only is everybody that was in young frankenstein literally dead
everybody hackman was the last one i think um doesn't matter they they all could be dead
you you people you don't have gene wilder yeah that's it it's that simple you don't have gene
wilder this is literally nor do we have anyone who who has anywhere close to that vibe or energy
anymore you know that people say jeremy allen white kind of looks like him and sure but can
you imagine him acting in anything comedic now granted he's nominated for best comedic actor
every year for the bear everyone's favorite comedy starring opus is aoe to barry but you don't
but here's the thing wilder is more than just the the tornado force carrying every scene in the
movie he's the writer yes and the creator with now with mel brooks i know but you guys you it's
literally like saying i want to make tomato sauce and i don't have garlic or salt yeah well you
it's not gonna work it's you could make something that looks like it yeah but it's not gonna have
any flavor you you it's crazy man it is crazy like i don't understand i just don't get it and
is there even an audience for this is there a young gen z audience clamoring for for a young
frankenstein sequel well it's ffx so my guess is they're trying to get some of that what we do in
the shadows heat the like you know all right horror mixed with like you know like you know
with with comedy who knows you know but like mel brooks is 15 years older than larry david like
well what he's not going to be writing sharp comedy at this point i mean he's just not he's
still you know on and funny but it's like give me a break even rickles wasn't hitting a thousand by
the end there anyway anyway uh do we do a movie corner or do we just get straight to opus i mean
we're deep into this thing uh we can we can we can go to
why don't we do one each okay and then and then go right to opus i agree um casino kind of counts
as a long movie corn can you go first so i can pour a coffee for sure i would like to recommend
especially at this uh time in the world history a small non -war related movie
uh about iran that
is an amazing movie i would say a masterpiece it's one of the great foreign films and it's
called a separation came out in 2011 stress directed by excuse me if i'm incorrectly
pronunciating oscar farhadi and he's made many really good and interesting movies but this is
his best in my opinion and it is just a it's got almost an uncut gems of iran feel it's just one
of those where every little decision is made and it's just a it's just a it's just a it's just a
it's just a it's just a it's just a it's just a it's just a it's just a it's just a it's just a
it keeps causing bigger and bigger problems and it's a married couple they're divorcing
but they still love each other they're trying to figure out should they stay in iran or not
there's a parent with alzheimer's so that complicates matters and to i don't want to
spoil any of it quite frankly it's it's a thriller but it's entire it's very very small
you know it's it's a movie
um that's just beautifully beautifully written and put together and i really don't want to go
too much into it if you have any interest you know we tend to i i say we but i think people
tend to look at iran the middle east as kind of just this almost as if they're not people
you know especially when you all you just watch is these news reports and you just don't think of
like them as having human lives just because we always were
portrayed they were always portrayed in movies as terrorists and only and that's the only way we
saw them the certainly the only way i saw them in missouri because no one that looked like that
lived near me so um a movie like this i think does a great service by just showing you what
real human life and marriage and family is like in a place like iran and so often my feeling is
i don't want to watch that tonight that doesn't sound like fun this movie is is fun it's a great
thriller uh with great characters it's brilliantly acted i believe it won best foreign language film
and deservedly so and uh this was my second time watching it i just think it's fantastic a
separation joe uh this is this is something uh different than usual for the for the corner but
i think it still counts uh i'm gonna just talk about two youtube channels that i've really been
enjoying um i watch a lot of youtube
and i was like i'm gonna have to start talking about this in my movie corner because i watch a
lot of it in place of television or or movies but um there's two channels that i just really enjoy
the first is another uh fellow sort of movie uh channel uh called the cobwebs channel and real
simple it's it's one guy i'm i don't know his name i should look that up um but he does mostly
lists
of horror movies so it'll be like 10 movies on 10 amazing horror movies on tubi right now
yeah or or horror movies based on fairy tales or you know uh here's a bunch of horror movies
that will leave you disturbed and ruin your night um and he's a really passionate very very well
you know schooled guy in in the in the cinema department particularly with horror
and i love the channel i learn about movies i didn't know about he he will review things and
shed new perspectives on horror movies i'm already a fan of or sometimes convince me something i
liked wasn't as good as i thought or or something i thought sucked was a little bit better he's just
got a good take on everything and he's you know introduced the channel has introduced me to a lot
of different things uh that that i've found to be great so shout outs
to the cobwebs channel go check out that if you if you if you like and then the other one is
skywalker stories this whoever this guy is and he's using ai which i know we bitch a lot about
ai but he's creating star wars scenarios with full ai that that look real and they're like
it's like mark hamill young luke and it's like all these scenarios post return of the jedi or
in between the one of the coolest ones was it was like darth vader qui -gon who was liam neeson's
character in phantom menace qui -gon appears to vader after vader fights luke on bespin so it's
like it's like vader coming back from cloud city and empire strikes back after he just chopped his
son's hand off and told him he was his father and he goes into his meditation chamber and then
qui -gon's ghost appears to him these things are so awesome the scenarios are so amazing
it's so cool it's everything you wish they were actually doing with star wars right now
yeah uh it looks incredible you're like if i didn't know i would think liam neeson shot this
right now it's insane if it gets big enough they will definitely hire him because they seem
rudderless over there yeah uh and and it's they're incredibly written the dialogue is
awesome like it's it's a really cool channel and look ai is going to be ai it's here
it's it's it and it and it can be used as a tool just like the cell phone or the whatever
uh or you can use it incorrectly and i'm happy to see somebody using it for something that you
literally could not create in any other way there is no other way to create a scene that took place
during return of the return of the jedi era of star wars with a young mark hamill you can't do it
yeah so i'm like this is this is actually a
cool use to me of ai uh you know we could have a different discussion about likeness rights and
all that stuff that's a different story but um you know i you know i'm at that point with content
where i'm like okay if you're gonna use ai at least make it good use ai to be like hey here's
a whole new indiana jones movie and harrison ford's in it and he's 25 awesome is it good i'll
watch it so um anyway
they are now talking a lot about rebooting the indiana jones franchise
you think there's a chance that part of the idea of the reboot is is what i just said i mean we're
not far away from that we're not far away from fully led uh you know cast being fully led by
a completely fake human being we're not uh i don't i can't imagine people would go see that
but i've been wrong before um they're they're talking about chris
evans glenn powell and believe it or not folks pedro pascal is in the mix
i don't know if you're aware of him or if you've seen him in anything yet but um he's up and coming
yeah uh runner -ups include bobby cannavale and keegan michael key keegan's cooled off i got to
acknowledge keegan's cooled off a little bit yeah i should stop making fun of him i i run into him
sometimes i mean really i don't know i don't know i don't know i don't know i don't know i don't know
all we're saying is you work a lot it's not that insulting it's actually the opposite of insulting
we're just jealous yeah and it's also i think the guy's hilarious and it's like i wish he'd parcel
it out a little bit more you know or a little more sparingly rather but if you've never seen
wanderlust which was a a david wayne uh movie with paul rudd jennifer aniston a it's super
funny you've probably seen the scene of paul rudd talking about i'm gonna get that dick in the mirror
there's also an alternate cut of the movie a full 90 minute alternate cut like they did with
anchorman and they let keegan go on some improv runs in that that had my jaw on the floor like
we've we've not seen his full potential really he's he's very very gifted at improv and very
funny the um i uh uh yes i agree um okay here we are uh opus
824 which i texted paul
yesterday has now in my opinion become blumhouse in their own unique way mass layoffs happening at
blumhouse i would imagine 824 is next uh this movie is proof this is this is garage band
filmmaking i'm speaking of the app uh on your on your computer i thought you meant it was punk rock
like superman uh this is this is
this is garage band filmmaking when garage band came out people said well now anybody can make
music there's just loops and whatever and it's like yeah that's that's true but only people that
know how to utilize the tool will make good music with it and everybody else will make stuff that
seems on the surface like actual music but then it sucks this is exactly that you know the the
the title shot when the when the word opus finally comes on screen and and the way that
title card is designed and the way that the music plays at that moment and the way that
the camera pans down to begin the movie from that title card was a nice little sequence but i was
sitting there going jesus christ is every fucking movie now like anybody can do this you could you
could make that title card in 10 seconds on your computer everything is just being plucked from
other things at this point um which i get that's that's it's part of the whole whatever
but this is so clearly a movie for more reasons than that that was directed by a person who has
never directed anything had no from what i can tell business directing anything and a studio
said don't worry about it there's a crew and there's a then they'll be there to help and
that's how this is done now yeah mark anthony green he was an editor at gq uh the movie
costs 10 million dollars
for a newcomer who's never done anything in the world of film and the movie grossed two million
dollars so a loss of eight um and it's it's really bad i mean i think it's probably the low
point for a24 it's beneath even like something as awful as death of a unicorn and when you watch
the trailer for this thing it's that oh it's that well you know you should really meet this guy he's
very eccentric
that little sound you know well and then they're driving out to it the mic cut out what was the
sound you just made is it going through no no it's weird yeah i mean it's very high only dogs
can hear it but i'm doing the exact sound they make in the trailer which is just a one quick
swipe on a violin you know oh yeah the thing that that everybody has stolen from the original
trailer of texas chainsaw massacre in texas chainsaw massacre it was the pit it was the
sound of the camera that you mean the remake right
they did it in the actual original trailer and then the remake okay because i remember the first
time seeing it in my movie going life was in the the remake trailer that that's because they did
it in the original trailer but yeah it's the sound of the camera going off in that high -pitched noise
after and then that that eventually became the violin scrapes yeah yeah um the trailer is just
that like oh so wait a minute this is starting to seem like it might be a cult you know that
pull on the violin strings it's like guys we're getting
10 of these a year now and then hulu does 10 tv versions of this story every year now yeah
this this these rich people are actually fucked up uh this this group of people who seem like
they're happy and living in harmony are actually fucked up they're a cult it has no power to
surprise us anymore and if you're gonna do it find a way to surprise us yes this is our yearly remake
of get out yeah it's so similar to the
the kravitz thing that we reviewed on here which i keep wanting to say you're next that's not even
the name of it blink twice think twice and blink twice we did not we did not get a good review from
us but jesus christ blink twice is it was better stunning compared to this movie this movie is
fucking terrible it is terribly directed it is terribly scripted it is terribly acted
malkovich quick quick pause there that was my big surprise is how
acted it was particularly by the leads they're in io is embarrassing in this and malkovich is
embarrassing that we're supposed to buy him as a former sex symbol rock star
clearly he wasn't the first choice he's awful in this movie he like sort of i was going to say he
kind of clumsily lands the plane because he's so weird it's kind of like if you toss if you
toss jeff goldblum into something he'll clumsily landed at worst you know like it's jeff gold it's
the same with nick cage this would have worked better with goldblum or cage 100 percent um
i like that malkovich worked better i like that malkovich actually sang the songs i thought that
was kind of cool or at least it sounded like it was him again you could that might have been ai
you could say ai make john malkovich sing this pop song and i don't know if he did or not um
yeah the story is uh uh a an aspiring uh music journalist who they establish right off the bat
is basically a spoiled fucking brat they established that immediately um and continues
to act like a spoiled brat throughout the movie to the point that even when she's right about
something being amiss in this whole scenario you don't care or you don't you don't want to side
uh she's surrounded by a bunch of other characters that are equally as spoiled and selfish and vain
and boring uh and they somehow manage to do zero commentary with any of that whatsoever nothing
no commentary nothing whatsoever there's no even differentiation between these awful people it's
just like they're all kind of bad but not in any sort of real believable good way um anyway this
this music this is a
this musician who i would describe as a mix between bowie and prince uh comes out of uh
uh anonymity after 30 years uh to to release a new album and it's this it's the biggest thing
in music history uh this is another thing that kills me about the movie in order to translate
to you how big he is as a performer the beginning of the movie shows a bunch of people headbanging
in slow motion to one of the music that's going to be played in the next movie and it's going to be
one of his songs the song is a jimmy hendrix style somber guitar solo number one and the and the
footages of people really like you know what i mean it's not people kind of high and and swaying
they're throwing their bodies back and forth it makes no that makes no sense uh then it's every
and you're you're like guys i i get it like let's let's be inclusive of everyone if we can be but
like you know in the movie i mean but like guys like this is the wrong song to play if you want
us to believe that everybody on earth feels this way no matter what walk of life they're they're
from right yeah it's just it's just an odd choice it doesn't make any sense and then when
you get into the actual movie and they actually start to show you who this guy is he's a pop
singer yeah and you're like well why the hell didn't you play now if you established at the
beginning of the movie that during this credit sequence where you wanted us all to believe that
every person again alive from every walk of life and every age group is into this then play
something like thriller or beat it or michael jackson -esque that you can believe that you can
literally swept a globe britney spears that that kind of thing yeah yeah yeah the people like
mosh pitting to it it's like they don't even know what their own music is like you're you're trying
to create a character and a persona and we have to believe he's the biggest star ever but we never
even get a grasp on what kind of music it is we hear some of it it's not good it's not catchy
they have uh 60 50 year old white men talk about how great they are and they're like oh my god
he was bill burr wolf blitzer you know it's like these are the people telling you how much they
love his work it's just very confused you know everything about it is confused and i didn't
understand it yeah um anyway when the cult stuff starts happening you know there's there's violence
in it the only thing that seemed sort of interesting was when they you know that that
girl's mouth is expanding and i had just watched the ugly stepsister and i was like
this is like a gross out thing but with no personality with no charm yeah no anything
so what happens is this is a key plot point they they they he's going to release a new album and
by invite only people from the music and journalism industry will be invited to his home
where he has been a recluse for 30 years to hear the new album and our lead character
for well they explained at the end why she was invited
but whatever uh is invited along with her boss they go and then again it's just get out they go
to this place it seems serene it seems beautiful it seems lovely everybody's rich everybody's happy
and uh and but there's evil behind their eyes or whatever turns out john malkovich is a cult leader
uh which they hint at initially through the explanation of this religion he practices
that's sort of like scientology called levelism uh -huh um and then slowly but
early people start to die now here's the thing the first guy that dies
well actually jesus christ it's not even that one guy dies first the guy's hit with the arrow
no he lives that's the boss that's just there's just no point in that yeah that's just literally
there so so before that the the guy getting the massage is murdered oh right right yeah
and they set up prior to that that this guy and and malkovich's character had a beef
so you go okay this is a pretty pedestrian idea but i get what's going on here malkovich's
character is going to exact revenge on all these people that slighted him over the years
one way or another through their music journalism and i assume these murders will replicate
how they slighted him in some way you know yeah and i'm rolling my eyes at that people it's not
that no it's not even that it's literally just he has a cult and the cult is going to commit mass
suicide and for no reason whatsoever he kills a couple people on the way to getting to that point
in the film it's they they give a very flimsy explanation that it's because he suspects that
those people will disrupt and not appreciate what he's doing and he's going to commit mass suicide
and that's what it is they're about to do yeah it's not believable it's not it does not drive
what is going on home well you know theater of blood the vincent price movie that this rips off
is a really fun like black comedy horror theater of blood where it's a theater actor who's killing
off his critics and clearly that was an inspiration here but it's got the psycho ending you know
but it doesn't matter with psycho psycho is like this this flawless
perfect early horror movie and then there's one 30 second scene at the end that explains it but
ultimately you don't care you've been on the ride you're just like this has been a blast whatever
this movie has that too where they try to explain everything in the final minute in an embarrassingly
written and performed scene between malkovich and io and it's like this doesn't help me at all it
it doesn't it doesn't make me enjoy anything i've seen
anymore it doesn't it explains it but not in any sort of real satisfying way um it just leaves you
feeling worse you know you're like well at least at the end i'll find out what's going on here and
then you find out and you're like what really it's just a bummer it just sucks man yeah and
then the the big ending is that malkovich invited her because he read something she wrote when she
was in college and he knew that she was the person to write because it ends with her writing a book
about her experience with the cold quick interject though and i wish they i wish he had just said i
read a piece that you wrote in college and i thought it was so masterful whatever he says
the way you described that that artist's chin and i knew that you that that you would that's
how you would describe me like respectfully because of the way you described his chin or
whatever she's a she's a she's a she's a she's a she's a she's a she's a she's a she's a she's a
he read her college paper give me a fucking break man i guess that's supposed to be he's so vain
that it's just fucking dumb it's a dumb piece of shit movie it fucking sucks it's it seems like
really no thought was put into it it's like he had the 10 million and was like i'll write it on
the day sort of vibe no i see i i disagree with that i think this is i think this is
filmmaking at its at its worst i think this is a guy that thought he wrote something really
brilliant didn't know what the fuck he was doing and because he was probably again i believe
surrounded by enablers and friends he got to make his movie this is there's no other way the editor
an editor not the editor there's no other way an editor at gq gets to make a movie like that
there's there's no way it's true it's it's got to be it's it's it's it's
official nepotism it's people around him with money and and ability saying we will just allow
you to do this because you're our friend yeah i mean and everybody in it you know tony hale
has a cameo it feels like a movie where everybody he you know he just called anyone he knows who's
famous uh lenny kravitz appears for five seconds you know rosario dawson is the voice of the billy
holiday puppet in one of the stupidest scenes i've ever seen where they do a disturbing puppet show
and by the way remember how they set that up for a full hour that it's going to be the children
putting on a puppet show yeah and then the children are doing a puppet show and it's all
adult voices and they never explain why yes yeah it's just the children's puppet show asleep at
the fucking wheel you know like and it's the kind of thing where any decent crew member any good line
producer or whatever you want to would walk up and go hey this doesn't add up and i by the way
i've had moments where i've had moments where i've had moments where i've had moments where i've had
moments like that they just they just did one on and just like that where they mistakenly killed
off a character they had already killed off it can happen but somebody you know i can guarantee
at some point said to this guy hey wait a minute you said these would be children remember and he
was like ah who cares my friend rosario wants to do it there's a whole there's just an attitude of
who cares throughout the whole thing that translates to the audience i certainly didn't
give a fuck about anything that happens in this movie yeah uh a24
officially sucks which is a bummer because they put out great stuff for so long and everything
they're doing the reason i said they're like the new blumhouse it's because you know blumhouse's
thing is we're going to put out a million shitty movies and they're all going to have the same
tone which in blum for blumhouse is uh women are strong that's every movie uh a24 is like we're
going to put out a million movies uh now they're all going to be shitty and they're all going to
have the same tone which is everybody is west hampton and they're all going to have the same
anderson and it's like yeah and rich people are bad yes yeah they yes that too while being a
company you know if i exclusively run and catering to rich people like look at look at the price of
their merch for christ's sake look at the price of an a24 beach towel for christ's sake what
they're marketing to the rich by criticizing the rich and it creates this echo chamber of just shit
yeah it's classic rich people behavior let's pretend we're let's
criticize what we do to make ourselves feel better about doing it you know yeah that said i am
extremely excited to see eddington this weekend are we doing it on the show or are you done with
ari aster joe i'm fine either way i don't i don't know i i gotta admit i am cure i am a little more
curious about this one given the the subject matter i might see it i might see it the fact
that it's not horror and is being described as a western and it's the only movie really being made
to address what we all went through for two years
i'm very excited to see what it is and obviously i love the guy way more than you but
i think he's the guy to do it the reason i want to see it uh the or the one thing that makes me
want to see it is is i want to see if i'm wrong about saying what can you do out when you take
the shock value away this doesn't sound like something that's going to have a lot of shock
value yeah in it so i'm curious but isn't doesn't this also star pedro pat yeah of course joe look
at the movie in 2025 it's going to have pedro pascal you can't really avoid that uh are you
gonna see superman or no i'm gonna see it but i get if you're like i can't do it but don't worry
about it if you think it's average or below then no if you think it's amazing i'll go see it but
krumholtz is actually playing super girl's father so my interest went down a hundred percent he's
not in superman bradley cooper plays superman okay yeah super girl is in this yeah um
q uh brian quinn saw it and i was like and he's a tough critic with this stuff but i was like how
how was it and he goes it was good man he was like he's like look the plot's not gonna rock
your foundation but he was like he's like it's good man it's he was like it's really fun it's
not too funny superman is like bright again and like yeah you know all right let's do it i'll go
but i you know i gotta wait till my sty goes away before putting on the imax 3d glasses and passing
it next week or something i was uh i was like lightly troll eddie pepitone on instagram like
it'll be a picture of what's that the funniest yeah he'll post like a picture of him with like
a famous person and i'll be like this is so embarrassing that you would superimpose yourself
into this photo like but he posted a thing of him at superman with the glasses on and he's like
superman in 3d and i wrote uh this is so sad that you would bring glasses from home
pretend like you upgraded to the 3d screening that's fun yeah uh he he is a dude who i'll just
like leave my house at at 9 p .m on a tuesday and go see at a local bar just because i need a good
hard laugh he's so funny he's got a new special coming too tell him about your special joe more
importantly uh uh yeah it's it as of well this will be out right before the special officially
drops it's a it's available right now on disruptor comedy
if you want to own it and also see it commercial free uh and completely unbleaped it will probably
be unbleaped on youtube as well but there will be commercials unless you have the premium
subscription to youtube but anyway it hits youtube on july 21st monday july 21st uh my
youtube is at joe de rosa comedy go click subscribe watch please uh i hope you enjoy
this i worked three very long years on this
it's the best thing i've ever put out anywhere uh so you know i hope that uh the the audience
enjoys it as well um and that's it and then i'm you know and i'll be on the road in august uh
rhode island uh first weekend of august um yeah comedy connection and then comedy works
south which is in colorado just outside of denver um that's the third week of august i think but
you can go to jodorowska .com for the link to the link to the link to the link to the link to the
tickets for all of that um you know so come through i got other dates in the fall and stuff
and and and blah blah blah but but let's get this special rolling pat folks i'm at instagram at the
patrick walsh uh we are at uh jesus christ blanked out we are on instagram at see you in hell pod
which is being run by the great emily florence and now will potter we can get see classic clips
fan art all kinds of fun stuff we got a nice little following going there too as always folks
our patreon is not really something we can get new fans on so please tell your friends tell your
family uh tell everybody about the we'll see you in hell podcast help us expand and uh that's it
we will be back talking about help me joe final destination final destination colon bloodlines
um and that's it we'll see you in hell
love you we will see you next time and we will see you in hell