Welcome to We'll See You in Hell, folks.
My name is Joe DeRosa.
And my name is Patrick Walsh.
How are you everyone?
And how are you Joe had them?
Okay.
It's a rainy Sunday, the third day in a row in New York with a flood warning
all day, yet it doesn't rain.
Uh, and then when it's not a flood warning without rain, it's an air pollution
warning, uh, without bad air.
So, uh, a friend of mine, his theory is that after COVID, they will now.
Right in us to death with, with like every day, it's gotta be a different
problem, even if there's not a problem.
So I don't know if that's what's going on.
Sounded a little paranoid to me when he said it, but, but I gotta say, we
got a lot of flood warning days and there ain't no damn rain coming down.
So I don't understand how you make a mistake like that.
Yes.
No.
How do you make a flood warning without the key element?
I don't know if it started pouring, then you could make a flood warning
immediately because there's an actual chance of it happening.
I would have no rain as blind melon told us.
I mean, your life's pretty plain.
Uh, you're not in any danger.
Talked about a guy that did it right.
Just got out.
I've actually only ever heard that one song.
Usually, especially in that time period, I would always like seek out other songs.
If I liked one for them, it was just the one, don't know if they had another single.
I want you to do me a favor, do yourself a favor.
Sure.
Uh, their second album, I think I was just called soup.
I don't remember the title of the second album, but the first song on it is called
galaxy first or second song.
It's called galaxy.
I say first or second song.
Cause I remember the album has some weird like jug band intro that goes like 40
seconds and I think that's connected to galaxy.
Like, I don't think you can separate the two either way.
I don't want you to hear this intro and think that's the song is what I'm getting
at, uh, if, if they can't be separated on the, when you play it digitally, but
listen to the song clearly don't know how much I love the sweet, sweet sound
of Dixie jug band, so, uh, I'll be fine.
I'll be just fine.
Um, listen, I wrote it on my phone.
I'll listen to it.
I searched it on Spotify.
So it'll pop up.
It is in my top grunge era songs ever.
It's an awesome song.
And obviously, sonically quite different than what you'd expect from them.
It was a different light, different sound, but still very melodic.
And it's a great fucking song.
You're going to love it.
I'm in.
Was it a single?
Yeah.
It was the first single off the second album.
And I remember seeing the video and immediately going, this song is awesome.
Like, wait, I don't, I didn't think I liked this band.
I, this song is awesome.
Well, he was one of those things.
It says galaxy slash.
Hello.
Goodbye.
Does it turn into a Beatles cover?
Hello.
No, I guess that's the B side of the single.
I think, I don't know.
I just had to pay a Ringo star $175 ,000 to go.
They're there.
Set up day to day to say hello.
I say hello.
Hello.
English culture, English, England culture, London culture.
It's one of those cultures where you go enough guys.
I'm into it.
I mean, I like it, but it's enough guys.
There's comment down for, I love blur pulp and stuff.
There are bands that go too deep into it.
Like I would say the kinks, even though I love the kinks, they have whole albums
where it's like, well, I'm wearing my chiffon color peddling my unicycle down
to the marketplace and you're like, come on guys, come on.
Now you must have other things going on.
You ever try to fuck a girl.
Let's think about that.
Rolling stones.
No, that we don't care about your limey chiffon collar.
Yeah.
You say, or you'll be like, you'll be like, you know, Hey, are you hungry?
I could go for a spot of cabbie boats.
What I am feeling on my package.
I am what's like, just say sandwich.
Asshole.
I lost everything here.
I got you here.
Still.
You're still here.
Headphones are out of batteries.
Once that we're getting all this on tape.
Pat still hasn't figured out how to buy a pair of headphones that
don't require batteries, ladies and gentlemen, the man uses headphones
that require batteries.
Uh, he's got a microphone, the same microphone that I use that you plug
regular headphones directly into.
It's the simplest thing in the world.
Get a, you know, when you go to like a CVS and you, and you
see behind the counter.
They got like cheap headphones.
Here it comes with another chargeable pair of headphones.
Guy just can't learn his lesson.
Just doesn't learn.
Doesn't learn all you got to do.
You go into a CVS, you buy what's that brand with the, with the like skeleton.
It's like a kitty, but a skull and crossbones.
It's called like skull candy or whatever.
You buy a pair of skull candies.
They're, they're five bucks, maybe 10 on a bad day on a real bad day.
10, usually five bucks.
You buy them, you plug them directly in, into the microphone and you're,
you're off to the races.
They don't need to be charged.
They don't need anything, but this man, here he goes.
The second pair of charging necessity, necessary charge.
I just trashed you for 15 minutes while you're gone.
Well, I mean, how do I know they're going to go out, out of charge?
How do I know?
I'm just going on about like a pit stop in days of fun.
That was how fast I changed it.
Why don't you, uh, just not use chargeable headphones?
That's the part I don't get that.
That's the, the other kinds that I have are on plugins, you know, they're
Bluetooth based and I can't use that on my computer for summer.
These plug, these are these ones I have.
If you type in earbuds on Amazon, they're five bucks.
I think it's skull candy.
Plug them right in.
No charge.
I mean, this is going to sound like an excuse, but those don't fit in my ear.
I have weird ear holes.
I can't wear the earbuds.
They fall out.
Now I feel bad.
Now I feel that I've shamed you.
No, no, no.
Every, since I was in Atlanta, which at this point is over a year.
I haven't, I haven't changed these batteries.
They have an exceedingly long life.
They just happened to go out now.
I'm over it.
All right.
It's fine.
It's good content.
Just say about me in a world where, where you can get earbuds behind the
counter itself at a CVS for $6.
This guy's using chargeable headphones.
You know, that kind of stuff.
What did I just tell you?
They don't fit.
Yes.
What I said, you didn't ask what I know now after you came back.
Okay.
I thought you were continuing in it.
No, no.
While you were gone.
That's what I said.
Uh, let's, uh, I got some, I gotta think I got a new psycho here.
Hold on a second.
Oh, we're, by the way, we're doing, this is your Indian dial of destiny
review, cause we never got to it.
Uh, we wanted to separate Indiana Jones and the dial of destiny.
Yeah.
We were taken away.
I am supposed to remind you to go over the theme as I'm sure you remember, but
we're heading into the fifth and I presume final of the indie franchise
today as a continuation of our last episode.
I have a prediction for the character.
Yeah.
I think Harrison Ford is done being indie in the way we know.
I feel like, well, actually after this movie is technically a flop, even
though it made a gazillion dollars, it, you know, it wasn't enough or whatever.
But so I don't know if they're going to,
in week two, it lost to the new insidious, like the seventh insidious.
That that's tough.
That really is.
Cause those movies are always 5 million bucks, you know, and it did
not look good for old Indy.
By the way, I went, I was fucking around on the internet last night.
Couldn't sleep.
It was like 4 a .m.
I woke up and I'm on, I go on my iPad and I see that this new insidious
is out in theaters and my head dropped with the weight of, it was like in
Glen Gary, Glen Ross, when he thinks he has to go reclose all of his deal.
I was like, we're gonna have to go see insidious and cover this.
I mean, we have to, right?
I feel like we, you know what I keep reading the scene with the, the scene
with the MRI in the trailer is very scary to me.
I think it's good that somebody finally realized how terrifying an MRI is.
It's the real life equivalent to being buried alive.
Uh, I read a couple of reviews that said it's a sentimental
sendoff for the family.
I, I read that Patrick Wilson directed this and he got his favorite band,
this band called ghosts to record a song or record a cover of a song.
And Patrick Wilson is on backup vocals.
He sings it.
I think it's lead buddy.
I don't think it's backup.
I mean, that's wild.
That's real wild.
That that's, that's a Clint Eastwood and grand Torino, but usually you
got to be 90 to have balls like that.
Um, this was a news psycho from a while back.
Uh, I, I, I don't know why I never got to it.
The full Monte actor who was fired from the show, Hugo Spear, speaking
out about what happened, uh, this came from movie web and 97 Spear was one
part of the, okay, uh, Spear, right.
Right.
The hell is, what did he do?
Uh, oh, he was getting changed on set.
So Disney said, uh, that he was terminated for allegations of inappropriate conduct.
He came back and said, this is bad timing.
I was getting changed on set and a female crew member saw me naked by accident.
Uh, the runner who was in her early twenties with, and I love that movie
web points this out with little film experience, cause that is actually
relevant, knocked on the door to his trailer while he was changing.
He says to the person, hold on one minute, but the request is either
unheard or ignored and she opens the door, sees him nude.
And this person is traumatized from this.
And gets the guy fired.
That's, this is insane.
If that's what happened.
Am I wrong?
No, I read this too.
If that's the full story, I think that's complete madness.
There were people in the comments, like the full money is about old
men taking their dicks out, like relax a little bit, bringing that into it is
not accurate to me, you know, it's not, if it's a movie about strippers, you
still got to be respectful of people.
And there's a time for making the art and a time for backstage.
But if it happened exactly like we're led to believe here, um, this, this
man could have been naked, uh, jacking off with a bowling pin in his
rectum in his trailer.
And if this woman walked in, it's on her.
That's her fault for being, for entering his personal
trailer and being traumatized.
I'm sorry.
Um, that's her fault that, that, because a trailer on set for these actors and
it's hard to feel any sympathy for actors, but they spend 12 to 18 hour
days in these trailers, sometimes doing nothing.
It's their home.
They go to the bathroom, they jack off, they call their friends, they watch
TV, et cetera, it's their home.
And everyone knows you knock before entering a trailer, just like you would
knock before entering a home.
I don't care if she's knows anything about the business or not.
Says she knocked and his one minute, whatever was ignored or unheard.
She goes in anyway, which, which you don't do either.
I've, I've been in trailers and they've knocked and I've had to yell, come in
seven times to the point that when they finally hear me say it, I sound like I'm
angry because I'm like, come in, because they keep knocking, uh, this is firing.
By the way.
And then it says, then he immediately rushes behind a changing thing and
then like, talk to her like, Oh, what's up, you know, whatever.
So he gets called in by the powers that be this, this reads like the Jerry
McGuire saint with Jay Moore, he goes, I said, what I've never in 31 years
had a single complaint about my conduct.
The guy said to me, you've been seen undressed in your trailer.
Spear said, yeah, Spear said, I couldn't believe it.
I said, okay, that's my trailer.
That's where I get dressed and undressed.
And then the guy said, it's serious.
And Spear said, Whoa, stop.
What, what's serious?
What's going on?
Which is the reaction of a person going, wait, am I getting fired?
What is happening here?
What movie is that?
Wait a minute.
My name is why, uh, it is.
Yeah.
So, and, and, and I hear you like, um, like a strip, a show about strippers,
that's not an excuse to act in inappropriate conduct.
I agree with you on that, but it does make it kind of funny to, for
this to be the circumstance you're working on a show about male nudity
and something this benign and of a big of a misunderstanding is so shocking to you.
It's like, well, but you're working on a show that's you're going to see nudity.
That's the show you're, I don't understand.
Like this, the context of this nudity was even more innocent than the nudity
you would see in the actual scenes being shot because those scenes are about
male strippers and therefore a little salacious.
So, uh, it's kind of a wild story.
Isn't this show on Disney plus too?
Well, yeah, that's, that's also odd to me going on that Disney plus is doing the
full month, but I guess the movie didn't have frontal nudity, did it or did it?
It, it came very close, but like bright lights obscured it, but it was an R rated
movie, you know, like I just don't understand that Disney plus the reason I
don't have it is I don't have kids and I don't give a shit.
Like why would the full Monte be on there?
It seems like they're just trying to rile people up sometime.
They're reviving every group of characters that has ever existed in any setting.
They're like, you know, it's like, they're back.
It's the full Monte.
You're like, okay, I guess.
Like, did we need this with your original cast?
You're like, who?
Like, did they get Tom Wilkinson back?
I don't think so.
Yeah.
And also wasn't the joke originally that they were already old.
And now they're old and out of shape.
Yeah.
Look, I haven't seen it since the theater, but I saw it twice in the theater.
That's how much I loved the full Monte when I was in high school.
I also love waking Ned divine about the old Irish guy who wins the lottery.
They were sweet, fun, really funny indie movies, very of their time, but
like bringing them back now, who knows?
And who knows the movie who cares?
Maybe it's good.
I don't know, but, uh, it's wild.
Um, there's a lot going on lately that, that just has me a little rattled.
Now, by the way, this man could be a sociopath.
He could have made 20 inappropriate passes at this girl for all we know, but
you'd think she would have included it in her report if that's what happened.
Try not to give everybody the benefit of the doubt here.
I, I, I agree.
My take on these things is usually, of course, you know, I want to hear both
sides and I want to believe people, but the belief has to go in more than just
one direction all the time and you know, I think that's only fair, but with that
said, I kind of feel like, and maybe this is a flawed barometer, but I feel like
if you're not like Joe Biden or Donald Trump level of power, if something like
this happens and 20 other things don't come out immediately, yeah, this is
probably a pretty accurate take on what happened, you know, like if you look up
the second, like for Cuba, Gooding's a good example.
Cuba Gooding wasn't really famous when he got accused again or for the first time.
And immediately it was like 20 women came out and they're like, yeah, he did
that to me too, he did that to me too, you know, and then next thing you know,
he's settling out of court on something.
So again, that might be a flawed way to, to, to judge these things, but that's
kind of, uh, you gotta have some kind of barometer.
That's what I try to use at this point.
Well, this guy is a struggling actor who may have, I mean, I haven't looked
at his credits, but he may have had to return to a day job since the full
Monte came out and was probably just thrilled to have this opportunity.
And it sucks because as far as the facts we've been presented with, this just
seems completely innocent and benign, but what are you going to do?
Is the show out?
Um, yeah, it's been out.
Is it good?
I don't think he's in it.
No, he's, he's not.
He's booted.
Yeah.
Um, before, uh, we continue with the highly anticipated Indiana Jones episode,
I'd also like to update you on another cliffhanger, which is the
Barnes and Noble experience.
Um, I went in there, there was a giant guy who looked like Harry
Knowles, um, big sort of red hair.
I'm like, Hey, I explained the situation.
He rolls his eyes and goes, son of a fucking bitch.
That's where we're at.
And I kind of look at him like, is he mad at me?
What's going on?
He starts scanning my stuff and he's like, I'm not mad at you, sir.
I'm mad at the idiots that work here.
Oh, I like, you bought a membership, you bought a membership yesterday.
And then he spins his computer around.
He goes, look at this.
They didn't even leave me a note.
I'm going to give you the 10%, but whoever you spoke to, and I believe
that you spoke to someone here, didn't even write a note in your account saying
this guy's coming all the way back up to the store, please give him the 10 % off.
Yeah, man, that sounds pretty bad.
Then our friend who I'm not mentioning, who works at the other Barnes
and Noble wrote me, he said he's, you know, ashamed of his company.
The sounds about right for where the company's at, blah, blah, blah.
I'm not going to get him into any trouble.
He also volunteered to fix the situation for me, but I told him
Harry knows already did it.
Um, thank you, Barnes and Noble for repairing it, but this place is like
a lot of, a lot of places out there on, on its last legs.
And by the way, this is where we're at.
That at one time you would have went, yeah, no shit.
Barnes and Noble sucks.
This is all we got left is Barnes and Noble and you're going, please just
stay pure Barnes and Noble, like, you know, like this is where we're turning.
Pop Barnes, the mom, noble, the pop.
Okay.
I like, I'm going to do a quick movie corner and get us over to Indy.
I got, yeah, I got one for the corner.
Just one.
Okay.
I'll kick you off.
You kick us.
You go, you go.
I finished the new eight 24 HBO series, the idol, which was announced as being
six episodes, only five aired.
There was some controversy about whether they actually shot six or what happened.
But I don't know if you read the huge expose about the show.
They said the, the show they had fired, uh, Amy Samats, who was a indie filmmaker
who had had a couple of very small films, maybe like less than a million.
They immediately give her the reins to this.
Gigantically budgeted show starring the weekend and this big, like sex expose
with Lily Rose depth, Johnny Depp's daughter.
You see her naked in it constantly.
You see her naked more than clothed.
All right.
Um, I think she's like 20, Joe, but, um, 20, no, she's like 25.
Is she not?
Yeah.
I don't, I don't think she's pretty young, but, um, 24.
Thank you very much.
24.
All right.
Well, feel, feel pride in your lust.
I mean, that's the show.
The show is like everyone lusting over her.
And then there's a team of executives on that bicker and argue that team is
Hank's area using a more extreme accent than he's ever used before playing a
French guy, wild performance in an otherwise fairly serious show, uh, divine
joy, Randolph, who is usually funny and solid, uh, Jane Adams, who I normally
like, um, you got Dan Levy from Schitt's Creek, you got Eli Roth playing a really
perverse kind of manager guy.
The entire first episode is locking a intimacy coordinator in a closet so
that they can shoot this like really fucked up sexual video.
Then, especially when you learn about everything that went on on set,
where the intimacy coordinator felt underappreciated and so forth.
It's like, Oh boy, it just seems like all this Sam Levinson can do.
I like euphoria most of the time, just because it's completely perverse
and fun and sick every week.
But his movie like Malcolm and Marie is two actors arguing about reviews,
movie reviews that they've gotten, but it's clearly just a guy getting
back at his own critics and that's all he can do.
I mean, this show is five hours of the most stupid, naval gazing bullshit
dialogue, the weekend plays like this Sven Gali type who assembles a cult of
young women and men who he trains to become great artists through abusing them
through like sexually controlling them and manipulating them in the end, they
try to pull some 360 where this guy is the hero, the misunderstood hero.
Um, it's a really, really bad show.
Like a lot of eight 24 stuff.
It tries to just get by on vibes, but there is nothing else to it
other than vibes and nudity.
There's a scene at one point of a man standing over a young woman.
They've got her wearing some sort of like, I hope anyway, a camel toe prosthetic.
So we're like looking into like almost a gynecological view of what appears
to be an 18 year old girl for like a 32nd shot.
Just, you know, I'm, I'm no,
do you watch this series front to back?
And I'm, I should be ashamed.
Cause I asked if she gets naked at it in a benign way.
I asked it too, by the way, you, you still watch this whole thing front to back.
True.
Yeah.
Um, look, I always complain.
Where is the sex?
Where is the nudity?
And something like this, just the fact that it costs, they, they shelved
a hundred million dollars of this in favor of shooting a new version with Sam
Levinson behind the wheel, it looks like it was improvised, you know, probably
$150 million went down the toilet for this thing.
It's always nice to see sex.
It's always nice to see nudity, but I gotta say, this wasn't even sexy.
It's like the episode would start and it's the weekend eating her out, driving
around Beverly Hills for 10 minutes, like the backseat while someone's driving
them around, it's like, all right.
I've had just about enough of the weekend.
I've had enough.
Uh, he's a talented guy.
He's on some Ben hell bent mission to, uh, depict himself in the
most unlikable ways possible.
I think he is potentially, potentially, I don't know the guy.
I don't know anything about him, but he is potentially like, like another
shade of an army hammer in my opinion, where it's like, are you trying to put
it under our noses that you're a fucking sociopath because dude, you played
yourself, yourself in uncut gems as somebody that is sexually assaulting a
woman in a bathroom, like, and that was you playing you.
That was consensual and uncut gems.
No, he's like, he's like shoving himself on her and she's like, am I
misremembering I think they were just having sex as far as I remember.
Cause if they had introduced that into the movie, it would have been, they
would have had to deal with it.
So let me be wrong.
Let me re let me rephrase it.
Cause I could be wrong too.
I know this much.
He portrays himself as creepy in uncut gems because every person I've ever
said, it's weird how the weekend plays himself, right?
And everyone was like, yo, yeah, that is weird, right?
Like, what's he doing?
Um, and now he makes this show and this is like his swan song, this thing.
This is like, this is his big fucking project, man.
This is his Chinese democracy.
And you know, he's playing again, like a goddamn fucking creep.
There's all the stories, the stories about now I get it.
You don't hand the reins of a project this big to somebody that's barely
experienced, but they get that lady out.
And then this next guy comes in and then all this shit starts coming out from
behind the scenes about the intimacy coordinator bullshit and all that stuff
that you talked about, it's just not a good look, man.
It's not a good look.
And it's like, when you go back, it seems like he was like, I am doing this
show so that I can feel up 22 year old girls, so I'm not dealing with some
fucking intimacy coordinator, get me the euphoria guy, you know, like that's
what it seems like happened.
Um, the show, like he, he has scenes in this where it is assault.
They're in a, uh, Beverly Hills store.
She's trying something on and he starts fucking her from behind.
And she's like, don't come in me.
And then she's like, Hey, don't come in me.
What did I say?
It comes out and it's played for comedy.
He's like complaining that he's not allowed to calm.
So then he comes on like some $1 million dress, like wipes his dick with it.
And it's like, yeah, this is an odd sort of thing to put out there.
If the guy is playing essentially you.
And you're not going to agree with what I'm about to say.
And by the way, you want to date 22 year old girls?
You want to date 18 year old girls?
God bless.
Uh, you're not doing anything illegal.
I don't give a shit about that, but you want to fucking keep per per per, um,
portraying yourself on screen in these like really like, like maniacal
sexually maniacal ways.
That's the part that's questionable.
If this was a TV show about 38 or 44 or 52 year old women, it would be weird still.
It's like, what are you doing, dude?
Like, it's just, I don't, I don't get it.
I just don't get it.
Um, you know, I don't, yeah, but I don't mind shows about sex in all its forms,
but yeah, for a guy that is around the youngest of women who writes songs only
about fucking while completely out of your mind on cocaine, um, it's a,
it's an interesting choice.
I, the first three albums, the trilogy, you know, when the weekend came on the
scene, I was obsessed with the guy when he was like coming out of Canada.
I thought his first three albums were incredible.
The best fucking music of my generation.
I was into him before most.
And I think as a pop songwriter, he's great still to this day.
But I do think there's something along the lines of a MJ and R Kelly coming
our way, that's going to be not surprising because there is a need for
some of these people to just kind of hide and blend site.
Um, the worst part about the show is that it's boring.
I mean, you're looking at piles of naked flesh and you're just bored.
That's the issue with the show.
All right.
Yeah, go ahead.
Do yours.
We'll do one each and we'll get to, we'll get to Indy.
Well, I was going to say you that it's just, it's just, and this is where
you're going to really disagree with me.
This is Todd Solon shit.
I can't fucking Stan Todd solons.
I hate his work.
Uh, I think he makes stuff that is just disturbing and gross and weird.
And look, I know you love happiness and I know certain people think it's a
masterpiece, but I'm like, I just don't need to see any of this.
I'm not into it.
And, and I'm a hypocrite because there's things I love that people go like hostile.
People go, I don't need to see that.
It's just disturbing.
Whatever.
So I get it.
It's there's an audience for it out there somewhere, but when it gets, this is
my weird territory, man, like this kind of shit.
You know, like, like Todd, sound storytelling, like, uh, um, euphoria.
Yeah.
It's just guys.
I don't know, man.
If I want to watch gratuitous fucking, uh, I'll watch it in, in adult cinema.
And if I, if I want to see gratuitous fucking in non adult cinema, then I
don't want to see it with a weird edge of assault or racism or force or whatever.
It's just weird to me.
I don't understand it.
I just don't.
I don't, it'd be like, it'd be like making a TV series where your
protagonist slash hero is, is a pedophile or something.
And you're like, this is odd.
Like, I'm not saying don't make movies that tackle this, but like in
this fashion, it's weird to me.
Sure.
No, I mean, I, I absolutely love happiness while also I wouldn't
recommend it to almost anyone in my life.
It's a, it's an abhorrent movie, unquestionably, but like the two of
the people you mentioned as making extreme movies, Jane Adams was in
happiness and Eli Roth directed hostile.
And I think this guy thinks that just by putting these people in his show, um,
they'll associate him with them.
But happiness to me, unquestionably has more going on than the fucking
idol in its head.
Um, and even hostile does hostile is exceptional horror movie, but it's also
a funny comedy with some great social commentary.
Um, I did not get any of that from the idol, but I do think.
And Hank Azaria is another one.
I bet he hired him just to be like, can you believe this fucking a poo shit?
They won't let you do a poo.
You know, he just puts together these people who are like, you know, in some
trouble and throw it like, but Jane Adams, they interviewed her and they were like,
what do you think about feminists who are disgusted by the idol?
And she goes, fuck them, fuck them.
She goes, people were more upset about the idol than happiness.
Are you out of your fucking mind?
You know?
Um, and I get it.
You want to defend the thing you're working on, but all I can look at is, is
the show itself, which was just boring, had nothing, nothing to say about.
Pop stars and what they go through.
I mean, like Britney Spears, lucky video tells us a more realistic story.
They do the black Swan thing where she's got like bloody calluses on her
feet at the end of the day.
And you're like, you've been doing step touches.
You're doing the choreography of like a Britney Spears.
Like, let's not pretend this is ballet here.
It's just a stupid show.
That's all I can say.
Not even really good spank material.
Uh, hell of a year for the depths.
Uh, I will do a quick one.
I watched this last night after I asked you if you had any interest.
You said, no, it's about doing another pod, uh, paint starring Owen Wilson.
Uh, this is a comedy about a Bob Ross type character played by Owen Wilson.
Who meets his, who has become sort of arrogant and bit of a weird guy.
A womanizer, uh, and comfortable in his, in his, in his space as being, you
know, uh, a celebrity in Burlington, Vermont, uh, it's clearly based on Bob
Ross, um, uh, you know, he's got the Afro and the pipe and all that stuff.
Uh, and, uh, it's, I thought it was going to get like dark or something
and it doesn't really, it's, it's honestly just a kind of a light
little comedy I enjoyed it because it feels 1000 % tonally like these
comedies they used to make the indie comedies that came out in like the
early aughts, uh, and in the late nineties, I'm trying to think of, uh,
you know, well, Owen Wilson came from that, you know, bottle rocket, right?
Um, yeah, uh, I'm trying to think though of, of, of, of other examples of, uh,
these, what's a good example, Pat of, you know, like drowning Mona and, and,
uh, welcome to me, the Kirsten Wigg movie, bats, swingers, you know, like
it just kind of felt like one of those.
Will Ferrell one where they, they want him to sell all his
belongings in a garage sale.
Where he lives on his lawn.
Yeah, I forget what that was called.
Uh, everything must go.
Yes.
And it just kind of felt like one of those movies, uh, a little more in the
vein, you know what, perfect example, Napoleon dynamite had the vibe of a
Napoleon dynamite was shot very similarly.
Everybody sort of seems to exist in another time period, even though
it's in present day, it's very light.
You're kind of waiting for these odd, quirky characters to take a dark turn
and it never happens and it's got quite a delightful, happy ending.
And there's some big laughs in it.
It's not a great movie, but it's very enjoyable.
Uh, it bombed horribly.
It made $800 ,000 and it got bashed by critics because they just said
there's just nothing here.
Um, but I look to be, oh, I'm guessing on SNL and does a sketch as Bob Ross.
But beyond that, I was like, I can't fathom this making it to feature length.
I just can't even imagine that.
It's a very, just light little, you're in, you're out.
I enjoyed it.
And there's a great, there's one like classic Owen Wilson line in it.
Like, uh, he's, it's, it's right at the beginning and he finishes his, the,
he's doing his show and it's when you first like see him off the show and how
all the women at this network fawn over him, like they're all falling over him.
And, uh, and he's like having like two conversations at once and the
one woman compliments him and Owen Wilson goes, thank you.
Thank you for saying that.
It's just so hard when you're, when you're the whole picture, because people
just tend to not see the gift inside.
And it's a very classic, arrogant, like it's just a great Owen Wilson moment.
He's funny in it.
It was fun.
Honestly, it was fun.
See, you know, Owen Wilson just kind of be funny again.
Uh, so anyway, that's it.
Uh, indie picture as we go into, as you made the joke last week in indie
picture, Indiana Jones and the dial of destiny, the last hurrah.
Oh, this is the prediction I was going to make earlier.
I was saying with, with this movie, not doing that well, I don't think they're
going to pursue any of these spinoffs that, that they sort of hinted they
might pursue before this movie came out.
But if they do, I don't know what they were talking about, but my, my
assumption is Phoebe Waller bridge is doing her own, like they pulled the
plug on it.
It's the same issue as with Shia LaBeouf.
If you are going to do a spinoff, then you take this giant movie that everyone's
eyes are going to be on and give us an undeniably great character that we want
to see go on more adventures.
They did not do that with Shia LaBeouf's mutt character.
In my opinion, they absolutely did not do that with the Phoebe Waller bridge
character, and they certainly did not do it with the kid whose name I don't
remember, who I barely remembered being in this movie.
He's going up against short round and it's a kid with no personality.
I disagree wholeheartedly, but, but, but before we get into any of that, all I
was going to say is that I could see him popping up again as in the, if they were
to do one of these shows, not in an adventure setting, but just in a, she
goes to him for advice or something.
You know what I mean?
Like, but I think they'd need him to be in it in some capacity.
Cause if it's, if it's Phoebe and that kid, this movie is going to make $10 ,000.
It's going to make less than paint.
Nobody gives a shit.
Well, it was supposed to be a TV series and it's not, they announced they were
working on a TV series and then they said, we're not doing it anymore.
And it's obvious.
I mean, I don't have any proof that it was her and the kid, but obviously when
you see the movie, like what else the hell else would it have been?
But let's, let's, let's, let's the movie itself.
Uh, this is a movie that is about the last and Harrison Ford said this a
lot throughout the promotion of the film that he wanted to visit the character
in the last phase of his life, like a final chapter where this guy ends up.
And that is very much what this movie does.
This movie feels to me a lot like, uh, now I found it more enjoyable
than the Godfather part three, but I feel like this was the same approach
that Coppola was trying to have with the Godfather part three Coppola said
many times that was not supposed to be part three, it was supposed to be.
The epilogue of Michael Corleone.
So you could see where this guy ends up.
That is exactly in my opinion, what this movie is for Indiana Jones.
You get a really exciting opening 20 minute sequence with him as a young
man during the fall of Berlin fighting Nazis, where they set up what's going
to happen later in the movie with this device, uh, that they're going to
search for or try to protect.
And it's, it's Indy at his best.
It's Indy when he's young, it's Indy kicking ass.
It's got the humor and the, and the spunk and the spirit of the classic
Indiana Jones movies, he is de -aged.
That is distracting at times.
Uh, I said though, on the last episode, were you to watch this?
If God forbid you can see anything anymore that isn't in startling 4k
stunning that, you know what I mean?
Like everything is so fucking clear.
It's got to look like, you know, you're, you're, you're, you're peering into
your fucking fish bowl in your living room or something like, but you know,
it's, I think, I think some, some grain and some film old film stock would,
would do the de -aging well to hide it.
But with that all said, if you get, and I'd like to interject by and say that to
me, this was the only movie I've ever seen where the de -aging to me was not
noticeable, it was completely fine.
I saw an IMAX.
Um, of course, you know that the man has been de -aged, but I, it did not bother me.
I did not see any trace of like, Oh, this is in its early stages.
Like I did when they did it to Patrick Stewart and the X -Men or certainly in
the Irishman, it didn't bug me at all.
I thought it was pretty seamless actually.
Did you think in the Irishman, see in the Irishman, when you first saw
De Niro and Pesci de -aged, I was like, Oh, that's noticeable.
And then it just went away.
Like by the time you see Pacino and the Irishman, there's not one moment with
Pacino where I'm like, he's de -aged.
I'm like, Hey, Pacino looks great.
And then you see him in interviews and you realize how old he is in this.
I was, I was way more like, Oh, he's been de -aged.
But in, but in the, here's the thing that when I saw the commercials on TV, I
was like, that looks incredible.
It wasn't until I was sitting in a fucking like RPX, you know, like
whatever theater that I was like, Oh, I noticed it now, you know?
Um, yeah, I guess it didn't bug me.
I mean, part of it's in the Irishman that gave them both rosy cheeks.
Um, they had them like stomping, you know, especially when De Niro
stomping on the guy, it did not look, we've seen too much of De Niro
stomping on people's faces for that to be believable, but, um, something about
this, I think it's just that they've had enough time to kind of work out the kinks.
It didn't bug me.
And I was still just as, cause a lot of times these, these flashbacks
take all the suspense out, you know, Indy survives, but I thought it was all really
well done, especially in the first half of the movie where most of it is.
I thought it was, I thought this whole opening was awesome, man.
Like when he's going down that hill on the motorcycle with the Nazi and the
machine guns spinning around, like I've, I found myself like jumping like, Ooh,
Ooh, watch it, Indy watch, you know, like I was, I was, I was exciting.
I was excited.
Uh, and you get the, you get hero Indy in this whole opening.
It ends with that great moment where, uh, Basil played by, uh, um, Toby.
Keith, Toby, what's his name?
Toby Jones, Toby Jones.
Yeah, Toby Jones, uh, they jump off the train at the end and the train crashes
and explodes and they w they swim onto shore and Basil's like, right.
Can't believe we're going home empty handed after all that.
And, and, and Indy goes, not exactly.
And he pulls the, the Archimedes dial that they find on the train out of his bag.
And it plays the music and it's happy.
And I'm like, there you go.
They just, and it took me two watches to realize it, but I was like, there you go.
They gave you the upbeat, happy Indy at his best everything in that first 20
minutes and why, so now we can jump forward, uh, 30 years or so, and now see
him at his worst as a man that needs to be redeemed.
There are some people that are saying like, Oh, I wish they would cut the
beginning off and it was just about the old man and I'm like, no, the beginning
is what, and I'll, and we'll get to this, but like the beginning is what makes
the fact that he is kind of sad throughout the movie.
Okay.
Because if you don't have that beginning, you don't know what he's redeeming
himself to in the very end with that beginning, it allows you to accept
him as an older grumpy man.
I love that when you first see him, he wakes up by the neighbor,
jolting him awake, he's 80 years old.
As you said, he still looks, he still looks fantastic, but you know, he looks
better than most of us look at age 40 at age 80, he's a fine specimen of man,
but seeing him shirtless when we first see him as an old guy, it's already
jarring just like it was in Crystal Skull when he's in sort of that 50s house
environment, because you're used to seeing Indy in the 20s and Nazi times,
you know, so even just the 50s was kind of startling.
In this movie, it's the Beatles playing.
So, you know, it's late sixties.
They're playing Sergeant Pepper, and it's the real, not the aged Harrison
Ford, his body's got some sag, some give to it, you know, that as any
80 year old man would have.
And I love that.
I love that started us off on a new foot.
They're not hiding his age.
They're not pretending that he's some spring chicken anymore.
And that is what gives the movie thematically everything that works
about it is the age, him reckoning with his past, him reckoning with his
mistakes, his regrets as an old man.
That's what makes the movie work for me.
And I think these are the issues we're going to be having as we go.
The action wasn't there, even though there were plenty of action sequences
that I enjoyed, I didn't think this was anywhere near as fun, as exciting as an
Indiana Jones movie should be, and it's two and a half hours, whereas all the
other ones got the job done in two.
Um, these are my grievances.
And then of course, the supporting cast who I just thought, let's get to it.
Let's I feel a little more protective as we discuss this one to get to it a
little more linearly as we go through it, because I feel like there's things to
point out about each section of this movie that you, you and I might agree
with or disagree with.
I don't know, but that, that him at the beginning, when you see him at
with the shirt off, that's your first recurring theme temple of doom.
Full circle.
That's the first full circle to temple of doom.
He's shirtless in temple of doom.
Remember you point that out and how good he looks and how turned on you were by
that, uh, and yeah, they just told them, you know, you're not going to be
wearing the, uh, the khakis throughout, uh, temple of doom.
We're going to have you shirtless a lot.
And he put on 20 pounds of muscle.
And I don't think in his entire career, he ever looked better.
So, you know, when I, what Joe's going to get to, and then I noticed in certain
scenes is that he's referencing his other adventures, but he seems to only
be referencing temple of doom.
And Joe really kind of helped bring that home and that it was bringing, bringing
the themes of that movie into this one.
And I think that's true, but it's an odd thing to do to put so much time on
most people's least favorite indie movie.
I love it.
Temple of doom, as you know, it's my favorite, but it definitely feels like
a weird sort of parallel journey with temple of doom, but that makes sense
because chronologically that's the first indie adventure we see.
So enter.
So you see now he's, and I love this next, he's yelling at his neighbors.
They're too loud.
They're too this, right?
He doesn't know that it's moon day.
He doesn't know that it's the celebration of the moon landing.
So now you're seeing the themes come in of this guy.
It's the, all of society is moving forward.
This guy's not moving forward with it.
He feels left behind.
Uh, and that's, that's made pretty clear right off of the bat, right
off the bat in the movie, um, he wakes up with a glass, an empty glass in his
hand and you get the idea, okay, it looks like he fell asleep drinking, did he?
And then sure enough, he's in the kitchen making his coffee and he pours
into his coffee and you're like, okay, they're going right at this.
He looks down at divorce papers.
He's not, he's not John McClain.
You know, he's not John McClain where he wakes up and, and six whiskey
bottles fall out of bed onto the floor.
Indiana Jones is a guy we've seen drink, you know, we've seen him when he
thinks Marion is dead with the bottle and the monkey, you know, but we've
never seen him as a whiskey in his coffee kind of guy, we've never seen him
as carrying around a flask kind of guy.
So yeah, that's some, some new lows for him in this one.
Yeah.
You see the divorce papers.
He puts the, there's the picture of Marion on the fridge.
He puts the magnet over her face, uh, which I like.
I also like in the opening scene, you see the, you see the picture of
the crucifixion from Connery's house.
You see the picture of Sean Connery.
You see the picture of Shia LaBeouf.
Um, and he goes to school and you see him in his class.
And for the first time ever, Indy is teaching a class full of
kids that don't give a shit.
They're not listening.
Nobody cares.
And they're really hitting this point beautifully of the past is over.
It's 1969.
We landed on the moon.
We're moving forward.
Nobody cares about what's buried out in the desert somewhere.
Um, you then see his retirement party.
Uh, and you realize, and he's joyless about it.
And then I love that he's then in a bar drinking and, uh, that's when you
first meet his niece, uh, uh, Helena one, her nickname is wombat.
And when you first meet her, there's two things in this that I really
love that we're telling, and then I'll shut up, sorry, Pat, I don't
mean to talk for too long, but there's just two things here that I really loved.
I love that she goes, you don't recognize me, do you?
And he says, look, whatever I did, I'm sorry.
And I'm like, yeah, this is awesome.
It really like, they're really driving home.
Like this man has made a lot of mistakes and here he is.
Here he is.
Remember when he left Marion tied up?
So the Nazis wouldn't know he was there.
This is coming back to haunt him now, you know, like, so there's that.
And then I love that he immediately says, she goes, what are we drinking?
And he goes, I'm celebrating.
And you're like, you're not celebrating.
You're not, you're not happy about retiring.
You're fucking in, you're an alcoholic and you're drinking at three PM.
You know, yeah, that stuff's all great.
And I also like how they don't, they don't actually put it in dialogue.
Like most movies these days, you know, that's a, that's the seventies
kind of where you're not shouting all this stuff out.
What, what, what it almost cried out for and thankfully didn't do was like,
you're the relic now, Indy, you're the, the piece left in the desert
that nobody cares about.
And he re you know, he realizes he is, they don't make that explicit,
but that's how you feel these things that he used to run around the world
collecting and say it belongs in a museum.
That's Indiana Jones.
Now he belongs in a museum.
He's, he's past his prime.
He's past his sell by date.
Nobody cares and nobody's out looking for him except this one girl.
And he's just doesn't even want her to want to be bothered.
And Phoebe Waller bridge.
Now, again, here's another recurring theme from temple of doom.
Her pitch to him that they need to go find this Archimedes dial that her
father was obsessed with, and this thing drove him crazy.
She's her whole drive is fortune and glory.
It's it's she's young Indy.
Like people go, she's not very likable.
And it's like, well, neither is Indy.
If you watch temple of doom first, you only like them in that
because you already know him.
He's a fucking bastard for a lot of that movie.
And then he become, he redeems himself and becomes human just as she does in this.
So I really like that detail.
I like that.
I love the line where he says, why would you try to search for the, where the
thing that drove your father crazy?
And she says, wouldn't you?
And you're like, yes, he would.
Yes, he would.
And we saw him do it.
So, um, and at this point, he, he takes her to a sort of not safe deposit box,
but an area in his school where he has stashed away the piece of Archimedes
dial that he has and the, the, the, the, the dial supposedly can locate fissures
in time where you could essentially travel through time or affect time.
He shows her the dial and anal fissures, oddly enough.
It can only detect two sorts of fissures, fissures in time.
And then whether or not you have an anal fissure, so you can get it looked
at before you start time travel.
So, you know, you get it back in time.
They're not going to have the proper medicine to fix something like that.
Uh, so she, he shows, he shows her this.
He, he has her father's diaries, uh, which another callback to crusade.
Um, and at that point, we meet the bad guys, Mad, led by Mad
Mickelson, Mads Mickelson, who I think is awesome and I think is the best
indie villain since Molaram and, and Belloc.
I really, I really like Mads Mickelson quite a bit in this.
I thought he was great.
He's great.
You know, it's what was, we were promised with Blanchette, you know,
you see her with the eyepatch and the Nazi get up on crystal skull and you're
like, finally they put down some money to get like an actual villain.
It's like when Philip Seymour Hoffman is the villain in Mission Impossible
three, and then the rest of the movies don't have one for the most part.
And it's like irritating.
Um, great.
They're getting a great actor to do it.
And, and he's up to the challenge, you know, he's having fun with it
without being cartoony like Blanchette did.
Uh, I thought Mickelson was great too.
And, and they, they were, they were ballsy for an independent, for an
Indiana Jones movie with, with they, I love the scene where the black
waiter brings the food in and Mads Mickelson goes, where are you from?
And he goes, I'm from the Bronx, sir.
And he goes, no, where are you from?
Or however he says it.
And he goes, I'm from the Bronx, sir.
And you're like, that's fucking edgy.
Like that's the, they don't do that in Indiana Jones movies.
They don't have a guy be like, you know, they're Nazis, but even though
they're Nazis, they never say anything.
They never say anything racist, you know, not one Indiana Jones
Nazi has ever said, and the Jewish people never, they're just
Nazis and you know, to hate them.
And I gotta say, apparently they went further with it.
And this has been one of the mild spots of controversy about the movie
because all movies have controversy nowadays, but there's a black actress
in the movie who is a, you know, very low on the call sheet.
She's a supporting actress, but she's got a little moment.
And then she's just kind of shot and that's it.
She shot and killed by the Nazis.
But, um, apparently originally in the movie, they referred to her as a slur.
The actress was like, is the actress was like, is this really how it goes out?
He calls me a slur and shoots me and I die.
That's it.
And I guess Mangold was like, you're right.
Let's try that in a different way.
Not that they necessarily gave her a great sendoff, but I think there was
maybe a concerted effort to make the Nazis more Nazi ish in this one.
Well, it's some survived.
Some didn't.
It's great because the, the, that, that guy, that, that henchman
that kills her is great.
The guy that plays like the redneck henchman.
Right.
Uh, and she calls him cracker at one point.
So I'm assuming the slur was a callback to her cause she calls
him a trigger happy cracker, which I bummed me out that she didn't call
him a trigger happy honky.
I thought that had a better ring to it, but, but she says cracker, whatever.
Uh, but, but he might've been more seventies.
I'm, I'm just going off the movies of the time, but I'm, I could be wrong too.
But there is like, uh, an underlying racial tension there that this, this
Southern guy who is pledging his allegiance to a Nazi is getting bossed
around by a black woman in 1969.
Like this is headier stuff than you see in a lot of, in my opinion, I love
Indiana Jones, but this is headier stuff than you see in these movies.
And I liked that they brought it into this.
This is where all the action sequences begin and essentially the chase and
fight for, for the idol, uh, which in this one, again, is this Archimedes
dial, uh, Mads Mikkelsen wants it because he's going to go back in time and kill
Hitler and win the war for Germany.
That's another great line that he says to the waiter, you didn't win the war.
Hitler lost it.
That's a, that's a very well written line.
Um, but, uh, and I liked the, I liked you were saying you didn't care for the action.
I thought the action in this was awesome.
I liked the horse thing with through the subway and the chase scene through
wherever the hell they were with those buggies and I thought it was fun, man.
Yeah, I mean, here's what it is.
I think if, if you had talked to me, if we had kept going on that episode and made
it like a four hour episode of Indiana Jones last weekend, I think I would have
been higher on the movie, but what I just had to be honest with myself with is that
a week later, Indiana Jones has not popped into my head in any way.
I haven't thought about this movie in any way.
Now that doesn't mean I didn't like it.
Doesn't mean I didn't have a lot of fun, but nothing really stuck with me in a
way that I wanted to that said nothing stuck with me in a Oh God way, as it did
with crystal skull either, I think it's just a real rock solid action movie at a
time where we don't get many of them.
So I got to give it its props.
I think it's, it's a solid B movie, but I think you go higher than I do.
And I think you're saying it's up there with kind of the original
trilogy in certain aspects.
I can't meet you there, but I will say.
It's the best since the original trilogy, which isn't saying a lot actually,
but it's really well done for sure.
I like the movie.
I I've been pretty Indiana Jones obsessed since I saw it.
I saw it twice.
I want to see it again in the theater.
Uh, I've been playing Indiana Jones video games.
I've been watching Indiana Jones, YouTube videos about stuff.
And I've been having a picture of himself in a white briefs and a whip the other
day at, uh, you know, in my opinion should have just been something that stayed with
Joe, but it was cool to see him having fun.
Um, the, uh, the, uh, the, the, the, the chase begins, you know, as I said here
and, and, and, you know, for the rest of the movie, it plays out as you would
expect it to play out with an Indiana Jones movie, it's a race against time to
beat the Nazis and stop them from utilizing this device.
They have to complete it.
The problem with the device is they have to find the other half.
And there's a series of tasks they have to complete in order to find that other
half, uh, but once the device is complete, they will, it will be able to be utilized
to, to, to travel through time.
And the Nazis would essentially take over the world.
So there's another obviously recurring theme they're up against the Nazis
potentially taking over the world yet again.
Um, I thought that the, um, I loved, you, you said he didn't do anything for you.
I can't remember if you said it on here or somewhere else, but I really enjoyed
the whole sequence with Antonio Banderas.
I thought he was really funny.
I thought he was a great Indiana Jones type character.
I love the whole creepy crawly sequence with the eels, you know, like that was cool.
It felt like the old stuff.
It was, I kept thinking like, what are they going to do in this?
That's going to, they've already done snakes and bugs.
What are they going to do?
And they did eels.
And I was like, Oh, that's perfect.
I never thought of that.
It's a funny joke.
When the kid goes eels, they look like snakes.
And he's like, no, they don't like that.
You know, funny.
That was funny.
Um, the scene though, on that ship, that whole sequence on, on Bandera's
ship, you know, that's most important though, is where he's talking.
And this is where you see the humanity in, in Phoebe's character come out, where
she starts, stops caring just about getting this thing to sell it and starts caring
about Harrison Ford's character as a person and realizing there's more to life
than the money is she says, if you got the dial, what would you do?
And he says, I would go back and stop my son from enlisting.
And she says, what would you tell me?
And he goes that he's going to die.
And I was like, Jesus Christ, like that shattered a super, a super moving
moment, uh, and, and it needed it.
You know, it's like, it needed that moment.
It's the most Harrison Ford has tried in an action movie in 15, 20 years.
Uh, he sells the shit out of it.
You totally believe his loss in that moment.
You understand that he lost his son, which in turn caused him to lose Marion.
But the way he describes it is like, I told Marion, you know, if we lose our son,
I'm not going to be able to stay with you.
You know, like it, even that is like completely heartless.
It's like, yeah, we, you know, pretty much knew that was going to be the end of us.
It's like, but he doesn't try and he, like, he doesn't say that though.
He says that her grief is inconsolable, but is that, is that your, well, here's
what's interesting, Pat, that you just said that he definitely phrased it in a way
on, in that scene where it's like, I knew that, you know, because she was so upset,
we were, we were gonna ruin our marriage.
You know, that, that, that to me was his tone with it.
Well, it's interesting.
Cause when I'm going to jump for a second to the end, when you see her at the end
and she says to him, I heard you were back and, and it's a play on words, meaning
both physically, but then she goes, are you back, Indy?
Meaning like, you know, as a, as a person, in that moment, you realize like, it
wasn't that she was on console inconsolable was that you were, this is the whole thing.
This is the whole, this is the whole, this is what I loved about this movie.
I'm like, this is the whole character.
Like they bring it to this place where it's like every, everything he had through his
life, like the problems with his dad, the problems, not sticking around for his son,
not even knowing about his son, not staying with one woman, running out on Marion more
than once, like all this stuff comes together in that one moment where she's
like, it's you, it's this, this is what you do.
Are you done doing this?
And you realize in that moment he is, but, um, I, I wet, I cried like a fucking baby
during both of those scenes, like, like, oh, they got me.
They just got me in the gut, man.
So, you know, uh, I'm surprised to say it, but they just, both times I
cried worse the second time.
I got to go see it.
It did not hit me in that way.
However, these are the first even attempts really at those kinds of
moments in Indiana, India, in an Indiana Jones movie.
And I think that they were beautifully done.
Uh, and when Karen Allen does come back at the end, yes, it's great.
And it is a very sweet, beautiful moment.
However, it's all the more necessary for what they did to her fucking
character in Crystal Skull, where she was an obnoxious at times, insane
woman, um, fighting with every single thing Indiana Jones said, you know, she
was more obnoxious than, than Capshaw in Temple of Doom.
Um, and for her to go out like that, it was completely unfair to both
the actors and the characters.
So they redeemed her in a big way in this one.
She said when Spielberg was involved, she was more part of the adventure in this one.
Yeah.
Uh, I think what they did was really good.
Um, I got to say, you know, speaking to the action sequences and, and a lot of
people have been massively critical of them and a lot of people have said, this
just doesn't have the Spielberg magic.
I got to be honest with you folks.
Crystal Skull, Ready Player One.
I think I mentioned this in the last episode, those movies were made
it pretty obvious Spielberg's head isn't in this genre anymore.
I don't think he could have made this movie.
I think if Spielberg had made it, it would have been another Crystal
Skull kind of movie where it would have been like, yeah, it's light and goofy,
but like, I don't know, man, he's 80 and they got him fucking jumping off
buildings and shit, you know, like, like, I like that this was man goal was like,
no, man, we're not going to make it funny that he's old.
We're going to make it real that he's old and we're going to have him do just
enough that he's heroic, but it's going to be pretty fucking realistic.
Like as far as a movie, like this is concerned.
People go.
The, the whole last act sucks.
Oh, Indy's on a plane with Nazis.
He's been captured.
He needs, he needs to be saved by her.
It's like, yes, that's what the movie's about.
The movie is about him being saved literally and figuratively.
He can't do it anymore.
Now that said, would I have liked a little moment of him outsmarting them or
something on the plane or using his brain to get out of a situation?
Sure.
But I didn't write the fucking movie.
So I'm not going to sit here and go, it should have been this.
It should have been that.
Um, the, the, I mean, thematically it's, it's Indy is luring, learn, has
learned that sometimes you've got to give control up a little bit.
You can't be in charge of every situation, especially when your physical
and mental capacities are not what they used to be.
And especially when we see how the movie ends, which was kind of frustrating to
me because I actually love the swing that they wind up back in time.
You sort of wonder why it took them so long and why they weren't time
traveling throughout because it's very fun.
Maybe they felt with all the multiverse movies, we've kind of seen that, but
they do, they go to the wrong time.
They're in what the 1500s where Archimedes is building the dial.
Like, you know, right.
And yeah, and it, you know, I felt the audience kind of like, Oh boy.
And kind of not loving it at first.
And I thought maybe they were just going to fly through and fly out, but
they spend some time there.
And I thought it was really well done.
In my mind, I was saying, Oh, what a perfect ending.
They're going to leave Indiana Jones in history.
What better ending for this man who spends his entire life looking
back and looking to the past.
However, that's not thematically on point either, because Indy is a man
who is learning in this movie that he can't stay in the past as much as he
wants to.
So when I was watching it, I thought, boy, it would be great to leave him here.
What a dream until you realize that his real prize, his real treasure is at home
in the present day with Marion.
And that is a really beautiful ending.
It's just not a super satisfying ending to the action junkies that go to these
movies, but as a wrap up to the franchise, I thought that was all really well done
too, from a story and from an emotional standpoint, everything worked to me.
I missed out on the great indie action, but not to a point that I did not like
the movie.
I think this is a very clearly the fourth best Indiana Jones and it's head and
shoulders above crystal skull.
I can't imagine anybody suggesting otherwise and a great ending to the
franchise.
It's just, to me, it wasn't perfect.
Although what is I'm just saying, I like a lot about it a lot.
And I had some things about it.
I didn't like a whole lot.
I love that I like that last scene where she's telling him he can't stay there and
he's he's going, just let me stay.
He's giving, he's giving up basically.
Yeah.
And, and, you know, and then also, yeah, he's in history, like he's going to just
be a part of history now.
And she's like, you can't stay.
And then when she starts crying and you're like, that's what I thought.
That's when I was like, this character is great.
They really brought her on a journey.
She's, I mean, look, she tries to get them killed at the beginning.
She's like, fuck you, get out of my way.
I'm trying to make money here.
I don't, you don't care about me.
She, she brings it up.
Family's never been your strong suit.
If only somebody stuck around when my father went crazy, a father figure, I
don't know, a Godfather, which he is to her.
I liked all that.
And I, and I thought it really justified why she was very much like, I
don't give a shit about you.
I love that they never once heavy handed you with I'm a woman and you can, you're
just cause you're a man and there was none of that stuff like, you know, it was
like, no, you, you're saying it without saying it.
Great.
That's what all the indie characters were awesome at.
Like the female, it can be leads were always like that.
They were strong.
They didn't have to spell it out.
And I thought that that was a smart move on their part.
And then the final scene where they call back, they call back Raiders.
Where does it not hurt?
I mean, God almighty, I was gushing, I was blubbering like a fucking, you know,
and, uh, and, and you realize his future.
Here's his future.
This is how he moves forward with Marion.
As you said, uh, so by the way, solid, we missed it, but Salah's was awesome.
Like Salah's little sequence where like he shows up and like punches,
knocks the guy out for him.
Uh, and then, you know, and, and, uh, and then brings him to his apartment in
New York and it was great seeing Salah.
The only, my only two real gripes with the movie are, and then of course,
the final shot where he, the hats on the clothes line outside and he grabs it
and pulls it in and you realize he's got his spirit.
He's, he's, he's always going to be Indiana Jones, which it's a great moment.
Um, my originally almost identical to the moment at the end of crystal skull,
where the hat flies into the shy of both hands and then he takes it back.
It's like, I could have gone for a different final moment, frankly, but okay.
I, the, the final moment I sort of fantasized about, but I think it would
have taken away from the point they were trying to make would have been Marion
driving him, you know, the museum that they've hinted at in every one of these
movies that Marcus Brody curated.
Yeah.
That was part of the, an extension of the school in Connecticut.
Like I was like, I, I was like, Oh, it'd been cool if she like took him to
that museum to show him, like, do you see like what you've done?
Do you see your worth?
And like, I was like, no, but that's not what it is because then it's her
accommodating him again, and that's not what this is.
I like that when she comes in at the end, she gives him almost zero slack.
She's like, Oh yeah, it's you, you know, like, and that's the point.
She's basically like, are you going to be different now?
And if not, just say so and let me quit, you know, wasting my life.
And she, she gives them nothing else.
Um, what was I going to say?
Uh, Oh, my two, my two gripes were, uh, I'm pissed.
He never fires his revolver.
You never get to see him.
He shoots plenty of guns in it, but he, he never shoots the classic indie revolver.
And I was sad that that never happened.
Um, yeah.
And well, that's cause in a deleted scene, he goes into the future
and he's at Columbine.
They just happened to cut that out of the move, but it
changed his whole opinion on guns.
My other gripe was, but it was very small.
I love indie and the dial of destiny.
My hog is way up.
Uh, I, I will see this movie at least once, more likely two more times in the
theater, once with my folks and once by myself, I will definitely be buying
whatever 4k package they get me to buy when it comes out, but quite happily.
And I I'm just thrilled that this character, in my opinion, got the
sendoff he deserved.
I'm glad that Lucas was involved as an executive producer.
I'm glad that Spielberg was involved as an executive producer.
I'm glad that, um, uh, who's the guy married to Kathleen Kennedy
that produced all of that?
Marshall, Frank Marshall and Kennedy, Kathleen Kennedy.
The whole team is there in one way or another.
And Mangold was, it was a great guy to step into this.
I feel like my hats off to the guy.
He made a movie that I would have said, if you showed it to me on paper, I
would have been like, Disney will never let him make this and he got it made.
And I think, honestly, I think it's because Harrison Ford has still
hold so much fucking water in Hollywood that he was like, this is what the
fuck we're doing or I'm not doing it.
And they were like, okay.
And there you go.
Yeah, it's, I mean, Mangold's masterpiece is Cop Land.
We've talked about it a million times on this show.
And it's got a lot of that same spirit of kind of taking a guy way
past his prime, full of nothing but regret.
Um, just trying to kind of go out with some quiet dignity.
And that winds up being a story that he tells really, really well.
And it works, you know, for all these reboots and, and franchises and
everything, the fact that this one is kind of a, it's not really
having its cultural moment.
There's not a lot of discussion about it.
It's, it's not a big hit.
That's a bummer, but I do think it is a movie that people will catch up
with and eventually reevaluate.
And, uh, it's extremely well done.
I enjoyed it very much.
Well, you know what I think is interesting as we close out here.
This movie, and I think I might've read this in a review somewhere, but this
movie is being treated the way the character is being treated in the
movie by the people around him.
Yeah.
Society is going, we're, we're done with this.
We're over it.
This is stupid.
Nobody cares.
Fuck this.
Da da da da.
And there are a few people out there that are going, no, man, this actually
was a really, really beautiful worthwhile thing and they did a nice job with it.
And whether you liked it a little bit or loved it like me, I think like if
you're in that camp of enjoying, of having enjoyed the movie, uh, you're on
the right side of history with the movie.
That's, that's my opinion.
And, uh, I certainly treats the character with respect.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
So anyway, folks, we'll be back with, um, uh, the, we're doing the
Pope's exorcism, Pope's exorcist, Russell Crowe, and we are doing a Renfield
starring Nicholas Cage and Nicholas Holt.
The Nicholas's, um, and we're also going to be doing the new mission impossible.
And I think that's all we know of and the new insidious.
So that's a lot coming your way.
Uh, Joe DeRosa comedy on GMA or sorry, on Instagram and, uh, Twitter, um,
and threads now folks, uh, I've got major, major tour dates coming up.
People please go to Joe DeRosa .com for all tour dates, but I am going to be
in New Jersey starting in September.
I'm going to be in New Jersey.
I'm going to be in Philadelphia.
I'm going to be in Toronto.
I'm going to be in Denver.
Uh, I'm going to be in Salt Lake city.
Uh, there's one or two others I'm blanking on, but go to Joe DeRosa .com.
That's all in the months of September, October, November, and I
think a couple were in December.
Uh, you can get all your ticket links and all that stuff on my website.
Salsa windfall.
The single is out now mouth on my money.
Thank you all for your really, really kind reception to it and enthusiasm.
It's been very heartwarming to see Paul, my bandmate and I are more than thrilled
that everybody seems to be enjoying the song it's available on all digital
platforms, full album comes out August 4th, uh, on all digital platforms.
It's called artificial birth.
And then if you're in New York, please come to Joey roses seven days a week.
Sandwiches booze the whole night.
Joey roses, NYC .com.
I didn't know the song was out.
I'll be giving it a listen myself.
I am at the Patrick Walsh on Instagram and I am also on the good Christian fun
podcast, uh, discussing the movie contact, the Robert Zemeckis, Jodie Foster,
Matthew McConaughey movie, uh, about sort of science versus faith.
That is a very, very funny conversation I had with those two.
And I urge you to check that podcast out as well.
Thank you very much, everybody.
We will be back.
We will see you next time and we will see you in hell.