Welcome to we'll see you in hell it's the podcast reviewing and discussing films I'm Joe
DeRosa and I am Patrick Walsh and this week's show will be reviewing promising young woman
who's how they used to refer to me in junior high and high school and now they don't say that anymore
about the unfortunate no no no no no what are they calling now old made yeah old made or go fish or
um ball and chain the old battle axe yeah like for sure that promising 30 year wife frequently that way
will you say to her oh the better know the ball and chain was home we haven't spoken in years
and uh it keeps you from getting in fights which I love um just a simple nod on the staircase as
we pass each other is usually how we right separate beds like Dick Van Dyke like you know
yeah the old TV shows exactly the wife I was telling you Joe uh didn't get me a Valentine's present
it's a risky risky business risky conversation and I'm like what the hell and I had all these gifts
for her and it made me feel stupid and I was like I mean we're in a pandemic but she's vaccinated
I mean she could have gone either's Amazon you know you make me a handmade card I don't care
and I was fine all day and then finally at the end I was just like you know in this quarantine every day
is the same and if something like Valentine's Day comes up you'd like to know that your wife thought of
you she the next day came through card gift she got me a bunch of different kinds of uh mustard
well what was the reason for the no gift to begin with I didn't really get an answer I mean
she was she was like well Val I hate Valentine's Day it's stupid it sucks blah blah and I'm like
that may be baby right but um you know it's just like okay so let's say I don't I she honestly wouldn't
have said a word if I didn't get her anything for Valentine's Day but it's like I can't say you
know Valentine's Day is stupid well you can't it sounds like I guess I could I mean I I asked
I asked her are you you're saying going forward we'll just stop celebrating Valentine's Day because I'm
fine with that right and she was like no no I'll get you a present I'll get you a present but um
dad you not in the celebrated in the past we've celebrated every time in the past she's usually a great
gift giver it wasn't a forgetting about it like in a in a sitcom or something I think it was just
sort of a fuck you to me the husband rash move just owning it too I love that she's just
owning it it was wild it was wild but um it's a wild time you know yeah I uh I got myself a little
something what'd you get I did I did a whole act out you know like oh my well who are these candies
from two sides of conversation you know it's it's it was a sad scene it was real sad you got yourself
the plastic tube full of M &Ms with the little stuffed bear on top yeah I I made a huge meal for myself
on Valentine's Day okay and I think my mom thought my mom was like did you spend Valentine's Day with
anybody I said no and I could tell she that made her sad and I was like mom it's fine like you know
nobody's really around and it's it's okay yeah and she goes would you do and I go I made a huge meal
and then I had to quickly be like because it was Sunday not because it was Valentine's like I have
to clarify all this right mom or she thinks I'm doing it to to to to to create a you know to fill the
void of the you know she doesn't know I have the humans I stuffed doll for that sure sure yeah
may I fed some of the meal to her like Jane is her name now does she have the parts the necessary
or a fun friend doll we're just friends okay but you know she's there when I need her
nah I think I know what that means if you fuck the dolls mouth Jeff it doesn't have a mouth
it's for jacking off isn't it from the film 10 to midnight uh yeah uh how is New York is it bouncing
back is it uh I mean I I went for a walk yesterday around LA and it might as well have been
28 days later out there there's no one here no one out we're at 25 % indoor dining again as I said on
the other episode um on the VFW episode we also uh movie theaters are reopening you can go inside
places again our stores and stuff never shut down on when the second shutdown happened stores and
barber shops and places like that all stayed open the only things that shut down where it was just
indoor dining so you couldn't sit inside any bars you couldn't sit inside any restaurants uh and the
movie theaters have never opened so everything is getting slowly back to normal vaccination sites are
all over the city um they're widening the net of who is able to get them and who counts as an essential
worker so you know it's getting easier by the day but it is taking time also the rapid testing
game here is on point like you can yeah you can get tested whatever so you're able to kind of work
around this situation and have some semblance of a normal life um I have friends now who are vaccinated
and I have friends uh who are able to easily get rapid tested so you know look you're not having parties
but you can you can see people and it's safe and normal sure uh and now the weather is getting normal
too we're back into the low 50s high 40s weather we're getting sunnier days
you know it's it's it's starting to feel like a city again so you know fingers crossed we continue on
in that direction and that's it okay yeah California new thing is that they were all worried about the
new variant which was much more contagious than harmful and then they announced they were like this
is coming to LA it's worse than it was before it's gonna be bad and then they were like actually the
variant has become the top strain of coronavirus in Los Angeles which is somehow being played off as a
good thing but now apparently we're the one of the only cities in the country where this mysterious
strain from across the pond is like prevalent so we're saying it popped up in New York now too I mean
luck yeah I am a believer in the pandemic and I believe in staying safe and cautious but you know
some of this a lot of the news that goes along with it I think is sensationalized and meant to
keep this manic energy going of you know like and I feel like these variant stories are
the news related to them is changing so rapidly that I'm like you know you can't help but be like
is this just to kind of keep the whole panic thing going as things are getting better uh you know
and why would they want to because then that's good for news good money yeah I mean then bad news
is good news you know so it's like sure and that's what we you know I was a hard -nosed uncompromising
reporter for many years and that was our slogan yeah well when they started it was Woodward Bernstein
and Derosa but your your anti -Semitic remarks got you edged out of that team not not out of the
edward never had a problem it was Bernstein of course of course but you know the card in the fedora
and the side of the door sure I didn't that's me I invented that right I thought that was uh
fuzzy bear and uh great muppet -caper no it was me I did this kermit and fuzzy and jack warden was
their boss at the paper I used to love that I used to think when I watched great muppet -caper the jack
warden was my grandpa when I was a kid I was like that's grandpa my parents were like wrong with you
no jack warden looks and talks exactly like my dad's dad but um my parents would be like no that's
beloved character actor jack warden now let me pitch okay let me pitch you something as we talk
about a movie where humans mix in with fake things okay can we review do you want to review
tom and jerry on this podcast because I am dying to see what a train wreck this thing is and also
how they are justifying that two cartoon animals are running around in real life I mean after
Roger rabbit you can't do it like that anymore no Roger rabbit was like no we're gonna establish that
there's a place called tune town and it'll make sense it's like you can't just now have cartoon
a cartoon at mouth let's call it now we'll do tom and jerry next time I was not planning on watching
it but let's do tom and jerry let's promise to watch it together okay maybe probably in shifts because
I don't think I'm doing a whole two hour tom and jerry I don't as I get runs two hours I think it's
probably about 87 minutes and it's got a hot 23 % on rotten tomatoes that's what made me want to do it
I didn't know what the vibe was on it but I haven't read many reviews of the film but as I text to
Joe there was an interview with the director Tim story the guy who did like barber shop and stuff and he
said you know it's not you know man against man anymore we're doing this like it's sibling rivalry
so I said well there are a cat in a mouse how are they siblings now what the fuck are you talking about
so I think it's going to be either their friends from the jump which will be maddening or they
become friends by the end which will also be maddening it's going to be like in that fucking three
stooges movie and I don't think the far the fairly brothers did this I think the studio made them do
this but like they had the scene in them in like the third act where you realize mo actually loves his
brothers and you're like what are you doing yeah what is this yep it's oh god it's going to suck
yeah the one review I said it said it was missing all of the anarchy of the old cartoons
it's in scratchy on the Simpsons which they've been doing since the dawn of the show like how they
brutally murdered each other every week some of those were disturbing when I was like a grown grown man
but um why wouldn't Tom and Jerry then go okay we can still keep a little bit of the edge I mean
we've seen what a a graphic violent version of this is we know they're not going that route
but what kid wants to watch a cat in a mouse be pals you know well and that's and that was one of the
one of the things I tipped my hat to the new looney tunes cartoons on was I was like okay at least
they're still doing horrific things to each other on sure but I like that I like that they kept
that aspect of it I mean it's just it's just nuts man it's just nuts I I will send this to you
after the show Joe and I when I I know sometimes you recommend things on this show and it's like watch
them or don't I don't care but this is a must you're gonna have to google it and find it but it's a
30 second video clip called Tom game cold as fuck bro like Tom's game hitting on women is impressive
is the translation Tom game cold as f bro and it is a guy doing a commentary on like what a
player Tom is when he's hitting on a woman the cat the cat and this thing is hitting on a female cat
okay and it's just a 30 second clip of Tom and Jerry with this hilarious dude commenting on like
how impressed he is with Tom's game and I this cannot be oversold I mean I watched this again and
again and again and added it to like my permanent things I can look at on my phone if I need a quick
cheer up check out Tom game cold as fuck bro all right I'll check it out but yeah we'll do Tom and
Jerry it's on the max what else does HBO Max have coming they did this big thing like we got every new
a new huge movie every week so like when is doom uh I don't know well the next big one is uh you
know and I'm sorry you're already committed to it on air but Justice League is is dropping in about two
weeks four hour Justice League the producer of the movie said watch it in four parts like okay he's
getting out ahead of it and be like don't don't try to do this all at once this is crazy yeah I read a
big interview are a very big article this week that I I'm sure came into your field of vision
as well but it was um it made me like the man a lot more I mean that he's obviously had a very
tragic time the past several years uh Snyder but there was a great article that went into what went wrong
on Justice League what happened with Whedon um you know Christopher Nolan and this guy's wife apparently
went in and saw Whedon's Justice League and we're like you must never watch this don't watch this movie
promise us and uh you know I love behind the scene shit that's a great article to read let me get the
the magazine for you yeah I'm excited for it um you know I'm always I've always been a DC guy I did
start watching Juan division I haven't watched enough yet to give any sort of review but yeah I
mean I'm enjoying it so far like it's it's a weird premise but I don't know that's all I can
really say right now I don't really know how it's gonna unfold but um but I'm a DC guy at heart and
I I you know I don't need to say it anymore like I you know where I stand with this stuff so I'm
excited for this Snyder cut um I'm curious to see what he does with it uh it sounds like it's
gonna be very watchman -esque um and I didn't really love watchman but watchman with characters I
actually am interested in uh yeah okay no I want to see it the article was in vanity fair it's called
Zack Snyder's Justice League colon the true story of the Snyder cut if you have any interest in this at all
I obviously don't care and I still found it a great well -written article so check it out
Juan division you know obviously we don't give a shit about Marvel too much in the show I don't
give a shit about any of it um but I try every time I sit down this one I was excited about because
I was like it's I heard it was like I'll also a history of the sitcom and um that intrigued me but
I I made it one and a half episodes it was playing to me like a very bad 100 year old multi -cam sitcom
where the jokes didn't hit the plot didn't hit whatever I was supposed to be getting out of it from
a Marvel standpoint made no sense to me so I guess I'll continue you know but as of right now I
I don't know what I'm even looking at I'm I'm baffled by the thing and I don't know why they would do
two episodes in this old black and white format because they didn't do anything good with it I think
it's just obviously you know going to be they're living in a fake reality they've created or something
and then it'll slowly be explained but right and I'm assuming I never read the comics so I'm assuming
this is a nod to something they did in the comic books at some point I don't know but um is Wanda
a character in the Marvel universe? Yeah yeah she's uh she's scarlet witch and her name is Wanda
in real life I guess her real name is Wanda yeah I never knew that okay all right uh interesting and I
know uh you know my old pal cat Denny's in it which I love I'm a big fan of her and is she playing her
Thor character or a new character no no she's the the the lady from Thor interesting all right cool
so yeah I'll finish it up um news psycho sort of relating to this uh Jezebel ran an article about
the new mortal combat trailer which finally dropped looks pretty good pretty good yeah uh mortal
combat trailer nice and violent nice and crazy look look looking like they did the characters a lot
of justice looking like they're actually sticking to the mythology that created in the video games which
is pretty cool um I don't know why the main character is a character they made up I'm assuming there's
going to be some reveal that he's actually Johnny Cage or something like that yeah because Johnny Cage
is not featured in the movie apparently so whatever we'll wait and see but the movie looks pretty good
but the new psycho is about the fact that Jezebel ran a trailer or ran an article written by a
supposed fan of the mortal combat series who was complaining that Chun Lee was nowhere to be found
in the trailer uh Chun Lee is of course of the street fighter franchise yeah he even had a street fighter
movie called Chun Lee so uh it's one of those things and then they ran a retraction like whoops sorry
the wrong franchise ha ha ha and it's like look is this hard hitting news no but it's like guys can
you be a little responsible with what you're printing you know if you're not confident you you have to
you in this day and age when you have google for something like that it's just unacceptable I mean like
they weren't trying to be the deadline on this fucking story it's unacceptable and then like the way
the article was written it was written very like snappy and colorfully so as you're reading the
original article you're even like I can't tell if this woman is I well I shouldn't even say woman
whoever wrote it I'm I'm shortsightly assuming woman because it's Jezebel but I know they have
male writers too but I was assuming the person who wrote it uh was a fan and then as you read it
you're like wait are they mocking mortal combat like uh because this movie to me kind of represents
everything that an outlet like Jezebel would not like you know this seems to be very much in the
way also toxic toxic masculinity and yeah each other's arts out the thing and they're also pointing out
that Chun Lee the female hero is not to be seen uh and against because she's in a different franchise um
but I guess what might take away of that was it just bothers me that in all news right now whether
it's entertainment or political reporting or whatever it's like retractions are just a thing now it's
just like you know what I mean like retractions used to kind of be the the safety net like oh shit
we fucked up we thought we vetted this we made a mistake sorry yeah supposed to be an occasional
thing it's become the norm you know now where it's like no just get it out there and we'll just say sorry
later which is I think good little by little people are and I was talking about this for my buddy the
other day when I go out at night like when I can't take being the house anymore and I go for an hour
long drive generally capped off by eating a sandwich while parked in the dark but um I find that people
are very slowly losing their minds they're going insane so I know that I myself am at my worst
mental health level I've been in in quite some time I wake up some days I don't want to get out of bed
you know some days I wake up and I'm hey I'll go run a mile you know I'm all over the place I don't
know what's going on and I think that a lot of people are suffering with the indoors especially
people who are alone I luckily have a wife it's it's a very different ballgame I know I'm not complaining
but I see people you know will drift across five lanes slowly like unaware that they're just
nearly getting hit by five lanes of traffic people doing crazy ship I see out what you're talking
about with the writing like all these retractions it's an hourly thing like oh we said the completely
wrong deal sorry about that it's obviously not just Jezebel and obviously it happens with much bigger
issues like our our about our our government our world you know and people are just printing things
that don't add up and I think what it amounts to is that everybody is doing their job at about
40 percent during the pandemic I think everybody is doing their worst work they're not focusing
their brains are all over the place I'm not making an excuse for anyone especially in the journalism
world but I think there's a lot more of people trying to write an article while two babies in a cat
climbs all over them you know and the quality of everything is is suffering for sure and people are
suffering I'll tell you New York has always been a place you know that I that I thought you could
set your drink on when it came to customer service you know you got your food fast you got your
drinks fast you created a rapport usually with the server or the bartender whatever
it is really really dipped yeah because the people that are going back to work I'd imagine it
kind of feels like I'm stuck working everybody else is sitting home right now yeah I can't imagine
when indoor dining opens again in LA what the site of that is going to be I mean when things were
perfect you were waiting 45 minutes to get eggs yeah you know I can't I mean LA is the other place I've
ever been where you'd say to a bartender after 15 minutes like hey could I get those beers and
and they'll literally say like can you just calm down actually like you know what I mean like it's not
like sorry about that yeah we started at a very low low low low base customer service wise and I mean
I am I could not be more understanding if a place takes a long time during the pandemic but it is
that like if I go up to get a sandwich which usually a sandwich let's be honest every time it's like
hey I'm just checking in and I'll wait forever I'll do it like at the 20 minute mark because I'm like
I'm not doing anything what do I care yeah and you know I think people are just really scatterbrained
I do my best to be to be cool with people even people who are being an asshole I'm just like I get
it man I mean what what a nightmare but yeah it's it's a crazy time in terms of Jezebel I wrote
an article about Mortal Kombat called how can they rip the hearts out of men they don't have them yes
I you know I should say Jezebel is a fun site to make fun of but I always read Jezebel I love that
they challenge me on shit I love that they take big opinion swings even if I don't agree with them
I find myself more and more reading the opinions of people that I just don't agree with and I think
it's because I got addicted to anger throughout the election that's a good thing to do it's good to
read opposing opinions yeah not enough people do that anymore yeah it's a very important part of life
informing your opinions and perspectives it's you know it's it's almost like we should be listening to one
another sure but anyway you know I think people are trying to transfer because you can't even see
or hear Trump anymore which is great of course but he's he's he's off the map I mean we if he wants
to say something to the world they don't get the information and what I feel from like Twitter
and beyond is that people are like I need somewhere to put my hate and that person very quickly
stepped forward and his name is Ted Cruz I mean he's the new what a hate hateful hateable
piece of shit that guy is but yeah it's it's weird you can get so addicted to anger and hate and I
my fear my concern is that everyone is in that place and that when society does sort of open up
that big door it's just gonna be bad you know it's gonna be bad nothing's gonna get better it's gonna
be terrible no it's it's and look there's also a blame addiction so yeah you know I'll say this
Trump is like booze you know it's it's really easy to to pinpoint certain behaviors and
truths and realities on this this thing that was muddying the the perspective and and in the outlook
of everything for so long and then once it's out of the picture it's like okay now we don't have
people that are not going to be able to come to terms with oh I'm just fucked up like I have
things I need to work out in myself here and that's that frightens me but well this a long time
forces people to look at themselves you know like I mean it does and it's not good you know it's I
don't like what I'm saying I know there's many more that don't like what they're saying but it's just
like so come to terms with it and deal with it and and and and become better I mean that's the
thing everybody loves to say do better nobody wants to do better you know right so you know man
it's anyway let's let's let's let's get over to the movie corner sure sure
Joe you want to start you got one handy I'm gonna do three sitcoms all right I'm gonna start with
the best all right I finally watched news radio I'd never watched a news radio the whole thing
I wasn't able to see the whole thing but I was able to stream season one season four
and season five two and three weren't available for streaming I'm eventually just gonna buy it
because I want to see the whole show you can hold the whole series for 20 bucks yeah so um but
I'll focus particularly on season one uh it's great it's hilarious it's you know it's another one
of these multi -cams like everybody loves Raymond or Seinfeld where it's just the entire cast
ensemble is at the top of their game everybody is hitting home home run everybody's carrying their way
and uh and it's original within three minutes of the pilot you know who almost every character it's
just so well written it's so strongly written uh and it just reminded me of what sitcoms are
able to be when they try and when you don't have a million people sticking their fingers into it
and ruining it right um well and and NBC famously hated that show and wanted it off the air because
they thought nobody on it was likable and that was a young dude Paul Sims who now does Atlanta and
you know is very much still a big player in Hollywood but that is one of the all -time great multi -cam
sitcoms it was very well reviewed very well liked and NBC just made his life miserable every day
they said we're like what are you doing we hate this it is 12 perfect characters played by the perfect
people amazing jokes amazing relationships heart without it ever feeling like heart I mean
you're rooting for fully and more attorney more than almost any other sitcom couple than like Sam and
Diane and yet they never lean into schmaltz or even a little bit of that you wouldn't you wouldn't buy
it from day fully you've seen kids in the hall you know that's not where he operates from it really
feels like two people who are living in the real world who are falling in love with each other and
who have big problems as well yeah I mean you're you're like an episode two when when fully and uh
tyranny have sex right you know and it's like you know it doesn't get into I just like that it doesn't
get into but he's the boss that's not appropriate or she's this and that's not appropriate it just
gets into it's gonna get messy you guys you guys have to work together and you know that they respect one
another you know that they actually like one another and it's just about that and it's about why
it's hard to date somebody that you work with yeah it's a great show fill heart man you know what a
what a swan song for that guy I mean you know it's it's a bittersweet reminder that he's gone far too
soon that's his finest hour did you see the episode where he gets the cane no it's not in no that is
that is the highlight of the show if you see the boba fed episode with the poker game no yeah
I really think two and three are the highlights I gotta get yeah I'll get I'll get the whole series
but I did see the episode where he gets a butler yes had berry played by mr. what's his face from
Seinfeld Elaine's boss oh right yeah mr. Pitt yeah mr. Pitt it's it's a it's a great show it's a great
show they and you know it's it's impossible to think of it now but like NBC at the time was like HBO
like they're sitcoms the reason they were able to get the best people to be on this show is because
like that was the crown was an NBC sitcom so what you're gonna enjoy as you watch through it Joe and
anyone else who wants to get it is that almost every guest star as it goes is played by an awesome
comedy person you know so like they're actually Dennis Miller has a great episode in it David
Cross Odin Kirk you know but it's it's really it goes through like the history of comedy with
their guest stars it's such a great show I saw the cross Odin Kirk one with the barbershop quartet
that was great yeah that was great news radio you can play several different people love it's
coming in like three different guest star roles and then becomes a cast member and then takes over
the show yeah how was that season five with love it's was it okay I didn't get to it yet okay I got
to be honest it's I'm enjoying Hartman so much it's almost like I'm avoiding finishing season four
because you're just like man I don't want it because I do remember when they did the episode that
starts season five where the character where his he's died in real life and then he also died on
the show and you're just like it's really sad yeah I'm like I don't want to and I read a thing about
it where it was like the cast was crying they had to keep stopping takes and stuff I was like I
yeah I don't want to I don't want to get it's it's the reason I haven't
watched the documentary about Patrice yet the comedy central did because I'm just like you guys
one of my closest friends it's like right I'm it's too sad right now I don't want to I don't want to
I don't want to go down that road of loss you know yeah it is a great documentary when you do get
around to it but yeah I mean it's amazing I find myself dodging super depressing shit now lately as
well news radio the complete series available on Amazon right now for $20 probably just buy it
you can also buy the first season second third fourth and fifth for $20 each if you'd rather go
that Amazon make some sense once in a while we me Jo and I have been talking all week about the
pathetic fucking deals they have at Amazon like I mean are they hurting financially over there
just horrible deals I mean we ratio hornblower the complete season two on DVDs like one of their deals
yeah which I were which I described to you as a slap in the face it is personally insulted by that
it is yeah and then yeah and then it's like shout factory on special and then it's like the welcome
back codder which I love welcome back codder but it's like the entire series is four dollars off
and yeah not even a good deal you're like eighty five dollars for four seasons of yeah
yeah so I saw folks a documentary on Netflix called Crip Camp colon a disability revolution
which you know a Barack Obama and Michelle Obama produced this movie and I cannot believe
they allowed their names to be put in a movie called Crip Camp I'm not saying I'm bothered by it
I'm saying wow like I mean how did their people not go yeah you're gonna have to change that title
anyway uh this was a really charming documentary that was not at all what I expected I think the
Obama's producing it made me expect something very sanitized and very uh hokey I guess
I love the Obama's but I just I didn't imagine that they they would be putting their
their names on a project like this because it's really edgy and kind of weird um it is about
a camp in the early 70s that was down the street from Woodstock the famous festival
and a revolution blossomed there as well it's a camp for disabled teenagers um some of them have really
extreme uh speech issues motion issues uh they're in wheelchairs they you know really extreme handicaps
down to sort of milder ones and I found this uh really entertaining I mean they they're dirty and they
let them be dirty like they're they're just like are you know I the one girls I I want to
impression of these people but she's like I I wanted to you know she's talking in this extremely
affected voice and it's telling the story about how this guy was driving her
down the street once and she was like you know I just sort of felt like I was gonna die soon and I
didn't want to die a virgin so I just fucked him this is a deeply handicapped girl who was
fucking a non handicapped guy who's driving the car and she's basically like I just sort of spread
my legs and said hey I don't want to die a virgin and the story is treated like a charming anecdote
and look I I'll just say that's what I enjoyed about it I enjoyed that they were not cleaning up
the stories good yeah um these people lived sexual lives and why shouldn't they you know well yeah it's
cool it's a cool little movie um moving touching I liked it who does to you for not doing the vocal
impression I don't think you needed to do the physical impression but I'm not doing it you know
I'm doing like that what's that sign felt weird he does the impression of the guy stopping on
the floor and then he thinks he's making fun of his handicapped remember that it's the commercial
sign told her is it uh oh oh oh the wind or not the wind not the wind the uh the crazy it's like
the crazy Eddie guy yeah yeah the discounts on what he thinks they're making fun of his yeah his
footfalls asleep right right yeah uh all right I will go now to the worst of the sitcoms
that I experienced in the last few weeks head of the class which is coming to you from HBO Max or
remake yes uh what can I say I put it on because I just wanted some as I keep saying on episode
of the episode escapist television to watch by the way if everybody remembers when Pat said on the last
episode or two episodes ago how he does he's off alcohol completely and he's drinking a beer right
now it's uh it's true uh so anyway this is why I scoffed when he goes I'm off booze uh yeah
well somebody left this in my fridge at some point I guess somebody came over so I'm like all right
I'll do it uh I I put it on because I just wanted to see a simple show and I was like you know what
there's there's some similarities here this is sort of the anti welcome back coder uh and and maybe
it's shaves a little more closely to that show than I ever realized as a kid um and I love Howard
Hesseman I really am just a sucker for that guy I don't know what it is about him but I love him um
okay look it's not a good show it's not a terrible show I mean you want to talk terrible
it's a cookie cutter sitcom I also re -watched alf alf is a fucking disgrace I mean it is it is an
abomination was obsessed with it so was I as a kid but I mean it's it's terrible I read recently
about alf because of the puppet they didn't they could never shoot in front of an audience so they
would just do take after take after take with no audience there and like it was just fucking miserable
and whatever so alf is a is atrocious it should never have happened it should not have lasted as long
as it did it should not have spawned a movie and then a talk show alf does not deserve to be an
comic book franchise and comic book and cartoon two cartoons two yep alf does not deserve any and
bouillabais ball cards which I collected every one of the uh a soup joke for kids he's an atrocious
character everybody on the show sucks the show sucks he hates willy max fry he's the only one
that I sort of kind of like but yeah he's even tainted himself he would have breakdowns every day
and scrant there's there's footage apparently of him choking the puppet yeah he forgets and loses
himself and chokes the puppet you know I just I haven't revisited it but I certainly love it back
yeah it's terrible head of the class is more just a paint by numbers sitcom that doesn't do anything
to do it to reinvent the wheel however then this is the reason I wanted to bring it up it is still
10 times edgier than any sitcom out right now which is pathetic yeah it's pathetic that a show about
a high school class of gene geniuses and every joke is like kind of like a nerd joke about history
or something and then like the problems on the show are like the the 12 year old super genius wants
to have a party and the older kids aren't having fun because she's 12 and doesn't have to throw a
party this is the show that still makes like call me cat makes this look like they're doing the
sopranos it's insane yeah that and call your mother holy shit Joe and I have actually talked
off air a lot about these programs and holy shit something gang something else anyway
so arvand is the like aggressive nerd the screech right I'm just going off my memory yeah
but he's way more likeable than screech and then Dennis is the big fat guy who later went on to
the last all kinds of children on Nickelodeon Dennis Blondon is the man yeah that we're on
nighter who allegedly has has you know I don't want to be legally proper here allegedly I'm gonna
I'm gonna be inappropriate you consume me I'm gonna take the allegedly off it I know I've spoken to
people oh well I haven't but I don't want to know anything I don't need to end up with a 22 bullet
behind my ear no I mean there's been documentaries killed by that guy's law team and I didn't know
the hanging out hanging by a thin thread the other guy though went on to be a decent the kid that
plays like the tough kid who doesn't want to be there but he's he's brilliant so he has to be he
he also is a Nickelodeon guy but he's clean you know he hasn't okay you know he I think is a decent guy
I think and then he went on the that was Daniel Dale Lewis right he became beloved actor Daniel
Dale Lewis so and then you know Hesmond leaves eventually in the last season and then Billy
Connolly comes in I haven't gotten that far yet but yeah I remember watching those as part of TGIF
I think at the class I always saw in reruns but I remember I liked Billy Connolly I thought he was a
step up actually I remember liking him and I'm a fan but I was sad to see Hes I love I loved Hesmond
as a kid because the police academy too I still love him you know I just I don't know just a big fan
of that guy folks I watched crime scene colon the vanishing at the Cecil hotel I'm doing all Netflix
documentaries this week and this is one of the worst I've seen it's really really bad it's pretty
unanimous that everyone just thinks it sucks and what I do think is happening I talked about this
when I discussed the vow is that people know that everyone is trapped at home and desperate for
entertainment and I think they're extending these things they're going back to and this is all speculation
but I think they're going back to these people and saying hey how much you got the cutting room floor
and they're like six hours of footage they're like okay let's put five it on the air as episodes
like stuff that just shouldn't be in there and isn't interesting and who cares so this is by Joe
Burlinger who is one of the greatest modern documentary directors he did the three movies about
paradise lost the you know I love all those he well he made his narrative directorial debut with
book of shadows Blair Witch 2 which is why he went back to documentaries horrific but it is he did
Metallica some kind of monster which is one of the true great documentaries and is probably
respond as as responsible as sopranos for like getting guys to go to therapy and talk about shit
getting that kind of guy to go to therapy anyway Burlinger has lost his touch or they forced him to do
this and stretch it out against its will or what but it doesn't work at all the first one works it's
about this woman named Elise Lam who was a young girl who was visiting Los Angeles she stayed at
this hotel and was never seen again the last video footage of her is her it's the elevator one
I remember seeing that video online right she's in the elevator it looks like she's talking to somebody
she's like waiting for the elevator to go up but it doesn't there's something that there's a mysterious
quality about it and she was never seen again and they also never saw her leave the hotel so like
they're like she's here but we don't know where she is her parents come in you know they're traumatized
everybody's traumatized there's some suspects and it's all great you're like okay well let's see
where this goes and then for the next three hours it's that room 237 that fucking shining
documentary where it's just a bunch of crackpots telling you what they think might have happened
and this is why I didn't watch this so it's like it's gonna be a bunch of people theorizing
it is and it sucks I mean there's some like kind of gruesome highlights there's this like 20 -year -old
couple that comes here from overseas and there's the thing at the hotel and they describe like how
the water tasted terrible and they were like this hotel sucks and then they come to find out
that the girl was actually in the water supply her body is in the hotel's water supply and they've
all been just like drinking it Jesus God so look there's some like gruesome details like that that's
why there's grosses that is that's why you come to these true crime documentaries is for
juicy shit horrifying shit like that there's a few of those moments and it's it would be gross
of me to complain that it's not salacious or juicy enough I just don't think it's a good documentary
it's it's boring and me listening to people theorize is not a documentary I'm not being told anything
that's it's why I don't like that guys docs he did one on um the theory that we're all living in
a simulation that I just saw at Sundance and I didn't like that one either he just lets these people talk
about whatever crazy shit they believe and it's like that's entertaining to some degree but at the end
of the day it's just I could go to a bar and hear crackpots talk about what shit they believe I don't
it's not a documentary to me it's just kind of look at these freaks and I don't like them
I will close my segment side of the movie corner out with a third sitcom that I think falls
in between the two I've discussed uh the crew on Netflix starring Kevin James and my good friend
Dan Adute uh new sitcom uh is it great no is it edgy no uh but does it take the uh is it better than
what's out there now as far as multi -cams are concerned absolutely 100 % and is it a throwback to that
sort of classic straight up just it's funny sitcom thing that King of Queens was yes yes it does
is it is as good as King as King of Queen no not not at all but but it's an enjoyable show it's a fun show
Kevin I like it because Kevin James is basically playing that character again
and there's a lot of food jokes a lot of fat jokes uh and I don't know I just like it and I thought
it actually did take a kind of interesting commentary on the whole woke versus old school thing
it's about up a crew for NASCAR getting taken over by the owner the owner the owner steps down who's
like a good old boy and his daughter takes over and she's you know she's from Stanford and she's into
marketing and business building and she's very woke and she wants to replace the driver with a female
driver and whatever and I and I think it hits the that discussion from both sides fairly well and it
makes both sides it exposes the flaws and the and the attributes of both sides of that of the that
discussion so it's a fun show it made me laugh a few times uh each episode had a couple laughs that
you know whatever and it was it was a fun escape for me I just enjoy it I like Kevin James and I like
when he's making food jokes uh call me simple but uh I hear it but I enjoyed it there's a there's a
joke where he's eating cake that he says I think that cake made us all sick yesterday because the because
he forgot to refrigerate it and then like you know he's having a discussion and mid discussion it cuts
back to him and he's eating cake and the girl's like isn't that the cake that made us all sick and he
you know what all right and he goes yeah at this point I'm building up a tolerance
all right I like that yeah that's like a funny like you know that's a care queen show
so uh I enjoyed it all right fair enough got out to my buddy Pete Corrielli one of the funny
stand -ups out there he works on the show so and always good to see Danny a dude and stuff Dan's
Dan plays um the uh salesman on um Cobra Kai as well he plays the head salesman that helps uh Daniel
out I've met the other guy a couple times Brett Ernst yeah that's great he was he killed one night at
the improv I saw him uh funny guy great set my last documentary is called fake famous is actually not
on Netflix it was on HBO Max um if you've been noticing it on the app it's the hot pink one it's it
just kept catching my eye and I was like I'll check this out what's fake famous all about it is uh another
really bad documentary it's it's got an interesting premise which is where they're going to take three
people and give them a bunch of Instagram followers and see how their life changes you know see how
that kind of fake fame of like buying yourself a bunch of bots a bunch of followers can can change your
life and does it change your life and is it positive or is it negative sure great interesting setup for
documentary the movie two of the three people don't wind up doing this they they bail they're like I
don't like where this is going and they get out before it even starts to get kind of interesting
and in my mind then you don't have a documentary a documentary in its purest form is I'm stating
a hypothesis or a theory just like a science experiment and then you show us you prove it to us or you
don't or whatever this is like here's what we're gonna do okay that's step one two of the three people
didn't do it okay well then you don't have a step two which is the most important part of a
fucking documentary you don't have one so in my mind when two of your three subjects don't agree to
go forward with what the documentary is about you have to recast you have to start over you've lost
that footage and all these documentaries these days are shot using iPhones or cheap cameras or drones
more and more just start over that they two thirds of a 90 minute documentary is focusing on people who
don't wind up doing this experiment so I I was blown away at the laziness on display here it
seemed like he had a deadline at HBO Max and he went in it was like look I don't have a finished film
here what do you think of this and they're like yeah we'll just throw it up that that's how lazy
and like just almost rude to the audience it seems you have to start over when two people don't do the
experiment you you don't have a documentary so then by the end the pandemic hits and then 20 minutes
of the documentary is taken up with like generic shit about we all remember where we were on March 8th
and I'm like this is supposed to be about social media you idiots it has no focus it is it is
terribly done and usually I think I would not say this to the filmmaker I would say all this to
the filmmaker I think he should be ashamed that he got this opportunity and did this because it isn't
a finished film out enough well I'll tell you what is a finished film pat yeah promising young woman
today's feature sure I'd like to start nice I'd like to start by saying Emerald Fennel the writer and
director of the film and and a fantastic job she also ran season two of killing Eve which is a show I
like but I want to start this by admitting to you folks that a few days ago I looked up Emerald Fennel
on Twitter and I saw that she was following me that was pretty cool holy shit how long has this woman
been following me so I followed her and then today I go to her page and see that she unfollowed me
oh she's one of those she might have been following me for five years now the second I click she's
out yeah that's that's that's a that's a strategy you you follow a big fish with a lot of followers
and then they follow you back and then you drop you just follow people to get the followers back
would the director of this movie need to do that at this point in her career and Jesus Christ you're
you're shocked that that that somebody's strategizing in in Hollywood uh it hurt my feelings but I'm
not trying to try not to take that into this review because I did I do think she did a great job I mean
it's and alarmingly similar Emerald Legosi followed me in real life not in on Twitter wasn't that
catchphrase bam yeah bam bam Margera's catchphrase was Emerald I like this through the plot Joe walk
us through the plot well it's it's a movie about a woman who has she has experienced something traumatic
and tragic relating to men it's very obvious that that's the case uh but but before you even get to that
sorry uh she's she there's a one she's drunk in a club she's in coherent she can barely walk a bunch
of creepy guys are saying they want to help her get home one of them does sell then he gets her home
and then tries to have sex with her when she's in coherent so it's a date rape situation uh and then
all of a sudden she comes to and you realize she's not drunk she's faking it and this was a setup of
some kind in boom title screen and what you learn immediately in the film is she has experienced something
tragic regarding involving men you're not quite sure what it is yet you're assuming it's rape or
something like that uh and that she this is her pastime now she pretends to be black out drunk in
a club so a guy can take her home so then she can show the guy I was tricking you in your piece of
shit is she killing them is she torturing them is she blackmailing them you don't know they don't
reveal any of that up front um in the midst of all this you eventually learn that what happened and
why she's doing this is not because of something that happened directly to her it's because of
something that happened to her best friend in college um and she did not go with her best friend to
this frat house or something where the best friend was blacked out drunk and was fucked by several
guys while she was unconscious uh the trauma of that led the best friend to suicide and now this is the
woman's reckoning in dealing with this uh and that is played out in conjunction with her being
pursued by a guy she went to college with that she rekindles a friendship with played by bow burnum
and um and you know will she be able to love again will she be able to ever trust a man again
we get into all those themes um and that's that's basically right is it by missing anything?
no that's the just i mean it's a lot of twists and turns from there um but it does keep you
throughout in a state of not really knowing what's going on and so there's going to be spoilers here
when we talk but the for me the most unsettling use of that were these these two back -to -back scenes she
goes to lunch with her old friend Alison Brie who's drinking way too much and she she knows that
she's gonna drink a lot and carry Mulligan by the way i don't think i said it was played by carry
Mulligan i apologize who's great she's great but um yeah she sits down with Alison Brie and Alison Brie
winds up drinking way too much and Mulligan goes over to this guy and you leave that scene thinking
that carry Mulligan has just convinced this guy to go rape the unconscious body of the brie
character as some sort of revenge because brie didn't have her back when she was assaulted in college
but you're sort of putting all this together when your friend was insulted yeah brie yeah because
brie says like hey you know i don't know what you want us to do like if you get blackout drunk and you
have sex all the time nobody's gonna believe you when something bad happens which is this thing which
is an argument that people make you know this this really does get into the nitty gritty of
of the uncomfortableness of the different perspectives in this discussion right um really i should
it's probably better work yeah but you leave that scene thinking that this person who you're like okay
it's cool that she's you know beating up guys or or playing around with guys who are scum and trying
to rape or date rape and and i like this character but when she is setting up what appears to be a
rape of Alison Brie to punish her for not having her friends back years ago then you're like oh okay
i don't know if i like this character at all this person is a psychopath where how could you think
that's that that's a deserving punishment for this woman then it goes directly into a scene where she
picks up this young girl on the street or you know she's 15 or something and then goes into her mom
who's played by the great Connie Britain from Friday night lights and basically tells her your
daughter's being raped because the Connie Britain character was Dean at the time when this sexual
assault took place and she didn't have the back of her friend she she so you're like so now the
kid got to graduate and everything they dismiss the the act right so now it's like okay well your
punishments are not fitting the crimes anymore i mean uh these women didn't these women did terrible
things do they deserve to be raped or have their daughter be raped that's where the movie becomes super
dark you know it's it's dark from the jump but where to me you know i watched with my wife and we
are like what are we watching here but to a kind of frustrating degree you don't really know what's
happening throughout all these scenes you're you're putting the horrible details together in your mind
um and that's that's the fun of it to me it in a in a way of like a Tarantino or somebody there's
a lot of playing with time a lot of uh you know camera camera tricks a lot of narrative tricks a lot of
not knowing what's going on till five scenes later that kind of thing and that's
where i think it has a lot of fun it's written in such a clever way that it keeps you going to the end
even though it to me i felt a little annoyed never knowing what was happening or i i felt a little
rudderless i think you're supposed to i mean she does eventually say nothing's happening to your
daughter she's at a diner right now and later she re - she meets up again with Alison Brein and she
says nothing happened i got put you to sleep in that room and that's it and you do i think you're
supposed to believe her i don't think you're supposed to question whether she's telling the truth or
not i think like i believe her there he's just trying to scare people but i think that's one of the
strong points of the movie is i like that it's you know look we've talked about movies that deal with
this gender these these gender concerns and and these terrible things that are happening in the culture
between men and women and you know a movie like black christmas comes in completely paper thin
completely heavy -handed in its argument and it stands and fails because it writes completely shallow
characters that you can't relate to in any way you feel nothing for any of them and it's just sucks
whereas this you feel terrible for Mulligan's character but then like she meets
Molly Shannon who plays the mom of her friend who killed herself and Molly Shannon says
you have to let this go like you can't this isn't helping anybody at this point that you're still
this obsessed with this you have to forgive yourself i found that there were levels to these characters
there was nuance and and it was prodding you to question well how far would you go if you were in
this situation how much how justified is justice i thought that that was great i thought that that
was great and i thought one of the most impressive things i have ever seen in a movie like this
from a writing and directing and acting standpoint was when the big showdown finally happens
and she goes in to torture torture isn't the right word but antagonize she infiltrates a bachelor
party at the end of the movie that is all the guys that were involved in this rape or the cover -up
of it her love interest throughout is this guy bo burnum bo burnum's great in the movie but he's
plays who seems to be a super nice guy but you learn he too was sort of involved in the cover -up he
saw it happening and didn't do anything right exactly which again another interesting detail when he
says like what was i supposed to do i didn't know what to do and even though you find that his
silence is despicable and you don't agree with it there is a part of you that goes my god if i was 18
and i was put in that situation what would i do what i you know what i mean would i come to this awful
peer pressure and not say anything would i be a hero and go say i don't know like it's very challenging
in many ways um and i thought it was great and i think the crowning achievement of the film to me aside
from how well it handled this whole discussion and debate was and i and again this is a nod to direction
and writing first and foremost and then to then to sit the actors when she finally does infiltrate
this bachelor party and she pretends to be a stripper and they don't realize who she is they make
it's almost like wet hot american summer they make these guys that you're supposed to hate so
fucking funny that you're just like i can't believe they're pulling this off right now that kid
from the single girl uh the new girl and the girl max grandfield yes she's this christ dude he's
hilarious and you and you made him but he's funny like and it's an on purpose that way like i just
the writer director did such a good job with that like it was it was just man it was well done it was
really well done i agree i actually what you're saying right now actually sort of helps me out a bit
with it because i've had this i've had more conversations about this movie with friends and any other
movie this year which is always a sign that a movie is good you know what people some people hate it
some love it i've see i've read some really strong pieces where women who have been sexually assaulted
despise this movie and i've also seen the flip side where they passionately love it
and just the fact that a movie like this exists that can have these kind of conversations i think is
great um and of course compared to black christmas which you don't talk about for one second after it's
over you know like this is how these movies should be done but um yeah my issue with it was the
tonal shifts you know we're dealing with such heavy stuff and then also some pretty broad comedy
like those guys but what the way you just said it i actually agree with i think that they're trying to
paint the the guys who rape women are charming the guys who who pull off these date rapes have
charmed them enough to get back to their apartment you know and then the evil comes out and i think
what they're doing is trying to make them seem as charming and funny as they probably seem to the
poor girl who went back up to a room with them right and also the denial of it all like you know
so spoiler alert the the the guy that was sort of the the main culprit in the assault
ends up murdering strangely in self -defense ends up murdering Carrie Mulligan at the end of the film
well so i mean self -defense pushing it because he he definitely chokes or more than he needs to
to defend sure sure sure but she's got him handcuffed and he's she's going to start carving
into his chest and he's right green kills her yeah yeah i agree it's it's you know um but
but he murders her and and then greenfield comes in the next day and finds the body and the guy is
beside himself and he's like what did i do what did i do i'm in so much trouble and there's that
scene where greenfield's holding his face and just going this isn't your fault right and it's it's
hilarious yeah i don't know what it's it's it's it's uh the most frustrating one that we couldn't
see in a theater this year because i would just love to see how people would react in a theater and
i bet there'd be fights that would break out yeah we yelling at each other you know like why did you
laugh at that that kind of thing um and that's very exciting to me we never get movies like this anymore
and i i loved the range of emotions i went through but i do i uh yeah i do think that that joe really
helped me here kind of understand why it's bo burnum it's adam brody it's sam Richardson it's all
these very funny charming likeable actors and it's just making the point that these rapists are not
going to be like the date rapists in black christmas where it's a guy like twirling his mustache you know
wearing a shirt that says i love rape or something you know like right and then also and then also the
other side of it where they they do muddy it up they do muddy it they muddy it they say well
you you know the women say to other women you were partying too much and you you put yourself in a
dangerous position and this and that and i'm just supposed to take your word for this whatever they
muddy the entire thing yeah so you don't know exactly how you're supposed to feel quite about anybody
i mean obviously you're on mulligan side and you feel terrible for the girl that you never even meet
and what what happened her but they make it complicated in a way where it's it's challenging as the
best word i could i could use and the fact that this um that this plight costs carry mulligan her life
at the end of the film again and yet in another level was it worth that is that good is that bad
is that the ultimate sacrifice was it right was it shortsighted in a way it's just an incredible movie
and it does end on this mildly open ended note where which again i thought this was just brilliant writing
where the guys that kill carry mulligan's character get apprehended the wet they're they're at their
wedding and they get busted at the end and they get taken away by the cops but bo Burnham is left standing
there on his own and he starts to receive some automated text messages from her phone
that she pre -programmed to send out after she died um and they're and it's like doing the thing
where it's the three dots and you're just waiting it's torturous waiting for the next text to come
through and you're just looking at his phone and you're wondering is the next text going to be i turned
you into or you know i sent the here's the video of the rape that i were and and i sent this to your
boss or whatever it is and it just ends with her saying enjoy the wedding and i thought that was
brilliant writing too because i was like no that's so true to life there would be the the guy that's
on the outskirts of this thing that doesn't know if this is going to come back and and bite him in
the ass or not and just has to now live with this it's not always cut and dry it's not always you don't
get busted or you get busted you're you're home free or you're not home free you're in jail or you
were you running all over the place it's not like that all the time there are guys out there that are
that have to sit and live with their judgments and their past actions and and are it will be in constant
fear that something they did will come back and get them and i i just thought every part of this movie
was perfectly executed uh i loved it i loved it uh i can't recommend it enough i'm not
white sure why it's getting tossed into the horror genre it's not a horror movie um i guess at first
you think it might sort of be like a monster kind of thing where she's killing people and then
but once the reveal is that she's not i guess it does it's a thriller it's definitely a thriller
uh but but it's a black comedy before anything i would say i would agree i like the golden
globes which are you know each year exposed as more of a complete sham but they're coming up on Sunday
the golden globes the uh they're putting it up for best drama and out of those choices drama or
comedy why would they not put this as a comedy they'd be guaranteed the win and it truly classifies
the martian won best comedy five years ago so like promising a young woman to me the most surprising
aspect of it was not just that it was funny but that in terms of tone and like the neon colors and uh
there's a paris hilton sing along with bow burnerman kerry mulligan in a in a convenience store
like it plays like a weird romantic comedy while doing all this other shit and that's that's what i
think everybody can agree to on this i've had friends who said like i had a buddy say i hated
Jennifer Coolidge in this movie i love Jennifer Coolidge hey i've known her a long time but i thought
she was great in this dramatic role but almost everything i've said to someone about the movie
they've disagreed with a hundred percent i love this this and this oh that's what i didn't like about
it oh interesting i so like i just think it means a lot to a lot of different people it's a movie
that'll be rewatched for a long time discussed for a long time i think it's probably the best of
these movies that have come out in response to the me two movement um yeah it's great it's very cool
even though this woman followed and unfollowed me on twitter you hogs up to hogs way up young woman and
that's our show folks check out the taste buds podcast me and salvolcano on the no -press network on
youtube you can get all episodes there they drop every Monday at 11 a .m. and also the hey bay pub
can cast on there with christus definitely and so uh joderos a comedy on twitter and instagram joderos
a comedian on facebook thanks for listening thank you for the support we can't thank you
enough for uh you guys all sticking with us so so we appreciate you we love you
indeed we do thank you to emily as well for running the show as fantastically as you do
you know running that press machine getting those grams up running that facebook page emily also
told us that you guys are in the market for another commentary track uh joe and i are definitely not
opposed to that it's just difficult it's difficult enough to just record the two of us and people's
internet being spotty and zoom and all that shit but we will do our best we thought we were going to be
able to do it through the um the oculus but i don't know that it's going to be possible to record and
watch at the same time we might be able to we're we're trying to figure it out but uh i mean pet
couldn't even figure out a upload a picture so you know um anyway uh we'll be back with uh
most likely tom and jerry and then and then uh the dark and the wicked which is supposed to be awesome
on shutter and is from uh the guy who brought you the strangers which is a you know one of the best
horror movies of recent years i'm excited to see that and then justice league probably after that so
justy league all right folks we'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell