Summer is here, and Bet MGM Casino is coming in hot with casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer, or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz, only available at Bet MGM Casino.
Spin on spectacular slot favorites like Cash Eruption, 88 Fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp, Rakin' Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand.
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action.
The football season is full of guarantees. And here's another. No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the Fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if your football bet loses, you'll earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with Fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan cash. Guaranteed.
Switch to Fanatics Sportsbook. Winning hits different here.
Must be 21+. Gambling problem? Call 1 -800 -GAMBLER. Offer not available in all states. Terms apply. See Fanatics Sportsbook app.
Hi, everybody.
Just you all know we're going to talk over this movie, correct? We were worried that you wouldn't and you would hate our guts.
Pat, stand up for this part. Oh, yeah. The first ever live, the live recording of We'll See You in Hell.
We might as well show them off.
Have you guys heard the podcast before? Are you just? Oh, listen, that's if we reach one person, that's all that matters.
Two. Thank you so much. We're just amazed people are here at 820 in the morning. Yeah. That's awesome.
And give it up for Fangoria for bringing us out and having an awesome podcast network.
Yeah, these prizes sound like they are worth more than the price of admission. So you're already winning.
We could bomb horribly and you'd already be winning. Yeah. And we will.
I have to appreciate the level of maniac that comes out for an 820 screening of Maniac Cop.
Well, I assume they're maniacs just scrolling the newspaper for other maniac events.
Maniac Cop. OK, sure. I'll do that.
The people in the theater. That's that's all they're doing all day is looking for screenings of Maniac Cop to maniac affiliated.
Are you guys excited to watch this? Let's get the energy up.
It's 820 in the morning. Who's drinking? We're drinking already.
We've we've had a couple down here already.
Has everybody seen Maniac Cop 2? Are there any newbies?
OK, we're going to have a good time. It's great movie.
You were at Silver Bullet last night. You were blown away by Silver Bullet.
This movie is going to fuck you up.
This is really going to you're not going to know what to do after this.
Go to sleep. I want to tell a really quick just intro.
Horror Fest story. We should share a quick horror fest story.
And for those of you listening at home, this is when you want to queue up Maniac Cop 2 so you can watch along with us, right?
That's not going to work because who cares?
All right. So I'm in the hotel last night at the front desk.
This 90 year old man walks in and he goes right up.
I'm just in the middle. I'm in the middle of checking in. He walks up. He goes, Excuse me.
Can I have this cup? Just takes a plastic cup.
The clerk's like, Yeah, it's a plastic cup. He goes, No cups in my room.
Astounding. Not a one.
And the guy goes, All right, I'm sorry. And he goes, Here, they wanted me to give you this envelope.
And he goes, What the hell is it?
And the guy goes, I don't know. They just told me to give it to you.
The guy goes, What's in it?
And the guy goes, I don't know. And he goes, All right, but I'm taking the cup.
Okay. He's like, Yeah, we get on the elevator.
It's me, him and another guy.
Whole ride up. Just dissertation about how there's no cups in the room.
Sure. And I go, I go like this.
I go, Not even. He goes, Not even in the bathroom.
And I go, That's amazing. That's what I was just going to ask you.
Not even a glass of the bathroom.
And then he goes, You gonna eat breakfast next door tomorrow?
It's very good.
And I said, I don't know. I got to do this screening at 830.
And he goes, Oh, Christ. God bless.
And he gets off the elevator.
And the other kid goes, Bartender from The Shining.
Damn.
He's here.
And I was like, One of the most chilling characters in The Shining
is like a sort of cat -skilly zinger man.
Okay. The twins from The Shining are here as well.
I have not yet seen them or met them.
Anybody who's seen them?
They're great. I would love to.
Everybody keeps saying they're very sweet. I look forward to meeting them.
Do you have a good story? I know you do, Pat.
Well, I woke up this morning and I had a night bag.
Oh, you know, whatever you bring on a trip.
And I had a little tiny pocket cologne from a previous trip
where I might have thought I would get laid and didn't.
So I had this little thing and it had gotten loose in the bag.
And my toothbrush that I kicked my day off with at 7 .15
was coated in cheap sample cologne.
And that's what I'm tasting.
Even after drinking a Bloody Mary, I taste horrible cologne.
That's my story.
No, you got another one. Can I tell the other one?
Don't tell him.
Okay. It's disgusting.
There's a way better story that Pat's keeping from all of you.
It's a mixed crowd.
I made love to Robert England last night.
I made sweet love to Robert England.
Did everybody like the horror -themed rock songs before the screening?
Today, a little abracadabra, black magic woman.
Abracadabra, does that really count as horror?
It's got a mysterious, supernatural theme.
Mysterious, I'll give you, but not horror.
Pat and I had fun doing a little ad -lib down here
where Santana was trying to explain that he was saying
it was a black woman that did magic.
Yeah.
And they wouldn't let him emphasize the right syllable.
He was hitting black way too hard, and they were like,
Carlos, baby.
It's the 70s, man.
No, I like her, man. I like it.
All right, guys.
Let's all just yell and get our energy up,
and let's get into Maniac Cop 2. How about that?
So on three, one, two, three, scream, Maniac Cop 2.
Let's do this.
That tapered off very quickly.
How are you doing, Joe?
I'm well. Good. I'm well. I'm surprisingly awake.
I like this, that you can get food in the theater.
Is this your first time in an Alamo?
I went to one in Austin that I loved.
What did you see?
I saw Aloha, which is the worst movie I've ever seen in my entire life.
Aloha, the Bradley Cooper movie?
Sure. Anybody see Aloha?
Just terrible, wasn't it?
What?
It was a romantic comedy, and you couldn't follow it.
A little trailer for Carrie.
I forgot how scary that shot was.
Sissy Spacek, what are your thoughts?
I love her.
She's great. Of course.
Where's she been?
She's in stuff all the time.
I'd like to see a sequel to Carrie now, Sissy Spacek, like old Carrie.
Well, we got it called The Rage Carrie 2.
No, but that was a new Carrie.
Yeah.
I'd like to see Carrie, she's in a nursing home, they're all mocking her.
She sets it on fire.
I think it's a great idea.
There's the twins.
There's the shining twins.
We're sitting very close to the screen.
Is this too close for you?
No, I'm all right.
It's too close to you.
What a cocksucker.
So this is Maniac Cop 2, or as it's known in 2015, Regular Cop 2.
I'd like to start with some political humor.
You see, because cops kill people all the time.
Take it easy, Pat.
Should have a nice up -the -middle podcast here.
That was a sharp commentary.
Thank you.
That's from my Daily Show packet.
The thing I like about the Alamo theaters, there's the first theater I ever went to that did these like old school retro bumpers.
Not every theater does it, but Alamo I think started it.
What they could use is a Let's Go Out to the Lobby with the singing candy.
Yeah, yeah.
What I could use is another screwdriver.
All right, here we go.
We're in.
It's happening.
Recap of Maniac Cop 1's ending.
Right.
By the way, is this a dream note from a studio if you're a writer?
We want the first six pages to just be the last six pages of the other movie.
Yeah, and we'll pay you again.
They also show the entire sequence of the Maniac Cop getting shivbed in the shower.
They show the exact same sequence.
That's not in Part 1, is it?
It is in Part 1.
It is?
Yeah.
I thought it was only in Part 2.
I love the hand.
I want it more ugly on the face than Maniac Cop 1.
You get it.
We got a couple tears.
Nothing extraordinary.
Still.
I learned in my research I did on the drive over here that this movie was not theatrically released.
It went straight to video and HBO.
Maniac Cop 2.
$4 million budget straight to video.
I'd like to point out, too, that we're under two minutes into the film.
We've already seen three people go up on harnesses through the air.
Yeah, I love that.
Somebody gets punched, they fly through the air.
I love it.
I love it, too.
Bruce Campbell, man's man, as we all know.
Now, you think the physics of that works?
That you could be stabbed by a log if you drove into it fast enough?
I don't know.
I hope to never know.
I believe a real man goes off the side of the truck here when it goes into the...
That's a real guy.
That's very impressive.
Great stunts in the Maniac Cop series.
Well, he died.
So it wasn't that great a stunt.
Look, that's a real guy, man.
I know, Joe.
That's one of those, we got one take to do this.
Don't fuck it up.
But I don't like water.
That was him flying through the air.
All right, now we're into the...
That's how you open a picture, folks.
This was kind of like going by the Evil Dead 2, Evil Dead model.
It's almost a remake because there's a lot of very similar elements, but it works as a sequel as well.
I don't agree with that at all.
I believe this is a true sequel.
I guess I'm just saying because they show that entire shower sequence, which I was just baffled by.
Hey, I'm never complaining about a second play of a shower sequence with all men in prison.
Yeah, I was watching this on the plane on your iPad, and I'm like, oh, okay, this should be pretty safe.
There's a 20 -minute strip club sequence, so I'm angling the iPad to the window, hoping no one sees it.
Then I finally shift it back, and I'm like, okay, now we're safe.
20 -minute shower, man's ass stabbing sequence.
Not the kind of stabbing you think we mean.
No, no, no.
In an all -male prison.
Robert Davi of Goonies fame.
I once was in a bar in New York with the guys that host Red Eye, which was a Fox show that used to have a lot of comics on.
And I was absolutely shit -faced, and after we left, they said, do you know who you were just drinking with?
That was Robert Davi of Goonies.
You didn't recognize Robert Davi?
I didn't recognize him at all. I talked to that guy for 40 minutes, he was yelling at me.
Matt Cordell, not an icy cold name.
It's a terrible name for a show.
Freddy Krueger, and then you got Matt Cordell.
Jason Voorhees, Matt Cordell.
Sounds kind of like a dick.
Yeah. Well, he is a dick. He's a maniac is what he is.
He's a maniac dick.
Charles Napier. Charles Napier was in every movie from 1970 through 1985.
Who is Charles Napier?
He was one of the Nazi, no, one of the cops in Blues Brothers, I know that much.
And he was just in a lot of like Robert Altman movies.
Okay.
You'll know him when you see him.
He was in the Strip Club.
No, the show. I love the guy hosting the Strip Club.
I guess they just told him to improv. You'll see when we get there.
He's like, isn't she beautiful?
I was watching it with subtitles and 80 times the subtitle was, isn't she beautiful, folks?
It's like, come up with something new to say.
Look at her. Isn't she beautiful?
I auditioned to DJ at a strip club once.
Oh, wow.
I was 22 and the guy that ran it, the main DJ fucked me out of the job.
How so?
He would tell me to do stuff and then I'd do it and he'd be like, you don't ever want to do that.
And I was like, I get it. It's your turf in here.
He didn't want me getting any of that sweet stripper play that I guess he was getting.
Was that a low point for you not getting the call back for the stripper DJ audition?
It was a high point that they even brought me in for the first interview.
I didn't care.
I was driving to work the other day to my writing gig, told the guy at Carpool with,
we're doing a screening of Maniac Cop 2 for my podcast and he goes, never seen it, not familiar.
But what else did William Lustig direct?
New William Lustig, no fucking clue what Maniac Cop 1 or 2 was though.
That's odd, isn't it?
It's a big Lustig buff.
Do you know what else he directed?
I know he directed Maniac.
He also directed Uncle Sam.
Oh, Uncle Sam wants you to die.
That's the tagline.
Uncle Sam wants you, I think it's just dead.
Do you know the Maniac Cop tagline?
No.
It's the best tagline ever. Ready?
Yes.
You have the right to remain silent forever.
That's good.
It's fucking great.
I used to live on Dr. Giggles, the doctor is out, dot dot dot, of his mind.
And I remember I said to my mom, I was a little kid, I said, Mom, you know, they also could have made this, the doctor is in, dot dot dot, sane.
That's better.
And she said, that's really good, Pat.
Yeah, I fucking know, Mom.
That's when you knew you were going to be a writer.
Dr. Giggles, I mean, what were they doing to me as a kid in the 80s?
I mean, that guy played the retarded guy on L .A. Law.
Larry Drake, yeah.
Yeah, and then they got him as the bad guy in Dark Man and Dr. Giggles.
It was spinning me in all kinds of directions as a kid.
I couldn't handle it.
Well, actors play different types of roles, Joe.
Is it wrong that I said retarded?
It's not great, and you're saying it again now.
Let's move past it.
Mentally handicapped is generally preferred.
This guy stole a gun from a Civil War museum right to a convenience store to rob it.
You know, you can't.
He's got pocket hair combs on the wall behind him.
You can't find those at a convenience store anymore.
Not these days.
Used to be going to a convenience store.
You pick up a pocket hair comb.
We talked about this this sequence earlier.
This drives me crazy.
This guy gets into the car with this wonderful pizza feast.
They get a call.
Why does he do that?
Save it for after.
You make the bust.
You have a celebration with some pizza.
It is insane.
Put it in the back seat.
Well, you know how pizza tastes terrible when it's cold.
No wait, it's even better.
It just this.
That's the only thing in this movie that strains believability for me was that they threw the pizza out the car window.
This guy's teeth.
Just a black magic marker job.
I believe his teeth really look like that.
OK.
I was trying to figure out earlier what drug he's on.
It's a drug I haven't done.
It's I felt meth -y to me and the teeth also indicate that.
But was meth around in 1990?
I think it's always been around.
It's probably a different name.
You know, I briefly worried today.
I took my probiotics in the morning and I worried that I had taken a Molly from a previous trip to Las Vegas.
And I worried that this podcast was going to be real crazy.
I didn't know that you're flying around willy -nilly with Molly in your bag.
Well, I put it in a pill thing and you don't you can't tell the difference.
But that's a problem because you could just take it by accident.
So if I start making out with you, you'll know you're a bad man.
The guy auditioned the guy that auditioned for the shop clerk role went in and said, now, listen, you know, Hispanic actor.
This will be a respectful, not racist, stereotypical role.
Right. Of course.
Go ahead.
No, you're good. It'll bring a lot of pride to your family.
There he is.
First sighting of the maniac cop.
Thank God you got here.
Never mind that there's fog on the floor.
I.
Why does nobody notice the fog on the floor?
It drives me crazy.
It could be coming out of the freezer, a particularly overactive freezer section.
Goodness is its own reward.
Not today.
Yeah, I love how there's a full shootout and the guys still very focused on the lottery ticket.
Yeah, there's also a deformed zombie standing in front of him.
Yeah, it's not that dark in the store.
Yeah, the fog is on the floor.
There's also a red light coming up from the bottom of everything.
Can't make out the guy's face at all.
This guy, I mean, just takes his life into his own hands right here.
Now, my question I had throughout is, does the maniac cop just sense that crimes are going on or how does he keep showing up as crimes are happening?
You know, they never explain it.
It's like a Superman kind of thing.
Right.
He just knows.
Fourth harness jump.
They love a harness jump in these movies.
Maybe they explain it in Maniac Cop 3, which I've never seen.
I haven't either. I think it's called Badge of Silence.
Yeah, that's what made me not see it.
But I do like the first two.
The third one, I don't know, Badge of Silence.
Look at that. That's not a winning ticket today, is it, Pat?
I know. Everybody lost.
I won $1 ,000 on a Missouri lottery ticket when I was in college.
What did you do with the money?
I put it in the bank. It's a terrible story. I had no money at the time.
It's a shit story. Jesus Christ.
You'd love me to go on some Ferris Bueller style adventure with it, but I put it in the bank.
That's why I'm a hone owner today.
Hone owner? Let's cut off the Bloody Marys.
Yeah, and that's why I still rent.
My most important bill to pay every month is what Blu -ray am I buying?
Bruce Campbell, a real handsome man in his prime.
Can we say that?
Yeah, he's gorgeous. Michael Lerner, also a very sexy man.
This character is a heavy set man with a pipe and a shitty attitude.
Get Michael Lerner.
Michael Lerner is actually in the office. He sensed that it was coming.
He's like the maniac cop. He senses when they need a fat guy with a pipe and a bad attitude.
He's right there.
Sounds like you need Michael Lerner, baby.
Nominated for an Oscar two years later for Barton Fink, which is honestly kind of a horror movie itself by the Coen brothers.
He's tremendous in that film. He's great.
And I believe Lerner could have played, I believe Goodman and Lerner could have swapped roles.
I would have bought him in either role in that film.
You wouldn't have wanted that much Lerner, I'll tell you that.
I like a peppering of Lerner. You don't want a full two hours of Lerner.
I learned that the hard way. Folks, these are the jokes.
A young Daryl Hannah type.
I was positive this was the woman from Flash Gordon, the movie, and it's not her.
They look almost identical. It's crazy.
Bruce Campbell, one of my favorites.
He's coming off Evil Dead, Evil Dead 2, and then like what? He did like Crime Wave?
I think this is pre -Evil Dead 2, if I'm not mistaken. Evil Dead 2 is like 90, this is like 89, isn't it?
I'm pretty sure Evil Dead 2 is 87, and this is 90. I don't want to make you into an asshole in front of all these people, but I think you're just wrong.
I guarantee we could ask anyone at this horror festival and they'll tell us that Evil Dead 2 was released.
Does anybody know? You can yell it out.
87? I think it's 87.
You like those bangs? I do, I like this chick.
You take her or you take checker boards here?
I love that little interaction they have there where he's like, look, we both know we saw a zombie, but God damn it, the pension.
Well, nobody ever believes it. Let's say one person comes to me and says, hey, I saw a maniac cop.
I'd be like, well, somebody's been hitting the sauce pretty hard.
Three people come to me and say they saw a maniac cop.
Did you see that stunt? That was outrageous.
That was a real stunt.
That guy just fell two stories onto a bed.
By the way, he's also actually dead.
Everyone who did a stunt in this movie died, which casts a certain realism to the part.
Lustig insisted on it.
Here he is, in the same costume he wore in The Goonies.
Give me the cheapest fedora you got.
I picture this guy as a street cop that wears a fedora.
He plays this like it's, you know, Godfather 4.
He takes it very seriously. He plays everything. Yeah, I love it.
He sings opera in The Goonies. Yeah.
You know, my lawyer, my ex -lawyer was Chunk.
Yeah, he's a big Hollywood lawyer. Yeah, that's true. People are laughing. That's true, though.
Yeah, the actor who played Chunk is a big Hollywood attorney.
Yeah, real thin now. I didn't like that. I wanted him to be fat.
That's the Future 2 poster up there. It was 1990.
All right, we get it, nerd.
Well, Jesus Christ, it's like an almanac of movies over here.
Speaking of nerds, I would have my dad quiz me from the Leonard Maltin's video guide.
It was the only time he would speak to me, so we had a good rapport going.
I'd be like, Papa, just a couple more questions from the Maltin guide?
And he'd throw his bottle of bourbon at me and go, I'll give you two, and then it's bedtime.
Right. You know, take a swing at my mother.
First question, why are you such a pussy?
Question two, how are you my son?
I'm a man, so how are you my son?
This isn't true, folks. He's an okay guy.
This one here reminds me of The Departed.
I think The Departed took a lot from Maniac Cop 2.
Scorsese, I heard, had this in the screening room every morning before he started shooting.
What I want to make here is like a maniac cop, but instead of a maniac zombie cop, it's corruption.
There's a maniac cop inside of us all.
That's my Scorsese impression.
Actually, it's off the cuff. That's the first time I ever did it.
It's good. As ridiculous as Maniac Cop 2 is, even they wouldn't end it with a rat crawling on a windowsill as The Departed ends.
I remember, I fucking love The Departed, but everyone in the theater was like, are you serious with that rat shot?
Yeah, that rat shot's bad.
Marty says, Marty, what are you doing, bro?
Maniac Cop 2 wouldn't dare try to convince us that Mark Wahlberg worked his way up the ladder in any occupation.
No, no, no.
My favorite Mark Wahlberg wrote Robotics Expert in Transformers 4.
Or how about...
I've been working with robotics for a long time.
How about Scientist in The Happening?
The only less believable scientist is Denise Richards in that James Bond movie.
And college professor in The Gambler.
Yeah, oh yeah, that was ridiculous.
I like The Gambler, but yeah.
I stayed in for about half of it that I bailed out.
Those scenes where he's like teaching the class, you can see him straining to remember the dialogue.
We love you though, Mark. I'm sure you're listening.
I love this lady. I'm in love with this psychiatrist.
I do too. I like when he tells his story about how his wife...
His wife left him.
...was under close scrutiny by a psychiatrist for a year and then she left him, so that's why he hates psychiatrists.
That's the backstory they give you for this guy?
Look, this guy's old school. He doesn't have time for the mumbo jumbo. You know what I mean?
Sure.
You go to work, you go to sleep, that's it. That's how life goes.
This is a strange outfit choice.
I was just about to say, it doesn't match, Bruce. It doesn't match.
I'm a black actor and I want to make sure this isn't going to be a stereotypical black role that I'm playing in Maniac Cop 2.
Well, as we told the Hispanic guy, totally respectable role.
I love how he tells the story about how he... All he has to say was the guy was cold.
The Maniac Cop touches him and his hands are cold.
And he tells this horrific story of being face down in the muck and war with bodies on top of him to prove that he knows how cold flesh feels.
Right. Typical executive note too.
You're just like, he's blind so we couldn't see him. But why is he blind?
Let's have him tell a story. Doesn't that give it more stakes?
Here's my impression of the notes for the new Angry Birds movie.
But why are the birds angry?
Nobody gives a shit.
This shocked me the first time I saw it. That Campbell goes down this quick.
I couldn't believe it.
It's like Psycho. You kill your star right off the bat.
I couldn't believe it. He gets all the way through the first one and they ice him right away in this one.
Oh yeah. Daddy like.
Just kidding everybody. I actually do like it and I'm not kidding.
I don't mind corpse nudity because I know the actress who played the corpse was alive.
So I can just imagine that she was sleeping.
There's a movie playing at this festival about three teens who have sex with a corpse.
Robert Davie chooses the fedora with Levi's.
Sometimes Joe will just ignore a point that I made.
I didn't hear what you said because I was so distracted by that outfit.
It is a wild outfit.
He's all Marlboro man on the bottom. All Sinatra on the top. I don't know what the fuck's going on there.
No belt. We're coming off a scene where Bruce Campbell is wearing old Navy khakis, white New Balances, a black trench coat and gloves.
Who's doing the wardrobe? And whoever's doing the wardrobe forgot to give this corpse a shirt.
Folks, but there is a movie playing here. It's a Spanish movie.
I think we're going to see it this afternoon. Yeah.
And it's three teenagers who sneak into a morgue to have sex with a corpse.
I don't know why I watch this movie. I know I signed up just because it sounds horrific to me.
But yeah, I do want to see it because there's got to be a twist, right?
I mean, I assume that she comes back to life or something.
Do you ever see that movie teeth where the girl has teeth in her vagina?
Yeah, I sure did.
I called my friend the day I read the synopsis of that movie when I heard it was coming out.
I called my friend. I said, if they were making a movie called teeth and it was your dream movie, what would the plot be?
That's all I asked him. He goes that a girl had teeth in her vagina that bit guys dicks off.
And I said, well, it's your lucky day.
I'm in the car outside your house. Let's go.
He didn't believe me. He thought I was making it up. I was like, no, it's a real movie.
I like to imagine like the guy who directed this movie we're going to see, which is called I think the corpse of Ken. What's it called?
The corpse of Anna Fritz.
Anna Fritz.
Imagine like you call your mom and you go, Mom, I'm going to make a movie. I got a budget. I got actors. It's all happening.
Honey, that's great. What's the movie about?
And you have to say it's about three teenagers who fuck a corpse.
Does your mom just give up on you at that point?
She says at that point she goes, well, at least it's not like the one you made about the girl with the teeth in her pussy.
It's not the same director.
I know, Pat. It's a bit for Christ sakes.
Well, Lerner, we just missed him. He was back with the pipe.
I love the weight of the worlds on this guy's shoulders.
Christ, give me my pipe. Just constantly smoking and he can't handle.
What the hell's happening?
Here we go. Let's just listen to this speech real quick.
Just a ridiculous overshare to a woman he's just met.
I admit I'm not the easiest guy to live with.
I didn't ask.
Or the best dresser. And I wear ridiculous hats.
I admit sometimes I pair 501 jeans with an elegant trench coat and a fedora.
I'm still wearing a class ring. Hey.
There's a horse looking thing on my tie.
Suspenders. That's why he's got no belt on. He's got suspenders on.
You ever worn a pair of suspenders in your life?
Once.
I was in a stage production of The Little Rascals.
Kidding.
No, yeah. I had a wedding or something for a tuxedo.
They did suspenders instead of the vest or something.
Yeah. Right here, folks.
Little movie trivia. This is Angel Salazar.
He is a comedian who I knew fairly well in New York from doing shows.
He also played Chi Chi in Scarface.
Famous line Scarface. Chi Chi. Get the yayo.
That's Chi Chi.
He had a bit in his act where he had stripped down to a teal thong on stage.
I'm sorry I missed that.
Once he was on stage and I found several multicolored fluorescent thongs in the green room.
And I said to my friend, these are the bits he decided not to do tonight.
These are the jokes that didn't make the cut.
Yeah. But he's a great guy. Very nice guy.
He was also in the movie Punchline. He's the guy with the big boom box in Punchline.
Go ahead.
The thing is, and I really haven't seen it in other movies, is that it's a standard setup where they portray this guy as a complete yuppie asshole.
He's rich. He's terrible. And you're expecting him to die.
And then they kill the good, nice cop.
Well, because the maniac cop is trying to create turmoil in the police department in City Hall for what they did to him.
So in this movie he steps it up and he goes out of his way to kill the good guy and let the asshole live.
So it makes even less sense to them than the first movie.
And this guy just saw a man get killed and hung on a hook and all he cares about is the ticket.
He's a ticket obsession in this film.
I relate it to him to be honest with you.
Excuse me, traditional horror movie character who's always a black guy that can't see.
Can you give me the clues that I'm looking for right now?
Is he wearing horrifically painful 80s contacts or are those his actual eyes you think?
I don't know. The makeup in this movie is very good so I can't tell who actually had a disability of some kind.
This movie, remade today, would be so timely.
In the first one when that woman is just scared because she gets pulled over.
You could make some really prescient political shit out of this movie today.
Well you already did when you said it would be called regular cops.
Yeah, well I remember that.
This is like in Jeepers Creepers when that island lady comes in to the police station like I heard it on the radio.
I always love…
I got psychic powers. This is convenient.
Come back here and let me give you some jambalaya to warm you up.
She's like hey did you see anything last night and he's like hey how about a five minute monologue about my experience in the war.
Where I had to cover myself, I had to use corpse blankets is what the monologue is about.
She's like why is everybody telling me their personal shit today?
Well she's a psychiatrist, she's used to it.
The guy from Goonies just opened up about his wife leaving him.
Look I'll admit I'm not the easiest guy to live with.
That's not Dana Carvey and that's not Brett Ratner. No matter what everybody thinks.
He looks like Martin Short there.
I love how everyone in the movie knows that the cop is six foot three.
Six foot three. All scarred up is the detail of the face. Not blue skin.
Did he have any zombie like qualities? No I just scarred up exactly six foot three is all I remember.
Was there fog on the ground? I couldn't say.
Probably. I didn't look down.
What are you wearing Robert Davy?
He clearly bases the whole outfit on the suspenders matching the tie and then he lets it fly from there.
Look at that piece he's got man.
That's a serious good. Acne scars on Davy or what do you think?
I would assume so unless he was hit with some kind of fragment bomb.
That's what Bill Murray's got.
Yeah I think it's probably acne scars.
My dad has some scarring like that. I always feel for those guys.
You know I had horrific acne and I can't believe my face looks as beautiful as it does now.
I can't either.
You hear that silence where everybody in the theater is nodding behind us. Yes that's correct.
I didn't know you had acne and I thought that this morning.
I saw your face I said I can't believe how beautiful this kid is.
You rolled over you looked me in the eye.
I had I used to have to take Accutane.
Yeah I had to take that for a while too.
At one point about eight years ago my career had fallen to a point that I was so stressed that I had an adult breakout of severe acne.
And I had to take Accutane. That shit fucks you up man.
Every pill had a picture of a pregnant woman with an X through it.
Which makes you feel real good when you're a 16 year old going through all these changes.
And then now they've discovered that people who were on Accutane for long periods of time have severe mental issues and try to kill people.
There's lawsuits all the time.
You pointed out yesterday I was yelling at people. Maybe it's the Accutane.
It might have been the Accutane.
I killed two people this morning.
I like that amidst all the zombie cast she took time to crimp her hair up.
Yeah I mean that's like a two hour hair job.
Feed the fish. Make sure they're good.
Before I blow town I got to feed these fish one last time.
Look I've got a facial and a mani -pedi in about 10 minutes. Can we wrap this up?
Pat I'll tell you what I'm putting the order in. I'm going for another screwdriver.
Are you on two or three?
This is going to be my third of the morning.
What are you on?
This is my second.
Well I'm on my second but I'm going to go for the third.
You know what I'll take a third too. Let's go crazy.
The nice waiter here had to take the order slip out of my hand because I couldn't get it into the slot on the table here.
He was like I got it buddy just for Christ sakes.
Sometimes you drink too much you can't get it into the slot.
Folks.
This is possibly my favorite character in movie history.
This cab driver.
Now I'm an Italian actor. Is this going to be a respectable role?
Yep not stereotyping at all.
Put on this hot fries Andy Cap hat and get into this cab.
Care way too much about a 425 fare.
And then he has a weird thing about how cops always cause trouble and don't tip well in his car.
That's a good stereotype.
You know how Italians hate cops.
Like is that a thing that cops don't tip well?
No.
I don't know maybe.
This guy in a writers room.
I know a cop. He says they never tip.
We got to put that in the movie.
I don't think this movie had a writers room per se.
There's always a punch of room you know that.
That's right.
I own this cab which apparently is 15 years or so outdated.
Look at this Dick Tracy cab he's driving around.
You ever play the Roger Rabbit video game with Benny the cab?
No.
No Pat. It's really fun.
Who in Christ's name would have picked that game?
Of all the other great Nintendo games.
Every game I had was like an offshoot.
Whatever was in the clearance.
My favorite game was tubing.
About going in an inner tube down a river drinking beer.
Somebody should tell this cab driver that the maniac cop drives a newer car than he does.
Doesn't matter he's dead.
This movie had really good action I felt.
Yeah it's great.
Very like realistic.
I'm very excited for the sequence when he raids the police station.
I really like that part.
You know what I'm curious to know.
Remember how there's the one guy that hasn't seen this?
Yeah.
I think he's lost right now because we talked over it the whole time.
Could you guys shut up?
Or can you follow it?
You get what's going on right?
He said yeah.
They say the key to a good movie is you can turn the sound off and follow the plumb.
Fantastic car chase.
Again all very real.
Yeah.
This is all happening.
They shot this.
You know as of 2012 Nicholas Winding Refn was going to remake Maniac Cop.
I guess it fell through but you think that might still happen?
No no yesterday they announced it's moving forward.
Literally yesterday.
I mean obviously I love Drive.
I know you hate Drive.
I can't even imagine.
It's a horrendous film.
I hate it so much.
Hey I have an idea for a movie.
Let's have Ryan Gosling silent and take all the likeability out of Albert Brooks.
I hate the film.
I hate it.
Did you like Only God Forgives?
What the hell is Only God Forgives?
It's Drive in Thailand with Ryan Gosling.
Same director same everything.
Never saw it.
It's good.
I never saw The Place Beyond the Pines either.
Love Place Beyond the Pines.
This is great.
This whole thing.
That just happened to be there.
This is a great little detail right here.
Yeah there's a function.
That was in a store though right?
The chainsaw wasn't just on the street?
No yeah it was in the store.
Let's the car go down the hill.
She's fucked.
Now here's what I don't get.
He catches the chainsaw.
Why can't it cut him?
I don't know.
I guess he's invincible in some way.
I think it could cut him and not hurt him but I would still think it would cut his hand.
Yeah.
Am I wrong?
Again this is real.
They got a lady hanging out of a car going down a street.
It's fairly fast.
Apologies to those of you listening at home.
We can't really speak a lot during these sequences because it's just loud heavy action.
But we're still here.
She's in the car.
Now for those of you not watching she's just crashed into a pile of boxes.
That always upset me because she pulls off getting back in the car and not dying and then they just have her crash.
I feel like she should get the victory of landing safely and not just immediately crashing.
Wouldn't you say?
What are you going to do?
I was six years old when this movie came.
Has anyone seen Maniac Cop 3 Badge of Silence?
By round of applause?
I'm seeing nobody.
Literally nobody.
Well now I don't feel bad.
I thought they were going to be like you're a fucking travesty.
You've never seen the entire trilogy.
I feel okay about it.
Here comes drinky number three.
And Ken Lustig, doesn't he run a DVD company now like a specialty DVD company?
Which one?
Blue Underground.
That's awesome.
This is the end of the line, huh?
Our bill has come.
Somebody must have told them, look give them the bill.
They're done drinking.
Let's get back on track here.
Last night we saw Silver Bullet here and when the bill came I had to wake Joe up.
Always good.
Nothing against the film.
I was so tired.
Midnight screening, I understand.
I liked Silver Bullet.
I had never seen it.
I enjoyed it much more seeing it on the old film stock and everything.
The first time I saw it was on Netflix.
I thought Busey was fantastic.
And I liked, oh here we go.
Busey, I guess, like he had been nominated for an Oscar two years prior.
It looks like he just put on a ton of weight and then wound up being in Silver Bullet.
When I first saw this film I couldn't believe that this guy wasn't Mick Foley from WWF.
It looks like Mick Foley.
So much that I literally thought it was him at first.
But now you pointed out to me that it's the guy from Analyze This.
Which blew my mind because he looks nothing like him.
This is Charles Napier.
I love Charles Napier.
Favorite Charles Napier line is in Cable Guy.
Do a song for us.
He was the cop. I love when he says that.
That's true.
Strange that any news show would have a good hair and makeup team that couldn't take care of that shiner on her forehead.
Bring the bangs down.
The other lady's got bangs covering her entire face.
Take a tip from her.
I like that the news reporter is like, oh so you say there's a zombie on the list.
What would he have to say about this commissioner?
Nobody bats an eye.
This guy's my favorite character in the whole movie.
It was a really interesting development because it becomes a whole different movie at this point really.
Yeah.
And he's like almost has a crush on the maniac cop.
To the point where he has to tell him he's not gay.
I like that part.
You want to come back to my house and hang out?
And then they do.
I like that. This guy, whatever his name is, he's a tremendous actor.
He plays this character great.
It's always nice to give a shout out to whatever his name is and reward him for his work.
I'm sorry I don't know the name of the supporting cast of Analyze This.
I didn't play a movie quiz with my uncle as a child like you did.
My dad. I like to analyze that.
We all know he was actually your uncle.
I play a different game with my uncle if you want to get into some real dark shit.
Why would you?
Analyze This is great. Analyze That is just as bad as it gets.
And Analyze The Other, the unmade third.
Did I ever tell you my idea for the third? Please do.
Analyze Me.
And it's De Niro has to analyze Billy Crystal.
I like that.
It's great. They'll never make it, but I like it.
Just.
Do you get uncomfortable when there's nudity in a theater or no?
I saw the movie Welcome to New York, which was what's -his -face that made Bad Lieutenant.
Abel Ferrara.
Abel Ferrara, one of his later films.
I saw it at a screening that Abel Ferrara hosted, and the sex was so graphic that I literally felt like I was watching porn in a theater.
It made me very uncomfortable.
It makes my upper lip sweat. I get very uncomfortable.
It reminds me of my parents walking in while a sex scene was going on. It's very uncomfortable.
Yes. What made it worse was during every sex scene, my friend Brian would reach over, grab the back of my head, and try to force my head down like he was trying to get me to blow him.
Okay.
Then I'd pull back, and he'd go, all right, relax.
He kept doing that every sex scene, which didn't make it any better.
That's some 80s underpants right there.
That's 80s everything. That's 80s body.
That was a real 80s body back then. That's how the bodies were. 80s hair.
You ever just cover your body in glitter, Joe?
I'm covered in it right now.
Look at this guy. Just act like you're having fun.
He's doing all he can to get on screen as an extra.
I mean, for this guy on the right, this old guy, can you imagine how happy he is he got into being an extra?
In the strip club scene.
Make $100 to do this all day?
I'll tell you, I love this girl. I want to marry her.
Isn't she beautiful, folks?
Yeah, when does that happen?
He was doing it. We've talked over it.
That movie, Welcome to New York, did they play Taylor Swift's Welcome to New York over any of the sex scenes?
No, and in fact, it came out years before that song came out. It's a great song.
No, it's not. No?
Degree of disagree.
I have a question for you. You know I'm dating Taylor Swift.
I have a question for you. What?
If you could be a maniac something, sure, what would it be?
And what would your catchphrase be?
Well, it's hard to find one that hasn't been a movie.
Like even The Dentist was a movie with Corbin Berntson.
That's okay.
I guess I would want to be, do you have one ready to go?
Yeah, I've been thinking about this for the last couple days.
Okay, that's weird, but share it with us.
Mine is a maniac boxing judge.
Okay, go on.
And then I would cut people in half and I'd go, split decision.
Okay, all right, that's pretty good.
Do you have any other quips or it's always going to be a split decision?
What else do they say, what else do boxing judges say?
Knockout, total knockout.
I've never seen a boxing match.
They say I'm Rocky Balboa. I don't know anything about boxing.
Can't wait to see Creed. I'm very excited.
Yeah, but it's going to have to be pretty good to beat Rocky Balboa because I thought they ended the franchise perfectly.
I cried my eyes out during Rocky Balboa.
I am from Philadelphia so it really held a place close to my heart.
Tears of excitement, tears of sadness, Adrian's dead. Oh my God, I love that movie.
These horror movies, when I lived in New York for 10 years, these movies were what made me never want to move to New York
because everybody lived in one of these motel things.
Yeah, and it just looked like diseases were brewing in there and everything.
And then when they call for help, they're like, I don't want any trouble.
Did you ever see the fly, you know, the Goldblum one?
Yeah, we've discussed it at length.
It terrified me to move to New York. I was like, you got to live in a warehouse?
Yeah, that's true.
It was crazy. I was like, what the fuck is this?
For me, it was the Muppets Take Manhattan.
I was like, Jesus Christ, if these Muppets are living like this, how am I going to do?
They got singing rats preparing meals.
What's up with that new Muppet show, by the way, with all the dick jokes?
I hate it, if I can be.
What are they doing?
I don't know. It's like Kermit's like, hey bitch, get in here. It's terrible.
You know who runs the show?
The guy who does Big Bang Theory.
The guys that did Anger Management, the Charlie Sheen sitcom.
That's who they got to run the Muppets TV show.
They make like gay jokes?
Like, I mean, like that are disparaging to gay people.
Yeah, like Fozzie's a bear, but he's also like a bear, that kind of thing.
Yeah, it's upsetting. It's not a good show. I don't know why they did that.
You ever see Meet the Feebles, Peter Jackson's?
Yeah, it upset me.
It actually made me vomit.
I don't like when kids' things get turned dirty.
I read the book Wicked and the witch is having sex in it and stuff.
It bothers me.
Two harness throws on that one.
I think I would love to be thrown by a harness.
I think it would be a lot of fun.
I'd like it.
So the maniac cop has just rescued what apparently is a serial killer.
Right. Imagine, so that girl's like, hey, that was strange.
One guy breaks in, tries to rape me.
A maniac cop comes in, saves him, and then runs out with him.
And prevents the rape.
Yeah.
You know?
Look at these people dancing up in the window up there.
I wonder if they knew they were in the shot or what.
I like that this guy appreciates a tight around the buns pair of pants.
Sure.
That's where he tells him he's not gay, but just come back to my house.
You know, I gave it some thought and I think I'd be a maniac tailor.
Okay. And what would your thing be?
I don't know. I have to give that some thought.
That's where he would not do my work.
I know they've never made a movie about a maniac tailor.
That's why I'm choosing it.
I would, if I was a maniac tailor.
A lot of inseam material and you cut the guy's dick off.
Yeah, exactly.
We got to take this jacket in.
Yeah, yeah.
I don't know. You cut the guy's side off. I don't fucking know.
Look, it's a work in progress.
He's not at all.
There's no part of him that's like, what is wrong with your face?
Yeah.
They're just hanging out.
So he killed all of these women, correct?
I guess. And it to me looks like a lazy serial killer.
What's that? Five, six chicks?
Yeah.
These guys better get on it if he wants to make a name for himself.
By the way, I lived in New York 10 years, had an upstanding job, never an apartment this nice.
Oh, no.
Look at this fucking place. Exposed brick. He's got four rooms.
I lived in a railroad apartment, which meant that if my roommate wanted to go to the bathroom, he had to walk through my room.
He had to open one door, come through my room, go out the other door and go to the bathroom, then walk back through three times a night.
I had that in college.
Wow.
And my place was robbed and they took the door off the hinges to get in.
Right.
And I called my landlord, who was named Mr. Stool, and he goes, I said, hey, my front door is off the hinges. I don't have a door anymore.
And he goes, did I take your door? Why are you calling me? Did I take your door?
Wow.
So you're not going to fix it? He didn't fix it. I had to leave the apartment.
That's really incredible.
That was in Williamsburg, which is now Disneyland.
Yeah.
They cleaned it up, baby. But back in those days, I lived on the corner of Stabington Street and shoot them up. It was terrible.
There was a, I thought it was a maximum security prison.
I thought it deserved more than it got.
There was like a prison next to my building. It was a horrible, horrible place.
Love that. Cordella spoken for the first time.
I'd wear that shirt.
Cordella?
Yeah, you'd wear it now.
You'd wear it now.
This guy's so good as a serial killer. I really mean it. I mean, I really enjoy him.
We're back in Davi's office now.
What is he writing there?
He's filling out paperwork.
He doesn't seem like a guy who'd be above paperwork.
No, no cop is.
That's below his pay grade.
That's part of the deal. I shot some son of a bitch in a grocery store robbery, and they got me doing paperwork.
Now I gotta push pencils.
The only paperwork I wanna do is the trash I wrap around that piece of shit's body.
You know, they always say stuff like that.
Sure, sure, sure.
Now he's wearing a denim shirt with...
And her forehead's cleared up? Oh no, it's taken on a new one.
It's got a welt on it, but this is, again, good makeup in this film that looks like a progressive, yeah, a progress bruise.
You know?
He never sticks it to this lady, does he?
Sexually? Sorry to put it so...
Sticks it to her. It's amazing that you have relationships with women.
It's 9 a .m. I've had three screwdrivers already. I'm sorry if I'm not tactful at this point.
He never sticks it to this bro.
It's called making love, Joe. You might try it sometime.
I don't think Davi would put it that way.
No, he wouldn't. Especially not with that ex -wife. Look, he knows he's a difficult man to live with.
Well, I had this knife fashioned out of my nightstick.
It cost a few bucks, but it was worth it.
Who do you put in the Davi role? You're remaking Maniac Comp 2.
I already don't know who Davi is. Robert Davi.
Oh, Robert Davi. Jesus Christ.
Who do I put in that role? I'm going to go with Paul Giamatti.
Okay. All right.
I thought that could work.
I mean, I like him in anything. I don't know that it could work, but I'd watch it.
You know what? I'll tell you that back. I'll put Paul Giamatti in this guy's role.
Yeah, that makes more sense.
In the serial killer role, I'm going to put Mickey Rourke in the Davi role.
See, I think you want Rourke in the Maniac Cop role.
Because he's got a huge face.
Yeah, he's got a huge, bloated plastic surgery.
Rourke is the Maniac Cop. I'm going to put...
He goes into makeup and they're like, we're all good. You're good to go.
Yeah.
Let me just put my kid away, you freak.
All right, then I'm going to put...
You know, there's no Italians in Hollywood anymore.
I don't know what Italian actors are out there that could play the Davi role.
There is no tough guys in Hollywood anymore.
The toughest we got is Chris Pratt, who's not tough.
No.
You need a man's man.
You know what? I'm going to do it a different way here.
I'm going to put Marisa Tomei in the Davi role.
Let's switch up the genders.
All right, sure.
I'd buy her as a no -nonsense, plain -clothes cop.
Maybe some high -waisted jeans, showing some of the front puss.
Oh, my God.
I doubt she has one, but...
As opposed to the rear puss.
Well, you know, that...
Do you know how women's bodies work?
The mom...
Oh, wait, I didn't mean front put.
What did they used to call that when the mom would have the little belly bump,
and they'd call it the bussy?
Do you not know what I'm talking about?
No.
That was a common thing when I was a kid. That was a phrase.
The mom jeans?
Yeah, but the mom jeans were high -waisted, so it would show if you had a little bit of a gut,
and then kids would call it the bussy, like the belly pussy.
Okay.
Sorry, is this too much?
I mean, I'm rolling with it.
I was kind of mad you don't see Rob the maniac cop's dick right here.
I really thought we were going to see some maniac cop dick.
Some dick?
He must have had it in his contra.
Well, there he's wearing...
Oh, those are...
Okay, he's wearing jeans.
Robert Czar, we found out last night from our friend.
Kent just passed away, right?
Very sad. Rest in peace, sir.
Oh.
Yeah, that's rough. They cut his face all up. That's gross.
If I'm not mistaken, this entire sequence, beat for beat, is in Maniac Cop 1 as well.
Is it in Maniac Cop 1? I don't remember it for some reason.
Except there's a 20 -minute panning shot through the prison that I guess they just used to kill time.
I like this push -in on the Maniac Cop.
I remember it like it was yesterday.
Look, that lady looks like Marisa Tomei.
Yeah, I love Marisa Tomei.
I love her.
And it'd be a wrestler reunion, which is exciting.
That is exciting.
Well, then maybe we make Marisa Tomei the stripper role again.
Sure, anything.
We need somebody in this cop role who's playing Davey in the remake.
Um...
All right, let me look.
How about Robert Loggia?
Loggia is older than Robert Dick, I know.
They have a similar quality. They do.
All right, how about...
Mark Wahlberg.
Mark Wahlberg, there we go.
Yeah, that's good. That's good.
Yes, very good. We got it.
Hey, we gotta get this Maniac Cop.
I put an Affleck in the role, too.
I'm tired of this Maniac Cop doing stuff in my city.
We gotta get him.
That's a decent attempt, right?
It is.
Wait, what was that?
Oh, Leota's good, sure.
Leota would be great.
Leota's also having some weird face issues.
Leota's like...
You're just like, why on earth is Ray Leota getting a facelift?
It's just tragic to me.
Yeah, I don't know.
He's got an eye lift. It's just sad.
Everybody got facelifts. It was no big deal.
Okay.
That's a Nicholson bleeding into a Leota.
As far back as I can remember, I wanted to look like an old woman.
Leota's a difficult impression.
I can do the laugh.
I won't do it into the mic because it'll blow your ears out.
But I can kind of do a good impression of his laugh.
I've been trying to get a Sam Rockwell down.
I can't get it.
You don't see many apartments with that brick arch in them.
I kind of like it.
It's an awesome apartment.
Yeah.
It makes me mad that he has this apartment.
I mean, it's windowless.
Now, I think this Syracle wants to bang the maniac cop.
I have no doubt about it.
And I think he kills the women.
Or, as I put it, stick it to him.
I think he never found love, and he's killing the women because he can't face his homosexuality, is how I took this movie.
Yes.
Now, the girls are doing table dances.
Have you ever had a table dance, Pat, or a lap dance of any kind?
I have.
I went to a strip club once in New York called Mixed Emotions, which is the best name for a strip club ever.
And what happened in Mixed Emotions that fateful night?
I had mixed emotions about being there.
My friend got a hand job, I believe.
He got a hand job?
Yeah.
All right.
This chick's making a thousand bucks a week, she just said, as a stripper.
I think, what do strippers make now?
A thousand bucks a week.
I'm trying to do the conversion math here.
A thousand bucks a week?
Should we call your sister and ask her?
A thousand bucks a week in 1990.
What would that be now, about $85 ,000 a week?
I think so.
She was doing all right.
Why is she living in that shithole?
She's like, I make a thousand bucks a week.
But I like to stick to my roots.
You think you could live in an apartment where the landlord wouldn't ignore your rape?
There he is.
Just shoving strippers off the stage trying to catch this guy.
We got him.
They just got them serial killer, for those of you at home.
Have you seen a jail where they let you keep your jacket on and everything?
Don't take the ring? Nothing.
Well, why do they take it, so you don't kill yourself or others?
Yeah, they kind of take all your shit from you.
You ever been to jail?
No. Have you?
Not jail. When I was about 10, some buddies and I walked a quick trip at like 3 in the morning to get candy.
And this cop picked us up and brought us to the police station and called each of our mothers.
And every cop that came in was like, did they steal the candy?
And he was like, nah.
They were like, why would you bring them to the police station?
That was a maniac cop.
And then my mom was like, Pat, you're in jail at 3 in the morning? What were you doing?
I'm like, I went to buy some candy.
I like how you tried to make it sound like you sort of knew what jail was like and the story started with when I was 10.
Well, I mean, I'm not saying we were put in the big house, but we were at a police station at 3 in the morning watching actual criminals.
It was horrifying.
I got busted stealing cassette tapes from a department store in Pennsylvania that was called Ports of the World when I was 14.
But they didn't call the cops. They just fined us through the store and told our parents.
And I got a good beating that night.
Yeah, they just called my mom and they were like, yeah, your son's in the police station. No further information.
At that point, like I had never missed a day of school.
That's the kind of kid that I want.
Oh.
Now, what's the other movie? They do this now where they're in the shooting range and then the maniac cop kills them all.
What's the other movie where they kill everybody in the shooting range?
I've never seen one.
Maybe The Heat with Melissa McCarthy?
No, I don't believe so.
Righteous Kill?
Oh, God, with 50 Cent?
Yeah, I would have said with De Niro Pacino.
No, I consider that a 50 Cent vehicle.
I don't know. I've never seen a bunch of people get killed in the shooting range, which is why I like it when it happens in this one.
Sorry, guy that's never seen this. We just ruined what's about to happen.
I imagine 50 Cent is the toughest vitamin water executive.
There's probably no vitamin water executives tougher than 50.
Here we go. Machete, right?
That is machete.
No dialogue.
And there on the right is the landlord from It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia, a show I used to ride for.
Do we see him again?
Yeah, you see him.
Clarence Williams III.
This guy never doesn't play a guy that seems to be coked out of his head.
Just a hundred yard stare.
So this guy was the lead on The Mod Squad, which was a hugely successful show.
And now like ten short years later, he's got three lines of Maniac Cop 2.
I mean, you see that happen to a lot of TV stars.
Yeah, it's just sad, you know.
Whatever happened to those girls from Too Close for Comfort?
I don't know.
I follow one of them on Twitter. She follows me back.
Okay, brag much?
You know who he's reminded me of here is Terrence Howard.
He's got a very similar quality.
And not just because he's black, Joe.
You mean they both look crazy and it makes me uncomfortable the whole time?
Yeah, and they talk at that kind of like sexy whisper.
I like a sexy whisper.
Do not use as a urinal.
I got to get that sign from my house.
I had a big poker game the other night.
Clarence Williams is holding his dick right now.
And he actually says, I'm going to hold my breath and hold my dick.
I had a poker game the other night with like ten guys at my house.
And at the end of the night, I realized the floor was covered in pee.
And I put forth like a clue -style investigation.
Like trying to like casually ask people like, who pees on the floor of a man's home?
Well, who did it?
And then I knew it must have been one of my close friends.
In the living room?
No, in the bathroom. But just like such a miss of the toilet that it was like they'd never gone to the bathroom before.
And in that case, you got to sit down, my friend.
I'm not above sitting.
Well, I'll take a seat.
I'm not above it.
Here we go.
If you peed on my bathroom floor, come forward.
I agree.
Wipe it up. Who doesn't wipe it up?
Absolutely. You got to wipe it up.
Look, occasionally I have what's called a forked stream.
Where it'll shoot out in two directions.
You got to clean that.
Usually caused by sex.
Always caused by sex.
We're jerking it.
All right, Joe.
Jerking it, working it. There he is.
Great shot. That's a really tremendous shot.
Now this is the part where he starts busting through all the glass.
I really like this part a lot.
Upgrades the gun.
Smart move.
Maniac Cop 2 on his way to shoot up the city of New York Police Department, it seems.
That is where he is now, correct?
Now the cool part about this sequence is he starts walking through windows.
The Maniac Cop throughout this movie does seem to have very vague goals until now.
Like he just kind of shows up places and is like, I guess I'll do this now.
Why wasn't this his first order of business?
He had to just work his way to the top.
All right, fine.
That one broke before he walked through it.
That's the one you pointed out before, right?
A couple of these windows break before he hits it.
But it is a cool visual, like a guy that can just walk through walls.
Very cool.
Oh, yeah, that's the best one.
That's the mother of all harness throws.
Uh -oh.
I'm still thinking about what kind of other maniac occupation I would have.
You know?
Maniac cobbler?
Yeah, like you're a pair of shoes, but you're also a maniac?
No, you're a cobbler, you make shoes.
You're not a pair of shoes.
In this market, you think cobblers don't also repair shoes?
They have to make money.
Yeah, but it sounded like you said you're a pair of shoes.
You repair shoes.
Oh, repair shoes, okay.
Jesus Christ.
Yeah.
What would the catchphrase be?
I got nothing.
No, it's tough.
All I could think of was that split decision thing, and I got nothing since then.
You peaked too early.
Close your eyes.
You may see something you like.
Come on, man.
I see this woman as a poor man's Rachel Wise.
Rachel Wise hasn't been in a movie in 10 years.
She's in The Lobster with Colin Farrell, which is about to come out.
It looks tremendous, right?
That's a poor man's Rachel Wise.
Sure.
I'm going back to him.
Well, I think that's where it's going to end.
They're going back to sensing.
No, he wouldn't let that happen to a pleasing personality like yourself.
Listen, I just want to have a rational talk with this guy.
Let's talk about sensing.
There he is.
Oh, yeah, you're right.
He's the guy that the DeVito won't ever pick.
Okay, yeah.
I really like that the serial killer is so crazy that when he's talking to the maniac cop, even the maniac cop is like, yeah, you're a little much for me.
Yeah, we're going to recruit an army.
You go ahead first to recruit the army and I'll catch up to you.
Okay.
Michael Lerner pissed off again.
What the hell is this?
Betty, grab my pipe.
Lustig never really went on to have that big success.
This is a very well -made action movie.
Why did he never get other work?
And he considers this his masterpiece, I read.
Well, it's certainly what he's known for.
I mean, I'd give Uncle Sam a ride around the block.
Sure.
I've never seen it.
Ken, have you seen Uncle Sam?
No.
Have you seen Jack Frost?
Jack Frost.
Well, wait, which one? The Michael Keaton one or the horror one?
The horror one.
Which, by the way, when I worked at Blockbuster, many people mixed those up and showed their kids the horror one.
You know what I thought you were going to say?
I thought when I said the Michael Keaton one or the horror one, you were going to go, what's the difference?
Yeah, well, they're both.
Jack Frost with Michael Keaton is one of the worst movies ever made.
It's what sent him into retirement for like 15 years.
And the horror one, he assaults a woman with a carrot.
How happy are you that Keaton's back?
He's the best.
Very happy about that.
Because now finally we might get that Jack Frost sequel off the ground.
I have an idea for Keaton.
I'm pitching this out loud right now to everybody.
Mr. Mom sequel.
Mr. Grandmom.
That's good.
It could work.
Yeah, no, I'm not saying it could.
I mean, I mean, it writes itself.
That old man.
I mean, the stunts again.
Incredible.
Absolutely incredible stunts.
They use zero models.
This is all.
This is like smoking the band and level stunt work or Blues Brothers.
I got to tell you, Michael Lerner versus the Maniac Cop is not a fair fight.
For those of you at home, Robert Davy just told Michael Lerner he was the only one that could stop the Maniac Cop.
Which Michael Lerner, if he could eat a sandwich without panting, I'd be shocked.
When he pulled that gun just now, they had to like take us a break for about a week.
And let him rest up to continue the scene.
By the way, we had a giveaway before the movie and I want to apologize to the young woman who got the Poltergeist remake.
Terrible.
Just terrible.
Sam Rockwell, my favorite actor.
We talked about it on the show. It was just a tragedy.
Terrible.
I don't know if that's even considered a prize.
Rockwell impression, ready?
It's more of a punishment.
I'll take my Sam Rockwell impression.
Ready?
We got a Poltergeist.
This house is crazy.
That's good.
One guy back there or lady gets it.
Somebody's cackling.
I tell you, between my Wahlberg and your Rockwell, we could really not do anything with these impressions.
The only other impression I can do is Tom Waits in an interview.
Let's hear it.
Well, I like the film Maniac Cop because I've always related to justice.
That's sort of a thing.
That's good.
It's a decent impression.
Yeah.
Do you have any others?
I do a bunch, but they have to be just spontaneous.
I can't do them forced.
Well, then they're not really impressions, are they, Pat?
No, not at all.
Sounds more like flying by the seat of your ass.
Oh, I do a Gandalfini.
You ready?
Yeah.
What are we going to do about this Maniac Cop?
Carmelo, what are we going to do about this Maniac Cop?
It's terrible, right?
I still stand by my claim that The Sopranos is one of the worst television shows of all time.
Jesus Christ, AJ.
Yeah, you hate everything that's good and love everything that's bad.
It's not true.
It's not true at all.
All right.
You have no other examples.
Don't say Tower Heist.
I'll hit you with this fucking microphone.
Oh, yeah.
Joe was like, Pat, you got to watch Tower Heist.
I sat and watched this thing.
He's like, huh?
It's a funny movie.
All right, fine.
Tower Heist.
I didn't say it was great.
I said it was enjoyable.
You like Norbit.
I thought you'd enjoy it.
Yeah, you own Norbit.
I tolerated Norbit.
I own Norbit because it's a masterpiece.
It's horrifically racist, Norbit.
Eddie Murphy is it.
It is terribly racist.
Yeah, you're right.
Eddie Murphy is the Asian guy.
How that got passed.
I have no idea how he got that in.
But Eddie Murphy as the husband and wife is masterful.
Yeah, it's got some laughs, Norbit.
That also sounds sort of like a like a like an Andy Garcia.
Yeah.
What are you doing AJ?
Carmella.
Is that Gandolfini?
Yeah.
I keep having visions of this woman in season four.
Show stinks.
Well, you've seen three scattered episodes from different seasons.
I don't give a shit.
All right.
I know bad when I see it.
It is just widely considered pretty much the best television show ever made.
But go ahead and have your opinion.
You going to tell me it was better than True Detective season one?
Yeah, I am.
You fucking asshole.
They also managed to sustain the Sopranos for more than eight episodes before falling into a cauldron of shit.
Look at this guy.
Richard Grieco made it out.
Whatever happened to Grieco?
He had that if looks could kill, which was supposed to be his James Bond.
And then we never heard from him again.
Yeah, that was like how the guy that played Nick on Family Ties was in My Demon Lover.
And then that was the end of the line.
Grieco was in Night at the Roxbury.
As Richard Grieco.
As Grieco.
Never a good sign.
That's like how Screech was in Made as Screech.
Yeah.
And the joke was Vince Vaughn Cohen.
Did you just fucking let Screech in the club and not us?
Right.
Never a good position to be in if you're Screech.
Or Billy Zane in Zoolander or whatever else.
I love Billy Zane though.
Sure.
Billy Zane used to be in all those soft core like porn movies.
Red Shoe Diaries.
Yeah.
And this was like the typical like Billy Zane description in the TV guide for a movie.
It'd be like a reluctant handyman falls into the wiles of a lonely housewife.
That was like Billy Zane's whole career.
Then he got Titanic.
Insane.
Insane that he got that part.
Do you find Billy Zane a little hammy in Titanic?
Little over the top?
Yeah, he's a little hammy but in a good way.
In like a Pacino way.
When he's drop kicking babies into the ocean and everything that he does.
He's like Pacino hammy so I like it.
Alright.
Michael Lerner is now trying to defuse this situation by telling the maniac cop that his conviction which was wrongful to begin with will be reversed.
Hopefully that'll stop the killing.
Problem is you still have Clarence Williams III.
Who's just got a hard dick to kill something.
And the other guy that looks like Mick Foley.
Still alive Clarence Williams III?
I believe so.
I mean I'd love to just go to that guy's house on a Saturday night and explore the mountains of cocaine that are being stored.
Allegedly.
I'm just saying he looks like a guy that parties.
This guy in a towel.
Towel perfectly staying on.
I'll tell you if I'm in prison I don't walk the grounds in a towel.
This is an awesome sequence here.
They light maniac cop on fire and he still takes everybody down while he's burning.
Again real stunts no CGI fire.
That guy is on fire right now.
Very Frankenstein -esque.
Nice.
Oof.
How did they do this shit?
They have a safe word like in case he actually gets burned.
Just seems terrifying to me.
Well there's a technique I think it's called like cold fire or something but they put a gel on you that burns and apparently the fire is cooler than normal fire.
Something like that.
But I'm sure there's a safe word yeah.
And then they have like eight guys with extinguishers ready to put you out you know.
Serial killers burn up through the wall.
They fall to their deaths.
Now I'm going to go out and live here and say that just because you're on fire and you fell into a bus it wouldn't explode like that.
No I agree.
What do you think?
I agree.
Here we are in our final scene.
Now surely no one could have been surprised that that hand coming out of the coffin at the end of this.
Stop ruining it for the kid that's never seen it.
He would have had no way of suspecting the maniac cop would return.
He knows that there's Maniac Cop 3 Badge of Silence.
I know I'm kidding.
Badge of Silence.
What does that even mean?
What does that mean?
It's the worst title I've ever heard.
Badge of Silence.
Worse than Children of the Corn, Fields of Terror or whatever the fuck that fucking sequel was called.
Actually Quantum of Solace is probably the worst like big title I've ever heard in my life.
I still don't know what it even means.
Daniel Craig doesn't know what it means.
Quantum of Solace.
That's a good name for an action movie.
They are giving Matt.
What's his name? Matt Cornell?
Matt Cornell.
Maybe Matt Cordell.
Give Matt Cordell a proper burial at the end of the movie here.
He's been absolved of all falsely accused wrongdoing.
I love how they come to pay their respect.
Like you know he was a good guy after all that maniac cop.
Despite the women he murdered in the first film and the shop owner and newspaper clerk and decent cops that he murdered in this film.
The traffic cop that he hung from a hook.
We should go to his funeral.
He seemed like a cool guy.
Yeah literally Michael Lerner is just like the lesson is Michael Lerner being like I was asking for it. I'm sorry.
Yeah it's a terrible message.
Look I've made mistakes.
It was a terrible message.
Why did the picture suddenly get incredibly clear?
Looks really good.
This is the 25th anniversary by the way of maniac cop.
Happy 25th babe.
Sure.
There's that badge of silence.
Half melted from the fire.
Uh oh.
Shouldn't have done that Davi.
That's all this guy needs is his badge back.
I also found, well you're going to see it here in a second, but he has a very non -threatening hand bust out.
He just kind of casually grabs his badge as you'll see.
And do you think these two are off to shtup?
I hope they do it in the graveyard.
You ever make out in a graveyard?
I think I was fingered once in a graveyard.
By a corpse?
I did, I once made out with a young lady in a graveyard and she was wearing patchouli and every time I smell it to this day I get an erection.
I get a corpse motor.
Lasher, that's a much better name for a maniac cop.
Jack Lasher.
No, let's go with Mike Cordell.
Matt Cordell.
Sounds like a good name of an MTV VJ.
Yeah, it's Matt Cordell.
He brings the hottest indie jams.
You guys like that one? That was the Gin Blossoms.
I love the Gin Blossoms, they're an underrated band.
Now this guy's come back from the dead twice.
Do we want to cover the coffin with anything?
Nah, it'll be fine.
Should we put some dirt in there? Nah, just leave it an open grave.
He's fine, he's dead.
Michael Lerner apologized to him, that's the end of it.
How was your day at work, honey?
Oh boy, I tell you.
I thought that was a good bust out and grab.
Alright, I was wrong.
Ladies and gentlemen. Folks.
Hold on.
Let's all just take in the song and the closing credits.
Please listen to this hip hop explanation of the plot of Maniac Cop 2.
As Ken pointed out last night, you weren't a movie in the 80s
unless they recapped the plot at the end with a rap song.
Right.
And then Will Smith brought it back with Men in Black and Wild Wild West.
Okay.
That's a terrible one.
Set him on fire, shoot him with his, you'll show up in your jacuzzi.
That doesn't happen in any of the movies.
No.
As far as I know, correct?
That's like some Maniac Cop fan fiction where the rappers are like,
what if he was in our jacuzzi?
He'll show up in your jacuzzi to do what?
Yeah.
Then I was like, oh, who'd they give him to do that?
When you get Run DMC or whatever at the end of the movie,
it's like just two guys' names did this rap song.
Like Matt Cordell.
Matt Cordell.
Rap by Matt Cordell.
Ladies and gentlemen, Maniac Cop 2.
Let's hear it.
Thank you so much for coming, everybody.
Thank you for coming.
This has been We'll See You in Hell, production of the Fangoria Podcast Network.
If you want to learn about any other Fangoria podcasts,
whatever, go to fangoria .com.
You can email our good friend here, Ken, at fangoria .com.
Thanks for coming out, everybody.
You were really a lot of fun.