I'll see you in hell back with our final episode for the month of November.
discussing the film heretic or yes you called it heretic heretic heretic heretic
I've heard various pronunciations heretic Harry dick it was the working title
which I thought was a good good move Tom dick and Harry dick but yeah the
new 824 picture Hugh Grant from Beckin Woods the team that wrote a quiet place
then John Krasinski said thanks boy I'll take all the credit from here and then
they made Haunt which we reviewed on the show but I remember nothing about
Haunt is the where they go to the haunted house but it's actual murderers or
whatever yeah yeah I don't remember it being very good I didn't care for
that but I also didn't care for a quiet place yeah so well here what you
thought about heretic I watched an interview I'm just glad that good go on no
I was gonna say I watched an interview with Hugh Grant recently promoting the
movie and he said like they were asking about like his bumbling you know how
you he would always be like like all the time you know he said when he when he when
for weddings in a funeral hit he he wrote like the public liked him as that
character and he said so I thought I should just be like that in my interviews
all the time like yeah basically said that that was his you know his approach
which is interesting again you grant much like we talked about with Rocky
Belbow and Sylvester Stallone if you meet Hugh Grant and he's not doing that
you're gonna be disappointed you're like please be bumbling drop something and well
the new Hugh is an asshole and I love this Hugh way more than I love the old
Hugh because now when you see him interviewed on a talk show or something he's
usually just being kind of mean there was a notorious interview where he really
dressed down the lady for just asking like generic questions and that interview he
comes off like a big asshole but in the other ones he just seems like he's a grump
and he's always got a little bit of a smirk and a twinkle in his eye and I like that
vibe for him I like him playing villains because it was always there it was like
he was America's sweetheart male division and then we come to find out he's
banging like a real sex worker like this wasn't a high class call girl you know
this guy simple taste as a freak side to him yeah and I don't know why he didn't
embrace it at the time for a while he tried to be Mr like extreme measures and
all that stuff like he was like a straight man and I'm like I'm not on like this
at all but I do love asshole villain Hugh Grant I like to miss the bad guy in
Addington to I liked him in this and I didn't love the movie but I liked him in
this I it would be interesting to see because he was the male version of Julia
Roberts that's why I said America sweetheart yeah I'm thinking now let's get
third act of Julia Roberts playing like villains and stuff that'd be fun well
Julia Roberts I had never heard it until very recently but she is rumored to be really difficult
which she kind of avoided that reputation for a very long time so as Hugh Grant by the way
it's supposed to be very difficult but yeah you know at some point yeah you got to just be like
I don't know it's much harder for me having worked with assholes to allow the behavior I used to always
be like hey as long as the final product is good but yeah it does kind of eat a way at you
and kind of change your perception of people when you find out what they did I didn't
heard anything particular about those two I just always kind of heard they're rough I also get it
to if you're the person being like hey guys everybody's here because of me like this is happening
because of me so why don't we get our shit together like I get that I get it somebody yeah by the
10th movie like for Christ sakes guys please you know when Tom Cruise blew up at everybody on top
gone about the COVID restrictions and that tape got out I was like he's 100 % right yeah yeah he's
the reason everyone has a job if he gets sick they lose a hundred million dollars like where you're
fucking shit where your mask he was right sometimes they're right and sometimes you need the star to be
the one to kind of yell at everybody because people will listen to the star but it is this bad system
where if you're told you can have anything you want from the age of 21 on it's not going to make you
the most level person probably no it should but it doesn't no no and let's let's be honest Pat
when I don't have everything we want and we're not the most lovable people so maybe it's just kind of
the way it goes with everybody yeah I I've got a scary stuff please this is just for the Star Wars
fans in the room Star Wars Outlaws a disaster of a video game that dropped a few months back it was the
first open world Star Wars game it was basically Grand Theft Auto except Star Wars everybody was
excited there'd never been anything like this in the video game universe for Star Wars finally you
were gonna be able to go and and and sort of live in this world and whatever the game was poorly received
it was plagued by terrible stealth mechanics and there were many levels where you had to do stealth
missions and it was extraordinarily frustrating I did a video on Instagram where I in real time
videotape myself ejecting the game out of the PlayStation and throwing it across the room
because on the 65th try of a level because the stealth mechanics are so broken you're just like I'm
done I'm not doing this anymore anyway there were other issues as well Ubisoft who put the game out
uh the the director of the game uh or the head of development of the game whoever it was has stepped
down there is a new person in that role and this new guy has said we are doing a major overhaul of
the game it is coming soon and the reports keep building that this major overhaul is going to fix
every issue with the game to such an extent that it will be a new game to play so I am hopeful
I am looking forward to trying the new version I'm gonna have to rebuy the fucking game
because I just traded it in I was so mad at it um but I'm looking forward to that what did they do
do they release like a patch that updates it or what yeah yeah they'll they'll do a major pat it
you know with with all these new games you can you can kind of fix things in sort of real time so
yeah they'll they'll introduce a major patch I'm sure it'll take an hour to download it
and it will reconfigure the way the game functions so um I'm looking forward to that I want to see
what that's all about fingers crossed it'll be good and it's hopefully going to drop around the same time
as the other video game I'm terribly excited for which is Indiana Jones in the Great Circle
um which is coming from Bethesda in December it is the first first person Indiana Jones game ever
I think it's gonna be awesome to play as Indiana Jones in first person uh and early reviews are
are mostly positive and one of the review one of the things that's consistently I'm seeing in the reviews is
it's fun and it's funny like it feels like Indiana Jones like he's kind of clumsy and you know
like it has the quirkiness and fun and funniness that that the original movies had so um I hope that
characters like Indiana Jones get to live on in countless adventures in video games they're used
it's not Harrison Ford's voice but it is his likeness and the guy playing Indian it I forget his name
he's great like when you watch the trailer you're like shit dude I thought that was Indian I thought
that was Harrison Ford um so fingers crossed that this is the start of something great and we'll get
many more stories um that we can experience and be a part of so I'm excited
very well um what have we been talking about in the world of movies Joe you and I privately I mean
yeah what have we been shitting on um we got a we got a collection of never before heard
stand up from Robin Williams coming out which feels real weird to me especially considering does
the does the guy have any famous stand -up bits obviously a comedy legend does he have like a killer
stand -up bit that I missed yeah yeah he uh well you know I don't know I mean yeah there's the thing
from the one special where he's doing like the Shakespeare thing that everybody always liked uh
but no I don't know I don't fucking know you know the the the albums called working on things
yeah and as I said to you see so you're putting on an album given by the title of sort of half -baked
stuff that he was just kind of what it playing around with that you recorded by and I don't
mean any disrespect but guys even the guys finished product is still him kind of winging it and whatever
you know what I mean what the hell does the half -baked thing sound like so I don't know it just
seems like squeezing the last bit of juice out of the lemon um but who knows uh I mean we we still
get a new uh biggie and two pocket album every two three years so I guess why can't we do in the
comedy world too I sent you something last night I had purchased the blue ray of you've got mail
which to my surprise included a bonus DVD of shop around the corner starting Jimmy Stewart with
that was a nice surprise when I opened it and saw that in there I'd never seen it that's a really
great movie so really it is it's awesome I watched it last night I watched both back to back
but yeah the reason I texted you was because the back I mean talk about a movie where nobody gives a
shit and then the phrasing so this is the blue ray release of you've got mail huge font at the top
of the back of the box the modern romance classic gets a seductive high -deaf sparkle
what housewife is is excited about that yeah because let's be honest there's two people buying
this movie three you me and housewives there are no other yeah uh men and there's a wild one but
I'm not saying a housewife like can't care about a high -deaf movie but she's not going oh
thank god you've got mail finally that's the high -deaf sparkle honey it's a sensual high -deaf sparkle
they're saying can we buy it tonight would you watch it with me they're saying it's seductive
my favorite blue ray case remarks is this one from Jennifer's body I wrote it down years ago
it says sexy temptress Megan Fox is hotter than hell as Jennifer a gorgeous seductive cheerleader
it's like fellas is she good looking do you think maybe you could clarify if she's attractive or not
holy shit that whole description is basically saying guys as far as miners go it doesn't get any hotter
than this crazy yeah you're gonna love Jennifer's body wink wink uh yeah pretty wild that the people
who do those are like the people who who do promos for your show you watch the promo for your show
and you're like wait you didn't get this at all why are we letting people who don't understand the
business write the copy but the thing is you're not gonna hire professional writers to write your little
DVD sticker so you get these losers and then you wind up with these insane paragraphs on the back
of a DVD um here's another one I sent you here's a guy whose reviews I'm gonna start reading based
on the the the title of this review and just his name yeah this guy reviews for the New York post
his name is Johnny Aleksinsky okay sounds like a bully from a Stephen King now no I love that he's
still going by Johnny uh yeah I didn't read the review oh shit it's Johnny we gotta run we better make a
good movie Johnny's here um it's just the title just killed me red one review Colin Chris Evans on the
rock kill Christmas with a zero star 250 million dollar turd Jesus Christ heard that's somebody who
went to the Rex Reed School of Journalism uh we may or may not do red one around Christmas time I
mean it's supposed to be as you just heard a turd and yet there's something calling me about it I don't
know what it is audiences are liking it it's audience score and rotten tomatoes is pretty high
uh yeah or at least fresh critics are hating it I gotta say when I saw the trailer I was like I'll
just go see this with my mom like it'll be a fun thing to watch with my mom like it seems harmless
enough so I don't know I don't get but I mean there are like YouTube videos about this thing dissecting
why it's so terrible I'm very curious to see what's so offensive about this movie yeah well it's um
it's Jake Kazden who did the new jumanji pictures which I thought were way better than they needed to be
so I guess I'm hoping it's in that camp and I like that they brought Bonnie Hunt back I feel like
Bonnie Hunt has played Mrs. Claus a thousand times whether that's true or not she gives me strong
Mrs. Claus vibes yeah and JK Simmons the man that has always was born to play Santa Claus in some
iteration yeah you got the rock in Evans usually you know for a movie like this bringing all the charisma
you could possibly need uh and then this does nothing for me the rock he was kind of a laughing stock
this week because he talked about how he saw did you see this he talked about we saw
a Oppenheimer in iMAX and he went up and was like I want the Christopher Nolan seat where does Chris sit
when he does his screenings and he was I sat down I'm watching Oppenheimer I'm swept away and uh
at some point I step out I text Jake I go red one on this screen we got something real hot here baby
it's like you're you're watching Oppenheimer and you're thinking about your kidnapping Santa movie
also had you never seen an iMAX picture before the rock all of your movies come out in iMAX it's one of
the weirdest news stories I've ever seen and it was all week in movie news look at this idiot who thinks
that red one is as good as Oppenheimer I'm like he's not saying that but why is he pretending he just
learned about the iMAX format I just got something wrong with the rock he's weirdo
Jake Quaid just did two episodes of red letter media you know I talked about that length on here
there but there's a really funny thing man where they're they're they're all they're all talking about
these movies they watched and they're doing the reviews and they're drinking and you can see in
their eyes they're all like shit can't and uh Jake Quaid at one point goes Jack Quinn or Jack Quaid
excuse me goes uh yeah last time I was here I was who's when I was shooting Oppenheimer and uh Mike the
guy from red letter meter he goes oh yeah how'd that do that do anything that go anywhere
uh kind of make the big one something that connects with the public it was weird because I actually
hung out with uh Jack Quaid once with Sal it was me Sal Jack Quaid and Harvey Gillian from what we do in
the shadows I was always there whoever's hanging out he's he's the fourth guy he was they were both
awesome I bonded a little more with with with Harvey like uh Harry Harvey I'm now blanking
on his name Jesus anyway I actually kept him touch with him for a little while he was very nice
but so was Jack but it was like we were like I think I was playing like beer pong or something with Jack
Quaid in this bar and then like half he he was just talking like just we're talking about life and
he was like yeah it's weird you know my mom and my dad you know they like to go did that and I'm like
he's talking about fucking Meg Ryan and Dennis Quaid like this is nuts like what is it like I'm
I thought about this last night watching you got mail what is it like for your mom to be Meg Ryan
that is wild for sure mom's Meg Ryan like that talk about America's sweethearts as we talked on the
last episode I mean that's old I couldn't wrap my head around if it's if it's all you know I guess if
you're just with your life I don't know what to say I was friends with Eden Brolin when she lived in
New York and when we both lived in LA and she's Josh Brolin's daughter right she sent me pictures
once of Josh Brolin playing with my dog because she was watching my dog which was really weird uh to
see but anyway um yeah one day we're hanging out and it just hit me and I go Eden what the fuck your
grandmother is Barbara Streisand like your step grandmother is Barbara Streis and she's like yeah
and I was like what is that like she's like I don't know if she's just barb yeah I guess so like you're
just like this is the lady by grandfather married is her mother um Diane Lane no her stepmom's Diane
Lane her mom her mom was actually actually my acting teacher I would I would do one -on -one such as
with her mom and she was great she helped me a lot when I was doing better calls to blame oh boy
oh boy um nice family very nice family very nice people our brother was lovely good good kids that
does Brolin okay Brolin Brolin Brolin Brolin mm -hmm right mm -hmm there you go yeah yeah anyway
I just was looking here to see if I had missed any big news stories or isn't it didn't but 15 minutes
ago they announced that Warner Brothers has just formed a giant production packed to simply develop
remakes oh Jesus Christ they're just saying the quiet part loud now it's like we have a whole new
division for remaking shit that's we just laid off all kinds of creative talented people and now we're
gonna give you more of the same it's it's getting sad out here it's sad we're in a phase where it is
such a fuck you to the audience it's insane you know I talked a little bit about the Jake Paul Tyson
fight and I was saying to I was with my buddy Scott who you've met yeah brought up when we came to
your house and drank the weed lemonade and watched old school and went into a another dimension
after each after Scott and I having two sips and then a Scott reminded me coming to and being like
what planet are we on looking over and watching you finishing off the full bottle
and we were like I don't understand um anyway we um we were talking about the Tyson Paul fight
and I said you know man just these two it was just such bullshit like you know they just
danced around for the money it was so it was such bullshit and he was like well you know what are
you gonna do he's an old fighter and I said yeah I can't argue that you're an old fighter go make
your last bit of money that's what you do you know it's the same thing as a comic you know going um
70 I'm gonna go do this cruise ship I'm gonna mail it in I'm gonna take home some cash and I'm done
whatever I get that yeah I said you know what really bothered me it was the hype leading up to it
30 20 years ago that fight would have just been that fight and everybody would have said
it's an old guy fighting a young guy he can't get hurt it was what it was it was a money grab who cares
now I said when you do a month lead up of the boy is in trouble Mike what's your prediction in the ring
smashing uh we're gonna press conference where I slap him in the face and all this I go
at that point you're swindling the audience but they can't and then they so they swindle the audience
then they give you the product that is a complete letdown and contradiction of everything they told
you it was gonna be and the message is we don't fucking care we got your money you watched we're
done here go complain to somebody nobody's listening it's literally the thing in uh Glengar
Glenn Ross where ad Harris goes you don't sell a man one car you sell him five cars over 15 years
but these people think we know what we're gonna do we're gonna go out and take everybody's money and
then skip town because nobody ever thought of that before that's what's happening now it's we the
entertainment business is in the stage of real estate sales that Glen Gary Glen Ross takes place
in where it's like this used to be a business it is now just a scam and they don't care they just
don't care that they're scamming you yeah I didn't watch the fight and all I heard about it was
they had streaming issues but was it an additional rate or was it just your Netflix subscription get
to you into the fine no no it was just part of the Netflix subscription but you know dude there were
streaming issues it crashed Netflix and when's the last fucking time you heard that happening it crashed
Netflix um right that's how many people were watching this thing Pat I was out hey I was actually with
Q I was out hanging out with Q we were like bar hopping around this fucking thing was playing
everywhere bars were like designating rooms to it this was a massive massive massive
massive event and the fact that they built it up in the way they did knowing exactly what it was
gonna be it's not just being okay with swindling your audience it's saying we don't give a shit that
we know you're you're being swindled now and it's so sad it's so sad and it's reflective of politics
it's reflective of everything now it's just this is what we live in tough shit well what was the you
know the brief synopsis of the fight what exactly happened how long was it and so I know Jake
Paul won Tyson through 60 punches in eight rounds which okay if you know a fight that's insane
um yeah Jake Paul threw I think 130 um they danced around one another barely connected
and Jake Paul won by decision it was a it was a fucking
bars now again 20 years ago it would have just been like guys it's an exhibition match they're
not gonna get too into it he can't get hurt all that stuff and you would have just left it there
but that's not what they did what they did was this marketing blitz where where they made everybody
think Tyson was going in there hungry for his last hurrah for his swan song as the greatest fighter
that's ever lived and right and it just wasn't and it was just such a hustle man it's just it's just
lame it's lame it's lame it's lame and the monopoly that Netflix is now attaining
uh in in the entertainment business and look I collect checks from Netflix okay I'm not saying that
uh that you know I've said a million times on here I've had plenty of criticisms for Netflix and
I also say if they're if they'll give you money to do something do it it doesn't mean that I have to
approve of everything they do and I certainly don't approve of the fact that they're forming a full
fucking monopoly on entertainment now with live events and all this stuff and this this is a terrible
precedent to set if this is where we're starting that this is this is the event the sporting event
you know WWE is going to Netflix uh yeah raw and I think Smackdown as well are going to be on Netflix
now the two TV events every week and it's just it's just a shame it's just a shame but I don't know
I guess their defense would be well yeah but we can't tell them what to say we can't tell them what
to do and what are we going to do tell them not to hype it up so you know I don't know
it's where we're at it's everything it's everything now you know we talked to Mike Tyson and Jake
Paul got some money well you and I talked about the thing with um when I emailed you when I got
when I when I got my screen factory order and my copy of Halloween 4k was not only unwrapped but the
box like the case was damaged not the cover art or the slip cover right and I emailed them and I was
like hey guys you know this came it wasn't wrapped for some reason and the plastic is damaged it
looks like you sent me like a used thing and the response was that can happen during manufacturing
that's normal yeah then they don't address the package being not wrapped and then they just say
anyway if you want to return it here's a link and you go figure it out for yourself and it's like
what is this what is this come on come on man you sound like Joe Biden right there come on man
I mean come on I hear you everything is bad I need to share an email I got from an Amazon the other day
Amazon by the way now gives you 24 hours to ship something used to give you three days they did not
tell me that they changed that I'm a I sell stuff all the time and all of a sudden I got like 12 late
shipments which works against my seller rating they're a dirty company so here's what this guy wrote
me his name is Greg hang on Greg
he says hey I'm wondering this is just something he found online that I was selling this is a once
upon a time in the west the 4k came out and immediately went out of print I bought it for 20 bucks
I'm selling it for like 85 dollars okay okay so you can it was a special edition that I didn't need with
all kinds of features and I'm like I'll just get the basic version and make 65 bucks buy something
else on Amazon so I have it listed and this guy writes me I want to bring up the exact wording it's
always very important why can I find it I don't know it's okay though it's gonna be okay
where do you I'm not I don't know you know what's that I'm just trying to find this shit where do you
find your messages on oh excuse me it is a nightmare trying to find yeah dude it's forget it man it's
it's nuts yeah all right then I'll just have to give you the gist and I and it's as close to
accurate as I can get this guy writes me and he's like hey I'm wondering about your 4k of once upon
a time in the west I'm like this isn't how this is supposed to work or you ask me about something I
have for sale this isn't a brick and mortar shop it keeps happening people are like does this
have the slip cover on it or whatever this guy goes I noticed you have this for sale I'm wondering
if I could get it for half price say 3999 question mark I'm wondering if I could do this as sort of a
thank you from my loyalty what an ass I write him back and I go I go sir what loyalty are you
referring to you've never bought anything from me and he goes well I'm about to buy this 4k from you
dot dot dot or am I fuck off I'm like you're talking about loyalty even though you've never done anything
for me and now you're like being weirdly threatening so I said no I'm not dropping the price for it
that's the price he goes so what if I were to say that maybe I'll buy future products from you that
wouldn't change anything in your mind I go you're talking about future loyalty like you're going to
maybe buy something from from my little Amazon store in the future how do you know what you're
going to want and if I have it then I realize I'm talking to an insane person I wrote him back I
said it just sold for the full price I just sold it for 80 bucks so please stop emailing me that's the
other thing at Amazon if somebody emails you you have to respond or your account gets shut down
you have 24 hours to respond it's like gun to your head shit so that when some cook writes you like
you know visibly drunk in the email like hey how much is your beast master DVD going for
you have to respond and go the price is listed it's x amount of dollars like the whole system
they've decided to make it more customer friendly and what's that what that's leading to is people
ripping off the seller I get a lot of people getting the item saying they didn't get it and wanting
their money back there's only so far down that road I can go before I'm losing money baby yeah
it's losing sell through as they call it in the business yeah that's let's get to that that's
fucking ridiculous though and yeah and it sucks because you can't message the guy back and say no
fuck off oh that I've done it and they immediately report you and then you get into a bunch of
trouble but I have done it it's too tempting sometimes to be like shut the fuck up you lose
and then they immediately forward it to Amazon by the way if somebody writes me fuck you you loser
that me I sent it to Amazon nothing happens they're like you're the seller the customer is right
hey let's get to that movie corner I mean I don't even know if I fucking seen anything here
I'd you start us Joe I've only got a couple yeah I've got
well I watch I finally I watched that I got the Prince of Darkness as I was talking about the
screen factory stuff I'll talk about my two two screen factories that I watched I got out of that
hall the ones I led with were Prince of Darkness I you know I'd never seen it we we've talked
about it a million times on the show I tried to watch it a couple of times I found it boring
um I just it wasn't grabbing me and I'd never finished it however I just watched some
John Carpenter documentary I can't remember what I saw it on
excuse me it must have been YouTube or something I don't know I watched something about John Carpenter
where he talked about the thing was the movie he put everything into you know he considered it to
be like his masterpiece and then it bombed terribly and he was so fed up with the studio system
and the idea of you're making somebody else's movie whether you like it or not that he went and
signed a deal for two independent films uh and wanted to get back to his roots and the first of those
two was Prince of Darkness and given the footage they showed in this little doc um I was like oh
that looks like there's cool shit in Prince of Darkness all right I want to give it another shot
then I ended up buying the 4k also because the 4k was on sale but also because everybody said
it out of the Carpenter 4k is that one arguably looks the best uh it does it looks excellent
and I did enjoy the movie it takes a minute to get going but you've got Donald Pleasants in it
doing this thing which is great the whole cast is great and it's creepy it's spooky once it gets
rolling you're really you're really into it um it's basically a movie about uh spirituality
meeting technology um it's uh it's definitely it definitely has the feel of sort of classic John
Carpenter uh it it fits right into that wheelhouse um I think the idea was conceived by
uh well actually it says it was just written by Carpenter I thought he had written this
um alongside um Debra Hill but he didn't I thought she was involved in this too and I guess
she wasn't maybe she was a producer on it no I don't know she didn't work on this one with him
anyway uh I liked I liked it it's it's like I said it's it's about it's about a team of uh physics
students led by Victor Wong who plays the professor uh who are summoned by a priest played by Donald
Pleasants whose character is just called priest which is interesting um they he says you must come to
our church and help us they go Pleasants reveals they have found this room in the church it was sort of
a secret room and one of the priests there that had died was doing research on something happening
in this room and you realize what is happening is the antichrist is coming uh and they basically
set up computers and uh machinery in order to monitor it and see what's going on uh and it goes from
there of course it gets out it infects one person and then that you know sort of like the thing and
then the infection is jumping and killing everybody and blah blah blah uh it's it's I'm not doing the
plot full service it gets into some very cool existential and philosophical concepts uh but that's the
basic just um it's something that could have sort of lived and died in the world of like an evil
speak where it was just a sort of cheesy demons coming out of the computer thing and it goes far
beyond that um and it's an enjoyable film uh it's not too long you know 101 minutes uh and I think
it's worth a watch excuse me I think it's absolutely worth a watch and uh I'm glad I own it I will
revisit it and it it's a great one to put on at Halloween time I gotta give it another chance
I've never been a fan of Prince of Darkness and I watched it fairly recently so that's probably just
my opinion but oh well um I sure Olivia Rodrigo the guts world tour sometimes I just want to know
what's going on with the young people I went and saw the Taylor Swift era's tour show the live uh
or not live the movie theater version and I was like I get it I had a good time even though this
Taylor Swift show was way too long I had a good time I see why people like her and I like Olivia
Rodrigo I have both of her albums I think she suffers from what a lot of pop stars suffer from which is
that the songs that are great are very great and the songs that are filler are very filler so when
you're Olivia Rodrigo and you're only pulling from two albums uh the concert's gonna be half filler two
you're not like Taylor Swift where you're pulling from a hundred hits uh I didn't know Olivia Rodrigo
was a child she's she's 21 years old I didn't know a lot of things but um this felt a little more sort
of kitty to me definitely than the Taylor Swift thing I felt a little purvy watching it at times
um but the music is good I like that Rodrigo had the breeders open for her on this tour I like when
somebody young uses their influence to like introduce her generation to great older people um and
she's got a lot of energy she's a great performer you know my one kind of complaint about the modern
female pop world is that like back in my day the 1800s folks Liz Fair would have a song about like
like she has a song called fucking run that I love fucking run even when I was 17 fucking run
fuck and run even when I was 12 my dad used to sing that around the house
um but she was like the shocker you know she was like the oh my god this this beautiful young woman
is singing about sex and saying dirty words and stuff and it was a novelty almost now even the most
popular you're Sabrina Carpenter Shappell Rowne you're Olivia Rodrigo there's this love of saying
fuck and when you're saying it in every song it loses its power like I loved when Green Day would say
fuck when I was 13 years old I'd wait for it I'd get excited I'd shout fuck along with them um
that's a big part of growing up but I think these newcomers are missing the point if you say fuck
every time it loses its power I'm not trying to be approved I'm just giving you a tip like Shappell
Rowne this song casual is one of the most beautiful songs ever about somebody like not valuing you
or respecting your time and treating you like shit but then there's like four lyrics in it where she
talks like the choruses need deep in the passenger seat and you're eating me out is it casual now
she's a great line but then by the time the song ends she's fucking this girl in the bathroom while
her parents are sitting at dinner and you're like no no no now you've lost me now we can't relate
to what you're talking about we've all had someone go down on us in the passenger seat and then pretend
they didn't know who we are but we're not all fucking our romantic partner in the bathroom while
their parents sit at the dinner table now you've lost me in the same way I've lost you the listener
if they will see you in health podcast Olivia Rodrigo a fun show something to have on in the
background some catchy tunes I like the hits show all right the second movie I watched at Halloween
been my haul excuse me from screen factory was the Halloween 3 4k another carpenter
um man season of the which season of which is a hell of a lot of fun it's a batshit movie it's great
though you know we don't need to go down the road of if you watch it and don't put it as a Michael
Myers isn't here movie that's great you you all know that but the 4k looks awesome at times it really
enhances the visual effects of the movie there are a couple moments where it sort of takes away
from them a little bit because of the clarity but overall I thought it looked great and the movies
just a hell of a lot of fun man it's just a hell of a lot of fun and I love the Tom Atkins plays
a divorced guy doing his best to still be a decent father he's a good doctor that cares but he's
also a drunk and they don't shy away from it it's it's just a really really fun movie to watch the guy
that plays the bad guy the old guy I forget his name you know he's one of these classic actors that's
in tons of stuff he's awesome he's sinister he's great I love that it gets into it's not just a movie
called Halloween 3 that sort of has stuff to do with Halloween it really gets into the mythology of
uh I always wanted to say Sam Hane but however that fuck you pronounce it's Sao and Hague and I don't
fucking know anyway I like that it gets into all that Sam Hane you know the name for Halloween it's
you don't pronounce it like that it's called like it's Gaelic or whatever so it's like Sao and Hane
I don't I can't remember how to say it okay Salma Hayek is I believe the pronunciation um it's uh
yeah it's it's just it's just a fun movie I mean it's just I it was it was one that I have the Halloween
blue race set and there were a couple movies in that set that I felt were worth getting additional
4k versions of the first Halloween was one of them Halloween 3 was the other I love Halloween H2O
I love Halloween 4 I don't need 4k's of them the blue rays would do me just fine uh
Halloween 2 I love again I'm fine with it with a with a blue ray but uh these two in particular I
thought would really enhance the experience in having the 4k uh and I wasn't wrong Halloween 3 is
worth checking out in 4k special features are a lot of fun and uh it's great it's just a great fun movie
and I mean a a perfect perfect Halloween movie not just in the series but to watch at Halloween time
it's it really gets you in that zone in the way that trick or treat does or I scary stories telling
the dark yada yada it's a great movie it's got the new 4k of trick or treat which has tons and tons
of features I'm excited to check it out I also got the new screen factory 4k of my next pick the
stepfather directed by Joseph Rubin I fucking love the stepfather I also briefly tried to watch
the remake which seemed to be as bad as people claimed with Dylan McDermott I didn't get far
um but the stepfather is great it's terio Quinn from lost and you know beloved character actor terio
Quinn he is the reason the movie works he is excellent in this it's kind of like a star making
character performance from this guy the movie is super low budget there's not much to it
but it just really works I remember for whatever reason the combination of me my mom and my sister
rarely watched a movie together but we all watched the 10 p .m. channel 11 edited screening of the stepfather
one night was one of my first horror movies I remember it well every time I put this on this is a great
autumn movie it opens with one of my favorite horror kickoff scenes which is him in a suit and a
briefcase coming downstairs from like showering and shaving and as he walks out the door to start his
workday he passes by his entire family who have been brutally butchered by him walks past his dead
little daughter dead little kids goes out takes the ferry and to work and the movies underway that's a
hell of a kickoff Joseph Rubin is great at this kind of stuff he did a lot of like almost really
good movies he's one of the one of one of our greatest almost great directors of movies he did sleeping
with the enemy stepfather the good son dream catcher which I still have not seen he did return to paradise
with fence spawn money train just a lot of good but not excellent movies of those stepfather's got to
be my favorite the good sons kind of like the stepfather with a little boy I like that movie a lot too
actually but um you know it's a guy who gets bored with the family that he's the stepfather of
so he kills them and moves on to the next one and he's been doing this serial killer style for a while now
he charms and infiltrates a family usually with a hot daughter and a hot mother and then before you
know it he's killing them and moving on to the next one as well when they start to figure him out when
the daughter starts to realize what he's doing is when the movie gets really kind of crazy the great
moment and they ruin it on the box is when he forgets his own name and his wife looks at him really
confused and he goes wait a minute who am I here classic horror line for some reason written right on
the cover of the box but the stepfather is a great thriller along the lines of him of a misery good
son sleeping with the enemy something like that it's not horror per se but it's really really fun stepfather
2 not so good and stepfather 3 really bad but I wish we had more movies like this hand that rocks the
cradle style the blank from hell was a shot like the temp the temp from hell we had so many of these
and now we have none and I want more Joe I've never seen it I got to check it out it's really confused
it with the dentist for some reason uh yeah stepfather's a little classier but yeah I could see that
I got to check it out um speaking of ordering things in the mail I go out on my porch
yesterday I have two chairs out there with cushions on them and the cushions are getting like you know
pollen on all over them because of the pollen and uh pick up the cushions to like beat the pollen
off of them whatever yeah do it on the first chair I go to the second chair I pick up the cushion
what do I find underneath a package from amazon that has been there since september
because the guy who delivered it thought let me put this someplace safe I'll put it under a cushion
yeah I'm like what the fuck is this I pick it up I open it it's my death wish 4k that I forgot that I
never received that that can happen if you don't keep an eye on it it's an insane place to put a package
it's insane I agree um agreed Joe anyway we got that downstairs did you watch it it happened yesterday
so no I haven't watched it yet but I I will I've seen one two three and then the Bruce Willis remake which
we did on the show but they're good I mean that the later sequels get more and more insane but in a fun
way you know like just it's just him blowing up city blocks by part three yeah three is supposed
to be the ultimate canon movie like yeah it's fun yeah like it's batshit whatever um all right let's
talk about heretic heretic heretic a movie about Mormons trying to recruit new Mormons
two Mormon girls around the age I don't know 16 their their missionaries they go door to door to try
to spread the word about Mormonism there has been a request from an older sort of creepy odd
gentlemen for these Mormons to come and sell him on Mormonism at his own they do so he locks the doors
and we're underway for a sort of much tamer or more cerebral take on the like the human centipede type
movie where somebody comes upon a creepy house at night and it holds untold horrors inside this
goes nowhere near that movie's uh extremities and depravities it's much more a thinking man's horror
movie and in that way uh it was boring to me it it was like it seemed like a play it seemed like
Hugh Grant was doing an extended monologue it seemed like they were trying to criticize man's
explaining but it was written by two men and they didn't really dig into that enough for it to have
any sort of impact but the movie was weirdly kind of religion heavy uh which I was definitely not
expecting and Joe maybe you can take it from here I don't know your opinion of this movie at all I
was really underwhelmed by it but what did you think um I thought it started great
um real yeah it's the first act it's the trailer you're like I'm in and they just miss it unfortunately
go ahead I thought uh one thing I was kind okay I missed the detail that he had requested though they
go there um so that actually solved my one logic issue where I was like wait a minute why is
why is he doing this like what is you know but but it didn't really matter ultimately I was just
curious um he clearly has brought them there to to prove a point and to test them um
the first I don't know 40 minutes of this thing I found to be riveting I thought
his luring them in was interesting once you realize they're sort of trapped it was interesting the way
it's written the way it's played by Hugh Grant where he's like being like you're not trapped here
you can go at any time you just have to go through one of these doors that's the only way to get out of here
it did make it a little more interesting and even more sinister somehow but he wasn't like
looming over them uh and being crazy um yeah I thought all the dialogue
were rather diatribe when he does the whole breakdown of religion and he's comparing it to
monopoly and the different iterations of monopoly and how monopoly was ripped off of this feminist in
the 1920s who had a game that was identical to it and she never got any credit and how that game is
basically Judaism which is the first organized religion and all these other religions just
ripped it off and never gave it credit and they're all derivatives yet somehow people believe the
are more popularly following the later versions the thing where he talks about why is the iteration of
the iteration the thing everybody knows he breaks down the thing about creep being a copy of a song
from the 60s and then radiohead getting sued for that but then radiohead in turn suing Lana Del Rey
for ripping off creep I thought all of that was really well written really interesting and funny
like some of it was really funny I laughed out loud a few times um it was it was well written it's
Hugh Grant performing really long well written monologues pretty well there's nothing
scarier suspenseful about these scenes but as a student of music a lover of music like I knew all
this I knew that radiohead had sued the hollys and Lana Del Rey was sued by radiohead and all three
songs sound alike there's a funny sort of in joke over the end credits they play a cover of Bob
Dylan's knocking on heaven's door that sounds exactly like fade into you by Mazzy star and I was like
this is kind of a fun little nugget I'm just not sure what what it was doing in this movie
um the you know religion is a rewrite and a copy and we we absorb some of this and make it into
something else okay I got it I just I'm I'm for me I'm like what is this lengthy Ted talk
that is detracting heavily to me from the horror elements and the suspense elements and then the
sort of pick a door element I'm like so this guy made his house into this like I don't know maybe
I was looking too much logically at it but I'm like who is this man why does he want to do this to
people like that was what I was saying like I was a little confused like so does he have this all set up
just for the finally to get the chance to do this to somebody right but then so anyway the the
the basic plot is as once he has in his head diffused any possibility of them believing in their own
faith he says you have to pick one of two doors belief or disbelief he's clearly hinting that
you can renounce your faith now and go through the door of disbelief and get out of here or you can
take belief if you want to stick to your your ethics and and you're gonna have a harder time they choose
belief you realize immediately that both doors lead to the same place so it doesn't matter um he then
does this whole thing about death and resurrection where this sort of zombieish woman comes into the room
um you think she might be a ghost of some kind you're not quite sure you realize she's not a ghost
she eats a poison pie she dies and then she is resurrected he then kills one of the girls
in order to resurrect her it is revealed that the resurrection thing is all a magic trick and bullshit
the woman did die and then her body was replaced by another woman that looked similar to her
this is where I here's where I step in Joe yeah I was following everything that was going on
on this movie I didn't feel lost at this point but I felt like it was getting really stupid
well it's yeah it was getting well it was getting clumsy in my opinion because when they explain how
the woman switched places with the dead woman it was like see the other woman came out of this massively
heavy trap door in the ground in a room that is not big enough to hold more than 10 people
and yeah you would and and somehow because they were distracted they didn't realize the door was
opening and it's like you would hear the door you would hear the table that the door is under move
you would it just starts to be like guys come on man like this is this is a little much anyway
once and then who was this woman does this woman not have free will what makes her come in and eat the pie
she starts that's the point of the movie is that when the when the remaining surviving
Mormon girl wants to go down into the into this trap door to see what's down there he says down
there you will find the one true religion she goes down into the other the sub -basement of the
basement and she finds a bunch of old women in cages so then the idea is I guess these are women
that were once like them that he has trapped there and he reveals to her that the one true religion this
is where I was logic aside and parts where I was like this is getting a little dumb this is where the
movie lost me when he then does the monologue on the only true religion is control and I was like
this is just right now like the concept of you know religion is mind control it's like guys
when when when George Carlin said that in the 80s it was an edgy ballsy cool opinion because
you're living in a time of more majority and all this stuff it's like guys we're 40 years past that
revelation at least and I don't even know that when Carlin said it was it was a new thing I'm just saying
like it's just not a very riveting new revelation and everything before that that he revealed about
religion and what religion is on was kind of interesting and some of it was kind of new or at least
lesser known and and for that to be the big reveal this the only true religion is control
and I have controlled you I forced you to make every decision you have made today
it's like sort of sort of you did you know I guess some of it was through whatever it doesn't matter
anyway at that moment in the movie she stabs Hugh Grant in the throat he is left severely wounded
she breaks out to make her escape and then in an inexplicable move that I'm still trying to figure
out why she does this she gets to the top of the stairs she has her way out and she instead
which here's what I would do I'd go find a god damn knife or something I could use as a weapon
and I would squat with my back against the wall in the corner of the furthest room
so I could know when he was coming at me if he makes it out of the basement and kill him
instead she goes back down the other doorway into the basement and you can see when they're in the
basement that there are two stairwells leading into it so the fact that unless I miss something
that she didn't grasp that the other door wasn't the way out that it just led to the same room or
didn't somehow figure that out when she figured out all this other inexplicable shit was such a weird
stretch she's not going back to save her friend because she knows her friend she thinks her friend is dead
so she goes back into the basement maybe I don't know maybe the the door in the room was locked
still wait there until you know the guy's dead and then figure out how to get out don't run back
towards the guy that might still be alive it just was such a dumb move I didn't understand it
she ends up in the basement Hugh Grant pops up he's still alive he stabs her in the gut they're gonna
dot they're about to die and then the friend that you think is dead pops up and kills Hugh Grant
because she's still alive or something I don't fucking know there's a lot of people you think
are dead who are still alive especially for a movie that has like four characters in it there's also
though here's where I was just fully baffled for about 10 minutes Hugh Grant kills one of the girls
are you think she's dead this is about the mid midpoint right he comes in she's bleeding out
he cuts her arm open and removes this metal object from her arm saying it's a microchip that proves
she was not real the world is a simulation the other girl goes no it's a contraceptive implant
I had no idea what was going on in this moment this is a Mormon missionary who's got a birth
control implant in her arm yes is that correct yes what's going on there they don't have sex
uh a Mormon missionary is not fucking she's not gonna have a I think it was supposed to be a
birth control implant I think it was I think it was supposed to be before she converted to the church
she had that put in or I or I took it at they did kind of explain that the girl does explain it
I forget what she said but I just took it as either a she did that before she converted or be
she she did it because because when she gets married she doesn't want to worry about kids I don't
know that that that didn't bother me terribly well it's also like what he didn't know that in cutting
open her arm he was going to find that chip right so what was he looking for no no that's what he was
looking for and he was claiming he was like that's a microchip she's a robot or whatever and the girl
was like no that's a birth control but he believed that I don't know no I think he was fusion I think
no I don't think he believed that I think he was I think everything he said he believed was all the
ruse to psych this girl out and control her and then she figures out you're full of shit and I'm
going to call you out on everything you said that you know as a lie and then he's kind of like oh
you got me all right oh you're a smart one you know whatever and you know how does he know
there's going to be something in her arm I don't know just like I don't know why a man just reads
like a coincidence yeah I don't know how he knew that and I also don't know why a man said his
house up as a mouse trap exactly it's like if you want to teach people a lesson about religion this
just seems like the most insane what are you going about it to me but this is where
or why excuse me this is why I had such praise for the substance if you want to make a
batshit movie where you can go in any direction you want to make the commentary you want
it make it a satire make it crazy so I will go with you on these things and this is not a satire
this is a very grounded film where nothing supernatural is happening where these are real people in a
dire situation and it's it's it's a lot of big asks it's a lot of you want me to just go with this go
with this and I'm like I guess so yeah but Christ almighty there you could have replaced that
birth control thing with a million other little plot details that where he could have done something
to fuck with her head she could have just said you didn't just take that out of your arm her arm
you you hummed it by the way the whole crux of the movie is magic she accuses him early on of doing
a magic trick and he's offended because he's like how dare you I'm showing you true yeah
spirituality and god and all that stuff and then it turns out it is a magic trick and he's like
you got me it was a magic trick when he pulls the thing out of her arm she could just later say
you didn't pull that out of her arm you bombed it it's another cheap trick instead they show him
literally dig it out of her arm and the truth is he dug it out of her arm it's just stupid yeah stupid
it is I don't know they did it that way to add a little gore to a movie that was kind of violent
lists or what but it was one of four five little scenes in a row that had me going what
and I felt like I was following the movie and I was interested and I just was let down again and again
by these leaps they were asking me to take in TV rooms we have this thing called the house of buys
I don't remember who came up with it but it's like do you buy that these two people would be at the same
barbecue at the same time and this guy used to work with would call the house of buys he'd go they buy
it they buy it we can use it but you can't have people try to buy buy crazy things in an episode you
get one and in a horror movie I'll buy one crazy thing I'll buy your weird premise whatever the
substance is a great example Joe it has an insane premise it goes to crazy places there's all sorts
of gore and explosive you know explosive bodies and heads and stuff however we fully believe it we
understand the rules we understand the world we're in and we're off to the races we buy everything
because we buy the whole world this movie starts with a very believable small world and then just
keeps pushing us pushing me anyway into areas where I was like I can't go with you on this this is
getting too weird and you're right it never goes supernatural which is always a cop out and I hate
it when a movie is not supernatural to the last five minutes and that's the explanation but there's
too much in this that just doesn't work I don't buy it I don't believe that this is how any normal
person would react in said situation and when you're dealing with a small character study that can't
be the case you got to be in your character's heads so I didn't like this movie at all really
despite liking certain things about it like the the discussion of the songs and all that but at the
same time I was kind of like this is just kind of show offy dialogue it's not really
well it's not helping the story forward you know yeah and also too and you know this is just
marketing I can't blame the movie for not being constructed in the way I thought it would be in my
head but yes the marketing of this thing and and also the fact that he's got this model of his house
with all these passages and everything you see I thought it was going to be the setup that we saw
and then they then descend into like a labyrinth where it's going to be almost like
saw or something except instead of these death traps where they have to cut off their arm or
die or cut off their arm to live or whatever I thought it was going to be like
all of these rooms where their faith is tested in a way you know kind of almost like the end of last
crusade where it's like the you know three obstacles of such lethal cunning like I thought
they were going to go through like rooms like that and each one would be a test of their faith
which I thought would have been really cool and it wasn't like when they get into that basement I
immediately was like oh they're just going to be in this room the whole time aren't they and I
that immediately deflated me yeah and and that was kind of that man and then also too the idea that
he's got this gaggle of women and cages in his basement and he's saying like they choose to be there
yeah I mean I guess they didn't and that was the point like no he's just a psycho and he thinks
they choose to be there but I was also like wait do they choose to be there I don't fucking know
I don't know it was fine too much too much unknown but like when they opened that final room and you
see that there's 30 women and cages it didn't have any sort of impact it's like I don't know how
they missed all these like these reveals are just not hitting like there's a post to you're not
really scared you're not really disturbed I was just like is he fucking these women is he like what is
his endgame what are his goals and for somebody who spends the entire movie pontificating on what he
is doing and what his goals are and what he's trying to prove his methods never make sense at all
to me and that makes for a movie that's very unsatisfying that said great performances by the three
cast members absolutely sure and then a pointless absolutely pointless
force character of the guy that runs the mission or whatever it's called call excuse me did you
know that was Toe for Grace what no it wasn't my my the different day but she turns man she goes that's
Toe for Grace and I said no it isn't she goes yes it is I said no it isn't credits roll Toe for Grace
as the guy that like gray bull cut and a mustache yeah it was him
Jesus then when I realized it was him I was like oh is he gonna like whip his wig and mustache
off and be a undercover cop or something no they just cast him as a weird Mormon missionary
well very strange an absolute waste of a character and an absolutely pointless character
because this guy realizes these women have not returned and he goes looking much like in misery
when the sheriff goes to the to the Kathy Bates homestead and as you might have if I take a look
around and then she kills him and it's tragic because he almost saves James Conn and in this
no the guy just comes and believes him that they're not there and then just leaves that's the end
of it there's no point any of it so it doesn't doesn't sort of increases tension for like four minutes
nothing comes out of it anyway my hog has lost faith in heretic it is down a plus performances but not
a good movie yeah I was really I guess I wasn't surprised because quiet place you know obviously
was heavily rewritten and I didn't like haunt but I was just kind of like this looks good and
for all the horror movies made about exorcisms and with religious themes there are very few horror
movies that actually look at religion and what's fucked up about religion and explore religion so
I was excited and intrigued that this was going to do that but it just let me down at every turn
it feels like the first draft of a much more interesting movie that just needed more time
in the incubator my hog is down as well yeah I think these guys have a major logic blind spot
with their movies yeah I said it extensively about quiet place there were major logic blind spots
that just ruined the experience for me did I was so delighted that I'll never watch it again
got what's that sorry me neither I was delighted by quiet place on a first viewing and then when I watched
it after talking to you about it I was like oh wow I missed a lot of red flags in this movie but quiet
place whether it was the the mastery of Krasinski or whatever it was I was still riveted by it like you
can make a movie with a lot of mistakes that's still really suspenseful and holds your interest
this just to me didn't work on any level we don't quite have picks yet for next month but there will
probably at least one Christmas horror as we usually do we are on see you in hell pod on Instagram
I am on the Patrick Wall should Instagram Josephus folks as I said last episode please come on out for
the December 7th show and summer villain it's going to be a lot of fun and also the new tour the
joystick tour in January kicks off 2025 new material new cities some some familiar cities come on out
joderosa .com for all tickets if you're in New York come by Joey roses the new sandwich day viewing
well once once you hear this it'll be out well it comes out November 20th which is Wednesday
the stuff yeah the stuff or Thanksgiving sandwich it is one of our home baked
rolls with stuffed with homemade stuffing turkey spicy cranberry cherry glaze fried turkey skin
Brussels sprouts and sweet potato mayo it is a banger come on out and get that through Thanksgiving
all right we'll see you next time folks we'll see you in hell