Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and the Wizard of Oz, only available
at Bed MDM Casino.
Spin on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp, Raken
Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM in Game Sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as an almost durable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
The football season is full of guarantees, and here's another.
No other sportsbook has an offer this good.
With the fanatics game day guarantee, every single game day from now until October, if
your football bet loses, go earn up to $100 back in fan cash.
If you bet on football with fanatics, you're either winning or winning money back in fan
cash.
Guaranteed.
Switch to fanatic sportsbook.
Winning hits different here.
Must be 21 -plus, gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberer, offer not available in all states
terms apply, see Fanatic Sportsbook app.
Welcome to we'll see you in hell, everybody. Hey, Pat Walsh and one of your
Joe DeRos and the other, how is everybody? How you doing? They can't answer us.
It's not a call -in podcast. I suggested that it could be. Not yet. It is a
podcast, however, brought to you by the Fangoria podcast network. For more
information about the network including other programs and how to follow this show those shows any
shows find past episodes of we'll see you in hell or any of the other pods please visit vangoria .com
and now here we are just see we'll see I worked that announcement in that bumper I thought we were
just talking like old friends yeah no I didn't realize you were reading something that was all
business how are you doing Pat I'm good we're about a week out from Thanksgiving I think this will
probably drop a couple days prior. And we're doing a reverse theme episode because we're
going to watch Stephen King's thinner. And Thanksgiving is all about getting a fatter.
We're switching it up. We are switching it up. Now's the time to go to your Netflix box, your
Roku, your Apple TV, your PS4, your Xbox One, whatever it is. If you want to watch the movie along
with us find a thinner on your Netflix queue it up as soon as that first frame
comes on hit pause and we'll count off the play in a few minutes here in the
meantime speaking of Thanksgiving this is not our Thanksgiving episode I think
we will probably drop a special Thanksgiving episode I'm hoping I guess we have
to now that I said that but I am hosting Thanksgiving and Pat is you're
coming I'll be there I'm making my traditional sweet potatoes
It's worth the so delicious last year, but you don't eat them you don't like
I don't like them kind of a slap in the face to me because everybody raved. I like sweet potatoes
I don't like the way you did them. Oh, that's more personally that that style of sweet potatoes are
cared for I mean candy d 'amps. Yeah, I don't like it. It's too sweet. No, everybody loved it. Well, you know, everybody loves that
You know that new fucking
Bieber record. Oh, yeah
That was but the best thing I could reference. I couldn't think of it. No, you're right though. That's I mean
I haven't heard a song on it, but everybody's like do we have to really start taking Bieber seriously. This is really fucking good
You know what it isn't
I haven't heard it and I know it isn't that's a piece of shit and you keep
You keep playing his game. He's an animal. He's a fucking monster. Why is he a monster if you heard of nothing?
He's done in the past several years. I've heard of he gets hookers here and there
I'm not talking about hookers. He's egging homes. But then again, he's 18 years old. 18 years old. He's been
fucked in his head since he's 14. I mean, it's what you know, if I was 18, I got that much money.
I'd be a fucking asshole too. But we're all just like, oh, what's what's Bieber up to? What's Bieber up to?
We shouldn't care. You shouldn't care what your 18 -year -old nephew was up to. Yeah, or your own son for
that man. And these people don't, by the way, they care more about what Bieber's up. And look,
Maybe I'll go home and put this album on and I'll be like do I gotta start caring about Justin Bieber this is like, you know, this is like when
That fucking Taylor Swift album came out and I actually love that
Okay, you'll probably like this album you fucking douche. Yeah, maybe I will but like Swift seems like a class act
Does she like a pilot dog show does she kind of tired of her fucking aw shucks stammering, you know
I'm just a girl from next door that just stumbled in the fame. She lost me when she started trying to
Copyright phrases she used that she didn't invent like what I didn't have like whatever her catch phrases are a lot about
Says all the time she tried to like patent them
And it was like you didn't make up the words like what word
One of them was literally like it's all good or so squad squad goals or whatever
I think it was like it was like shit that like some of them was like I guess you could have that one
But there were like ones where I was like that's like a phrase that exists. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I don't know
Did you like when Tegan and Sarah went all pop? I didn't care for that either. No, I didn't like that record. I love
Many of Tegan and Sarah's albums, but the last few have let me down a bit
Yeah, why they've released that like pop dance record
Because they want money, you know
And they're they're getting it ain't that the business we're in it is I
Speaking of great pop music I actually love the new grimes album. I don't know if you know grimes
I don't first album was fantastic second albums just as good
But in a popular direction in a great way, so I'm still very experimental. I'm not against pop music
No, well obviously don't betray me. Don't you don't put you don't you put that tag on me check out the new grimes
But I also think the new to us will tell him is great speaking of pop music. I just watch the movie Danny Collins
Yeah, it's a perfect movie to watch with the folks. Yeah, it's got a little edge to it. Still rated R plenty of fucks. Okay, uh, some drug business in it. Okay, let's put you to the joint. No, he carries a cross filled with cocaine around his neck. I'll roll with that.
So, but I love the movie, cried in the last scene on the airplane.
I really thought it was a wonderful film about family, about love, about a man finding
himself.
Let me give you my pick for a great airplane or HBO on demand when you're hungover movie
or family parent movie.
What movie called the intern, starring Bobby Denise?
How was that?
An An Half.
I liked it quite a bit.
It's too long. It's kind of rambling, but it's it falls in with it. It's complicated and all those movies where I just enjoy it
Yeah, I saw it's complicated in the theater. I did so I like male friend of mine. I find and we enjoyed it
It's there's a great line in the movie with Alec Baldwin where he he's talking about a stepson
If a kid's name is Rod Rigo
Great Wardo
I think it said Wardo
It's very important that you remember Lake Bell plays the like fiery Spanish girl friend or whatever. Yeah, and
Doesn't look Spanish, and she's but yeah, she's but then he says
It was a Glenn close
What's your name? Merrill Street street other Glenn close. Yeah, Merrill Street passed them about like food because she's like she cooks and bakes
Then he goes
unfortunately
Originally, Rodrigo picks most of our meals, and he has a very limited palate.
Yeah, that's reasonably funny.
It's a funny joke.
Let's get into thinner man.
What do you say?
food all right on you should see a couple paramount stars cut starting to swoop in yeah we'll count
one two three then say play on play you play it one two three play uh wait a second
posit we're not it didn't go why didn't it go is there still on the side up titles we're watching
it with subtitles so we can just like what you know hear what they're saying oh wait I know
one, two, three, play. Nope. Didn't go again. God. But what the hell is wrong with this?
All right. All right. Guys, ready? One, two, three, play. Okay. Still let's go. Hold on a second.
Wow. Just get back to that first. Go back to the beginning. You should be two seconds in at most.
You got it paused and now we're going to go one. Oh, wait a second. Give him a chance to rewind it back.
This is brutal. This is just brutal. This is the stuff people like. This is the real stuff. If this is the first one people are listening to, they're never coming back. Well, hey, we don't want you then. Yeah, that's true. Scram. Okay, ready? One, two, three, play.
Hey, there we go. Now we're rolling. I don't know if the subtitles are going to be on Pat. We the problem with the reason we were having problems is because Pat wants to have subtitles on
Because we talked through the movie and we wanted to be able to see what was being said pretty reasonable in case we weren't listening.
And I couldn't get it off of the subtitle thing.
I saw thinner for the first time, probably 15 friends and I always thought the preview is hilarious when the old gypsy goes
My friend Jim who we've mentioned quite a few times in the smoke. Yes, you used to always say that we're in high school. Yeah, I got to tell you
I would love somebody to curse me thinner now to do any work
And then you know, you cut it off at a reasonable time
Gypsies are usually pretty cool about cutting off a curse when you ask them nice
As we'll learn now right off the bat. I'm excited your boy Tom Holland made this movie. Why I see my boy
Tom Holland is a director. Can you not you know are you unfamiliar with anything Tom Holland has done?
I thought Tom Holland did like Larry Sanders show and stuff like that or am I crazy the Larry Sanders show
I thought he was a TV director, but maybe I'm on Malcolm in the middle
Are we talking about the same Tom Holland? I think you're thinking about Savage Steve Holland who directed better off dead
No, who is Savage Steve Holland? He boy, I just said he did better off dead. That's the guy's real name
Savage, yeah, Savage Steve Holland, Savage Steve home. Was he a wrestler before he directed? No, he did one crazy summer better off dead a few others
All like a very heightened comedy style and they would actually put the word savage look. Yes
like a macho man Randy
That's insane man
What's fucking insane? It was Tom Holland Tom Holland directed I believe fright date. Oh, yeah, that's true. That's correct
I like Friday night and I actually kind of like the remake of Friday. There's also an English actor named Tom Holland
Is that the kid that's playing Spider -Man? Yeah, it is. Now the actor name so glad that rebooting that again. Are you?
Fuck no, you and I saw that second Spider -Man just train wrecked terrible. I sat next to the original the OG Spider -Man
Toby McGuire at a Mexican restaurant the other night. How did you talk to him about Spider -Man? No, I didn't
It was him and his wife
Who I got to say I guess this is pretty commented on not a traditional hollywood type lady
Like I think she's like his high school sweetheart like he fucked everyone in the world
He was in the de Caprio pussy posse where they fucked everything that moved and I guess he just called his high school sweetheart
I'm like, yeah, I got out of my system. You want to come back? Well, that's what I was sad to hear these
Matt Damon divorce room were swirling because he's married really because high school sweetheart
Are they swirling?
Joe, you're right out of the pages of an us weekly.
You go to the grocery store or something?
That's all right.
I saw it in the grocery store.
It was in the cover or something.
But I mean, I find it.
Joe just said, Matt Damon divorce rumors are swirling.
I find that the gossip rags are often true.
It often comes true.
Look at Sheen.
Charlie Sheen.
They were saying that.
Did it sad?
But he can a thinner.
Oh, come on.
All right.
I didn't feel great about it.
but it's right there.
They were saying that for years.
Is this his wife?
Yeah, that's his wife.
Well, this guy is a handsome chap
when he's not in the fat suit.
Robert John Burke.
You know what?
I gotta say, in the fat suit, I find him a handsome chap.
You're kind of feeling it.
I'd like to lay next to this guy.
That shake that his wife just made him,
now it starts with a fat man.
That's the whole premise of this movie, obviously.
But shake looks like it has about 1200 calories.
For some reason, the daughter looks to be half black to what completely white bread parents can pretty much guarantee she's a good looking gal these days.
Uh mildly creepy, but I I know what you think she's 15 16 here when I would have been 15 16 so I'm still going back to the age when I saw it.
Looks nothing like either parent.
No, not at all or even in their races as you said.
What I always wonder is like you see thinner or you see like nutty professor like a movie where the whole thing is this guy's a huge fat guy and everybody's laughing at him or you know that's the plot hinges on him being fat and you go see this movie what if you're fatter than him wouldn't it make you feel really uncomfortable or wouldn't well they they go to the you know I mean they they try to go to a certain extreme he's 300 plus pounds in this well he's 300 we just saw
which he lied to his wife said he was 297.
He's a big guy.
I mean, I don't think the average heavy -set person is under an illusion.
Six, three, three of those boys, they wouldn't have any illusions.
Pope fiction, yeah.
Now, what's this guy's name?
You knew his name.
Robert John Burke, I believe this is not.
Robert John Burke.
This is Joe Montana, of course, fat Tony.
What is Robert John Burke also in?
This is the only thing I've ever seen him in.
He's in kind of a lot of shit. It's mostly like TV kind of stuff, you know, I think he's in like, you know, Chicago
Hope hope fire dentist one of the one of those I
Think he's a Chicago mercy
I like this grease ball. That's a slur. I believe oh shit, is it I think it's a slur. I didn't even mean I tell you
I mean it looks greasy
uh well it is a trial for mobsters. Oh is it? Well look you just saw Joe
Montana. What else is going on? I thought he was an attorney. No he plays a mob
boss in this. Okay so clearly I don't know. What is Joe Montana ever not played?
Yeah. A mob guy of some kind. I don't think I've ever seen him play anything else.
It's a good point. How's it cards? Great Joe Montana film. I love house cards.
Day of now. Yeah. Joe Montana was the original Ricky Roma on Broadway. He's
the actors the actors curse or whatever it's called forgot all his lines on
stage opening. No Jesus went blank. It's a lot of lines too. I mean I think he
recalled them but he had a moment of going severely blank. Now Joe do you think
the same Gypsy who made this guy thinner put the actress curse on him. Hold on
let me finish Mike. Oh damn Joe. I got the joke but we're gonna miss this. Pat just
in the last thing goes, I didn't even know they were Italian. It cuts now to a scene
of that about a speedboat with a gray -haired woman serving them food. Not just food, it's
like a giant spaghetti meat -a -boos. Linking red wine glasses, stokies. Yeah, toasting wine
on a speedboat. All right, now I understand. I think I have both red thinner and scene thinner
and I did not remember any Mafia element at all.
I never read the book.
I always wondered if this was in the book.
Then it follows the book pretty carefully.
But I remember the book just being a much better version.
Written by McDowell who also wrote Beeljuice
or Koro Beeljuice.
The screenplay, not the book.
Oh, yeah, the book is written by Stevie King.
Yeah, Steve King.
Steve King.
I watched a pretty entertaining horror movie this week
on the Indy side called we are still here and it was a horror movie that came out I believe this
year 2015 and if you're a horror fan I urge you to check it out it's short it's fun scary
and it's like you know like a creepy like main haunted house kind of movie okay but like
it goes insanely gory which those movies never are I love it and it wound up being a good mix it was
really fun. Where'd you see it? I rented it Netflix. I still get the red envelopes.
I'd love to. I'd love to. You're still doing hard disk. I do one at a time. Hard
mail Netflix. God bless you. Sometimes something comes out and I just want to see it or like
if something's not on streaming, I get it. God bless you. Going for a nice bleeding.
Yeah. I like a blue ray. Watch a hard copy Netflix. Plus, you know, even if you return it four times,
which would be low. You're getting these movie for about two bucks. You can handle two bucks.
I just I have so many DVDs of my own that I've never watched. Yeah. The streaming they're certainly
not sponsoring us. I think we can all agree. Netflix streaming. Yeah. Doesn't have the greatest
selection a lot. I guess they won't ever be sponsoring us. Yeah. I mean, or they could actually up
their thing and listen to their customers, but like we tried to watch a Friday the 13th. We're going
to a special Friday the 13th podcast. We're like, yeah, we'll watch one of the numerous Friday the
13th movies that have to be on Netflix streaming and there were zero. I couldn't believe there wasn't one. How hot is this gypsy, by the way?
I actually just stopped talking because I fell in love with her.
Much like a gypsy curse. Is that carry -war?
I don't know. Let me look it up. That's why the iPad in here. I saw her in the credits. I think it's gotta be her. Who's carry -war?
She's just a hotbed.
they announced today that they're well they've been remaking Baywatch for about a
decade but they're doing the movie Baywatch and the star will be D 'Dario. I mean
maybe that's looking woman a lot. She's my favorite Alexander D 'Dario from
True Detective. Yeah greatest nudity in TV history and perhaps film history. She
might be my favorite woman that's ever existed. I actually when I saw that
today in the in the old movie trades yeah I Google your reading your variety out
on the brand. Yeah. I Googled her name plus boyfriend and was legitimately sad to find
out that she did have a boyfriend. Who's she dating? You thought you had a chance?
Uh, I don't know if I thought I had a chance. I just, I just, I don't know who she dating
is. One of those Christina Hendrix things where it's like kind of a nerdy dude. No, she's
dating Percy Jackson. Oh, the lightning thief? Yeah, the kid that plays Percy Jackson.
the poor man's Harry Potter. Yeah, I said it. By the way, this is Carrie were her. And look
what she's doing in. Oh, she's where her right here, I would ask her to be my life mate.
We got her in these pictures. These red carpet pictures and she's doing the whole gypsy thing
in those. It looks like they got her wet on the red carpet like through a bucket on her.
What is she from Baywatch? I know her from a great movie. I've mentioned on this podcast
before called King of the Ants that no one in America has seen, but it's kind of a horror movie.
Isn't it a Shatner film? Is she?
No. You asked me that last time too where I have the exact same conversation.
We are. It's not. It's a Lovecraft adaptation from Stuart Gordon director of Reanimator.
Oh my God, what's happening?
And it's not the, it's not a remake of the Shatner film, but I ask you that too.
It's definitely not. It's a really disturbing, unsettling, like realistic horror,
kind of like a thriller type to. She was also in Sharknado 2, Anaconda, the original Anaconda.
Yeah, eight -legged freaks. That's a powerhouse cast, the original Anaconda. Sliders.
The show with Jericho. Yeah, eight -legged freaks with David Arquette, who she only does big
spider -ship. A lot of big spider stuff. Yeah. David Arquette is the star of eight -legged freaks,
and he is also, as you pointed out to me, I just saw the billboard the other day.
We have to go. I wish we could do a live podcast from the balcony of Sherlock Holmes. It's supposedly a comedy. Yeah, I'm sure it's hilarious.
I'm still confused by it though.
Not Joe, I don't know. It's like some sort of interactive theater experience where David or Kepler Sherlock Holmes.
I've been sent a lot of material about the Sherlock Holmes. I am on some mailing list that gets me Sherlock Holmes mailers.
really yeah that's why I brought it up I got it like 12 emails about it it's
one of those things where living socials like you want a 50 % off ticket how
about a 60 % off ticket two weeks later how do you feel about a 75 % off ticket why
haven't we gone we should go we should go I'm 100 % in I think we'd be like this
will be hilarious and then two minutes in we're like all right let's go I'm just so
curious of what it could be. It's just such an odd thing. Yeah, this is a
hand job seen in the movie. His wife, his wife is going to give a moral
sex in the car here, which I found strikingly out of character for the wife
character. There's Steve King. There's Stephen King, which means he approves of this
adaptation. Yeah. But not the shining. No, not the shining. He prefers to
Steven Weber, we've talked about this, I mean, it's terrible. This guy is one of the
most disgusting characters I've ever seen in a movie. This old gypsy man with a big sore
on his nose. Since I have to mention the movie Parenthood and every one of these, there's
also a blowjob seen in while driving in parenthood, Stinberg and Martin. I remember asking my
mother, I watched it with my parents, what's going on? And I was, this is how good my family
was with handling sex questions. No one answered me. They just didn't answer. No one had made up an
answer. They just kept staring blankly at the screen. That movie has a blow job seen in it. Yeah,
steam Bergen's sister says whenever, whenever Moranis gets tense, I blow him while he's driving.
And later on, Steve Martin's super tense and steam Bergen leans over and then the next shot is a car
are crashed into a telephone pole.
Isn't that a PG movie?
It's PG 13.
I mean, you don't see mouth penetration or anything like that.
Oh, really?
You don't see full penetration?
No, you don't see.
You're just like slurping and sucking.
You handle this pretty gruesomely, realistically.
I like it.
Yeah, me too.
So for those of you not watching, his wife giving him
the blowjob led to them hitting this old gypsy woman
in the street and killing her.
Yep, and
This big guy this fat guy is a big -time lawyer and now he's got to go on trial and you can guess what's gonna happen pet?
I can guess maybe he's gonna pull a few strings
Maybe he's not gonna be honest about what happened in that car
And maybe he's gonna beat the rap and maybe just maybe
That's gonna lead to a curse. Yeah
What kind of curse chips the curse thinner curse?
that's right ever gotten a blow job in a car? No. Really? Well I have in a park car I have
I never heard not where we were driving. I have. It's actually very difficult to focus
small on on either thing. Like you're not giving either 100%. I once got a blow job in an elevator
at a kinkos at a kinkos. Yeah. Why do they even have an elevator? There was an all night kinkos
in Manhattan and a girl and I that I was girl I was dating went went in with me to this elevator
that was stationary didn't move probably because it was three o 'clock in the morning and they didn't
need the elevator and she blew me in it to completion you guys really put the kink and kink us hey
can't believe I never thought of that shows you what kind of a comedy writer I am sure it wasn't
a FedExXX. Oh, God. These are off the cup. Get a little UPS. There you go. Jesus. I'm glad.
I just didn't you're elevated. So he got off. Yeah. His judge his big -time
greased -up judge friend, right? Who was the guy sucking you off in the
elevator? It was a it was a very nice girl. She got married I believe. Let's
leave her name out then. I'm not going to say her name, but she got married
years ago and she was a lovely girl. It's a crazy thing to
to sit there, you know, you look at your lovely wife of 30 years and, you know, at some
point, she probably blew somebody and a kinko's elevated. This is just the life in which we live.
This is just, this is the hard -called truth of the world we live in. The old days you marry at 18,
no one ever touched her. Everyone's terrible at sex, you never learn, you divorce 40 years later.
Now our main man's been cursed thinner at this point.
Oh, yeah, he's down to 280 he probably thinks it's all the stress
He's well he thinks so this is just great. I'm just losing weight
You think we got enough potato chips there to put across the thing that he's fat. Look at this
He well, I like when he we came out of the I liked earlier when he came out of the trial of the mob boss eating Doritos
Yeah, I think I was my lawyer I'd be like you think you can hold off on the Doritos. Yeah, so you get home
Hey, Tubby, that's my mob guy getting mad at his fat lawyer this guy does exactly what I do
Hey, I'm down 20 pounds think I'll eat yeah, I do that stupid it's stupid every time then you get back up
And you're like what the fuck was I thinking? I have a I have a light day and I go and eat you know
I go get fried chicken as a celebration of a little war and then you never get that chiseled lean body that you and I deserve
You know, people expect really from a Pat Walsh and a Joderos.
I'm just never gonna have a hard body. I have accepted it.
And I'm fine with that. I'm fine with this.
We have a lot of sex with each other and others.
You don't have to have a chiseled bunny.
I'm plenty happy with having a gently soft body.
Sure.
You ever see the movie Hard Bodies on USA Up on Night or otherwise?
No, what's it about?
It's your standard T &A movie, but it's a really good one because it was Italian.
It was, you know, funded by Italians, but made in America, it's just your standard spring
break movie, but it had a real, even for like an 80s tit flick, real liberal nudity.
It's called hard bodies.
They made a hard bodies too, cool.
Anybody have no tenet?
I don't think so.
now 80s movie they just they just remade zapped really we're sorry who a
girl and she's like looking at dogs what's the point of doing a female zapped no
offense but here's what kills me about that it's somebody saying like oh let's
do like the feminist thing and remake it now with a girl and it's like a girl if
if you found the male one despicable the girl version isn't any better it's still the same person
doing despicable shit yeah right well all i remember that they did in zapp was look under girls
towels and dresses did they do what they do what else do they do they probably shouldn't have been
doing that yeah it was Scott bale's their powers for so is this girl gonna be looking at dogs as my
question i don't know i didn't see if pat i didn't research it i didn't even bother to read about
it. It stars Scott Bale and Willie Ames who later went on or maybe before
went on to star in Charlton Church. I wonder if they make cameos in the remake
of Zapped. Oh god can only help. Bale, I was so happy when I saw him in arrested
development. He had great timing. He was funny. It's a recurring theme on this
podcast. I love a comeback. Who does he play? He was Bob Loblaw. Bale? Yeah. You know
I never saw a lot of the arrests and developments hold on I'm looking
up zapped on my iPad here I want to see more about this remake it's uh here
we go here we go uh 1982 oh god it's a Disney Channel original movie what
is does after remake oh well then what if the kids seek out the original and see
that it's softcore porn. It's based on a book called Boys or Dogs. Let's see here.
Is this a remake? Is there an exclamation point at the end of Zapped? If so, then it's a remake.
No. But it's called Zapped and the Z is like a lightning thing. Okay. It could be
something different. Well hold on. I'll look it up. Only one of us can look up at a
time, Pat. I'm not looking it up. You can't look up on your, every time I look over to you on your
iPad, I'm trying to just be here with you, be present. I'm just trying to get us some, you know,
some info. You need the, okay, it's, I guess it's not a remake. Okay. And then I got to take back
everything I just said. Okay. But there's the original poster with them pulling up a girl's
dress with static electricity, right? Yeah. I bet it was pitched. I think it came out in like 81. I bet
it was pitched like as carry but a combo they use it yeah to look up grill skirt it's
pockies meets carry here's your check no I got a whole story I don't need to hear it here's
your check says telekinetic powers yeah that's what he used him for let me take this opportunity
to recommend a great little pop punk band in the vein of weezer called telekinesis they're really good
It's all what they have a fantastic almost perfect album called I think 12
desperate lines that would be the place to start okay it's the one guy he plays
all the instruments writes all the songs insanely catchy like two -minute pop
punk songs he does them all in his own they're very like early weasers check him
out telekinesis that's amazing all right I mean the he's a very good job in this
film of showing the gradual weight loss, they do. I buy it. And I don't think it was nominated
for the makeup Oscar. Of course not. Because the matter of what horror and comedy don't
get taken seriously. It's back up to really bothers me. He's looking good. Yes. Have you
seen the specter yet? No. Is that guy inspector? No, it's just not good. Oh, Inspector, that
was weird. Spector has an amazing opening and a couple decent scenes throughout
otherwise it's pretty shitting. You don't see the villain till like two hours
into a two and a half hour movie. Christopher Walsh. Yeah at some point you're
like what am I following here? There's not even a and then he shows up at the
very end. I just don't have a big James Bond interest. I never have. Same here
Joe and I always try to convince myself I do, but I don't. I mean you went to see the
peanuts movie the other day. So a peanuts movie alone. That's where I'm at. But I always
love peanuts. Oh my god. It was really not a good movie. Of course it wasn't. It was a CGI
peanuts movie. Yeah. The hell did you think was gonna happen? But then they also like will
superimpose the black and white comic strips next to the CGI action. Like somebody thought
That was a cool idea or else Charles Schultz be on the grave was like you have to do this
Well, I think that is kind of a cool idea that was the only part that sounded kind of neat
They did when they do it once you're like, oh, that's cool and then by the end you're like stop taking me out of the story by
imposing drawings on
Not that I was into the story because there wasn't really a story
This was a misstep by the way of the prop department's part
He had a corn on his plate already and he points for another piece of corn
Why would you do that can he two things a corn?
But why wouldn't you just eat the first one and then ask for another one?
You know what I mean? I guess you know he's gluttonous, but it's
He's I was like that party pulls a piece of meat off his lap
Did you see that done it?
But it was like a nice long piece it really worked look at this here's just dessert
All right, not that you and I have a great deal of self control. What do you eat if you have a week where you know you can just do whatever you want?
Um, I don't know what I mean, I kind of eat whatever I want all the time. Yeah, I don't probably shouldn't be doing it.
It doesn't show, but I really do try to regiment myself. I have a salad every fucking day for lunch. I have a juice every fucking day for breakfast.
but I slip up what do you have for dinner I tend to not eat dinner but you know
on the week when the weekend comes around you know people are like let's go
do this let's go do that you go eat some drinks you do this you do that what
is your terrible genes I do my best what is your what is your you know biggest
guilt meal. I don't know that I have one thing. I think if I could eat anything it would
be like a sheet cake from Ralph's. But I don't do that. But you're big on like let's
go over to the grocery store and get a piece of cake.
Wait a second. Slow down this conversation. Let's back it up just a bit. I've never purchased
just a sheet cake and eating it.
I'm saying that's what I would eat
if I had the thinner curse.
You're saying, you need a whole sheet cake.
If I had the thinner curse and could eat whatever I want,
my first move would probably be something
in the sheet cake family.
Look.
And definitely not like this stupid cool whip frosting,
but the good like, although
like a red velvet with it,
like a cheese.
Definitely not red velvet either.
Yeah.
I'm talking about like a child's birthday party
She can which you get like in an office when somebody has a birthday. That's gross
I can't believe that's the kid. I love a cake
But I can't believe that's the cake you go for I go for like a double chocolate. No, I have no interest in that
But now if somebody brings in one of those like the icing flowers or like we had in my house for my birthday party
I
Get one spoon of that icing and I want to just go into a coma and die
I I think it's disgusting. It just tastes like sugar. It is but like you know
Certainly when I was a kid I was like how do I get my hands on somebody to me
nothing beats a Dunkin Hines chocolate cake yeah or a Betty Crocker chocolate
cake and with the pancake and then you put the chocolate frosting on it just
sounds very boring to me oh so good man so good no I'm my biggest Achilles heel is
the old you know like fried chicken sure ribs which actually I gotta be
honest I think has helped me in some way weight wise over the years because it's
it's it's not good for you obviously food but it's not sugar heavy yeah that's
true so even if you're eating fried chicken as your shit meal you're still at
least getting the protein of the chicken and stuff there is some value to it I
at some point I used to have a pretty extreme sweet tooth and at some point I
kind of lost it which is great because you just start to feel gross about any
sugar at all as you get older. Mine's grown over the years but I still don't have an amazing one
which is why I won't eat those damn yams thanksgiving sure I love I love the am I would
got like restaurant wise I think I could shithouse like some some pizza maybe would be good
you know just I I'd love to have this curse it's what I'm saying I don't I don't think you would
pet he gets frighteningly thin I don't remember how it ends I don't want you to tell me and it's my
hats off to the actor because he he really does get kind of skinny in this. Yeah, you know, now he
isn't getting the con he's skinny, but he gets skinny. Now, do you think they did castaway style
where he went away and lost the weight? Or do you think he played the whole movie rail thin
and just pick up to adding makeup to him throughout? It's probably smarter like take six weeks off
production. Wait, that's hard on the crew. Like is he this entire time? Is he rail thin? And they
just keep taking makeup away, right? Or is he normal? And then once
in him to lose weight, he went away for four weeks and lost
a ton of weight. I don't know. That's a good question. I
was wonder how they do that. I was there's that one episode of
it's always sunny where called how Mac got fat. Right. And it
starts with him fat. The wrap around is him fat in confession.
Yeah. And then the story is when he's in shape. And I was
always like, how did they do that? They just thought of that
ahead of time basically and shot the scenes ahead of time.
Yeah, but I was like, what if he never got, what if he failed in getting fat?
Yeah, well, that time and energy. I think he knew that's what I want to do for
this entire season. But what if he was unable to do it?
Everybody's able to get fat. I don't think it's as easy for some people.
Yeah. You know, and he's a pretty in shape, fella.
You know, he is super genetic. That's really, it's really shitty.
this part scary where the he now he's at the judge's house here and he's
talking to the wife but he's saying I haven't seen the judge where is he and
she you this is where you find out that the judge was cursed lizard they cursed
him lizard yeah and he became a lizard he's growing she's she's talking about
memory the judge had that like scaly thing on his chest yes there's that's she's
Telling them like that turned into like scales
What did the old gyp say to you?
Is that what he just said what she said?
That's a slur, isn't it? I didn't know anyone ever said chip in that context like it's short for gypsy
Yeah, that's why somebody goes you jipped me. I know that you're not supposed to say that anymore
No, I know that I'm saying that's what that is
But how can it be a slur if like you've never encountered a gypsy in your entire life?
Well, who's it offending? Gypsies are real people. It's a Greek origin, isn't that? I
Guess, but it's not like Greek slur. It's a slur against gypsies. What's that? It's not a slur against Greeks. It's against gypsies
Well, I'm just saying like if I if somebody was like, hey, that's a slur against leprechauns. I'd be like
Yeah, I never got a leprechaun. So who cares? I think it's more like
How Sicily is part of Italy okay, and you're Sicilian if you've been sold in the Sicilian
You can sell the Sicilian you're selling selling Italians
Maybe something like that does that make sense? Yeah, I guess I didn't realize you worked for the gypsy coalition job
I'm just asking
I'm just asking I let me cause the mob boss and goes do you believe gypsies can curse people?
this, this sort of shit in movies like two gorgeous girls staring
loggingly at Joe Montana. We just believe this shit. He's a mob boss. And
the girls want to be with a mob. Well, I guess I want to be with Tony
Sprout. I mean, yeah, it's, it's, it's, it's the green that gets
some wet pet. You know what they say? Where there's fresh green, there's dew on the flowers.
I've heard grass in the field play ball. I've never heard the other one.
That's something. My Nana told me when I was very young. She told you the green dew?
Oh, okay. Jesus Christ pet. I don't know your Nana. She could be a freak.
guys losing weight at rapid speeds and his wife is still not concerned there's still no
part of her that's like I think he might be sick. Why don't they do the same where he's like
let's bone down I'm all thin now. Look at it out in the clumps. It was like I can see my dick.
I think he's freaked out at this point. Man at this point has lost about 150 pounds and he thinks
that he's got and he thinks he's got like cancer or something. Yeah. I wonder if not that
Robert John, he's a good actor, but I wonder if they tried to go after like thousands of big actors in Hollywood and they wouldn't do the weight
law. They had to go after bigger actors than Robert John Burke for the lead in this movie.
I don't know. I mean, this is the actual release. This type of movie didn't pull in a major star in the 80s.
All right. You don't look at the other king adaptations, uh, night, uh, pet cemetery.
Yeah, true needful things. I had side out and ad Harris
Side of the main guy in needful things the old guy is the old guy. Oh, I didn't know that ad Harris Bonnie Badelea
Ed Harris and Bonnie Badelea both in
Believe in Creepshow
Is that Harris?
Ed Harris is in the first story of Creepshow a young ad Harris. I believe it's his first film. Okay. What is this guy's name?
Who the doctor? No, the actor. I want to look at Robert John Burke. Robert,
12 ,000 calories a day. John Burke. And none of them are freaked out.
Number, the doctors are going, you eat over 12 ,000 calories a day and you're
still losing weight. It's incredible. It's like, we thought I was a doctor. Wouldn't,
wouldn't you be like, clearly you've got a disease that we don't have on the books
yet yeah well plus losing weight that fast it's terrible for your hurt oh he
looks good these days man yeah he kept it together he's got like a rugged like
older what like big show is he in now because I think he's in a well he was on
rescue me there it is yeah he was the priest in rescue me he was in limitless
didn't say it he was in true story the
John Hill James Franco vehicle maybe the worst movie of 2015 he was in Robocop 3
yep he played Robocop he took over for Wellen he did I think what's
I'm mistaken let me see here
Jesus Christ Frank Miller wrote the Robocop was one of the letters of the Robocop 3
true story there is a scene where Jonah Hill and Robert John Burke are walking
down the worst location in film history like this like a band and riverbed and
they're walking down it and the camera is like going out of focus the one point
you can't see either of their faces and it looks like if it was in a student film
you'd be like guys you can't release this this is a major motion picture it was a
terrible film. What is the what is the plot? Well, it's a true story. And actually at the end,
when they cut to the real guy that Jonah Hill played, it's the first time in movie history where
the actor was worse looking than the person he was playing. I was like, wow, so I wonder how this
pretty normal looking guy felt about having Jonah Hill play. Oh, that's right. Now this is where he
he goes and visits the deputy that was also part of the lie, the trial, the deceitful
trial. This guy's been cursed with like acne or something. Oh, this is, he doesn't look
good. He doesn't look good. That's a Kruger from Seinfeld. Yes. It's got a lot of shit
on his face here. And this guy's going to say, you know, the guy touched, I think what
He says he doesn't say acne. That's not that's not a good curse. She cursed me. Zits.
Yeah, I forget. I think maybe it's boils or something. Okay. But wait a second. Back to true
story. What is the true story is a true story. The Joan Hill character is our actual author.
He decided to go in and interview the James Franco character who's basically like a sociopath who kind of like plays
Jonah Hill from inside jail. He's like convicted of murder or something
It's really really bad and just like badly shot. You could tell they both thought it was gonna be their big Oscar shot
It's not good. What's the what are the performances like?
like Jonah Hill is like really earnest, like at every scene he's trying not to be funny
instead of acting.
Uh, is he good at it?
No.
And uh, Franco isn't great at it either.
I, it's, I have a hard time taking Franco seriously outside of anything where he's not.
Oh, there you go.
There's a good look at the guy's face.
Let's see what his curse is.
Where he's not a stoner.
Yeah, I can't.
I gotta tell you, I'm not a huge, serious Franco fan by any means, but one of the few movies that has made me cry 127 hours, I loved it a lot.
I'm a big Franco fan. I just like him as a goofy guy.
Yeah, I agree.
I had a hard time with him in Oz, the great and powerful. I just didn't believe that he was in Kahneman.
No, the movie was terrible.
Yeah, it was not Sam Raimi's best.
No.
love in that new Evil Dead show.
As far as I'm dying to see it, it's hilarious, the action's great, I love it.
I don't have fucking stars, so I can't watch it.
Yeah, the pilot is really, really good and it's not on a, it's not on a, what's it called?
Netflix.
You got, I know you can watch the pilot free online, but not the other ones.
Where do you watch it on?
Oh my, I just Google watch it for free and I'll pop up.
I did he say it what he was cursed with?
No.
It's not good looking. It's pretty bad.
It's pretty bad, right? Yeah.
So everybody involved with this hidden run gets cursed?
It's the three of them. Yeah. That's different in the...
it's different in the book. Hold on, I'm going to, oh, I've got that zip guide just
killed himself, or he popped a zip one of the items. I'm going to go back here because
even with the subtitles on, we missed what his goddamn curse was. Hey guys, I'm also going
to tell you because I only mentioned it at the very end of one podcast that are opening
theme written and performed by Jody Russell. It's a very catchy song. Thank you, Pat.
That's very nice. Sure. And as always, thanks to the fans who reach out. We love your comments.
I'm going to single out someone who goes by SLO Jen, who's always like almost does a commentary on
the podcast through Twitter. And it makes us feel like we're being heard. It makes us feel special and
happy. It is very nice, isn't it? Thank you, SLO Jen. It is very nice. Boyles. So his was
Duncan becomes mutated with large boils okay now here's what I want to find
differences from the book because in the book I think it's three different it's
two different curses I don't think it's boils I think it's I think it's
something else Pat and I can't remember this is the hard part about doing research
and being a co -host you know it's well enough you've done research you know all
us prior to the podcast. That's what research is. Why can't you do? What is he eating now?
He's eating the car. He's just picking up a turkey carcass. Yeah. And just eating meat off of it.
You ever get to like a, that's something I always find healthy. Maybe it's not as healthy as I
think, but like getting a rotisserie chicken at the grocery store. I do it all the time. I do it all
the time too. But what makes me so sick is obviously not eating the whole thing at once.
the next day when the the chicken has like that disgusting thick glaze on it
that's so gross to me what is it it's the fat congeals it's the grease congeal so
you gotta peel it off I do but if you heat it up it'll go away I mean it just
will yeah but that's so sick it is gross it's really gross alright plot here I'm
the book here okay. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Uh -huh. Old man gets the scales and
then Billy is cursed with horrifyingly extreme case of acne. Yeah. Both of them eventually
commit suicide. All right, I guess you look at all like I can. Uh, they made it a little
more like tumourous in this movie. Yeah. Which is pretty gross. It's not, look up real quick.
Well, I'm going to look it up. It's my turn. I want to know what was nominated for best
make up this year I bet it's gonna be like Elizabeth or something stupid like
that they never get they never give these movies they're due yeah now this
movie should this movie should have been nominated now what do you think it is
wife number do I find her attractive yeah absolutely I think I've seen her in
something also I don't know what it is what is this 96 I think it was 96 yeah I
I just was in a diner in New York who walks by Chris Nooth
For starters sure and then they get all of them once in New York the guy that played the bad guy in dirty work
Chris from McDonald. Yes, most people would have gone shoot him a Gavin happy Gilmore shoot him a Gavin as well. Yes
This movie is a 16 % on run to man. That's bullshit. This is a good movie. I
I like this movie. I'm just just angry. Well, I'm just saying I like it. I'm just saying that for myself. Yeah.
All right, 1996 thinner. The nominees were deservedly nutty professor, which won.
Ghost of Mississippi, which I remember having particularly bad makeup.
What the hell was the makeup in that there's a Rob Reiner shitheele movie what was the makeup in it though just like I think James Woods played like an old racist everybody aged with the makeup was bad as
person yeah where he's an actual old risk and Star Trek first contact with us had okay makeup. What the hell is going on with James Woods man. Yeah, I don't know. I'm reading the stuff on Twitter. It's
I mean, I don't care that the guys are Republican, but I mean, my God almighty's calling people pigs, and yeah, it's going nuts. You see a Trump supporter?
I'm sure he is. I mean, I bet money. I wouldn't be surprised if he was a Ben Carson supporter. Yeah, I mean, he is fucking way out, man. Yeah, tweeted to Obama to put down the crack pipe.
I didn't see that yeah now he's suing some guy because some guy called him a co -cat or something I did know that and you're gonna tell me James Woods hasn't done more coke and you were I could ever hope to see in our life I mean that is actually I take it back I don't want to get sued try this again for 10 million dollars yeah you can't do that look you played lester diamond people are gonna assume you've done coke once or twice I can't believe that's the guy that played lester diamond yeah
That's amazing to me.
Kibbley, that's the guy from John Carpenter's vampires.
Oh, I hate them.
Terrible movie.
The running joke on that is that he asks like, oh, what do you,
what do you got a little wood?
Get a little teak, a little mahogany to a priest.
He lists different kinds of wood.
Yeah, it's to a priest too.
Hey, father, when I wrestled you to the ground there, did you,
did I feel that you had a little mahogany?
A little, a little redwood, a little oak.
I love that this is movie is.
I didn't realize it's possible to read us clearly, but I didn't realize it up until the late mid to late 90s Doritos
We're still in the old school bag with the clear front cool ranch. When did they change it?
When I am done with this Hollywood life
Maybe a year and a half from now
My goal is to purchase a
Ranch that I will call the cool ranch
You didn't answer my question. I
Would it was your question? When did they switch the Doritos bag? I've never been a Doritos guy. I don't know
I miss that clear bag man. That was so much cooler than the one I hate the one they have now
They're it's like a kind of an extreme bag now and it's been like that forever and it makes it so much less fun
And I miss the old logo
At a class at a time, you know now it's it's cheesy looks like snowboarders eat it
We mentioned rob Reiner last week I came over to do the Friday the 13th and we didn't wind up doing it
But I was telling Joe last week
a night, wasn't it? It really was. I was always nice to see you there.
That was nice to see you, too, but we sat down had a drink and then just didn't do it.
Yeah. I went to a writer's guild event. They picked the 101 funniest screenplays of all time.
Number one was Annie Hall, which is not the funniest movie of all time.
But I don't I don't argue that it could be the that ranked the best comedy of all time.
Yeah, I think I should have just said comedy screenplays. Funniest I kind of threw me
Yeah, but it was really cool and they interviewed Zucker Abraham Zucker the interview the fairly brothers
They had all these right right or mid -night run anywhere on the list. No one said kingpin
It was not on the list dumb and dumb or was give me a break someone on Mary was give me a break
Well, give me a fucking break. I love both movies kingpin is a funny look. They're both funny movies
There's no way they they go both on without kingpin. I agree
But kingpin is the funniest movie ever made America doesn't that I agree with as well. I think
But what I was going to say, Rob Reiner, who directed Ghost Mississippi, people forget the man had such a streak he did. This is spinal tap.
Misery, stand by me. Princess bride, when Harry met Sally.
A few good men, like just off the charts, like every movie he made was great.
Yeah. Now not so much. Putty of mine is working with him. He said he's great.
and Rob Reiner hosted this event. He must be 70 years old. This guy was so fucking funny.
Yeah, well, he's Rob Reiner. He did not, he didn't read anything off the paper he was supposed
to read. He made fun of how shitty the event was. Like, he's like, what are we doing? A powerpoint
presentation? Then they list the movies. Like, the list goes up 100 down to one and they keep putting
him up and he goes, we're in one of the nicest movie theaters in America. Nobody thought
to put a clip up. We're looking at yellow text on a blue screen. He just was breaking
everybody's balls. And the funniest part of the night was John Favreau goes up because
they were honoring swingers, which was like the number 100 movie, which is way too late
in the list.
Yeah. There's no way swingers is below something about Mary and dumb and dumb or I'm sorry.
the hangover was number 30 folks the hangover line so he good I'm saying hangover
should be not on the list I'm not saying I agree okay so and I like the hangover fine fine
but it doesn't come on top one hundred let me break Riner is standing up there and he looks
pretty good and he goes ladies and gentlemen John Favreau and Favreau comes up and he's huge and
we just watched this clip where John Favreau is in a wife feeder looking really cut with like
muscles. And as he walks up, Rob Reiner goes, look at you. Jesus Christ, you got fat. Holy cow.
And then to have to walk up here right after we see that clip where you look so beautiful and
such good shape, you got to do what I do. I've always been a little chubby. Then when you're chubby,
when you're 70, everybody's like, yeah, he was always chubby. You, your 40 years old, you come up here
looking like you three hundred pounds it's crazy my god you put on a lot of
weight he goes on and on and on favor I did not laugh not at all I wouldn't have
laughed either but the audience was roaring it was really really funny
favor didn't laugh at all well he went up and he was like oh I'm so glad I came
thank you for that wonderful but you know he didn't laugh now do you think he didn't
laugh because he was offended do you think he was just playing like the
straight man. No, I think he was probably a little both. They had Peter
Bogdanovich there. Right. Who directed the last picture show on my
favorite movies? And Rob Ryan goes, first question I got to ask right out of
the bag. Why do you think you can wear the ass cut? Why do you think you can pull
that off? Like every line he had was great. And he's killing with the audience
The audience was roaring. That's great. Buck Donovan's goes, well actually it's a it's a bandana, not an ass cut. And then Rob Riner goes, oh yeah, that's much less pretentious.
What's happening now that this became an action movie? No, he's having a nightmare. Oh Joe, good call. I mean Pat, come on. I am very frequently fooled by the nightmare.
So you're you're you're you fall for that every time not every time start going
Hey why are you go this movie just went off the rails you don't stop first to
go maybe this is a dream sequel if it's too ridiculous I do but if they're
doing it with as they should be doing it then you can't tell I mean that was a
scene of a lizard man driving into a tractor trailer people watching a
horror movie being driven by a gypsy is the world where curses exist yeah I'm
just saying all right I'm just saying uh now he's been kind of the same size for too long I feel
yeah has he I mean he went from 300 to 150 in 20 minutes and now he's been 150 for
an hour now he's getting a little gone and that's the word right yeah gone works terrible vocabulary
Pad have ever told you that get a word of the day calendar. I died. I got no
I can't remember the goddamn words anymore. You don't need it. I mean when
somebody drops like some giant word talking to me I'm like get over your
fucking self. I don't think all this person's really cool because I got this
huge book. I know a lot of words you know I was always really into language and
shit. I'm not going to use them in conversation and when they put them in
movies I'm never like oh good writing. I'm like bad writing because that's not how
people talk. My writing job, I work with an author and he dropped some words
sometimes and not pretentiously. It's the way he talks. And I literally, I'm
like, so I'm like, what do you talk? You need to dump it down a little bit. Yeah.
He had to use the context clues. And he's always nice. He will explain the word
and then apologize almost like, sorry. Yeah. But sorry, you're so dumb. Yeah,
I'll say that, then I'll get him against the wall.
Call him a nerd.
Give him a handsome.
Our man here, our main character,
is in pursuit of the gypsies.
He's going to try to get the curse lifted.
Is that what you would do?
Try to get the curse lifted?
If you had the curse, would you try to find the gypsies
to get it lifted or would you just be like, yeah, fuck it.
This is where we're at.
If I thought I was going to die, yeah, I'd try to reason with the damn gypsy, sure, I don't think there are people to be reasoned with as the problem. I mean
Anyone can be reasoned with. She's a gypsy. I assume I don't remember. I assume the gypsy asks them to do something for her
To get the curse reverse probably. Well, where do you see? All right, where do you see if they can be reasoned with?
because he's gonna have it in counter with him believe it or not as you could
imagine I'm surprised it didn't go the route of him going I wish I was thinner you
know like was the plot of all these movies back in the back and it you mean
like it big yeah so you wanted this to just be big yeah no phone booth that
dates up. Let's look up the other cast members see what they're up to in this. Is this podcast
too low energy people? Again, another can't answer us. The'll answer us on Twitter. Okay. What's
going on in your life? Mine? Yeah. I'm just working on this writing job right now for the
I'm working on a writing jump.
I'm very, that's holy cow.
What's up?
That's the daughter now.
She's now 34.
So she's already, she's my age.
Well, I'm a little older.
She probably wants somebody close to her age.
See, exactly, like when I said she was hot, it was OK.
Oh, wow.
Bethany, Joy, Lens.
You look fantastic.
She's a member of the band Everly.
I think I know that band she's married. Oh, but divorced. What's Everly? I think go like a pop band
Is that what she does now?
I believe so. Let me look up acting she was on soap opera
thinner one tree hill. I never saw one tree hill. I always thought it was a great
horror title, but it's not a horror show. No, it's about casting the news shonda rhymes drama
Don't know what one tree hill was about. I believe it started Chad Michael Murray
I never watch it. I watched Dawson's Creek and that's about as far as I went is that part of the same family
Yeah, along with Seventh Heaven
starring
convicted child molester
Again, you got a slip in a reference to molestation
Who that was some really weird shit like he's just showing his dick to children. Hey, it was upsetting
Well, man, it was very upsetting because I really like that guy. Yeah, he was always sunny. Yeah, he's great on it
He and he never leave it. You're like he's the greatest guy that's ever lived and you fought you're those stories. Yeah, I'm like oh boy. Oh
boy
Yeah, one tree hill
Who who did you say was in one tree hill?
She had Michael Murray
What the fuck is that some pretty boy? Yeah
some little bitch. He's like a big comedy reference guy a lot of times because he has three names.
I have no idea who he is. I've never heard of him.
He's got a lot of white men from town like it's dances with wolves or something.
It's how the gypsies talk.
All right.
What do you want? You know?
That's how the gypsies talk.
I told you they can't be reasoned with. He's trying to reason with the gypsies here and they're not they're not having it.
See, what is this accent? He's a gypsy.
I don't think they did a lot of research in the gypsy community.
He's it's a Greek thing. I'm really looking at over there. Huh? Is that the daughter still?
Yeah, I'm looking up like a beautiful woman actual pictures of her, like, you know, more
candid shots of her these days, 34 divorced. I love that she's divorced.
This is what happens. I got to say you're talking about the authenticity of gypsies,
just looking at duty picks. It's not newty picks. She just looks like a nice lady. And I'm not
afraid to say it. She was on Mary and Rhoda, which was the Mary Tyler more Rhoda reboot.
I worked with Rhoda, lovely lady. She's still alive, right?
She's hanging in there. Yeah, she had brain cancer, she's hanging in.
She's doing okay now. Yeah, you know, she had a ton of lines on her show, she got them,
she got them down. Valerie Harper. Yeah. Charlie Day was on that show.
Really? Oh yeah, the Mary Tom. The Mary and Rhoda. Right. He was the mail room kid.
I never knew they rebooted it. I think it was like a maid for TV movie, I thought.
Oh, I thought it was a sitcom. All right. I'm obsessed with this daughter right now. Yeah, I know.
She's with a man named Wes Ramsey, who of course is gorgeous.
and he's my age damn you damn you Ramsey look at this guy that's your chance again Joe look
at this guy come on probably cheats on it oh god look at this hair on that hat this one he's
got a strong his mouth what is he an actor too you know who the hell knows yeah American actor
star of the douche award. He played in Charmed. Oh God. Guess is where they met the Charmed
One Tree Hill. Although she was married for about ten years. So she must have remembered
him from their Charmed One Tree Hill days. Is Charmed is not part of the One Tree Hill
universe is it? It was like on the same night on the WB. But Dawson's Creek One Tree Hill
and seventh have entered the same universe?
No, no, but they were all part of the WB deal.
Oh, I thought you were saying it was like the, like,
there was a crossover.
No, they made a lot of shows with the same kind of aesthetic.
She, uh, the gypsy just shot something through his hand
with a slingshot.
How mad would you be if somebody shot through my hand
with a slingshot?
If a girl jumped out like she just did
and yelled ho or whatever she yelled and shot a hole through your hand with a
slingshot I mean I would be it's a great question Joe I would actually be very
angry I'd be furious yeah because my hand would have a big hole in it yeah well
it would hurt too yeah the the pain part I didn't even think about
so now he's cursing them back
can he do that? Well, you know what his curse is, don't you? No. His curse is
Joe Montanian. He's gonna go to the, he goes to the mob guy now who, who doesn't
dabble in supernatural forces. Uh -huh. He dabbles in maximum forces. Oh, he hasn't
go rough him up. Yeah, he's gonna go now in the way the way the white man from
town retaliates. How long into this movie are we? Pat, I'm gonna be honest with
you. I like the movie quite a bit. Not long enough. I was tired of
hell right now. And I lose my voice when this thing started. Now it's barely hanging
in. I'm tired of hell right now. Well, we get we got a rally. We got to give
these people what they want. We are. I just took my pants off. I got two more days of work
this week and then I'm off for the week for Thanksgiving. I can't wait. I can't wait. I can't
wait to cook a bird for you and my closest friends. Well, what are we going to watch for Thanksgiving?
Because Eli Roth's Thanksgiving is not a real movie. Well, if Thanksgiving is on here, we could watch
that. Is that a real movie? Yeah, it's the one with like a killer turkey. Oh God, it's not on here,
Pro it used to be I don't know if it still is
Thanks killing um
But I almost think we could watch like a
Like like you know, there are so many great ones for Christmas. Yeah, I just feel like we could watch a Christmas one for Thanksgiving
And they you're right like maybe we watch black Christmas for Thanksgiving and then we watch gremlins or something for Christmas
All right, everything's giving eye watch plans transomobiles. My favorite movies of all time
My friend once said if you don't cry in the last scene, you're not a human being. I don't anymore because I've seen it 80 times
But I did when I saw first. It still gets me. Yeah, it depends on if I've had a frosty cocktail or two certain movies still get me every time at the end
Malcolm X sure at the end always gets me
We'll play his friends and Uncle Buck. Give me if I allow my brain to think about John candy the actual man
What part of Uncle Buck makes you cry? There's no sad part. It's that final freeze frame. I miss John candy
What's the final freeze frame in Uncle Buck? He waves. He puts the whole family together. It's got kind of the same ending as home alone really
You know, he's washing them the mom comes home. They're all hugging he waves
they're gonna be okay he's gonna be okay he taught them something they taught him
something but it ends on a sort of like a freeze frame on his face just I I I
I'm sad that he's dead is all Joe is that all right he was not cursed
thinner unfortunately too much oh John candy I thought you've been Joe
Montaigne? No, John Candy. Yeah, it's a bummer. Joe Montaigne is his
Simpson's character. That's Tony. I mean, it's, he's the only person on
Simpson, it was side from Phil Hartman, where it's like it looks like him. It is
him. Who is your favorite outside of the main family? Which shouldn't be your
choice anyway, but who would be your favorite Simpson's character? Uh,
Moe. Moe. Interesting. Yeah. I mean, come on. He's the best.
Would make my top 20. I love Moe. Moe wouldn't make your top 20. You might make my, you
might make my top 20. Come on. Who's your favorite? I think I got to go Lionel Huts.
All right. And Troy McClure is on that list as well. Yeah. That show, I mean,
Brandon, they've had good episodes through the years since, since this, but when Phil
Bartman died. That's kind of the beginning of the end of the show.
I would put side show Bob.
I love, actually.
Fairly high on the list.
I love side show.
I'm just a sucker for Kelsey Grammer anytime he talks in that Frazier voice.
That's the only way he talks.
In interviews, he kind of doesn't talk like that and it upsets me because I just
want him to be Frazier all the time.
Yeah.
You know what I mean?
that's uh I use a uh Sacha Bob line all the time at work
well I think it's the I think it's a Cape Fear episode when he's in in the uh court
room and he's talking about killing Bard or whatever and then he goes at
cheerfully withdrawn when they object to it he goes cheerfully withdraw like he's
taking back his, thanks so at work whenever I'm like pitching something, people don't like
it or whatever, I throw him a cheerfully with the straw mail, I always enjoy that.
Oh, it's nice.
I don't think I know where it even came from.
I just kind of use it as my own.
Well, that's theft.
Yeah.
I learned it from the fat Jew.
He's talking about the Twitter person, not the main character.
Oh, yeah.
Film.
I also love Nelson. No, not Nelson.
Milhouse. Ralph Wiggum. Yeah. Yeah.
Milhouse is hilarious. Milhouse is dad is hilarious.
I like the losers in the Simpsons world.
Where would you put flanders?
Flanders is funny. A little one note for me.
Mr. Burns is always hilarious. Smithers is worthless.
You know, I like how you said you like the losers in the Simpsons. There are no winners in the Simpsons. Yeah, that's true. That's true, you know
I haven't seen a new episode of the Simpsons in
But sometimes people will be like I watch the other night and it was really funny. I believe I'm never an avid watcher
But I watched a couple ones from this season on Hulu and they were fine. They were funny. Okay
Yeah, you know, they were, I mean, I was my whole life for 10 years comedically.
So I love them so much.
Which your favorite sitcom of all time?
Seinfeld for sure, but Simpson's if I'm just looking at like the 10 year block that I love would be very high up there.
Sure, sure.
It's been on 30 years at this point.
It's which is nuts.
Yeah, it's nuts. I remember when it came out of such a huge fucking scandal George Bush was like don't let your kids watch this
But my parents let me watch that but not in live in color, which falls a little racist. I thought racist when you just said it. Yeah
Now you see what Joe Montana just did he went and poisoned all the gypsies dogs
Right put signs up that says like the white man from town says hi. Yeah, you know whatever very Italian way to say it
But, you know, you think this is the only movie where the mob goes up against gypsies?
Yeah, you know, I don't produce Scorsese script. That was supposed to tackle the same thing but
I'm supposed to finally make that Pacino, Pesci, Danero, Nicholson, Scorsese, and Mob movie. They're saying they're making it.
We'll see. I better do it quick before they all die.
Uh, De Niro's looking good.
De Niro looks great.
De Niro looks fine.
Scorsese looks good, but he's 80 and he did Coke for 30 years.
Lots of Coke.
He's like 75.
Okay.
Right.
I feel like he was 40 and 76.
Oh, this is the beauty of the iPad.
He's about 80.
I just picked it up and saw the guy that's dating the daughter from this movie and I hate
him.
Maybe Coke keeps you alive. I work with Garrett Morris, who's 80. He looks 40. He did cocaine for 60 years.
Yes, Chris says he's only 73.
Okay. All right. That's good. And he's, you know, he's one of those guys that like, as long as he's directing a movie, he won't die.
Yeah. That's probably true. Do you know what I mean? But he's always directing. So he's got to die on the set of a movie at some point.
I think like he, I just think he's going to be like a lane stretch where he finally goes like all right folks, you know, I'm done. I'm going to retire and like the next day he dies. Yeah, he's going to be one of those guys.
She lived in New York at like a famous like showbiz hotel, so she was like in her fucking
like 80 or so that kind of manner and then she's like, I'm gonna move out my family in
Virginia, whatever it was, died like a week later or something like that, you can't live
New York that long and then go to Virginia, you're gonna die pretty quick. Yeah, it was kind of a
bummer, man. It's saddened people like her die. You know, it's very comforting to know they're out
there. Yeah, Rickles will be sad as hell. Apparently he was on Kimmel recently, still rapid fire. All right.
You know, I was supposed to see him, but you failed out. We made a mistake, Pat. But you've already seen
him. I'll never say. I saw him with Frank Sinatra. That's pretty awesome. I mean, if you think you're
going to dance into my life and top that experience. Would you rather see Don
Rickles and Frank Sinatra or Don Rickles and Pat Walsh? I'm gonna go with the
former. Sorry. However, Frank Sinatra and Pat Walsh you might have a deal.
There you go. That might be a deal. I would sing you a little Sinatra if I wasn't
clinging to the lash shreds in my voice right now. I mean folks we have to talk
look so long for these fucking plants.
Would you just have pity on us?
Oh, that kid's dead.
They shove it rooster in his mouth?
Yeah, they paid the kid to like go be a lookout or something and spy on the gypsies.
Something, I don't fucking know.
And the gypsies knew what was up and murdered and put a rooster in his mouth.
Because he's a cock sucker.
was that what he's a gay he's a gay he was a gay prostitute I didn't even put
that together talk sucker that's interesting thank you oh that that made it
like a lot cooler that scene yeah like it's way creepier this whole movie like you
know it's well -directed well -acted the makeup's great the effects are great I
don't know why it's got such a low rating this people just treat hard like porn man
it bothers me yeah it bothers me if it's not like a masterpiece they're like oh this is stupid yeah
and it's like and then everybody just decides to get behind certain things once in a while where you're
like but why did you all like this movie yeah and it's like you know much indie horse shit I've
seen yeah oh yeah completely half fast put together but because it's an indie movie and people think
It's supposed to like it. It's got like a 98 % rating a perfect example in a movie
I think actually has a 98 % rating as I just watched the Academy Awards
screener of grandmaw starring Lily Tomlin which I would give an F.
It wasn't great. I despised it. She was she was really great in it. I thought
she was kind of cartoony and not right. I thought she was funny. I enjoyed her
quite a bit in it. But first half of that movie is so poorly done. When she's
beating up the boyfriend, I was just like, what are we doing here? I didn't buy
any of it. I didn't buy one that little girl punched her in the face. She got a
black eye, a five -year -old girl punched her in the face. My take on the movie was
free. My take on the movie was it was only good because she was good in it. Like it
was anybody else playing that part it would have been a bad movie. I thought she was
Hamming and has been better in 800 other things. I enjoyed her. What could I tell you?
You're in love with Elitom. I like Elitom quite a bit. The only scene I liked and I liked
her and him was the Sam Elliott scene. I thought he was great. Well some corn. Yeah. I'll
just made some corn, that's some corn. I'd like to be around that guy. Good energy I bet.
Yeah. Yeah. You want a beer? Right? I feel like going to Dill Taco tonight.
I would just feel safe around that guy. I'll take a lot of the mild, so please, mild. You got
near them there, French fries. Well, now you're not a sling -blood tart. To put those on my taco.
you a tater taco. Give me three of the tater tacos. Sir, this is the bank. He's crazy
in this first. Everywhere has tacos. Yeah. It's just Los Angeles, isn't it? Give me a
money taco if it's the goddamn bank. Put some money in a tortilla and slide it over. That's
So really it do see I pictured a money taco being a bunch of nickels inside a dollar bill
Like the the dollar is the I pictured it with shredded bills as the lettuce
Well, and it's called the call cash lettuce and cheddar so now you already got two key ingredients
So the shredded bills are the lettuce and then what's the what else is you got to make the whole thing out of money?
Yeah deposit slip is the tortilla
Yeah, all right, not technically money, but fine, and then you throw a couple pennies on top. Yeah, all right
That's fine. I love that my tini goes in posed as like a FBI agent
and
Yeah, oh this guy's a do -it -all mob using one -stop shop for a mob guy. Well, huh was it ether? Oh acid Jesus
That's a rough scene. He says acid, bitch, and then throws it in her face. We've all been there, but that's not the real acid. Now he puts the real.
That was fake acid, see, to warn her about future acid.
So he took the time to prepare a solution of fake acid, he did it to throw in her face, and then immediately tell her it was fake acid.
He's really rough in this chick up.
Why did he do that, though?
Because he puts real acid on her forehead in a second.
Okay, cool.
I find that effective.
You throw a fake thing on her to scare her and then you go, by the way, here's the real thing now.
All right, they didn't get a take of the spitting scene where it wasn't like a baby blowing a raspberry
The real deal
There's a point on our tits they put it on our coat
Thank you for explaining every second of this movie because apparently I'm not following anything
I mean with the subtitles on you can't follow it
I haven't even looked at the subtitles that I demanded you put on that was a waste
Yeah, we're wasting good subtitle money. No, they're helping a little because at least I I kind of know what's happened
This is a great scene. He puts the he puts a jar a mason jar of acid on top of the girl's forehead
Just to lie there still so she can't move. I got to tell you I would just stand up real fast whip up
And it would flip back behind you maybe getting your hair. No, it would not and it won't fall wrong
You know what, feel a glass with acid and we're gonna try this.
This is what you do.
You do what she's doing.
Or she whips her head to the right or left.
But I think you get out from under it.
Look, she did it right.
Her hands are free.
Yeah.
Well, of course, she's gonna get out.
He gave her a message.
He was just scaring her.
She wouldn't have died if the acid fell on her.
it just would have burned her. Yeah, but looks like the family opera for the rest of her life.
Well, he's got a pretty mean gash in her forehead. So he says he said to her there,
you tell the old man to meet us at the watch tower where everything to help was lighthouse
with the and lift the curse. So this is this is we're in the home stretch here.
He's going to go sit down on the on the bench near the lighthouse and wait for the old gypsy man and
And you know the solution's gonna come through
Or do you know what the solution is?
No, I do
Come on, do you want to
Let me just watch and enjoy we can't just watch it enjoy. No, I mean, let me watch and talk to the guy
Enjoy podcasts that we do we have to talk through in this fucking prism
This verbal prison
So thirsty. All I want is a drink, so I'll water it, uh, well, White House action.
Ever see the fog? Yes. I like the original. The remake was real bad. Remakes terrible.
Those remakes are never good, but I love the original. Here's the gypsy with the solution.
very interesting solution I hate this character he's gross yeah he's gross he's got
that thing on his nose how does a man with an open sore on his nose get a woman does he does
what? Does he have a wife? He had a daughter. Well, the daughter was the old lady he killed.
Yeah. That's the, that's one of the gags. He's, uh, split in some pie by a lighthouse as the horror climax
here. No, he's telling, he's telling him how he's got to fix everything with his pie.
you bleed into the pie see see you give the curse to the pie that's ridiculous
it's not ridiculous this is pretty why the pie this this part's pretty rough
I Joe just jumped ladies and gentlemen well because he shoved the knife through the
hole in his hand. And I mean, my God, how bad would that hurt rather than put a knife
through the hole in my hand than pure hand again. With that pie, taking that blood, pie
gyrene, bubbly bubbly gyrene. See? He puts the curse into the pie. Why the pie?
Because he's got to now give the curse to somebody else. Oh, Jesus. Give a
pie two now see because he thinks his friend is banging his wife I missed that
completely of course you did sit over there yapping I have to I know I'm kidding
come on I'm just giving you who's he thinks banging his one his doctor friend he
thinks his banging his wife okay but he's not banging his wife he's just like
telling his wife he's concerned about him right you know but this is the
problem now blood for blood he's got to go now give this somebody else which
that never works out when has that ever worked out now Joe if I show up to your
house with a blood pie is there anything I can say that makes you go yeah I'll take
a slice of that blood pie well he's not gonna tell him it's a blood pie it's
full of blood. But it's pulsating. He doesn't know. It's a cherry pie as far as this guy knows.
Did it reseal itself? Yeah, it's a magic putt. All right. For Christ sakes. It's a magical pie.
Here's a little Hollywood trivia. That pie is actually the same pie used in American pie.
Yeah. And that's how he gets rid of the thinner clip curse. It goes into Jason Biggs' dick.
Yeah, I just looked up that pie on IMDb and it was in American pie this movie and
Pie the Darren Aaronovsky's first movie. That's one of the movies I was talking about when I said just because it's an independent movie
He gets 98 percent. Oh, yeah pies an obnoxious movie. I saw it in the theater
I hated every second of it and I like Darren Aaronovsky. I do too. I fucking love black swan. I'll tell you that much
Yeah, I never saw it. It's so good and the wrestler is one of my favorite movies of all time. I love the wrestler. I
Think I've only seen the wrestler
Wasn't he supposed to do the Robocop remake? Yeah, yeah, you didn't see Reckon for a dream. Oh, yeah, that was great
You see the fountain
No, okay, how was the fountain?
And I found this visually amazing, it's kind of silly, but I liked it.
And I actually was one of the few people that like Noah with Russell Crowe, I thought
it was pretty cool.
That's air enough.
Yeah.
That's the air enough?
That one a lot of people said air enough, you know, but not me.
I said, air more.
And he said, it'll never be enough because I'm daring.
brain. We're really bringing out the
amateur. I'm so tired that I've
contemplated three times just falling
asleep on the podcast. Well, the
whiskey didn't help. I didn't need
that one whiskey. It was like it was
like a sedative. Doesn't have that
effect. I mean, whiskey in particular
or jolts me up.
Pat's been drinking oddly every week
when we do this, or every other week when we do this.
I have one drink just like you.
No, I know.
No, no, no, no, I'm not saying you,
let me finish the sentence.
All right.
I'm not saying you've been drinking every time.
I'm saying it's odd what you've been drinking every time.
I bring a diet soda from the burger,
and I mix it with a little vodka.
It's a delicious drink.
It seems disgusting to me.
That's like a you know cream sickle or something. It's really good a hate cream soda love cream
Some diet creams is much better. It doesn't have that. Oh, that's right. He gives the pie to his wife
He doesn't give it to the guy that he thinks is banging her
Oh geez, it's pretty rough because he thinks his wife because he blames her for everything
She because she had to suck my dick
Yeah, she blew him. He crashed the car
This is the first wife in history who got in trouble for doing a blowjob, okay?
Jesus
Well, then he really resented her that she didn't believe him and then he believed that she was having an affair
So, you know, look he's he's gonna die with a dirty soul as the gypsy warned him
Here's the next morning the assumption is the wife is eaten the pie
this part's pretty disturbing. I guess she just had to take like a slice right
shouldn't have to eat the whole pie. Yeah she just had to eat a piece. Okay. Does
this daughter eat a piece of the pie too? You want me to ruin it? Oh, sorry.
right? Yeah. So there you just got blood pie. This is the part I don't get is he's I mean
it's gross that he kisses his like rotted wife's face. Why would he do that? I don't
know because he's he's lost a shit. You remember the Clint Eastwood movie Blood work? Yes.
It's pretty bad at some point he just opens fire on a public intersection with a shotgun. I don't
even think he's a cop in it. Maybe he is. But, uh, one of my friends accidentally, he's gonna say,
let's go see that blood work movement. He accidentally said it's in high school. Let's go see that new
Clint Eastwood movie Bloodwipe. We all started laughing so hard thinking a movie that's just Clint Eastwood
wiping his ass and they're being blood on the paper. It's like the opening scene. Because that's
probably what Clint Eastwood faces every morning in his edge. And we just laughed and laughed
and laughed. Blood wipe. It's another blood wipe. How do you explain this to the cops? Your
wife has rotted in bed. Well, I assume you just said, shit, a bad piece of pie. And they go,
okay. Leave. You know, it's a funny story. I didn't kill my wife for say. I was cursed by a gypsy.
I had this cursed pie um funny story that and here's the part where the daughter's home
She's not supposed to be home. Yeah, that's a good little twist and there's a second plate of pie in the sink
Oh boy, which means the daughter is eating some of the pie and now he's upset because it the gypsies words have come to fruition
Oh, no, there she is
She's alive. She's alive. But she ate it for breakfast. She ate the pie for breakfast.
And that's it. What are you gonna do? It takes a little time to incubate. Huh? It takes
a little time to incubate. I think she ate it for breakfast whereas the wife ate it last
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
See, she just had the piece of the piper breakfast.
It was delicious.
She's being like extra cute and funny.
Yeah, I know.
This is the finishing move.
Put her finger into it.
Licks it off.
I gotta tell you, I wouldn't accept that kiss.
That was a...
That kiss always struck me as odd from daughter to father.
She licks pie off her finger a little seductible and then leans in like almost asked perked out and kisses him on the cheek
It was not at all a weird kiss
I'm just saying I wouldn't take the kiss from a daughter who had that pie in her lip. Oh, that's what you were saying
Yeah, I was saying it was an odd way to kiss. Oh, I didn't find it weird
If your mother kissed you like that you wouldn't think that was weird
Well, there's no affection in my family of any kind, but if my mom kissed me on the side of my mouth or something
And I'd be like, all right, I'm not talking about your mom kissing on the cheek all loved ones kisser saying if she sticks her ass way out
Licks pie off her finger
All right, and then perks her ass out and kisses your cheek. It's weird. You're right. That would be weird
Well, here's Mike his friend the doctor now Mike. Can I interest you in the piece of pay?
Blood pay I think he's gonna give a
Some strawberry pie to Mike now breakfast pie
Mike's like yeah, that makes sense
He said that for those of you not watching he said I'm gonna dig into a big slice of this breakfast pie
He's holding the whole pie in his hand by the way, I do love breakfast pie
So this is it he's gonna die now. Yeah
And he just called
Damn, but that's something I don't get is he laughs that he's gonna kill the doctor as he shuts the door, but
He's already over his daughter dying. I mean the man's clearly just becoming an animal
Well, what are you gonna do folks now? He's a single man free to do what he wants, you know, I think my theory is he kills himself there
He thought about it, but then I think he got turned on by the thought of killing Mike and now he's fine
I hope you're not getting thinner this week because it's Thanksgiving. Hope you have
a happy holiday. Hope you eat a lot of food.
say hi to a friend, kiss a loved one, say hi to a friend, keep the tweets
coming at us, we love it, we are taking your suggestions, we're going to start
doing them once we're out of these holiday theme episodes. We just appreciate
your feedback, give us five stars and iTunes if you can, a nice little review if
you're enjoying the show and keep your mouth shut if you're not.
Let us know your thoughts if about us going off Netflix because I got to tell you,
I was looking today for a movie to watch.
It's getting to be slim picking.
Yeah, I mean, we could always find something,
but we would kind of like to know if you guys are,
it seems like most of you are not watching the movie
along, you're more just kind of.
So then we could just start going to DVDs
and up the classic content.
Right, right, bit.
This has been, we'll see you in hell.
Presentation of the Fangoria podcast network produced
by Thomas DeFeo, executive produced by Ken Hanley.
love kangoria love Ken love Thomas never met ever met Thomas symbolized guy
It's not that I don't love you Todd's never mentioned for press opportunities advertising inquiries and information about we'll see you in hell
Contact Ken at fangoria dot com
Very nice and for those of you that live in New York City
I'll be headlining Gotham comedy club December 18th and
19th and
I believe I will be at the stand in Grammar C on New Year's Eve
So come on out. Yeah, and if you're fans of both horror and the Gilmore girls
I am appearing this week on the Gilmore Guys podcast, which is one of the biggest podcast there is
I think that drops probably Monday
The same day as this believe so you can get six hours of me if you want all right
We'll check that out also if you're in LA. I have a new weekly stand -up show at Mallow on Sunset and Silver Lake
called Creep Show. Come on out and check that out. And watch two broke girls.
Sure. And it's would a ten -season? Fifth season.
Fifth season. Yeah. Which premieres when?
It just premiered. Thanks Joe. Just premiered. All right folks. We'll see you next time.
Thanks everybody. Happy Holidays.