Welcome to We'll See You in Hell, or as we've been calling it lately,
we'll see you in the present environment we're all living in.
I thought you were going to go with America, but both are good. Yes.
Hello, folks. It is almost the end of the year, 2021.
And it looks like we're signing up for another year of the clusterfuck as we know it.
It's a shame. I just told Joe SNL pulled the live audience tonight.
That's when you know things are going wrong.
Those people need laughs.
So they're just going to do like on stage with no audience, are they going to do one of those Zoom things?
I did it all throughout the early days of the pandemic.
I thought it was always on Zoom.
They did a couple on Zoom. Those were those were death.
Yeah, but then they actually did ones in studio with no audience.
I didn't know. Right. Yeah.
It's and you couldn't really tell much difference.
You know, nobody was laughing.
And I was talking to Bobby, two of my favorite comedians and friends, Bobby Kelly and Rich Voss today.
Yes. On three way call and Rich Voss said, Yeah, this is terrible.
Because my shows were like a third full last night because of this, the spikes.
And then Bobby said, I wouldn't blame the spikes.
And then Rich said, I wish I had a spike to drive through your chest right now.
I mean, in fairness, how on a call with ball busting comedians could you say my audience was only a third full because of I mean, he must have known he was walking into it.
Yeah. So anyway, what do you think?
Future nations, I mean, a future generations, if they happen, will think of us.
What do you think? I mean, won't we just be the most disgusted look to look down upon time in American history outside of slavery and the Holocaust?
For what? For COVID?
Just everything like this little like the whole, the Trump, the COVID, everything, the insurrection.
I just think these are historical events. They're so recent. So we just kind of, but how are they going to look?
But don't lay it on one side of the political aisle.
No, I haven't seen Joe Biden in a year and a half.
So I did, you know, the clip I just saw of him was a reporter goes, now that you have more deaths from COVID during your presidency than Trump did, don't you think we should ask China to be transparent about what's going on here?
And Biden laughs and walks away.
Joey, I haven't seen that clip. I've just seen him falling asleep and in chairs and offices all across town.
Here's the worst part.
Clip could be completely fake for all we know. Anybody can put John Travolta's face on their cat with an app on their phone now.
What the hell? How do you know what's real anymore?
Look, there's there is a guy and I assume he is a hellion, a listener of the podcast, who the other day put together basically the trailer of Home Alone, but with me saying all the things Macaulay Culkin said or whatever.
And it looked like something he had done in like five seconds with an app.
And it was just me acting out the scenes of Home Alone without consent. It was horrifying.
Anyway, thank you, young man. It might be the same guy. Somebody sent one to me of me and Dracula Untold.
OK, yeah, probably the same guy, I would say.
And it was like, I mean, look, obviously it looked rushed by today's.
If you showed this technology to like F Murnau or whatever his name was, you know, he would have thought like the Antichrist had risen or something.
You know, to wrap his head around it.
Yeah. By the way, did you notice in Day of the Beast, they use the word hellions or they said they'll say we'll see what hell and hellions.
No, I didn't. That's pretty cool. Very cool.
Today, folks, we are we are talking about Videodrome, the 1983 David Cronenberg classic starring James Woods and Debbie Harry.
We'll get to that, of course.
But, Joe, what's new with you? Did you read about Nancy Reagan's head game this week?
What is that?
This was a big story.
This woman put up, you know, how people do this, like put up two pictures of people and be like, which one's better or whatever.
So there's a picture of Madonna, age 61, left it hanging out, lying on a bed, you know, like a bustier, right.
And then there was a picture of Nancy Reagan, like in 1984 or something.
So it said, no, it said, this is Madonna at 63.
This is Nancy Reagan at 64.
Which do you prefer, trashy or classy?
And so, OK, you know, who gives a shit?
But thousands of people started commenting that Nancy Reagan is legendary for giving the best blowjob in the game.
And she was known as being like the MGM blowjob queen who started each morning under a different executive's desk.
She got into acting.
That's how she met Ron Ron.
Presumably, she showed him her gifts and they made it work.
So this woman who's like, can you believe what a whore Madonna is, was getting just quote after quote after quote.
They talked to Maureen Stapleton, the great actress who was roommates with Nancy Reagan.
And they had interviewed her at some point.
Maureen Stapleton. Yeah.
Isn't that Jean Stapleton?
I get them mixed up.
The heavier one, her sister from from Michael.
Are they sisters?
I believe they are. Yes.
OK, well, I should look.
I'm looking.
All right.
Maureen Stapleton goes, yes, I was her roommate.
They go, is this true?
She was not only is it true, she loved it so much she kept a banana in her nightstand that would practice for an hour before bed each night.
Oh, boy.
Fascinating. Then Mr. T, of course, goes, you know, talks about how much he loved Nancy Reagan.
And everyone's like, oh, interesting.
You know, like every there was just millions and billions of jokes about it all week.
And also, of course, she turned her back on the AIDS epidemic.
Let a generation of gay men die.
Maureen raised money for gay.
Maureen Stapleton, yes, from Johnny Dangerously.
Yes.
And are they sisters?
No.
No, they look alike.
Didn't appear to be.
All right.
I'm trying to see early life.
I'm not seeing any mention of Jean in here.
OK, fine.
Anyway, you know, and but I like they enjoyed that story.
Here's what's so hypocritical about this.
A lot of people on the Internet, they've been shitting on Madonna for the last year.
Yeah, because she's got like a 22 year old boyfriend.
Uh huh.
And she's always like out like fucking party and whatever the fuck she's doing to Madonna shit.
And everybody's been like, grow up, Madonna.
Grow up. It's time that you did.
And it's like you fucks.
You fucks.
You know, it's it's like it's like when you don't like what the older person is doing, you call them a boomer.
You dismiss them.
You say that they're out of touch.
Of step.
And then when you don't like when an older person's acting just like you, then that's also bad.
It's just a very boomer mentality to have all the fun you want and then immediately decide nobody else can have any fun.
That's what my dad did in raising me.
That was his number one right tool and raising me.
I had all the fun.
You will have no fun.
And then, of course, you learn what these people are doing behind closed doors.
And it's like, what are you?
What are you doing?
Why are you attacking with Donna for having a good time?
Who knows?
She's not hurting anybody.
You know, I saw Matt Gates the other day going on and on about something, you know, some issue that he had a problem with news.
Can you believe the hypocrisy?
He's all angry.
And I'm sitting there going this man was running underage girls across state lines to fuck.
Why would he?
Why is he even showing his face?
Why isn't he in jail?
But they still just go right up and criticize everyone for how they live their life, even when currently being investigated.
It's just disgusting.
It's just this.
This is your own lawn.
Quick.
Just mow your own fucking lawn.
Quick, quick news.
Psycho.
Pat, I'll say in advance.
You don't have to go with me on this one.
Linda Carter coming out against J .K.
Rowling is J .K.
Rowling said that the debate about trans, I guess there was a debate in the UK about trans, about a rapist, a male rapist, male born rapist.
If he was said, well, but I identify as a woman.
They were asking the cops or the authority figures, would you then have to register him as a woman?
And they said yes.
And J .K. Rowling's made a quip about it was like the man, the penis man that just raped you is a woman.
And Linda Carter took shots at her and was like, it's not easy to understand humanity.
Stop picking, you know, I'm paraphrasing, but, you know, it's just understand the plight.
And it's like, first of all, Linda, who cares?
All right.
First of all, second of all, Linda, you supported the Clintons.
This is what drives me crazy.
You supported a literal assaultist.
You supported it.
And now you're going to give J .K. Rowling shit because she's saying it might be a little crazy that you're saying a man who raped says I'm a woman.
You have to go. No, you're a woman.
That's fine. When it's coming out of the it's the fallout of the last two or three or four or five years where all they have said is, you know, men rape too much.
Right. I haven't heard of women raping.
I'm sorry. I just haven't. I haven't heard of women raping.
I've heard of men raping a lot. Men raping men rape men raping women.
So I don't think it's that crazy when you say a guy raped a woman and he goes to the police station and she he goes, No, I'm actually a woman.
You go.
Let's can we discuss.
Can we discuss just for a second.
Can we talk about it?
I'm just I mean, how how did Linda Carter she was what Wonder Woman?
Yes.
What? Why were her remarks something that everyone knows about like other people speaking.
She was the most famous to speak out.
This is where I don't understand.
And by the way, and this is rolling.
Go and count your money.
Stop. It's the same with the fucking IT crowd guy.
I was so thrilled when he followed me. I was like, Oh, wow.
Which guy?
The creator.
Yeah.
It's all excited.
I was like, Oh, this guy's a legend.
This is amazing.
And I thought and at some point he went from jokes, funny jokes to his entire account being takedowns of trans people.
Is there something in the water over there like I don't listen?
Here's the thing. Here's the thing.
I get it.
If that's your politics, you don't agree.
Whatever.
But we're talking about it every second of the day.
I was Chappelle, by the way.
I go as far as to say this.
I don't get it.
I don't get a heavy interest in going after.
I don't understand it at all.
I have trans friends.
I respect the trans movement.
But this idea that you couldn't possibly say to somebody, for instance, a male born rapist, maybe you're being a little full of shit right now to try to get some.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
Come on.
Did that happen?
Or was it a hypothetical?
It was a hypothetical.
Then what?
I know everybody's mad.
At the end of the day, it's J .K. Rowling and Linda Carter arguing about a hypothetical scenario.
It's an insane.
Well, that's what I tweet.
I tweeted.
So Wonder Woman is mad that the Harry Potter lady might have offended trans rapists.
Guys, what the fuck are we even talking about anymore?
And I pulled that tweet down because people because there were people.
And here's the problem now with everything.
The people that agree with you or disagree with you will agree and disagree for all the wrong reasons.
Yeah.
So then the people agreeing with me are like, you know, being like and Chappelle's jokes and this and that.
And it's like, guys, we're not talking about jokes from a comedy like stop.
Right.
And then the other is no nuance.
You have to be 100 percent within the other people or against each issue across the board.
And that's what leads us to despair.
It's what has led us to where we are now.
And then the other people that were like seemingly agree with me or be like, you think mutilating your genitals is.
I was like, Jesus Christ, guys, I'm just pulling the fucking tweet down.
I'm saying what what what is the debate even at this point?
I don't understand any anymore.
If I see somebody presenting as a woman.
And they are a trans person or vice versa.
Yeah.
I hope I have a thousand and ten percent respect that.
And I would no matter what the circumstance, I wouldn't argue it in any way, shape or form.
But at the same time, I'm like, so any dude can or whatever can just say to me, like, what is that?
That's my wedding ring.
Oh, I thought it was your wife was trying to come.
No, it's my own.
It was like the back to the future trick where I'm seeing my hand.
I'm saying like you can't even, again, in an extreme case, say to a guy, hey, dude, you just did the most heinous thing that the most heinous men only do.
Right. And now you're going to tell me you're a woman.
Are you sure you're not doing this just for a little bit of fucking slack to even we can't question it.
Like, I don't know. I just I don't understand.
It's like Sean King is getting Sean King is still getting like credit.
This guy basically was pretty lied that he was black.
It's basically a white guy.
Sean King, the snowboarder.
Sean King is a is like a like a sort of socio political activist.
Oh, that's Sean. Okay. Yeah.
And it's like this guy's more or less to be black or what's more or less been caught being like you have no proof that you're a black person.
And like, but people are just like, it's okay.
So no, it's like, what the fuck is going on?
He did like a Dolezal or or what? I never even heard of the guy.
He he's adopted.
And when he was pressed on the issue and they said, you know, your parents, this, that his response basically wasn't looking up.
This response basically was, well, there's there's there's reason to believe I could be black.
And it's very clear that he's a white guy that is steered a thousand percent into trying to look black.
Okay. And my point is, is like, this is a guy that's still getting credit for like what he's discussing racially.
And when he brings up injustices and these things, it's like, guys, just because you're on the right side of history doesn't mean that you're right in who you are.
You could be on the right side. You could say I identify with the struggles of black people.
However, I think Hitler was a great guy.
Technically, you'd be on the right side of one part of history. Yeah.
And on the very wrong side of another part. Yeah.
So my point is, is you can do both. You can be an asshole, but still be on the right side of history in some way, shape or form.
And I just don't get why we can't we can.
I just don't get why it's so inflammatory to question it in any way.
I just don't get it. I don't. Am I making sense? I'm making sense.
You're you're making sense.
This is not a world that often makes sense. Stop making sense. Stop making sense.
I had an experience, everybody. Merry Christmas.
I had an experience this week where so I do letterbox where for the most part, I just give movies star ratings and it helps me be able to pull up what I'm going to be talking about on this show.
I saw the film Benedetta, which will be the first in my movie corner this week, the new Paul Verhoeven movie Lesbian Nuns.
Spicy film. Spicy. I want to see it.
I was just a fantastic film.
So how could you actually, I don't mean to be crass, but how hard could you really jerk to this thing?
They get in there. You could do it with ease.
So, and I'll get to the movie but so generally I don't review but I had kind of an amusing thought and I threw it up there.
My review was, honestly, it just felt good to get hard in a crowded theater again.
A lot of people liked it. Fine. And this guy comments on my thing.
The fact that grown ass men have the audacity to post shit like this publicly, seek help immediately.
And I go to the gentleman's account.
And he's reviewed Benedetta as well.
And he said, saw this with my girlfriend and was disgusted at the amount of single men in the theater.
I mean, I wanted, if I knew where this guy lived, I would drive over to his home.
Movies used to be, a whole lot of movies was sex.
The appeal of sex, eroticism, going to see somebody naked, see two famous people have sex, whatever.
That's why Paul Verhoeven made it, for many other reasons, to titillate.
That is not only a goal of a lot of filmmakers, I think it's an admirable goal.
And he's one of the few people still making a sexy picture.
But by the way, was I saying I was waving my boner in people's faces?
How does he know they were single men, by the way?
How does he know they were single men?
How does he know they weren't gay men?
How does he know anything?
And a single man can't go to a movie with sex in it?
Who's this guy?
Because you have a girlfriend?
Put his name in the comments.
I want to, you know what I mean?
Type his name into, I want to see.
I want to look him up.
He has one follower, which I assume is his girlfriend, who probably secretly hates him.
He's not somebody we need to concern ourselves with.
But, one's Christ.
Anyway, Benedetta is easily, easily one of my favorite movies of the year.
Paul Verhoeven is a master.
Even his bad movies are good.
Of course, you know, Basic Instinct is kind of the classic erotic thriller.
Robocop is kind of the classic of that genre.
Erotic thriller.
You know.
I found Robocop very erotic.
Sure.
Starship Troops.
I mean, the guy makes good shit.
And in recent years, he's had to go with very small budgets because he did Hollow Man and a few other movies that lost money.
And it's made him, in my opinion, a much more interesting filmmaker.
He's writing these movies himself.
He's clearly a guy with just like really interesting fascinations and fixations and movies horny as hell.
I'm going to tell you that it's in the late 17th century with plague ravaging the land.
Interesting. Kind of like today, Joe.
Very much.
You know, I thought of during this Christmas break, having a steamy lesbian affair with a nun.
You should.
I mean, it seems like they're happening in all nunneries, really.
And I get why.
Plague ravaging the land.
Benedetta joins the convent in Tuscany.
Capable from an early age of performing miracles, her impact on life in the community is immediate and momentous.
Boy, I'll say it is.
She starts banging this young nun who's very, very into her.
I thought this actress was 18 until I looked up and found out.
Thankfully, she was 29.
She looks very young, but they're having loads of sex.
There's a crucifix carved into a dildo at one point.
When the movie starts, you think you're watching like Lady Hawk, like she controls an owl with her mind.
And I'm like, what is this movie?
It's it's nuts.
There are special effects scenes in it.
She's constantly fantasizing about having sex with Jesus.
You want to talk about Day of the Beast pushing some buttons.
I would imagine Benedetta not getting a release in Spain.
But you know, I can't imagine somebody going to see this movie and not just walking out like it was fucking nuts.
And I had a great time.
It's you can tell people in the audience haven't seen sex on a big screen surrounded by people in a while.
Like there was people were shifting in their seats and uncomfortable.
There's a scene of sexual torture that I said to my friend that I saw the movie with.
I was like any other director would have cut away from this 45 seconds ago and Verhoeven stays on it a long time.
It's really uncomfortable.
He knows how to put it in your head.
He does.
And there's scenes with like CGI snakes and stuff.
If I had to give a fault that definitely show the restrictions of not having a big budget,
it's kind of crazy to watch a Paul Verhoeven movie that has special effects that look like they came out of a YouTube original.
There's a few effects scenes that you wish you would have just cut or found a different way to do the snakes coming into sex acts.
No comment.
All right.
But it's part of the it's part of the fantasy.
So I'm not looking a lot of the movie is kind of in her head, too.
So the effects aren't that glaring, I guess.
But overall, I had a blast.
I can't wait to see it again.
I hope we get a screener.
If you never saw Black Book, which is kind of the movie that sort of kicked off the second chapter of Verhoeven's career.
I recommend that one, too.
But Benedetta is awesome.
Highly recommend.
Oh, very good.
My one and only.
I'm going to sneeze.
Geez.
I also have a new psycho to do.
But hold on.
I lost my.
Wow.
Geez.
You hear that?
We talked a lot.
Let me do a quick new psycho and I'll do a new psycho.
Then I'll do a I'm just going to weave it into this stuff.
I'll do a new psycho.
Then you do your next movie corner.
But we talked a lot about Will Ferrell in the last episode, and I was very disappointed to hear about the falling out that he and Adam McKay had.
Same.
Especially because it seems so avoidable.
Like it wasn't any it wasn't like he banged his wife or something.
Apparently, Will Ferrell and Adam McKay have parted ways and they have not spoken in a very, very long time.
And Adam McKay says that he has reached out repeatedly to Will Ferrell to try to talk about it.
I will say this and got no response.
I will say this about Adam McKay's reach outs.
He did say, like, you know, I wrote Will and was like, you know, many times I've been slighted and didn't say it's like, dude, that's not how you apologize.
I apologize.
But apparently it's all over this new L .A. Lakers movie that's coming out that Adam McKay did where Will Ferrell was going to play the coach.
And the part ended up going to John C. Reilly and Will Ferrell apparently is very upset about it.
And that ended their friendship.
I will say what's interesting.
I've always had nothing but admiration for Will Ferrell.
And he seems like a nice guy.
But I've seen now a couple phase on love interviews about the movie Elf.
Uh huh.
And phase on is very close with John Favreau, directed elf and also directed phase on in both that and made phase on is said very publicly.
That he does not like Will Ferrell and that Will Ferrell is a diva and a problem.
And as he's gone as far as say he wants to make health to without Will Ferrell.
So who knows?
Love wants to do this or Favreau wants to do.
Phase on love has said I would love to see an elf to without Will Ferrell like John Favreau is my boy.
I love this guy.
Will Ferrell made his life hell.
He's a bad guy.
Huh?
So who knows?
You know?
Now all I have to go off is when he hosted SNL and I thought he was the nicest man I've ever met in my life.
Seems like a nice guy, right?
Yeah.
But maybe elf your first movie.
Who knows?
It seems like he's a sensitive guy like a lot of comedy folk.
I don't know.
I've never heard terrible.
But I've heard Jim Carrey is a nice guy, but I heard he's also a pain in the ass.
You know what I mean?
Sure.
So it's like maybe one of those things.
I was just watching Jim Carrey in black and white talking about depression for like five minutes.
And I was like it was one of those Instagram things that goes past as you're scrolling.
And I was like, God, this guy has just disappeared up his ass.
You know, like there's nothing in his eyes that shows the comedian that once was.
Yeah.
Well, once you started talking about how everything's an illusion that we're all living in.
Go hang out with.
What's the guy?
Brand Russell Brand.
You guys can wear, you know, I like Russell on your on each finger and talk about philosophy.
What's your Russell Brand?
I don't like him.
I like his Jim Carrey.
He's just not as big.
I like his YouTube show.
I think he's got a very balanced perspective on everything.
And I like that.
He's like, I want to talk to people I don't agree with respectfully.
I think that's pretty cool.
All right, Joe.
I've never seen it.
I saw the new West Side Story directed by Steve Spielberg.
I was.
Look, I love the movie West Side Story, the ridge.
I've seen a stage production or two.
I like the music a lot.
And, you know, the story is basically Romeo and Juliet with street gangs.
I've never been a fan of the movie, but I'm a fan of knife fighting.
Yeah.
Well, again, speaking of Will Ferrell, that big anchorman scene where all the
different anchors come out is a West Side Story spoof, you know.
So why did Spielberg remake this all time classic?
I don't know.
It's his first full on musical.
For some reason, he brought on a guy, Janis Kaminsky to shoot it, who is
Holly Hunter's husband, the guy who shot like Saving Private Ryan.
And sure enough, it's West Side Story and it looks like fucking Terminator
Genesis.
It's like that kind of like chrome color.
And the trailer looked ridiculous.
It looked like I was like, is this live happening in front of me?
Like, it looked crazy.
It's, you know, we saw on the big Dolby screen and everything.
And it just didn't work.
I mean, to me, the biggest issue is Ansel Elgort, who I think is one of the
worst actors currently working and has been me too.
But nobody cares.
He's still the star of West Side Story.
Brought up like hundreds of text messages of him, you know, basically
confirming that girls were underage and then saying, OK, then I do want to
fuck you.
You know, like not great stuff.
So not a good look.
So Ansel is singing in this and acting.
He's not really great at either.
I thought he sucked in Baby Driver.
He really sucks in this.
They've corrected something.
So the most glaring error with the original West Side Story is that they have
half the cast in brown face.
Right.
You can actually see the makeup like sweating off them in certain scenes.
Yeah.
Like a Giuliani press conference.
Right.
This tries to correct that by casting some actual Latin X folks.
And can you is it Latin X?
I still don't know if it's Latin X or Latin X.
I was brutally mocked once for saying Latinx.
So I know it's not Latinx.
It's not Latinx.
I just say Gas X to be safe.
Sure.
It's you know, the cast is good.
Pretty much everybody except Ansel Elgort is good.
The problem is he's the head of this street gang or he's the guy we're spending
most of our time with.
He falls in love with Maria, a Puerto Rican woman and you know,
it causes all kinds of friction.
The all white street gang from the 50s.
What a thing to fear.
And all of the guys in Elgort's crew are more interesting or better singing,
better performers.
You care more about them.
And that's your problem.
You want to spend more time with his henchmen because he's so boring.
Rita Moreno steals the show as she did the original West Side Story.
Now, she's like 90 years old.
She looks great.
She sounds great.
She sings a song.
They do kind of change the order of some of the show and some of the songs.
I thought it made it worse.
It's longer than the original, which is already a two and a half hour movie.
There's great stuff in it.
There's songs in it that, you know, you almost applaud at the end.
They're so well put together.
Spielberg's not like being lazy here.
It's just kind of it just seems like there was so much effort put into this thing.
And there's no real purpose for it to exist, in my opinion.
All right.
And it lost a tremendous amount of money.
So apparently everybody feels the same.
And then my last one, folks.
Oh, wait, I got one.
Oh, okay.
I thought you said you didn't.
No, I got one.
And then I'll do a scary stuff and then we'll move on.
Okay.
I've been watching the new season of It's Always Sunny.
Same.
First episode, not good.
Second episode was The Gang Makes Lethal Weapons 7, which I thought was was very funny.
And, you know, they did a commentary on how the lethal weapon episodes
excuse me, that they did before had been pulled from streaming.
And in the episode, they said our versions of Lethal Weapon 5 and 6
have been pulled from the library for Mac's poor decision to do blackface.
So I thought it was a funny commentary on what actually happened with the show
and what was happening with the characters.
And then they go on to make Lethal Weapon 7.
And it's just disastrous and problematic.
And I thought it was very funny and sharp.
The two episodes after that, I did not enjoy.
However, when they finally get to Ireland in episode five,
I thought episodes five and six, it really became It's Always Sunny again,
particularly because of the all time classic episodes, the Ireland ones.
They were really great. Thanks to Glenn Howerton, I think.
I mean, he's 100 % agree. 100 % agree.
He's just a master.
He's a master.
When he's yelling at Mac about identity doesn't have to affect everything you do.
He's like, if you want to go have sex with a bunch of men,
then have sex with a bunch of men. If you don't, then don't.
You fool.
Joe, you fool. I rewound again and again and again.
And I rewound it so many times that I was watching their faces.
Like, how did Charlie and Rob not laugh when he says, you fool?
It was the best, the best line of the show.
Can't tell if he ad -libbed it.
It seems almost like he's forgetting the lines and then just says it.
It felt so ad -libbed that you fool.
That's why I thought I would be able to catch them laughing, but I didn't.
Yeah.
Seasons are sorry.
Episodes five and six are great.
It's a subplot of DeVito getting,
the whole subplot is him getting a seed caught in his teeth,
him trying to get the seed out with a screw.
I wonder sometimes if DeVito isn't like,
you guys brought me to fucking Ireland and all I'm doing for two weeks
is trying to get a seed out of my fucking tooth.
I mean, they don't even give him a story anymore.
And then the other one, he's just trying to burn papers for the entire episode.
Yeah.
Which another, which it's always said he always did well was like,
they would coin like a term for something that I'd never heard.
And in this one, it's Frank shredding documents
because they proved that he had been present on the Epstein Island.
And they were calling it a shred and spread,
where you had to shred documents and spread them around
so they couldn't reconnect.
Look, it was 95 % legitimate business.
And then, you know, the other 5 % kind of tainted though.
It did. It really did.
There's a whole...
Those were really great episodes.
And then casting Cole Meany, an actual great Irish actress,
Charlie's dad made those scenes.
It was very emotional, really,
like with the first scene where he's saying goodnight to dad and all that.
It was great.
And then finally, like the Frank spiel about Bill Gates fucking the manatees
at Epstein's Island and like how it was mutually consensual,
but the manatees were so depressed that when Bill Gates didn't come back,
they swam themselves into boat motors.
Yeah, it was amazing.
Yeah, so it was amazing.
And every time they'll do something like that,
a long monologue about Bill Gates fucking manatees
or an entire episode about a monkey running the bar and making them beers.
I think about how many times Mr.
Charlie Day has lectured me about a story being too broad.
And I keep it to myself.
I did not enjoy that monkey episode.
No, I think it's been a solid season.
It's considering they're in season 15.
I mean, them and Curb are keeping the comedy lights on, really.
Well, it was the wrong kind of monkey.
You want like an any which way but loose chimp.
And they had like some sort of weird like tree monkey.
And it wasn't like it wasn't a fun monkey.
There's a great idea.
Fuck their mouths before he left.
Yeah, that was funny.
There's a great Seinfeld joke where he goes, he goes, My neighbor got a pet monkey.
You know, people, I got to say, if you're at the point of needing a pet in your life
and you get a monkey, you might want to think about having a kid.
If you hit the level where you need a pet that can roller skate and smoke cigars,
think about starting a family.
He's a good comedian.
I don't care what people say.
I love him.
But that's I expected that kind of monkey.
I expected like the gang replaces D with the monkey.
I thought it was going to be like a monkey in like a tuxedo walking around.
You know, maybe with a platter like an orangutan or something.
And it was it was it was not it was it was not a fun monkey.
Right. But anyway, it looks like they're still in Ireland next week.
So I hope we get another couple there.
It's it almost pieces together like a movie.
It seems like you believe by the.
Oh, God, sorry.
No, go ahead.
Can you believe that?
And I don't think they're going to do it because the last episode was very focused on
Dennis having covid.
But can you believe by the way, Dennis with covid incredible.
And then him talking to the castle ghost.
I was like, holy shit.
Like, I mean, and then his other thing about how women with red hair smell.
I was like, everything he's doing in this makes no sense.
And I love it.
You have no odor.
Grabbing her hair and smelling it.
Yeah.
And then I smell your hair and there's no odor.
That's weird.
That's weird of you.
It was so crazy.
So crazy.
But but I can't.
And again, I don't think they're going to do it at this point
because they're already doing an episode where Dennis has covid.
But I thought for certain this season, they were going to do a sequel to the gang
quarantines, which they did in that flu season and is one of the greatest
episodes ever, ever, ever.
If it's always sunny.
And I was like, there's no way they're not going to do like a covid
quarantine sequel because they always do sequel might.
So maybe.
Yeah.
But we'll see.
Anyway, that's that's all I got.
And my last one is Red Rocket, which is one that they're talking about for
maybe some Oscar buzz, et cetera.
I think ultimately it's the kind of film that Oscar voters will not like, but
you might see Simon Rex get a nomination.
It's Sean Baker who did Tangerine, which is a really funny movie that shot on
an iPhone.
Highly recommend.
He did the Florida project with Willem Dafoe, which I really liked a lot.
He did this movie called Starlet about a woman working in the porn industry
with hardcore porn scenes in it.
They had like actual porn actors shoot the scenes.
Red Rocket is stars, Simon Rex, who was at one time like a sort of actor.
He was always in like National Lampoon's Dorm Days or whatever.
He was in the scary movies.
Yeah.
It was an MTV VJ.
Mostly known for in college.
Your friends going, hey, you remember that guy, Simon Rex?
Yeah.
And then they would show you a picture of him masturbating because he did some
solo porn scenes back in the day.
He was very young, not underage, but young.
So cute.
And cute.
Him being given this part.
I mean, Sean Baker really sees things in people that, you know, this is way
beyond Tarantino.
It's not like Simon Rex was some great actor who's getting another chance like
Pam Grier.
This guy was nothing.
He's handed an amazingly written part and he performs it incredibly well.
It's the kind of thing that really makes you realize how much people blow
acting out of proportion sometimes.
Like a really well written part is oftentimes what makes great acting.
You know, if you say a really well written part, odds are it's going to be
good.
But he's incredible.
I think he's going to be one of it'll be like the Captain Phillips guy, the guy
who was like, I'm the captain now.
He'll never work again.
I don't think it's unfortunate because it's like, you're not going to see him,
you know, in a romantic comedy or something next.
It's kind of a one and done.
I could be like, maybe it'll be George Clooney, but no, it's kind of like
Napoleon Dynamite.
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
He's incredible in it.
It's a character study.
It's so he's kind of down and out in LA.
He is an ex porn star in the movie.
He goes back to Texas where his ex wife and mother -in -law are living.
Almost everybody in the film is played by non actors, which gives it a whole lot
more of a real feel, a documentary feel.
And while he is banging his ex wife every night, he starts a flirtation and
romance with a 17 year old girl who works at a donut shop.
And I was convinced this girl was 17.
The scenes are really creepy because he's about 50 and he's hitting on her and
it's uncomfortable, especially in a comedy.
It's like, this is really, it kind of made me feel like that Observe and Report
movie, which I thought we'd never get a comedy like that ever again.
And it is, it's really weird.
Then they start fucking and this girl is in graphic sex scenes and we have been
led to believe that she is 17 years old.
So there were walkouts.
There was a lot of kind of audible noise in the theater when I saw it.
And I certainly was having a bit of an issue with it myself.
I looked her up.
She's 26.
Sure.
But I saw it the day after Benedetta and I'm like, God, there's just, you know,
I don't know what it is, but there's a, there's a
She's supposed to be 17 in the movie.
She's 17.
And it would have been so easy to make her 18 and take just a little bit of the
awkwardness out of it.
No, but that's, but to me, that's the point.
No, it totally is.
It's a character study of a fuck up.
It's a character study in the best way.
Like all the seventies films were right.
The movie is really funny.
And just, it's that feeling that I personally crave when I go to the movies
and never get anymore, which is surprise.
I was surprised in almost every scene by what was going on.
Okay.
Super outrageous.
It's super R rated for sure.
But I dug it.
I really did.
It's an interesting movie.
I think you'll probably get the screen or jump.
It's worth a watch.
My only real grievance with it is it's two hours and 10 minutes.
And you know, there's 20 minutes of this thing that snip out and make it an all
time masterpiece as it is.
I think it's one of the best movies of the year,
but I would have cut it down a little bit.
I just got a house of Gucci in the mail.
I'll get which ridiculous, but I dug it.
Yeah.
I mean, I've been watching more and more eclipses.
This thing is like Amos and Andy for Italian people.
I mean, it's outrageous.
You will not believe.
You will not believe what your boy Jared Leto was bringing to that table.
That's the ever review of red assess said that where they're like,
we don't understand what he's doing.
Like, I don't know if it's good or bad.
Yeah, it is a combination of of Fredo and Mario.
The character Mario.
That's somewhere where it where it was.
Yeah. The clip that keeps seeing on the Internet is always like,
you're going to make me cry.
Yeah.
But he has good jolly.
By the way, then you see, I looked up the real guy.
Yeah.
He was a slim, handsome man.
We didn't look like fucking like out of shape.
Jeffrey Tambor was obsessed with Oscars.
That's all he wants.
It's like they made him look terrible in this thing.
You look up the real guy.
You're like, and then the real guys like kids and grandkids are like,
hey, fuck you.
My dad wasn't like this.
Like, yeah.
Well, then really Scott is getting real surly in his old age.
Somebody was like, why did you cast Al Pacino in this?
Like he, you know, our dad was much more something.
And he's like, yours should be so fucking lucky.
Oh boy.
You should be so fucking lucky to be cast by an Italian legend.
I don't know.
He's just, he's cussing in every interview now.
I think he's pissed off about the last duel probably, but.
Oh yeah.
I know.
Starts talking about aliens in the middle of the Gucci interview.
They're like, yeah, exactly.
That's not what we're doing here.
I know he's not happy with the new, uh,
FX alien show that's coming out.
Who's not asked them like,
It's from the guy that did the Fargo show who I liked a few seasons of that.
Um, but I don't know.
I don't know.
I don't know why they're doing an alien show.
I'll watch it.
Alien talk about another franchise.
They need to let die.
It's like, you got one in two.
Yeah.
For some people, three, for some people.
Four.
I'm surprised to hear you acknowledge two.
Um, I'm, I, I can, I'm not a fan,
but I can recognize why people like it.
You know what I mean?
Like it's like, but I mean, from three forward, you're like, it's like,
what are we even talking about?
Yeah.
I dig three.
I mean,
Going back to them is a lot like revisiting the matrices,
matrixes as I did recently, you know, like when you're there in the theater
and you're all amped up and you know,
you can almost not help but be let down.
It's never going to be the original,
but when you watch them with some distance,
there's always good stuff in them.
I think alien three has got good stuff.
And I think the matrix sequels have great action in them.
They're just not great movies.
Curious to see this new, uh, this new one.
Uh, which by the way,
we'll be doing the new one and we'll be doing, um,
Nightmare Alley,
a combination of the 1947 film with Tyrone power,
which spoiler is awesome.
Awesome.
Old movie.
Uh, and it's on the criterion channel.
And then we're going to be talking about the new nightmare alley,
Guillermo del Toro's.
We're also going to do the new matrix.
Yeah.
That'll be the next two.
And then we'll probably, I got to tell you,
you're going to be surprised here.
It's coming from me.
Maybe we'll do the new Spider -Man.
I want to see this new Spider -Man.
I want to see the return of Defoe and Malina.
I'm going to go now and I'm here.
I'm hearing it's awesome and you have to see it and it'll,
it don't get it spoiled.
And then I also realized that it's the third,
I really liked those Spider -Mans with the kid,
the real young guy.
I love those.
They're fun and they're funny and cool.
Uh, so I'm excited to see it too.
I think.
Is this the one where they bring back everybody?
Is that a good thing?
What about McGuire and got elect?
Well,
there's rumors that McGuire and Garfield show up,
but it's not been confirmed.
And they're trying to keep the spoilers offline as to whether or
not that happens.
But.
As you know, from the trailer,
You have electro Jamie Fox.
The worst.
Sandman.
Thomas Hayden church.
You have green goblin, Wilhelm Defoe.
You have doc,
Alfred Molina cool and you have lizard from the first spider -man movie played
by the guy that always played you know the guy from Big Lebowski that plays
the Stormer yeah he played the devil in
Constantine and right you mean the guy with Buscemi and Fargo right yeah yeah
Peter Stormer so that's that's the crew and I'm sure there's some more surprises
but you know they're doing this spider -verse multiverse thing which is
also what they're doing with Flash with Keaton so you know look man I I want to
see it I well wasn't Keaton in the first of these as Zendaya's dad Keaton is
vulture the villain vulture oh yeah but he was also I'm sure I have a feeling
he's gonna come back and be they're gonna do the sinister six you know the
sex whatever villains but anyway I want to see it it's actually out now I might
go see it during Christmas but anyway so we'll do that one as well coming up
those are the movies let's get on to Videodrome yeah Videodrome I mean I've
seen this movie five times and I love it and I would say I'm a little more
confused by it each time it's like it gets less clear to me over time and I've
never really had that experience but wild flick wild fucking flick man it's
truly wild it is like you know it's like what David Lynch does it's it's it's
putting you know these dark visions dreams you know whatever Cronenberg has
going on in his brain up on the screen and being like you know roll with it or
don't you know it's just kind of like an assault of incredible images you got a
sleazy James woods woods at his best yeah it's a shame I mean classic woods
man classic woods yeah he is really just like sweaty and smoking in every scene
he's rail thin you know you can smell the coke spoon coke spoon I don't know
what the hell I'm talking about okay can you walk us through the plot Joe I mean
at its core this is really just kind of a satire about Walsh no I can't I don't
know what the hell is going on in this movie but I loved every minute of it he
as far as I can tell woods it's timelier than ever I mean it's it it feels like it
could have been made yesterday for sure he works at a local TV station that's
bordering on like almost like public access access and they want to he you
know he's a big fan of it you know it's it's the 80s it's it's the era of the
shock jock and when you know rated X and all these these things were happening
in entertainment and nasties yeah yeah and and woods wants to explore that and
push the envelope and he gets wind of a TV show called Videodrome that is
basically airing or a channel or something where it's airing snuff films
basically and but they're fake but they might not be and he's not sure so he
wants to basically bring the broadcast of Videodrome into his network because
this is gonna make them huge and blah blah blah and of course once he starts
to watch Videodrome he starts a descent into into madness and it becomes much
bigger than just a TV show the first thing I thought was and become it
starts to sort of fuse with him like he's he's inserting the VHS tape into
his chest at one point and then he's touching the screen and the screens
touching him back and it's like is this alive what is it you know yeah there
too there so yeah two of the most insane visuals in this thing are James Woods
forms what looks like a chest pussy yeah that he the original title was chest
pussy actually and it did not get passed he inserts videotapes into it yeah why I
don't know he hides a gun in it at one point yeah and then at another point the
TV screen which is this is back what your tube TVs with the rounded box TVs
that sound your floor when your TV was a piece of furniture not just a flat thing
that hung on the wall the the TV screen itself forms almost a vaginal crease
that he fucks with his head almost yes in the meanwhile he's dating Debbie
Harry who plays a woman who like can only get off on like the most violent
disturbing creepy sex while being the hottest woman you've ever seen and you
do Debbie Harry I got to tell you Debbie Harry's was so amazing because she's
like she's so hot but she's like yeah she's like regular hot like you could you
could imagine meeting Debbie Harry at a bar and actually talking to her you know
what I mean she's not like she's not like Sofia
Vergara hot where you're like she looks like a fucking vogue cover this is
ridiculous I can't picture this you can also imagine Debbie Harry being drunk
enough to speak to you listen according to the stories she was back then like
apparently she really liked them sex yeah and she was like she was fun but
anyway my point is is he's dating her and she's really into like you know
violent sort of sex and he gets on this you know he gets on the road to trying
to track down the makers of Videodrome and it's odd because as he goes to find
the maker he he he it starts to get into this sort of I don't know what the it
starts to move more and more into a hyper reality where like at one point he
encounters a homeless shelter that is based upon bringing homeless people in
to let them watch TV yeah so they can get the fix they need but he doesn't
there's no there's no commentary on like that's odd or that's weird it's just
accepted in the movie so the movie very much revolves around the obsession with
television and and and all that stuff that was happening at the time but yeah
it's like he doesn't do that extra step of having people say like oh this is
weird and that he just presents you with a society that you you take it
value you know and that's kind of the interesting thing about it it's so short
it's 88 minutes and when it ended yet like I like I said again I felt like I
had missed something or I felt like it needed to be 10 minutes longer unlike
Red Rocket but it's it's an experience unlike any other it's an incredible movie
and clearly not on a huge budget he the movie has like a feel and style and vibe
all its own it's awesome it is an awesome movie visually stylistically
thematically it's one of those things it's it plays a lot like I would I would
equate it to like a Samuel Beckett play where in the sense of even if you don't
fully understand what's happening at all times you know there's a reason for it
you just know in the back of your head there's a reason this is happening well
it's definitely absurdist it's it's great it's it's it's great and then of course
the great line that the movie ends with long live the new flesh yes James would
shoots himself the head yeah typically dark ending from Cronenberg well like
the fly also as with the fly getting shot in the fucking head yeah but um it
another movie that is and you know horror purists will will be upset no
does it but it's begging out for a remake because the only thing that dates
this at all is the VHS tapes to make them what the movie is about is this
complete control you give the TV in this case or you give to your devices how
easily does it translate to your cell phone all these people that you're
giving your phone number your email your passwords your bank information you know
like I was doing that with my account in the other day she was like can you just
email me your bank passwords and your credit card passwords and I start
writing the email and I'm like no no I'm gonna give you a call like that's
insane so and everything that he is predicting in this movie has come to
pass these devices have complete control over our lives you see what's happening
with Facebook and Zuckerberg and all this now and the people who are
controlling what we absorb all day every day do not have our best interests at
heart as they certainly don't in Videodrome either great the guys always
done super political movies but they don't skimp on the fun it's not like
the political movies now where it's all political there's no entertainment value
he just does a great job of giving his movies meaning while keeping them fun
crazy exciting I agree the run this man had I got a shout out in the 80s alone
79 you got the brood which is awesome on criterion you got scanners which is
another wild one it's not a favorite of mine but very cool movie on there but a
huge scanners fan but but yeah solid stuff and that's also criteria it is
Cronenberg criterion is only second to Wes Anderson is that right I believe so
I think Cronenberg has the most movies in criterion next to Wes Anderson yeah
they did crash they did Videodrome but um yeah his 80s the brood scanners
Videodrome the dead zone with Christopher Walken which is fucking
awesome one of the best King adaptations the fly which is my favorite horror
movie of the 80s I think it's way way way way up my ladder yeah yeah I mean for
me it's that poltergeist the shining it's your classics and then dead
ringers closed out the decade with twin sadistic gynecologist played by Jeremy
Irons that is a very fucked up movie since then he's been more hit and miss
but I think he's made two masterpieces history of violence with Vigo and
Eastern promises with Vigo and apparently he's working on an Eastern
promises sequel as we speak yeah I mean you know talk about a guy that's had a
great career starts out making these low -budget horror sci -fi rumps in
Canada yeah comes down to the States starts doing something slightly bigger
budget but basically would equate to cult films starts getting all of his
stuff into the criterion collection which is amazing and then late -era
basically in his 60s or whatever starts doing movies that are getting nominated
for Oscars you know Cronenberg's a pretty amazing guy he truly is and I
have heard he's in failing health I hope that's not true but his son did
possessor which came out last year you ever watch possessor Joe no it's fucking
awesome and it's like you know like he's he's as good as his dad on his first
movie or a second movie so hopefully the guy's got a big career ahead of him but
it's he's you know sometimes if a kid does something and their dad was a
director they try to do something very different like Jason Reitman sure he
Cronenberg's son said I'm going to make a David Cronenberg movie exactly like my
dad did but luckily he's got the chops to do it I mean it's an awesome movie
with Tilda Swinton check it out all right I would say two hogs way up for
what videodrome my hog is way up for videodrome yes oh by the way you got
Michael Ironside in there let's not forget well he's no that's scanners shit
wait who plays the guy oh god who plays the guy then like the actor on the guy
that's on the TV the whole time the guy that like comes somebody's like we
invented videodrome and we need to experiment oh that guy's great I'm
beginning mix I thought that was Michael Ironside I got mixed up for a second
no I mean Cronenberg gets just fucking great performances out of people love
this movie check out all of his stuff especially his 80s stuff we will be back
next time with some combination of the new spider -man the new matrix and
the new Guillermo del Toro I'm on Instagram and Twitter at the Patrick
Walsh thank you to Emily for all of your help this year and every year and thank
you to all of our patreon fans for keeping the show going Joe thank you
all Joe DeRosa comedy on Instagram and Twitter thank you to Will Potter for
delivering the art we appreciate it thank you to all the fans we love you
guys we can't believe the support we can't tell you how much we appreciate
the support and you're all the best we hope to see you soon live which we are
trying to plan but unfortunately COVID might be setting us back a little more
on that but we'll get at you soon and one of the milder variances is rocking
the nation we'll see you at that time all right and we'll see you and hell
Merry Christmas Happy New Year