folks it's a very early recording of we'll see you in hell by that I mean Pat
and I are recording at what is an early hour for me in an ungodly hour for him
Pat what time is it where you're you're at right now well I'll tell you oh I
just got interrupted by my rooster sorry it's the crack of dawn here 834 a .m. some
of you get up this early every day most of you most Americans get up to go to
but this is early for us so leave us alone now for Joe it's almost 11 a .m. I
don't know what he's complaining about well almost 11 it's almost 12 it's a
left almost well no I this is not early for me I just I went out too big last
night and stayed out too late thinking I don't got anything to do to 1130 yeah
next thing you know you're going can I get six hours of sleep in five I'll
survive you know the old Larry Miller routine it's fucking New York you know
you don't need that additional two hours of party time two o 'clock is a very
reasonable time especially on a weeknight to shut down the ship and go
to bed that's what you say till you don't have it anymore and then you're
like fuck you do need it I wasn't out till four but you know you come home and
then you eat as one does a full chicken dinner you mean sides I had collard
greens I'd cooked I had chicken that I'd baked I ate the whole thing neither of
those things are the worst thing you could eat those at night and be kind of
it sounds like to me you had a keto meal yeah we're heading to bed yeah it's I'm
not kidding I'm not beating myself up about what the food was that I ate it's
just ridiculous to be coming in drunk yeah at 230 and then being like let me
sit down for a southern -style chicken dinner literally tucking the napkin into
your your shirt like a bib Joe's also not mentioning the half cherry pie he
while waiting this wasn't a dessert this was while waiting for the chicken to
heat up in the microwave well you know it was sitting on the window sill we're
gonna let it just sit there yeah yeah anyway today we are tackling scream six
they're back now to putting the numbers on the screams last scream was just
scream again and why not scream again scream again is a better time I agree
scream again as I said it I was like scream louder scream again and and by
the way that'd be a fun titling for the franchise that fits the franchise like
scream bloody scream and you know what I mean like they should they should do
like those hammer style titles that would be that would make sense but but
we pitch screaming in our own creation we have it earmarked by our old archives
we could find out when we copyrighted it we do scream and in which is a spin -off
which is Gail Weathers working her way up from like a newsroom PA to the Gail
Weathers we know Courtney Cox now not a bad idea why wouldn't you watch this
scream in it I know why I wouldn't watch it but I would sell it well yeah there's
gonna be a lot of spoilers so I mean if you care if you don't whatever but let's
let me just start by asking well we'll get to the movie I can't I'll wait I'll
hold my question anyway so that's that's coming today speaking of screaming and
I thought I had one and now I can't remember what the hell it was well
there's not there's not a lot going on Hollywood has completely shut down the
moment we are awaiting the writers guild strike so there's not a lot of big
announcements happening although we're getting close to some big movies it's
only a month before we talking about the next Indy Jones right here in this
yeah that's coming up exciting stuff what talking about Evil Dead next
fucking week you know Wow yeah that's that's wild I saw an article today
about Carrie Russell discussing her new project the diplomat and how she's not
playing a baddie anymore yeah it was like finally Carrie Russell's playing a
good guy one of the good guys like it's all she's ever played outside of one
fucking TV show am I missing something are they referring to what the Americans
I guess oh yeah she wasn't bad on that she was just Russian if you want to
consider Russian bad that's all you do we usually do no I mean she was a
character you know granted she did some fucked up things but she was killing
spies and murderers I don't think she was the villain of that piece I do like
Carrie Russell I like her too I just didn't understand this take of yeah and
then I see oh this is the screaming and I want to discuss you know look I I'm an
idiot because I keep going to movieweb .com to get all my movie news and
they are pretty good about delivering the news but they have become a bit
tabloid ish in certain ways in other ways they really deliver some some
great articles they had one the other day that was like why the success of
Mario Brothers is bad and we're like you ready for all these shit video game
movies we're gonna get now that was like that's a very funny spot -on article but
then they print something like this I'm trying to get to the damn headline and I
should have bookmarked it and I didn't but anyway I'll just paraphrase it it was
basically saying like why Brian De Palma's name worth is is lower than it's
ever been and and the know this is so weird because I have never gone to
movie web I went once this week I read one article and it was this exact article
you're describing this is very strange but go on it is strange it disgusted me
like because the the angle was like you know this guy used to be one of the
greats and now you can't sell bupkis with his name attached yeah and it's
like he's 80 yeah it's like what are you talking about guys he doesn't work
anymore like what like yeah it just really bothered me I was like this is
what's wrong with the goddamn culture this is what we do well the man had a
nearly 50 year career not quite that long but dozens almost you know at least
interesting movies and the article was like so when he came on the scene he's
hot with Carrie like yeah you mean 1976 five years before I was born yeah yeah
we had some success then it went through the 70s 80s and into the late 90s three
decades of success and they're like but in recent years he's only had a couple
of independently financed movies yeah so you mean he's still working as an old
man and by the way the independent busy independently financed because they were
like wild ideas when he was like I'm just gonna go the shout outs to a guy or
props to a guy kudos to whatever the fuck you'd want to say it to a guy
that's like hey I'm in my 60s I'm gonna hit the Indy circuit now yeah like come
on man Jesus Christ like the guy's a legend I don't understand they're big
on these like the seven best movies of whoever then you look at them and you
don't agree with any of them I saw Nicolas Cage interviewed the other night
they asked him his five favorite movies of his own and I was like these are some
awful choices Nick he only acknowledged his recent small Indy career he said my
fave five favorite movies of my entire career are Mandy okay I'll give you
Mandy Joe pig and by the way these are just names that has college movies called
Joe and pig it's pretty impressive but um yeah it was the all these indie things
he's done in the last five years and it's like so what are you embarrassed of
you know like what are you doing who knows they ran another article here's
another scream it in for you what the hell did I just do here damn it David
Mamet movies ranked mm -hmm 24 meaning every movie he's ever written
co -written or written and directed okay some of these are right where they
deserve to be on the list some of them I'm like what are you talking about so
they got they got American Buffalo and Hoffa at 23 and 22 mm -hmm they got
Oliana at 21 right out of the gate guys two of the man's most riveting plays
that he committed to film mm -hmm you're saying are the lowest of the list these
are the reason the guy gets a list or the two of these things yeah yeah above
those on the list let me guess they didn't like Oliana because the the
subject material was daring or something it's getting to a point where
just having a daring subject matter is a problem which I don't understand they do
say the movie comes out as possibly problematic and necessitates multiple
visions to completely deal with it I don't know if that's why it got so low
Buffalo sounds like an interesting picture to me yeah takes place mostly in
a single location with a fundamental with which is fundamental to elevate
even more of the dialogue parts of the screenplay the actors are in good shape
and deliver strong performance I don't even get why a Buffalo is so low Hoffa
to me is an awesome movie I don't know why that's so low but but even if you
put it low here's what's above it at number 20 Hannibal guys come on 19 the
postman always rings twice now come on that movie sucks at 17 made for
televisions Lake Boat okay I don't know what Lake Boat is it's it's based on his
play you know fine they've got Edmund at 16 which I was talking about on here the
other week Edmunds an interesting movie it is not better than any of the movies
I just mentioned behind Edmund at number 9 18 is the edge the edge is a better
movie than Edmund 15 they've got red belt which was I mean red belt is fine
but like it's it is not anyway 14 things change have you ever seen things change
I've seen things change yeah 13 this is where I started like screaming at the
Winslow boy come on come on get out of here with the Winslow boy no nobody
wants the Winslow boy for the people at home who don't know what the Winslow boy
is it's all in the theater I describe it as the whitest movie ever made the plot
is literally old English people in 19 you know in the year 1878 or whatever
fucking year it is going your son was accused of stealing two shillings that's
like the plot of the movie what the fuck is this anyway state and Maine
masterpiece number 12 okay heist masterpiece in my opinion I know you
don't like it number 11 Spartan which is a great movie at 10 that is not better
than heist or state and Maine number nine go good I mean this is what they
want Joe they want I don't want you going nuts that's the point of these
lists we just feed right into it number nine Spanish prisoner yeah great movie
eight wag the dog great movie Pat you ready for this yeah number seven
Vanya on 42nd Street starting while the Sean I've heard enough I've heard enough
number six Ronan which he only co -wrote Ronan's good Ronan's good though they
got the verdict at five which I guess is good I find it boring house of games it
is amazing I got a real Paul Newman slaps that woman across the face I never got
through all of the verdict I just find it a little too dry damn I'll go back to
it and and you didn't finish it one of the most memorable final shots in the
history of film interesting I don't I never saw the end I know that's what I'm
saying okay number four house of games fair enough number three homicide that
should not be above how that shouldn't even be in the top ten but it is good
movie though two and one they did this to fuck with you man they did this to
fuck with me they did ready for this I'm assuming Glenn Gary's too yes yeah how
is it not one foolish one is the Untouchables the Untouchables is awesome
I will you get about that yeah but come on it's not above Glenn get Glenn Gary
is the man's he won a Pulitzer Prize for it for Christ's sake it's a masterpiece
yeah anyway um yeah this this site would just make me mad every day I'm gonna I'm
gonna skip it I do need a new ain't it cool or something because ain't it cool
has one update every six months by like a convicted rapist so I tend to not go
over there too much but a screen rant is good okay okay screen rant is good I
like screen rant sometimes they get a little too woki on the sleeve yeah but
but but but they're good I like screen right um I got a little scream in it
maybe that's not what it is not it's um what's the other one that we do that I
never have understood scary stuff scary stuff yeah I ordered a place to pretty
nice size order from indicator who do great boutique blu -ray releases of
mostly older classic movies and some box sets like for example Joe I'm showing
you now this handsome Columbia noir set Humphrey Bogart classics I love what
they do mm -hmm and I have purchased from them before but only their region one
material they also have tons of really cool shit that is region two or region
B I never really understood this shit I never understood why these countries do
this why players only play certain DVD it makes no sense and maybe you have an
explanation Joe I don't know but I was told that my 4k player should play them
it does not I was told that the ps4 will play them and it does not do you
have advice for watching such a film well the ps well you can easily get a
region -free blu -ray you know you can get that on like yeah like the Best Buy
website today okay like 95 bucks so I would just do that if I were you the PS
5 will let you region switch but the only let you do it so many times well I
can do it on ps4 I never watch a movie in there so I'll just set it up for that
I think it will let you there are also certain regions that the ps4 will play
that aren't region one I don't remember how that works but 4k is regionless
which is a good thing so anything 4k which should play in any 4k player so
maybe they're finally stopping with this but as like an extra twist of the knife
this indicators logo or whatever is this kind of beautiful rainbow or like the
the RGB of color spectrum so I get this beautiful screen up on my television
multicolor and it's like hello we just wanted to say that we apologize for any
inconvenience but you will not be able to watch this film and I'm like how does
this screen come up but nothing else I don't what who is it protecting and what
is it for region thing yeah that I don't I assume it's just because of like you
know like codes like you know they have these these codes like the like the
rating codes and all that stuff and things get released in different areas
under different titles and on different formats and they're available I don't
know you know it's like it's like Netflix it's like why the fuck is next
you know people will use those the whatever those things are called like
those proxy servers that protect your identity people use those more for
streaming in other countries than anything meaning like you can just log
in and say you're in Japan and then you can access Netflix Japan okay it's a
completely different library I don't know why I don't do that I should but
um you know but the same thing it's like why you go to Canada in Netflix is an
entirely different library and a better one right so I guess it's got to do with
what they're trying to make money off of where you know obviously that's part of
and I assume it's all gonna go away but what I would just think me me buying a
blu -ray or a blu -ray box I you know spending the same amount I would pay on
Amazon or anywhere else I just don't get why I can't watch my own shit but yeah
it's stupid just get a region free player but what is the what is the
company called again that puts this stuff out that you said they are called
Indicator and they're they're a British company they're great they do a bunch of
limited -edition they also go out of print so like it's it's not the end of the
world that I've got this stuff I can't watch if I can't because it'll sell it
always sells but um that's a beautiful box set that Bogart thing I would buy
that look at it be enamored by it and then never watch it oh yeah do the same
thing with this Mae West box and wait a minute hold on do you really 10 10
movies of a woman who's basically was the Miss Piggy of her day like her whole
character was like oh baby why don't you come up and suck on my tits for a while
yeah I had it's one of my favorite Seinfeld lines ever and I the episode
was on the other day well I was eating dinner and I was streaming Seinfeld
cleavage no the one where she gets the tickets from the dentist who what's the
dentist name that cramped in Wadley Wadley she gets the Super Bowl tickets
from Wadley yeah after Jerry gives him the Super Bowl tickets and he wants them
back yeah and she's she gets the tickets because she it goes up to his apartment
with him after their date yeah and uh Seinfeld goes of course you got the
tickets you ask him to go upstairs like you're Mae West perfect reference at
least layer I don't know about Jerry but Larry must be obsessed with old movies
when you watch the old Seinfeld he's big and I like the old war dialogue and so
especially in the early days yeah that's another oh god sorry no it's just it's a
fun addition to the show when they when he's got them talking like old you know
hard -boiled New York cops or whatever it's always very funny to me he does it
a lot with Newman there's the great thing when they kidnap the dog and the
cops show up at Newman's apartment he opens the door he goes what took you so
long yeah yeah all this an excellent yeah I have a good I have a good scary
stuff that I'm excited about excuse me when I was a kid when Raiders of the
Lost Ark came out I was a big action figure kid I was I was really into the
Star Wars figurines and he man was huge for me and when Raiders of the Lost Ark
came out where they put out a line of Indiana Jones action figures and it was
very unique and and indifferent because it wasn't this big franchise yet but
there were these cool action figures from this movie we all loved and there
was just something a little more elite about the Indiana Jones action figures
you didn't see them everywhere nobody really had them if you had a friend that
did have them it was like this treat and I was always really kind of obsessed
with them but never was smart enough to ask for them for Christmas or whatever
so I never got my hands on them anyway cut to now in as we as we lead up to
this new movie they have re -released them they re -released the five core
figures it's Indy Marion with a little monkey she comes with the little monkey
and she's in the white dress from when Belloc gives her the dress Belloc and
the robes at the end lock or look I forget the guy's name but the guy that
wears the black hat with the glasses that guy uh -huh and then the German
mechanic that Indy fights fistfights in the plane they re -released all five they
put them in identical packaging to the original which is awesome to the original
packaging which is awesome because what they do sometimes with this is like they
re -released replicas of like the return of the Jedi action figures and they put
the Kenner logo on it even though Kenner doesn't exist anymore and like the
Mattel logo is on the back it's very cool but then they fucking put this big
thing on the front that says retro and you're like yeah ruins it that's like
don't put that on there with these they didn't do that it's just the exact
packaging replicated I got all five figures they're $11 .99 a piece on Amazon
and it's a cool I don't know what I'm gonna do with them well he gonna have
them fight is what you're gonna do I'll probably play with them just you are at
an age Joe where if you're gonna involve Marion and especially if you're gonna
involve Marion and that monkey I need to know things aren't getting sexual in
these play times they won't I need to know that Marion is is either cheering
on Indy or having fights of her own I don't want her fucking people here all
right anyway go get these things I think you can only get them at like on Amazon
and like Target I don't know like you'd think something like this would add a
release or a bigger announcement it's a it's a really cool re -release of
something but anyway check them out if you're if you're into such a thing we'll
do that is something that I would actually enjoy I I am the Funko people
went under didn't they I don't think so did I have a couple of those I it's it's
it's odd to me they're considered so uncool and then I think they pulled the
manufacturing of them I felt ashamed even having them because people make fun
of the people who own them so much the Funko figures yeah I thought they were
still hugely I don't know I don't I mean maybe I missed it something happened I
guess I think they stopped manufacturing them let me look this up because they
have a huge store here I've never seen like a physical place Funko oh that's
interesting they actually have a store in LA I've never seen that it's what I
just said no no no I'm saying it back to you okay relax oh so there's been a
bunch of firings and they dumped 30 million worth of inventory so they're
clearly just hurting what does that mean they dumped 30 million of in what does
that mean keeping excess Funko pop collectibles in an Arizona warehouse is
coming too costly so they trashed 30 million worth of them they trashed it
instead of saying to people guys come on down to the Funko pop warehouse we're
gonna have the sale of a lifetime I can't even wrap my head around why you
would do something that stupid or sell them for a dollar a piece and then you
make 30 million dollars or here's an idea and a great PR move send them to
charities and tell the charities to auction them off for charity money
yeah instead you're literally putting a bunch of plastic directly into a
landfill maybe you send them out to orphanages for children don't have toys
boy that'd be a great idea very nice this is when Walsh I want to dress up
like a Santa Claus yeah that eventually goes on a killing spree because he's
trying to do the right thing but he's so sick with humanity yeah it's time it's
time you got to do your fat man which I still haven't seen I want to see fat man
come who's in fat man there's another one of those Gibson baby things Mel
Gibson that's two or three years old but I see it on peacock all the time all
right folks let's get to that corner I got some big titles today number one
Bo is afraid oh you saw it I did and I love or I don't love this I have a habit
of titles sometimes get in my head as parts from songs if that makes sense I
know what was I telling you we did on this one what was the other one that I
had what's a what's a recent movie we did I was telling you that I have these
little mental things that I can't shake but you were this one yeah I I remember
you saying it I remember you singing it but I don't remember what the hell it
was but I always think of the single by puddle of mud when I see Bo is afraid
would it a Bo is afraid remember that song I'm always afraid no can't stop so
every time I see Bo is afraid I sing it like that irrelevant but the movie
itself is pretty incredibly great for an hour it was knock at the cabin you were
doing something oh yeah knock knock at the cabin to the tune of shout out the
devil yeah it's and it's not something I'm like what boy what song would fit
this it just happens and then I can't shake it whenever I hear the movie I
think that the movie to that title it's a little bit of my OCD I think but Bo was
afraid I saw it in IMAX which just the fact that that this is a movie about
rippling nightmarish anxiety that destroys your soul from within IMAX in
IMAX yeah so I was very excited there is a certainly one of our most heated
episodes both of them come with two of Ari Oster's films midsummer and
hereditary I was pretty passionately pro on both Joe was less so Joe really did
not like midsummer and we fought about it but Bo was afraid is the new one and
I was like okay so this is new one it's not horror the cast is very interesting
Nathan Lane in Patti LuPone you know Richard kind all these just interesting
characters character actors Nathan Lane in like a very straight dad dude role
which is really funny he's got a little mustache or whatever but um here's the
movie for one hour this thing is like a it's a mix of Charlie Kaufman and Looney
Tunes it is huge crazy comedic set pieces insane things happening new
graphic nudity graphic violence horrifying images and it's all to paint
a picture of what it is like for Joaquin Phoenix every time he leaves his
apartment like anything you're seeing like you're seeing like things in his
head that he's afraid will happen or something well I mean there's nothing
that says that this is like fake it seems like this is what his life is but
it's probably what it seems like life is like to him so in the beginning like
he's trying to get across the street to get something and everyone on the street
is basically a zombie movie basically there's there's rapes going on there's
people beating the shit out of each other there's just horrific things and as he
walks through props open the door to his apartment with a phone book because he
doesn't have his key he lost his key and he goes across the street to go do his
business and as he looks over his shoulder all these zombie people are
just filing into his the open door and going up into his apartment then these
people live in his apartment like going crazy taking shits on the floor fucking
each other orgies and everything it's it's I can't explain it really but I've
never seen anything like it it was extremely funny it was extremely weird
and it felt exactly like what crippling anxiety feels like obviously this
Ari Aster has some major mental issues if you saw his early short film about
the guy like blowing his dad at at a party that's yeah that's how he kind of
on everyone's radar you think about the John's but I'm who rapes his father yeah
exactly yeah so the guys got issues and the movie is all about mommy issues
usually if you're seeing a movie about parent issues that's daddy issues this
is all mommy the mom as played by a young woman is played by Zoe Lester
Jones and played as an older woman by Patti LuPone the great Broadway actress
so that first hour is more than enough for me to strongly recommend Bo is Afraid
I thought it was brilliant and I don't use that word I hate that word I think
people use it to describe anything that's okay especially British people
enough enough the second hour of the movie and it's three hours folks second
hour Bo Joaquin Phoenix is on his journey he leaves New York and goes out
through the wilderness so for a long portion of the movie he is staying at
the home of Amy Ryan and Nathan Lane who hit Joaquin Phoenix with their car
while he is completely naked and bring him home misery style and lock him up in
their bed then you're waiting for that to get dark you're waiting for that to
like into a torture situation it does very much get dark and weird there's a
16 year old daughter who's like walking around in a bra a lot and she's taking
pills every time you see her she's shoveling a handful of pills into her
mouth everything in the movie is designed to just put you on edge and
that's what it does second hour is also kind of successful it kind of works then
he's in the woods and then we get what we have in the in the trailer which is
him walking through like a world of like paper mache and then like the thing gets
really surreal and that's really cool it's a big like surreal almost like
animated midsection of the movie and you're like okay I get that it's a big
journey of the man's soul or whatever I got it then in the home stretch things
get pretty bad things get really boring Ari Aster failed yet again to land the
movie after a series of horrifying images that's weird well I mean this the
sad truth is I don't think this guy had a point he was even shooting for unless
he was just saying like I want to show you the life journey of a man who is
miserable you know and that works for longer than you would expect in a three
hour movie in the home stretch so many things happen in this movie I almost
can't believe it but in the home stretch he's reunited with an old flame who he
had a crush on when he was a kid she is played by Parker Posey I love Parker Posey
have always loved Parker Posey yeah she has a 20 -minute graphic and very very
hot sex scene with looking Phoenix who looks terrible you know he's in like I
there's also not a subplot but it is a subplot basically we learn that Joaquin
Phoenix father died the first time he ever came and it was into his mother he
came giving birth to Bo and then died so Bo has the same testicular disorder as
father which you hear kind of rumored about that the cum was built up so much
that it like killed his dad so you've got Parker Posey who is in my knowledge
never been nude in a film and I used to look I used to be very into Parker Posey
when I was like 16 and scouring mr. skin for her she's now 50 something years old
not that that's it's an odd time to decide to get naked for the first time
as an actress but she's real naked she looks spectacular it's like her tome moment
you know I was just like whoa she's fucking him and she's sitting she's got
this sorry sorry dump truck ass amazing but it's sitting on Joaquin Phoenix giant
basketball sized testicles and you're watching this sexy I'm hard you know
this scene is like sexy and they pan back and show you these giant nuts and
it worked on me I was like this movie is fucking insane all right when I what I
am about to say now I can't even explain and I saw the movie would you believe
that the movie practically ends with a 20 -foot combination dick and balls slash
Godzilla kept in a clock kept in an attic like screaming trying to kill
people a dick with a face and teeth I don't know what to say about this movie
was madness the ending is felt like defending your life which I did not
expect either it is Richard kind on one side as a lawyer passionately arguing
against the life of Bo and then another lawyer argument on his behalf there's a
20 -minute monologue from Patti LuPone where the movie really grinds to a halt
in my opinion I don't know what to tell you I have to recommend the movie it's
his least successful movie by a long shot it's not scary but I just love when
people take this kind of risk the fact that they put this this money up for
this movie is like something that would have happened in the 70s it can only
happen when you make two five million dollar movies that make a hundred each
and I admire when somebody gives you a chance that you do something fucking
nuts and swing for the rafters so I admire it but I think most people will
hate this movie I think it'll have a cinema score of a d -minus problem it's
being touted as very polarizing oh yeah it's it's madness you know the reviews
are are you know a lot it's it's a lot of like you know Joaquin Phoenix can't
can kind of save this thing but you know I don't know it's got a 76 percent on
Rotten Tomatoes a 71 audience score that will change as it goes out of New York
anyway I with major reservations kind of I loved it just talking about it now I
was like how did he even cram this shit all in there you know but I'm gonna do
interesting move I'm gonna do just one because we're yes we're hard into the
into the show at this point but but I will I will match your it was gonna do
80 for Brady but I can't do it I didn't watch the whole thing I just turned it
on thinking it'll be a light -hearted romp any laughs I knew something was
wrong with Joe when he was watching that the other day any laughs no okay not one
it's it's basically a made -for -Hallmark movie that somehow got into the theater
and it stars for well I would say artists true artists Tomlin Fonda yeah
and marino like there these are Bob Balaban's in it like these are art like
these are people I consider artists of cinema and it's just it's just fucking
terrible but you know I guess you get to an age and you go fuck it they're gonna
put a bunch of us in our 80s and 70s in this movie like let's just go have a
good time and get paid yeah if it's not Shakespeare I meant I meant to to share
this very brief anecdote but I was pitching this company not pitching but
having what we call a general meeting which is usually a huge waste of time
it's an hour where you talk to somebody who works at a studio or company or
network you shoot the breeze and if you hit it off as people you got a good
contact in the industry or maybe they have a project you're right for and one
of the big questions I always ask is like so what is your company's MO like
what kind of stuff do you want to do when they always have like a you know a
mission statement and this woman is like you know we are just committed every
step of the way to making the kind of quality entertainment that you can't
find anywhere else you know we're we're here to make challenging works we're
here to make art which is also commerce you know we're here to just make
beautiful and I go okay great well like do you guys have anything coming down
the pipeline and she's like our first movie he's called 80 for Brady and I
just had to bite through my tongue a two -minute mission statement about how
we're trying to make that we're trying to hit that sweet spot where art meets
commerce they've made one movie 80 for Brady a big question is how was Keegan
Michael Key in it I assume he had a dual role I didn't get that far I don't even
know if he's in it I just assume if it's a comedy made in 2023 he's got a
part or two Guy Fieri's in it I'm assuming as Guy Fieri I assume that was
what he's playing Raj guy who's dating Lily Tomlin the plot you know what I'll
just do 80 for Brady fuck it do it's just such a we want such a contradiction
to it's it's a movie about four 80 year old women who watch who are obsessed with
Tom Brady and his team because they started watching the the games when
Lily Tomlin's character had cancer and her friends were helping her get through
and they become obsessed they they have like rituals around the games to bring
the team luck and everything and then they're like this is it we want to they
go we got to go to the Super Bowl we have to go they win tickets through a
giveaway on like a sports podcast to get four tickets to go to the Super Bowl and
that's as far as I got I couldn't I just couldn't do it it's just it's just a
terrible terrible terrible movie it's just and I'm a sucker for shit like that
I love old people doing things yeah you know I love old people dating I love you
know like I love stories about older people I just really do it's one of the
reasons I'm so obsessed with the Golden Girls I love stories about old people
that don't focus on that they're old it's you know that's that can be a
opponent but that's not the whole point it's like no they these people have
lives and you know even something as as as stupid and dismissive as there's a
scene where Lily Tomlin Rita Moreno spills her tea and like there's like a
thing in their in their superstitious like ritual they do with the game where
like Rita Moreno's character has like drink tea at an exact time yeah because
like that's what they were all doing when they won the game to go to the
Super Bowl I think it's the Bills right I don't know football at all I thought
Tom Brady was the Patriots but I know less oh no that's right it's the
Patriots excuse me but yeah because they really lean into I know more than you
into the anyway and then what they all want to fuck Tom Brady is that part of
the play definitely I do like that they don't hold back from all of the being
like oh he is gorgeous like I like that they all do kind of what a fuck him
anyway Rita Moreno spills her tea and they need the tea for the for the
superstitious setup or whatever and Lily Tomlin runs literally runs from the
living room to the kitchen to get tea and I was like even just something
stupid like that I like that they've got Lily Tomlin running and they're not
being like you're 80 you need to take it be careful you know and all that shit
so yeah Fonda it's got a I mean they're all they're all fine in it like they all
play the version that you want them to be you know like Lily is like the sort
of bossy one Sally should you play lesbians in her things or no they don't
I think she's a widow in this from a man I think Fonda is like the saucy one
it's like still out there dating and stuff you know Sally Field is a little
more of the like you know like you expect Sally you know that she her husband
she's married to Bob Balaban and she's sort of the proper you know she's the
Charlotte if you will of this group I will I will Moreno is her character is
is a widow and I would say she gets the funniest stuff to do out of everybody
but that's not saying much but you know look at the end of the day it's a movie
that was released in 2023 that went into theaters that stars people in their
70s and 80s yeah I want to support that I don't want to tear it down as bad as
book club the second chapter looks I'm glad that there's still somebody making
this these things you know and letting people work Christ Almighty it's 28
million dollar budget too this is a paramount pictures movie Sally Kirkland
is also in it well as I think I told you paramount told a friend of mine that
their target audience is Diane Keaton going forward they they're like said
that there yeah my friends brought in a very funny comedy about two thirty five
forty year old women and they were like sorry guys but this is too young for a
graphic and I was like what yeah we're targeting Diane Keaton so I don't know
why paramount decided they'll be the old network but somebody needed to pick a
lane you know these I think a lot of these places are gonna go under with
this strike because they got to pay us residuals and I don't think a lot of
these places can afford it by the way Tom Brady is gonna be a wild year Tom
Brady is in the movie oh thank God but I will say this it is one of those weird
things like like you know Stuber was one of these things you know the wizard with
Fred Savage is one of these things it is one of these things where it's like
we're taking just a pop culture thing that's happening Tom Brady right and
we're just gonna build a movie around it yeah sometimes it's Nintendo sometimes
it's uber sometimes it's a person but it is definitely one of those things where
it's like it's kind of a weird approach yeah but but anyway 80 for Brady hearts
hearts in the right place but you know I wish it was better anyway Pat do you
want to I'm gonna get a coffee do you want to set us up with scream 6 or do
you have other things you want to discuss before we go to it um we can go
to it we can go to it I'll be I'll be doing my movie corner so I'll be getting
into all this solo here in a few days scream 6 as Joe said we got you know my
history with the franchise is very different from Joe's I Joe did not see
scream 2 3 or 4 he's a fan of one and the recent reboot I think scream 1 is
excellent a true horror classic I think scream 2 is a lot of fun also Parker
Posey I should add and really this new scream reminded me the most of that
scream 2 scream 3 period where it's like bringing in outside villains it starts
to feel a little Scooby -Doo ish where you're just like yanking masks off
people again and again but I do think that the rebooted scream series is
working the franchise is good and it seems to be in good hands these are
really solid well -made slasher movies with people for the most part you care
about I think Jenna Ortega is a major star I don't know what it you know it's
that it's that star quality thing it's just one person a year has it and they
become a huge star you know you can't keep your eyes off her she's compelling
and I think her older sister played by Melissa Fomero is just as great I used
to love her on this stars show called Vita that I just stumbled upon and
watched two seasons of I really loved it I came for the nudity literally but I
stayed for a really great show about a pair of Latina sisters or Latinx anyway
they I think make these new screams work the sisters the bond between them
you you believe them as sisters you like the characters a lot and to me that
helped make up for the loss of really the heart of the franchise David Arquette
was killed in the last scream but he was the emotional highlight of that movie he
gave a great performance you really cared when David Arquette died in that
I agree they don't bring him back obviously because he's dead but they also
don't bring back Neve Campbell because apparently they did not they did not
offer her enough money Courtney Cox is back but kind of pointless you know it
she's her story she might as well have just been another you know random setup
murder so let's like it's yeah go ahead let's start with Cox this was my first
problem with the movie first of all it wasn't anywhere near to me it was not
anywhere near as interesting or cool being set in New York City I didn't
think they got any real extra mileage out of moving the location to New York
City outside of just well because they filmed it in like Cleveland I mean that
nothing has ever looked less like New York City in this movie and when they
zoom up to the New York skyline in the final shot of this thing I'm like guys
put up a matte painting or something or go get a picture of New York this looks
like literally Kansas City Missouri like there's no New York flavor to this movie
at all but go on so yeah so the the idea here was we're gonna get them all in a
new location and it's gonna be New York and that's gonna change the dynamic of
what's happening it doesn't in any way there are there's a plot point of there
in theory ghostface killers and you could do that anywhere outside of one
sequence on a subway which again you could have just done on a fucking bus
or something in another city or another town or in a supermarket whatever it's
like I don't know it's just it's like you've gotten nothing was gained by
changing the setting from the suburbs to New York and it wasn't as cool and it
is scary in fact it made it less scary because I feel like when you're
surrounded by people I don't think a guy in a goddamn ghost mask is gonna stab
me to death like I just think it's gonna be a lot harder to pull off so that's
that's the first thing there but Courtney like you said with the joke
titles like ghost face takes Manhattan or something doesn't have to be that
corny but like that's what we want you know that that was my main issue with
this movie is like Jason takes Manhattan is a piece of shit but at least you see
Jason in New York City killing people this this just yeah that even the subway
I was like have you guys been on a New York subway I don't know the whole movie
was very inauthentic it's not hard to go to New York and get get the feel for it
there's also that terror I mean it's just okay I don't want to be all over the
place but but the group I want to get back to Courtney Cox but the group the
go into the subway I hated this movie I thought it was so lazily written and
executed that when they went into the subway it's directly after a scene where
they say be safe travel together what guys you live in New York in the age of
uber you're not gonna get into an uber together and potentially deal with one
the driver if somehow the fucking killer got your uber and signed up and is now
an uber driver you're gonna go into the crowded subway on Halloween packed to
the gills where everybody's a suspect and everybody as you've established in
your movie through news footage everybody is dressed up as ghostface
this Halloween this is the it's just lazy stupid writing they get immediately
broken apart as a group in the subway because it's so crowded that doesn't
happen no there's a scene where the one girl gets split off from the group
because her brother can't hold the doors open to the subway that I was like I'm
done that is literally the biggest gripe I have with the subway is any schmuck
can just hold the door open and they do it all the time mainly children who are
waiting for their friends to catch up it's so so there's a lot of that in this
movie in the big Courtney Cox sequence when she's on in her Upper West Side
apartment and ghost faces in the apartment talking to her from the
apartment guys I don't care how big your two -bedroom apartment is in New York
City you're gonna hear somebody talking in the other room she can't hear this
guy talking in the I mean just a lot of really lazy lazy writing lazy there's
also that moment and it's the first time in the scream franchise where somebody
has had this idea to call ghostface back so she goes I'm gonna call you right
back she hangs up dials and then the audience all gasped and like applauded
when his phone rings in the closet but I'm like ghostface doesn't leave his
phone on silent when he's hiding out in a woman's closet yeah it's just stupid so
Courtney Cox she was the one glimmer of hope that this was not in my opinion a
cash grabs franchise sequel that it wasn't an unnecessary sequel the fact
that she went back when Nev said fuck off said something to me Courtney Cox
in my opinion I'm not counting anybody's money I would assume Courtney
needs the money a lot less than Nev might she's a Friends alumni I would also
has minimum minimum 500 million dollars yeah I would also think that Courtney
probably has a higher price tag than Nev Campbell because of her you know she's
she was in Friends she's been on she's been she's more she's more much more of
public figure than Neve Campbell is yeah and Neve Campbell also often does
like a lot of indie you know interesting stuff and so my point is is
like for Courtney Cox to come back to this thing without Neve Campbell and say
well I'll do it I was like they must there must be a reason for that this
thing must really you know there's got to be some heart in this thing and and
there's got to be some true connective tissue to the to the other movies and
what do they do after Courtney Cox is the goddamn hero of the last movie they
bring her in and they hit a fucking reset button on the character and make
her a money -grubbing exploitative reporter right off the bat that the two
main girls hate because she went wrote a book exploiting what happened to them
and caused them all these all these problems and if that's not bad enough and
enough to the character they then dismiss all of that in two seconds by
like the girls trading like quips where they call each other bitch and then
they're like okay I'm over it help us and it's just terrible man this fucking
thing sucked I hated it I hated it and I just hated it I thought the movie was I
thought it was unnecessary I thought it was fucking pointless I thought if you
didn't remember every detail of every screen movie that preceded this fucking
thing this movie made no sense and the way they fixed that was through stupid
exposition expositional dialogue explaining everything this can't work
on its own it's it's just it just sucked it just fucking sucked I don't feel as
I don't think it was good but I don't I also don't think that it sucked what's
weird is that the go -to screenwriter for this franchise now is well it's Guy
Busick who wrote ready or not which I enjoyed and James Vanderbilt who wrote
fucking zodiac he wrote zodiac and now he's doing the scream franchise and the
zodiac one of my favorite movies of all time so who knows what happened there
but I think this movie in the way of a scream 2 or a scream 3 keeps things afloat
for the franchise this is a stronger franchise to me than the Halloween
reboot franchise would you agree with that or yeah I don't know I would
absolutely agree with that yes this is look I you know where I stand on those
Halloween reboots I thought they were I thought the first one was at best
marginally passable but a bad movie and then the other two are abominations yeah
this was pointless yeah but at least at least it didn't have terrible acting at
least it didn't have stereotype characters yeah well it kind of did you
know like but but I love I love the sisters I think that the sisters were
good those two are great I like them as characters and I think bringing in
sisters is a great idea you know just it just adds something new to the
franchise their friends the black are they brother and sister I think so yes
very conveniently yeah you know they're likable enough but it's it's strange
because everyone had such strong funny personalities like in the original
scream and they keep talking about the core four in this one they say it a
hundred times and the whole core four survives again right they do and and it's
like who gives a shit I don't care about this girl's girlfriend we've known for
five minutes getting murdered like that's not a heart that's supposed to be
like a heartbreaking scene it's like I don't fucking know this character I don't
have no investment in this and it's given them the Marvel thing this girl
is is stabbed in the stomach on a on a subway and the next time we see her
she's skipping down the road you know it's like what's going on here at least
the guy who got stabbed hundreds of times he's completely fine at the end
too at least he looks bad but they stab him over and over again so it's getting
that Marvel feeling of nobody can die and people can come back and that's
usually when a franchise is at the end of the rope this one it brings in an
outside villain it's not a villain from the franchise even though there's a loose
connection but I guess we don't need to talk about who that is but this talk
about who that is it's stupid it's Dermot Mulroney who just happens to be
the chief of police at the precinct where these girls just happened to move
to yeah far far away to start a new it's just stupid and then it turns out
he's the dad of the kid from the last movie that yeah it's just lazy have him
just come in as the dad of that kid and be like my son was a horrible person I
want to help you have him be the person there parentally in a way helping these
girls who again they go out of their way to talk about how they're parentless and
they've got nobody have this guy come in as the parent the the the the the
unexpected parental figure because I'm actually the father of the kid that
tried to kill you and let me let me make up for that let me give him let me pay
penance for him by assisting you and instead it's like no we'll just make him
coincidentally the chief of police who also coincidentally works with the FBI
agent of a character I don't even know what fucking scream that lady was in
you're supposed to be like when the when she turns around in the chair you're
supposed to be like oh shit I'm like Hayden Hayden Pantaner I don't remember
who this is Joe I when they did that like heroes reveal of Hayden I really
reacted strongly to that because I was like I guess she's in part four which I
saw but don't remember anything about but yeah she's she plays a big role and
there's a moment where we're supposed to be like did Hayden Pantaneri turn
against them but you're you don't know who she is so you don't care by the way
which would have been interesting yeah yeah and and I was actually like oh okay
fuck man that's cool like one of the legacy characters is he's the bad guy I
like that right it's like you know in scream to the killer if memory serves is
Loomis's mother Skeet O 'Rourke's mother played by Laurie Metcalf unhinged funny
and this is kind of going for that too trying to bring in an unexpected parent
but that one works because she was the mother of the killer in the previous
film it's and it's also a movie that pays homage to other horror movies that's
Friday the 13th the mom did it this one you can't just bring in somebody you
know and especially if that person is Dermot Mulroney I like him occasionally
in things he you know he's the guy for my best friend's wedding and about
Schmidt and stuff but he's doing like big hammy I'm the villain stuff here
which is fine with Laurie Metcalf Dermot Mulroney doesn't pull it off at all and
they're having him shoot for the stars and go big and him and his kids are all
going really big and it's it's kind of dumb that part is kind of dumb I'll
grant you the writing is not as strong as in the previous outing the amount of
times we go to the inside baseball well about horror this is just like in you
know that's always been a fun aspect of scream they overdo it here too much for
sure they do it that that girl self -referential stuff the stabbed in the
yes you know she is such a wholly unlikable character throughout this
entire thing like she's the now granted she saves her friend from potentially
getting date raped in the beginning yeah like weird opening to this thing that
whole date rape opening because that's not an energy that's really been in
scream before it was it was interesting I thought it is a weird opening and it's
just it's just like we're we're putting a bad guy into this that doesn't need
that doesn't serve any fucking purpose other than this or the other bad guy by
the way they could be the Indian guy at the beginning yeah who is set up and
then gone well then there's also it's weird and then there's also this thing
of like Jenny Ortega's character can't take care of herself yeah and she's
trying to prove that she can take care of herself and I don't know I don't it's
confusing but but but the point is is that character the one that plays the
Jamie Kennedy thing she's so fucking unlikable and like she's monologuing
about the history of horror movies as everyone around her is dying and it's
like part of that's the fun but she won't stop she talks only in monologues
and also Jamie Kent when they did it with Jamie Kennedy he wasn't reveling in
no I don't trust any of you you could all be killers I'm gonna be an asshole
about it he was like we all need to be like he was it was cautious it was yeah
this is the only franchise by the way that could ever make me want to see Jamie
Kennedy resurface but but but you know I just it's just not it just wasn't good
to me I just I just I was like there's a way to do this character the her
character has this real like yeah deal with it I'm a bitch and it's like okay
it's not likable and the sister characters have so much heart right
eventually I feel like these sisters would tell this girl like would you
chill the fuck out yeah you're being really fucking crazy right now and then
I guess in the end she's justified because the one friend the kid that she
hates through the whole movie you're like what the fuck she's so mean to this
kid and like if I was this kid I'd be like fuck you lady but then eventually
he's one of the he's in on the killing or whatever so I'm like okay it was
justified but I just didn't think it was very well executed I didn't give a shit
I didn't like watching anybody figure anything out I did care about the
sisters that's more I can say about any character from the new Halloween movies
I loved scream 5 I thought this was pointless and tarnished screen 5 but I
don't think it was anywhere near as bad as Halloween 2 & 3 in this last run but
my hog is down but this Cox die I don't remember my hogs also down yeah Cox
dies and that that was an issue to me too you're gonna bring in our cat give
him like almost a Western style heroes ending he does die but in a great
exciting way Cox is here to just get stabbed in an apartment and be a bitch
you know like it is really weird that I mean look they probably offer a million
dollars and she said sure and I get it but why don't why not write something
for her she's been in ten of these things help her out a little bit well
six of these things six yes my I would let me just interject really quick I
think yes I think a perfect analogy for this is scream 5 to me felt like
Halloween h2o where I was like they're doing some crazy reboot it's not gonna
work and then it worked and I was like wow guys kudos my hats off scream 6
felt like Halloween resurrection you bring back Curtis you kill her in the
opening five minutes yeah and then the rest of the movie you know I don't
really give a shit and whatever yeah and it and it took the ass out of everything
h2o did so that this was that's exactly how I feel about these two movies yeah I
my hog is barely down barely down I because I was entertained by it but
nothing Joe said is wrong it's it's sloppily written and stuff there's just
an energy to them and kind of a fun to them where I hang in there and I'm not
really bored and I do think that the franchise is stronger than most this far
along you know the fact that they're still making watchable movies at this
point is kind of commendable I like the franchise I'd see another one if they're
gonna start branching it off into like you know side quests and origin stories
and stuff that I'm not doing but we'll see I don't under I'm out on this
franchise I think I don't understand what's going on anymore like I'm like
it's so up its own ass at this point it's like there's the movies themselves
then there's the movies within the movies then they're referencing the
movies within the movies but then they're also kind of referencing the
movies you're watching and I'm just like I don't know what the fuck is even going
on anymore I'm lost yeah beyond any museum honoring the franchise in the
with like costumes from the original scream in it it's strange and it's
beyond it's beyond horror movie rules at this point there'd be like they've done
everything you can do with a franchise with like exploiting the rules of how
it would work I'm just like I don't know what is even left so anyway I agree my
get my guess is the next one will be an origin story of some sort and then
this is exactly what happens with the origin story you know probably I am on
only an Instagram at the Patrick Walsh the Miss Pat show airs on BET plus and
that's all I got Joseph I'm on the road folks please come see me you can get all
tickets and show information at Joe de Rosa calm I got it I got my fucking
domain name finally after all these years there you go Joe de Rosa calm you
can go there and see all my dates and info but I will I'm in Cleveland tomorrow
night I'm in Columbus Ohio the following two nights weekend after I'll be in
Baltimore Maryland weekend after that I'll be in Pittsburgh May 3rd which
falls in between some of these dates I will be in New York at the Crane Theatre
and then September I got shows in Jersey that just posted so come on out and see
me doing the new hour I never promised you a rose garden and I don't always I
don't often plug the other podcast on here but we are doing our first ever
live stream of taste buds on May 10th you're a fan moment comm is hosting it
you can check us out on there and we're and there's gonna be actually a live
show component to that for the first time ever where we're gonna be in New
York City where you if you know limited tickets but if you can come out please
come out and if you can stream it please stream it it's gonna be a lot of fun a
lot of big stuff going on fact Pat we should do something like that with this
show but we'll talk about that off -air that's it folks we'll see you next time
and we'll see you and how we'll be back with the new Evil Dead