🎵 I'll see you in hell. I'll see you in hell. And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say. I'll see you in hell. You know I will. I'll see you in hell. You know I will. 🎵
I'm Patrick Walsh, and today, I know we usually focus on the big budget blockbusters, but today we're taking a look at some indie cinema.
Indiana Jones, folks. We're going to be discussing the entire, how would you even say this? I know there was the alien quadrilogy when there was four of those movies released on Blu -ray. So is this a quintology?
I think that's a good word for it. I'd like to point out before we start what a good friend I am. We had a false start. I had to do this intro twice, and I laughed twice at the indie cinema joke. That deserves something.
I appreciate that. And I saw the laugh. It seemed less genuine the second time around, but I accepted.
It was. The first time was genuine. The second time was when you've already seen the movie, and you know a funny part is coming up, and you're watching it with your mom, and you laugh because you're trying to indicate.
Pat, we're both here at crack of dawn, but we're up early. You're up earlier than I am, but it's early morning for both of us, more or less. It's a Saturday, July 1st.
Saturday, 730 a .m. I woke up out of a deep sleep. I jolted up like Kevin's mom in Home Alone, and I was like, it's July 1st. The Hellions need entertainment. And I went running up to my computer and flipped it open.
Pat ran to his window where a small orphan boy was walking by, and he said, tell me I haven't missed it.
And the boy said, what are you talking about?
Where are my parents? Yeah, exactly.
Mom, come quick. You hear about this woman, I mean, speaking of creepy pedophile shit, and lately it's not more women, of course, it's always going to be men, but I see women in the news with this shit.
Oh, yeah. It's all coming out in the wash now. Everybody.
I know.
It's just spreading. My friend Heather said last night on a voicemail, the pestilence is upon us. It's no wonder you're gloomy, and I was like, yeah, you're right. Jesus.
Everyone I know seems like a frayed wire that's like sparking, like just ready to get, you know, somebody spills a cup of gas on it or something.
But I was reading about this woman. There's a kid playing in his yard like a five -year -old boy.
This woman pulls up in her car, says she's child protective services, starts talking to the kid.
Then when the parents look out the window to check on their kid, she's like stroking the kid, like petting him and trying to get him into the car.
Then finally they hear their kid go, I need to go talk to my parents.
And she's like, no, you don't. No, you don't. That's the problem.
Your parents, they come out. She's got whiskey breath pretending to be child protective services to get a toddler into her car playing in his yard.
Nightmare. Nightmare. They said she had like, you know, alcohol.
She was like, tells the police as by means of explanation, I'm sorry, I'm really drunk.
OK, cool. Wow. Anyway. Yeah.
The balls. I mean, it's we've we've unfortunately traded so much.
And then we'll get to the movies. We're just going to do all five indie movies today.
You know what? Well, let's just keep it light.
You got a funny story.
Yesterday, you had left me a six minute voice memo and then a text under it saying, you know, warning if you don't want to hear this story twice, don't listen to that memo.
So I was like, OK, he wants to tell it when we record.
I only know. I'll say this much, and I don't mean to spoil it, and I hope I don't.
But when I spoke to you on the phone last night, briefly, you said the story had to do with you being accused of being shoplifting was one of the elements of it.
And I jokingly said, but were you, Pat?
And you very seriously went, no, I wasn't, Joe.
I was like, oh, geez, was they like beat him around the store or something?
Like you sounded really upset.
No, I thought I told you earlier in the week I got accused of shoplifting at Amoeba.
I did tell you. Yes, you did tell me that. I thought you were saying again.
No, this is this is a different and worse story.
I was saying that this is even worse than that.
But at Amoeba, they forced me to take my records out of an Amoeba bag that I had brought from home and shove the Amoeba bag into my pocket.
Because they said you can't walk around Amoeba with an Amoeba bag.
OK, by the way, the exact, the exact kind of store that wants brownie points for selling tote bags so they help the trees.
The exact kind of I got so fucking mad at Trader Joe's during covid.
And it was long after they had said, guys, you can't get it from surfaces.
So stop wiping off your groceries and stuff.
It was long after that. Right.
I went into Trader Joe's with my own receptacle to to put my groceries in.
And they're like, sorry, got to leave it at the can't do that.
I'm like, you guys like created this.
This is your thing. Yeah.
Well, they've created this new system where you're allowed to steal.
They can't stop people for stealing, I thought.
But I was accosted by two men at Amoeba.
And then I went on to spend one hundred bucks there.
And I was like, why am I even giving them my money?
I don't know why you keep going back after all your Amoeba stories.
Well, that last one might have put me over until I had an even worse customer experience at Barnes and Noble.
And it also involves a tote bag, amongst other things.
But I'll tell you the tale.
I'm going to and it sort of factors in because I'm running, not running late for Indy, but I got about 15 minutes
and I'm about to order yesterday on the Barnes and Noble 50 percent off sale for Criterion.
You know, I collect Criterion.
I tell my buddy, hey, let's go up to Barnes and Noble.
I have an old fashioned store experience because Amazon now matches Barnes and Noble.
So when they go 50 percent off, Amazon matches it.
And I'm getting I have the movies in my cart and I go, no, I.
What's that? Oh, I was just going to say, can I tell you to you?
You text me the sale was happening yesterday.
I feel nothing about this sale anymore.
It's up there with the Scream Factory sales.
They're doing this thing every three months at this point.
Somebody is doing a Criterion sale.
It's ruined. They ripped the luster right off of this.
Well, I had also read that Barnes and Noble are like pretty much how they're staying in business is these Criterion sales.
So, you know, it makes up a huge amount of money for them because people aren't buying books anymore.
And granted, there's no one else in the store.
But also, I want to say we have a listener who works at the Americana Barnes and Noble Hellion.
Great guy. I'm not going to say his name.
Don't want to get him in any trouble. This was not that Barnes and Noble.
This was the one up in Burbank where I was seeing Indiana Jones.
Anywho, I go in and had the movies in my Amazon cart, but it was like I'd rather go in and have a store experience, support a brick and mortar store.
I walk in. I'm looking around. I go, hey, where's your Criterions?
Oh, we keep them behind the counter now.
The entire collection. Yeah, all of our DVDs and Blu -rays are behind the counter now.
A lot of street resale in the 4K Elephant Man.
Yeah, exactly. They spread it out on a blanket on the streets in New York.
Hey, who wants Petite Maman? The recent French film Petite Maman.
We got a 4K and a 2K restoration done by Janus Films.
A more esoteric picture, but nonetheless celebrated.
So I'm already like I'm just defeated by this news.
I see them like behind glass and I'm like, okay.
So I say to the woman, I got to be honest. I said, that's a little strange.
My whole reason for coming is that I really love looking at the boxes and reading the titles and stuff.
It's fun for me. She's like, yeah, sorry.
Okay. I said, so how do I find out which ones I want?
And I got a list on my phone.
She goes, well, I can just look them up for you in the system.
Okay. All right.
You know, I have like 10 here. She goes, oh, you know, I can't just look up 10 movies.
I have to do other things.
Unbo... What other things? These are the things you have to do.
She's like, we only have the one cashier.
There's several people walking around stocking books and stuff like that.
Just one person at the cash register.
I'm like, all right.
Well, do you want me to point out the ones I want to you behind the counter?
Sure. So we go back there.
I go, I got to tell you, I go, you can keep a very close eye on me.
This would be much easier if I just grab the ones I want, put them in my basket and hand it to you.
She's like, no, I'll need you to point them out.
So I'm like, all right, first title up.
The Time Bandits 4K or whatever.
She turns around, starts looking.
She's like, well, I don't think we have it.
I go, no, I see it. It's the blue one right there.
She goes, no, these are alphabetical, sir.
I go, they're alphabetical by like the T's are together, but they're not in strict alphabetical order.
I can see Time Bandits. It's there in the blue. It's thicker than the other movies. It's 4K.
I'm pointing at it.
She goes, sir, the movies are arranged alphabetically.
I don't know what to tell you. We don't have it.
I said, ma 'am, I see it.
We go back and forth like the world's most boring and annoying who's on first routine until finally she's like, oh, OK.
Oh, OK. Here it is.
Well, I don't know who alphabetized these.
How old is this person? How old is this person? I'm just curious.
Forty, fifty.
OK. Oh, so it's it's I'm picturing a snippy millennial, but this is more like like annoying grade school teacher energy.
We'll get to the snippy millennial as annoying as this woman is.
She's not the true villain of the piece, believe it or not.
Right. All right.
So she as I say time, I go time, Bennett, then I go to like Thelma and Louise, which is like next door.
And then I say something that's in the A's.
And I see the sigh leave her as she gets up and walks one step over to like the earlier letters in the alphabet.
And I'm like, why is she behaving this way?
Like you've put yourself in this position. You put the movies behind the counter.
I don't say any of this, but I'm getting frustrated.
She's getting frustrated.
And finally, when I get up to like the 10th, 11th, 12th movie that I want, she's actively rolling her eyes.
There's there. It's noon at a Barnes and Noble.
There's nothing happening. So I get the movies I want.
She brings them over, sets them on the counter next to the snippy millennial.
You know, the cat class, the Lisa Loeb glasses in in 2023, you know, like like she's trying to be.
I don't know. I don't even know. It's a low.
I guess I walk up.
I'm like, hi, I just pulled all the criteria on there with the the woman that right there on the counter.
She picks them up. There's a posted on them.
She goes, I'm sorry. What's your name?
My name, my name's Patrick, but she just set them there.
I just picked them over that. She must have seen and heard this.
We're at the same counter. She goes, what's your name?
And I go, Patrick Walsh.
She goes, huh, takes off the post.
It studies it as if it's like a novella.
She goes, I'm sorry, your name's not on there.
Let me just call her back over to make sure.
I said, you didn't watch her pick these.
And now I am getting a little frustrated.
And I'm kind of like raising my voice, not screaming, but I'm just like, what?
You didn't see this happen?
She goes, no, sir, the dates on there.
So I know that they were pulled today.
I just need to make sure this isn't an online order.
And I just bite my lip. But I'm like, I watched her place them.
OK, fine. She calls the woman back over.
The woman goes, yes, those are his.
She goes, can I interest you in a bag for 10 cents?
I've got a pile of 13 movies.
Like, yeah, I'll take a bag, please.
She gives me the bag.
Then she goes, can I interest you in our Barnes and Noble membership program?
And I said, no, I did it before.
I didn't really use it.
Sorry.
She goes, well, now you can get an extra 10 % off of all these criterions here.
I go, are you telling me they're 50 % off and then I get 60 % off of each one?
Because that would be worth it.
She goes, yeah, each one gets 10 % off.
I go, are you sure?
It's not like, because these are sale prices.
They're half off.
Interrupts me.
Sir, yes.
That's what I'm telling you.
It's 10 % off sale, sale purchases, anything.
Okay, great.
Great.
Let's do that.
Then that makes sense.
I go in.
It's like $20 for the membership.
No, it's actually 40 now.
Oh, it's doubled in a few years.
Yeah.
Well, you know, things are tough.
Okay.
Yeah.
Does that still make sense with my purchases?
If I get the 10 % off?
She's like, I don't know, sir.
You brought it up.
I'm like, okay.
Yeah, no, an extra 10 % off these.
And I kind of start tabulating it.
I'm like, that makes sense.
Let's do it.
She scans them.
She goes through.
When she's done, she goes, and you get to pick a free tote bag.
I said, oh, okay.
Here it is.
Very ugly.
It's blue.
It looks like something a fat woman would bring to the pool for kids sandwiches in it.
I'm like, yeah, okay.
I'll take the tote.
Then I said, well, I guess I don't need that bag.
Right.
And she goes, I'm sorry.
I already rang it up.
The 10 cent bag.
And as I start to just lose it, I go, Pat, it's 10 cents.
I'm sticking with my breathing.
You know, I'm like, it's 10 cents.
Let it go.
She puts the movies in the 10 cent bag and hands me the tote.
Cool.
Thanks.
Appreciate it.
Then I say, now, can you tell me, and here's where I think I uncovered actually an Aaron
Brockovich style conspiracy going on at Barnes and Noble, and I'm not kidding.
I said, before you ring those up, I go, can you just, and I'm sorry to be annoying, but
can you just make sure one more time that it took an extra 10 % off these movies?
And now I get a visibly flustered woman who like look like she's collecting herself and
her temper.
And she goes, sir, I'll say it one more time.
Okay.
All of these movies take an extra 10 % off anything you want to buy in the store.
If you want to buy this pen, if you want to buy this stuffed animal, if you want to buy
this bookmark, it doesn't matter if they're on sale, you'll get 10 % off an additional
10 % off.
Okay.
I'm like, sure.
Thanks.
I had asked, this was my third time.
I don't think that that's insane because I just didn't trust it.
She hands me the purchase.
She tells me the total and it seems high.
It seems real high.
I know how much this shit costs.
I buy these all the time and I was like, no, that's not an extra 10 % off.
There's no way I had already done the math in my head.
And I go, all right.
And I said, can I just get a receipt please?
She goes, yes.
Yes, sir.
Of course.
I take it.
I call over to my buddy, Charlie.
We're going to go see Indiana Jones.
I walk out the door.
I opened the bag and there's no receipt.
I go back in.
She's checking out a person and there's a person behind him after my epic checkout.
So I'm standing there.
Then I go over to the woman who helped me get the movies off the shelf.
I said, Hey, could you help me out here?
I just need a receipt.
She goes, sorry, I'm not behind the counter.
She'll have to, she'll have to find a transaction and print it up.
I go, I was, I just did the transaction now.
So I wait in line behind the first guy.
I say, excuse me, sir.
I'm not waiting for the second.
I go up.
I'm like, can you just print me out a receipt, please?
This woman looks like she's going to kill me.
She prints me out a receipt.
I say, thank you very much.
I walk out.
I get in the car.
I open it to see if I got the extra 10 % off.
And it's a gift receipt with the prices eliminated from it.
There's no prices anywhere on it.
I've missed 10 minutes of trailers for Indiana Jones.
And we still got to park at this, this, uh, insane Burbank complex over there.
And I'm like, just fuck it.
I'm I I'll just tell, take her word for it.
What am I going to do here?
I go in.
We watch Indiana Jones.
I come out.
I go home.
I can't resist it.
I do the actual math.
I'm times things times point one to make sure it came off.
And I realize they didn't take 10 % off these moves.
They took the 50 off.
They didn't take the extra 10.
Now I bought a $40 membership with this goony ass tote bag.
And I'm like, all right, I'm going to call up there.
I call up.
I get a woman.
I say, hey, here's the situation.
I explain what happened.
And I go, look, this isn't a she goes, it must have been a misunderstanding.
I go, this isn't a misunderstanding.
I clarified it again and again.
She like made me get this and assured me repeatedly that it wasn't.
So I don't think it was a misunderstanding.
Then as I start to say, I got to tell you, it sort of feels like she screwed me over here.
The woman goes, no, no, didn't happen.
Nope.
No.
She doesn't let me get the words out.
Screwed me over.
She's yelling no.
And I go, well, look, she seemed extremely knowledgeable.
I don't think it was her first day.
I've got her name right here on the receipt.
It sort of seems like you guys are.
She goes, nope.
Nope.
Excuse me, sir.
Let me put you on hold.
And while I'm on hold for seven, eight minutes, I'm like, I think because it happened at Blockbuster when I worked there too.
You had Blockbuster rewards and they would say anything to get you to sell these things because it looks good to the corporation.
So they'd be like, check them out and then credit them the total.
We do that all the time.
Give them Blockbuster rewards and then credit it off.
It still counts as a sale.
And something is going on here at Barnes and Noble where they lied to me about the thing and then wouldn't show me the receipt.
So she gets back on the phone.
She goes, sir, bring your receipt and all the product back up to Barnes and Noble today by close.
And today only will give you that 10 percent off.
But this will not happen again.
I go, no, then I don't want the membership.
I'm like, I need you to cancel the membership.
We can't cancel the membership, sir.
You it doesn't you can't cancel it.
No, we can't do it.
OK, well, then I really feel like you've screwed me over here.
No, sir.
No.
If you want to bring them in today.
And I go, I can't come up today.
You give me three hours to take a 45 minute drive.
That's not going to work for me.
She's like, I'll put on your account that you can come in today or tomorrow and get 10 percent.
Give me the whole.
She's so pissed at me now.
You have fucked me out of money.
Now I have this stupid ass tote.
I got to make another trip up to this Barnes and Noble.
Hopefully I get the same woman so I can ask her what happened.
But to our friend who works at the Barnes and Noble, I'm coming into your Barnes and Noble this weekend.
And I need you to explain to me if something's going on behind the scenes, because I think I've uncovered something like all the president's men style here.
Well, you're you're putting this guy in like a Newman position where he's going to have to pull you aside.
They'd be like, just walk out the door.
You don't want this heat, brother.
No, it's not.
It's not even a suspicion.
The way that she cut me off and wouldn't let me get the words out means she's heard this a lot and they know what they're doing.
It shook me.
That's what that's what all these stores do.
They say they just they're instructed clearly because it happens at all these big box stores, which, by the way, this is where we're at.
Supporting a brick and mortar now means going to Barnes and Noble, you know.
Yeah, exactly.
I did it earlier today.
I go, why do you even shop at Amoeba anymore?
It's like, well, because I can answer my own question because that's one of the only record stores that has more than six things or you don't have to sit through piles of used stuff like you're in some guy's back room or something.
Like, you know, sometimes you just want a neat, you know, experience.
Look, I own a dive bar.
I love dive bars, but sometimes you don't want to dive.
Sometimes you want you want a Starbucks or something, you know, so I get it.
Well, I realized I get more of a shopping experience on Amazon because you can read about the product on Amazon.
It's certainly better than me pointing them out.
The ones I want, you know, and it pissed me off.
Also, like then anyone that comes into the store is not even going to know this sales going on.
It's just the worst business practice.
It's like speaking of Bird Bank, there's a restaurant I like up there, Wild Carvery.
They have good salads and shit.
They close at seven every day.
It's a restaurant.
They're closed on Sundays and they close at seven.
So me and my buddy are going to meet there before a movie earlier in the week.
It's like, what are you doing?
Like, it's like these people hate money.
I just don't get it.
And I've had enough.
And as I told Joe yesterday, it's all going to Bezos now.
I'm not leaving my home anymore.
All right.
That's fair.
But at least I got a tote.
I'm sorry.
I said fat woman takes to the pool.
I meant to say something different and it came out fat.
I was just picturing a very specific lady bringing this bag to the pool.
We got it.
We know you weren't fat shaming.
It was a joke.
I was picturing Lizzo.
I had a, she's fat.
But she's happy about it.
She is.
Ain't nothing wrong with it.
Ain't nothing wrong with that shake, baby.
You know what I'm saying?
Absolutely not.
Can I get some fries with that shake, shake, baby?
Yeah.
I was, I had a different experience.
My story will be much shorter, people.
Don't worry.
I mean, it's a story that let feeds off the details.
I mean, I had to get the details.
I know.
I'm just kidding.
I went to see Indiana Jones on Thursday at 3 p .m.
First possible screening I could go to.
And I went alone, which I'll often do the first, I've seen it twice now,
but the first time I'll usually go alone with something like this,
because I'm like, I don't want anything ruining it.
I don't want any variables.
I don't want a person sitting next to me going, oh, come on, or anything like,
you know, I just want to kind of do it as I need to do it
and experience it as purely as possible.
I get to the theater.
I'm already worried because my local regal often there's like teenagers
and I've complained about it many times on the pod, but it's a good,
it's a nice theater.
It's a very nice theater.
And it's a state of the art theater.
But it's often, you know, compromised, the experience is compromised
because there's teenagers being loud or whatever, you know?
Yeah.
I go in, sure enough, there's kids like running back and forth in the hallway.
I'm like, God damn it, they're going to be in this movie.
I know it.
There's a dad in front of me at the concession stand.
He's got six kids with him.
They put my water down and the dad goes, that's not mine.
And I go, I know, sir, it's mine.
I'm like, this asshole is going to be in, I'm already,
stomach is doing somersaults.
God damn it, it's going to be ruined.
I get into the theater.
None of these people are in my movie.
I'm thrilled.
Like, oh, man, look at this.
Everybody in here is like calm and it's mostly people by themselves
or people with one kid versus five or something.
I'm like, this is all very controllable environment we're in right now.
Sit down in my seat.
It's hot in the theater.
It's hot.
Air's not on.
I'm like, God damn it, I'm going to walk all the way downstairs.
I'm going to come back.
My seat's going to be gone or something.
I don't want to take any chances.
I look up for the first time ever, ever at the Regal Cinema,
I see an usher inside the theater.
Wow.
This is amazing.
It starts to run away from you.
Yeah, I walk down to the guy.
I'm 10 feet away from him.
He's already like, may I help you, sir?
I'm like, this is great.
I go, hey, man, this might be a tall order.
I don't know if you could do anything about it,
but it's kind of hot in here.
Is there any way they could turn the air up?
He goes, you know what?
I think there is.
Let me check on it for you.
It's like we're in a Regal commercial right now.
I'm like, this is amazing.
He's got the usher uniform with the silver medallion on each shoulder,
like a tin soldier kind of vibe.
Yeah.
Bow tie.
I sit down in my seat.
I'm back row, middle seat.
It's a perfect seat.
Nobody on either side of me.
Woman comes in.
Huh?
You do an IMAX?
No, regular.
But the back row in these theaters at my Regal,
it's a perfect distance.
I'm sitting there.
I'm relaxed.
Lady comes in, has the seat directly next to me.
I'm like, there's no way she's going to just sit in the seat.
The whole row is open.
She sits down right next to me.
I'm like, son of a bitch.
She starts rummaging through her purse.
I don't know what's going on.
Maybe she spilled something.
She's got her phone light on, like looking for something.
Something's going on in her seat next.
I don't know what's happening,
but I'm getting antsy that this might not stop.
Now, I'm also afraid to stand up and move seats
because she's not a white woman,
and I'm afraid it will look racist.
I've been in this experience.
I'm panicking because I want to move,
but I don't want to look racist.
Finally, I go, you're being ridiculous.
It's not racist because you want to move a seat.
It's racist if you don't move a seat.
You know, that whole thing.
I'm being silly, like as if the gods themselves
were speaking directly to me and this woman separately.
We both stand up at the same time and move one seat over.
I'm like, this is fantastic.
It's all working out.
Was there a visual acknowledgement,
or did you just make the move?
No, we just do it.
We just do it.
I'm like, this is amazing.
We sit down.
Here we go.
Lights go down.
Trailers start.
I literally start meditating because I'm like,
I need to breathe.
I need to just take this movie in.
This is it.
This is your last indie movie.
Just enjoy it.
All right.
Last trailer hits.
I feel the gentle breeze of the air conditioning kick on.
I'm like, oh my god, it's all working out.
This is going to be the most perfect movie
experience of all time.
Regal bullshit commercial comes on.
I'm like, OK, here we go.
Movie's starting.
See the Sony logo.
I'm like, huh, that's weird.
And I see the Columbia logo.
Like, well, that's weird.
Then I see the Marvel logo.
I'm like, what the fuck is going on here?
What begins into the Spider -verse or whatever,
across the Spider -verse?
Worst case scenario for me, movie I'm dying to see being
replaced mistakenly by the movie I have zero interest in
seeing, a Marvel movie.
I'm like, god damn it.
Am I in the wrong theater?
Did I fuck this up?
Yeah.
Lady next to me, the one we moved away from each other,
before I could even almost put my head up to assess what's
going on, she looks at me.
She goes, this is the wrong movie, right?
I go, yeah.
Before I can get the first word of the sentence,
should we go?
She's out of her chair.
She's like, I got this.
Out the door, like Jesus Christ herself going to just
save the fucking day.
Yeah.
Goes down.
She comes back.
She's laughing.
She's like, yeah, I fixed it.
They're going to fix it.
That was crazy, right?
So this isn't you're in the wrong theater.
This is a playing the wrong movie.
They played the wrong movie.
Wow.
She sits down.
We're laughing.
I'm like, here's a person that I wanted to move away from
because it was weird to be seated right next to a stranger
number one.
And then number two, she was rummaging a bit and I was
worried.
And here now we're bonding and laughing.
Yet another, as I talked about in the last pod,
experience when I take the scowl off my face for five
seconds.
I actually have a human connection and it's quite nice.
And then the spider verse played for 10 minutes.
I couldn't, it is, it somehow made me less interested in
seeing it.
I was like, I don't care about this at all.
Yeah.
I'm like, I'm supposed to be looking at Indiana Jones
right now and they're like here in the Gwen spider
verse.
I'm like, I don't give a fuck.
Anyway, and then the movie played and it was fine.
And I saw it in RPX, which is an amazing sound
experience if you have the chance to do that.
Does it rock the seats and shit?
It really did.
Like not because of like gimmicks,
but like it literally made the seats rumble.
It was crazy.
Like how the sound system was insane.
Anyway, wait now is this, when you showed me this
the other day, they also had sense where they,
that's putting sense into the theater.
That's called four, four PX or something.
That's their like all immersive experience,
which they are showing Indiana Jones in,
in some of the theaters where it's lightning,
thunder, rain, fog, sense is the last word.
You can't hear a word of the dialogue probably.
So anyway, yeah, cause that's what you,
you want to smell indie after he's been in the
Amazon for five days without showering.
Yeah.
Anyway, we'll get back to dial destiny.
We're going to cover the whole franchise today.
Starting with, if you don't mind Walsh,
if we go chronologically here,
cause that's how I watch these things to prepare.
And that's very significant to my review of dial.
I would love to start with doom if we could,
unless you have a problem with it.
Actually, if we're going chronologically,
wouldn't we be starting with the first part of last crusade?
Good point.
When do you think, do you think they'll release
the Coppola cuts of Indiana Jones where they put it all?
Oh, at some point for sure.
I, I watched, I was going to watch them
chronologically as you did,
but what I wound up doing was going backwards.
I did crystal skull last crusade temple Raiders
with dial of destiny mixed in between temple and Raiders.
So when all over the place experience,
but I've seen the original trilogy more times
than I could possibly count.
So it was great seeing them all on 4k.
I will say starting with doom,
the best transfer of all of them.
If you're going 4k is temple of doom,
because I do think these movies are,
these movies shine on 4k when they've got bright colors to the pop
and all that, like the red section at Collie's,
you know, temple is just incredible.
I think the definitely the coolest transfer.
If you just want to buy one is temple of doom,
but let's start there.
Happy to.
You're starting with a much angrier Indy Jones in temple of doom,
which I love.
Yep.
And I'm, this is still,
still, even after rewatching all of them, my favorite.
And I don't care if that's controversial.
Maybe it's the one I saw first.
I don't honestly recall, but it's my favorite.
It remains my favorite.
It's to me, an Indiana Jones movie is the action.
It's the nonstop action.
Of course I love the character,
but I like the thrill ride of you're going from one
crazy set piece to another.
And the one that packs the most action into its runtime
is unquestionably temple of doom.
And it's my favorite for that reason.
Doom is a lot of fun.
I saw Raiders first as a kid.
I loved it.
And then I remember going to the movies opening weekend to see doom
and my mom and our neighbor, Kathy Pickerskill talking about
a great last name.
It is a good skill.
I might save that for a movie or something.
It's a good last name.
They were talking about how like they were like,
I hear it's really graphic.
This one and very dark and blah, blah, blah.
So that I remember when all that clamoring was happened.
I remember when they invented the PG -13 rating because of temple of doom.
Yeah.
And gremlins.
Both 1984.
In starting with doom.
First of all,
if you watch these and put everything out of your head and just take it in
totally,
it makes sense that doom is first because it is the darkest.
That's what franchises do.
They start darker and usually get lighter as they go.
They don't usually start lighter and then get darker.
And once in a while there's an empire strikes back or something thrown in,
but usually franchises will tend to sort of broaden the scope of it as they go.
So doom makes sense to me as a first entry,
not just chronologically because it does take place earlier,
but for that reason, also for the reason that it's the only standalone,
it's the only one that does not cover Indy's life with the connective tissue of
Marion Ravenwood and some other characters.
And then you watch this thing and it's a batshit.
It's the most batshit out of the three of them or four or five of them.
Yeah, for sure.
It's wild.
So as I told Joe, I think if they did start with temple,
I don't know that we'd have a 40 year franchise on our hands.
I think people would have been like,
Oh, this is like a weird, cool, interesting little movie.
But I don't know if there would have been the demand for more after template now.
Yeah. And that's an interesting perspective.
I wonder that I wonder myself if that would be the case.
So they you start with doom.
Doom has the best opening out of all of them.
And when you're watching it being introduced to the character for the first time
with him walking into that nightclub in Japan or no, they're in China.
I'm sorry.
And and they sit down at that negotiation and you're like,
Who the fuck is this guy?
And within five minutes when his back is against the wall,
he kills a guy and also basically takes a hostage with Willie.
Like he doesn't give a fuck.
The guy is like he's he's he's he's out for himself.
He's out for what he's the treasure.
He the riches he came for.
And he'll do whatever flaming skewer through the heart, too.
It's like it's not an indie like whipping somebody or shoot.
It's a flaming skewer through the heart.
And they like the guys like it's it's very graphic and violent.
Yeah. And it's great.
It's really that to me.
I love the musical that opens it up to me.
I mean, that's that musical is what makes Kate Capshaw not unbearable
throughout is that like she actually is talented and charming.
And part of this like, yeah, I really love the musical into that.
And then how the music plays with it.
And to me, that's the best build of action is up through when that boat
starts going over the waterfalls, it doesn't stop.
And I checked and kind of laughed to myself.
It was twenty five minutes before we got anything that wasn't like
four to the floor action in this movie.
Yeah, this whole opening sequence is is is just awesome.
The antidote to the poison you just drank Dr.
Jones. Yeah, the lines are just amazing when he looks.
What is that antidote that that when he when he pulls her in
and puts the fork to her side where he's going to stab her,
if he doesn't give him the diamond and he goes or anything goes.
The reference to the to the to the song.
The board is also never better looking than in Temple of Doom.
I agree. I think he put on like 20 pounds of muscle or something
because he was playing a slightly younger version.
But like he's breathtaking.
He's beyond Gosling or anything else.
They got him shirtless in the back half, which is what I loved about
Dalla Destiny. We open with him shirtless and it's like, OK,
he still looks incredible, but you see the ravages of time, of course.
Well, and we will get to it when we get to destiny.
But I will say there are absolutely on purpose.
And there's going to be spoilers and dial.
If you haven't seen it yet, you might not want to listen.
But there are absolute direct references to Temple of Doom
throughout Dial of Destiny.
And I was watching this going, holy shit.
I'm only aware of this because I decided let me watch him in
chronological order and see if there's anything to that.
And sure enough, I was like, James Mangold is tying this directly
full circle to Temple of Doom with the concept of who that character
is when you first meet him, who he was as his younger self,
who he was then versus now, blah, blah, blah.
And we'll get into all that.
But one of the things about Temple of Doom that I love and that I love
starting with it is he's an asshole.
He's out for himself.
He doesn't give a fuck about saving the children of this village.
He doesn't give a fuck about any.
When the when the dying kid comes back with the parchment paper
or not parchment paper with the scroll of the of the of the of the Shiva
thing, whatever, and he realizes the Shankara stones are in the in this
temple, he's not he doesn't care that this kid, if he's dead or alive,
he immediately focuses on the scroll and is like talking about fortune and glory.
And he's like, I'm going to go and get these stones and become a famous
archaeologist when they land.
I love the detail at the end of this one, too, where he goes when he gives him
the rock back or this stone, he goes.
Yeah, you know, they're like, don't you care?
And he goes, no, I mean, it'd just be another rock collecting dust in a museum,
because all you hear him say in the other ones is it belongs in a museum.
You know, he he gets his code at some point,
but he does not have that code in Temple of Doom.
Exactly. That's another part of it.
He says the museum line and dial of destiny.
He says it in almost every indie movie, I think.
Yeah. After this, I think, you know, I think in every every one.
Yeah, it belongs in a museum. Yeah.
This is also the first the only indie movie where you do not see him teaching.
So when he says when they're stranded in India and he's trying to figure out
how to get back to Delhi, he says.
I'm a professor. I need to get back to my college.
Now, you know, later, Indy doesn't teach in Delhi.
Maybe he does. Maybe he doesn't at this point in his life.
I took it as here's a guy that will say anything to get what he needs.
We've already seen him kill a guy,
threaten the life of the woman he's with right now,
scream at a kid and have a kid drive a car,
put a kid in harm's way amidst gunfire or whatever else.
You know, fire a gun in the streets of Shanghai.
Like you're like this guy does whatever he needs to do to to move forward.
And it just is these these little details make all the difference to me
when you watch these out of order or out of the order they were released.
And then. You know, he he he also to just and I might be
I don't want to put too fine a point on anything,
but even like when he when they're on their way to Pencock Palace
and he he finds those voodoo idols in the far in the jungle with the blood on them.
Yeah. And he tells them, don't come up here.
He doesn't want them to see it because it's too disturbing.
That to me reframed entirely, entirely.
And then his experience in the temple itself with the booby traps and everything
that reframes entirely the opening of Raiders.
Like when he gets to that very similar looking idol at the beginning
or stone carving at the beginning of Raiders, he immediately he's like, this is it.
This is the place. And you're like, of course, he's seen this before.
He's been down this road already when he goes into the thing with Alfred Molina
and he's like, wait a minute, stay out of the light.
You're like, I've seen him fall for these booby traps already.
Like it adds such weight to his knowledge or such depth to his knowledge.
Now, I love that they reward that kind of attention.
And I still know people who I blow their minds when I say Temple of Doom is a prequel.
You know, I always feel like a nerd saying it, but like people don't know, realize or care.
They just think it's the next adventure of Indiana Jones.
But they really do when you watch them back to back and kudos to Mangold for rewarding,
paying attention and actually doing the same thing, continuing it because Crystal Skull did not.
It's a very cool thing how they actually pay attention to his life and what he's been through.
It's pretty cool.
I also think that Doom. Oh, the other thing, too.
Now, now he gets to the Temple of Doom.
He witnesses the thuggy ceremony.
He witnesses a man get his heart ripped out.
He witnesses he gets tortured.
And what a set.
What a fucking set.
Everything it is action packed from start to finish.
But when they get to the temple itself, it's like, my God, this would be we should a lot on CGI.
But that would not be a physical set that they're on.
They would be in a computer generated world.
And it looks so fucking great.
This is also a movie and a lot of movies of this period do this that uses matte paintings where like when they're coming up upon Delhi,
the first the first half of your screen will be real.
And then like they did in Wizard of Oz or something, it's a painting, but it's seamless.
You can tell in 4K, but it's not like it matters because all it makes you do is sort of Marvel at how and pun,
I guess, intended Marvel at how real it is.
You know, like and you respect the craft like you do with physical effects and like practical effects.
It's like, yes, it looks a little fake.
You know, there are moments in Temple of Doom, especially in 4K, like when they all start falling off that bridge,
which is another amazing scene when he goes, shit, and then cuts the bridge.
It looks a little superimposed, a little phony.
But to me, it's just like I love that I'm seeing the craft.
You know, it may look a little fake in 4K, but technicians and craftsmen come, you know,
made this happen and it's it's a more beautiful lived in experience.
I just think it's an incredible looking movie.
Yeah, I agree about the effects, which is why I'm also forgiving of the.
Questionable de -aging moments in Dial of Destiny.
I was like, this is this is the modern version of that.
And if I was watching this on grainy film, the effect would be completely hidden,
like it was when I saw Temple of Doom on grainy film.
And now when you watch Temple of Doom crystal clear, you go, that's fake.
But I don't care. It's there to tell a story.
It's not there to be gratuitous. It's there because there's a purpose for this.
So anyway, but what I was saying was.
He gets tortured with the blood of Kali.
He becomes evil temporarily because he gets brainwashed
by the voodoo spell or whatever you want to call it.
Again, when you watch this one first,
it adds so much more weight to to Raiders when he says
when he's excited about going after the Ark and Marcus Brody is like,
it's just like nothing you've ever gone after before.
We don't know what power it holds.
And he starts laughing.
He's like, oh, Marcus, you're talking to me about the boogeyman.
You sound like my mother, you know, and you're like, of course,
this guy is crazy shit.
And he's like, this is nothing. This is don't worry about this.
I got this. Don't worry about it,
which ends up being hubris because it does, in fact, hold great power.
And ultimately, but I think, you know,
and then finally, the other thing I wanted to. Oh,
oh, from a directing standpoint with Temple of Doom,
one directing trick that that Spielberg does throughout the movie.
And I really noticed it on this recent watch.
He puts the the immediate threat of whatever it is.
Indy is obviously often in harm's way in the movie.
He puts the immediate threat.
He or he makes the threat so immediate
that time wise, it would be impossible for him to escape it.
And it just adds, you know, like a great example is like when they get
in that that chamber, which is my favorite indie trap ever.
And the spikes come out of the ceiling. Yeah.
When the spikes first come out, they literally come out.
They're almost touching him immediately.
And you're like, well, that's impossible.
He would he would be dead in 10 seconds.
Yeah. And that's that's from these old serials.
Yeah. Like when they're put when he's pushing Indiana Jones's head
towards that steamroller thing in Temple of Doom,
which the guy eventually gets ground up in Russia. Yeah.
Like what you're saying is correct.
His hat is practically touching the thing when you first see it.
And they keep cutting away. But it all works.
And it makes you put you on the edge of your seat
because you're like, oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God.
You know, it's great. Soderbergh puts together
a version of Raiders, which is black and white with no sound.
And he walks you through it and talks about how no one on Earth
shoots and cuts and stages a movie better than Spielberg.
And it's a great exercise.
I watched a few sequences in Temple of Doom sound off.
And it's like the story is so clear.
You know exactly what's happening.
And these directors rarely are going to suck off a appear,
you know, like Soderbergh and Spielberg.
Usually you're talking about Hitchcock or something,
but it's well worth seeking out because the Soderbergh's like
I watched Raiders of the Lost Ark before I do any movie
to remind me how to like stage a scene.
And yeah, it's it's amazing shit.
It's like we talked about when we did Jaws there.
Every scene you're like, there's no better way to shoot that.
You know, and compared to Marvel, these action scenes,
you always know what's happening.
Who's chasing who?
When the insanity starts with the actual roller coaster
through the mine shaft, which when I was a kid to this day
is my favorite indie sequence, I think it's a deleted.
It was taken from the script of Raiders that was supposed to be.
Oh, wow. I actually didn't know that.
But yeah, it's just you're never confused.
It's always clear who's pursuing who.
And you cannot say that about any action movie nowadays
where it's robots throwing each other around and stuff.
It's always like just chaos.
No matter how chaotic these action scenes get, they're clear.
They're beautiful. You get it.
It's perfect.
So the best part of Raider being Temple of Doom.
And again, if you're watching these chronologically.
Indie finds his humanity.
He's out for his fortune and glory.
In fact, the reason he gets abducted by the thuggy cult
is because he goes down to get the stone.
Willie says to him, you're going to get killed
going after your damn fortune and glory.
He says, maybe so, but not today.
He goes down to get the stone.
He gets abducted, blah, blah, blah.
When he finally breaks free of the curse
because short round burns him and he frees Willie.
Now, this is a woman at the beginning of the movie
he's using essentially as a bargaining chip.
And throughout the movie, he says to her,
not throughout, but it starts with him saying,
I'm allowing you to tag along.
I mean, he's a prick.
Why don't you just shut your mouth, sweetheart?
You know what I mean?
It's a lot of that kind of stuff.
So when he comes out of his spell and he saves Willie,
and then they're home free.
Literally free as Willie.
Free as Willie.
And then they're home free.
And she goes, let's get out of here.
And he goes, yeah, all of us.
I get chills thinking about it.
And then it cuts to him in the cave
where the children slaves are.
And he starts freeing them.
You're like, holy shit.
Like, he's going to do it.
He's going to free the fucking children.
And he does.
And then just that ultimate showdown
while they're being pursued,
like you said, the mine car race.
They end up on the bridge.
I remember in the theater when he cuts that bridge.
And I remember my mom going, great.
People were screaming and shit.
It was so insane.
Like, what the fuck?
End of the movie.
Yeah.
And then the end of the movie, he walks in.
And now here's yet another, by the way, yet another recurring theme.
Now you see it in Doom.
You see it in Crusade.
And you see it again in Dial of Destiny.
It's a perfectly tent -pulled theme throughout the franchise.
Indy is seen by a secondary character
as some sort of mythical figure,
as a beacon from another place and another time
who was sent miraculously
to achieve the goal of a certain individual.
In this movie, it's the leader of the Indian village
thinks he was sent by the gods to save the children.
Indy, of course, scoffs at this at the beginning of the movie.
What happens at the end?
He saves the children.
They all come back.
The celebration at the end
of the parents being reunited with the children.
The music is playing.
He kisses Willy.
I mean, it's a fucking amazing ending to a movie.
It's just so it's such popcorn.
Awesome.
Iconic.
The amount of childbeating you watch in this PG rated movie
like Short Round gets whipped again and again.
But when Short Round is beating up the other boy,
the voodoo boy, see that and Temple of Doom,
especially when you read up on it now,
so many people like on my letterbox were like,
this might be the most action packed,
but I got to deduct a star and a half for racism or whatever.
Now I get that this movie is problematic in certain ways,
but to me, the heroism they give Short Round,
Short Round has so many moments where he is the hero.
It completely washes away the moments
where he's walking on a bunch of cockroaches
and he goes, this is like fortune cookies.
That to me is if you want to look at it
in the worst possible terms, it's not great.
But Short Round, it's K. Huy Kwan, of course,
is almost as much a hero as Indy Jones in this thing.
So to me, I get it, it doesn't bother me.
Now I do have a very close...
He also, by the way, let me say,
he has said several times now in public
that he does not find the movie problematic,
that it was a tremendous experience for him,
that it broke open doors for Asian actors and whatever.
But I'm glad the white male who reads The New Yorker
on the app has decided what racism is
and not the actual Asian person that was involved.
All of these complaints were made by white people, yes,
but I do have an Indian friend who hates the movie,
who has written threads about it on Twitter,
and I asked him to just kind of explain it to me,
and he did, and he was very eloquent about it,
but he said when he was a kid,
so excited to see Indiana Jones,
he goes and sees like the gross foods thing
where it's like monkey brains
and they're eating snakes and all this shit.
And he said that made his childhood experience a nightmare
because everyone thought that's what he ate.
Everyone thought that's what Indian people do.
And yeah, you don't think about this shit
when you're growing up, and I totally got it.
It's othering and so forth.
But to me, I don't think that's what anybody was thinking of
when they made this movie.
Context does matter.
I don't think Spielberg said like,
let's fuck over Indian kids, you know.
But it's worth discussing because clearly that's a problem
that everyone has with this movie today.
That's fair.
Me watching, and of course I'm a white dude,
it's never really bothered me.
When I watch it now, I don't cringe like I do
when I see 16 Candles, for example,
where they play a gong every time the Asian character enters.
That said, that's another very lovable character,
and I don't think they're trying to villainize these people.
It was obviously times were different,
and people regret certain things, and people change,
and culture changes, and so forth.
But Temple of Doom is, for me,
what I look for in Indiana Jones,
which is relentless action.
Sometimes the story aspects, even in Raiders,
start to kind of weigh the movie down.
Raiders is a little bit slower than I remembered.
There's a lot of material in it that is not action -packed.
And for me, that's not what I want.
I get that people don't like Temple for that reason.
There is no real classic story to it.
However, it completely works.
I think Raiders is the best of them all.
Sure, I think most people do.
That's my opinion.
But I think Raiders also, chronologically,
makes far more sense as a sequel.
It's a much bigger movie.
It's much higher stakes.
His connection to the ingenue is much deeper.
There's more backstory that you learn about him.
And in Temple, he's this guy who swings in, swings out.
You're like, who is he?
He gets into these muckups all the time, I guess.
In Raiders, now you're seeing his life.
You're seeing he teaches at this college.
You're seeing that you learn that he's a complicated man
or a problematic man or whatever term you want to put on it.
Because even though he does do good things,
he's made some hard adversaries,
including a friend of his who doesn't speak to him anymore.
Why?
Because insinuated, he fucked the guy's daughter.
Who says, I was a child,
and I think they figured out that she would have been like 14
when Indy was hooking up with her,
which adds a whole new element to the story.
I took it as, I mean, I don't know.
I can't say.
Well, somebody figured it out using the script,
that in the original planning stages,
she was actually a little girl.
And you can hear, I think Spielberg and Lucas discussing this.
I know they at least have the words of what they said.
I don't know if they have the audio,
but she was thought to be a little girl.
And they just kind of were like, yeah, great.
Again, a different time.
Like a teenager, though, not like a fucking...
I don't think...
14.
Yeah, but like, I mean, look, hold your thoughts, people.
I realize what I'm about to say is iffy,
but I'm saying like, meaning like she was young for back then.
No, exactly.
But it was sort of okay, but not really.
Yeah, it's just talk about a throwaway line
that would a billion percent not be in this movie today.
I was a child, Indy.
It's like that, you know.
Well, it's followed with, you know what you were doing.
He says that.
And then he goes, look, you don't have to like what I did.
You're going to help me or not.
He's still a prick.
Well, because I was about to say, you know, in the first one,
he goes after this much more traditionally glamorous,
voluptuous woman.
And it makes sense that he would grow into falling in love
with a real genuine person that he has a connection with.
Not that Karen Allen isn't one of the most beautiful people
that ever lived, but it's like, oh, okay, he's matured.
And then it also throws right back in your face.
No, he was also an older guy kind of preying on a younger woman.
It worked out and that's great.
But yeah, by the way, I love this stuff about Indy.
I love that he's not perfect in any way.
That's what makes him special.
I Raiders is just a fantastic ride the whole way.
This is where we first meet Sala.
This is where we first meet Marion Ravenwood,
who ultimately becomes the most important character
in the entire series outside of Indy himself.
The set pieces, of course, in this Bellocke,
well, first of all, Molaram's an awesome villain.
Bellocke, in my opinion, is where we first see the truly,
like a truly awesome Indiana Jones villain.
Like somebody who's sinister, not just sinister,
but plotting, conniving, smart.
Bellocke really is like his Lex Luthor,
where you're like, this fucking guy is really sharp
and he's really good.
This is where we first meet Marcus Brody,
who we get to see in one of the other films.
And I'm sad that he wasn't around longer.
The actor, D 'Home Elliott, wasn't around longer
to be in more of these films.
And this is where you also start to,
this is where they establish the character, excuse me,
of Indiana Jones as a sort of superhero.
You see that he's the mild -mannered professor
during the day, and he's respected at the university,
but when he packs to go on the trip to pursue the Ark,
he throws the gun and the whip into the bag,
and you're like, that's his cape.
This is where we learn, that's his cape and cowl or whatever.
One of my favorite scenes in the entire franchise
is the two government agents coming in,
the heavier of the two men, I was texting Pat,
is also the guy that, so the guy,
that guy, he's a big guy.
He plays Porkins in Star Wars,
which we've always laughed at the choosing of that name.
I find out in this movie -
Him getting the sides.
His agent sends him the sides and he opens it up
and he's like, Porkins?
This movie, his character's name is Major Eaton.
And then I discover, and I never knew this,
he's the guy that plays Bullock in the Tim Burton Batman,
which is one of the great unsung scumbag characters
in cinema history.
Bullock is such an awesome character.
This man had a career.
He's probably been in more giant hits than most actors.
I mean, this guy, that's three right there,
three of the biggest movies of all time.
I'm sorry, not Bullock.
Bullock isn't who he's based on the comics.
He plays whoever, the guy that Nicholson shoots.
Anyway, this movie, this is the first indie movie
to really put a focus on the importance
of the secondary villains.
You've got that amazing guy in the black hat
and the Nazi walking around.
Yes.
He plays Eckhart in Batman, got to say it.
Eckhart, that's it.
That guy's walking around.
He's just an awesome secondary villain.
This is the first movie where Indy goes against the Nazis,
which will become sort of his life's blood,
or the bane of his existence, rather, is the right term.
He's going to battle them many more times.
But the big takeaway from this movie for me
was the further seeds it plants,
and again, this is a theme we're going to see
throughout the series, the further seeds it plants
for the problems that will haunt him when he gets older.
The most telling scene is when he goes
and he finds Marion and he's so relieved she's not dead.
He thought they had killed her,
and he kisses her and it plays the romance music,
and then he goes, I can't untie you.
I have to leave you here because if I free you,
they're going to comb this place for us,
and it'll blow this whole mission.
And you see right there, like,
this guy puts the work first every time.
And I get it in the sense of,
if the Nazis get hold of this arc,
they could end civilization as we know it,
but you do see that, like,
this guy's essentially got a one -track mind,
and it's complete the mission.
A fantastic ending.
Oh, and then they really nail, by the way,
this is the movie where they nail down,
they start with the snake stuff in Temple of Doom.
You see that he doesn't like snakes.
You see that they freak him out.
And then in this one, it's...
I feel like the fear is solidified
because when he falls into...
when they go into the Well of Souls,
and he falls and there's snakes everywhere,
and that cobra sticks its head up,
which, by the way, in the Blu -ray and 4K,
they erased the reflection.
You used to be able to see the reflection
in the glass that they put between them.
But when that happens, you're like, oh, there it is.
There's the moment where he becomes
irrationally afraid of snakes,
whereas he just really didn't like them up until now.
I asked Joe last night,
why don't we get updates on all these characters
except Jock, the guy who flies his plane
at the beginning of Raiders
when he's escaping the boulder.
Unfair.
What happened to Jock?
Never comes back.
I believe he's played by Frank Marshall, by the way.
I think Frank...
Oh, wow, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's right.
I think, yeah.
In watching Raiders last night, for me,
it solidified something that I thought
I just thought as a kid.
I used to think,
could we get to the action here in Raiders?
And I know it's considered
one of the most action -packed movies ever,
but I felt it.
At the end of this movie,
before you get to the faces melting
and the head exploding,
which I always forget about,
like a pre -scanner's head explosion,
or is it pre -scanners?
Maybe not.
I don't know.
I can't remember.
But insane thing to see in a PG movie,
a man's head literally blowing up.
But before that,
there's like 15 minutes where Indy's on a ship.
And I always, up to and including last night's viewing,
forget that this section is in the movie.
When he's on the ship,
the movie kind of grinds to a halt
before the final action climax.
And to me,
and I know that this is going to seem like
a blasphemy to people
because a lot of people consider this
the action movie,
the definitive action movie.
To me, when you're watching this
again and again and again as I have,
I feel like they have a little bit of a struggle
balancing the plot scenes with the action scenes.
It airs a little too heavy
in the plot column for my taste.
Here's where I disagree with that.
I think that it's an approach.
I'm only aware of this because I remember
watching the Phantom Menace special features
when Lucas did it.
And I remember he was talking about
the pod race sequence.
And he said,
well, after the pod race,
they're going to need a break.
And I was like, oh.
And then I remember too,
funny enough, in the movie Mr. Saturday Night
when Billy Crystal, his comedian,
when that buddy, whatever, the comedian,
is talking about how he builds a set.
I think it's in that.
I might be wrong.
It might actually be a literal interview
with like Milton Berle or something.
But just the idea that you go with a huge punch line
and then you go with a smaller one, smaller one,
and then you go with a huge one.
So I feel that Temple takes the approach of
fast and furious or that type of action approach
where it's like, no, it's just going to be run and gun.
We're not going to give you a chance to breathe.
And at the end of it, you're going to go,
wow, that was a ride.
Raiders, I think they're like,
we're going to go with some real big set pieces
and we're going to give you some recovery time
and then we're going to hit you with another one.
So I guess it's just really a matter of preference.
But it's a much more classic entertainment.
It's a much better scripted movie.
Don't get me wrong.
I just prefer Temple.
And I would say that Raiders is,
if you want to talk about,
there's a sequence in each indie movie
that kind of reinforces what a badass he is.
In Raiders, it's that whole thing with the truck chase
where he goes under the truck
and then he's being drugged behind it
and then he climbs back up onto the truck.
It's just awesome.
There's no better punch than an indie punch as well.
Each punch is just the best.
And then I agree, the gunshot noise,
his revolver firing is awesome.
There's classic, the whip noise,
there's classic reoccurring sound effects
that are as crucial as John Williams' score is
to the sonic experience of these movies.
And you notice how much better sound mixing was.
You know, Joe's talking about the Spider -Verse.
I had no idea what was being said in that movie
more than half the time.
I think they actually issued a patch
to fix the sound of Spider -Verse,
but indie, the mix on this thing,
the score, the dialogue, the sound effects,
the punching, the whip cracks, everything is perfect.
I didn't find myself turning on subtitles
as I do with every modern movie.
I didn't find myself rewinding to say,
what did he say, as I do with every modern movie?
It was just a better time in terms of craftsmanship
and they weren't rushing everything.
I, you know, this is, as I said,
we meet Marion in this movie,
and the reason I feel like it feels more like a sequel is,
the last reason I'll say is because
I feel like this is the movie where they're establishing,
like, okay, you met the guy in the other one.
He gets the girl, all that stuff.
Here's where you're gonna actually meet the people
that we're gonna bring.
It's like John Wick.
Nobody from John Wick 1 comes back.
You know what I mean?
The recurring characters in John Wick start,
well, except for Deadwood, that guy, but.
Ian Machine.
Yeah, so, and sure enough, in the next movie,
Last Crusade, we go a little further
into this life that was established in Raiders.
Last Crusade feels like Raiders.
And we're gonna go a step further now,
where we're gonna see a little of Indy's backstory
in the cold open,
and then we're gonna see where he is now in his life
and where his family life is now.
You know, now we're getting into his roots
and what shaped him and what made him the person that he is.
And of course, this is the one that features the dad
played by the great Sean Connery.
It really is the perfect addition to this franchise.
The Great River Phoenix.
Talk about a compliment to Ford,
where they're like, how do we show you young and old?
We'll get the coolest old guy and the coolest young kid.
Yeah, exactly.
And Phoenix, I mean, I am every time so impressed.
I'm like, he is Harrison Ford.
It's crazy how much he nails it.
He nails it.
And to me, they give him, you get to see everything.
You get to see the origin of the snakes,
the origin of the whip,
the origin of the scar on Harrison's Ford's chin
in this opening sequence.
And to me, it never feels like overkill.
I know for some people it's like, oh, that's corny or whatever.
It's just, it's beautifully done.
And when like the camera is flying alongside of the train
with a giraffe's head sticking out and everything,
yet another moment where I was like,
yeah, they're filming a train, you know,
that's moving at top speed.
You know, even in Isla Destiny,
there's a pretty cool train sequence
with the get down under the tunnel and all that.
But you never forget for a second that you're watching
something that's being designed by computers.
In Last Crusade, all this train shit with all the animals,
they're real animals.
They're not CGI.
There's a real train happening.
Some of them are fake.
Some of them are like animatronic.
They look real.
I'll tell you that much.
The elephants are fake.
You can tell that they're fake.
But yeah, no, this opening, yeah,
they shoot this opening sequence like Buster Keaton style.
It's crazy.
It's awesome.
It's just awesome.
And then also too, another, now yet another,
laying a little more groundwork for the man he's going to become.
We've seen now a little bit of this in both movies
that we've discussed already,
but a little more groundwork into the things
that might come bite him in the ass later.
You also see where the hat and whip come from,
and they come from a guy at the beginning of the movie
who's dressed like that,
who Indy is trying to justly steal the cross.
This is interesting.
I didn't notice this until right now.
Indy as a young boy is trying to steal the cross of Coronado
back from this guy because he catches this guy excavating it
from the cave in Arizona.
And Indy as a kid is saying it belongs in a museum.
And this guy is dressed exactly like Indiana Jones,
and he's a fortune and glory archaeologist, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Then when it jumps to Indy grown up
in what his present day is,
you then see Indy wearing the same outfit as the guy.
It's the outfit we've all come to recognize him as Indy's costume.
And you're like, that's interesting.
That's actually really interesting.
As a kid, he knows the right thing,
but yet he still admires the sort of swashbuckling,
self -centered archaeologist
and does become that guy for a while
and then has to come back and do the right thing again.
I don't know if that was on purpose.
He's literally a Boy Scout too, which is a great touch.
He's on a Boy Scout expedition at the beginning of this.
Indiana Jones, The Last Crusade.
He has to pursue the Holy Grail. Why?
Well, because the Nazis are after it,
and if they get their hands on it,
they're going to end civilization as we know it.
Why is his father there?
Because his father was obsessed with grail lore.
It drove a wedge between them and their relationship.
Now you're seeing that he's got family problems of his own
coming from the other direction.
Connery is not a good dad in this movie.
Their chemistry is off the charts.
Connery is beyond charming.
It may be the most charming he's ever been in a movie,
but he's a bad dad.
At the end, Indiana Jones tells him three times in a row
to stop calling him Junior.
It's like the end of the movie.
He's like, all right, Junior, let's go.
The final line is him not giving his son what he wants.
Then the sweetest moment of this is when he believes Indy to be dead,
and he comes crawling back up the mountain,
and you see Sean Connery just rake.
He's so relieved and happy to see his son.
It's the one moment where the love just kind of flows out of him,
and they have him catch himself,
which I didn't love Fablemen's,
but you realize that's Spielberg.
That's a lot of people's relationship with their fathers.
But he has this amazing look on his face of like,
oh, my God, my son's okay.
And then he pulls it back.
He's like, I can't let my son see this.
He immediately is all business again.
So you get it.
It's like they don't make it sappy in any way.
You get the feeling that this guy was not fun to be around
when Indy was growing up.
And they have that discussion where they're sitting having the drink,
or I'm sorry, where they're on the motorcycle,
and he says, this was an obsession, Dad.
I never understood it, and neither did Mom.
And Sean Connery says, she understood it too well,
and she unfortunately hit her illness from me.
It's been a rough family life for this guy,
and it's a trait that he...
Which Indy brings into his own relationships up to dial a destiny.
You see how that shit affects the son.
Sins of the father affect the son.
Yeah, exactly.
So the ending of Crusade is an excellent ending and a wild ending.
This is what drives me crazy.
When Crystal Skull came out and everybody said it was so nuts
that there were aliens at the...
I'm like, he fucking found a 300 -year -old man in the last movie.
What are you talking about?
They all end in the same.
The difference is you were a kid.
That's what it is.
Look, watching Crystal Skull again, I think the ending fucking sucks.
It sucks, but not because it's too crazy.
It's just not executed well.
The old man and the sipping of the grail thing is to me
easily one of the most memorable sequences in all of Indy cinema,
but I love it so much for this reason.
It is the most action -packed franchise that could probably ever be,
and the climax of this movie, which is action -packed as well,
is a simply done kind of which cup is it thing.
It cost almost nothing until the guy drinks it
and then his head turns into a mummy
and the gray hair comes flying out of it, which I love,
but it's a pretty simple non -action scene
that's still completely riveting and great.
I love that the studio did not come in and say,
no, this needs to be shit popping off and exploding.
It works. It completely works.
It's totally compelling all because the script is great
and so is Spielberg, but I love this as an ending
to what at the time was an ending to the franchise.
It's not action. It's just simple, and when Indy picks,
no, this would be a carpenter's cup and picks the most simple cup.
It all makes perfect sense. It's really well done.
He's an archaeologist. He would know.
That's great. That's great at the end.
His adversary in this movie is this guy Donovan,
who's a formidable adversary for Indy.
They once again have Donovan, the main villain,
paired with a secondary Nazi villain who's also very cool.
Not cool, but you know what I mean, like a good villain.
I mean, forgettable, but he serves a purpose.
The lady Nazi.
And then there's the lady Nazi.
This is the first time the woman betrays Indy.
Right.
By the way, talking about ahead of its time,
they got a female doctor in this thing.
It takes place in 1939 or something.
I think the best Denholm Elliott moment,
I love him as kind of a befuddled old man in this,
but I laugh every time when they're zooming in on Indy's face
and he's like, he knows three languages.
No matter what the environment, he'll find his way out.
Oh, he'll be fine.
They cut to him and he's like, does anyone know English?
Can anyone help me, please?
It's a huge laugh in the book.
And then there's the great callback to it
when they're trying to figure out how to get out of the room.
They're stuck in.
And he's like, did you mean that stuff about Marcus?
And he's like, what are you kidding me?
He got lost in his own museum once.
He's all books and no whatever, no street knowledge.
Sala comes back.
Awesome seeing Sala again.
And the ending of this is awesome.
It's they ride off into the sunset
and we all thought this was going to be the end of Indiana Jones
and it was a perfect ending watching them ride off into the sunset.
Last Crusade is my third favorite of the original three.
I think the original four movies go from best to worst.
I think it's Raiders, Doom, Crusade, and then Skull.
I go Temple, Raiders, but Last Crusade only slightly below,
especially when you watch them back to back.
I think Last Crusade hangs in there beautifully.
I ranked the first two five stars, Last Crusade four and a half,
and we're getting to Crystal Skull, which I'm generously giving two and a half.
I think it's, especially when you watch it as part of the franchise,
especially when you see the new latest entry,
Crystal Skull is kind of an abomination that everybody,
it's the abomination everybody says it is.
There's fun in it, don't get me wrong,
but what they do to Karen Allen in Crystal Skull I think is criminal.
You can tell she doesn't even know how to play it
and she comes off looking like she's crazy half the time.
Crystal Skull, so I was terribly excited when Crystal Skull got announced.
I was terribly excited when the trailer dropped.
I couldn't wait to see this thing.
I was like, oh, that's cool.
They're going to pair him now with his son.
He was with his dad in the last one.
I think they biffed.
The opening of Skull is still fun to watch.
It's not great, but it's still fun seeing him.
You know, I talked about their sequences where you're going to see, oh, wait,
but Crusade, end of Crusade.
That's, again, now, as I said, tentpole theme throughout the series.
He shows up and the knight says,
you're the knight that was sent here to relieve me of my duties.
This is the second time now.
Yeah.
Indy is taken as some mythical figure to a person of another place,
another time with a very specific goal.
Anyway, Crystal Skull and Indy declines in that one,
just as he declines in Temple.
And we'll revisit this theme in Destiny.
But Crystal Skull, if I may, I love the opening of this movie.
At the time, everything about it bothered me.
It was such a letdown and the effects looked like shit,
and they still do in a lot of scenes.
But I really love the opening when he's in that.
It's almost like a Twilight Zone thing.
When he realizes he's in the, it's a nuclear family, little joke.
When he realizes he's in that like little testing site
and then the bomb comes and even through folks,
I didn't realize how controversial the fridge thing was at the time.
People have got to calm down about it.
Yeah, I mean, I wasn't, I guess as online or something,
I missed the controversy.
But up to and including that, I think it's great.
I really do.
And in reading about the history of it, Spielberg goes,
that was my idea, the fridge.
And then they talked to George Lucas and he goes,
Steven's being nice.
That was 100 % my idea.
He didn't want me to take yet another kick to the nuts after Star Wars.
And I love that about Steven Spielberg.
He took the hit for his friend, but I think Lucas was like, look,
I still say it's a 50 50 chance he would survive in that fridge.
And honestly, who cares?
It's a movie with magic in it.
Like there's magic.
I think the opening is awesome.
Here's my problems with it.
Well, first of all, it's a great reintroduction of the character.
We hadn't seen him in 20 years or whatever it is on screen.
And he gets pulled out of that trunk at the beginning.
They throw the hat on the ground.
It plays that little sting and you know,
and then he puts the hat on in the silhouette and then it plays the indie music.
And you're like, wow, this is holy shit.
He's back.
Yeah.
They immediately play a little bit into his age.
Not too much.
He's still fully capable in this movie.
But, you know, Blanchett in theory, a great villain, but not really.
Yeah, but it so but it starts with the line of
this is this isn't going to be easy, not as easy as it used to be.
We had guns then, blah, blah, blah.
They're insinuating like he's not quite who he used to be, but he's still that guy.
Yes, that whole sequence in the in the warehouse is cool.
This was the first time we'd seen them call back a previous movie where they go into the warehouse.
You know, like, holy shit, this is the warehouse from the end of Raiders.
This is where they hid the arc.
In fact, you see the arc at one point.
That's not true.
They call back the arc in Last Crusade, too.
I'm wrong.
You that whole sequence is wild, but fun.
Everything from the beginning of this movie up through and including the chase scene.
In fact, I'll go even further.
Everything up to including them finding the skull itself is solid.
It's really solid.
Like, you know, my it's got a good first act.
The motorcycle chase with LeBuff and Ford is awesome.
It's really great.
It's shot amazingly well.
And when they, you know, they go up on the campus and everything, it's a great Indiana Jones chase scene for sure.
My problem with it is.
And I know that as soon as I saw it in the theater, I because I did what I did for this last one, I went by myself at like 11 a .m.
or something and I was like sitting there and as soon as he goes.
Blanchette walks up, she's she's good.
She's threatening, like, but it's cartoonish.
She's they make her cartoonish and it's like a Pink Panther villain or something.
And then she's like, where would you think I am from, Dr.
Jones?
And then he they cut to him and he goes, well, by the way, you're sinking your teeth into those wobble use.
I would think he's a terrible line.
It makes me laugh.
I hate it.
It feels.
And that was the moment where I was like, something's off here.
This is shot like a sitcom.
It looks way too bright.
Why are they putting soft filters on everything?
There there are moments in this movie where I'm like, this looks like the like the Golden Girls.
Like it's like it's like it's why and why it's Spielberg.
It's it's a return to the biggest franchise ever.
And you think they do anything in their power to get it right.
And it looks like such shit from start to finish.
And the effects look so bad from start to finish.
When they show up in that camp.
Now, again, it's still OK up until this point.
They they do the interrogation where they meet.
They meet John Hurt.
Is that what you're talking about?
Yeah. Yeah. And up until they meet Karen Allen, it's all fine.
They put the skull in front of Jones.
They interrogate him with it.
There's the great line.
As soon as I get out here, I'm going to break your nose.
They unlock his wrist.
He punches Mac in the face.
You broke my nose.
I told you.
Like that got a huge laugh in the theater.
Like I'm like, this is all like this is still working.
Yeah. And then you meet Karen Allen, as you said.
She's given nothing.
My friend, I remember my friend said to me, he goes,
why did Karen Allen not enter that scene?
He's happy to see her.
And then she punches him in the face just like in Raiders.
And I'm like, I don't know.
You're 100 percent right.
That's how this should have been played.
I don't buy for a second.
And this is something that hats off.
Entertainment said in his YouTube video.
I don't buy for a second that this kid is talking to him about
Howard, Harold Oxley and his mother named Mary Williams.
And he can't figure out that he's talking about Marion.
I think they tried.
So what he says in that video is Karen Allen was supposed to be a surprise.
And then they decided halfway through promotion that they weren't going to
keep it a surprise anymore.
And it's like, yeah, then you should have that.
Then it hurts the script.
This should have she's not Marion.
And when I saw it for the first time, I thought that Karen Allen had
lost the spark.
I thought that having been away from acting for so long that she was not
good anymore.
And when you watch it now, you realize she's lost.
She was given an unplayable role, even though she's playing a role that
everyone loves.
They did a, I mean, infinitely superior job of bringing her back in
Dial of Destiny, but because she's herself again, you know, she's lost a
little bit of the twinkle of her eye, but she's a real person.
I felt in watching it this time that she played Marion more insane than John
Hurt was playing the insane man.
She's nuts.
Here's the thing.
They're all playing it insane.
They've got Indy making jokes that he would never make at moments where he
would never make them.
They had a chance to set.
Who wants to see Marion and Indy bickering the whole time?
They're bickering like it's shitty sitcom.
It's sitcom bickering and that's why it sucks.
All they had to do.
And by the way, she deserves some comeuppance because you're like, where is
she?
What happened to her after Raiders?
He ditched her.
What happened?
That deserved wait.
It doesn't get it.
They sacrifice tension for humor, which sucks.
This thing could have just been set up as my mother is Marion Ravenwood and
they have got her and Indy from the jump could have been like, I'm going with
you to save your mother.
What did she get herself into?
And they just for this dumb surprise.
And then later, by the way, he goes when he realizes her last name is
Williams, or because he knows her last name is when he realizes like you
married Curtis William or whatever the guy's name is, you know, like he's
Indiana Jones.
He would have put this together.
Like, why are you like she doesn't need to tell him this for him to figure it
out.
Mutt Williams could have been a really cool character.
I felt like it would have been more interesting if they made Mutt.
They said, well, we want to give India run for his money.
OK, fine.
But you could have given him a run for his money the way his dad does make
Mutt such a nerd that he's got to bring the tough guy out of his father.
And his father is like, you can't fucking handle this.
I need to go with you instead of making it like, no, what's what's the 50s
version of an Indy?
Agree, sir.
And it's just they're doing Marlon Brando, the wild one, you know, and they
got him in the exact same outfit as Marlon Brando on that movie.
It never plays like an actual character at all.
I love Shia Labeouf.
I really do.
And I think he's perfect casting for this, although obviously they couldn't
stick with him.
But he him saying daddy, oh, and shit.
Oh, God, it's painful.
It really is painful.
They also they also the hell was I just going to say?
He damn it.
Well, I wanted him to be a nerd, but he's not.
I don't remember.
Anyway.
Oh, well, this is another thing, but I was going to get to it eventually.
The action in this because they went for this.
Oh, oh, that's what it was.
Spielberg said, if you watch the special features on the on the Crystal
Skull special features, he Spielberg repeatedly is like saying he didn't
like the idea.
He says at one point he goes, I just figured I didn't want to do it.
Yeah, he goes, who cares?
I won't even direct it.
We'll get some young hotshot to direct it and me and George will just
produce it.
So who cares?
Then he ends up producing it or directing it.
And his heart is one of the few Spielberg.
Well, I shouldn't say few.
I think this this is where you saw Spielberg's heart is not in this kind
of movie anymore.
He doesn't care.
It was evident in Jurassic Park 2.
It was evident in this.
It was evident in Ready Player One.
You can see like Spielberg does not give a shit about doing these kinds
of movies anymore.
Period.
He's just shooting the script.
He's not elevating it.
And the problem is a lot of these scripts are subpar, including all three
that you just mentioned.
And, you know, there are I thought there was going to be a lot more
moments of this Spielberg magic and they're not there.
They're just not there.
So that, you know, to be upset about James Mangold not being Spielberg.
It's like, no, he is trying because he's trying to live up to Spielberg.
Spielberg was no longer trying to live up to classic Spielberg.
He was getting bored.
That's that's why I say I'm glad his career went the other way.
That's why I say when you meet Marion, and I don't mean just because what
they did to the character.
The second you meet Marion right after that is when they go into the pursuit
and God damn it, they start the pursuit in the jungle.
Yeah.
And you're like, guys, this literally looks like a like if Happy Days got
stranded in the jungle.
It looks so fake.
It's crazy.
The quicksand scene with when he throws him a snake instead of a rope.
I'm like, guys, guys, that quicksand thing looks like they threw up a set on
the Warner Brothers lot or the Paramount lot or whatever in 20 minutes.
It's just a pathetic set.
It's weird.
And I think there's a choice they made that they said we're going to do the
fucking work from here on out.
You're blessed with one more sort of interesting action sequence, which is
with the ants.
It doesn't carry a lot of weight because it is so obviously CGI, but the
ant sequence is still pretty cool.
The chase through the jungle is kind of pointless.
Everything else from here, the thing in the temple, them getting chased by
the natives.
None of it has any weight.
The action sequences are so stupidly cartoonish that you're never worried.
You never cringe.
The alien thing at the end, the last half hour or so, is so devoid of
suspense of anything.
It's like I just saw the new Wes Anderson, which I liked a lot,
surprisingly, Asteroid City.
And the reveal of the alien in that, it's played for comedy, but it has more
wonder to it.
It has more something to it.
It's actually a way better reveal.
This movie is aliens who look like every other alien.
They don't do anything.
They spin around like one of those amusement park rides where they spin in
circles really fast.
And there's no tension or suspense.
You're just like watching special effects that aren't good.
And then, by the way, the shitty explanation of their interdimensional
beings.
Guys, explain that.
Like, have Indy figure that out.
Like, why is it being?
Knowledge was their treasure.
Like, why is the space between spaces and the fact that they're not
actually aliens and all this stuff?
Why is that being explained as a tagged on line?
Just rushed.
Yeah.
By John Hurt.
And, by the way, during the sequence when you can barely hear him say it.
Yeah.
It's crazy.
Like, it's crazy.
And then, and then the ending, you know, when I argued with this with Pat
Oswald, he made fun of me about this.
I mean, he described the ending of all three Indiana Jones movies.
And then he said, this one ends with a bunch of old people walking out of a
church.
And I was like, yeah, well, you got me there.
I can't really argue that.
Yeah, no, it's true.
And LeBuff grabs the hat at the end and Ford snatches it from him.
And you're like, OK, we're setting it up for more LeBuff adventures.
I don't think they even ever seriously discussed that because LeBuff came out
and was like, I feel like I let everybody down.
Nobody likes this movie.
And Spielberg famously was like, there's a time, you know, where you're doing
great work and there's a time to fucking sell used cars.
And this was a time to sell used cars.
You know, he was so disappointed in LeBuff.
It kind of killed his career.
And well, then he really killed his career by his own actions.
But nobody seems to like this.
Nobody seemed to like it at the time.
When you're reading the Wikipedia page and so forth, Spielberg almost from the
jump, it's like Joe was saying, he didn't like the idea.
He didn't want to do aliens.
Nobody's heart is in this.
Ford is much more engaged in Dial of Destiny and in every other movie of this
franchise.
It's just the worst of the franchise by a significant margin.
And it's the scapegoat for a reason.
It's not good in any way.
Folks, we will be back with a full and thorough review of the Dial of Destiny.
Yeah, we don't want to, you know, shortchange it because obviously people have
been waiting for this.
Also, it's July 1st.
The movie came out yesterday.
A lot of you probably haven't had a chance to see it.
So we're going to go in deep, indeed, indeed on Dial of Destiny with our next app.
Joe DeRosa Comedy on Instagram and Twitter.
I have a major tour launching in the fall.
Dates will be announced next week.
But please follow me or visit joderosa .com for ticket information and show
information and venue information and links and all that stuff.
I can tell you right now, though, Philadelphia is on sale, the TLA.
New Jersey is on sale.
Toronto is on sale.
Please, please, please come out to see me in these new venues that I'm doing.
And I hope to see you out there.
Also, the single will be available this Friday, Salsa Windfall.
Finally, on all digital platforms, Mouth on My Money.
Album comes out in August.
Go check that out when you can.
Thanks for listening.
I'm Ed Thee Patrick Walsh.
I'm also on my friend Kevin Porter's Good Christian Fun podcast discussing the
movie Contact, which I believe is about to drop.
So look for that.
We will be back with Dial of Destiny and, of course, later in the month with the
new Mission Impossible.
That's what we know for now.
Thank you all very much.
We obviously had way more to say than we expected about Indiana Jones.
And we'll be back to talk about it even more.
We'll see you next time.
And we'll see you in hell.