I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell
And when the sound of your screams becomes a thing of my dreams
You know I'll say
I'll see you in hell, you know I will
Folks!
We'll see you in hell is back
With a new ep
Here it is right now, happening to me and Patty Walsh
Back to talk to you about these movies
Here we go
Maybe, I mean I don't want to nitpick right off the jump
But that was probably the worst intro you've ever done
But you will
I don't know what that was, I didn't like it
It was not involving, it didn't invite me into the podcast in an exciting way
It's not for you, to be honest
I don't know who it's for, it ain't for the listeners
It's for another demograph
I don't know, I just try to mix it up, you know
I try to, I mean, you know
These people that listen to this show, they're sick
They listen to episode after episode
You're going to give them a different intro once in a while, you know
Yeah, no that's true
We are also, I learned the other day nearing episode 300 of the show
Oh wow
So we should do something special
I think we're closer than we realized
Maybe like next month
We'll do something special and by that we mean it'll come and go
And we'll say, we should have done something for that
Or we'll go, oh by the way, oh Joe, before you cut us off here
This is our 300th one that we just did
And then we'll cut off the episode
Maybe we review the movie 300 for the 300th episode
I have not seen that since the theater
Me neither, let's do it
Alright, I remember loving it in the theater
I have a feeling on a second watch I'm going to think it is utter dog shit
And that if you took away the Sin City like graphics or whatever you call it
It would just, it's just going to suck
I remember it as being powerfully homoerotic
Yes
Just like a lot of oiled up shirtless dudes, loincloths flapping in the breeze
Yeah
You know, it worked
I remember Dave Chappelle doing a joke about that at the time
And talking about particularly how it was the bad guy, the bald dude
Yeah
And he would impersonate him swaying back and forth and being like, yes Greeks
He's going, you're fucking up my movie man
Stop doing that shit
Yeah, what was that, Zack Snyder, right?
Zack Snyder and the world's introduction to one Gerard Butler
Gerard Butler
Who we all thought was going to be, you know, another like, you know
I think Christian Bale or something
And I guess has just kind of become an action star with a beer gut
Which I don't mind, I'm not knocking the guy
No, he's our Chuck Bronson
He really is
Vince and I saw Plane last night, the movie called Plane starring Gerard Butler
And I realized I hadn't seen a Jerry Butler picture in a decade
I bet the last one I saw was Olympus Has Fallen or Olympus Is Weak or whatever the fuck
The first one was called
Plane, Angel Has Fallen, Paris Has Fallen, London Has Fallen
Yes, I only saw the first one, I believe called Olympus
Yeah, that was the first
And since then, you know, I haven't missed the guy
I find him to be kind of a charisma vacuum
I remember when I was on Always Sunny, this girl that was a writer on The Room
Went out with him and he was like hot at the time
And she was in all the paparazzi's like tongue kissing him
We were all giving her shit
Wouldn't do that now, but
We were all like, look at you
But, you know, he hangs in there
Everybody's making pig noises at her
I was always respectful
I was in rooms where people weren't
I enjoyed Plane
I'll get to Plane in the movie corner
But Gerard Butler, he didn't have a beer gut
He looked alright
But, my God, he looks like he's in his late 90s and in the face
It looks like he's just been pounding, pounding
Drink after drink after drink
Take after take
I remember back in the 90s when Jerry Garcia died
Yeah, this is just where I thought you were going when I was talking about Gerard Butler
Well, because what you said late 90s
I remember seeing comics come home
The Dennis Leary thing on Comedy Central and Nick DiPaolo had a joke where he goes
Jerry Garcia died, who would have thought that health nut would have kicked out early
And he goes, they said he was 55
I thought he was in his late hundreds
Gerard Butler
I mean, here's the track I thought he was
When 300 came out
I was like, that guy's fucking awesome
Because he was doing like a Braveheart thing in it, remember?
Sparta!
You know, instead of yelling freedom
And then I looked him up and I was like
Holy shit, that's the guy that played the Phantom in the Phantom of the Opera movie?
Like, this guy's incredible
And then after that it was just
He was in some romantic comedy where he was just like out of shape
And then it was Olympus movies
There was like a PS I love you in there, I think, with Hilary Swank
Hilary Swank, they gave her like two or three cracks at the romantic comedy
And then everybody was just like
Sorry, it's not
Some people it doesn't take
She's a perfectly attractive woman
But when you kick off your career
As she did, it's like people get an idea in your mind
And it's like they never see you romantically
It's very odd
Well, cause she followed
She followed Boys Don't Cry
With the Million Dollar Baby
Yeah, she really typecast herself
And also too
The same with, I think, with Butler
Like, once you do the
I was shocked
When
Back in Gibson's heyday
When he was able to pull off the What Women Want thing
I was like
When I saw that trailer
I was like there's no way anybody's gonna
And then it worked
Like people liked it
See, he was always funny and had romance and shit in his movies
Like the lethal weapons and stuff
Granted, he played a suicidal cop
But he was romantically funny
Well, who's a better example of like
Like, okay, a better example is
When Schwarzenegger did Kindergarten Cop
And it worked
Remember, like that was like
Wait, he's doing a comedy?
Like, what are you talking about?
And then
Yeah
It kind of worked
You're like, okay, I get it
It worked at the time
I watched it recently and
Wow
Is it bad?
Oh yeah
Junior is another not great one
They shot
Well, I mean that was like
That, the junior was the equivalent of
If they were like
Reitman, Ramis, Murray, and Ackroyd are back together again
You'd be like, this is a swish, right?
And then
Yeah
You know, and then it's junior
Because they all did twins
Right
Vito, Schwarzenegger, Reitman
And it was like, this is a no -brainer
Let's do junior
And then it was like
We're never getting that twins, by the way
We're never getting that triplets
It's not common
I feel pretty confident
Well, that'll never see the light of day
I mean, once they
Once they said it's not gonna be Eddie Murphy anymore
It's not gonna be Tracy Morgan
And Reitman is also dead
I was like
All right, guys
Like, I don't
I mean, I never really wanted it to be
Right
Well, today they announced
They had hired a new writer for the Splash reboot
Starring Jillian Bell
Fuck you
I was like
Didn't we already do this once?
And I looked in the article and it says
In 2015
There was a version of this happening with Jillian Bell and Channing Tatum
They're on, like, their fourth version of the Splash reboot script
So, wait
Channing Tatum left the project
It's just Jillian Bell
You're like, guys
The ship is sinking
It's time to move on from this project
By the way
I liked it the first time I saw it
When it was called Shape of Water
Which was basically Splash
Yes
Rolls reverse
Is Jillian
Is it roll reversed?
Is it a merman coming out of the sea?
The horror
It was Channing Tatum and it was a merman, yes
Oh my god
And it is a horror movie
It's like Humanoids from the Deep
Where they're all
No, I don't know what
But
There's that
Joe and I were talking earlier this week about the Faulty Towers reboot
Which sounds intriguing because
Cleese is doing a documentary about
Cancel culture at the moment
He's real hung up on that
He's hung up on it
Which is not good
It ruined the life and career of Graham Linum
The IT crowd gentleman
Who got obsessed with trans people for some reason
But
Yeah, it's
Fuck
Sorry
What's the matter?
I thought it was a spider
It wasn't a spider
I'm over it
Where was I?
British people
Graham Linum
Oh, John Cleese
So he and his daughter
Whose name is
What?
Camilla Cleese
She's a friend of mine, yeah
She's a friend of Joe's
Which makes me nervous because I always shit on my anybody thought
And I'm always scared she's going to hear it
Well, I love the OG Faulty Towers
I'm excited they're bringing it back
I mean, Cleese has got to be in late 80s or something
But if they do a version of it that is about his obsessions
Like Cancel Culture
It'll probably be pretty damn funny
Rob Reiner's producing it
You know, I'm on board
I'm into it
He's reprising the role
I like that
I like that he's just coming back as the character
It's not going to be like, you know, he plays, you know
The guy that leaves the place to the new guy or whatever
Yeah
So, yeah, I'm curious to see
I mean, look
Zac Efron inherits the hotel from him in a cameo at the beginning
Yeah
I'm
That just really seemed to make you sad
Just thinking about it
Well, because
Made our movie
Because these things anymore
It's like they're like hexes
Like we say them flippantly
And then the next thing you know, there's a demon standing over you
It's like that's going to probably happen
What you just said is probably going to happen with this
That's true
You know, it's just a terrible
It's just terrible
When you
I woke up this morning to your text
Because I was in bed when you sent it to me
And it said I saw plane with Vince Norris vibes
And dude, I didn't even know a movie named plane existed
I didn't know what the fuck you were talking about, dude
I had to look it up
Yeah
Well, butlers generally go to theaters
Because they're pretty red state type pictures
And then they also usually go to
Streaming right away
So you can rent plane for 20 bucks at the moment
I'm good
Yeah, I mean it didn't
I'm not against it
But I'm not going to pay 20 bucks for it
I'm going to
I watched
And I'm not
I'm not going to
I mean, I don't think we're going to review it for the show
And it's not really a movie corner show
But I did finish the third
In search of darkness
Which this one is five and a half hours long
Yeah, I didn't make it far
Did you know any of the movies?
No, which is what I liked about it
You know, I was talking to Pinkstone about it tonight
And he's like, I don't know, man
I didn't want to watch it
Because I was like, is this just the scraps?
I go, not only is it not the scraps
It's five and a half hours
I'm like
This, it just keeps going
I was like
I look at these movies like an omnibus of 80s horror
Like
The first one was the one where I was like
They're going to tick all the box
They're going to do all the hits
Yeah
And then as Jim pointed out
The hits they didn't get in the first one
That was half of the second one
And then the other half of the second one was like
Obscure stuff
And then this one is like all the other obscure stuff
And you know, I sat there with my phone
And my notes app open
And I watched it in increments, obviously
I didn't watch the whole thing at once
But I jotted some titles down of movies I want to see
Or perhaps purchase
And I enjoyed it very much
You know, it's perfect pre -bed TV
It's perfect like while you're eating dinner TV
Blue shirt guy is not in this one at all
Wasn't in two either
He was in it like for
Like they went to him twice
Like it was
Oh, okay
They don't go to one
I would imagine if they read any online review of that
That everyone had an issue with that guy
Everyone
Yeah, so
And also too, I'm happy to say
Light on the Alex Winter
Who I've really just kind of had enough of
In these talking head things
But everybody else
You know, everybody in it I enjoyed
And they had some new faces in there
Which was great
They went very heavy with Fangoria clientele
Not clientele, excuse me
Fangoria staff
And then a guy higher up from Severn Films
Which so I thought I thought it was cool
I enjoyed it
And some interesting flicks in there
All right
I'll watch
I mean, I find it odd in five and a half hours
You wouldn't have known any of the titles
I didn't
That's pretty obscure for them to go
I'm exaggerating when I say I didn't know any
But I didn't know a lot of them
And the ones that even that I knew I hadn't seen
Yeah
Like I was like
I was like, oh, Extro
I've seen that move
I think we have a fucking thing of it on the wall in the bar
I think
Yeah
But I've seen that poster a million times
I was like, I never saw it
And then like
So it was like that
One or two
You know, a handful of movies in this I had seen
Jaws the Revenge was one
I'll tell you what though
And this is a thing that I'm noticing
In horror
In things that review horror from that decade
That book, The Horror of It All
Is another thing that did this
They
Without going after them
They go after Siskel and Ebert pretty good
They go to a lot of clips of them
Sort of talking out of their ass about horror movies
They seem dumb about horror, yeah
But then some of the clips are very much in context
And it's very funny
Like everybody that talks about Jaws the Revenge
Including the people that were involved in it
Are shitting on it
And being like, this was a fucking nightmare
It's a horrible movie
Is that Michael Caine?
Yeah
Yeah, that's the one where
His famous quote was
I have not seen the picture
I have seen the house that the picture bought for me
Which is great, good for him
I've only seen the original
I've never seen any of the other Jaws'
Jaws 3 I remember as a kid
Enjoying because of the 3D elements of it
I couldn't
And it's Dennis Quaid
I can't remember
I couldn't tell you now if it's any good
Jaws 2 seems like a direct rehashing of the first one
And Jaws 4 is the worst idea ever
Where the mother
What's her name?
Who plays the mom
Lorraine Gray
The woman where it's personal, right?
Yeah, the shark
A relative of the original shark has followed her
Down to like Bermuda
It's so fucking insane
And she has like a telepathic connection to the shark
It's crazy
They show her walking by some beachside bar
And there's a shark with sunglasses
Who like looks over her shoulder
Looks down the sunglasses at her
While he's sipping a pina colada
Trying to go incognito
Making lurid remarks
Hey, sweetheart
Mario Van Peebles is in it
Poor Mario Van Peebles is in it
Poor Michael Caine is in it
Poor the guy from The Last Starfighter
He's the one that they interview
Robert Preston?
No, the main
The guy that plays the kid in it
Okay
He's the one they interview
Because he's like the main character
He plays the son growing up
They were able to get the kid from The Last Starfighter to do an interview?
Well, he's 60 now
Yeah, yeah
But he's like
Yeah, man
I did all the acting I needed to do for this in three weeks
And I was there for five months
Yeah
Nothing worked
It was horrible
Yeah
How have they not rebooted Jaws?
It's got to be coming down the mountain when she comes
I don't know
I mean, you know
Let's go
Let's do a little news psycho
Okay
I've now talked about this publicly on a podcast
Guys We Fucked
And on the Bonfire Radio Show on SiriusXM
And let's talk about it here
Because my thoughts on it
Which guy you fucked did you talk about?
Say again?
Which guy that you fucked did you talk about?
Come on
It was the bad guy from 300
I have talked about this twice now publicly
And I want to talk about it again with you
Because my conversation about it started with you texting me
This White Men Can't Jump trailer remake
Is one of the worst things I've ever seen in my life
Yeah
Written by the gentleman who wrote today's picture
You People
Yes
That we'll be discussing
Kenya Barris
Also created Blackish on the ABC network
Yeah, I mean
So Jack Harlow
I only know the one song which is
First Class
I'm gonna put you in the first class
Not a great song
But catchy enough that I remembered it just now
So he's catapulted to stardom
Somehow he's the lead of a movie having never acted to my knowledge
And then his partner in the movie
I've never seen the guy before
There's no Rosie Perez character who is the breakout of White Men Can't Jump
That I saw
Well, that we know of yet, right?
So who knows?
The guy opposite Jack Harlow
He was on power
He's been in some things
But he's not a name
Or at least not yet
Jack Harlow is in this movie
Why?
Because his number one song on Spotify has over a billion listens
Is it first class?
Probably
I don't know
I like Jack Harlow
He's a really good rapper
But you know
God forbid they break a kid in with supporting roles in something
To see if
You know
Yeah, it's like
He was decent hosting SNL or something
But you can just tell he does not have the charisma to be the lead in a movie
I mean, you can tell from this trailer
In my opinion
In a comedy
It's like the hardest thing you could ever have to do is carry a comedy movie
First movie had two guys with masterful comic timing
Who have now each had 50 year careers
Doing a variety of genres
Both at like the peak of their game
Yeah
Brought to you by the man that did Bull Durham
Yeah, Ron Shelton
And that's what we used to get
You'd get the top of the line
Like Rosie Perez got nominated for an Oscar for White Men Can't Jump
She's so funny in it
The movie's sexy
It's funny
The plot twists are great
It works
I'm not saying this won't be great
I'm just going off the trailer
But it's like
Why back then
Did we get two rising like huge comic stars
Like we had seen them on
Rudy on Cheers
And Wesley, of course, in Major League
Passenger 57, et cetera
They're coming together
And the chemistry was off the charts
Why now do we get a TikTok star and Jack Harlow?
Why do we deserve this?
We're still, we're paying double the cost for the tickets
Help us out
Find us a star
It's crazy
We did
On Bonfire, Dan Soder and I went back and forth with dream castings of a White Men Can't Jump remake
Yes
I said if we can go, no age limit, nothing
You can do whatever you want
My dream casting was
I had a realistic casting and then I had a dream casting
Realistic casting, I said you put Jason Siegel in there in the Woody Harrelson role
Yeah
He's going to knock it out of the park
With who?
Jason Siegel would have crushed in that Woody
Siegel
He would have been great
He would be
Well, you clearly haven't seen this shrinking show
Well, alright, but you know what I mean
The man's not playing basketball these days
I'll tell you that much
Well, in any case, that wasn't my dream casting
I'm saying if you want to go star that can do a comedy, right?
Put him and Kevin Hart in there
Yeah
But dream casting, you give me a Vince V, a Vince Yvonne, and a Mike Epps
I'm watching it all day long, baby
Sure
I mean, I smell franchise
They go to Japan in the sequel to play in some tournament
You know, something, you know
Well, I'm looking now
I talked about the House Party remake on the Pat Solo movie corner
And I remarked on how horrifically directed it was
And it was by a guy named, single name, Kyle Maddock
And who's directing this White Man Can't Jump remake?
Kyle Maddock
He did two movies in what, six weeks?
And the thing is, is Andrew Schultz, who's a friend and a comedian
And I'm not just saying this because I know him
He's got a supporting role in White Man Can't Jump
Now, I know Andrew Schultz is not as famous as Jack Harlow
But Andrew Schultz has a massive fucking internet presence
And he's a funny actor
Put him in the goddamn lead and let him be funny
Put somebody that has a few million views under their belt
It has to, no, it has to be a billion
Has to be bigger, always has to be bigger
I'm not saying it would be a dream
But even somebody like Pete Davidson makes more sense
Absolutely
Than anyone we're talking about here
Yeah, it's a bummer
It's a bummer
And then, you know, they're just gonna
It's just gonna keep coming
We're gonna get my cousin Vinny's
We're gonna see it all again
And I guess our parents felt the same way
I mean, there was that period in the early 90s
Where it was Beverly Hill, Billy's, Adam's family
You know, just all the TV shows that they grew up on
But at least that, Pat
And this is why this is worse
In my opinion
At least that was a run of movies
For a very finite period of time
Where the movement was
We're gonna do, in theory, edgier movie versions
Of old comedy sitcoms from the 50s
Right
It was a very targeted, very specific thing
It failed tremendously
It was terrible
And I'm willing to bet
It was probably all one studio that did it
Paramounts, for sure
I'd say the most successful
Probably that first Brady Bunch picture
Yeah, those were funny
You know, but it was like
It was a very targeted thing, you know
And it made some kind of sense
Like, we're gonna do My Favorite Martian
And Christopher Lloyd is gonna be the Martian
You know, you're like, oh, okay
I get it
It's not gonna be good
But I get it
This is not that
This is not like, hey
You know, we're remaking all the old sports movies
As new sports comedies
With a different angle and a different edge
This is, we're gonna remake anything that we own IP on
So we don't have to pay a new writer
What we're supposed to pay a new writer
We're gonna rework IP that we already own
So we can get it at fucking cost
Yep
And that's it
And we're gonna just keep plugging
These music video style directors into it
Why?
Because it's gonna bomb anyway
We don't give a shit
Like, I mean, Jesus Christ, dude
You know, Pete Holmes used to have that joke about
He used to have that joke about Subway
Where he'd go, this is what they're doing in the front?
What are they doing in the back?
That's a funny line
That's how I feel about these movies
I'm like, this is the front?
What was happening in the Batgirl movie
That that didn't even get released?
What were they fucking, like, killing puppies on screen in this thing?
Like, Jesus Christ!
I saw on Instagram or something
I saw Brendan Fraser who, I hate to say this
Just annoys me more and more by the fucking day
He's too weird
He's too fucking weird
And he's also, it's getting too, like
It's getting too, like, patting myself on the back
Oh, yeah
Like, immediately
Look, I mean, I'm just a humble performer
I mean, just shut up
And Walsh, can I just
I'm not cutting you off
I just want to just
I want to say it quick and I want to own it
Short round?
I've had enough
I can't do the pictures of him hugging people anymore
I'm done
I can't do this anymore
Yeah, K. Huy Kwan
I think even his wife's had enough
I mean, we're at our limit
I was telling Joe
Who would have thought six months ago
That we would be sick of seeing
The actor who portrayed Short Round in 2023
But here we are
And by the way, Kwan
I got your number
I've been to your Instagram
He's just like everybody else
He follows like 115 people
They're all notable, famous, cool kid people
It's like, fuck you with your bullshit
I'm just happy to be here thing
You slid right back into this
It's all publicist stories and etc.
And this like fragile journey of Brendan Fraser back to the screen
I'm just, I'm not buying it
I feel like some people's stardom ends at the right time
Freddie Prinze Jr.'s stardom ended at the right time
Brendan Fraser does not deserve this second life
But the Batgirl movie
He talks about it on Stern
And you can find the clip on Stern's Instagram page
It's like a good two -minute talk
But he says that it was a pretty good movie
And he's standing up for Batgirl
What the hell does he know?
He was in Dudley Do -Right
He was Dudley Do -Right
Yeah, this guy's acting like he knows how to pick gems
Hey, babe, the whale was a fluke
They threw you in the...
Hey, babe, the whale was also bad
But I mean
Let's talk about this guy's track record
This guy's done more bad movies than almost anybody else
Have you ever seen Blast from the Past?
Blast from the Past and Sinomand
Which is his like top rated movie
Which is not a good movie
He's done one good movie, School Ties, one great movie
I thought Gods and Monsters was good as well
Yes, yes
George of the Jungle
George of the Jungle is terrible
The Mummy
I don't get the love for that thing
I don't understand
I'll give him the Mummy
You know what? I won't give him
Tomb of the Dragon Emperor
Whatever the one that was called
The sequel, sure, sure
I'm looking for his full credits
Because we're forgetting a lot of movies in there
He was in Crash
Okay
But that's not like... Crash doesn't count
Monkey Bone
Oh, Monkey Bone
Holy shit
Follow Dudley Do -Right with Monkey Bone
Be Dazzled
In my opinion, the worst of these is Be Dazzled
Believe it or not
Looney Tunes back in action
Holy cow, was that bad
I watched that the other day
I'm not going to do it in the movie corner
I watched it because I've been on some weird Looney Tunes kick
I've got to say, the first like 30 minutes
I was like, this is kind of fun and funny
It's like Roger Rabbit -y
And then it becomes fucking awful
That's tough
I did love Airheads
I'll give him Airheads
But that's more
Bishemi and friends than Sand
Did you watch the thing with him and Sandler
Talking about Airheads
Like discussing each other's careers
And Sandler is sitting there being like
I mean, I work with this guy, man
I mean, you are so committed
It's like, Adam, it was Airheads
What are we talking about here?
Stop it
Always on set, you could fall right into the character of
Stoner number two
That you played so beautifully
God bless Adam Sandler
I probably just have a mean thing to say about anybody
You want to see how much these publicists work for people
I just saw on Brendan Fraser's trivia section of IMDB
The first thing that pops up
Has developed a reputation for being extremely approachable
And friendly to fans who meet him on the streets
Ooh, I just remembered another one
The Scout
Oh, Christ
The Scout is so bad
It's so bad
That is Albert Brooks' lowest moment, too
Good call, Joe, I had nearly forgotten the Scout
That is the only movie
I have ever heard
Albert Brooks' bad mouth in an interview
Not comedy in the Muslim world
Brooks has some gems
He's got some doozies
The only one I have ever heard him shit on is the Scout
The Scout's really bad
With honors
With Pesci as a bum
They find him rummaging through the trash at Harvard
Or whatever the story was
By the way, Pesci
You want to talk about a guy that did a run
Unparalleled of the shittiest movies
It was after Goodfellas
It was Goodfellas, then My Cousin Vinny
Which was Pesci's Get Shorty
Where you're like, alright, he did a good one
After the big comeback one
And then it was like
It was all phenomenons after that
It was just like, holy Christ, man
Yeah
God
Yeah, I mean
Mrs. Winterborne I'm looking at here
Starring Ricky Lake
He had a wild career
Mrs. Winterborne
What is that?
Sterling McClain and Ricky Lake
And Brendan Fraser
I saw it
I don't remember anything about it
I think it's an adaptation of a Jane Austen novel or something
Remember Pesci did Gone Fishing?
Yeah, it set him out of the business
We didn't hear from Pesci or Glover for
I thought they died after that
Written by J .J. Abrams
Gone Fishing
Pesci, that was like
It was like eight heads in a duffel bag
Jimmy Hollywood, Gone Fishing
Jimmy Hollywood like opened in like 18th place
I mean, imagine waking up that morning and picking up the variety at your coffee shop
But Pesci never seemed to care, really
Yeah, you go to buy the variety
And the barista's like
Mr. Pesci, they didn't deliver it today
Trying to cover for you, doesn't want you to give you a copy of it
Under the counter, he's holding it up to a little fire
He's got it down there on the stove
It's a crazy thing
Black smoke billowing up
What's that smoke?
That is a new type of coffee
All the coffee makers on the fritz again
Yeah, I guess he was just taking whoever offered the most money
But that Lethal Weapon 4 is really bad too
Well, look, there's been bad movies forever
But it does seem now that we're in a
Just a boring time
I guess I would say
Let's go to the movie
Let's get to that movie corner
Let's get over there, Joe
Let's get on it
I saw bringing them up on my letterboxed app
Hold, please
Oh, are we going to do Skinnamarink?
I don't know that I can sit through that film
And I don't think we're going to have too much to say
All right, let's go
Let me just do Skinnamarink
Look, there's this whole YouTube genre
I haven't seen it of these like
They call them creepy pastas
I read up on it a little bit, you know
They make little creepy low -budget things around the house
And cool, you know, more power to them
That's how this kind of felt to me
It's like it was made on the cheap
The guy, I don't know anything about him
He's a young guy
Of course, now he's being courted by Hollywood
But this is not like Blair Witch
Where there's a narrative you're following, per se
Right
It is just kind of
It feels very David Lynch
But people are comparing it to Inland Empire
Which is not his most accessible work by a long shot
That's the only Lynch movie I've refused to watch
I was like, I'm not doing it
I mean, you can skip Inland Empire
I'll try it again when they bring out the criterion
But it's a tough watch
This is only
Well, it's 100 minutes
And for a little kind of experiment like this
That looks like it was shot on VHS
You don't need to be going anywhere near 100 minutes
And I think it's even longer than that
But really, it's long, static shots
Of things that look sort of vaguely creepy
Its goal is to recreate the feeling of being like
A kid out of bed late at night
Running around the house
And you're scared of shadows and stuff
There is, you gather along the way
Some sort of entity in the home
I've seen people sort of pontificate
On what the whole meaning of it is
Or is there some hidden secrets
It's one of those things where people wind up
Making it seem incredibly deep
Just because there's nothing there
So it's like, you know, The Shining
Is not a nothing there movie
But you watch that Room 237
You see people can put whatever they want onto a movie
I can't stand it, yeah
Yeah, so I mean this
I think it's very empty
And it was not scary at all
I think in a theater it may have been more scary, perhaps
But I watch it at home, lights out
And you know, if you're looking at a little toy phone
For 45 seconds
And then all of a sudden the toy phone moves
And it makes you jump
You know, that's about the easiest thing in the world to do
I don't know why anyone who does it
Gets a movie career these days
But maybe the guy will be great
It's like, it's got an interesting vibe to it
But I would have rather watched it as a five minute short
It's on shutter currently
How is it making the money that it's making
I don't understand
There's not an ad campaign that I've seen
You know
It made like two million bucks on a ten thousand dollar budget
I'm sure they did some sort of
Fans, or like people across the nation
Can't stop thinking about Skin of a Rink or something
That must have happened
But
Terrifier 2 at least was a sequel
So I don't know
I mean, look, props to the kid
It's not like the movie made me angry or something
It's anytime anybody takes limited resources
And makes something happen for themselves
I'm happy for you
I guess my question is, and this is very cynical
This is very cynical of me
And again, congrats to the kid
Is it that?
You know, with some of these things
This is not a movie I hear people talking about
This is not a Blair Witch situation
And I start to go
Well, is it that?
Or is it a fifteen thousand dollar budget
With a two hundred thousand dollar ad campaign
You know, I don't know
It's just weird to me
Where I'm like, I don't understand how this movie
Made two million dollars this quickly
Yeah
Nothing just doesn't smell right about that
It's not Terrifier 2
Which came on the heels of Terrifier 1
Which came on the heels of another cult thing
That launched that character
And finally, after all this time
And all this hard grassroots work
With very limited release and tons of word of mouth
They break through
This is like, nobody knew any of this at all
In any way, shape or form
And it made two million dollars
Something doesn't, that doesn't sound right to me
Yeah, my guess is
When they saw how much low budget horror was making
Just because for whatever reason
Right now, people love going to the theater
To see horror movies and they'll see anything
I'm sure the studio behind it was like
Let's give it a push, give it a release
You know
Sure, yeah, okay
And look, I thought the same thing when I watched Sick
Sick is a much more commercial movie
That should have played the theaters
Just because it would have turned a nice profit for them
But, you know, these people aren't smart
What are you going to do?
And these hoes ain't loyal
Well, along these lines
I can't remember the kid's name
And the series is getting turned into a feature length thing
And the kid who is 17 years old
Behind the viral series is going to direct it
On his summer vacation from high school
Wild, but the back rooms
I checked out a couple episodes
Man, it's really well done
The kid knows what he's doing
I don't know how he pulls off half of the shit he does in this thing
Because you start watching it and you're like
Oh, good for him
He found like a big weird labyrinth of rooms
In some corporate office building that are empty
And he's going to
And then as you go through it
You're like
No, that's impossible what I just saw
He's like putting graphics into this to make it look
Yeah
He's doing very, very good work
He's doing very, very good hybrid video work
Yeah
Within something that looks like he shot it on an old VHS
It is freaky
It is kind of scary
The monster in the one I watched was scary
Good for this kid
Like go check out the back rooms web series
And I look forward to seeing what he brings to the screen
That's it
That's all I got on that
All right
It's your movie, Joe
Take us away
I'm going to grab a little water
No, no, that's it
That was my
Oh, you just watched the short
Yeah, no, it's a web series
I watched it
But that's my
Yeah, that was my entry
My first entry
I only have two today
Because we might do Wolf of Snowholler, right?
Or no
If we're not, I'm going to
I'd have to rewatch
I watched it a year ago
But yes
Maybe even more actually
All right, I'll hold on that
I only have one other one
So you do one more
Or do two more
Whatever
I don't know where we are in this
I think you have two more
I only have one more
Okay
I saw Save the Tiger
You ever see that movie, Joe?
Yeah
Jack Lemmon in quite a fine performance in this film
Well, I mean, look
I didn't love this as much as Glengarry Glen Ross
But it occurred to me that David Mamet must have loved Save the Tiger
I wouldn't be surprised
Like, it really, really feels like you're watching the Shelly the Machine Levine character from Glengarry 20 years earlier
As like a man kind of nearing the end of his career
Like, he is so good in this
He's got like a dressmaking factory
A couple of factories that make men's clothes, women's clothes
And he works with a partner that he's been with for years
But he keeps wanting more and more money
So the opening scenes is like a 15 minute hitman and his wife just hanging out at home
Beautiful mansion
And then he goes into work and you realize his life is just in complete turmoil
And they cooked the books last year
And there's an audit plan
And little by little as you realize more about this guy
He sets up one of his clients who's visiting town with a prostitute
And then the client winds up having a heart attack
While fucking this woman
And really it feels like an early sort of prototype for Uncut Gems
Because it's Jack Lemmon
One of the all time great people at performing like a man rotting from the inside out
Or a man on edge
Just put in this one awful uncomfortable situation after another
And by the end you hate him
I mean he's a Sandler
You love him throughout Uncut Gems no matter what he does
The Lemmon character keeps getting worse and worse
He's just a man whose soul is rotting in the pursuit of capitalism
Which makes it a very timely movie too
Yeah
Somehow I'd never seen it
Jack Lemmon one best actor
It's from John G. Avildsen who directed Rocky as well
Highly recommend it
I found it on Canopy which I've talked about on here before
But you need a library card
And they have a better library than any other streaming service for free
So you get 10 movies a month
I fucking love this movie
I thought it was awesome
And it's very weird
I was like why just Jack Lemmon got the Oscar and not other stuff
And I got it by the end
It's a very sort of sad weird movie
But man Lemmon's amazing in it
And for fans of Glenn Gary Glen Ross
You gotta see this movie
It's like the prototype
My last entry today is Triangle of Sadness
I finally saw it
Watching it on airplane
Very good movie
Very very solid movie
Enjoyed it
Sharp commentary on the wealthy
The rich
And more so the class
You know classes
Social classes
You know along the lines of the menu
Without the horror elements
And much more
I'd say
Weirdly
Even though it's not a horror movie
It's a much more chilling take almost
I liked it's a very good movie
I'm not saying anything otherwise
The one thing that I find troubling
And it's been happening for about 10 years now
I don't quite understand what the word hilarious means anymore
I thought this movie had some very funny sequences
The thing that everybody talks about
Where everybody starts puking was very funny
All in all it is not in my opinion a comedy
It's haunting
It's dark
It's very dramatic
The stuff between the couple
Throughout the entire beginning of the movie
With the gender relation arguments and all that stuff
None of that is funny at all
In fact it's painfully fucking awkward
You start to loathe almost everybody
You're watching on screen
With the exception of Woody Harrelson
And the woman at the end who assumes command
Well until she assumes command
Then you start to hate her
And she becomes disgusting
When she's using it to fuck the good looking guy
When they're swimming on the island
And I get it that's the point
Look how quickly power corrupts or whatever
And then of course these are all spoilers obviously
But then in the very end when the assumption is
That she's going to murder the girl
Who you hate through the entire movie
And now at the end you're afraid for her
And you feel that maybe she has learned her
Well no she hasn't learned her lesson
Because she has that great line where she goes
I want to help you maybe you could work for me
And you're like oh god
And then the assumption is she's going to murder her
Because the taste of the success and the power is too sweet
By the way the entire third act of this movie
Is an episode of literally an episode of The Golden Girls
There's an episode of The Golden Girls
Where they get shipwrecked and they are on an island
Oh yeah not a good one
And they find out that they're right near a resort
And that's the resolution
I was a little disappointed to find out
That that's how this movie ended
That's how Shyamalan would have ended it for sure
Yeah but I enjoyed it
For my money I again I thought the commentary
Was extraordinarily sharp and insightful
I just kind of went in expecting this big crazy
I thought it was going to be like the Stanley Tucci movie
The Impostors
I thought it was going to be this big insane
Farsical thing on a boat where a bunch of crazy shit happens
And all of it is a scathing comment
The Impostors isn't this but in this movie
That it would all be a scathing commentary on the rich
And that's not really what it is
The boat aspect of it is sort of secondary
It's the middle of the movie and it goes by rather quickly
So it was a little different from what I was expecting
That's not their fault
It's just what your brain does when you hear certain things
And you see certain things on the internet
Trailers whatever it is
It's a very good movie
I get why it's nominated for Oscars
I don't know that I would watch it again
But for the time I spent with it I did enjoy it
Yeah I mean The Hype Machine is out of control at this moment in time
I heard it described as the new something about Mary
What?
It's probably my second favorite movie of the year
Of last year and I don't recall laughing more than maybe twice
I don't consider it a big comedy
So it's interesting in Babylon
Which I thought was overall just way too long and kind of a mess
But with some great stuff in it
There's a really disgusting scene where Margot Robbie is leaving this big fancy party
After yelling at everybody and being gross
And she comes back in to make herself throw up
All over the floor of this party like one last fuck you
And she does it and they cut to somebody going like
But they cut away from the scene very awkwardly
And I was like I guarantee right before this was coming out
Somebody caught wind about Triangle of Sadness and just cut the scene out of the movie
You'll know it when you see Babylon
That's all I got. You got any more for today's corner?
I do. I want to real quick do Piggy
Because people were asking about it on Shutter
Actually Piggy is not on Shutter
Piggy is available for rent. It's fairly cheap
It is a...
I want to make sure I get it right
It's a Spanish movie
She is bullied
It's a overweight young girl maybe 14, 15
She is bullied by these mean girls at her school
They one day take her clothes while she is swimming
And she has to run home naked
They show you this pretty graphically
There's sort of a lot of nudity or near nudity
For a girl who is supposed to be like a kid
And an overweight girl no less
And it's like I don't know it felt
I guess probably the...
They're going for the Carrie effect
Where you feel so bad for this girl
Because you see her go through all this stuff
But I don't know it just felt gross
Maybe it's because Sissy Spacek at that time was 22 or something
And had a different vibe to it
But the whole movie just felt icky
They target her
There's a guy who is obsessed with her
Like an older man who is disturbed
And he winds up kidnapping her tormentors
To show her he loves her
And then she winds up kind of having to break them out
Even though they are her bullies let's say
So you know it's not scary at all
It's supposed to be horror
I had seen this really raved about
But it sucked
I don't know if the only way to get it is dubbed
I never would have ordered it dubbed intentionally
All I can say is I've never seen a worse dubbing job in my life
They picked the most annoying people to do the voices of this cast
I can't recommend Piggy
I actually really hated watching it
So there you go
If you're wondering should you splurge for it
Spend your money elsewhere
Alright
And let's get to you people
Yes
Starring Jonah Hill
Written by Jonah Hill and Kenya Barris
A stacked cast
The plot is
Manny Murphy
Yes Jonah Hill has
Sort of a large Jewish family
Julia Louis -Dreyfus
David Duchovny
It's a big cast
His sister who ever played her is really funny
I recognized her from something
I don't know what but I like her
Molly Gordon
And anyway Jonah Hill gets into an Uber
Of a black woman
Something that happened to me with my neighbor
And it was very awkward and uncomfortable
She did not find it funny
So I was like oh I can't use that in something now
Did you awkwardly fall in love after that?
No she's married
So was I
He gets into the car of this woman Lauren London
She and him do not get along
They don't have any chemistry
Which pretty much continues throughout the movie
Even as we watch them fall in love
But Lauren London's parents are Eddie Murphy and Nia Long
And Eddie Murphy is a very militant
Muslim
I guess it's fair to say kind of anti -white activist type gentleman
Yeah he's a guy that converted to being a Muslim
I think they do at one point say when
It was like 20 years ago or something
Yes
So the stage is set here for like a real explosive comedy
And it's got the R rating
So I mean I went in pretty pumped
And left fairly disappointed
But Joe what were your initial thoughts here?
Well it's terribly directed
It really is
It started, I was furious at it when it started
I was like this sucks man
Like they do this sequence after Temple
Where all of these notable older Jewish actors are coming up
You know they're in cameo roles
Like I think
What's his name?
Barney Miller's in there
The guy that played Barney Miller
Hal Linden
Yeah Hal Linden
One episode of Two Broke Girls I wrote
The guy from Westworld is in there
The movie
Yep
Elliot Gould's in the mix
Elliot Gould
With one line and then becomes an extra in several scenes
Which I found painful
Rhea Perlman same thing
Perlman two lines out
And there's like this thing where they're all talking about the kids
About his dick and his sex life or whatever
And I don't know
I was like I don't find this in any way believable
I don't believe that this would be happening outside of Temple
But I felt like it was supposed to be a commentary on
Oh you know how it is with a Jewish family or whatever
Maybe it was
I don't know
I'm not from a Jewish family
But that's what it felt like to me
That they were playing on a certain trope or something
Well it missed the key piece
What it needed was Jonah Hill being like
Do I have to go to this reception?
I feel like all old Jewish men want to do is talk about their dicks
And then you go to the scene and everybody's talking about their dicks
Yeah
But to just have it happen is like
Are we supposed to know what this is?
Is this even a thing?
What are you talking about?
That was confusing
So I really was like I'm not into this
Like I'm not buying this gag
And if it's a reference to something then I don't get it
But whatever
But I liked Jonah Hill
And I was like I want this to work
And obviously I liked Julia Louis -Dreyf
I want this to work
So then Eddie Murphy's scene comes
And his scene has some laughs in it
Like when he's walking around
He's like you notice everybody's getting lighter
The skin's getting lighter
I was like this is kind of funny
Alright
That's a scene to watch for when you watch it
He walks in
There's four different drone cameras zooming around him
He sits at a table with his son and daughter
And it's people sitting at a table conversation
And every movie has a hundred of them
And they're zooming and whipping around
And you can't even hardly focus
And then Eddie Murphy goes
Doesn't it seem like everybody's hair is getting
What was it? Curlier or you know
That's what it was
I thought he was talking about complexion
No he talked
Yeah it was everybody's hair
But they
So you notice if you're going to watch this movie
And you haven't yet
It's not worth looking up now
But notice when he says this
There's a shot of nothing
Like this wasted shot where you can't make out anyone's hair
It's not focusing on anybody
It lingers for like five seconds
Then two women with maybe kind of curly hair walk
Sort of into frame
And it's like this guy can't do the basics
He can't land a gag
And he's already been given
As Joe pointed out to me
The Wizard of Oz
Well
So it is
It's
The directing is problematic
The writing is fine I guess
Like at times there are scenes that don't work
There are scenes that do work
Overall it's a very paid by numbers kind of movie
Look first off the bat
I know we're not supposed to talk about people's looks
I'm supposed to believe that Lauren London is in love with Jonah Hill
Give me a fucking break man
Well look everybody keeps saying this
And again we're not supposed to talk about people's looks
I thought they seemed like a perfectly reasonable couple
That's because they dumbed down Lauren London
And I guess because he's
I know him as famous Jonah Hill and et cetera everything
They they they hotted
Dumbed down as you know what I mean though
They like hotted her down in the movie
Yeah no I've seen her elsewhere and yes
They hotted her down and made him seem cooler than he was
Even though that made him seem less cool
Him trying to be like
Jonah Hill looks like he just came off
A 48 hour coke fueled poker tournament in this thing
I mean he looks he
And then went to his daughter's build a bear thing at 8am
That he almost forgot about so he got all this spray paint on
He's like literally graffitied
His clothes are like spray painted in every scene
A big laugh I had early on was when his sister tells me
He looks like a young Hulk Hogan that made me laugh really hard
I don't know why
Walsh I hated that joke
And I'll tell you why and it's something that you
Used to complain about
Is it that he doesn't look like a young Hulk Hogan?
No it was like a reasonable joke
Whatever but like
No it was like
Every fucking joke
For the first whatever was like
You look like you look like
Remember when that was like a complaint about movies
Was like is that all they do anymore is you look like jokes?
No honestly I was just
I perked up at that moment because I was like
Oh these are jokes
I don't even think I cared what
I was like oh wait a minute it's a movie with jokes
And I got excited
That's what I'm getting at
We're in such a dearth of actual jokes
That we're now like excited to see
A hackneyed version
Of jokes that we were
Tired of five years ago
Anyway
Jonah Hill and Lauren London fall in love
Of course there's the clash of the families
His Jewish family treats
Lauren London as she puts it very
Very appropriately later in the film
As a toy
They're bleeding heart liberals
They're excited that they know a black person
And a black person is coming to their family
Eddie Murphy treats Jonah
Hill like
You know who the fuck is this
White guy and
You're not good enough for my daughter
And that's where the comedy
Insues from I kept reading
Repeated reviews of this saying
It had no teeth when it came to the racial stuff
I disagreed with that
I thought there were some really
Sort of daring
Racial territories they went into
Like them arguing about
Farrakhan
Jewish people and
Muslim people arguing about Farrakhan
Arguing about which was worse
The holocaust or slavery
These are not comfortable
Things to go into
I did think it actually had some racial teeth
I really did
And I thought that it did have some funny moments
The thing in the
The thing in the barber shop is funny
When he's like
When he's like you know
Who's whatever honky
Or whatever and Jonah Hill's like
Am I so and so honky
And Eddie Murphy's like well it's not me
There were funny parts
But
It becomes
So heavy handed
Where
Julia Louis Dreyfus is
Is cartoonishly
Clueless about
What's appropriate
About what's appropriate
What's not appropriate
Just containing yourself in anyway blah blah blah
And guys I'm
Sorry it's the year
You can't have scene
After scene after scene where
Every single time a black
Character meets a white character they go
Why is this white person here
That's just not how people talk
Anymore it's just not
Like that does happen
And it happens the other way too
Like there is that racial
Profiling that happens in either direction
Absolutely but every single
Person a friend of mine pointed out he goes
Why are all of her bridesmaids
Confused about the appearance of a
White woman they know she's marrying
A white guy
So the writing becomes so
Right after a while and so just
Like do you remember who's
On what team here and what's going on
It's like come on guys this is elementary
Shit
Yeah for me I mean whenever
The scene you're mentioning the Farrakhan
Scene starts to dig into some racial
Territory it seems like elsewhere
They whenever they start
To they instead go
With a more sitcom
Lane it never really
I get both sides I get it not having
Teeth but I also get that they tried
In a few scenes to give it teeth
I know Jonah Hill kind of
Distanced himself from it like he
Wouldn't promote it so
My guess is it's heavily heavily
Compromised from what it was supposed to be
I also was reading today
And Andrew Scholes actually was the one who they
Interviewed about this but yeah
The end of the movie they don't actually
Kiss at their wedding they
CGI'd them kissing Jonah
Hill in London which means
I can almost guarantee
That she refused to kiss him and probably
Blamed it on COVID but
And they were like all right we'll just get close and we'll do it
Through CGI but like
This that's what the movie feels like Eddie
Murphy feels checked out to me
It felt especially coming on the heels
Of Dolemite where he was so on fire
He just seemed bored
Checked out
And I know along is given absolutely
Nothing to do
You know this is my problem with these movies
And Hollywood
You know the whole
Idea here is we're gonna make
Something that speaks to both cultures
And then what do you do
You take Jonah Hill's character's parents
You give
Julia Louis Dreyfus the
Equivalent
Now this movie is not
Sold to you excuse me
We're marketed to you
As a Lauren London
Jonah Hill movie it is marketed as a Jonah Hill
Eddie Murphy movie
Eddie Murphy is supposed to be the prominent
Character in this outside of
This couple that's the focus right
And in typical
Hollywood fashion they take a
Secondary white character
Julia Louis Dreyfus and give her
As much to do if not more than
Eddie Murphy they give
A third tier character who is
Also white David Duchovny
At least a funny hook
To return back to with his obsession with
The rapper exhibit which is kind of a funny thing
It's basically the same thing as
Michael Keaton's obsession with TLC and
The other guys but Duchovny was kind of
Funny in this
Neil Long
Given absolutely
Nothing to do except
Sit there and look
Cross for no apparent reason
When they establish that her character
Is far less
Far less a sort of
Fundamentalist Muslim person
Than Eddie Murphy's character
So it's
It's just classic and then even
In the end when
So eventually there is one
Scene in this that I think was actually
Very fulfilling there's a
Scene at the rehearsal dinner where the couple
Breaks up because the racial tension
Of it all coming from both their families
Becomes too much
Jonah Hill gives a speech to
Eddie Murphy
Where he goes off on him
And he says you've taught me
One thing I will never ever
Ever know what it means
What it means to be a black person in
America but I do know
What an asshole is
And I was like wow that was a great
Payoff scene and by
The way a great scene in a movie like this
Where it's saying it doesn't
Matter what group you are
A part of you can still be an asshole
You know what I mean you can still
Mistreat other people and I thought that that was actually
Kind of an edgy commentary to make
I thought it was I thought it was sharp
Equally as sharp
Equally as fulfilling
Equally as needed
To be said was
London's character
Saying I'm not your toy
You know I bet every time
You go out with me you tell your friends
That your black daughter -in -law is
Coming that whole speech
I was like this is great
This is great they're going into
A place that you don't see these movies ever
Go into that deal with this sort of
Stuff and then
They do this
Happy fucking ending bullshit
Coda thing
Where the parents realize the kids are
In love they they they do
Like a they set up a meet cute
For the two kids to get back together which
Is endearing yes I cried because that's
Where I'm at in my life emotionally but
Eddie Murphy in that scene though when he's
Like we thought about it and we actually
Love you Jonah Hill I mean he looked like
He was he
Right before shooting that said I don't want to
Do this scene he was playing a different character
It was completely
Different exactly I'm sure that felt like a
Reshoot that they had to go back and do
And he was like guys this isn't even the character
I was playing but you're paying me so
Here here we go that's what it felt like to
Me and this again to me
In my opinion
Speaks to Hollywood fucking
Racism they make Eddie Murphy's
Character come back in and now do
A night and day fucking shift
Where he's like suddenly Mr. Nice
Guy I was so wrong to have mistreated
You I am so sorry the black guy
Had in hand apologizing to Jonah
Hill yeah a crazy ending to this
Movie and then Julie Louis Dreyfus
Comes in does her apology and then
They give her a bunch of jokes to do
Where it's like no she's still like a
Fucking idiot and what and it's like
And then they walk inside and they
Have a surprise wedding and then they
Kiss and that's the end of the movie
Mike Epps funny cameo very
Or not cameo but Mike Epps only comes in
For a few minutes but he's very funny as always
Yeah I mean it's
They loaded up just like they used
To in the early the early aughts
Like they got Rob Hubel with
Two lines you know there's Matt
Walsh with two lines you know a lot of
Kind of comedy
Cameos throughout and stuff and
It holds your attention
Just because it's a it's a
Comedy with jokes like I said
And occasionally will come to life for a
Little bit but on the whole
I just did not think this worked in
Any way and I meet the parents
About race is genius
Great idea it's guess who's coming
To dinner they did it as guess who with
Bernie Mac and even that
As a b -movie was much funnier than new
People
I was bummed out by it I gotta say
I was bummed out by the
Potential because great cast
Great premise and just not a great
Movie unfortunately my hogs
Not down it's not up it's not
Straight out it's
Tilting it's tilting downward
You know I thought it had enough
Redeeming qualities to make me weep at
The end but I
Mean frankly a car
Commercial could do that at this point so
But I had I found
I would rewatch this movie
With my parents and be like yeah
Cool you know like sure
Easy enough yeah it's got
That feeling of like you know
Some my best friend's wedding or some
Comedy that would be on in the background or
Something it just immediately feels like a
Background movie which is not really a
High praise but I'll take
An average comedy at this point
We will be back with
Megan or M3
Gan or M Gans whatever
It is Megan Gans we'll be back
With Megan Gans yes the biopic
And
Yeah I'm on
Instagram and Twitter at the Patrick
Walsh Miss Pat Show
Season 3
Will start airing in April
And that's all I got
That's great I'm excited
For you I'm glad you're back
Working on season 4 right now
Beautiful I
Joe DeRosa comedy Instagram and Twitter
February 14th
Residency in New York City
Of I Never Promised You a Rose Garden
Valentine's Day get your tickets folks
Come on out
I'm also hitting the road I'm going
Into Louisiana in March
And to some other places
Go to JoeDeRosaInfo .com
To get tickets for all of these things please
And then Joey Rose's as always
The sandwich shop and bar
Open 7 days a week opening at 11 .30am
Every day come see us
JoeDeRosaInfo .com
I have a new
Content thing that I'm going to be launching very soon
I know I've been teasing it for a while
I know I've been saying it's going to be a podcast
It's actually not it's going to be something a little different
And I'll be talking about that soon
But not yet
Anyway we'll see you next time
And we'll see you inhale