I'll see you in the movie podcast you turn to when you want to hear discussions and reviews
about the movies you love the movies you hate and the movies you're indifferent about my name is Joe
DeRosa and my name is Patrick Walsh and welcome to we'll see you in hell today we'll be talking about the
lost George A Romero film called the amusement park recently found and you know smoothed out whatever
you call it what do you call it remastered yes putting a 4k setting gorgeously remastered
it's one of the shittiest looking movies I've ever seen so I can only imagine what it looked like
before they remastered it it's clearly I mean I mean you know we'll get into it later but it is
clearly a you know this was clearly some sort of independent you know passion project venture
it's weird because it came out amidst some of his already you know released films but this
clearly was just some like sort of short artists film kind of I have some history on it he actually
did it for like a city board we can we can get into it later but basically it was supposed to be
an educational film about how the elderly are not treated fairly and they wound up being horrified
by what he made it was too effective so it was actually made just like to make some money for the
city you know so okay that they're releasing it as a lost horror film with his is odd but he is a
legendary director so all right let's that that makes a little more sense we'll get to it but before
we do I guess we might as well get on with the show and at the same time on with the Joe you have
and let your light shine down Joe heaven let your light shine down I'm gonna let it shine I'm gonna let
it shine for him or live all I know to shine on me yeah yeah yeah right that's a good one man it's been
a while you know I put up a and I hope you all listen to it I put up a a solo movie corner that
wound up with like a half hour meltdown but before I ever got to the movies I was just having a very
bad day and a lot of people said it they related and it touched them and I'm glad I put it out even
though I almost didn't but I've been talking to some fans who have reached out those I haven't I'm
sorry I do my best I never check like Instagram DMs it's usually like weeks later that I see it but
thanks for all the kind words and the the thing most people have been requesting is you told us
the Joe songs were coming back you know it's not going to be an every week thing but I heard that the
other day shine listening to lithium the 90s grunge station and it seemed right still called lithium
still called lithium yeah I would have thought they would have rebranded that by now not because
of anything other than they you know serious XM rebrands there stations you by getting a celebrity
face for that station so so backspin which was the old school hip hop station which is my favorite
serious station became LL Cool J's rock the bells similar content but just a slightly different
take with with the face of LL Cool J I would have thought by now lithium would be like Eddie
veterans coffee house they haven't done it yet I mean serious is they've got a Tom Petty station got it
Beatles station makes sense and then it's like Dave Matthews and these bands where you're like really
although I guess Dave Matthews has a comparable fan based Tom Petty I might not I may not want to face
that truth but I think it's true he's huge yeah he is he's he's like I think Dave Matthews has his
own like festivals and stuff yeah like three -day things out in fields that you know like it's
he could be another like fish as he keeps going you know like we're people yeah yeah I got dragged
once and was bored out of my fucking mind you know just bored out of my mind and I hate all the songs
I I'll give him crash into me you know if I was fingering somebody I wouldn't mind having that on
the background I hate that song I mean it's his best I don't know what else is good I like the song
Crush which was on that scene no it was on the album after that he had a song called Crush that
was a single I mean it's just a little crush not like I paint every time we touch no that's a pop
no that's a pop song it's got if you heard it you'd be like oh that song yeah and then um
I don't know he's got satellite I like that song I like that better than crash and I used to like
ants marching oh the one of the worst I mean now I I get it I get like it sucks but like I at the time
I liked it yeah I was uh I do this this peloton uh which has been really helping me exercise every day
but the problem is you'll put on like you'll be looking through the music for the playlist and it's like
a lot of I mean it's designed for moms no offense to moms but just like you know like my mom like she's
listening to the top 40 and that's it so I'm trying to find oh here we go 90s rock that'll be great
I'll put that on for like an hour -long bike ride and the first few songs it's like oh the totes
okay all right chili peppers fine and then all of a sudden it's like where are you going
wherever you uh the six -minute Dave Matthew song and I'm like I nothing could motivate me less than
this clown singing he's also an actor he I watched I said okay what are the two
sanland movies I never saw and one of them was called just go with it which is a perfect perfect
perfect title for a movie where nobody's trying to just go with it uh but it's got another
group Barry Moore reunion film with him no so now it's called Kidman and Aniston are in this and uh
also Dave Matthews who plays like a cabana boy who picks at one point picks up a coconut with his ass hole
that's Dave Matthews role and this like otherwise fairly serious romantic comedy
what a career what a career soundless had those guys those musicians slide in here and there
and it was like when Harry Connick Jr. would pop up as like a serial killer suspect some more
freeman movie or something you'd be like all right I guess so I talked about him in uh in the movie
corner because I thought he was good in copycat he was the villain in copycat with uh
Sigourney and Holly Hunter which was a good serial killer movie remember when the criss uh
I'm gonna say Chris Elliott there's the Elvis get Chris forever blue Chris uh Isaac yeah yeah he showed
up and stuff for a while he was on you know I he I I didn't have a problem with him being in Twin
Peaks so that was fine but then like when they gave him his own like single cam curb your enthusiasm style
shell it was like give me a break man yeah he's he's actually right for the Twin Peaks world but uh
I never saw his show I remember always laughing at the promo because he would go uh did I mention the
nudity that was the end of the promo yeah it was pretty curb it was like back in the days of like
uh like californication or you know or whatever the hell was happening pre -air hey by the way
is definitely the most realistic portrayal of the writer's life
because they're in every time you leave your home three supermodels of various ages are on their
knees begging to fuck you that's that's always what my life was as a single writer in LA at least though
with it being decovny you could at least sort of buy it yeah the most outlandish version of that
was dream on with five foot one brine bend bend uh fucking like it you know in his late 40s
fucking like these hard body 18 year old I was like what give me a break with this shit yeah this is
even as a child I know it was ridiculous see I didn't and I think it starts to really fuck with
you because I was like I'd watch these shrubs I mean every movie was a shrub gets the most beautiful
girl in the world I'm rewatching friday night lights with my wife and they got uh dunce
husband Jesse plemons who's amazing on the show but he's with this just stunning model and their
juniors in high school and it's like no why are you why are you telling kids this will happen he's
doesn't happen yeah it happens when you're 40 you know he got dunce but it doesn't happen when
you're in high school it's all about appearances um yeah he's an odd uh well I already said it's
all finished he's an odd looking guy he's he's got an odd look he is but I mean good on him I mean he's
doing the scores says he movie right now I mean he's good at that movie same I got to read the book
which is what I've said about the last five score says he movies oh I got to read the book before
it comes out didn't happen on any of them I'm excited because it's de caprio and danero
and scorsese that's pretty cool I'm a little bummed because danero is playing I think like a midwestern
racist farmer okay I was I just wanted a little more of that scorsese danero you know sure
uh mean street stuff after the Irishman but uh but oh well I'm still excited to see it speaking of
HBO before we get too far off the subject this is sort of a new psycho but you'll certainly appreciate
it I can't believe I haven't told you this by now ed falco was that my show the other night really
not for me she was there for my buddy who's in a TV show upcoming TV show with her he was performing
but she was there and also on that same show performing were michael rapaport
engineering garafalo it hit me right before I went on stage three of the stars of copland are here
right now one of my favorite movies yeah it was a tough crowd boy I'll tell you it was a real tough
crowd was work but she was great she laughed heartily okay and was extremely supportive of all the
comics and I could hear her laughing when I was on stage and given that there was only like 22
people there I could see her and uh that was it old 80 falks that's great I I was the only thing I
read this week on twitter and I was very proud of myself was this lengthy thread of people with stories
about how awesome james gandalfini was to them yes I don't know if you read that but it was great
just like you know like uh oh the only bartender uh swamped at a big Hollywood bar party and
gandalfini hops up on the bar and opens all the wine bottles for and starts pouring drinks is everyone
had little tails like that was lovely yeah no it's uh that if you watch that like you know
entertainment tonight you know they do those like reunion panels of famous shows right you watch
the sopranos one when they start talking about him it's it's as sad as uh like the the news radio
app where the heart man dies you're like it's it's very sad and I'm not even a fan of the show but
just seeing how much they are clearly just destroyed that he's not around anymore speaks uh speaks
leagues about how the guy must have been well my uh little news psycho is the the many saints of
newwork trailer dropped I know you're not a fan of sopranos which I didn't know it was out
yeah I mean I uh we'll get into that you know you we've had our issues about sopranos I do think
you'd love it if you stuck with it but it's not my point it's not it's not my place to devote any more
of my life to getting you to watch this masterpiece it's fun but uh they the many saints of newwork
the trailer is out uh I sent it to my dad I sent it to uh my wife and both of them were like wow
this guy looks exactly like Gandalfini it's his son yeah and uh Michael Gandalfini I hope he can
act I've I've known he's been in a few things it looks like he's good in the trailer
they got Vera Farmiga as Tony's mom which is pretty spot on I guess uh in the show it was Steve
now she also it's grand is she moonlighting as a ghost hunter in this film as well
I think it is a crossover uh it was put out by Warner Brothers and they were like look we need to
make some money on this thing so uh it's pretty star light uh which is surprising to me they got
Leota in there um of it but it's not a lot of big names and I heard they were doing reshoots which
can mean a lot of different things uh but sometimes it means a project in trouble I hope that's not
the case I love chase of course I don't think the man can do any wrong but when I saw the trailer I'll
say my blood wasn't exactly pumping um I like the the little sprinkles of flashbacks in the sopranos
they never did a full episode or anything they they're really effective but I don't know that I'm
yearning for a prequel although of course I'll see at the moment it all this is the this is the
phantom menace of the sopranos world like exactly we're going to show you a baby Darth Vader we're
going to show you maybe that guy you always heard about but you never saw him he's going to be in it
yeah yeah and uh do you ever wonder who the bad guy's mom was here she is um well also in the new psycho
um the I can't believe I just blanked as hard as I just did you said it was starlight you're not oh oh
uh oh leota yeah oh for god's sakes well I don't remember look I'll see a gangster movie with leota in
it uh you know for sure I'm excited enough enough for I'm interested I should say it'll be so funny
to me if you wind up loving the many sense of new work and never watching these sopranos that
will make me laugh that would be right on brand with my personality that's the way I roll usually yeah
I like the one album everybody hates by the band you know right it's uh that's that's always how I do it
but uh you're a number four guy for stone temple pilots you like sour girl how dare you um
I'm an STP I'm I'm that first record all the way through 10 of this half of that second record
a third of tiny music I love it two songs on number four you like uh you're a hot dog
a chocolate star fish in the hot dog flavored water guy when it comes to live biscuit you like the
more challenging stuff we were a couple of comics I was at a show lesson a couple comics and I
were talking about how hard uh you get scrutinized when you do stand up and I was saying I was like do
you know how much slack you get as as in music I go you know how many comics I've seen get
booed off stage in my years like a lot including myself right uh I've seen two bands ever get booed
off stage and one of them was limp biscuit before they were famous because that's the level you have to
suck before the audience will actually boo you off of the stage you have so much volume as a band
you can just ignore it unless the booze are overpowering you I've been to
5 ,000 concerts in my life I've never seen it never seen anyone get booed off stage uh
that was the big one and I when I say two I'm hard pressed to think of the second I don't even know
if I think of a second band but that was the one I mean but it's like you have to be such a
numb nuts band right to get booed off stage like because they're if you're trying your best but your
humble they'll give you the give you all the rope in the world man yeah they're playing a palladium
like three months and I'm like who is going to that it'll be packed it'll be packed yeah it will be
packed all right it'll be packed I can't believe you you don't think that anyone there ironically
oh that's what I was going to talk about I just remembered yes the people will some but it will be
packed with true fans I've got another we only did this once about about uh uh uh um Tatum uh
not Tatum I'm not chatting Tatum Tatum O 'Neal uh not Tatum O 'Neal tip O 'Neal the dead right
fuck are you talking about right now we only did this segment one time and it centered on tip O 'Neal
hitting on his own daughter at a funeral Ryan O 'Neal Ryan O 'Neal sorry tip O 'Neal's a pitcher
Tatum O 'Neal I don't fuck any of the O 'Neal I finally have another one to do
this segment is called perfectly awful Hollywood and it's where in somebody in Hollywood does
something so perfectly awful it's astounding and hilarious but Cosby's reps have amounts that he's
playing a major tour yeah sought and Pat I'm not gonna lie to you you're gonna go I think I'm
gonna go I gotta see what he's gonna say you gotta see I gotta see I don't get try to get a
comp ticket Joe don't give the man a hundred and fifteen dollars I understand that and and please
understand listeners I'm obviously not I don't want to go to support Bill Cosby I don't approve of
Bill Cosby I have great issue with his acts against women all of these things that I would hope
would bet this point of the podcast you know us well enough to know that goes without saying but my
god almighty this is like somebody saying like you want to go to an execution yeah I think I do yeah
baby for the wrong reasons I don't know but like you know Netflix is gonna drop the special I mean
they don't oh yeah if there's blood in the water Netflix is chomping he posted the other day he's
back wearing the hello friend sweatshirt with the multiple colors and the letters okay and he posted
got a fresh cut for my birthday now off to dinner with my family he's he's doing the OJ thing
just like you know taking videos every day like hey here's me at the grocery store I we all know
he those shows will be sold out and they will be sold out predominantly much like the limp biscuit
concert by staunch supporters could be I mean you saw a Felicia Rashad she tweeted out like finally
justices served right and like 10 minutes later she was like I didn't mean that I don't think he
raped those women it's like yes you do Felicia good lord no one believes you she's nominated for an
Emmy this year for something it's like okay let's keep her warning her for the do you you all
excited about the Emmy Noms Joe were you up early to watch this is another yeah I set my alarm
for I am yeah no this is another news psycho people if you needed proof that this business was finished
all right I'm not saying it was a bad show I'm not saying I didn't enjoy some of the episodes I'm
not saying if you're a fan of the franchise you didn't love it but Juan division getting 23 Emmy
nominations is absurd these types of projects used to be maybe one of the actors gets a nod because they
were exceptional a la alliguinness as Obi -Wan Kenobi creating one of the most iconic characters in film
history right you'd see Catherine Haan get a supporting nomination and that great because they knew
that you you you you separated the the critical hits from the just money making endeavors which is
what Juan division and Haan 110 percent deserves a nomination she was phenomenal in the show yes maybe
once in a while like you know like like like the who are the people that did the matrix the Wachowski's
yeah so maybe they they they may have a different name now and that's not a joke I don't know if
they said no no they go by I think as the directing team they go by the Wachowski's okay just that yeah
they've obviously dropped the brothers part so but like but like you know so maybe you see
them or or somebody like them get nominated for like they revolutionize something in directing
this like genre film right you know that's the kind of stuff you would see to by the way they weren't
nominated for the matrix no they weren't but I'm just as an ex I think they were nominated for non
well they some maybe Saturn or whatever does it doesn't matter point is this the matrixes
yeah the point is this it's like you're to take a Disney plus TV show that is
a project derivative of a multi multi billion dollar franchise that is an expansion pack essentially
for a movie franchise something that would make zero sense to you if you didn't know everything
else happening in the Marvel universe and and to throw down with 23 noms on this thing that you
know which five years ago it would have gotten like best sound design and best special effects right
if this isn't proof of the monopolization and the corporatocracy of Hollywood and America and what
I don't know what what else could be I don't I this is what I mean when I hurang and I will say
her rangs I don't shut the fuck up about it but when I hurang on this show about Hollywood just being
it's done it's we're done on every front we're not just done politically in this country we're done
on every front the Hollywood is officially the banks or the church or the government or any other
major institution that has let us down tremendously in recent years it's over done I don't disagree
it's it's a very low time for for art I don't know that it's permanently done I mean these things go
through ups and downs but sure it was pretty bleak I mean I like I haven't seen Emily in Paris so
it's not necessarily fair I know a couple of people that worked there instead it was a miserable
environment the show is a kind of a laughing stock it's everyone just makes fun of how bad it is
when it got the Golden Globe nomination for best drama series or best comedy whatever it is
everyone took that as definitive proof as if the last 100 years weren't definitive proof that the
Golden Globe is a sham sure they were like all right clearly you can just buy yourself an award because
this is one of the worst shows of the year and it's been nominated for the best this is fucked up
and then it went ahead and got nominated for an Emmy too the one that's supposed to be the quality one
you can't buy even though that's bullshit too but when it's on that list you're just kind of like
all right fuck this like this this is a sham it's at this place and it's a shame it's a shame for
the projects that seemingly deserve and I'm not familiar with a lot of these but you hear about
these projects that seemingly deserve awards because of the fervor that happens you know in the outrage
that happens when it doesn't get nominated so you assume okay this must be a fantastic show if this
many people are this upset but like you know something like I will destroy you doesn't get nominated
last year everybody makes a fucking stink yeah and then this year it gets nominated and the headlines
are like I will destroy you finally nominated and it's like guys I'm not saying this about the
quality of the show because I've never seen it it could be a masterpiece it's a really good show I don't
know though if this is nominated because it should be nominated or if it's nominated because so many
people got pissed off that now it's just nominated to appease the public and when you see something like
wand division getting 23 nominations you go yeah they're clearly in the game of appeasing the public
right like you know like it's it's so crazy to me that a show like that and then by the way
zero backlash yeah where is all where is why why is Marvel exempt from all of the
racial criticisms that get law that get launched at every other Hollywood project
at the diversity criticisms that get launched wand division is an almost a hundred percent white show
right okay it is focused on for the most part white suburban life well then Don Cheetle got nominated
for a minute and a half of screen time in wand division and he tweeted out yesterday guys I'm sorry
I have no idea why I was nominated this is embarrassing like he doesn't get it it's so insane it's
insane people are online today thanking Tom Hiddleston for the for the finale of Loki as if he wrote
and directed the fucking thing yeah oh was he good as the character he's played for fucking 12 years
was he good was he good in the finale of the show are you watching Loki I haven't seen oh sorry
just hit the table literally would be like if I was like Kelsey grammar thank you for being so good
in that finale of Frazier you really nailed it it's like you finally discovered who Frazier was
after playing him for nine million episodes of television uh Joe have you did I didn't finish
wand division I just finished it I wasn't interested did you watch do you do you watch Loki no
Christ well here to be able to bring myself to watch suicide squad and I'm a DC fan and I'm just you
said you thought it looked good I think it looks terrible and I thought it looked better than the other
inside squad all right better than the other suicide squad I have god damn it keep hitting the table sorry
I have friends in it and I still don't want to see it and I feel bad saying that but it's like I just
don't want to say it it looks dumb to me it looks really fucking dumb and then James gun comes out and goes
I find most superhero movies these days boring fucker you all talking about yeah this is all you do
are these movies well everybody thinks theirs is different blah blah it's also so I'm looking at
the nominees here it used to be five nominees that was the case and now I mean both categories here have
eight so like what's up with that are are we are we trying to let more people in if it's an inclusion
thing okay great but it's like it winds up with people who I don't feel are deserving I'm not saying
these shows are bad I mean the comedy nominees are Kaminsky method which Joe likes I love Kaminsky
method the flight attendant which I haven't seen heard it's great Ted Lasso which is super entertaining
I disagree if I Ted Lasso to be one of the most boring shows that television has ever seen
and I don't understand why everybody is saying it's riotous and it is it's a nothing and I love Jason
Sudeik is it is a nothing premise it's it's it's a premise you you pitch when you get your first
general meeting and they go you know that's been done like eight thousand times right it is
major league the people who say it's riotous and hilarious I don't necessarily get but I think it
came at a time when everyone was struggling mentally and it's a show about a guy who's struggling and
you know I thought it was very well done hacks I like quite a bit that some friends of mine made
that the Gene Smart Show is is very good about a Paul a Poundstone style legendary comedian and
Vegas I have some friends on that show and I still need to watch hacks I've been seen it yet I heard
it's very good it's good Emily and Paris is ridiculous pen 15 which I thought was a brilliant show
in season one and I was left a little baffled by season two Cobra Kai made by dear friends of mine I
think you know that they were in my mind they were probably like look we were this hugely popular show
we're never going to get Emmy nominations but here we are I know they're thrilled about it right and
then season 48 of Blackish but like that's too many nominees people that's all I'm saying by the way
these categories were not expanded initially to diversify them they were expanded initially if
you remember so the Oscars were so the Oscars expanded to get more popular titles best picture was
expanded so they could squeeze up into the best picture nomination right here it's like what the
fuck is going on here guys like yeah it's a it's a fine cartoon film yeah it was not a picture of
the year this is insane well I the Mandalorian and the boys and I did not see the boys and I have not
seen season two of Mandalorian but they're both up for best drama and it's like best drama in my opinion
the superhero stuff is just like you take as your win that you're making 900 million dollars your
win should not also be that you're considered one of the finest dramas that TV has to offer I love the
Mandalorian because I love Star Wars right it does not deserve to be nominated for anything yeah by
the way it's got a cool special effect acting nominations oh for God's sakes it's some of the
worst acting on television it got acting and by the way I saw an article that said that the girl who
who spoke out about Trump or whatever Gia Cordellano or whatever it referred to her as a snub
that's my favorite is when they come out with the snub and I'm like what the fuck within seconds
of the of the nominees being announced here's a big list of snubs that people are furious about
and it's like come on guys I recently met John Carlo was it John Carlo Esposito yeah yes
great guy talented guy he's great on the show he's one of the few actors that I think actually
it's a good actor on the show I think Gina Carano was not very good I think the Mandalorian himself
is not often very good Boba Fett is great John Carlo is great
Burr was good in his second episode you know there's some good acting on it but nothing you know like
I'm like again this is this is like it's not a knock against anybody this is John remit
television making like there's already a prototype for you there that you can follow and once in a
while somebody breaks that prototype in a way that's sight unseen and I you know I love the Mandalorian
I don't think that that occurred on on that show doesn't mean it sucks doesn't mean it's not good
but I said I think it's crazy and it's getting nominated for Emmys for and in the drama category
I mean what yeah and it's also the you know people submitting themselves in the wrong category happens
all the time Cobra Kai I wouldn't call it a comedy at all I mean there's certainly laughs to be had
but it's not a comedy in any traditional sense it's a drama it's an action drama with a few jokes
so it's it is strange to me what they submit themselves as a lot of the time I remember the most
notorious Emmy clip package for me was for best actor I want to say 2006 and it was the season
where Carmella and Tony's marriage really comes to a head and it culminates in the season four finale
where they have like this hour long epic fight and Tony's punching the wall behind her head and like
I mean it's the best acting I've ever seen on TV from the both of them so they show the clip
of out nominees for best actor and it's Tony screen like my eyes were welling up watching the clip
and then the next clip was James Spader on Boston legal like eating a sandwich and like some meat falls
out of it and William Shatton is like can I help you with that sandwich and like that was his best actor
clip I just made that up but it was similar it was nothing and that's what it is I mean it's just like
Boston legal was clearly a comedy they're putting it up against high drama I never understood
I never under I think Spader wound up with the same amount of wins as Gandalfine yeah and I don't
know why they're nominating shows like the Mandalorian for best drama when there are so many
comedies out there that could fit right into that category yeah you know folks I mean these
comedies they show that the trailers for these things everything's about you know my life has been
destroyed and I you know I have to I just can't get it together and I'm suffering from suicidal levels
of depression and I'm like what is this what is this it used to be every comedy started with a guy
coming home and finding his girlfriend in bed with another man and that was problem enough but now it's
gotta be like you know hate crime committed upon you is like to kick off to a comedy and yeah used to
be I got fired from my fifth job this week right you know now I gotta I gotta work in a mail room
at a newspaper and then somehow I'm gonna work my way to the top you know whatever whatever the hell it
was guys that would be life as always a good setup sure I mean well it started with this you come
home you find your wife and that was another man that would trigger 10 % of comedies 20 % would be
I'm neglecting my family I'm driving to work with a big cup of coffee I checked the watch I spill the
coffee on my white shirt I miss the kids birthday party and something's gotta change then there's
getting hit in the head with an object that makes you like I'm talking I'm talking liar liar you
know I'm talking any movie where two people like piss into the same fountain and switch bodies or
this whatever vice versa they touch a totem at the same time you know yes simple simple and now
you know every comedy trailer I watch I don't see any laugh attempts well because the thing is
is like it would be like if you made a comedy about mental illness or people that suffered from it
it would be like the dream team it'd be like these guys get loose for the day go run
a muck in the city now it's like no we're gonna take you now it's like girl interrupted and they're
like this is a comedy and it's like it's not it's very sad I feel bad for these people they're struggling
there's nothing funny happening right now right even the Woody Allen movies like that would get like
you know like some of his better films like when they would get very dramatic at you know in the
middle of act two or whatever they still started like at least like with him like quitting his
writing job because they you know they took that they you know they wouldn't let him do the Hitler sketch
you know what I mean it started with funny events yeah eventually led to tragic ones and then in the
end they end sort of happy but like if I hit this fucking table one more time sorry God I mean it's
it's an awful sound it is and I'm sorry to the listeners and there's nothing I can do about it
we better get to that movie corner because we're we're Gavin away here let's do it let's do it uh
I will kick things off with Zola uh the new film based on a Twitter thread uh I heard about this
not very well reviewed yeah it's getting mixed I remember reading the Twitter thread enjoying it
when I heard they're making it into a movie I was like look people of course people are going to flip
out that they're doing this you know and I and I did it but it's got a lot of intrigue and suspense
and I see where they want to make it into a movie they got uh Janissa Bravo uh who has directed some
television and other films nothing I have seen and uh she's a very interesting director the movie
in a 24 style is it has to be shot in a way that you almost can't see the actors I mean it's out of
focus in several scenes right so they're they're going for the we're super grainy kind of 70s feel but
I'm not exaggerating when I say that very often it was not in focus um it's very very stylish it's
definitely style over substance the scenes of it's you know it's two strippers uh one that you
know the one says to the other the white girl says to the black girl let's go down to Florida and make
a bunch of money stripping when she gets in the car there's this pimp taking them and he winds up
being a very dangerous man it's also the white girl Riley Kio's boyfriend who's played by uh cousin
what's his name cousin Dave or something from succession I like succession the kids a decent actor um
but he's playing your standard white boy rapper type these are your four basic characters there's a lot
of violence there's a lot of craziness there is an extended scene in a hotel room where like 20
johns come over and fuck Riley Kio uh at 150 a pop like it's it's pretty grim you see a lot of dicks
one dick appeared to have some sort of tumor on the side of it I guess they cast the dick for shock
value but when this is shown on the big screen people screamed and and it's something that whenever
I close my eyes now I see this dick um but you know there is she react to it like what the fuck
they're doing it like the palm of style where that top half of the screen is dicks and the rest is
you know something else so you don't really see her reaction but there's all these sex scenes with
like you know big heavy guys or old guys or unattractive guys you see their come faces you know
in that in that regard inputting you into the mindset of a young sex worker look it's very effective
I mean it's it's rough to watch there's a gangbang scene near the end where if they had continued
with it and not cut it off when they did I imagine there would have been walkouts because just the
the opening of it was so unsettling they do some stylistic things that just do not work you'll know
them when you see them they take you way out of the movie the movie is 86 minutes and when it ends
the entire theater went what in unison it's not the ending there's it's not an ending to a movie so
sounds like a terrible film and you've not said one good thing well you know what it had going
for it is that I think spring breakers is a great movie but it's got that spring breakers feel of
like dirty sex it's hot everyone's wearing like g strings you know and I'm a I'm something of a perv
you know these sexuality is gone from movies so I actually had a really good time it's hard to
be bored when a movie is 86 minutes long and this filthy and I give it credit for that I like the
performances but yeah it's from a storytelling standpoint I think very often a 24 goes with this
let's just not answer this question let's end it in the middle you know they're getting two up
their own ass over there yeah people will say it's artsy they tried to sell a 24 this week for three
billion dollars yeah it's three billion little absurd I watched I finally watched in search of darkness
yes there's not a ton to say here I enjoyed it very much in search of darkness three is coming out
I should I assume will be another four -hour trek into the decade of the 80s and horror movies
I kind of don't get the point I mean I like watching it it's a great shopping guide for horror movies
um because you know you can sit there online as you watch and start finding all these movies that
you maybe saw and never bought or didn't see and want to see or whatever so I think it's great for
that reason it's it's it's it's extremely comprehensive eight hours between the first two installments
but you know I was talking about it with pinkstone and I was like I just kind of know it just seems
like they're just trying to hit every horror movie ever made in the 80s whereas I felt like they're
there could have been a little more I think maybe you'd get a little more out of a full documentary
about giallo horror in the 80s specifically or whatever instead of like these snippets but but I
don't know I guess that's what the point is it was a great decade for horror and they're covering all
of it so so I would say that it's a very good buyer's guide and it's better than part one because the
blue shirt guy is barely in it they had to minimize them uh I will say there was a good hour of it
that was movies I had never heard of and as a true movie aficionado that's too much like you're
going to obscure at that point I bought many of those films okay I hadn't heard of them either so I
thought that was cool yeah I think it is kind of cool to have you know I watched this metal Jesus
rocks channel on youtube he's a video game guy I'm a big fan and he does these videos called hidden gems
sometimes we're hoping like today we're talking about PlayStation 2's hidden gems these are games that
are great that never got a lot of attention and it's awesome because you find these like really cool
games you never know so I thought they were kind of doing a bit of that in this which I appreciate it
but at the same time it's like just do a documentary called the unsung heroes of 80s horror
and give me like three hours straight of like here's everything you missed right no name
in or whatever but anyway it's it's worth a watch you know and uh it's an enjoyable it's an enjoyable
you know thing that you can kind of just have on and you know not have to scrutinize the entire time
you're watching it oh and just in case you were worried they cover the nightmare announced
two thing for the 87 ,000 fucking time and once again it doesn't make it because Robert England is
being like we we were saying it without saying it we knew what we were doing and it's like
did you guys know what you were doing or not like what is it I mean Jesus Christ almighty it's this
back and forth we it was a game movie it wasn't a game movie right let's go to Robert England
who's for some reason wearing a black turtle neck and a beret to talk to us about playing
Freddie Krueger I watched new to HBO Max and weirdly I don't think released in theaters so I don't
understand sometimes they do sometimes they don't but uh no sudden move which was directed by Steven
Soderbergh and written by my twitter acquaintance Ed Solomon who did men in black and Bill and Ted
I want to see this in the theater but it's not in the theater I don't think yeah and that's weird
to me it's a Soderbergh movie yeah you know and it's not one of his I shot it on an iPhone joints
he's doing six movies a year at this point Soderbergh he's got the other in this one too it does indeed
it's it's a simple kind of it's it's it's film noir it's a simple baby sitting job that of course
winds up to be much more complicated than all the players think there's a lot of twists and turns
the cast is top notch Don Chiddle Benicio del Toro David Harbor from Stranger Things Ray Liotta John
Ham Kieran Colken Julia Fox who is bad in it but uh was the woman with the I know I'm not supposed to
talk about appearances but with the best but I've ever seen from Uncut Gems um she's like a fair
yeah okay um Bill Duke steals the fucking movie the legendary Bill Duke is excellent in this movie
I love that he's back he's I'm not back but I love that he's still out there he's awesome in it and
they and the biggest surprise to me Brendan Fraser who I was not aware was in this he's he's going
to be in Darren Arenofsky's next movie and I heard he was playing like a 300 pound man in that and I
was like oh well did he put on weight and then you see him in this and you're like okay Brendan Fraser
is not his no longer in Georgia the jungle shape uh he looks like Orson Wells so it's almost like having
a new actor on the scene when Brendan Fraser shows up and that's really cool to me I mean the
the guy I get it you know he starved himself he probably did terrible things to his body to get his
shredded as he did during those Encino man George the Jungle days and now he's just a big fat guy
who thought he'd never act again and he comes back and he's great he's a great supporting actor in
this really he's having to come back it's like almost like a Shelley Duvall's another one where I'm
just like fingers crossed I hope like she gets to you know what I mean there's people that you're
rooting for that have had a real bad run of it and you're just yeah and apparently they did an article
about her following up the Doctor Phil thing is the guy that wrote the article said I wasn't going to let
Doctor Phil exploit her like that and that be the last thing and the article is actually very
endearing and it seems that she's very happy and very private and is still married and has a good
life so I hope that that's the case but my point is his Brendan Frazier is another one of those
guys where it's like he took such a hard fall and then it was like I'm glad he's making a comeback man
yeah I'm I'm happy for the man I think Soderbergh is kind of doing the Tarantino thing now
of seeking out these kind of actors and that's very cool to me you'll notice I haven't really
mentioned my thoughts on the film the reason for that is you're watching it you're enjoying the cast
Soderbergh knows how to shoot a movie but this movie is done in this extreme anamorphic where the
characters are actually rounded at certain points like at the edges of the screen yeah the characters
are actually like cylinders all of it to me it's like the fish the fish by lands are what it's called yeah
the buster lands that he used in every video that's exactly right the buster rhymes lens and that's great
for a three minute video that's great for a scene if you're trying to show a character's mental
state or something but for a two -hour movie I I can't for the life of me understand why you
will shoot a shot like that the whole thing is shot in this fish out yeah and it's distracting and
it's annoying and Soderbergh I'm sorry you're bored with making movies in the traditional way but
we have to watch this shit yeah so it made me dizzy it made my head hurt a little bit and I'm usually
not susceptible to that kind of stuff and there's an emptiness to the movie I it's did you see a
most violent year Joe yeah with Chastain and and Oscar Isaacs wait yeah I did see that that movie
stuck it was so boring this this is very similar where like all the elements are there it's a genre
you love but they're going for some sort of statement as opposed to making an entertaining movie and I
just kind of kept waiting for it to take off and it didn't it's not bad all right but you know I'm
almost ashamed to say I preferred Zola because it was it was quick and dirty and fun and and and
and all you know unhinged I preferred it to this even though this is a much better and better made
movie because I was just bored throughout that's all I can really say about it all right I'll stay on
the horror theme I watched two sentence horror on two sentence horror stories on Netflix this is
an anthology series that was created I think originally for the CW and is now streaming on Netflix there's
two or three seasons on there I haven't finished it but I watched a bunch of it the reason it's called
that is because it's start every episode starts with a sentence that sets up the plot and then when
the ending comes which is usually a twist of some sort it shows that sentence again at the end of
the episode and then it follows it up with a second sentence that sort of puts the first sentence on
its head a little bit okay um they're usually pretty simple premises uh every episode is not great
but I will say this with the with a dearth of good truly good anthology horror out there you know our
thoughts on creep show you know our thoughts on overall on the twilight zone latest twilight zone um
American horror stories which is coming out now is a true anthology horror show from the American
horror story people looks stupid and sexed out and oh you know I just don't give a shit
so it's anthology style though each week's a new version yeah that's I look that's that that
might get me to watch it more than the others I mix look I was excited when I heard the premise
which by the way they're saying it like as if they created the description to set they make it
sound like as if they created this concept of course uh but like but like you watch the trailer and
you're like this is the fucking same shit from the show it's like it's like overly sexualized it's like
it's it's like people in latex that are supposed to be scary it just looks stupid to me so anyway
with with with such a lack of uh truly good horror anthologies out there I'd say this one
uh is it's definitely worth a watch some of the episodes are really great some of them are whatever
first episode in particular I thought was awesome um and I'd put it like sort of in that realm of like
fear itself or masters of horror where it's a little less I think masters of horror might be a
little bit better but it's it's up and down but but it's worth a watch all right uh my last is
documentary now streaming on showtime uh John McAfee recently either killed himself or was killed
yes guy who invented the McAfee spyware software um he so I'm reading here he went for millionaire
software mogul to yogi curts like jungle recluse to potential murderer and most recently a
prospective presidential candidate for the American libertarian party weirdly I did not know anything
about John McAfee um a couple friends of mine I guess had really studied the case and we kind of
told me some stuff I watched the doc it's a little dull you know they're following kind of it's
mostly following his time basically living in the jungle presumably having people killed uh taking
drugs getting increasingly paranoid etc the one thing that's gonna really stick with me about old
John McAfee is the five -minute segment in the middle of this where they discuss all of the very young
prostitutes that he would pay to have sex with and one after the other these women describe that none
of them actually ever had sex with him they laid on their back or he laid on his back underneath a
hammock with a hole cut out under the butt and these women would be asked to lie in the hammock nude
and shit into his open mouth below that's great that's great so this just for five minutes these women
talk about it and they're all clearly kind of embarrassed by it and then it just goes right back
into the story of John McAfee and I'm like that's your story who cares about anything that's your
story exactly right you want to pretend like we care about anti -virus software but all we want to
hear is what caused this man how much sex did he have that eventually he got bored with it and decided
he needed women shitting in his mouth by the way he's another one of these guys like a Jeffrey what's his
face Epstein not in this not in the sense that he molested or raped or anything but in the sense that
this was a guy that was being extradited back to testify in America and essentially killed himself
right yeah you know so um anyway he says in the documentary he's like if if I ever wind up dead you'll
know that I didn't kill myself Jesus Christ that's wild stuff yeah um all right my final film and then
again staying on the horror tip for today this movie is described as a horror movie if you read the
description it's described as the main character being a undercover serial killer it is neither of those
things this is a little picture starring Vince Vaughn called domestic disturbance uh I think I saw
that theatrically even though I remember nothing about it it's from that phase in Vince Vaughn's career
that everybody wanted where he stopped doing comedies yeah and started to do dark characters
right the first time around didn't work at all he was in like the the uh the cell and
and then he was in a lot of stuff like this second time around yeah second time around it worked great
it was all the zollard films and he's been awesome in them yeah um but this is unfortunately one of
that first round it's he plays a the stepdad of a it's Travolta and and uh Vaughn
who are not bad in the movie it's just a shit movie man it's just it goes nowhere it's the description
I read was a young boy realizes his stepfather is a serial killer and has to expose him I was like
that sounds interesting that sounds like a horror film it's not he's an ex like con man who is getting
exploited by Steve Buscemi uh and uh and uh and he murders Steve Buscemi so it's as to cut the paper
trail off right and the kid witnesses the murder um and that's kind of it and there's there's a
getting into trouble which is why nobody would believe him which doesn't really go anywhere there's
a whole thing that john Travolta is a recovering alcoholic all they do is show him one time have one
drink and somebody go don't go down this road again and he's just like okay I won't and that's it um
um Vaughn it like doesn't make sense why like he's like somehow left why he left the life of crime
that he did to live with with the with the it's the lady I forget her name but it's the meat the
fuckers uh why uh lady tarry polo yeah like why he is one it's a real nothing of an actress no offense
to miss polo yeah she's okay you know like it's like why did he want to come marry tarry polo and
raise the step kid like yeah why wouldn't he just give Steve Buscemi his cut of the money and then
on top of all of it it's like Vince Vaughn's like in this on top it's like the dentist it's like the
dentist too when he goes to the town so then like but then on like top of all that Vince Vaughn is like
running for like mayor and everybody loves him it's just it's just a dumb fucking who gives a shit movie
you don't care it's up there with you know like what lies beneath in the like lackluster suspense
department where you just don't care at all oh I gotta say I like what lies beneath but okay I hated
it anything I was like fuck you Zemeckis how dare you make Harrison Ford a bad guy I never want to
see Harrison Ford be a bad guy well that's your own shit I thought that was a really cool movie actually
I thought it started cool and then it got yeah all right then maybe this is more along the lines
of hearts in Atlantis there we go what's the one random hearts where he's on the plane random
hearts was absolutely terrible yeah yeah yeah there was a period I mean you want to talk about a
bad time for movies like 99 was a great year but all the commercial movies from like 99 to
oh four and domestic disturbance I just looked it up as oh one yeah how many thrillers were there
with yeah some combination of Travolta Sam Jackson Vince Vaughn and Tommy Lee Jones those
Freeman out Freeman came into his own Freeman yeah actually Judd of course had her like three movies
a year yeah but they would just sort of almost like like pop them into these movies whether they fit or
not you know they they don't there always be a courtroom section whether it needed a courtroom section
not where everybody's yelling at each other on the stand Jean Hackman did a lot of these two Anthony
Hopkins did a longest time it was Hopkins on the left side of the screen and a young actor on the right
it was Gosling it was Cuba good in junior it was just anybody and these movies were just they were all
the same they had the exact same low level of thrills low level of chills the story sucked my favorite
thing about that's of Atlantis is it's based on a Stephen King story that in the book it ties into
the dark tower yes how was this the what they're not discussing it they just swept it under the rug
but they fucked up the dark tower movie so bad yeah which I didn't see that it maybe do it for
the show you watch it I tried man it's terrible it's terrible it's not a fun it's it's terrible it's
fun terrible I knew when an adaptation of 12 ,000 page books presented us with an 85 minute movie that
probably they had made some mistakes but then Ron Howard or somebody was gonna make a dark tower
show for Amazon and they were way down the line in producing this thing or pre -production and they
that's probably my least favorite genre of Stephen King sub -genre but it sucks for the fans that's
such a potentially lucrative franchise they just blew it and then we're like ah fuck it
well before we get into amusement park one more thing about low rent thrillers
and I beg you I sent you the trailer I beg you please can we do it on the show the
film coming out called crying story yeah by the way it could there be a more generic title it
doesn't even seem to apply to what's going on it's terrible it's and it's it's it stars Richard
Drifus as like in like in the Liam Neesam type action role but also as an ex mobster
Richard Drifus walking around doing this Brooklyn accent that literally sounds like what you're
like acting teacher would do in your college course he's like walking around like I'll take care
of it okay of a it's like so ridiculous and then um Mira Sorvino shows up and I'm sorry to say it
I'm sorry to say it Drifus stinks in the trailer I think he stinks half the time sometimes he
nails something so I thought Mira Sorvino hadn't been working out of either choice or some sort of
evil black ball thing that Harvey Weinstein did not she isn't acting because she stinks
she's so bad at this trailer it's like she's like dad dad is everything okay she places daughter I'm
like this I was watching this tell I was laughing so hard and how bad this fucking movie looks
what's the last line of the trailer the funniest of all it didn't even make sense because I sent
it to people too then the last line of the trailer he's uh he's like why oh she she goes everyone that
you touch winds up dead and he screams back at her that's life that doesn't make sense it's it's
the closing line of the trailer and it simply doesn't make sense it kind of sounds cool if you're
an idiot but everything you touch winds up dead that's life doesn't make sense I'm sorry Richard
Drifus was good in jaws close encounters and Mr. Holland's opus Mira Sorvino was fantastic in
mighty Aphrodite and that is where it ends for both of them for me that's it I think both of us has
come together in this in this crime story Richard Drifus the least threatening looking man even think
think back to Richard Drifus in his prime being a heavy for the mob think of jaws Richard Drifus as
being it's absurd he's 4 -11 he's 86 years old but I I love Dick Drifus I haven't liked
him anything in the last time I even saw him in a theatrical release I think was the crew which we've
discussed on this show he's doing that kind of voice again he is but Sorvino and Drifus even though
they're both considered fine dramatic actors in my opinion are excellent comedic actors and not much
more like Sorvino Sorvino I think is brilliant in in Romeo and Michelle's high school reunion which
is great and fantastic movie you're right I forgot about it she's great in mighty Aphrodite and I think
obviously the Weinstein thing kind of took her confidence away she got cast in a CBS drama right
after the Weinstein stuff and they recast her so I think it's a mix of her losing her mojo and also
just never being that good of a dramatic actress yeah I mean that's you're you're really
stinking up the scenery if you're getting cast after the Weinstein controversy and then they
recast you I know I mean that's that goes to show you how thinly veiled any of these gestures in Hollywood
are I mean they're really just so full of shit yeah but Dick Dick Drifus you left off what about Bob
which is one of the greatest slow -burned comedic performances I've ever seen never been in the movie
never was a big fan of that or Groundhog Day I find I just don't know they don't grab me not saying
they're bad they don't grab me I'm not a fan that's all is it the kind of PG nature of them that
they're both like families I feel like there are comedies that were that should have been way
edgier than they were and they just never capture it for me like it's kind of like it's about
Bob does end up end with Bill Murray blowing up his home and winding up in an insane asylum it's
pretty dark movie I mean it's they fit right into that I I like Top Hat entertainment on YouTube as
well it's a great channel and the kid does awesome reviews of things and he's got a new series on
their called almost cult classics and he does funny farm great and he talks about how funny farm
like never quite it's a great movie but it never quite cut the cheese because it was supposed to
be way edgier and way raunchier yeah and then the director was like no we're going to class this
thing up and I feel like funny farms a good example of a movie like that the great outdoors is a good
move example of a movie like that whereas I find some huge laughs in those movies and I enjoy them
what about Bob is one of those films where I'm like it never quite captures the edge for me that I
wanted it to capture like I just for some reason just don't enjoy it at all I really deeply deeply
deeply love what about Bob I got a different with you but the um that's fine the what did you
mention prior Joe what movie funny farm yeah sorry uh no there's a real quick there's a pure cinema
podcast uh put on kind of buy the new Beverly cinema and once every couple months Tarantino comes on
and does a four hour podcast with them where he talks about lost gems and stuff they're great to listen
to especially going to walk because there's still long but uh on the recent one Tarantino talks about
how much he loves funny farm for over a half an hour that's pretty cool the man loves funny farm I
always liked it a lot uh I remember Cisco neighbor being like this is the only funny Chevy chase movie
and I was like you guys don't get comedy you're stupid but yeah I remember that too uh and there's
some really funny scenes in funny farm I want to watch it again after watching this hats off top I
think it's hats off entertainment sorry not top head editor I want to watch it again because he
talks about how like in the third act it suddenly becomes a Christmas movie and it's awesome for that
read that's one of the great things about it and just seeing the scenes in it I forgot like oh yeah
it's really funny when he pulls that eel out of the lake with the fish fishing like you know yeah there's
some really funny when he drops his what when he tries to carry over the threshold and drops her
they get so many laughs out of the it's it's a two it's a two half door but the top half and the
bottom half open separately they get so many funny jokes out of that but yeah a lot of ball hits on
the door knob yeah what was the scene where he has to eat sheep balls sheep testicles and that's
that's the big gross out scene it was written by Jeffrey Bowam who we've discussed on the show he
died at like 52 he wrote last crusade lethal weapon two all these amazing movies and he wrote funny
farm and he wrote it apparently very R rated the ball eating scene was like the norm and basically
the director who George Roy Hill who had done the sting and all these classy things was like no no
we're gonna pull the ball stuff way back and you know it works the movie is a good blend of like family
film and gross out film and I think it's very funny yeah it's based on a book yeah that's right the guy
also wrote uh there's another book he wrote that was we didn't know comedy I was like what like it
was just weird Tarantino discusses how there's Chevy Chase the reason they move to the titular funny
farm is that Chevy Chase wants to write a novel or write a screenplay one of the other and at several
points he describes the plot of it and Tarantino is like I swear to fucking God he's describing
reservoir dogs so I do want to watch it again to see if that's accurate but he's Tarantino is like
the whole time everybody's telling him the movie sounds bad I'm going this movie sounds fucking us
it's reservoir dog yeah that's that's really funny yeah there's a lot yeah there's a scene where
I completely forgot about where the sheriff is like the sheriff of the town is like a bumbling idiot
and you can't the gag as he can't drive and there's a scene where he pulls up to a crime scene and parks
in the lake gets out of the car and just walks no like god damn it or anything just gets out and walks
through the water back onto the land as if it was just like a normal parking spot yeah it was like
that's that's a really funny joke man that's a really really funny joke it's a lot of great recurring
gags they got a mailman who just throws the mail out the window of his his car as he drives by
and there's lots of funny bits we need to get to the amusement park though
or Jay Romero's the amusement park the amusement park let me
minute film yeah when I saw this was 54 minutes I was ecstatic but let me give you a very brief back
story and I am pulling this not from the Wikipedia which is actually pretty underdeveloped but a
fantastic review on rogerebert .com by great writer named scout to foya want to give him the credit
you can read much more about the history of this movie which is currently streaming on shutter
but what's important to note because I was confused when the movie started I had to do a pause and
say what am I even looking at here right um so here's here's the very brief gist he had not done dawn
of the dead yet Romero but he had done the crazies yeah look here the crazies which I don't love
it's okay I like to make better to be honest same but um you know he always did politically minded
movies Romero politically minded horror movies he's he didn't really get appreciation till after his
death so there's an interest in his lost work this was not designed to be a horror movie but in 1973
a Pittsburgh based organization called Lutheran Services approached George Romero who lived in
Pittsburgh yeah to ask if he'd shoot something for them about all the ways society discriminates
against the elderly Romero just wanted to work he was happy to have a good budget so he made the
amusement park which when you watch it that makes a lot of sense it is a very almost stressful movie
about what everyday life is like for the elderly and the Lutherans when they saw it were appalled
horrified disgusted and refused to release the movie Romero was moving on to other projects so he
didn't fight them about it any moved on and recently the film was found and sort of rediscovered
is it a lost masterpiece in my mind absolutely not but when you when you know the backstory that it
was made to kind of show the the elderly abuse basically that goes on and how we kind of just this
you know in my opinion the Simpsons did this better than anybody all the jokes about Grandpa Simpson
at the home were so dark and so funny um this is really sad it's really there's nothing scary
in it per se there's no there's no like things jumping out at you but it's just it's kind of taking you
inside the mindset of when your mind starts to go when you go out in public and everything's kind of
scary um it doesn't use the word dementia or Alzheimer's but you get the feeling they're kind of
commenting on that as well oh they definitely are they yeah there's there's some hard dementia things in
it yeah I thought um I mean look it's that we we've talked about it before that this hyperbole that
happens with the way they describe movies these days it's like a John Goodman and Matt and A level
of exploitation at this point yeah of language but you know I'm hearing about this thing getting
released it's called the lost film his people it's being referred to as his most terrifying movie he's
ever made yeah it's being referred to as a horror film it's none of these things uh it's confusing
at the opening when you see a guy telling you the main actor telling you what the movie's about
which is odd right because if you don't know the backstory this Lutheran thing you're like why is the
guy explaining it to me like yeah then you watch it and you quickly realize like oh I kept thinking
was like this seems like a short film he made about how old people get treated poorly and it's an
interesting metaphor with the amusement park but it's not scary no and then I was like but I was like the
one part that was was was really a truly freaky and so if you haven't seen it spoilers are coming but
the it starts with an old man all beat up and bruised and bloody and then his a better version of
himself comes into the room as that man's crying and he says to himself I'm gonna go outside and the
guy says you don't want to go out there trust me and the old man says I'll see for myself and he goes out
so right off the bat you kind of know I know where this is going this guy that just walked out the door
is gonna end up being the guy at the end of the movie all beat up but like you know and then his other
previous self will come through the door and it'll end where it starts but
but what's gonna happen so it goes out into the amusement park and the amusement park all the
attractions are represent mistreatment of old people in one way or another so like to get your tickets
to do any of the rides or attractions you have to give them your belongings and they undersell you
on all your belongings you know and so then you don't have enough tickets and then the bumper cars
represent like old people you know like you go in the bumper cars but then the young people
are mad at you when you crash into them if you're old and they say you can't see and you can't you
shouldn't be driving and all this stuff so on and so forth you get to just the truly want the one
truly terrifying sequence I thought was when the young couple goes to the fortune teller and says we're
deeply in love show us everything show us our life together and it cuts to them in their 80s
and though the wife is in a panic and calling the doctor and saying my husband doesn't recognize
me anymore and I was like wow that's really haunting and really interesting and really cool
outside of that it's basically just an old man getting shit on for about 55 minutes
yeah and it's I thought as I was watching it okay this looks really bad it looks like a lot of movies
from like 1973 a low budget movie back then looks so much worse than a low budget movie right now
you know like you can make a movie on an iPhone that looks incredible I while I was watching this I
said I could never love a movie that looked like this like it's it looks like it would they had
the shit filter over the camera like everything's kind of brown and grainy and they did a good job
with the you know I don't know why I keep messing up that word with the remaster whatever you know
I'm sure they brought it back from some really crummy film elements you're in time sorry because that
this was this this that that problem that you're talking about the visual problem you're talking about
that starts with in the late 60s when they transition from black and white yes to color and all
of a sudden all these things you kind of hide in whatever are really exposed on cheap home yeah
everything looks brown like seepia atoned and me that's just very hard to watch I've never
loved a movie that looked like that but yeah it's it for Romero completists you're gonna want to I mean
you're gonna be very excited to watch this it's like a lost movie by a great horror director
just know what you're getting into it's it's it definitely falls somewhere between educational film
made for Lutherans and horror movie it's it's not really either um but as as sort of a heavy
handed metaphor for aging for Alzheimer's it's effective but it's not scary and it's not something
you need to rush out and see unless you really love Romero and who doesn't then it's worth 54
minutes of your time yeah it's a it's a nice film it's you know it's a good piece of work it's just
it's just I was just upset that it was I was kind of sold a bill of goods right that it was this
lost horror masterpiece and and how dare you call it as most terrifying and give me a break come on man
I read a similar review that gave it five out of five stars and it kept it kept using the phrase
brilliantly edited I'm like guys what I don't think even Romero would say this was brilliantly
edited he just put the scenes together it had some cool cutaway stuff and at some of those cool
like flash inserts and you know brilliance too strong a word I think it's a well put together film
for what it is I don't think it's much and and it was never his intention for it to be much more
than what it is which is basically a little art house picture that creatively talks about the
the mistreatment of old people so it's not Romero's fault but these people I mean it's not come on
five out of fucking five give me a break it's like guys it's fine to find a little piece of work
worth seeing I don't think you're gonna throw on again I can't imagine ever being like let's put on
the amusement park tonight no even the poster is terrible the old man's head being unzipped and there's
a carousel inside his brain or whatever I was like come on but my issue is where the fuck is the
dawn of the dead blue ray you know I I watched it when I was a kid on VHS and I just recently watched
it on YouTube because you can't get one of the greatest hormones of all time on blue ray where is it
blue ray or was it well it's rare enough that it costs $500 to buy it so it's out of print okay
right yeah it's time criterion somebody I wonder if DVD is worth money I have like one of those like
cool like cardboard cutout case DVD things I'd look it up the bluer is worth a lot I think the DVD's
probably worth 50 60 but look it up anyway folks that's our show we'll be back in the next episode
we're covering I think you should leave season two and we'll talk a little bit about season one
to also the surreal sketch comedy show that certainly has many horror elements from Tim Robins Robinson
yes many as man and showbiz these days uh joderosa comedy on twitter and instagram give a follow if you
like if you're at sold out so never mind won't not gonna plug that if you're in I think there's
some tickets left for skankfest day passes in November at the secret group in Houston Texas amazing
venue an amazing lineup who's gonna be there jay ocherson eddie pepettone uh dug stand hope
jimmar neighbors uh Jessica kirson um bob saggett it's gonna be a hell of a good time so come out for
that if you're if you're able to I'm the patrick walsh on twitter and instagram you can hear me on my
good buddy scott wineberg's podcast one of the best horror film writers there is the best follow on
twitter if you're a horror movie fan um and we he has a new podcast called over hated where we take a
second look at movies that not we i mean it's his podcast but take a look at movies that were perhaps
unjustly hated like he goes back with a guest and they watch glee and say did this deserve to be
shot on in the way that it was me and scott did uh Freddie got fingered which I talked about a little
bit on this show but uh check that out and support scott i think it's patreon only but he he's great
that's it for me we will be back as joe just said with i think he should leave we'll see you next time
we'll see you in hell