Welcome to We'll See You in Hell. It's a special Q &A edition. We'll be answering
your questions this episode. Across from me is Mr. Patrick Walsh. Across the
country. Yes, Pat Walsh here in Los Angeles. The city hasn't really come back to life post -strike,
I gotta say. I still feel like I'm living in some sort of zombie apocalypse out here. How's
New York treating you? Had a good time out there at NYC, by the way, and thanks to all who came to
live show. It was fun. My name's Joe DeRosa. I thought when I said your name, you say my name.
It didn't happen. Oh, sorry. Thought I'd throw it to you, because that's what Siskel and Ebert
used to do, is go across from me is Gene Siskel, then Siskel would go, and then that's Roger Ebert.
No, no, you're wrong. He would say, and I'm Roger Ebert of the Chicago Tribune. They would
each introduce themselves. I feel like sometimes they did the flip. Alright. No, never. I don't
know. Regardless, we've whittled the questions down a little bit. Our last time we were going
through and it got a little frustrating because we were seeing stuff that had been asked before,
but that's not on you. We've been doing these Q &As for over five years, so we're gonna get a little
repeats. But if you don't hear your cue today, it's simply because we've already answered it.
I think it's on them. I blame them. I do too, but they are paying us, so I thought I would at least
try to couch it in niceness. New York was quite fun. We're gonna put the episode up
soon, this month, later this month. But yeah, it was a good time, and I had a good time with you,
Pat. We had a nice time. We went to, what did we do? We had the day at Arlene's where we did
our thing and all the other acts performed. We did. You know what, Joe? Let's talk New
York on the next step. Okay, good point. You know? We got questions. I agree. All right. Do
I sound okay on your end? It's a little boomy on my end, but I'm getting reverb in the room.
You sound fine. You sound fine to me. Let's kick things off. Let's kick things off. Let's
just let's take that cold plunge. Okay. You got your friends all talking to you about the cold
plunge, Joe? A lot of people are talking about cold plunge, venison meat. Okay, I haven't heard
that one. And a lot of man stuff. Cold plunge, venison. Yeah. It's getting to be like the 80s
all over again, where there's just like a million fads that come and go. None of them really stick.
None of them really work. Just people desperate to be happy and shape. I feel something again.
I had a thing I was working on in my act. I still haven't gotten it down, but you know,
people keep saying now is like the 60s. They'll be like, this is like the turbulent 60s all over
again. I'm like, we've blown pit. This is like the dust bowl. This is insane. The shit I'm seeing
online, watching a guy play drums, guitar, and harmonica all at the same time. Like it's crazy,
like carnival shit out there right now. Like he's doing it for money? I don't know. Like when you
were talking about how crazy the world is right now, the next words out of your mouth, I did not
expect to be a guy playing three instruments at once. I saw a guy, I saw a guy play. This is the
sort of crux of the joke is I was on Instagram and I saw a guy playing Queens of the Stone Age
covers. He's playing drums, guitar, and singing all at the same time. And it was excellent. And
to gain attention in such an odd way. Like it's so weird.
Yeah. I keep thinking of the Fred Willard character in the Tim Robinson sketch,
playing the organ while he's breaking his plates over his head or something like that.
All right. Question one. A lot of good questions, folks. And we always thank you for these. They're
fun. We're going to try not to rush through it. Last time we thought we had to like hit everyone,
this one should go smoother. What is your favorite classic universal monster movie?
I got the 100 movie set, which you can find usually for about 50 bucks on Amazon.
And there's so many of them I haven't seen. I've only seen the core eight, like your basic list.
And my favorite is going to have to be the invisible man. I just think it's hilarious
and dark and awesome. I love it. I love when an asshole, the invisible man is like his
power. Other than being visible, his power is like being a dick, which I love.
I like the invisible man quite a bit. I guess I would say Bride of Frankenstein,
or which is, you know, that's the one everybody says. I feel a little cheap saying that, but
but then also the Wolfman is my favorite of the characters. So I guess I'd maybe have to say
Wolfman and Abbot and Castello meet Frankenstein is probably my favorite of all time.
Yep. It's not really scary, but it's just so well done and so funny. So love it.
If the two of you were in a misery situation, who says we're not folks who would be Paul Sheldon
and who would be any Wilkes? I think that would fully depend on our on our mood on the day. I
easily be a victim or a brutalizer. I agree. Both of us have metaphorically torched the other man's
work, burned his life in front of him, made the other man cry. Yeah. Both of us have hobbled one
another. Did you know what the hobbling isn't in the book? I didn't know that. In the book,
it's just a hatchet. She just cuts his foot off. Yeah. And I guess they thought that would be too
horror movie -ish and the hobbling is so much cooler and more effective. It was a great switch.
Yeah. That is what kind of makes the movie special. If they had hacked his foot off
suddenly an hour in, in a movie that has no real extreme violence in it, that probably would have
been off -putting to say the least. I agree. I think we're both, and I also think we both have
a little bit of the straight story guy in us, the good -hearted sheriff. Yes. Who will be executed
before the end? Yes. Maybe by a fan. Who knows? I went out, I'll talk about that the next time.
I was going to tell a little date story. Okay. Hey boys, I just watched Flesh and Blood for the
first time, intense, but it made me want to ask, what's your favorite Paul Verhoeven film? So this
is the OG Flesh and Blood with Rucker Hauer and Jennifer Jason Lee. Do you have a ranking of his
movies? That's a little involved, but you know, favorite Verhoeven for me
is probably Basic Instinct, to be honest. You know, I love the erotic thrillers,
but that whole, I love his just American trash period of Robocop, Total Recall, Showgirls,
you know, he had a real prime there. And I think he did better work in America than he did in his
homeland. Frankly, I know a lot of purists would disagree, but I just love his big American trash
with tits and violence. I never saw Flesh and Blood, so I can't speak to it, but Robocop,
of the ones I've seen, undoubtedly Robocop is the one. Yeah. Hollow Man, not great. He's actually,
he's back to good. I mean, his last several movies have been excellent, I think. I love that last
one. He just went in on Lesbian Nuns. He was like, fuck it. I loved it. I loved it so much.
Who can do the better Australian accent? I have a feeling they're both going to be bad.
I'll start. Well, you got to start, to get into it, you got to go, that's not a knife.
And then, so which do you prefer, Crocodile Dundee or Crocodile Dundee 2?
I can't tell if that was good or bad. Honestly, I can't tell.
Well, you want to do New Zealand, which is like, no, no.
I got, I'll say, yeah, you boys want to go to the ACDC show, do yous?
I think that's Liverpool that you're doing.
It all mixes together. It does. It does. My manager's girlfriend has an accent. I can't,
I don't know if she's from England or Australia. I still don't know. Who does?
My manager's girlfriend. I can't tell what goddamn country she's from.
It can be tricky. I saw some guy on TikTok do like all the different variants of English accent.
You know, he's like, this is the Cockney, this is the, you know, then there was a million of them.
So it's hard to tell sometimes.
There's a thing where on the, what's his face? Comedy for drummers. What's his name? Fred Armisen.
Yeah.
It's one of the most amazing things I've ever seen. He does accents of the United,
North American United States, and he just, he goes from state to state.
As he's describing the state, he's describing the accent and he's changing into the accent.
And he does it seamlessly through every state. It's crazy. Yeah. It's so crazy.
It's really good. I've never seen that special.
If you were to cast a new and final Indiana Jones movie, who would you cast as the antagonists and why?
Maybe we'll just pick one antagonist. Hmm.
I would, I, you know who I'd love to, I'd love to see Anthony Hopkins as like,
He popped into my head too.
Yeah. Wicked mastermind, dying collector of some kind, like an old version of like
Belloc from Raiders, like that fights Indy with his mind, of course.
Yeah. Yeah.
That's, and I mean, at this age, Indy's fighting with his mind. I'd like to see
two gents like that square off.
You know who a young Indy would have fought is army hammer.
Army hammer just screams Nazi who's six foot four.
I've been very obsessed over the last week or so with the idea of casting Morgan Freeman as the
devil in something. I've never seen Morgan Freeman play a bad guy. He's played God. How great would
it be to see him play the devil in something or somebody like truly sinister? I bet he'd be great
at it. He would. I mean, the first time I saw Morgan Freeman, he was playing a pimp in street
smart with Christopher Reeve and he was horrifying. That was the first time I ever saw him in anything,
but Morgan Freeman now is going the Bruce Willis route. He just does direct to DVD shit,
which I find odd and kind of sad. Yeah.
Um, any thoughts on a hellion fest? Uh, you know, we're, we just did sort of that kind of a horror
fest, but yeah, we, we, we hear you on the live shows. You know, somebody on here was like, will
you ever do an LA show guys? We've done several LA shows. Um, we do our best. We live so far apart
that we do the live shows when we can. Um, but a hellion fest would be a blast, not ruling it out.
Who are your favorite male and female classic movie stars, meaning pre 1970?
Oh, well, easy. Uh, Jack Lemmon, uh, easily lemon and, and Mathal. I, I, I put them neck
and neck and then female, uh, God, there's, I mean, can we count Streep in there or is she,
I mean, no, she's a seventies actress. It says pre 70, pre 70. Yeah. Um,
I'm going to lemon and Stuart, Jimmy Stewart. Um, and then for the ladies, I gotta go
with Catherine Hepburn. I'm not a huge Audrey guy. I love Catherine say a tippy, uh,
Hendron. Yeah. Uh, yeah. And then I almost said Hepburn because you said Hepburn.
Yeah. Um, I mean, I like all the, all the Hitchcock women very much. Um, so did he,
you know, it's a tough, uh, it feels weird to say it. It's kind of a tough, well, actually,
you know, no duck, uh, you know, Carol Burnett obviously is, you know, uh, but I don't know if
she's a movie star, but not really, but I'll allow it, but it's tough. I mean, it's, it's funny to
say that the pre seventies, it's kind of hard to, to name starlet, you know, there's Betty Davis.
There's the, like the super iconic ones, but you know, obviously, uh, leading ladies were,
were a little harder to find back then. Yeah. Yeah. All right. Fair enough. Strange question,
but the guys know movies and shows. So when people are eating in a movie or show who makes
the food, is it good? What happens to the food after the scene is done? Um, I can speak for the
television world, uh, props makes the food or at least acquires the food. Generally, if the actor
has to actually eat and swallow, they will clear what the actor wants. So if the actor is a
vegetarian and they have to eat a hamburger, they'll make amends for that. Um, if they're on
a strict diet, they'll make a burger out of, you know, quinoa or whatever they got to do. Um,
and then generally, especially like in a scene like where Tony Soprano is eating a giant plate
of spaghetti or something, there'll be a spit bucket, which is disgusting, but these actors
can't be eating plate after plate of spaghetti, you know? So there you go. That's, that's my
knowledge on it. I think that's just, yeah, that's about it. The actor has the option. I just watched
an interview with David Hyde Pierce where he was talking about shooting Julia. Yeah. And they were
talking about how like craft services actually made Julia, uh, child's recipes. Okay. So it was
when they were eating the food and, and, and they were talking about how delicious it was. And he
was like, I ate 83 dumplings in that scene because we kept it, you know, I, I don't know. Yeah. I
don't know. You can keep eating if you want. I drank so much grape juice once in a scene where
I was shooting. I was, the gag was I was downing my wine and then I had explosive diarrhea because
you know, I drank a whole jug of Welch's. It's not a great story, but. Was it purple?
Yeah. It was, it sucked. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. Um, what is the worst horror cliche that,
that might be one I missed. I feel like we've done that, but for me lately, it's,
it's grief and trauma as a metaphor, which is, I think every horror movie that has been released
in the last couple of years. I will go to what I said, uh, in, uh, when the, in the exorcist
believer review, my new favorite worst horror trope is the Mexican priest who lives in America
speaks as if he just got here yesterday. That, you know, that the thickly accented Mexican priest
has now replaced the Jamaican, you know, uh, mystic woman that knows everything. Sure. Sure.
Um, top five Cohen bros movies. Um, I'm not going to rank them just because that's too
difficult in the moment, but mine are raising Arizona Fargo, the big Lebowski, no country for
men and a serious man. I will go Lebowski, Barton Fink, uh, No Cunch, um, Burn After Reading,
a huge fan of Burn After Reading and, uh,
uh, maybe Miller's Crossing or, um, yeah, maybe Miller's Crossing. I think we're raised. I like
raising Arizona quite a bit too. This is a long one. Is there a specific episode or discussion
argument that stands out to either of you as one of your favorites or as particularly,
particularly memorable? If nothing comes to mind, my backup question is what are your middle names?
Uh, mine is John. I don't know about favorite episode. I have all kinds of favorite moments.
Um, Bert Young passed recently. I loved recounting that night of his one act play
at the Mexican restaurant slash theater. Um, of course, you know, I think my, my favorites
in many cases would be the fan's favorites, making fun of my dad's Christmas jacket. You know,
we had a lot of good times throughout the years, of course.
I will go with, uh, when Pat, cause I've quoted it so many times and then we named a segment after
it. But when Pat very first said Rex Reed is a, just a mean old bitch. I mean, that made me laugh
really hard and it stuck with me. So, uh, that's, that's probably my favorite moment. It's,
it's definitely the thing I've quoted most to people when Pat's not around. And I talk about
that in a positive way. Jared. It's not a real name. Uh, pulled that out of her ass.
Jared is a real name. Not Jared. Jared. G E R A D. Look it up. G E R A D. Yeah, that's not a real
name. Wow. Okay. Interesting. I've never heard, never asked that. I think she meant Gerard and
fucked it up. Honestly, I think that's what happened. Yeah. That's like guys. Friendships
are so weird. You know, you can spend like years with someone and never even occur to you to ask
their middle name. And I feel like women ask these questions that women know everything about their
friends and guys know very little. Yeah. Well, that's why so many, that's why so many, you know,
that's why so many sitcoms are based on that, on that exact thing. Yeah. You know, like the,
everything the man forgets everything. Uh, what are your predictions for the film
and or entertainment industry in the year ahead?
Feel like we've kind of hit that from all sides. Uh, but I don't think it's good. I think that,
you know, the streaming thing is going to implode shortly. Uh, there are already people in Congress
talking about this fucking John Cena Wiley Coyote movie. Like that's now been a subject
at Congress. They're like, you can't keep making $70 million movies and then getting tax write -offs
of 30 million. You can't do that. So these little tactics that they're using to get around the
guilds and the strikes and everything are going to get worse, but they're already on such shaky
ground. I think there will be some sort of massive collapse of the entertainment industry in our,
my lifetime. I don't know how soon, but, um, yeah, we're going to be without new movies.
It's going to be another mini pandemic. There's going to be nothing for six months. Um, you know,
it's a dark time. What can we say? Well, at least the rebooting Garfield again. Thank God.
Never got it right. Once the only time I got it right was on Saturday morning, CBS.
Oh my God. Oh my God. The trailer is just. Oh, you're in the trailer. Yeah. It's out.
So wait, is Samuel L. Jackson, John, as you were speculating?
No, it's even remember that drunk on Halloween. Yeah. Yeah.
It's completely Jackson's playing John. There's no way it's, it's, it's almost as crazy.
It's, it's fully animated. I don't know who's voicing John. Chris Pratt, who should be voicing
John is voicing Garfield, which makes no sense. Samuel Jackson would be a decent Garfield.
Samuel Jackson is playing Garfield's father. Okay. So like his father moves in with them
and they don't have a good relationship. I mean, don't get me started.
His father moves in, like John adopts him. I don't fucking know. I just, there's, there's,
they run into his dad on a train and then, and then, and then like there's, you know,
they're all in the house together in the trailer.
All right. Yeah. I'll, I don't know. I used to love Garfield so much. I actually didn't even
see the Bill Murray version. I just loved the story that he thought the Coen brothers were directing.
Who has been added to the list of actors you're sick of?
Adam Driver has been mentioned in the past. Personally, I'll never watch a Hanks film again.
Damon is on the knife's edge as well. Yeah. I mean, we're just at a time where there's,
it seems like the pool of stars is tiny because they keep trying to grow it and nobody's really
taking. Like, I don't think we're going to still be following Jacob Elordi's career in 10 years.
You know what I mean? I don't think these people are going to go the distance. So
I'm sick of a lot of people, you know, there, there's almost nobody when I watch a trailer
anymore who I'm like, Ooh, great. He's in this or she's in this. It's very rare these days.
And so I can't really add just one person. I'm sick of a lot of actors right now.
And, you know, it's like they don't, you know, I just watched the thing with Tarantino
from a long time, so very old, but he talks about this. He goes, you know, these studios,
they have lists. And he goes, that's why you see the same five people in every movie.
Yeah. And he goes, he goes, and he goes, and I don't remember, he goes, they don't remember
you because you're good. They just reuse you because you're in the other movie. He goes,
I have a much bigger list because I remember everybody I've ever seen that's good. Yeah.
And I will use anybody I think is right for something. Now, he also kind of has his pool
of people, but he does hold fairly true to that. You know, I don't think, for instance, I don't
think Kurt Russell would have the mainstream career he's having right now that wasn't for
Tarantino bringing him back in with, you know, Kurt Russell was respected, but you know, I think
Kurt Russell getting to play Santa Claus and being all these different things has a lot to do with
Tarantino's use of him in Hateful Eight and whatever. So excuse me. So. But.
But he's right. And it's just it's just they don't even use people that are good repeatedly.
Like, you know, this Albert Brooks documentary is a great example. I haven't seen it yet, but
I've heard about it. And, you know, I know that there's a section in it where they talk about
a good dramatic actor, Albert Brooks is, and he is. So why the fuck has he only been in two movies
playing a dramatic part? It's probably because they won't use him. I don't think it's because
Albert Brooks doesn't want to work. You know, that's totally it. I mean, I mean, winding ref
and getting him to play the villain in Drive where he was incredible. And if he wasn't nominated,
he should have been. I think I think he was. Yeah. It's like. But you know, you can only do
it on a tiny budget. Like even on a TV show, you'll be like, oh, I want to hire that. Like,
I wanted to hire Adrienne Barbeau for something on The Cool Kids. They're like, who the fuck is
that? Like, we're not putting her on the show. Like, what does it matter? She's going to be a
guest star on an episode of the show. And I love her. And she's a legend. And they're like, no.
You know, so that's what it is. You have to have a certain level of power to even cast who you want.
It's so nuts. And then and then, you know, the other side of the Albert Brooks thing is,
now you have an Albert Brooks documentary. Yeah. And they're cutting to Tiffany Haddish
and Nikki Glaser. And Nikki's a friend of mine. I'm not like shitting on Nikki. But
why is Nikki commenting on the career of Albert Brooks? Like, like, this is what I mean. Like,
they just take, they take people that they think are hot, you know, in the scene and they put them
in stuff, whether it makes sense or not. And they just use people to, you know, again,
it's nothing against Nikki or Tiffany. But it's just such a fucking head scratcher to me that
it's a thing about Albert Brooks. And it's not only peppered with people that intimately know
Albert Brooks. And it's probably because they said, well, some of those people are not cool enough.
And we need some fresh faces in here and whatever standard thing. They're like, oh, no, we got to be
able to put young hot comics in the trailer or else nobody's going to watch it. It's sad,
but it's what it is. People have very short attention spans too. It's it kind of sucks.
Yeah. This is I combine two into one here. It's kind of the same question. If Walsh got a sandwich
named after him at Joey Roses, what would go on that bad boy for Joe? If Pat was a sandwich on
your menu, what would he be? So it's basically the same question.
Um, God, I don't like questions like this. It's not to knock the person that sent it in, but I feel
like there's it's tough on the dating game or something. There's not this pressure that I have
to think of some unique sandwich that describes your soul or something. I don't fucking know.
Um, Italian something. I put some Italian meats together. I know he likes Italian meats
and I do, but I'm Irish that I don't approve of on it that he likes that. I don't like to use
banana peppers. Yes. I mean, I'm Irish, so I think I would pick a corned beef with some spice
because I'm spicy. Okay, fair enough. That's fine. What horror movie would either of you remake if
you had full creative control? Ooh, that's a good question. I definitely am not going to pick like
my son went out. I can hear you. I go ahead. I got a battery switch. I would answer, uh,
gotta switches batteries. I don't know if you, well, if I heard it, you heard it. Um,
I don't know. It's funny that this question is asked right now. Um, okay. I have two.
I have two. Okay. The first is creep show. Not a, not a remake. Uh, so this is a little bit of a
but if I had full creative control and I could really do what I want it to do,
I would make a proper creep show, uh, three or four, uh, because tales from the dark side,
the movie is technically creep show four, three. Um, or I would make a new tales from the dark side,
the movie, uh, you know, it was all the same crew on, on, on those franchises. And I would, um,
I would make the version of that, that I think is worth making. Yes. Uh, that is worth making
and not the version that we're getting now with the, uh, with the shutter, uh, TV show.
So creep show, but that's a little bit of a cheat, uh, uh, tried and true, uh, remake
tried and true remake. I would do, and I just watched this and I don't know if it counts as,
I don't know if this counts as a horror, it sort of does, but I would remake the devil and Daniel
Webster. I just got that finally on criterion. Uh, I've always liked the movie quite a bit
upon this rewatch. I was like, I think this might become one of my favorite movies of all time.
And I was like, this would be a fun movie to make again. Uh, I think they made it with Alec
Baldwin. I want to say they did. And Jennifer love Hewitt and Anthony Hopkins and it, but it
was a comedic version called short shortcut to happiness or something like that. I think it'd
be fun to really remake like a, like, I make like a very sinister dark version of that, that story.
But, uh, but those are my two creep show and, and, you know, I, I did two, you only had to do one,
but, okay. Um, well, you know, I'm, I'm really pumped about this new Salem's lot. I hope they
nail it. It's supposedly fucking horrible. Yeah, I'm sure it is. I had to switch my
batteries on my headphones. Excuse me. Stepping away. I'm back. They also said, by the way,
they just said, um, like I just saw one of these articles where like despite delays and the fact
that it might not get released in theaters, Stephen King says Salem's lot is pretty damn good,
even though it's not his book at all. Like it's going to be a fucking disaster. It's going to be
a disaster. They just can't seem to get this shit right. Did you watch bloodlines?
Bloodlines? No, cemetery bloodlines. Oh God. No, it looks, it looks terrible.
You don't want to see a jacked Judd Crandall with an eight pack. Yeah. In 1993.
Um, wait, wait, wait. So what's your, uh, remake? What horror movie would you read? I mean, I said
Salem's lot. Oh, you would remake that? Yeah. Oh wow. Okay. All right. Yeah. All right. Like
I feel like they did a decent job, but it's time. You know, I like the Toby hoop version. Not bad.
Yeah, it's decent. Um, I just don't feel like we've gotten the definitive version. We haven't
gotten the definitive version of a lot of Stephen King stuff. Unfortunately we've gotten bad and
good, but there's a lot out there that they could redo. I'm surprised misery hasn't come up to be
honest with you as a remake with Melissa McCarthy or something, but we'll see what happens there.
It's, it'll happen though. They'll ruin it. Yeah. Um, best movie to watch post breakup,
uh, and hit this person's choice is swingers, which is a great choice. Oh, that's a good one.
Um, you know, I actually needed to get a lot of, uh, just sadness out of myself post, uh,
the most recent big breakup. And I watched this really sad punishing movies like blue Valentine.
Um, stuff like that. I don't find like, I want to laugh about it right away. I want to wallow
and get some of the sadness out. So I go pretty intense. I watched like scenes from a marriage,
the five hour version. I watched, um, blue Valentine marriage story, that kind of shit.
Uh, I don't know that I could, yeah. Oh, sorry. Sorry. No, no, no, it's fine. I, uh,
I would, I would delve as I do when I'm depressed into, uh, sitcoms of the nineties. Uh, and, uh,
I'd go on a nice Frasier binge or a rewatch of Seinfeld or something like that. Uh, take my
mind off of things, make me happy, order some fried chicken in a bucket, sit there, enjoy myself,
that kind of. Yeah. Yeah. Make sure that no one else will love you again. Yep. That's the goal.
Uh, best needle drop in a movie, meaning like soundtrack song used most perfectly and
effectively, et cetera. It's gotta be, nothing has ever topped the beginning of pulp fiction.
I mean, it's just like, yeah, it's like, I remember sitting in the theater opening night,
seeing that being like, Jesus Christ. Yeah. You know? Yeah. I got a few, I mean, I had a similar
jolting up in my seat thing for the departed. We've talked about that insane. I don't even
love the drop hit Murphy's. I don't even like them really, but it's just, it was hearing a punk song
in a Scorsese movie. Same thing with my way and good fellows. It just kind of throws you off a
little bit and it was very exciting. And the fact that that credits hits like 40 minutes into the
movie. Um, beyond that, I love the use of ELO's showdown in Kingpin. Oh yeah. That is a montage
for the ages. And then also good fellows, the, the, the beginning. Yeah. Rags to riches. I mean,
it's like, yeah, yeah, yeah. You're off to the races. Um, yeah. Scorsese is, is kind of the
master of that when he learns to leave the Rolling Stones down, you know, can't, can't use them every
time. Have either of you seen a Showtime masters of horror series? If yes, any favorites or dog
episodes in your opinion? Yes. I've seen three or four. Um, and I, I saw that really just depraved,
disgusting, uh, take, take, take the Kishi McKay one. Uh, I saw a couple of the John Carpenter's.
I saw a John Landis one with George Went, I think. Um, none of them that I saw blew me away,
but it's been a while and I didn't, I don't remember anyone being awful or anything,
but I wish there were more shows like it. I own the entire series. I bought it during,
uh, COVID. Yeah. Um, I, there actually are quite a few bad episodes where they're just kind of,
the most egregious of the episodes is Homecoming, which I believe was directed by Joe Dante about
dead soldiers coming home to vote against reelecting George W. Bush. It's just, it's just
terrible. Um, there's also a really bad one called Sick Girl about, uh, and, and, uh, uh, a bug
doctor. What is that called? Entomologist? Yeah. So I watched that one.
People say that's one of the best ones. I don't know what they are talking about. Um, yeah. Uh,
but, but the acting performances are good and it's just not a good episode. Uh, I really,
really love Dreams of the Witch House, which is the Stuart Gordon one. And I really like
Hackler's Tale, which is Clive Barker, I think. Um, those two are, those two are
hackles, not hackles, sorry. Those two are my favorites. Uh, Carpenter's got one called
Cigarette Bones. That's not really good, but for some reason I like watching it. Yeah. Um,
but you know, uh, actually another good one to give the man his, uh, flowers, it is called,
uh, Our Boy Cohen. Larry Cohen? Yeah. He's got one called, hold on, let me just find it here,
Pick Me Up, uh, with Michael Moriarty. And Michael Moriarty truly gives like an Emmy worthy,
the guy is such a good actor. Jesus God, he's a good actor. Yeah. Um, he uses him all the time,
Larry Cohen. And Feruza Bulk's in that one. And it's really fun seeing Feruza in something. I,
she's not in tons of stuff these days. So, um, anyway, yeah.
What would be the best way for somebody who doesn't live in LA or New York to successfully
sell a movie script or even just get it in front of folks's eyes? Uh, you know. Tie it around a
rock, throw it through a window. I don't fucking know at this point. Yeah. You know, I've had a
couple of family members or people from my past reach out for advice like this. And, you know,
what I say is, uh, harsh, but true. There's, there's no reason, uh, to try to do this at
moment in time. I really don't think so. If you, you'd have to be beyond passionate. I,
I'm glad I did it when I did. I'm glad I took the swing and I'm hanging in there and I've had a
career and will continue to have a career. But, um, breaking in at this moment in time, I just
don't see that in the cards for almost anyone. If you write something truly amazing and you live in
Missouri, your options are pretty limited. You'd have to know somebody in LA who had an agent to
or something like that. But, um, yeah, unfortunately writing something great is not enough.
You'd have to kind of be out here or at least know someone. There's no, there's no reason.
Well, not no reason, but the reason to try to get it made
because it's, it's dwindling by the second. And at this point,
what you would receive in order to make it, uh, in, and, and as far as compensation and all those
things are concerned, it's for the amount of years of your life that it would take and,
and the amount of anxiety and energy it would pull out of you and all this stuff.
By the time it was all said and done, you literally would have had the same experience if you just
tried to raise some money and shot it yourself. Like that's it. Like it's just, you can do it.
It's easier and easier by the second to shoot something by yourself. It just is. And there's
platforms everywhere to put it now. There's just not, you know, it's a situation where people
think like, well, I'll sell a script and I'll make $500 ,000. It's like, no, you'll make like
25 grand. Like it's like they figured out ways to give you absolutely fucking nothing.
Give you just enough to wet your beak, to keep you there. It's happened to me. I mean,
I don't mean to speak bitterly just because of my experiences, but it's happened to me
multiple times over now at this point where I get, you know, you get, you get a couple,
you know, 10 or you get 20, $25 ,000 to, to, to, you know, outline your script for them.
And then they hold it there for, for a year and a half and nothing fucking happens. And you never
get the money to actually write it. And it never gets made. And they have the 18th person take
over the position of the point person you were talking to. And over the course of 18 months,
it's a waste of fucking time. Most of the time. Most of the time it is. Yeah. I would agree,
make something and put it on YouTube, tick tock, whatever. If it's really great,
somebody will see it, send it out to a bunch of people, leave it comments on, you know,
movie websites, leave, leave a link. Hey, check out, if you like this movie, check out my movie,
you know, it's the only way. And obviously, you know, unless you're a master of computer
special effects, try to write something that's a small character piece. Cause you're going to be
probably shooting it on your phone. So there you go. Oh, this is just someone saying they love us.
Thank you. I appreciate that. Would you ever do a taste buds like episode where you scream at each
other over movie snacks? It's a good pitch for an episode of taste buds. We've done it. We've done
it on taste buds. Movie candy? Yeah. I feel like the only candy I've ever gotten out of the theater
was Junior Mints. That has come up. Yeah. That's, that's been argued about. In one way or another,
that's been argued. I can't remember how. Yeah. Also, who are your all time favorite adult film
stars? So maybe we'll just pick one here. Like porn? Yeah, Joe.
Well, currently my friend Alexis Fox is my fave. Okay. But of all, of all time, the greats,
Nina Hartley was always my favorite. Interesting. Star of Boogie Nights. Yeah. I just love Nina
Hartley. Yeah. I tend to know people not by their names, but by their bodies probably, or I might
recognize somebody, but I rarely remember a name. They used to call Pat the cock spotter. Name a guy
just by the side of his cock. Yeah, I could pick out a couple certainly. I like Mia Malkova. I'm a fan
of hers. Um, it's also like porn stars, I mean, women's obviously, but women's porn stars bodies
can really change like, um, depending on where they go with plastic surgery. And now with the fake
asses sometimes, like I always thought Mia Malkova had a perfect ass. And then she got like mattresses
put in each cheek. And I'm like, you already had a beautiful ample
dumper. What happened? What happened to what's her face? Look, I mean, we see what happens to
celebrities. I mean, they, it's like, what could be, what could be more difficult if you have any
sort of body issues than being a porn star and having to not only see every aspect of your body,
every angle of your body, but then have millions of horny dudes be like, I wouldn't hit it,
you know, while living in an abandoned, uh, rec room somewhere. Um, we love the porn stars.
We love them. I just looked up, uh, Sasha Gray. Remember her? Of course. I remember Sasha Graham.
She had a small arc on entourage. I think she's, I think she's out of the porn thing completely now.
She was in that Soderbergh movie, girlfriend experience.
They gave them a real fucking hard time about it. They did. Yeah. Um, if you could ban any
song from being used in movies again, what would it be? Let's just say, give me shelter. I mean,
it's right there. Otherwise maybe fortunate son in a Vietnam movie. I'm still shocked every time
that happens. It's happened 50 times, you know? Yeah, that's a, that's a rough one. Uh, I hate
to say it cause it was in the Indiana Jones trailer, but sympathy for the devil, anything
by the rolling stones. I just, I, I really don't like the rolling stones. I like them,
but it's enough. And they're the ultimate band where like, I just don't need to hear the vast
majority of your catalog ever again. Just don't need it. I love the new, when you see them live
now, like playing songs for their new out, they have a new album out. Right. Yeah. And it's like
the three of them upfront, like just looking like, you know, they look like, like Roseanne
at this point. You know what I mean? They're just like old and gray and then like the hip,
crisp line of young black musicians behind them, like filling out the spine of the band.
Yeah. They're actually 60 years old. They just look 25 compared to Keith Richards. Yeah. Um,
who would you rather take to the prom Betty or Veronica?
Uh, I was, who was the dark haired one? That's Veronica, right? Veronica. Yeah. Oh yeah. That's,
that's my speed. Same here. Um, despite what I just said about old Mia Malkova, I, I almost
without fail prefer brunettes to blondes. And I was just thinking the other day, I don't think
I have ever in my life dated a blonde, which is interesting. You know, people got their preferences.
Sure. Hey fellas, you have to pick a beloved childhood movie to remake
that would actually turn out good. Pick one.
Easy. Uh, something wicked this way comes 100%. Yeah, that would be awesome. Um, and I'm going
to go with the peanut butter solution. One of the most disturbing movies I saw when I was a kid
about a kid who's like bald and there's a magical paint brush. I don't even know if you could ever
find this movie again, but, uh, I watched it all the time and it was deeply disturbing.
They'll never remake it. No one has ever seen it.
How much money would we need to donate to a charity to have Joe watch the Sopranos?
I believe the only way it will happen is without pressure.
Joe's got to come to it on his own. We're never going to force him.
Another pandemic would probably do it.
If the last one didn't, I mean, I don't know what to tell you.
Well, the first one was getting my feet wet. I had a lot of
shows to tackle. I hadn't seen, you know, news radio.
Yeah. Joe's always like, I'd love to, but I'm on season 13 of step -by -step
with Suzanne Somers. So I can't get to the Sopranos.
I don't have the continued loathing for the show that I once did. I think I have a better
understanding of it now than I ever did before because of this podcast. Because of this podcast,
so many people have said to me when I run into them in public, why don't you like it and like,
and pick my brain. And as I've had those discussions, I feel like I have a better
understanding of the show than I ever had. So there's a greater chance that I could like it now
more than there ever was. But I also think the show is probably
at this point, pretty dated. I think like it was kind of like, if you weren't there, you weren't
there. It's not. All right.
It's not. Now the first couple episodes look like a little dated. HBO I think was operating
off a very low budget. I've been rewatching Six Feet Under and it looks terrible. It just looks
absolutely terrible. Like that's just how things were at the time. But very quickly Sopranos became
an HD show. It looks fantastic. Even the references aren't dated. But yeah, at first you'll feel a
little nineties, you know, can't be helped. But yeah, I think so you were thinking of it as like
a Godfather thing, but these guys are low rent. These guys are their favorite movies, The Godfather.
They're trying to emulate it and failing. I think if you frame it like that, you might
appreciate it. Okay. Okay, boys, Donnie Darko or Donnie Brasco.
Weirdly, a perfect comparison. I love them both about equally. But I do have to give the edge to
Donnie Darko. I love both movies though. Brasco for me. Darko is a great movie. It's not,
it's not for me. It's not my kind of, that was a very specific kind of indie cinema when Donnie
Darko came out. That was a very, that was a particular kind of movie that was being made
at the time. And I respect it greatly, but it just, it wasn't for me. But I'm a sucker for
Donnie Brasco. I also think Donnie Brasco is a great time capsule for, you know, we've seen
some fading grace with Johnny Depp and Pacino and you go back and you watch Brasco and you remember,
holy shit, there was a time, this was a clash of the Titans. This was like, Jesus Christ. And then
you got Giamatti in there in like a fucking throwaway role. I mean, it's wild. So yeah,
back when Madsen was playing like the meanest, baddest dudes in any movie.
And yeah, I'm a big fan of both. Bruno Kirby, you know, there's a Bruno Kirby question on here,
actually. If you all had to do a Joe Bob style double feature with intros, interruptions, et
cetera, what double feature would you talk about? Any, any two movies? I guess so. Oh, you mean,
well, I think a great double feature would be Donnie Brasco and Donnie Darko. That'd be a fun.
Sure. I would pick off the top of my head, Poltergeist and the Poltergeist remake.
Just because I haven't seen the remake since the theater and I would love to rip into it and
discuss just exactly how, how badly it went wrong. One of the worst horror remakes of all time.
Yeah. What is your favorite decade for each genre of film? Now we're probably not going to
do another Q and A guys, but that question, if answered properly would take 90 minutes.
So let's say, what's your favorite decade for film?
For me, the seventies, I think produced the most masterpieces, but I do think the nineties and
looking back at that decade, there was just so much great shit, especially that when indie movies
kind of started getting huge, like that Fargo sling blade era, boogie nights, you know, that's
the time where I was becoming 17 and starting to go to movies by myself. And it just seemed like
there were five amazing new movies every weekend at that time. I would go, uh, set, uh,
eighties for horror, nineties for comedy. Okay. And then, uh, seventies for a sci -fi.
Seventies is the most fun. Sci -fi is the most fun in my opinion, in the seventies.
Also, Pat, is it true that you think For Your Consideration is the worst Christopher Guest movie?
That is true, but it's just by default. I think it's a very funny movie and a great satire of
desperate actors. It's not worse than mascots. That's not fair for you to say. Oh, I mean,
I don't count mascots, but, um, yeah, For Your Consideration is better than mascots. So no,
it's not the worst Christopher Guest movie. Also, Christopher Guest directed Almost Heroes with the
late great Matthew Perry and the late great Chris Farley. So I'd have to watch that again to decide
where that ranks. What is the greatest movie score of all time? Well, Star Wars has the best
the franchise as a whole to me has the best music followed by the Indiana Jones franchise. I don't
think, I think, and then followed by the Godfather franchise. Great choices. Hard to argue. Um,
my choice, unfortunately, and I don't know why you told this guy to do what he did, Joe,
but, uh, Danny Elfman's fantastic score for Pee Wee's Big Adventure. Wait, what did Danny Elfman
do now? I'd also throw in Beetlejuice and Batman. Those were, those are some of the best scores
ever. I listen to those to this day alone. I just think they're so inventive and cool. And I hate
Oingo Boingo. So it's weird. I like the music that much, but, uh, Danny Elfman had some like
young, hot assistants that often write music and fully nude around, uh, which, you know,
that's his process. That's how he gets inspired. Um, you, uh, um, that's funny. Um, what's it
called? Um, yeah, I agree. Elfman's music. Yeah, that's a, I forgot about that. That's a good call.
That's a really good call. What movie makes you hungry every time you watch it?
Goodfellas. Yeah, it's definitely something Italian. Um, there were a few ZDs Carmela made
on Sopranos and stuff, you know, certain, certain dishes on that show that really stuck with me,
but yeah, um, that's a big one. Goodfellas and Fatso. There's several scenes in Fatso.
Yeah. Like every, every time they're eating in Fatso, it's like classic New York food. It's
sausage and peppers, pizza, Chinese, and every version of it looks like the like picture that
you have in your head when you crave that food. So like that's those two movies get me.
All right. Ooh, a little deeper. What have you learned through being friends with each other
and or what are your favorite things about your friendship?
Um, for me, um, it is having somebody who views the world through the same lens as I do.
I very often do not like to speak openly about how I feel about the world and the people in it
with quote normal people, with my friends, my other friends. Um, I don't want to seem like I'm
too down or bringing the mood down or whatever, but Joe is reliably, uh, always there to meet me
on my level of negativity of hate. Um, and even though maybe that shouldn't be a positive thing,
it's an extremely positive thing to have somebody who just immediately you call or text and say,
I'm so fucking pissed. And they just meet you at that level and get it. Um, that's why we're so
to me, I think. I agree. And I will also match that with Pat's willingness to always talk shit
about whoever you want to talk shit about. And it could be somebody he's on fine terms with,
and you could say, I know you're on good term, but can I just, and he'll, he'll go with you on it.
Yep, I will. I will. But if Joe shouldn't on somebody once in a while, I'll go,
that person's never done anything bad to me. I'll stand up for somebody.
That does hurt when he does do that, but then usually he'll make up for it by
later shitting on that person to me.
Yeah. I mean, really it's just, it's, it's a very, it's a very similar sense of humor,
very similar outlook on the world. And as we've discussed in the show is a very immediate
friendship and I usually am not that way. So there you go. I agree.
Favorite Ninja turtle. I was always a Donatello kid. I love you guys.
Leonardo for me. He can't beat two swords.
True. I was a Michelangelo guy, but I feel to this day, including in the latest Ninja
turtles movie, which I did like, the turtles need more separation of their characters.
They are too similar. Even the song when it was like, uh, Leonardo's cool, but rude,
Michelangelo. It's like, I don't even know if these things are true about these characters.
And if they are, they're true about all four of them. There's there, there needs to be a
dumb one. It's like, look at friends or look at any show. There should have been a dumb one.
Well, simply changing their, their weapons is not, not quite enough.
There's, there's, there's, there's more of that than you're given credit for. Michelangelo is
dumb one. He's like the party guy that always wants to skateboard and eat pizza. Raphael has
the attitude. He's the disgruntled one. Donatello is the quiet, brainy one. And Leonardo was the
assertive leader that often knocks heads with Raphael because Raphael's tired of Leonardo bossing
him around. So it's, it's there, but I hear you. It's not always as carved out as it should be,
but you want to talk about a great rogues gallery, TMNT, one of the better rogues
galleries and then they get credit for, you know, you got Baxter Stockman, you got shredder,
you got Crang, Bebop and Rocksteady. It's the list goes on. That's a, that's a nice
set of villains you have there. I agree. They were always much like with Batman,
my favorite aspect of collecting the toys and everything else. I love the villains.
Um, long one. And we were just talking about this, so we might just kind of skip it,
but do either of you feel we're witnessing a decline in the talent of actors growing up?
I remember being captivated by Morgan Freeman, Anthony Hopkins, Jodie Foster. These days,
I find myself disinterested. They seem to lack that unique spark, generic, blah, blah, blah.
Do you think our parents also experienced something similar in their time?
Yes and no. I often wonder that too. Like every generation starts to hate the music and the actors
of the stuff coming up. And I always want to be knowledgeable about what's happening in the world
around me. I try to keep up on trends. Part of it's just writing jokes. You need to know a lot
of references, but try to stay up on things. I think things now are worse than they've been
in a very long time and I don't think many people would disagree with that.
And I think young people feel that as well. I don't think it's just like old people feel
like there's nobody good anymore. We used to have, you know, it's not, there weren't pretty
boys in the nineties. There were Keanu Reeves and Chris O'Donnell and these people that did
not have a lot of talent, but we're good looking guys. But we were also developing side people,
Philip Seymour Hoffman, even like Ben Stiller is not, you know, not a great looking dude.
There were all these people that we were also growing off to the side, your Sam Rockwells,
your Giamattis, who would go on to become stars in their own right, even though they don't look
like movie stars. Nowadays, we don't have that crop. We don't have the crop of interesting,
weird character actors. They're gone. Everyone has to look like a TikTok star and the movies have
really suffered because of it. The only time you see a great character actor in a movie is if it's
I don't disagree. And I also don't care. You know, this new Frasier show is a great example.
There's nothing wrong with these scripts. They're writing for the show, but the show is just not
good because the actors are doing an impression of sitcom acting. And it was an issue also that the
Star Wars prequels had where most of the actors were doing this impression of what they thought
it meant to be to act in Star Wars. You know, you see it in Shakespeare and stuff like that too.
And then somebody like Liam Neeson is in Phantom Menace and takes the same dialogue,
the same stuff, and elevates it to this place where you're like, oh, he feels like a Star
Wars character. It works. And you watch this Frasier show, it's the same thing. You're like,
well, Frasier and the English guy are doing it. Why is everybody else? It's like, because they're
just not... And then in last week, it was a breath of fresh air. June Raphael was on. She played like
a potential love interest of both Frasier and the son. And it was great because she came in and she
had like a character and she did a thing. And I was like, yeah, this feels like a show now.
Yeah. And it's just not there with the rest of it. So I do think there's a decline because
Al Pacino said in an interview 20 years ago, we're not paid to act anymore. We're just paid
to perform. And that always rattled around in my head. And I think about that all the time.
And I think he's right. I feel like people are just so paid to perform at this point. There is no...
What's going on with the character? What's the backstory? What are we doing? And not every
director or writer ever wants to work that way. Mamet classically hates that kind of thing.
William Friedkin isn't a fan of that sort of stuff. But there was time and care and effort
and energy put into the skill and the technique and these means of giving the right performance.
And I don't think it's really there anymore. I know a lot of people who are in TV shows and movies
who I'm pretty sure have never even taken a acting class. I think it's most. I think in the 70s,
you had your stars, like Robert Redford, who maybe hadn't... I bet Robert Redford took acting
classes in his life, even though he was a great looking guy. But almost everybody, if you're going
to be in a movie in, say, the 70s, would have extensive acting training. Burt Reynolds. Burt
Reynolds studied his ass off. These guys went to like... People laugh like, oh, Burt Reynolds
made bad action movies in the 80s, where it was like, the guy knew he was an actor. He knew how
to act, like he was trained. So yeah, you just don't see it much anymore. You don't see...
As much as I've complained in recent years about Will Ferrell not doing anything funny anymore,
Will Ferrell has chops. He knows how to become a part on screen. And you don't see that level of...
You just don't see it anymore. You don't see it. My friend was talking about how he worked,
went out with him last night, and he was talking about writing for the show, Shit My Dad Says,
which was canceled very quickly and not a good show. But he was like, we had no idea what the
show was. It wasn't working. It wasn't funny. And they had as a guest star, Jean Smart, as the ex of
Shatner. And she comes in, suddenly the audience is laughing at every line. Everyone got their
confidence back. It's like a pro will come in. It's like you watch Friends. Friends is a very
well -written show, but very, very often the jokes, if you take away the incredibly charismatic
performer saying the joke, there's nothing there. Like there's nothing, which is not to say these
weren't good scripts. Friends had perfect sitcom scripts. Don't get me wrong. But they were milking
laughs, big, long laughs out of... And Seinfeld did this too, even though they had way better
material. But those Friends guys, a true star can make anything sing, you know? And lately I think
we're getting bad material being acted by bad actors. Well, look at Curb. Curb's the funniest
show on TV, arguably. And there's not one joke in Curb, not one. Right. In fact, there's no script.
It's all improvised. So it's like, there's a reason why it's good because those performers,
they're trained. They know what the fuck they're doing. And that's just all there is to it. So
Larry David's not trained, but that's different. Anyway.
And you know, he did stand up for years. That's certainly a kind of training for performing.
Yeah. Joe, we'd love to have you in Indianapolis.
Pat, with the writer's strike at hand, have you considered your own podcast? You are a master
rambler. I think about it. I like having somebody to talk to. I can't imagine just talking for an
hour, maybe an interview show. I don't know. One podcast is enough, I think, for this time in my
life. Recast Jackie Brown and go. I would also just like to say I accidentally received a piece
of mail from my neighbor across the street. Her name is Jackie Brown. I didn't, I knew her first
name, but not her last. And I found that very exciting. All right. Recast Jackie Brown. I'm
actually going to say no. I think that movie was perfectly cast and I don't want to fuck with it.
Yeah. I can't imagine who, who. I think you could have had a good movie with like Tommy Lee Jones
in the Forrester part, you know, something like that. I could see that working with other actors
or something, but there's just, there's something that breaks your heart more about an actor you're
not really familiar with. Like Forrester at the end, when he's watching her walk away, that messes
me up every fucking time. And if I was watching Tommy Lee Jones do it, I don't think I would care.
So I don't know. There's a certain specificness to those actors that just, they feel like they
are those people. So I don't want to fuck with it. Pat, your favorite Robert Altman film.
You know, I love Nashville like everybody else, but I actually probably slightly prefer
shortcuts. I think that movie is a masterpiece. Another great end of the road, Jack Lemmon
performance there too. And Joe favorite Batman graphic novel. The Long Halloween. There we go.
Yeah. Joe, what's your favorite pizza spot and why besides two bros?
I think they're joking about two bros. Is that the dollar 50 slice?
I think it is. There's two bros and then there's two boots. Oh, two boots is not a great piece of
pizza either. Well, you know, Joe's is really good in New York. There's a place by me called
Grand Street pizza that I really like quite a bit. Okay. Okay. Sure. And Pat, do you know how
residuals worked for actors and writers pre -streaming? Yes, I do because it continues
to be a very large part of my income. The quickest way I could say it to you is that
let's say I wrote the fourth episode of Two Broke Girls. That episode has aired in syndication on
television thousands of times. I don't like get a check every time it airs or something like that,
but they keep track of it. The writer's guild keeps track of it. And basically you're paid a
script fee when you first write the script. That is a nice amount of money. Then the second time
it airs, meaning a repeat, you get that exact same amount of money again, which is wonderful.
And then pretty much each time after that, it gets cut in half. And that goes for the rest of
your life. So I still make Two Broke Girls residuals. I still make It's Always Sunny and
Philadelphia residuals, but they get less and less by the year basically. The beautiful thing
about Two Broke Girls is that it airs in actual syndication and is not like a streamer show
because I would get nothing if it was a streamer. So that's what all the strike shit was about.
Basically, it used to be a much better system. That's my retirement plan. I'm going to have,
it pays for these dark times when we can't work. So that used to be the point. And the person who
actually got residuals was Ronald Reagan, who I know did not do a lot of great shit, but that was
pretty great because he was an actor. He only did it because it benefited himself. He was like,
they're showing these movies all day for free. Something's wrong about that. And he was right.
So he started it. What is your top movie that everyone else loves, but you can't stand?
Forrest Gump.
Yeah, there's a steady backlash building for that one, I think.
I've hated it from day one. I bought the goddamn thing at Sam Goody. The week it came out on video,
I hadn't seen it. And I loved Philadelphia. And I was like, everybody says this movie's amazing.
And I watched it. I fucking hated it then. I hate it now. I've tried to rewatch it. I fucking hate
it. I hate the character. God damn it. I hate that movie.
Fair enough. And I would have to say,
I mean, the biggest and best example is Marvel. I mean, that's where when I'm sitting in a Marvel
movie, when I'm sitting in the third hour of a Marvel movie, there's no time where I feel
more separate from society, different from society. When are we getting a goddamn Matt McCarthy
and or James Pinkstone episode? Well, folks, you will hear James Pinkstone on the live app.
He was our little cameo. We also in case you didn't see pictures or seen it online, we had
the great Lloyd Kaufman of Troma Films and the great Brian Quinn of Impractical Jokers as special
guests. And we'd love to have Matt on the show. These questions, you know, we just don't have
guests generally as a rule, occasionally on the live show. But yeah, it could happen.
I agree. PS come to a live show in Barcelona. Your Spanish Hellions have been neglected too
long. Look, me and Joe down in Barcelona sipping red wine on a veranda sounds fantastic.
I'll tell you what, if you guys can show us that there's a significant and this is serious. If
you can show us somehow that there's a significant amount of people in Spain that want us to come
there, we would come there. But you know, we got to know that, that it would have, you know,
it can't be five people. But if there's like a significant portion of people that
would want us to come out there, we would absolutely do it. Yeah.
What is a horror film you feel you could easily survive to the point of it not being all that
scary? Look, I'll throw out the one we're going to do next, Five Nights at Freddy's. I kept thinking
like, just go, just leave. Chucky is there's, I think I've seen a comedian do a funny bit,
like just kick Chucky in the face. It's a foot tall. So yeah, I mean, there's a few where like,
if you really think about putting yourself in that situation, you could get out of it, I think.
I've never thought that Night of the Living Dead seemed that tough to get out of.
Even with the world. I mean, you kind of have to imagine the world as being overridden, but they
are very slow. Yeah, it just always seemed kind of easy to me. But, you know, I guess that's the
point. Yeah. I've wanted to open a sandwich shop on Long Island for a while now. Do you slice your
cold cuts per sandwich order or pre -slice the needed amount for the day in the morning?
If you can slice per sandwich, you should. That's the best way to do it. Pre -slice,
you're going to, they're going to dry out eventually, and you're going to have waste
because you're going to slice stuff and eventually it's going to be too dry and
you're going to have to toss it. Whereas if you're slicing fresh, it's always right where
it needs to be with that moisture. Like a moist meat. Yes. Where are we at in the list? How many
more questions do we have, by the way? We're getting there. We're getting there.
Who is scarier, Mike Myers or Jason?
Myers to me.
Again, this is another one where I feel like it's easy to get out of.
They walk slowly, you know, I know in the movie they just somehow miraculously catch up to the
person and whatever, but it just doesn't seem that hard to outdo to me, but I don't know.
Yeah, I guess, I guess Jason scares me a little bit more. I guess. Fair, fair.
With only one choice each, which movie or series of movies defines your adolescence?
I think the best choice for me there would probably be like The Naked Gun.
I just, all the movies in that world had the, that and John Hughes had the most direct,
I gotta do this for a living and made me get obsessed with comedy. And then Raising Arizona
was the first time where I just rewound the movie and watch it again because I was like,
how did they make this? This is crazy. And then that kind of developed an interest in making shit.
Uh, I think, wait a minute. I don't know if I understood the question. I mean, I,
I don't think I heard the question. Which movie defined your adolescence?
Well, Star Wars. Undoubtedly. I was obsessed with Star Wars as a kid. I couldn't wait for the
to go on forever. You know, I can't think of anything that, that rocked my existence more
than that, that original Star Wars trilogy and has continued to have a great effect on my life
to the point where I'm still watching this fucking schlock that Disney is churning out.
Yeah. What is the most average movie you both have ever seen? A picture that perfectly embodies
a five out of 10. The most average movie ever made. I used to, I used to have one.
It's usually a plain movie. I think every Marvel movie is that from after phase,
from phase two on. Yeah. I really enjoyed the Marvel stuff up, up through and including
um, the first Avengers. I phase two on, that's every Marvel movie. It's just about every DC
movie. I hate to say, uh, in this new phase of DC stuff that they're doing.
I don't think anything is more mediocre and more celebrated and makes more money of,
unless of course we talk about the films of the great Jason Blum. I mean, I've just never seen a
man make more money off of just brainless average shit. That's five nights at fucking Freddy's.
Guess what? Guess who made it? Yeah. So, uh, they, I mean, they're 70 % of horror. Their name is in
every horror movie. It's them and a 24 is it. I think Blumhouse, Marvel and DC and Disney,
well, Disney is Marvel. It's my God, man. It's just the, the leading three brands of, of just
schlock. It's so fucking boring. Yeah. None of it is new or interesting. It's, it's, it's,
admirable only in the sense that it's, it's perfectly painted by numbers. But once you get
past that, it's just like, who cares, man? Oh God, I hate it. Yeah, I agree. And I would,
I would pick, um, maybe a recent one that I would pick would be a man called Otto with Tom Hanks,
just for being a average plane movie or a HBO on demand movie or whatever you want to call it,
very generic. And isn't it nominated or something? I don't think it did. It just kind of sits there.
Not a great movie. Um, all right. Favorite horror book.
Uh, I would say American Psycho. Nice. And I will select, um,
look, I gotta go misery. I gotta go misery. I really love it. Also though, uh, Skeleton Crew
by Stephen King. Uh, I think as far as Stephen King goes, you can't beat Skeleton Crew. It's just the,
it's his best collection, in my opinion, best collection of short stories. And you know,
I, short horror, short horror fiction is, is, is my favorite way to ingest horror. And I think that
uh, that book really is, is, you can't go wrong with that one, man. That's a good one.
Have you ever cried while watching a comedy special?
I would say probably not, unless I was just in a terrible place that I don't remember,
but I don't think so. I'm assuming they don't mean from laughter. Uh,
well, they say due to it being painfully unfunny, but then there's no question. So I think the
question is, have you ever cried while watching a comedy special? Uh, no, no, no. I've hate watched
plenty, but I've never cried. Uh, and none of their, none of these moving, moving, uh, ending
comedy specials move me at all when, when it gets poignant. Quite the opposite. Favorite place you
traveled to? Uh, Italy, Italy. All right. Yeah. And I would say Amsterdam or Greece. I love Greece.
What, who, who was Pat and Joe's favorite ska band?
There aren't many. I like the specials a lot. I'll go with the specials.
Okay. I would say operation Ivy is as close as I get to ska. Okay.
I really don't care for ska at all, but, uh, op Ivy drifts into it here and there.
Um, and I, and I like them, but, uh, who boss tones and all that crap.
I mean, no, no offense, but to the, you know, but Jesus God.
Uh, who is our new Bruno Kirby?
That's a, that's weird that that was asked. I know. Oh, you said earlier, there was a Bruno Kirby
question. Uh, I don't know. Cause it's hard. You know, there was a period where I thought it,
you know, I would have said Sam Rockwell, but Sam Rockwell, you know, bigger star. Yeah.
Leading man. Um, um, God, wait, I want to, I want to get maybe, maybe a Josh Gad. Maybe.
Uh, no, no. Um,
you know who it could have been if he was a movie star is Steve from sex in the city.
He's got a Bruno Kirby vibe.
I think you're giving Steve too much.
I'm definitely giving Steve too much. I'm trying to think of somebody though, that's been in like
a lot of iconic things. Yeah.
Miranda, but like you said, you were going to meet me on the Brooklyn bridge Miranda.
No, not necessarily his demeanor, just, just, just, but like,
you know, Bruno Kirby's in the Godfather and right.
Yeah. It'd have to be somebody who was a character actor through it all,
his entire career. Like Bruno Kirby never made it to leading man status.
You know, Danny Aiello was a Bruno Kirby. Sure. Sure. But he's, he's not the new one cause he's
dead. But, uh, but, um, maybe, uh, um, oh, for Christ sakes, there's, hold on. We can, we can get
this. I think that's just what we're talking about. There aren't character actors anymore,
so we're not going to get it. What's a show with a, you know, who, you know, who might be,
uh, not quite as Sean Hayes. Sean Hayes is our Bruno Kirby. No, not at all. Why? Not at all.
Doesn't even make sense. Why? I just disagree. Will Arnett, like he's in, you know, a guy that's
kind of around and he's good, but he's, he's not necessarily the lead guy. Yeah. Wait, I just had
it. I had it and I lost it. No, I did. Uh, Bradley Whitford. Oh, that's, that's perfect.
Thank you. That's perfect. Um, all right. Last page. Here we go. Lightning round. What did you
guys think of under the silver lake? Joe hasn't seen it. I watched it for the second time the
other day. I fucking love it. I think it goes too far off the rails, but I love it. And it is also
filmed on and around the street where Joe lived here in Los Feliz. Like it's crazy how like you
can see Joe's apartment in the movie several times. Oh, wow. Shit. That's not that weird for LA.
Most things are shot on a street you lived on at some point. Um, have you seen Gaspar Nose Vortex?
If so, what thoughts I have. I fucking loved it. I think that opening dance sequence is one of the
coolest things in the history of movies. At least watch that on YouTube. Um, and then it gets crazy
depressing. It's, I mean, uh, depressing and also disturbing. It's the guy who made irreversible.
Um, and eventually the movie gets very hard to watch, but I thought the movie was genius.
I love what that guy does, even though I rarely want to watch his shit a second time.
Uh, Joe, did you end up buying the vintage He -Man slime pit and what are your thoughts on the new
Master of the Universe movie being dumped by Netflix after 30 million in development?
Uh, I didn't get the slime pit. No, uh, only because upon further investigation, it really
looks cheap and, uh, I did not have the, the aesthetic I remembered it having. Um,
and I think it's disgraceful, uh, you know, the money they waste on these things and, you know,
and then, you know, the same industry constantly bitching about world hunger and, uh, you know,
what we need to be doing for, for the lesser fortunate and all this stuff. And, and, and,
you know, and they do this kind of shit, you know, I think it's really gross. And I think it's,
it's insane and it's idiotic. Like I just, I, I, and I look, it's, it's how big business works.
I guess there's more money to be, to be made in the tax write -off and the loopholes to jump out
of the project. And in the long run, they're going to lose less than dumping that 30 million
by dumping that 30 million. But I just don't understand. Like they make it so,
so complicated and they do it over and over and over again, and they do it constantly.
And it's just to a point where I just say, I guess that's just how the,
the business works. I, and I will never understand it because I don't do it.
Yeah. You know, so, uh, you know, it's like, you know, like one thing I understand about
business is like, is, is like, you know, like when, when, like for instance, like when everybody's,
whether you hate Trump or like Trump, you know, whatever, but when I, one of the big
criticisms of Trump was like, you know, he's never showed a profit on his tax return, whatever.
And I'm like, well, yeah, but that's common with businesses. Like they write everything off. It's
not that weird that a business person's businesses never show a profit because there's so many
write -offs and stuff like that. So I didn't think that that was that kind of weird, but a lot of
people did. And maybe I'm wrong, but whatever. But my point that I'm getting at is I'm using
analogy to say like, when you hear Netflix dumped the He -Man movie after spending 30 million dollars,
I'm like, I guess there's like a Trump thing to it that I don't get where like, you know,
when you're operating at that level, this is a tech tactic that you utilize for whatever reason,
but you know, I just don't get why it's so goddamn hard for these people to make a fucking movie
that people will like when it's all been laid out for them already. I mean, this is not rocket
science. It's all there. And again, we're going to review Five Nights at Freddy's, but
it's a startling example of what we're talking about, where it's just a movie you're watching
and you're just like, guys, you had a nine video game prototype franchised. This was so easy.
Yeah. And you fuck it up. And the He -Man, it's like, for Christ sakes, guys, he fights Skeletor.
There's a bunch of weird characters. He has to save Eternia. The end. That's the fucking story.
Right. You know, so I don't know. I don't know. It's crazy.
Have you guys seen the British TV movie threads? Yes. So yeah, if so, how depressing was it? It's
depressing. I found that to be a little overrated, but I think it was big in Britain because
people thought it was real, but it's like a, you know, a mock newscast kind of thing of the
apocalypse, basically. But I remember thinking it was entertaining. My theology teacher in the
12th grade, Mr. Dowd made us watch that in class. And to this day, I don't know why he has a weird
election. Yeah. And he didn't, not because of a religious thing. He just was like,
you kids need to understand how bad nuclear war would be. Like he showed us that movie. We were
like, what the fuck? But it was a fun way to spend two, two or three class periods,
not having to do work. Yeah. But yeah, it's an upsetting movie.
Yeah. Favorite sex position, Joe? All of the above. Oh, I like a nice,
I like a nice doggy. Sure. But I call me lazy. I really love a woman on top of me.
Like, yeah, that's, I mean, that's number one for me. It's, it's a boobs in your face,
you know, hands on an ass. It's just fantastic. It's hard to beat that. I find if I, if it's a
more top heavy lady, love her sitting on top. If it's a back heavy lady, love, love the doggy.
But I, I'll agree. I love it all as well. Missionary. I don't have really any use for it.
Do it. It's just kind of. Missionary is you on top? Yeah. Why couldn't, well,
isn't a woman on top of you also missionary? No, no. Why? Why is it called missionary?
That name's always bothered me. I think because that's how the missionaries did it.
It's the most basic way, I guess, man on top. Yeah, that's a terrible name.
Reverse cowgirl is great, obviously. My only fear with that is when it gets too
heated, I'm always worried I'm going to break my dick.
You know, just the tailbone bouncing around on it. Sure. Sure. I've had that once before. I've
heard of guys who've had like, you know, really messed their dick up in that position. I use,
my friend's dad used to be a nurse and had all kinds of stories about people breaking their
dicks and shit, crazy stuff. If you two were a couple, who would be the top and who would be
bottom? Well, obviously Pat would be the bottom. Obviously. I'm joking. I don't know. I think,
I think it'd be a switch off to be honest. We'd be verse. They call that verse means
you top and bottom. Okay. I'll tell you this though, I would not be a power bottom
where the bottom loves getting fucked so much they lean into it and start
humping back with their ass. I would not be wanting further penetration from a gay sex
experience. I'd have to ease in. Pat, what are your thoughts on Scandival? You mentioned
watching Vanderpump Rules for the first time not too long ago. Should Jacks return? Blah, blah,
blah. Yeah. I've seen every episode of Vanderpump Rules and the reunions.
Um, Scandival is not of interest to me. I think what is Scandival? So that's Tom Sandoval, uh,
cheated on his wife, Adriana, Ariana. And, um, she's always seemed to me to be the most level
headed of the group. She's awesome. She's extremely attractive and Tom Sandoval was always
significantly beneath her. Um, I think he probably cheated on her much more than he
did and got found out on the show for, but that Raquel is an idiot. She's also less attractive
than his wife. Um, not that cheating is only okay if somebody's hotter, but I find him to just be
stupid and completely unlikable. And, um, so was everyone on the show, which is what makes it
entertaining, but I don't care. I, I, I'm at a, I'm at a point now where I think the show's
going to get really dark, um, and depressing because we're watching people's lives be torn
apart. Um, but they're also animals. So who cares? If you've never seen Vanderpump Rules,
it is very addictive. I recommend it. Um, Dial of Destiny made me want a glass of whiskey. What
movie or song gooses you guys up for some real world vices? What movie gooses this up?
I think, let's say what movie, you know, like just so we said earlier, what movie makes you hungry?
What movie makes you want to go get drunk or fucked up? Oh, well, um, that's a good question.
Uh, what movie doesn't would be, would narrow it down. Tragically, I might have to say Bad
Santa, which is supposed to be an anti, but man, does it make me, uh, appreciate the drinking life?
Uh, Boogie Nights. Sure.
I mean, full disclosure, Boogie Nights makes me want to do when they're doing Coke in the room.
I'm like, I get like a Big Mac craving. Like I'm like, man, that looks fun. When they're like,
let's not leave this room. I'm like, Oh, they're having a good time at the party. Uh,
be on that bed with Heather Graham and Julianne Moore. Yeah. And, uh, but drinking, uh, uh,
again, the Scorsese movies always make me want to drink, you know, The Irishman. Yeah.
Let's bang this shot and then go talk to them. You know, uh, Goodfellas when they're at the bar.
Um, but I know I'm missing something here. Easy Money always makes me want to drink.
Uh, they're, they're just having a ball throughout that movie. Um, but I feel like I'm, you know,
Friday, my, my, my, uh, my vice is, is weed and, uh, Friday, of course, is an ultimate for that.
Sideways puts you in the mood for some wine sideways, but, but that's a cheat. That's
almost like saying like chef makes you want to eat. Of course, it's just, it's so focused on it,
right? Um, but yeah, I think those are, those are old school also. That's one where you're like,
you know, you're like, yeah, let, let shotgun a beer, you know? Yeah. Um, okay. What would
you consider to be the greatest punk band? The greatest, you might have to go with like
the Ramones, you know, like that is punk essentially. My favorite is probably the Clash.
Um, bad religion is my favorite and I think you could make an argument that they are the
greatest. They are considered the godfathers of skate punk. Uh, I mean, they're great. They brought
in my opinion, true like harmony into punk in a way that hadn't been quite done yet. Yeah. And,
I think they're the best, uh, uh, that ever did it. But, um, but, you know, there's so many,
but, you know, I would, I would put Dead Kennedy's way up the list.
Uh, of course the Ramones, um, you know, Clash, it's funny with the Clash, like,
I feel like all my favorite Clash stuff is the stuff that I wouldn't call it. I wouldn't call
like London calling punk, right? Or is it? Um, no, it's considered punk for sure. Yeah.
It is. All right. Yeah. Okay. Um, what are your thoughts on David Gorda Green doing an
Exorcist trilogy? We've covered that. We are anti. Where are your hogs at for Hugh Jackman
in the yellow Wolverine suit? Looks pretty cool to me. Is it out? Is there a picture?
It's a picture of him in Deadpool going for a walk. Um, yeah, why not? I guess so,
you know, it's, it's so funny to me that like,
they're this far down the road with, with Marvel and with Wolverine. And for the first time,
they're like, why don't we put them in the actual suit that Wolverine wears? Yeah. All the fucking
time. It's just so funny. And remember there was a time where it was considered crazy to do that.
They make a joke about it in the original X -Men, the Bryan Singer were to wear the suits.
Wolverine goes, Wolverine's like, we got to wear these things. Like what the black suits they
wear. And, and Cyclops goes, what would you prefer yellow spandex? And it got a big laugh
in theater because you're like, at the time, I remember you'd be like, you were like, yeah,
that would look ridiculous. Right. You know, cause that was like the, that was the anti
Schumacher phase of superhero movies where it was like nothing gaudy, nothing bright.
Yeah. You know, you were, you were, you were building up to the Nolan Batman stuff. It was,
it was, you know, it was a time to pair it all down again. So, um, it's just interesting that
just now they're getting to yellow Wolverine.
Pat, you and I are on the same page with Sopranos being the best TV show ever,
but what are your thoughts on the other HBO golden era stall worth the wire?
The wire, uh, you know, I'm do a rewatch, but I would say, uh, if you remove the final
season, which is merely a very good season of TV, um, then you have a nearly perfect show.
I think the first four seasons of the wire are incredible and I would put it up there with,
uh, not up with Sopranos, but I put it up there with six feet under and the wire and,
you know, they had a lot of great shows in the early HBO days. Sex and the City,
I'd throw in below those as well, but yeah. Um, Joe, what happened to Khan?
He lives with my parents. Okay. That's it. I, when I moved back to New York,
I couldn't have a dog in the apartment I was in. So my mom took them. I didn't know how long I was
going to be in the apartment. It was supposed to be temporary. Then COVID hit a month later.
Yeah. Uh, a few months turned into two years, whatever the hell it was.
And when all was said and done, I just thought I'm not going to pull this dog now that's living in
a house with two people instead of one and another dog with a yard out of all that to then try to
acclimate him into being a city dog that's going to be alone more and all that stuff. And, and
it just didn't make sense to pull them out of it. And it also, my parents had lost a, had to get,
they had a dog that had become very problematic that they loved very much, but had to get rid of
because they couldn't handle her anymore. And, um, um,
Khan kind of took the place of that dog and it was good for my folks. It was good for him. And,
you know, I see him when I go home and I sleep in the bed and he sleeps next to me and it's
a nice reunion. It's like, it's like, it's like, uh, like, uh, like seeing an ex wife
and you have sex. Yeah. And you say, remember what we had, babe. All right. I'll see you next year.
That kind of thing. Fair enough. There was a request for one last on with a job
and there it is. It cut out. I think I cut myself out. I was worried about shorting out the mic.
Try it. We'll do it again. Cause we, we got nothing. We got like an on, I got to back up with a job.
Cut out again. It's too high pitched. Only dogs can hear it. Keeps cutting out. That's fine. Um,
all right. Then let's, uh, last question. Thank you all. We're going to answer this and wrap it
up. Joe, what is your favorite childhood memory? I'm going to have to really search my brain.
The one that's coming to mind now, and maybe just cause it's almost Thanksgiving is I remember the
film home alone coming out. Macaulay Culkin was nine years old. I was nine years old.
I was obsessed with John Hughes as a nine year old. And now he had made a movie exactly for me
about somebody exactly my age. And the night before Thanksgiving, I want to say my whole family
went. Normally we had to wait until the dollar show to see everything, but we saw it opening
night for five 75. I remember my mother making sure we knew that it was five 75. That's cheap
woman. Um, but yeah, home alone opening night. I mean, I was in paradise and then we went and
the Christmas lights after, I mean, good times. Um, uh, probably, uh, going to see return to the
Jedi. It was the most excited I ever was to see a movie ever. I couldn't wait to see what happened.
I remember sitting in the theater watching Hans, seeing job of the hut for the first time after
they'd hinted at him for so long, seeing Han unfreeze, seeing Leah and Lando in disguise,
seeing Luke unsheathed the green lightsaber, seeing Darth Vader become unmasked, seeing the
emperor for the first time in the trilogy. Uh, it was just, it blew my mind. And my dad,
uh, I, I just very vividly remember my parents taking me to see it and their excitement for me,
my dad's excitement for me, my mom reading the opening crawl to me in the theater,
which I'm sure the people around us loved. Uh, it was a very, very nice memory. Uh,
and it has to do with movies. So there you go. Yeah. I do think any therapist would take issue
with both of our favorite childhood memories being going to see a movie, but that's,
that's where we're at. Um, thank you everyone for your fantastic questions. We'll be back
with an in -depth review of just one of the most insightful, uh, thrilling, scary, riveting horror
movies of the new year, five nights at Freddy's. Uh, you can watch it on Peacock or in the theater
if you like, and, uh, we'll see you next time. We'll see you in hell.