I see you on the.
Hey, I got a bonus app up there.
You got a bonus app right in your gooch.
It's a bonus app in your ray.
All right.
It is.
It's your bonus app.
We got a big one today.
We are, as I guess we are going to announce,
so am I as well tell you, but I think we're making a change.
We're going to take a little hiatus for my nuptials
and my honeymoon.
We're going to come back hot with season five.
Season five.
Somebody pointed out to us that season four
is now at like 53 episodes, which I guess
means it's been a full year, but that's great.
And I quite frankly couldn't be happier to have,
so this is the last episode of the month.
And the final free episode is the Infinity War episode.
So I'm very happy in classic and good entertainment fashion
to leave our listeners with a cliffhanger.
Will they return to this questionable controversial
and divisive format?
Some people have did some people hate it.
That's, anytime we do anything, that's what it is.
And that's what democracy is, people.
But a lot of folks were like, they should be done
with superhero movies.
I saw that a lot.
And then a lot of people who's feelings seem genuinely hurt
because they are like, now I can't watch these things
that are the only thing I love.
I can't watch anymore.
And then some people were like,
because we ruin superhero movies, right?
Which means you might not love them enough folks.
And then some people are like, I love this.
This is fun for me, you know?
People have different strokes.
Some fans said they enjoyed that it was,
they said it reminded them of them trying
to explain a movie to their friends.
Which is why I thought people would like it
because people who've often complimented us
and said, you know what I like about the show?
I feel like I'm watching a movie with two friends
that keep getting distracted.
Yes.
So why would a description of the movie be any different?
No clue.
Anybody that wants to hear me do a point by point,
100 % accurate description of the Avengers movie.
I mean, you get too much time on your hands.
Well, across the board, everyone said,
Joe was so wrong about every aspect
of the Marvel universe.
And I don't know if that's true or not
because I don't care.
But that was across the board.
And people thought you were very wrong
about a lot of things.
You know what I'd like to do?
No, I got to be honest with you.
What I'd like to do,
and I'm not going to hold you to this
because then you got to watch the movie.
I'd love for you to watch that movie
and you tell me how fucking wrong I was
because I wasn't that wrong.
I will.
I glazed over and botched things for comedy effect.
But overall, I told you the goddamn movie.
I mean, I didn't make anything up.
Sure.
Anyway, you know, you're all taking things
too seriously, let's be real.
We're going to get into these questions
because I don't know if we have four hours
of questions.
I don't know if we have 20 minutes of questions,
but we're going to get going.
And if we've done the question before,
it's going to be politely passed on.
You know that, folks.
And we'll do as many of these as we can.
I mean, if it gets to a certain point
where it's ridiculous, we can't do all of them.
But we're going to try.
Yeah, I mean, we want to give you a nice long app
because we are taking a little time off.
But for real folks, we haven't taken time off
in a very long time.
But there was a period where this podcast
we'd do like one March first.
And then the next one would be like late July.
And honestly, it wasn't a bad time.
I got a lot more work done.
Edmund Agabo asks, have you ever thought,
and this is a very interesting question.
Have you ever thought about working together
on an independent project?
No rules, no holds barred, anything.
Joe's.
And the truth is, with no details,
Joe and I have been talking about doing a little project, perhaps.
Yes.
That's all.
That is true.
Can't tell you anything, but we spent a little time on it.
It may or may not come to fruition.
Look, I like that he did specify, you know, no rules.
Like, you know, like this thing is just burdened down
with legislation.
Sure, I was sure.
Anyway, I think you just met no network interference.
Hey, we don't have any.
Yeah, at the moment, the, no, that's fine.
Yeah, no, I appreciate the question.
Yeah, we do talk about that stuff.
Yes, yeah, I mean, a big part of it, honestly,
of us not working together beyond this,
is it would kill me to lose a friendship with Joe and kill me.
You know, I imagine day four of working intensely
on any project, the friendship would be done.
The friendship would be done.
Yeah, it's, but it would be lovely.
And we did, well, yeah, we worked on a show,
but you want to talk about rules.
There were a few rules on that show.
A little interference.
But that was also a good scenario at the sitcom,
because you were over in the wing doing the writing
and I was down on the floor, and then you swoop in and say a thing
and then you bleed, you know, it wasn't like we were,
like, sitting at a desk together.
Yeah, my buddy Mike at our bachelor party really made me laugh.
He was my bachelor party.
He was like telling, in the process of telling Joe
that he liked his character was excited
to see all the shitty gets into in future episodes.
And Joe's nod in his head like, yeah, yeah, man, yeah, man.
It's like, you know, the Joe never going to be on the show again.
He was washing on the app or something.
Ken Hanley says, two part question.
One, who do you think you are?
And two, how dare you?
Ken really hated that last episode.
Ken did, I screen shot at Ken's blistering shots at Joe
on the last one, couldn't even make it through.
Blistering, yeah, why did he pick on just me?
I think Pete probably likes me more.
And also, too, I'm just going to throw that out there
for anybody that's sided with Ken.
And who also said that I was way off base.
And Pat's usually the voice reason.
Ken once said on Facebook that Halloween 3 is the best Halloween
and that it can't be argued.
He actually said that.
Well, it can be argued by everyone.
He gave his order of Halloween movies.
His number one was Halloween 3.
And he said, this cannot be argued.
I remember them.
So I love you, Ken.
But, you know, let's not act like we're all glass houses, baby.
Glass houses.
I love the passion of our fans.
I love that we piss them off sometimes.
It's all good to me.
And I know that there is a new fan fiction about you and I.
That's apparently lengthy and spectacular.
And I have not had time to read it.
I believe that's your boy, Scott Patton.
I want to thank Scott for writing it and sending it in.
I have not had a chance to read it either.
It's 18 pages.
Yeah, I mean, I've got a little bit going on.
And it's the continuation of the last one, I think.
I'm very excited to read this thing.
And in fact, let me give another shout out to, is this him, Tim?
Yeah, Tim paints the world on Instagram.
I don't know what this is real name though.
Tim paints the world, Timothy Atkins from Sweden.
Who sent us a DVD copy of a dark place.
The comedy show with Matt Barry and a few other folks from England.
But we weren't able to watch it because we had a neither of us had a region
for a DVD player, but it was a very thoughtful thing.
So thank you for doing that.
Can's actual question.
What 80s film property would you most want to adapt into a hit YouTube
bread series?
And, you know, I know I guess we're not doing movie corner, but my dear friends,
John Herwood, Hayden Schlossberg, Josh Eild, created and ran Cobra Kai on YouTube
bread.
I went to the premiere.
I watched all 10.
They did a great job.
It's a very entertaining show.
I look forward to seeing it.
But what 80s film property would you most want to adapt into a hit series?
That's a great, like I guess they mean update Cobra Kai style.
And I would say.
Oh boy.
There's so many good options.
I'm surprised they ain't cracked open labyrinth.
Oh, that would be great.
I mean, they are bringing back Dark Crystal, which is exciting.
Yes.
Has a series?
Yeah, Netflix series.
Okay.
I'll tell you mine.
And I just thought of it right now.
Yeah.
I think this is a golden idea.
Go ahead.
Weird science.
The boys now middle aged men meet up.
Life hasn't turned out the way they wanted it to.
They're estranged from their wives, kids, whatever it is.
Sure.
And they try to create perfect middle aged companions for themselves,
including children.
Well, you can definitely get Anthony Michael Hall.
And you can definitely get McKenzie, whatever his name is.
I don't know if you can.
That guy won't ever do like he never does
any of the bonus stuff for, you know, like on the weird science
DVD, Michael, Anthony Michael Hall says, like McKenzie, wherever you are,
yeah, you know, like it was fun.
Like, but nobody, I don't know what he seems to have disappeared.
My buddy has a great idea with the weird science franchise
that I almost just casually dropped.
I'm going to let it go.
But okay, I hope he, I hope it can make it happen.
Does it relate to mine at all?
No.
All right.
Well, good.
Then we can both have our own.
Great question.
Ken, Ken has another question.
The only person I'll allow to have more than one is Ken him.
Best haunted house haunted attraction experience.
Universal Hollywood Harness, the exorcist house.
Okay.
And the crampus house somehow was potentially scarier than the exorcist house.
They made a crampus, the movie house at Universal.
Yeah.
Halloween and hard.
The movie made $13 million.
Well, that fucking haunted house was scary as shit, man.
That big gas crampus coming out of a closet.
That is not, all right, it's not not scary.
I despise haunted houses.
I once went to a Queens of Stonehenge show where they were supposed to have this, like, you
know, like get your blood and heart check before you go in haunted house and people were puking
and shit.
That's not for me.
I don't do that shit.
But I remember when I was a kid, maybe five, six, seven, my dad took me to a haunted house
in the lake of the Ozarks.
And when you stepped on the mat, it just blew air at you.
And I don't even think it was an attraction.
It was just like cold air came at you.
And I started hysterically crying.
And since I didn't, I don't think I had seen any of the attractions yet.
So it's not for me.
Never was.
Also like you're giving people chainsaws to run at you.
What if they're mentally disturbed?
It's just some guy who's like 18, who signs a form.
I've often wondered how nothing ever goes wrong, because one of the things they did at
hard nights was the park, the theme of the actual park, like, just when you were walking around
was the purge.
So you had people dressed in like steam punk outfits running up to you, like waving like
knives in your, I mean, obviously they're, yeah, they're rubber or whatever.
But I'm like, you could still poke somebody's fucking eye out by accident.
Like they were getting really close.
So I'm like, I don't understand how there's never an accident.
Nobody ever like freaks and punches one of these people because they can't, I'm sure it's
happened.
You know, I saw somebody get their hand hit because they grabbed the side of the haunted
hay ride in Griffith Park, which is fun, actually.
But some guy jumps up and grabs the side and got reached over and bashed his fingers.
You can tell the guy was really hurt.
I love a haunted hay ride.
I'd like to do that.
We should.
It's very fun to have it every year.
Amanda Liebson inquires, what actor or actress would play you in the inevitable docu -drama
of this podcast?
Well, mine's obviously Paul Giamatti.
I mean, there's no other actor that could.
Yeah, I think it's got to be.
Play me.
Um, and for mine, I don't know.
I mean, the only, the only name I've gotten on a regular basis through the years is Timothy
Hutton.
Timothy Hutton.
But he's not funny.
I'd like to see a young Martin Mall play you.
Marty Mall?
Yeah.
Um.
It's too old now though.
Okay.
Yeah.
I don't know.
I'm going to say Emma Stone.
I mean, we want this thing to have good box office.
All right.
And we know we both have Reddish here, which I can admit now.
There's a little red to my hair.
Okay.
Um.
Can I ask a third question?
Now we're pushing it, Ken.
But here we go.
Most inappropriate time you've laughed during a public film screening or Q &A.
I once laughed really loud during a movie about human slave trafficking when the lead character
kept yelling, my son over and over, and I suspect everyone has had one of those moments.
Mine, 1000 % was Sicaria, which is a movie I loved.
But when I find dark shit, very, very funny, it's some sort of weird coping mechanism or something.
But when Del Toro is calmly detailing how he's murdered the guy's family, or he's going
to murder the family.
I don't forget exactly what it was.
I couldn't stop laughing.
I just thought it was so bleak and funny that like sometimes really dark makes me laugh
the most.
I don't have one that I can recall.
I will say this though, and I wasn't laughing.
But when I saw Gran Torino in the theater, yes, I was confused.
I couldn't tell if they were trying to be funny or not.
Sure.
Because I told you my story of Philip Simmer Hoffman howling laughing throughout Gran Torino.
Oh, you did say that didn't you?
Yeah.
Howling laughing.
Well, I was watching.
I was like, this sounds like the way your uncle would pull you aside and tell you an inappropriate
joke and a party.
I know.
Is this supposed to be funny?
It would.
That movie has a wild tone to it.
I don't know.
I mean, it's got the kid from the Sandlot as a priest, the fat kid.
I mean, I don't know what's going on with that move.
I want to see it again.
I would like to revisit it because I've only heard people either say it's terrible or it's
amazing.
I didn't like it, but I'd like to revisit it.
I don't know anyone who thought it was amazing, but I watched it with a laugh track by
one of our most acclaimed actors.
PSH.
There were rumors for a while it was going to be the final dirty Harry movie, which would
have been pretty cool.
That would have been awesome.
And I still think they should do it.
Yeah.
You know, it would have been cool to see like retired dirty Harry and then it dies like an
honorable death after he's kind of a slightly crooked cop all those years.
I agree.
Now, it wasn't dirty grand Paul, the last of the dirty Harry movies.
No.
It's not out yet.
Apparently it's called dirty Sanchez.
Okay.
And it's just him in an old age home wiping his feces on people's faces.
Right before we take this, Joe and I watched a video, you can find it online.
It's a woman complaining about her donut order at Tim Horton's donuts.
And after about 30 seconds, she's had enough.
She leans against a wall, shits on the floor, picks up her shit, throws it at the teenage donut
clerk, wipes her ass with an napkin and throws the shit staying napkin at the guy.
It's not pixelated in any way.
You can watch this online, Google it if you dare, but one of the best things I've ever
seen.
It's great.
Now, how does that tape get out?
How does the manager or Tim Horton's go?
We're going to release this to the public.
I'm glad he did.
That's all I know.
I'm glad he did too, but I'm just saying that.
That cannot comply with.
Yeah.
With franchise standards.
No.
It could be a cop took it.
I mean, who knows.
Sometimes cops look at these things and they slip it to a friend and they don't show
us to anybody and then it's on the internet.
Who knows?
You know, you're in a menace to society thing.
Yes.
Brook Adams inquires.
Maybe this has been discussed before, but top three favorite bands.
I guess that's got to be an all time question.
I mean, that's, that's difficult.
I know mine.
Go for it.
Fumantue.
Motorhead.
Bad religion.
Wow.
All right.
That's my three.
You like a, like a hard rock and tune.
I do.
Yeah.
And I like a sing song and tune.
Okay.
And I find that both bands, the bands will bring you both.
A stone groove, if you will.
Okay.
I'm going to say and don't hold me to this, but I'm going to say Elvis Costello on the attractions.
I'm going to say Queens of the Stone Age.
And I'm going to say Pixies.
Yep.
So they're all great.
Samantha Lippard in Choirs.
Creepiest encounter with a fan.
Coolest encounter with a fan.
Can be fans of the podcast or just y 'all's larger body of work.
You know, all my, I recognize you come from Vine.
And they're always very young girls.
And it honestly, they're not, it's just a girl saying, hey, I like your stuff.
Or whatever, but it always felt creepy because I felt like they're dads or something.
And one time these two very young girls sat at my table in Vegas.
They were like, are you having like, are you partying here?
Like we should hang out.
Right.
I was like, are you guys even 18?
Like, what are we talking about?
Right.
That was mildly creepy.
But it's nice to be recognized at our level where you're getting recognized once a bloom wound.
It's nice.
Yeah, yeah.
Drug history once in a while.
Been had any.
I haven't had any creepy ones.
I've had ones where like a guy, it's usually a guy who's too drunk to understand when the conversation is over.
Sure.
That's pretty nuts.
I wish you though, right?
Yeah, yeah.
It's me following them home.
So when did you first start to like me?
Yes.
But it's usually I'm approached.
Oddly approach, but stand up more by men and podcasts more by women.
It's almost exclusively one or the other.
Yeah.
But it's the guys that don't know when to quit usually.
But but not all of them.
Just some of them.
Sure.
And what about that period of time where Robert De Niro was a knife salesman.
And he was sort of your biggest fan and started kind of honing in on you and your family.
Well, that's back when I played major league baseball.
That was a long time ago and I can't believe that was a movie.
I'd love to see that again.
And he worked as a knife salesman for like three months leading up to the movie.
De Niro worked as a knife salesman.
Yeah.
They said he'd be coming with cuts on his hands.
I mean, the movie made sense to me at the time.
It was decent.
I never saw it.
But I was like, oh, yeah, it's like a taxi driver kind of thing.
It was decent.
I never saw it.
Gary Myron asks, who is Joe's biggest musical influence for demon riot?
Oh, wow.
Thank you for listening.
Few people have heard it.
Honestly, Tom Waits was the biggest influence.
I wanted to...
I was trying to make songs that sounded like, you know, if Tom Waits used electronic instruments
like his Catch Your Songs.
That's basically what I wanted it to sound like.
So Tom Waits mainly.
Okay.
Cody Vickner asks, if either of you could bring back any cancelled TV show, what would it be?
Pat, you can't choose your own.
Thank you for that.
Sure.
You know, I mean, the ones I truly love, I would be too scared to have them back and have
them suck.
You know, I don't need to see Seinfeld now.
Well, that's a cancelled though.
Well, yeah.
All right.
That's true.
You know, we're getting a lot of these.
Like, we got arrested development, although, you know, I'm not sure what that was.
I think the new season is supposed to be better.
Um, cancelled show, Joe, you got one?
I'm going to go with designated survivor.
Uh, you watched designated survivor.
I don't watch it.
But I read yesterday it was cancelled.
It's my dad's favorite show.
He has talked to me about it endlessly.
Is it key for that one?
Yeah.
Okay.
And when I saw it was cancelled out loud by myself, I went, oh no, I really feel sorry for my dad.
Sure.
He loves the show.
When I went to, um, uh, I did a WGA one day showrunner training course because I had never run a show.
And I was like, I should do this.
And the guy who did most of the talking was, uh, I believe the showrunner of designated survivor.
And he must, it's what it's what people do because your life becomes the show.
And you forget that most people don't watch the show.
But he would just say like, I mean, you all saw this episode, right, of designated where we were.
And you're like, no, no one has seen designated survivor.
But it was, it was funny to me.
Your dad would have been able to answer.
Um, yeah, if I could bring back anything, you know, I can't remember the last time a show's cancellation infuriated me.
I, I don't know.
You know what I really liked if I'm being honest recently was love.
I could have watched six more seasons of love.
Most of my friends hate it.
There's something so pleasant about it.
And I would watch it all 10 in a day.
It's the only show I binged.
It is canceled.
Yeah.
I loved love.
They got three scenes on Netflix.
Have you ain't seen it?
Check it out.
Tons of people have issues with it.
I love it.
A lady dynamite guy canceled too.
What the hell?
It was an interesting show.
I understand the cancellation.
That was too weird for even Netflix.
I think haters back off got canceled.
That never seen it.
That lady's got like, she's like one of the biggest YouTube.
Stars out there.
It's like.
I assume they didn't follow her to the thing.
I mean, if they were getting the numbers,
they wouldn't have canceled it.
I assure you.
Yeah.
Anyway.
Okay.
This one's a little.
I'm going to edit this one a little.
Scott Patton asks.
Pat, whatever happened to your writing partnership.
How do you feel about writing partnerships in general?
I, yeah, I used to have a writing partner.
The shitty thing about it is you split your money in half.
Yeah.
You're every week your paycheck is cut in half.
And eventually that gets to you.
Having a writing partner can be very helpful in the early days of your partnership.
Helping navigate it.
It's a terrible brutal business that helps to have somebody to talk about it with.
So go for it.
But you know, in my case,
I felt I could do it alone.
And you know, there you go.
Mike Madrigal asks.
Mike, go to Mr. Suit Records when you're in Lancaster, Pennsylvania.
Go to Mr. Suit Records.
Who do I talk to about getting a reboot of Colchac the night stalker starring the boys?
Follow up.
Who should play Colchac and who should play the editor, Tony Vincenza?
I've never seen the show.
But you can talk to everyone in the world and they will all tell you no.
But Joe, what do you think?
I think I'm without a doubt the grumpy hard -boiled editor.
Sure.
I think you're more the frisky detective.
Frisky sounds right.
But you know, so you're Tony Vincenza.
Yeah.
Nobody's buying me as a Tony Vincenza.
That's for sure.
They did reboot Colchac at one point with.
I'm going to have to look it up.
But Colchac was rebooted at one point to no success really.
But I actually agree Mike.
That's interesting that you asked that question because I recently bought the Colchac Double Feature DVD.
And I was, as I was watching it, I was like, why is this not a fucking show?
Like this could be a show now.
Yeah.
And you know, somebody should remake this.
And then I looked it up and it was like, oh, somebody did remake it.
And it didn't work.
So they're probably not going to remake it again.
I'm trying to find, let's see, legacy.
No.
Come on.
Yeah, here we go.
2005 television series.
Stuart Townsend played Colchac.
Okay.
Who also played Dorian Gray in the League of Extraordinary Gentlemen.
Yeah.
I remember him.
I think he was in Dracula 2002.
He's from Dublin.
He must be married to Charlize Theron.
Nice.
Good job, dude.
But anyway, he was in the...
It's not Tully, by the way.
Interesting flick.
It looks pretty good.
I mean, it's...
I like it.
I like a lot of rightman stuff.
It seems...it seems to be sort of an amalgam of...
his other movies.
Yeah, it is.
But it had a really interesting third act development, I will say.
Rightman's movies feel like they inspired like the Hulu boom of...
I agree.
The white people having issues.
I'll tell you my one issue with Tully.
They have...
Ron Livingston, the guy from office space.
Yeah.
And...
Mark Duploss.
Right.
And Duploss is playing Tully's brother.
Livingston is playing her husband.
So there are scenes where they're like standing next to each other.
They look like identical twins.
And they're not...
They're not brothers.
It was insane.
Yeah, yeah.
When I saw the trailer, I remember thinking,
oh, Mark Duploss is in this and then going,
oh, wait, no, it was Ron Livingston.
Yeah.
And then at the end realizing it was both...
When they're next to each other, I mean, my eyes were going back and forth.
I couldn't tell the two apart.
Mitch Oliver asks,
who would you rather take to prom Betty or Veronica?
The dark -haired one.
I think it's Betty.
No, it's Veronica.
Veronica.
Okay, I think I'm Veronica too.
Interestingly, and I just texted Joe this,
I was asked if I would have any interest in running a new Archie cartoon.
In the same world where we have Riverdale,
an Archie cartoon,
and then my agent sent this to me and was like,
they'd like you to have a pretty vast knowledge of the Archie verse
and also some experienced animation.
I was like, I don't really have either,
and I'm not sure I can pursue this.
If you want me to like create the Archie world.
Well, I was actually happy to hear that they're doing a cartoon.
I think it's depressing that the only iteration of Archie comics out there,
right now, is this fucking murder sex romp.
I mean, it's a good show,
but I think there should be the light side of it too.
I can't believe Archie has been around this long.
It's four teenagers hanging out.
I mean, I don't understand why people return to this,
but here we are.
You got me.
Lorenz Bunganiers asks to Joe.
I don't know if this is okay to ask,
but since you've mentioned it on the Emotional Hangs podcast,
and since I'm just really curious about it,
I was wondering if you've had any more sexual experiences
with transgenders.
I have not.
Okay.
For asking, I'm not, I'm not adverse to it.
You know, we've just got to have many transgenders.
The right time.
Approach him.
Yeah.
And thank you, by the way, to all of you,
telling me, congrats, and enjoy my honeymoon and all that.
I'm not reading it, but I appreciate it.
Thank you.
That's nice.
Stephen Rees asks,
or will you and Joe ever collaborate on a movie or TV script?
That was kind of the first question.
Hope so.
Michael Rose asked,
did you guys like fire in the sky?
And do you think moving violations would have been a hit
with Bill Murray instead of John?
I remember moving violations,
and I remember it being kind of funny, but I was a kid.
I tried to revisit it recently.
Yeah.
It certainly would have been a bigger hit with Bill Murray.
I would imagine Bill got the first offer before they went to John.
And I used to love fire in the sky.
It's a terrifying and really kind of naturalistic almost.
The alien sequences are some of the scariest things I've ever seen.
Yeah. Great.
Great moving.
DB Swaney, baby.
Awesome.
Huh?
He's a nut.
DB Swaney.
We also got a rubber Patrick in there.
Yes.
Playing like that.
Yeah.
Hillbilly guy with a pickup truck.
Do you know speaking of DB Swaney?
I don't even know if I told you this, but your competition for the role of the beloved
role of Gary on CBS's Living Biblically was DB Swaney.
He came in an audition.
He had giant button chops.
He was funny.
But it was DB Swaney.
The star of fire in the sky and the star of the cutting edge.
But he came in and it was a funny audition.
It was too big.
But it was funny.
And then at the end, he was showing a picture of this girl on his phone and started
humping his phone.
And it was just kind of like too much.
DB.
But he was great.
And I later had dinner with him.
And he drank a bunch and told hilarious stories.
He was a nice man.
Starting hanging out with DB Swaney.
Yes.
Douglas Wood asks, what is your choice for your unlimited last meal if and when you're about
to be executed?
Always a reliably fascinating question, a window into people's lives.
I know dessert for me is a full sheet cake.
Finally, I would be free to eat the sheet cake.
And then hopefully, I would just, oh, I think we talked about this once and you said you wanted
to eat so much that you shot to such a degree that the pigs who juiced you had to clean up your
shit.
I think we had that discussion.
Yeah.
I'd like that.
I'm going to go probably from a place that closed here in Los Angeles, my favorite dish at
my favorite restaurant was the Massaman Curry at Red Corner Asia Thai.
That followed by a full sheet cake.
I'm going seafood buffet.
The one that we go to?
No.
Good one.
Okay.
Like unlimited lobster, clams, what are they called?
Steam clams, mussels in a red sauce, crab legs, the big ones, and then a big, I'll also have
a sheet cake for dessert, but mine will be chocolate.
Now how about we get a half and half sheet cake so we're not glutton and they juice us right
next to each other?
All right.
I'm going to do it.
Where are you hold hands?
David Bellinger asked, what are your favorite movie soundtrack albums?
Terrific question.
Oh, man.
Mine is hands.
My number one is hands down the judgment night soundtrack.
I thought you might say that.
It's a great soundtrack.
I love it.
It's never gotten old to me.
It's great.
Followed closely by the trespass soundtrack, which is one of the great hip -hop
compilations of all time, gets almost zero recognition.
Cool movie, too.
I would say Boogie Nights is a big and the cassette I listened to while mowing lawns for
several years was the American graffiti soundtrack.
I also used to look, that's like 40 great oldies, and I used to listen to the Kirkland soundtrack
a lot, which is kind of great old soul music.
But lately, it's hard to argue with like a pulp fiction is a great one.
I remember my parents got it from me and I was so excited.
I had not seen the film and a boom box.
I played it.
It starts.
Any of you motherfucking pricks move.
I'll execute every motherfucking one of you.
Yeah.
My mom deleted the disc, put it back in the case, and said, good thing I kept the receipt and
walked it out of the room.
That's rough.
Yeah.
But all of Tarantino's, he does great, he does great soundtracks, and the carpenter's
stuff now is great for writing, as I've recommended.
I agree.
Alex J. Walker asks, who are some of Joe's favorite hip -hop artists that are currently putting out
music?
Well, Tsar Faces, my number one, I say that a lot on different podcasts.
If you're not familiar, it's 70 and esoteric, who were, sorry, seven Allen esoteric, who
were a duo from Boston, and they teamed up with Inspector Deck from Wu Teng, who's my favorite
Wu Teng member, and they did Tsar Faces.
They've got about five albums out at this point.
They really crank it out.
They just did an album with MF Doom called Tsar Faces, Meets Metal Face, very good stuff.
So they're way, way, way up my list.
I still like a lot of the digging in the crates crew.
They still put stuff out, show an A .G., and Lord Finesse and Diamond D, and those guys, and
then Wu Teng, I'll say too.
Also, yeah, they are still making music.
Yeah.
Now, are we going to get to hear that scurrelly?
Well, it was taken away from them so possibly.
They took, yeah, I hope so.
I love that the judge took it.
I mean, I hope they just made a shitty album.
He played snippets of it on the internet, and it sounded good.
It sounded good, but I mean, I heard 30 seconds of it, that was a fucking thing, but I'd
love to hear it.
Right.
Yeah.
Well, you didn't ask me, so I'm not going to tell you.
I do love one of my favorite albums for getting high too, is Young Thug's album, where he is
naked and covering his dick.
I don't remember the name of it, about three, four years old, terrific album, Young Thug.
I think you're right.
And you introduced me to a gentleman named Chink Struggs, who has a song called I'm a
Coke Boy.
I love the song I'm a Coke Boy.
He's a great rapper.
His name, sadly, is Chink Struggs, I don't know what to tell you, but he's great as well.
Yeah.
So there you go.
Now, this one I was hoping we would get because I wanted to ask you to do this.
Have you done this yanny or Laurel thing yet?
No, it's a sweep in the internet like that shirt that half the people thought was blue or
whatever.
Remember that one?
No.
Half the people were like, this shirt's blue.
And the other half were like, what are you talking about?
It's yellow.
And it went on.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
All right.
I'm going to play this.
You tell me if you hear the word yanny or Laurel, I know exactly what I heard.
But Heather, this morning, heard the other one.
It's nuts.
Honestly, we wondered if we should even get married if we, since we both heard different
things.
Okay.
All right.
Here we go.
Oh, yeah.
I agree to Twitter's use of cookies, bitch.
Yanny, yanny, I am blown away.
I can only hear Laurel clearly saying, yanny, I hear very clearly Laurel.
This is honestly very interesting to me.
I don't hear anything close to yanny.
I don't hear anything close to Laurel.
Well, maybe we're not supposed to get married either, Joe.
I mean, I'm going to tell you, I find that shit really interesting.
I don't understand it.
But now, how about this?
Let me set the stage for this.
I stumble up, shit face, saturday at the wedding, to the mic.
Socks, mocks, I just, let me say one thing.
And I do this for the whole audience.
Yeah.
And then I go, the beauty of these two kids, one of them heard yanny, the other heard Laurel.
And that's what it's about.
Yeah.
And don't explain what you're talking about, you know?
Because I'm sure like my grandma will know exactly what you mean when you get up there.
Lawrence Crazy Horse Anderson, a fantastic name, asked during the final scene to the series,
what was revealed about Joe's character and the Amazon show by night?
I understood Joe was the Rod Sirling host character, but the final scene was intended to make him
a part of the show and give his character more significance than simply being a host.
I didn't get the reveal, but maybe I'm dumb.
Love the show, Joe.
Well done.
Thank you.
It was fun to be a part of it.
And watch by night on Amazon.
Prime if you can, please.
Yeah.
It's, you know, look, I'm kind of in the dark too.
It's hinting that this, the basic hint or idea is that I've been in that room.
And who knows where in time and space it is with, with these recording devices,
recording these accounts that I'm remembering, these, these, you know,
these, these happenings that I'm aware of, which are the stories that you see.
And then the, the wolf who comes in when the, in the, in the fedora and the coat
is obviously connected to these things somehow because you see him in some of the stories.
So I guess the idea is that eventually we'll find out how I got there and why I'm there
and why I know these things.
Is there going to be a season two?
I don't know.
I guess it depends on how well it does.
When did you shoot this?
It sees in one.
It's shooting like a week and you just shot all that above and the afters thing?
They already shot the stories and then we're looking for somebody to come in
and be like a host.
And then, yeah, and then during that process, they made me a little, a character a little
bit bigger.
I don't even remember you going to shoot this or make a shot at everything in a day.
Oh, okay.
And the voiceover and every, like, the whole thing I did in a day didn't take long.
Samantha Kiefer asks, which A24 film is your favorite?
Lady Bird, disaster artist, sacred deer, Florida project, comes at night, lobster, ex -Mahina,
which moonlight, etc.
Tusk!
And I stand by it.
Oh, Joe, I mean, I love that you throw that back out there because it just gives me so
much more credibility.
I haven't seen killing of a sacred deer.
I've been dying, too, but I've heard it's like painfully slow.
So I've been waiting for the right time to do it.
And I also haven't seen it comes at night, but it's very divisive movie.
My favorite of those is probably Moonlight or ex -Mahina, I thought there were both great
movies, you know, very different movies.
Good.
Scott Swaney asked, did you guys know that 90s alternative rock band lit still exists and
have gone country?
What a wild world.
I knew who he has gone country.
But not lit.
Is lit.
It's been a while.
Lit is you make me come.
You make me complete.
Who's saying it's been a while because that guy does stained that guy does country now.
Really?
Yeah.
You know, good for them.
You gotta, you gotta adapt with the times hoodies made more money as country than they did
with hoody hoody knocked it out of the park.
Twice.
I met hoody.
Pete and I were hanging with the guy, the lead singer of the national whose friends
with Pete, I guess we went to some post Grammy party and hoody was there sitting completely
alone.
Couldn't have been nicer.
Delightful man.
I got no beef with hoody.
I hated his music.
But what are you going to do?
Why would you?
And then Samantha Lippert says, this news will have Pat feeling palm -freetly miserable.
So I must have talked about my experiencing lit on the podcast at some point, which I don't
remember.
But I saw lit at one of those 90s nights, sugar ray, gin, blossom, lit, etc.
They were good.
Palm -freetly, what the hell is that mean?
Their song is, you make me calm, you make me complete, you make me completely miserable.
Oh.
The night of, I was very high and I started singing, you make me palm, you make me palm -freet,
you make me palm -freetly miserable.
This is why they want you on the Archie show.
Yeah.
Exactly.
That's Archie level comedy right there.
Yeah.
If my offer from Bazooka Joe doesn't come through, I'll go do the Archie show.
Will Potorf ask, hey guys, what are your all -time favorite video games of all time?
Kind of a redundant question, Will, you put all time in two places just so you know.
Also Joe, have you ever played the Dark Souls Bloodborne games?
I feel like they'd be right up your alley with their horror influences and difficulty.
Glad you guys love the art.
We truly do.
Thank you for doing it.
I was joking when I made fun of your grammar, lots of love.
My favorite video game of all time, I have two, I have three.
Mario for Wii, the most satisfying game -beating experience I've ever had in my life.
Paperboy, original, can't get enough, and Tetris can't get enough in any form.
Joe.
My top three video games, Devils Crush for TurboGraphic 16, Resident Evil 4 for Super Nintendo, and
then, yeah, I haven't played Dark Souls, but I did play Bloodborne, and it was a gorgeous game,
and it was great, but it was too fucking hard, I couldn't get anywhere in it, man, I just kept
dying, like over and over, I couldn't, and everybody I talked to, I was like, I can't get anywhere,
they were like, yeah dude, it takes a lot of practice, and I was like, I only have so much in me,
but it was a great game, I just wish I could have been a bit better at it, yeah.
Okay, a pretty cool stuff.
Tim Letzo inquires, Joe, when is emotional hangs coming back?
I don't know if it is, you know, when Ferral Audio folded,
we lost our network, and we didn't have a home for it, and that coincided with Kurt being out of
town, and myself being out of town at different times, and you know, scheduling stuff, so I don't
know, I mean, Kurt and I have talked about it, we're open to the idea of potentially bringing it back,
but we need the right, you know, it's got to make sense, we got to have time to do it first of all,
and then we also have to find a home for it. I don't want to, what I don't want to do is start
an episode, do an episode, put it out, and then we can't do another one for two months,
right, you know, so yeah, but thank you for asking.
And then he asks, muah, what is your favorite movie from the criteria and collection?
It's tough to say, I mean, the latest sounds of the Lambs one is fantastic, I was going to do it for
my next Joe's scary stuff, but man, it's great, looks great. I love the night of the Hunter one for
an old movie. I love the days to confuse one. I mean, they do good work.
Nick Muscarra asks, why did Joe tell Disney to ruin the Marvel Cinematic Universe?
Salamanders says, have you heard that song?
See, these are jokes, people. A couple of jokes, we can skip that one. I'll read it for you.
Have you heard that song? The mom number five? Where does he meet all these women? Who are these women?
That's pretty fine. It says Seinfeld Boys. John Watt asks, how about an episode or bonus episode
reviewing at least the first episode of the Freddy's Nightmares TV show? It's the only episode
that tie in directly to the continuity of the films, and it turns 30 this year.
Look, I'm all for that. If Pat, if you want to do that, I would love to do that. It's that. It's the,
it's the old, sure, never seen. It is one of maybe three episodes of that show, and it's still not
great, but it's good enough. It's good enough, and it also really set us. I was a fan. I mean, I was,
when they announced Freddy's Nightmares was coming out, I was beside myself. I couldn't wait
to get my eyes on it. And that first episode is truly misleading, because as he said, it's the only
one that ties into the story of Freddy and everything. And then after that, every episode is just a
shitty dream sequence, where the person doesn't know if they're a sleeper awake. Yeah. And Freddy
doesn't show up except at the beginning to be like, this week's tale, you don't like to do like a
crypt keeper thing. Sure. But I'll review that absolutely. All right. I'm curious to see it.
I have them. I have the DVDs. I will lend them to you. Emily Florence asks, can we go to hometown
buffet when I come to LA for the live show? Of course. Yes. Emily and Ken have been doing amazing
things. We are putting some live shows together. Thank you to you both. I've never been to hometown
buffet. I've been to old country, and I've been to the Vegas seafood buffet here in Glendale,
which is for some reason called Vegas seafood buffet. It's a real shit show in that place, man.
Yeah. The Glendale one was passable. The other one is breathable. Yeah. The Hollywood one is rough.
Yeah. Let's do, uh, yeah, let's do it. hometown buffet. I think it might be
what old country buffet turned into. I think that's right. Or it's one of those Wendy's
Carl's Jr. situations where it's a different name. Adam Loundsbury asks, what are your favorite
movies that were made before you were born? That was born in 1981. I mean, there's tons. I guess,
I love Alfred Hitchcock's notorious. That's my favorite Hitchcock movie. I watched the other night.
Incredible movie. Incredible movie. I'll say that for now. There's a good recommendation for you.
It has an exclamation point at the end, which you don't see enough. Airplane and notorious might be
the only two. I'd have to go with Star Wars. It came out two months before three months before I was
born. Okay. Cut it close. But, you know, that was the year I was born. So I'm going to go with that.
Good answer. Mick Mack. No questions. Just love and thank you. Thanks for the laughs in the community.
You fellas. Can an Emily have built around this podcast. Thank you. Enjoy the break. As always,
I'll be digging through the archives anytime I feel the need to hang with the fellas.
I have an amazing wedding summer and break from the pod. Love y 'all like a plate of food. Oh,
snap. Oh, by the way, since this is a bonus episode, we should announce this. The patreon,
you know, we'll put it on pause starting in May. Yeah. Yeah. So, you know, obviously, we're not
going to ask people to donate when we're not putting out content. So we'll put it on pause until we
return. Yes, that's important to note. Tristan Avery says it's starting in June. I mean, wait,
what the fucking month is it? It's May now. We're mid May. June 1st, it'll pause. Okay. So you'll get
charged for May. And this will be the bonus episode for May and then no charge after that.
Right. There until we're back. Tristan Avery asks, have you played your PlayStation VR at all?
If so, any horror games, many of them are genuinely frightening. I would love to. I have not really
played my PlayStation at all. I played that game where the big rock man was beating up the city or
it's called like crank or something. Crank? Clank? Crank 2. Why don't you give me that VR?
You see this collection. I know. Forged here. I know. What are you going to do with it?
I, well, I'd like to at least try it, but I'll give it to you. You come over here. You play it when
you're here. I don't work. I was joking, but the fact that you went for it. Okay. That's great news.
Steve Kauppa asks, system of a down is an all -time favorite of mine. I even met their drummer
outside the Glendale Cheesecake Factory last July. I was probably inside. What is your favorite
system of a down album? Do either of you own system albums on vinyl or CD? If neither of you own
one of their albums, Jesus, this guy backup singer, I recommend 2002, steal this album or 2005's
Mesmerize Hypnotized. I've only heard the singles and of course I love. Wake up.
Yeah. You want to do it? That's all I've heard, but I'll check them out.
I think front -to -back toxicity is their probably their strongest album. Sure. I love Mesmerize. I didn't
like Hypnotize. I thought that Hypnotize sounded... It was very differently produced than Mesmerize.
It was much muddier. Yeah. And I also thought that it sounded left over to me. It was not as good as
Mesmerize, though, had that great song. What the hell were you saying to the poor?
I'll see. Everybody's coming to the party. Have a real good time.
Yeah. I remember that one. And Mesmerize has my favorite system of a down song on it,
but I think toxicity is just a bigger, probably more complete album. There are a median, right?
Yes. But no, I don't have them on vinyl. I only have them on CD.
Osla Kvinzland, sorry if that's wrong. I'm sure that's wrong.
Seeing the new Predator trailer, thoughts. Joe text me other day. New Predator trailer looks horrible.
It's terrible. I watched it. I was sort of indifferent to it. It looked kind of generic to me.
I'll see it. Chain Black. I love. I will see it with hope. Yeah. But it's a bad trailer.
That trailer is cut together like a TV spot. A month into promotion. That is not a premiere trailer.
There's no hero shot of the fucking Predator. The times they do show them it's like side angles.
I'm like, what are you doing? It's an iconic monster. This is a huge sequel. This is a return.
Put some suspense into this thing, man. So I thought that the trailer was bad.
I'm not thrilled that there's a god damn joke in the trailer because I feel like the whole
tone in the movie is going to be joky. Right. And the fact that they even have to slip a joke.
I mean, you watch the trailers for any of the other Predator movies, even the bad ones.
There's not a god damn joke to be had. Yeah. So the fact that they had to slip one into this,
I was like, that's not a great sign. Not also thrilled that one of the main characters is clearly
going to be this little kid. You know, Shane Black right and directed. He directed it. I believe
he wrote it. I mean, it's never written a movie that's bad. I'm not paranoid about it. I agree.
I love Shane Black. I, as I said, I'll see you with it. But it did go through extensive research
shoots. And there's been a lot of, you know, clamoring around it about like, you know, what's going on
with this brand thing was announced a long fucking time ago. Yeah. So I don't think Shane Black
fucked anything up. I think if it sucks, it's the studios for it usually is. Yeah. Sarah Catherine
asks, can you guys review hereditary as soon as it comes out? I need to know if it's as good as the hype.
I don't think I'm more excited to see any movie than hereditary. Yeah, wait. And we'll do it for sure.
I can't wait. And yeah, that's definitely on the list. Looks great. Tim Kalfblish,
also probably wrong. Kalfblish. Have you ever had broken bones or something requiring some immediate
medical care? Do you have a story for it? Doesn't have to be an SD, but it's encouraged.
Yeah. I, I broke probably both wrists falling on my face, walking home from a bar,
not that drunk. And I was so embarrassed that I just got one casted up and I kind of let the other
one go because I was like, I can't walk around with two casts on my hands. And I've read it ever
since. I have like a weird clicking in my wrists and I'll probably have arthritis, but that's it.
I only have broken fingers. But when I was a small boy, I fell and banged my chin on the edge of a
coffee table and had to get stitches. All right. That's probably. And there's still a faint scar,
almost like an Indiana Jones or Tina Fey. Yeah. I fell off my huffy sonic six and got amnesia when
I was a kid. I probably told that story. Oh, wow. That's pretty cool. Parents had to wait me up at
one, three and five every morning and ask you my name, address and phone number. If he says he
doesn't remember, he's fine. That's normal. I also was not permitted to see Beetlejuice at the
theater because it would upset me. And I was furious because I really wanted to see Beetlejuice.
You could remember that you wanted to see Beetlejuice, but you couldn't remember who you were?
I snapped out of the amnesia pretty quickly. So then when your parents awaken you're up, it's like
all right. All right. Chuck Andrews asks, do stand -up comics have to hand out flyers on corners in LA?
I think they're getting that from crashing problem. Well, they don't, but that was a thing in New York.
Yeah. Are LA comics more privileged or just lazy? Probably both. I get that LA is where it all happens,
but with Netflix and HBO having more shows filmed in NY, do you still have to live there to make it
in comedy? No, not at all. For the record, I'm not an aspiring comic, which is curious.
You're better off in New York if you're trying to make it in comedy.
I would say either or, right? There's a thrive either. But I'd say if you're if you're only
goal is I want to be an undeniable comedian, I don't care about anything else, you're going to get
a lot more bang for your buck in New York. That's probably true. But yeah.
He also asks, what are your three favorite metal bands, which is kind of your answers the same,
basically. Yeah, I'm not a big metal guy at all. All right. Yeah, we can keep moving. Okay.
Yeah. Anthony Guajardo asks, you guys both clearly hated the dog shit that was
chappy. I'm not a fan either, but the soundtrack is one of my favorite things to listen to.
Is it Diane word? Do they also do the music for it? I have no idea. Do you guys have anything like
that where you hate the movie, but love the music? I can't separate it. If I'm hating a movie,
I'm not like, ooh, but I like this tune here. It doesn't happen.
Shit. You know what? I think I do I think I do have one. Okay.
Yeah. You know what's a great soundtrack and not a great movie. And I'm going to get blowback
on this. No pun intended. Blow. The movie blow is like like it's like an impression of a
Scorsese movie. It is. And I saw it in high school, which is the time when impressions of
Scorsese movies are very entertaining to people of that age, boondocks, saints, and etc. But I
remember liking blow. I'll give it another shot. I like Paul Rubin's in it. It doesn't infuse. I
don't hate it. I don't think it's just I don't think it's terrible. But it goes. It goes. It's ridiculous
with the squirt. It's the freeze frame and the voiceover. I didn't know what was up but what was
down. It's very interesting to me how many times Johnny Depp has played gangsters like he's not in
any way Italian unless I'm crazy. Donnie Brasco black mass that one black mass he was supposed to
be Irish from Boston. And he's still it's I love black mass, but he sounded like he was from the like
Bronx. Yeah, I don't have that. And I do want to just state again on the record how much I hated
Chappy. Tucker, fuck Chappy. Tucker Roush asked if you could remake any film what would it be and why?
You know what? I would love to see. And it's a classic. But they've already made sequels that
have kind of tainted the brand is midnight run. You're not going to do better than deniro and
Gordon. But I'd like them to not cast comedians cast some real actors. I talked about gozzling
and trying to get more. Well, you know, I'd like to see it with with some serious actors of today.
You know what? Gozzling play. It might doesn't have to be gozzling. No, but I think he'd be great in
the deniro role. He would be. He would be. And then the the good adjacent Bateman maybe in the
Groden role. I like that. Who's the modern day Groden? I mean, Groden is a true original to me.
I mean, he's doing some nobody's doing the man's a powerhouse. Yeah. But I told him not my shoes.
Actually, he's in a move with Jason Bateman called the X and he's the only funny part of it.
Bateman's funny in it though because he plays a prick in a wheelchair. I always find that funny.
But yeah, Groden's the guys, the guys and I'll tell you what, I'd like to see it with gozzling and Groden.
Yeah, still Groden. Groden is an 83 year old guy running from the mob. Yeah, I'd do that.
Yeah, okay, there you go. Do you have one? What do you want to see remade?
Not really. No, I like that idea. Okay. Yeah.
Sean Pinnock, are you guys open to bringing any other people into the hog house like special guests?
We were just talking about this. We've never done it.
But I think couldn't hurt. I think it'd be fun. Yeah, we were just talking about this.
We're very open to it. We know that Karen Kilgarif would like to come be a part of an episode and
we'd love to have her be a dream. And if we were going to do this, I'm assuming she'd probably
be our first guest. But yeah, maybe some special episodes. We were thinking for the commentary episodes.
It would be fun to bring in a third person. Sure can kind of. Oh, that would help tremendously.
Yeah, mediate, pet me. Yeah, maybe even keep us watching the movie. Remind us that we're doing a
commentary. Kevin Marcinic asks, how much would I have to pay you guys to do a live episode at my
birthday party next year? It'd be a smaller audience, probably just the three of us in my danger pad,
parents basement. Depends on where you live. I mean, if you're in LA, that price is real low.
We'll be there. But if you're in Alaska, you know, they'd have to be an airfare. Yeah, probably.
Yeah, that's nowhere you live. I mean, look, everybody's got a price. I mean, springsteam plays birthday
party. That's true. We'd do it, Kevin. Talk to us. Talk to us. Money talks, baby. Leo Lopez, what are
your most unexpectedly emotional horror movie experiences? Sometimes a good script is a good script.
Also, Joe, I'd love to, okay, one, one at a time. Most unexpectedly emotional horror movie experiences.
Okay. My number one is the orphanage because it starts as this really kind of creepy thing. And you
think that this burned up kid is the ghost that's burned up kid is evil and whatever. And then you realize
that the Annie's not evil. He just like wants to be loved and it's this beautiful. I remember seeing it
with my girlfriend at the time. She was crying like it was beautiful. Yeah. And to that, very similar. I
knock up on me as well in a similar way. Right. Also, Joe, I'd love to hear you explain the razor soft
line of Sega Genesis games to an uninterested pat for a scary stuff segment. I'll tell you. Wait, I'm
sorry. The what? The razor soft line of Sega Genesis games. Oh, razor soft, the developer. Okay,
of of Sega Genesis games. What did razor soft, let me see what they developed. I'm not, we're not
gonna do it right now, but let me see razor soft. Joseph Ray goes in choirs. What are some of your
guys favorite Netflix series? I gotta tell you, I wish there were more that I love, you know, I know
everybody wants to be in business, you know, doing shows with them, but it's rare. I feel like it's one
year that I really love. I, of course, I loved love, as I said earlier, I like Stranger Things.
Yeah, I don't know. What are you like on Netflix? Stranger Things is my favorite by far. Yeah.
You know, I don't know. Yeah, no Stranger Things. I'm gonna go with that. That's my favorite by far.
You know, the other ones I dip in and out and I enjoy them and stuff, you know, but I like Stranger Things.
That's unexcited for it to come back. I care about the kids. I want to see, I hope the actors all
do well in their careers. Like, I just, I really am touched by the show. Yeah, I agree.
Alex Shipley asks, is there a movie that made you cry unexpectedly? I got caught off guard by how to
train your dragon. Yes, I mean, of course, I, yes, my big two are the final scene of about
Schmidt where I had to run ahead of my friends so that they would not see me crying. So embarrassed
was I and like right out of high school or something. And then 127 hours, a very similar thing where I
could not stop crying on the walks of the car on the way home. My friends were getting uncomfortable.
I feel like and I could not stop crying. And they're both about closing yourself off emotionally.
So there you go. But that's it. That's the last time that happened, I think.
Several times when I've watched the untouchables that I'm not expecting to cry, start crying when
Malone dies. Okay. When Connery gets killed. Yeah. And I mean, for some reason never expect it and
it happens a lot. Okay. That's that that that one's got me a bunch of times. John Devers, how do you guys
feel about Stephen King's The Stand reportedly being developed as a miniseries for CBS all access?
Well, I'll tell you, it's it's CBS. It's going to be a goddamn disaster. That's a guarantee. I
give terrible notes and they're terrible people. I look I mean, look, I'll watch any Stephen King
adaptation. I'm really excited for this Castle Rock anthology show coming out. Me too. The bar is pretty
low with the other stand adaptation. It's fine, but you know, he's never even about it. No, and I
got to say too that, you know, the problem now with the stand adaptation is there have been so many,
it's not Stephen King's fault. It's it's just what's happened in recent years. There have been so many
movies about plagues wiping out civilization. I think they're going to they're going to have a
challenge to make this feel, you know, as original as it was at the time again. Right. But, but I,
you know, I'll watch it. I mean, I thought they were doing a movie with McConaughey, but then I guess
probably that dark tower killed that, which I never even saw. Well, McConaughey played the man in black
in the dark tower. Yeah. And and that same character is also in the stand. He's the devil guy in
the stand. So maybe they were going to have him cross over and start like a Stephen King multiverse
kind of thing. But yeah, the dark, I'm reading the dark tower right now. It's a great book.
I had never read it. I didn't know much about it. And it's really cool. It's very like Star Wars
Esk. I never read those. I was not into it. Didn't see the movie. But then I was like, well,
I want to see the movie now. Like, so I went in online and started reading up on the movie and the movie
sounds terrible. It's supposed to be. Yeah. Yeah. Like, so I don't know. I'll watch it one day.
Kevin Driscoll, what who are your strongest writing influences?
For me, unquestionably John Hughes, I just I love that he makes every line funny and interesting.
This new kind of harsh re -examining of his work is valid, of course, but it's also a little frustrating.
I mean, the man did so many great things. And some things are unfortunately badly dated. But you know,
that's that's what that's what the entertainment industry is all about. I agree with Bill
Mars Point, which as a sentence, I rarely say on the John Hughes thing. He's like, you can't expect
woke to have happened before woke existed. You can't go back 30 years ago. He's called Bill Mar
for saying that. But you know, they did. They hated him for saying that. But I mean, that's how progress
works. It's true. I mean, otherwise, it's just consistency. The way you progress as you look back and
you go, oh, remember when that was okay. That's not okay anymore. That's fine. But to say, you know,
I question whether or not John Hughes was a decent man for missing this. Sure. It's a come on, man.
I'll say though, you know, when I was in like the I I sold a couple screenplays,
that couple like teen movies, whatever. And they seem to encourage for a while like what if it's
an ugly fat girl that they're hooking up with? And like, you know, that was always like the gross
thing like the guy had to like close his eyes and kiss a fat girl or some there was never a period in
my life where I thought that that was cool. I think what they're saying is people should have known
it wasn't right at the time. And I see I see both sides of that argument, you know, but I don't
I don't really love beating up John Hughes because he had long duck dong in a movie as rough as
that character is to watch now. Well, that that I understand. Yeah. You know, it's 1980,
whatever. Maybe you don't have a gong sound effect every time the Chinese guy walks in. Yeah, that
was nuts. Yeah. That, you know, some of this stuff I can see, and you know, look, when I first saw
the breakfast club as a kid, I didn't think it was okay to grope a woman. Sure. But I also understand
that the movie features characters that are fucking troubled. Jud Nelson is playing this fucking
problem kid like he's fucked up. Yeah. A lot of times now when people get upset that an awful
character like uses a slur or something, it's like, well, but are you not supposed to paint the truth
of these people? Look, dude, I'm uh, that that that does concern me about, you know, Lars, there's a big
stink about Lars van Trier's new movie. A hundred people walked out of the con screening. Look, by the
these cons screen and con things I'm talking to him now, but these cons screenings, there are two
options. One, the entire theater booze and walks out or two of 49 minute standing ovation. Right.
I thought the French were supposed to be like not easily impressed. Well, who's standing up applauding
for 10 minutes? I'd like walk out. Well, let me tell you this too. The hundred people that walked out
were American filmmakers, I guarantee it was probably eight people. And but anyway, but there's all
this stuff on, you know, it's disgusting. One, one woman wrote, yeah, the torturing of women and
children is not art and it never will be. And I think that's kind of boiling down. I don't think
that's the point. I don't think he's sitting there saying, isn't it artistic to torture people? Yeah.
It's a fictional story. He says in the fucking trailer, the voiceover is Matt Dylan going, people say
that we get our baser things out through our art that we can't express in real life or whatever.
So maybe it may be it's a commentary on humanity. Why is it? Why is the only interpretation?
This must be what Lars van Trier wants to do to people. Sure. I think that's crazy. Somebody wrote
the act. I can't remember the actress's name, but they were like watching her get tortured. And
it's like, you're not watching her get tortured. Right. You're watching a character. She's playing get
tortured. Yeah. And this person was in the goddamn movie. Like she clearly was okay with it. So it's
like just the man is a provocateur who made a critically acclaimed movie where you saw a dick get nailed.
Well, that got a ton of shit at Khan too. Yeah. I mean, don't go see Lars van Trier movie. It's
that simple people. He wants to fuck with you. He loves it. Yeah. One guy wrote, can't
Lars van Trier just make a normal movie for one? It's like, should you know what he does? And you're still
pissed. Yeah. Number one, why did you go if you don't like what he does? Don't go then. Right.
Anyway, uh, who was your favorite filmmaker asked Patrick Baxter? Scorsese. He's easy for me.
Joe? Uh, favorite filmmaker. Look, I, you know, another controversial figure, but I can't deny it.
Over my lifetime, I've gotten the most enjoyment out of Woody Allen's body of work. Like I, yeah, he's
put out the highest percentage of stuff that I've enjoyed. You know, because he also puts out a movie
a year. So if you don't like one, you're like, who cares? There'll be another one next year.
Ireland's Corsese for you. Woody Allen. Uh, only because of, uh, quantity. Okay. Because
Corsese, he's made a bunch of movies too. He has. I love Corsese. Corsese does a lot that I don't
care about. Sure. So once you start, once you go, okay, I don't want to see Cundan. I don't want
to see, uh, silence, silence. I don't want to see the set for the snores. One of the ones with
a plane and the sun in the background. Sure. Uh, those are few and far between. But, you know,
good fellows, of course, Cousine. Yeah. Yeah. Maybe. All right. I know Cape Fear,
Raging Bull Taxi driver. I'm going to put Corsese, neck and neck, but I will say this.
I related more to a lot of the characters. The characters I saw depicted in the Woody Allen movies,
the neuroses and, and Albert Brooks is a big one for me. Love Albert Brooks, but, but he,
he tapered off in my opinion, in a big one. Chris Good Knight asks, what comic books does Joe
read on any sort of a regular basis? Trades or floppies? I don't know what that means. Uh,
no, I do know what that means. I don't know what floppies means. Trade paperbacks, I think, right?
And then probably just the paper floppy comic guy. So, well, I read mostly the collections,
like graphic, not either graphic novels or the, I forget what they're called, like the Omni bus,
whatever collections. I'm not reading anything at the moment. I'm reading fiction literature at the
moment, but the last thing I was reading was saga, the swamp thing, which I'm still not finished.
And I would like to finish, but it's six volumes, and it's terrific, but it's a lot. It's a lot of
pretty damn good. I really would like to read, the next comic I will read is white, his Batman white
knight, which my friend, John Harrow, what's told me about. And it's a story of the Joker
taking a new medication that makes him sane. And then everybody thinks Batman is the bad guy
for treating an insane person inappropriately. That's a very, very sharp, uh, commentary for what's,
you know, what's going on right now. I should, I'd love to read that. And I haven't read a comic
since Alf had comics. That's true. Alex Nelson asks, what were each of your first official writing
jobs? Mine was my, well, my first unofficial was Robin Bigg, the MTV reality show. And Robin Bigg,
we're not speaking to each other in the third season. And I was brought in to write things for them
to say. Okay. But that was as a quote, creative consultant, because you can't be a writer on a
reality show. My first official writing job is it's always something I thought up. And mine was the
Pete Homes show. Yes. The late nighter. Yes. Actually, it's not true. That wasn't my first job,
but that was the, I wrote for some other stuff before that, but that, that was the job that got,
again, it was, you build as a consultant or whatever, but that's the job that got me into the
union and all that stuff. We are, we're down to like the last three, Joe. We're very close. Okay.
I don't know how long we've been going here. This is our longest yet. About an hour and 15. Okay.
Maybe not. William Shanahan asks, most overrated comedians or comedy actors. Oh boy, where to begin?
Most overrated comedians and comedy actors. I got to. I think this is dying out a little bit,
but I'm going to say the, the boom of handsome actors being comedians. It reached its bottom with
Baywatch where we paired handsome with handsome. There was no funny, man, the rock and Zach Efron.
Yep. You know, like an Efron, a Timberlake, all these people who, you know, have just kind of,
because they're attractive and we're shocked, they're not idiots. They're suddenly comedians.
That doesn't work for me. And then my other one is just this huge tier of 20 or so comedic actors
who play every supporting role in every major comedy. And I'm not saying they weren't funny at one
point, but you get sick to death of looking at these fucking people. Do they're one very limited thing
over and over and over. And of course, I can't name any of these people because I'll probably work
with them all at some point. Yeah. I'm kind of tired of awkward getting sick of it. That's still a
thing. That's still a thing. I don't know what I'm saying. I don't know how ridiculous the words
are coming out of my mouth. It was old, you know, four seasons into the office remake. Yeah.
You know, at this point, it's, it's just unfucking bearable. It's, you know, so talk like an adult
is always what I want to say when somebody's like, yeah, I can't stand that too. And look,
I'll say this flat out. Most comedians these days are doing one of two things. They're doing
baseless or unsubstantial sex material where they're trying to be cute and clever. And frankly,
both make me inherently just sick to my fucking stomach. I can't fucking stand it. People, I also
can't stand the amount of people that are trying to have suddenly have a perspective on things. And
it's like, dude, you were talking about skateboarding a week ago. Shut the fuck up. So, you know, comedy
really sucks right now. There's not a lot of people out there kind of being honest. And I think
that's why podcasts are doing so well. And I'm happy for my friends who have successful podcasts
because I feel like it's people being themselves and being honest in a humorous way. But they're
bringing some truth to the, to the table. You know, I mean, that, that's what I like. That's why,
you know, and there's not a lot of stand up doing that right now. So when you see it, it's pretty great.
Sure. Yeah. In terms of stand up comedians, if you want to talk about most overrated, I mean, I can't
name them. I got 24. You're right here. 20 of people that infuriate me. But I'll say something
positive. John Mulaney's new special great. Talks about it last week. Cat Williams new special great.
Right. Um, you know, those are two guys. So Laura Kightlinger, the other week at the end of Laura
Kightlinger. Fucking fantastic. Uh, you know, these are people that are, they're being themselves up
there. And they're not afraid to take some chances and, and, and be honest. And, and may the audience be
damned. Yeah. So, uh, that's, uh, check them out. Excellent. Uh, Jason Wybell, favorite works of
Asian cinema and know the Great Wall doesn't count. Uh, I love audition. I love old boy. I guess
I do love kind of the extreme Asian cinema, if I'm being honest. Uh, I'll go with all the original
Bruce Lee flex. Sure. They're really fantastic. And, you know, enter the dragon being the sort of
white album of those, right, of those, but Chinese connection is great. I mean, I like, I like that sort
of stuff. A rod dot worst, most embarrassing date stories, especially if they involve going to
the movies, but overall is fine. I mean, I, mine is way too long to tell you an hour and 20 minutes
into this thing, but I have had some dates that would, uh, who boy, make you go bold. Me too. Just dates
that went from one staggering low to the next. Um, but the one I remember most of the, well,
again, if I started, I want to, I'm not going to tell you the whole thing, but it ended with me
making out with her in Union Square Park in New York. And, um, about 45 minutes in to get
real heavy with it. She was like, I feel like I need to tell you something. I have hepatitis. Oh my
god. And not knowing if you could catch it that way, which you can with certain strains, it was
fun. I freaked out. And she didn't appreciate it, but I was like, well, you gotta, why gotta tell me.
Yeah, yeah. That was the, that was near the end of a, uh, a night that was just unbearable, but
something maybe some, maybe another time, maybe on a commentary if we want to kill some time. I
yeah, she, she kept talking through it. Yeah. And I shushed her at one point and she goes,
are you fucking kidding me? And she walked out. She's like, I'm fucked this. I don't want to see
this stupid fucking movie. Anyway, walked out and I had to chase her out of the theater. I thought
you're as a, you stayed. I stayed for about five minutes. Yeah. And I'm just going to stay. And then
I was like, I can't, I gotta go. You know, right. Uh, I did try to grow to see a requiem for a dream
once because something else was sold out. And she walked out of that as well. And actually was
very upset with me. And I said, I didn't write it. Yeah. I mean, it's like you, like you knew.
I mean, for Christ's sakes. Anyway, why did you tell Thanos to do what he did?
Very good. Uh, and this is the last one, Ben Lee, favorite class in high school or college, favorite
teacher. Favorite teacher. I mean, you're not going to know who they are. You're not going to
know who they are. That's true. My favorite class in college. Well, I, I'll, I'll, Roy Zurich, who made
every character in every movie in history, gay and thought that I think I don't know to this day if
he was insane or if he was fucking with the class, but any movie you talk about, he'd be like, well,
you know, obviously Bruce Willis and Diard is a closet in homosexual. Um, but a lot of my film
study classes in college were a blast. And the one screenwriting course I took probably changed the
whole course of my life because I loved it so much. There's a couple. I, uh, I'm Mr. Dowd by
theology teacher in the 11th grade, uh, who once, uh, when I was talking in class called me up to
the front of the room and said to me, I swear to God, if you don't stop talking, you son of a
bitch, I'm going to knock you out. And he was joking and it was hilarious. Wow. I laughed really hard
and, uh, and he laughed a bit too, but he was telling me to be quiet. He was doing it in a really
crazy, funny way. And, uh, I went back and told my friends what he said and they were dying. It was
awesome. That's, that speaks what I was saying right now. Huh? Can't, can't threaten to punch
a student in the mouth. Yeah, you can't. What am I going to do? Go back and go, hey, down.
Right. Right. It was okay at the time. And it made me laugh and he was being funny and it made him laugh.
Sure. Give a shit. Anyway, um, uh, that's our show, folks. Uh, that's our bonus episode for me. This
was a nice juicy, almost hour 30. Yeah. I hope you enjoyed it. No plugs, no nothing at the end
of a bonus app. You know that. We'll see you soon, um, when we're back with season five.
Thank you so much, everybody. We'll see you next time and we'll see you in a