Hey there folks, it's your bonus app, it's your
really, really groovy little bonus app, bonus app, bonus, bonus, bonus. Hello everybody,
we are here to provide commentary on convicted child molester victor Salva's latest picture,
Jeepers Creepers 3 has been well documented on this site. I enjoy the franchise,
Joe very much does not. All of Joe's points about Jeepers Creepers are both very funny and true.
I can't deny them. I just think the movies are kind of fun and have a kind of trashy glee to them.
This one I have not heard great things about. Neither Joe nor I have seen it. You're gonna be watching it
with us for the first time. It is streaming on Netflix. We have our cursor over the play button.
If you are ready folks, I'm gonna do a one, two, three and then play. Joe, are you ready? I'm ready. Let's get on with
one, the Joe, two, three, play screen media films. Here we go. Anyway, Joe, it's good to see you.
Pat, it's good to see you. Now, I just ate because I want the fans to know where I'm going.
Right, I just ate a 10 milligram gummy worm of weed and I have a little glass of whiskey here.
I am not drinking. I had a 10 milligram as well, which I think affects me in a very different way
than it would you. I have a higher tolerance. You want to eat another one? Maybe. So you're super
baked. I'll see how this goes. The pros are growing louder. We are watching this thing with subtitles,
which is, I think I suggested three years ago. Joe was like, no, you can't do it that way. And then
like two days ago, Joe was like, I had a great idea for the podcast. When we're doing a commentary,
we should watch it with the subtitles. That's our friendship to a tea. Neither tone that I took
was like that. I would say sinister music is playing Jeepers, creepers, three. Look, I don't know
anything about this. Did justy long come back? What do you think, Pat? No, okay. You know what? Let's not
start this episode with a bunch of stupid fucking questions. Okay. No, no, but I, you know, I think for a while,
it was rumored that he might return for the third one. Yeah, but he alas, he did not return for the
direct to streaming shot in Canada. Trying to close picture before the authorities arrested its
director. Jeeps creeps three. And look, there'll be some of you who say we shouldn't be supporting
this guy's film. And I can't disagree with you. I think at this point, it's just, there's nothing
funny about it, of course, but it is a real commentary on Hollywood that this guy has been able to continue
a thriving career. Well, look, I've made the argument before. You have. You have. It's, you know, he did his
condone and I hope he would never do it again. And you know, it's, oh, God. I mean, look, the biggest
offense is this film franchise. Yeah. I mean, you want to talk about something you deserve in
prison for. I mean, if this, if making these movies doesn't get you banned from making movies,
nothing will. To me, the fun spirit of the first two, I'll take it over, you know, over in
cities, the last key or whatever else any day of the way. Well, I mean, that's like saying, you
know, hey, you know, I'll, I'll watch Jeepers, Crippers 2 over eating this rotten salami. I mean,
come on, you know, give it a little, put a little something up against it. I saw a news story. The
other day, I guess this could go along with what do we call it? The podcast. No, no, what do we call
our horror? Oh, I changed the, I changed the title. Okay. I can't believe it didn't think of this
before. Ready? Yeah. Deadlines. Deadlines? Yeah, like headlines. Oh, okay. Deadline makes me think
of the entertainment news website. Well, that's it. That's better than news psycho, which was what
it. News psycho. Yeah. And then, and then my contract contribution was terrible screaming in. But,
and this news isn't about horror. It's, but it's a horrific story. A family goes to the grocery store.
They buy like a box of honey bunches of oats. They go home. They eat the entire box saying,
boy, this doesn't taste great. But, whatever. Maybe they changed their formula.
275. Yeah. Yeah. They finished the box. And then the dad's like, that last, that last
bowl was real gross. What's going on here? Flips it over. And notices that the box expired in 1987.
And they carefully monitored this family and they had no problems. They were just,
cause it probably goes by all the preservatives in it. But they were just like, you guys could,
could die. We don't know how this plays out. I thought that was a really interesting story. And
they bought it at a Walmart, which is not surprised. And they, and not one part of them said,
this doesn't look like the modern day box of honey bunches of oats. Yeah, I mean,
the 30 years, they couldn't tell 30 years ago. The weirdest thing was that the cast of Full House
was on the cover. Well, that joke doesn't work because they're spoiler house. But, you know,
I got you. I couldn't think of an 87 show. The prize inside was a Cosby show button.
Exactly. You know, something. Sure. The, uh, what's it called?
Mr. T serial. Oh, yeah. That's what Peewee's eating and the Peewee's big adventure,
which I always love. Yeah. Yeah. He pours it on the food. Even as a child, it infuriated me.
They did this wonderful breakfast of like pancakes, eggs, and bacon. And then he pours that shitty
cereal on top of it. And he's just eats the cereal. Yeah. It drove me. But I guess that's what a kid would do.
The, um, was it just going to say, um, about, oh, I had something for deadlines.
Oh, this 75 year old, uh, a SWAT team leader. You're being generous.
75. I mean, I'd pick that guy for an 80. Why is he playing the SWAT team later? Pat, why is,
how did this franchise get this? Maybe he was like, I want nobody even close to a child's age
around me at this moment. You're, you're one old people. You're asking the wrong questions here.
This guy's back. Wasn't this guy any other ones? I don't see just always play this character.
I don't remember him, but he's getting kind of a hero's entrance here. Oh my god.
This guy has definitely been a, like, sheriff or sergeant in other horror movies. Sure.
And I feel like maybe it was Jeepers creepers. He just said, oh my god, right? He did.
Yeah, I feel like he's back and he recognizes the van and he's like, oh shit. Yeah.
Well, I did. Now, they were talking about this on the, uh, in the Facebook page.
And apparently they've tripled down on the, uh, the van with the vanity license plate.
How do you triple down on something that's already a hard double down?
I love that the cop is wearing a heavy duster. Yeah. To floor length duster. I don't believe it.
Here comes Sergeant Jonathan Winters is getting involved.
He takes it off. He's got that granny wig on.
Takes the helmet off. He just told, he just told him hold it together and answer me. The guy looks
like he could not be less stressed off. Here's the official name of the news segment.
I just figured this out. Ready? Yeah. Folks, now it's time for deadlines from the news cycle of scream
and hand. That's, it's too much. I know, but that's why it's funny. Yeah. All right. Let's make
the, the, the, you think you're going to remember that in five minutes, let alone next week? Who knows?
Because Jojo eats a magic candy. It ain't working yet. So you can't blame it yet.
It hits me pretty hard. I mean, it hits me hard and fast. I mean, I know it didn't happen yet.
I'm saying I might not remember that. Right. And it does hit me faster and hits you.
That night in the Uber, I had regaled Pat with a story of a friend of mine once. We were at my
apartment and his, his gut was protruding and it caused the button on his shorts to shoot across the
room. We had just eaten some pot candy and Pat then said one of this whole theatrical thing about
the button shooting across hitting my, hitting my pet parrot. Yeah. I come out of the bathroom.
There's feathers up in there. Feathers in the air. It knocks the parrot out of its cage.
I say, what happened to my parrot? My friend says, jumps up. I says, I don't know with cake in his
mouth as his pants, pants fall to the ground. I think that would have been funny, pot or not.
Frankly, it was a funny bit. I, it would be funny, pot or not. But I was laughing in like
the way that I hadn't since college high. You used to get those bits in mainstream
comedies like dumb and dumb or wasn't above like a button flying off a pair of pants and bouncing
around the room. I mean, that didn't happen in dumb and dumb. But I miss, I miss, you know, it's when
every single note you ever get on something is it's got to be more grounded. It's got to be more grounded.
They have grounded comedy to the point where comedy is not funny. And that's what, that's what people
want. And that's what happens that jokes aren't there. Everyone has to talk exactly how people talk
and it's ruined comedy, frankly. WC Fields, one of my favorite WC Fields bits is I forget which movie
it is, but he, you know, it convinces his family. They've got to move to this farm where they're going
to be rich and then they get there and all the crops are dead. Yeah. And the farm house is like a just
a fucking dilapidated piece of shit. And obviously his wife is mad. And then he's like, honey, you just
got to trust me. I swear to God, once we get into this house, nothing else is going to go wrong.
And he steps on the porch and a board from the porch flies up and hits him in the face immediately.
It's a fucking excellent bit. Yeah. It's an excellent, excellent bit. Yeah. You don't see it coming.
What were you just pointing at? Be eating you. The license plate. Oh yeah, I know.
They're, they're talking. Oh, look at that cigarette. Pat, I'm trying to quit smoking.
As you can hear in my voice, I've got a little bit of a hoarseness and a little bit of a cough.
Never understood why anybody would start. I mean, born past the madman era, I just don't get why anyone
would start. Sorry, sorry, Pat. Can you say it again? It's hard to hear you down here with you way
up on your high horse. I think you said that to me last week. I did. It's from Peep Show and I'm
going to keep saying this is one of my favorite lines in Peep Show ever. So they, they are saying
that this van is a rolling history. It is of the Jeepers creepers. So they want to destroy it.
But now the creeper is going to kill them both. I mean, now just little details like this or why
this franchise sucks. He just picked up his, the creeper is the monster. Just picked up his big ax,
right? Right. He holds it up. It's gleaming. It literally looks like it just came out of
Halloween adventure. Yeah. It's like, add some thought to the details of these things, give him a
little bit of a cruddy ax, put some blood on it, something, give this some texture. He's got a gleaming,
shiny, reflective ax. Looks ridiculous. Maybe he polishes it. Well, I mean, he keeps that fucking van
going somehow or truck whatever the hell it is. Yeah, where does it get the money? It none of it makes
the question I have. None of it makes sense unless it's, it drives on horror. The car,
the truck drives on horror. Maybe it runs on fear. Oh, that's weird. As I said, that the detective
guy just goes fear has a scent, Danny, like it could sample fear right out of the air. So he's saying
the creeper goes where air, I mean, where fear is in the air, I guess. And that's how it picks
what parts of us to eat, just because those are the parts that I fear in them. What?
The fuck are they talking about? And I guess it uses the people it eats to rebuild itself. That
explains how the creeper keeps going. How does the truck keep going? It doesn't make sense.
The one thing they did right was it feeds every 20 whatever years and this was, this came out like
exactly 22 years or whatever it is from the last one. So I like what movies will do that kind of thing.
It couldn't land it at a better time even though it sucked. They're like, oh, it needs to be like
30 years transpire. Oh, well, then that means we have to set this in the 80s.
Right. Like, what a fucking wow. That's lucky. Very lucky. How do you feel about it too?
Just the chest. I'll see it. I'll see it. It's chest. You know, can I tell you something? Sure.
Let me put chest down on my list of people I'm tired of. Sure. That I find inherently boring.
Jessica, chest down. Uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, uh, Scott Adam Scott, who I've mentioned, uh, yeah,
Kristen Bell. I'm sorry. I know your friends with the guy. I don't need to see Dak Shepherd ever
again in anything. Uh, who else? Apparently on the show Chris Pratt, I'm tired of too. Get out of here.
He hasn't been in a movie in a year, but yeah, well, he's got that new Jurassic Park. Yeah.
Jurassic, the new Jurassic Park movie is called Jurassic World Colin. It can't happen a fifth time.
Uh, apparently on the set of ghosted, the Fox sitcom, Adam Scott was always saying things like,
guys, that's not how portals work. Like, he was all about the, like, the science of it to the
detriment of the comedy. And they would say, well, portals aren't real. And I'm going to stop there.
But I know a lot more about the, the man that I'm going to let go. Oh, God. I don't trust anybody.
Any man, he was funny instead, brothers, two first names. Well, that's saying these people are without
capability. And anyway, I'm just tired of them. I find them very boring. Yeah. Um, you know, now on the
other hand, you put John C. Riley, Mary Steenburgeon and Will Farrell in other film. I'm fucking there. Yeah,
I mean, we haven't had a real, like, this is a good shot. You know, the man knows how to shoot a movie.
I'll say that. Well, he did shoot powder. He did. Uh, yeah, that was a cool shot with the crow flying.
I'm kind of bored with everyone. And I think it's just that we haven't had that big star pop in,
in a long time. You know, like, it's been a long time since we've had a new comedy star. I guess,
Tiffany Haddish, haddish, haddish. Um, but, you know, I think Melissa McCarthy was the last one that
carried it for a little while. I think that's true. Yeah. So, um, but her new movie does not look
very good. I think it's a remake of back to school. It's not, but it's not. They just took the story and
called it something different. Yeah. I actually, I don't know why more movies don't. I guess they probably
thought, well, we're not going to get any money off the value of back to school. I just don't understand
you can just take a storyline like that though. Happens all the time. It's crazy. Yeah. I mean,
you know, game night, as I discussed on what the pod we did earlier, is the game with David ventured.
And, you know, you can, you can do stuff and hope you don't get sued. I can give a little more slack
if it's we're doing a funny version of this. And it's a satire area. Yeah. That I can, okay, fine.
But when you say, I'm doing the plot of a comedy. Right. That was a big hit comedy. Right.
You know, and we're just going to change the title. And then in the trailer, they actually say,
Melissa McCarthy is heading back to school. They say those words. Just like Rodney Dangerfield did.
In that other movie, that's got nothing to do with it. Right. The best Rodney Dangerfield line of
all time is in back to school. Is it the picture one? No, it's in my opinion. It's the one where he
walks into the boardroom. He's hired. He, he himself is a fat man. Yeah. And he admits early in the
movie that he, they only hangs around with people fatter than him so we can feel thin. Right.
So he walks into the boardroom of his company and it's all these obese people around the table eating
free like smorgasbord breakfast. And he goes, good morning, everybody. And everybody like mouths full.
Go, good moon. They can't talk. There's so much food there. And he goes, oh, take it easy, take it
easy, will you? And don't get any on the walls. That's good. I love, bring a picture every five minutes
till someone passes out, then bring a picture every 10 minutes. I don't do a good Rod. Wait,
is it reverse though? Doesn't he say bring a picture every 10 minutes till somebody does
out then bring a picture every five minutes? I don't think so. All right. Well, whatever. I mean,
that's a great line. Yeah. It's a great line. Like the, I mean, the man, this is a great shot. The
dialogue as I'm reading it is, you know, like school play level. But this is like a seventh grade
where they like think they're getting into some dramatic shit. It is beautifully shot. Look at that.
I remember this lady in it. This is the lady from a forget her name. She pops up in a bunch of
harsh stuff. She plays, do you ever see the minus man with Owen Wilson? Good movie. She plays the lady
who takes him home from the bar that freaks him out, even though he's a serial killer. Yeah. Yeah.
She always plays like a real weird lady. Go ahead. Sorry. My, my, probably ninth grade acting class,
when I was in drama, we had to do a two person scene. I got partnered with this girl that I had an
insane, insane crush on. She later, front today, very well -known local St. Louis rock band called
Solan, which is it. Solan? Solan. And they had a, they had a local big hit. I don't think they ever
went beyond that. They used to tour with local age and they were really good.
With local ages, big son. Born to be down. It's the get down. San it. Keep, I like that.
I like that. Yeah. They were pretty good. It was on my 90s master mix. I made a few years ago.
Yeah. Copacetic. They were good. And Solan's, you know, they had some hits as well. But
look, you know, St. Louis hits her and I did the Pulp Fiction scene where
if $5 shake in ninth grade and she, she brought it up and I was not yet allowed to see the movie and
I remember like lying and pretending I knew what I was doing. And I mean, just, just real stupid,
stupid shit. Everybody else was doing like death of a salesman. I did. Acting is very dumb.
My freshman year in college, I took, I was a theater minor throughout college. My first acting
class. We had to do a scene, but we had to do it in groups and we did the scene from Glenn
Gary Glenn Ross where Moss, I played Moss, where Moss flips it. I was so enamored after 12 years of
Catholic school that I was in an environment where I could say fuck in a classroom. And actually
received a good grade for him. Right. I couldn't wrap my head around it. What a great time
life was then. I received the lead role in, you can't take it with you, which was a Frank
Capra movie, but we did it as a play. Yeah. By doing the Steve Martin monologue from Plains Trains,
which is, you're like a Chetty Cathy doll. You added that into the, oh, you did that monologue to
audition. Oh, you did a monologue to audition. That's funny because I audition, well, I used to audition
in school with the, I want a fucking car right. Yeah, I would do that. Yeah. Great school,
not high school. Right. Yeah. That's a good monologue to do. It was. And then you could just turn
around and do the John Candy response if you needed a second model. As my friend Chip Jambrone,
dear friend of mine always said, if you watch that film and you don't tear up during that scene in
the end, there's something wrong with you. Then I'm doing all right. I don't cry during that scene.
I do cry at the end for sure. Not, not, not, the end is the tearing up. But he was like,
basically like, who can watch that scene and not feel horrible? Yeah. Well, you, because you put
yourself in, in both positions. Yeah. That's the beauty of that scene. And he'll often whip that line
out on people and it always makes me laugh, which somebody will criticize him about something very passive.
It'll be like, you want to hurt me? Okay. I'm an easy target. Yeah. Start going into it. It's,
didn't you notice on the plane when you started talking? Eventually I started reading the vomit bag.
I mean, didn't that give you some sort of clue? Like, hey, maybe this guy's not enjoying it?
Everything is not an anecdote. You have to discriminate. You choose things that are funny or mildly
amusing or interesting. You're a miracle. Your stories have none of that. They aren't even amusing
accidentally. Hey, honey, I've got a friend. He's got some amusing anecdotes for you. Oh,
here's our guns. You can blow your brains out. You'll thank me for it. I could tolerate any
insurance seminar for days. I could sit there and listen to them go on and on with a big smile on my
face. And they'd say, how can you stand it? And I'd tell them because I've been with Dale Griffith.
I can take anything. You know what they'd say? They'd say, I know what you mean, the shower curtain ring
guy. Whoa. Don't leave out. And here's an idea. Half the model. I tell these stories. Have a point.
There's a good idea. Have a point. It makes it so much more interesting for the listener.
This, by the way, ladies and gentlemen, is exploding out of the man that not just said,
the pot will hit me in a much lesser way than it hits Joe. But also, it won't hit us very quickly.
You just, you just, you, you with commitments spewed out the entire model. If this was working,
I wouldn't have remembered that model. I think you're in the zone, kid. I think I think we're
setting a set, settling in. I am loving this man with the duster, the homemade lanyard holding his
badge around his giant novelty store badge around his neck. And it does. It is like his granddaughter
went to camp and made her granddad a lanyard for his thing. All the fire that nothing from this
world or the next can get through. What is the wall of fire? I think he's saying, let's just
shoot the fuck out of it. Oh, I see. She may not fly, but this is our killing. This guy is like,
this movie's going to get me into that next realm of acting. By the way, that's the 80 -year -old guy.
Seeing him with that with the brown hair, he doesn't look as old. No, he looks like a 50 -year -old man
now. Yeah. He puts that helmet on. He looks like he's going to fucking kill over. Now, here's my question.
Why wouldn't you get Randy Quaid? Give the movie a little because he's not allowed to do
anything. Well, this was in Canada. I think it was. I just said that. What if they came to a
restaurant? A pretty sure way. And then Quaid would be like, the movie's being directed by a child's
list. You're arresting me? I am still heartbroken about Randy Quaid because he was a normal guy
that was a very talented dude, and something clearly snapped. And he went nuts. And when you see
the other guy, we use with Dennis Quaid, where he's just like, I miss my brother, man, it's all
I'm going to say. And you're like, you're like, that's a guy being like, something's wrong my brother.
Yeah. He's not just like being an asshole and running away from money or running away from debt.
The truth is every family has one, or at least every other family has one, a guy who just kind of
snaps. I know who mine is in my family. But add that into the Hollywood scene. I mean, I can't
believe more people, excuse me, Jesus, don't go insane. The question is, why did this happen? The
question is, why does it not happen more often? What's that? That's your Hannah and her sisters.
Oh, yeah, yeah. That expounds night out. Place the Jewish professor talking about the Holocaust.
Right. How does it not happen more often? Do you have bags some hay off you?
Our horses are up in Boulder. You're not up there with the rock. I can't read fast enough for
Jeepers, creepers three for Christ sakes. I will say now one had just in long and a few kind of like
unsettling shots of young boys. Two has a hundred shirtless boys, several of them peeing on the side of
the road and really doubles down on the creep. This one I haven't seen, I was just about to say I
haven't seen a boy under 25 and here comes one. Oh, that guy could easily be 28. He's probably, I
would bet casting this movie. What parent would let their child be in this movie? Let's be real.
I got news for you. What parent would know the guy's history? If I said mom, I'm going to go work with
Victor Salva this week. She would say, you're great. Well, you can Google them. I mean, if you're a kid,
actually, here's the thing as Bruno, Sasha Baron Collins movie showed nobody would care. These
kind of stage bombs just would not care. Even if you told them, yeah, go ahead. If my kid's going
to be famous, I don't care. Judging the style of clothing alone, I think this is in Canada.
These do look like Canadian outfits because look at the jack at this kids wearing. That wouldn't be
I'm not shitting on can I love Canada, but I'm just saying, never been. I don't think that jack
you've never been to Canada. No. There are great neighbors to the north. I'd like to go.
Toronto, buddy. Next time I play Toronto, you got to come with me, man. All right. You want to talk
about a fun fucking city, man. All right. Toronto was a great, wow, man. Toronto is fun. Good for
media shopping. Uh -huh. Good for comedy shows. Great bars. Okay. Very fun city. Very fun little town.
Which is like the strip club capital of the world. Is that Montreal? Um, it's a place. It's
it's a place called Clam Haven. Come on, Joe. Come on, Joe. You're better than that.
Not by much. I'm clearly not. But you're better than that. I'm clearly not. Uh, no, the strip
capital account in Montreal, Montreal, yeah. Um, but in Montreal is a good town, but I don't like
you're like, why don't I live here? Right. I think the most inviting people there. Montreal does have
a bit of a French sort of snooze to it, where there's a little more of the like, you like mannequins.
You know what I mean? Like, how often are they going? Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, that's what all
the guys yell at the strip club. Now, the lady says, or we don't do that here. Uh, is the strip club,
so it's like a bunch like in a row. Is that why it's called the capital of the world? They just have
a lot. They have a ton. And it's always my goat and a ton of sex shops too. And it's always my go -to line
if ever I'm bombing in Montreal. Okay. I go, you know, you fucking people act like you're so
sophisticated. There's a goddamn dildo store in every corner out there. You're not fooling me. Right.
And then usually they laugh at that and then I go back to bombing again. Now, why is that? Why is it
such a, uh, a sin haven, a deadwood, if you will? It's not really a sin haven. It's not like,
they're not whorehouses. And it's, it's also not like, I don't even think they do like lap dances
and shit. It's just kind of like, there's just a lot of sex stuff up there for some reason. All right.
But it's not like, I just wonder what, I mean, I guess Vegas, Sin City, you get it. I mean, I just,
it's interesting. But Vegas, you can actually sin. And Montreal's like, you go on a, if I remember
remembering correctly, you just go into a strip club. And it's like, yeah, there's naked girls dancing.
But like, that's it. Like, it's not like you're going to get lap dances, even from them, let alone
much more than, you know, they're probably nice. They're not nicer. Okay. I'm telling you that's
something. I spoke a little too soon because here come the boys. Now, Joe, let's say,
let's say you've been convicted of child ballastation. What is he never allowed to have a kid
under 18 in a movie? Why would you then? You got to have, it's the story. You got it. They're just
kids on dirt bikes. You, why would you cast four young boys in your movie? The two guys on the end.
They're definitely those two guys are in their fucking late 20s. Yeah. This guy is probably 22
with their top son. And the black dude is probably like 22. Yeah, you're right. You're right. In fact,
the black dude could be 53. These parts were probably written as 14. And then the producer was like,
come on, Vic, remember when we saw the craft, the black lady, she was 30. She was 17 years old.
It was miraculous. Sounds like Joe at the police station last week. You know,
this guy's, I mean, this guy looks like he's 40 on the left. Yeah, this is what I'm saying.
Like when it was the guy's, but he went out. He hired a bunch of older boys. Yeah. That could
maybe pass for younger boys. He's doing a 90210 right now. Right. Again, speaking of 90210, you know,
that Luke Perry is in, um, we talked about a river deal. Yeah. No, we didn't. Oh, we didn't. Yeah.
He's in that river deal. He is weathered, baby. But he's not playing Mr. Weatherby. Is there a Mr.
dad in it? Okay. Whether it was the poster, whether he is, I didn't know who was last week either,
when you mentioned he was the principal. Um, Luke Perry had one kind of one shot at the movie game,
and it was eight seconds, the rodeo movie. Well, he was also in Buffy the Vampire Slayer. That's
true. Which I love. Frankly, I loved it too. But Joss Whedon was disgusted by the interpretation and
reworking of it. I watched the first season of the show and I was like, this isn't for me. I get
why people like it. I didn't go any further. But like the movie, especially like Paul Rubens,
when they stabbed him and he's going, oh, yeah. Oh, it's got some big laughs in it. Yeah. No, I like
that movie over a hour. Well, it offended Joss Whedon's feminist sensibilities. Sure. Which we later
found out were, look, anybody protested in that much. Yeah. What is it? He doth protest too much.
I mean, I think the Whedon doth protest too much. That's how it goes. Okay. Kiss my ass,
you ugly old bitch. Now, he's saying that to the truck. So is the plot? Now, the kid says that he
threw a rock at the truck, the truck bounced off and hit him in the head, like magically,
like in a way that it shouldn't have. Is the plot of this film that his life force is this truck?
This one seems as the people on the Facebook page said it's doubling down on the truck. And Joe,
carry me for a moment because I'm going to get that Facebook page because we had a really funny
discussion. I'm going to include it. All right. So we got to talk about this movie for an hour and
40 minutes. I'll carry you. I'll carry you, baby. Here's something for deadlines from the news
cycle of scream and in. You guys have probably read this, but because of the success of Black Panther,
Disney just donated $1 million to, I believe, a stem cell research lab, which hats off to you,
Disney. We need stem cell research. We need to be using these treatments in this country.
They're miracle treatments. And it's ridiculous that we don't use them. And the fact that we don't
use them can only, in my opinion, speak to the conspiracy theories about our government wanting us
to remain sick. But I love that Disney did that. I think it's sad that we needed a superhero movie
to get us to the point of company, a company that big doing it. But hey, we got there. So thank you,
Black Panther. And thank you, Disney, for that. I think that's very, very cool. Did you still not see
Black Panther? I have not seen it yet because I'm, I kind of just, I mean, talk about the worst time
to say I was done with superhero movies. Interesting that that's the one. But I didn't see Wonder Woman
in the theater either. You know, interesting that those two are the ones. I saw it on video. I'll see
Black Panther on video. The only superhero movie I went willingly to see this in the last count
last fiscal year, which is the one word doesn't mean fiscal year, was justice league because I,
you know, I had some hope left in me. And that really just kind of took the last of it out of me.
Yeah. You know, and that was kind of it. Like when I saw, even when Wolverine was over a year ago
at this point, but even when I saw the last Wolverine, I wasn't in any stretch wanting to see it. I
haven't liked any of them. Still. I did see Black Panther. I feel like people probably
want us to do in the podcast, but maybe we won't. I mean, to me personally, and I don't, I don't
need letters, folks. I didn't see how it was any different than the other ones except it had a little
more obviously social political commentary, sure. But at some point, it just becomes the same thing
as everyone throwing people into buildings. And that's not that's not what I like to see. I just
don't. Yeah. Well, it's it becomes like the Ghostbusters remake where it's like, I'm happy that
that happened. And I was excited for women that that happened. Right. But I couldn't.
I can't deny the fact that they said, we're going to make another one. I'd be like, I don't know,
guys. Like, you know, like it's, you know, it is what it is. I just, I don't like that genre of
movie. So I don't know what to tell you. Okay. I used to really love it. And I don't like it
anymore because I miss, I miss the Chris Nolan days. I miss the Richard Donner days. Like, I just,
I just can't stand the level of humor and all of it anymore. And, and it's also not, I watched a really
great documentary about the Superman franchise, the original Superman franchise recently. And,
you know, half of what is so amazing about that first film is, you know, I came out in 1979 or
something like that. And the poster said, you will believe a man can fly because the whole thing was,
we have pulled this off. Right. We've created an effect where you're going to literally think Superman
is flying around. Yeah. And they did. And it worked. And it was great. And it's like the excitement of
that, the excitement watching the behind the scenes were like, oh my God, the first takes of him
flying were the worst things we were like, this is a fucking, we're going to die. This is going to end
our careers. Like, it was, it's just so good. And now in a day and age where it's like, you can make
anything happen whenever you feel like it if you have the money. And you go in knowing that Disney and
Marvel have the money. Right. It's just not as exciting to me to see like, I'll tell you what, man,
it's still I'm in with the Tom Cruise franchise with the Mission Impossible franchise because I've
liked everyone. Yeah. I saw the new trailer. And I'm like, that cocksucker is fucking hanging on the
out for that fucking helicopter for real. Yeah. The stunts in those, they feel a lot more real than
than all the Marvel. They are. He did the plane thing for real in the last one. Yeah. I thought all
those have been tremendously entertaining. And the idea to switch up the directors and have each one
be like an awesome director is very cool too. Yeah. Like, I love that the first mission impossible is
just like a straight up Brian Dupalma thriller. Yeah. Who's directed to the new one get weirder and
weirder. I don't know. Um, I, I'll look that up. Abrams did three Abrams did a, I mean, I love
Seymour Hoffman such a great villain on that. Yeah. And then I mixed the last two up, but they had some
killer scenes. The one like in the giant washing machine in the last one, uh, where I was fucking awesome.
Like the current where he had to stop the current. And he had like, yeah, just fucking awesome.
Mission. Listen folks. And they're, they're inventive. I think I've said it before in this podcast and
keep in mind, you know how much I love Star Wars. And this movie came out the same year Star Wars did
my favorite popcorn movie of 2016 was mission or 15 was mission impossible five. It was great. Uh,
I put it over the force awakens and I love the force awakens, but I, I was so fucking
taken aback. I just loved it, man. I loved it. So anyway, my point is is here's a guy and a company
in a studio, whatever they could fake it. And the fact that he doesn't for real to me is like,
that's Tom Cruise being like, yeah, man, like I want you to know, like I give a shit. Yes.
You know what I mean? So not that Marvel and Disney don't. I'm just saying like, it's just not as,
to be like, oh my god, the building exploded. And the guy did a triple windy off the ceiling. And
looks clearly fake. So, um, and I, I need distress. My girlfriend and I saw Black Panther opening night.
Um, I, I am thrilled that the movie exists. I am thrilled that
black kids have a superhero that's not blade, which they couldn't see. You know, I think it's
all fantastic. Blades and awesome superhero, but yeah, it was more of an R rated franchise.
I'm just saying to me personally, it didn't feel all that different from the other Marvel movies,
aside from having a pretty cool, uh, you know, social commentary and backdrop to it. Well, that's,
that's how, um, uh, uh, winner soldier was for me too. Everybody was like, oh, this is like a new game
changer for the Marvel films. And I watched and I was like, I don't know, it's just, I mean, it's a
little tonally different, but it just feels like the other Marvel films. I agree. And same with Wonder Woman
and, you know, I think down the line, they're, they're made under a pretty strict set of regulations.
It seems like to me. Here's two kids dead on a tree on the same. We really just have the step,
the, the, the spear under their arm. Yeah. Um, but you know, uh, the mission impossible franchise.
Number one, Brian De Palma, number two, John Wu, which was ludicrous and way too much mask pulling
off. Yeah. But it was awesome. Yeah. JJ Abrams, the third one, Adam Phillips,
simmer hopping into the mix was what kept that one going. Brad Bird did a ghost protocol.
What else did Brad Bird direct? Like the Incredibles and he's a Pixar guy. Okay. Uh, that to me,
well, that had the side of the building. Shit, I saw that in IMAX. There was some cool shit in that.
Five and six are Christopher McQuarrie, the writer of, uh, way of the gun and usual suspects.
Okay. Guys killing it, dude. He is. And hang on. I guess that's the new one too. I don't know what
the new one is. Six is the fun. It's called, um, fallout, I believe. Okay. Uh, I'm going to scroll
through. We'll see you in hell page. Uh, can't wait to hear Pat and Joe's reaction to shape of water
winning best picture. They were such huge fans of the fixed fish sex as Nick Amber. Um, did you
watch the Oscars? Not a fucking stitch. This was far and away the most excruciatingly boring Oscars.
I've ever seen and there's a lot of competition. Um, I was, I was falling asleep throughout. Um,
there was nothing surprising. It was dull. As someone points out here, they left, uh, old, uh,
John Mahoney out of the in memoriam. What? No, Mahoney, no tobe hooper and no powers booth. What?
Says T. K. Cosa. What? I mean, Mahoney's the most egregious because it's like, uh, if you're just
sitting and thinking without even looking it up, who died this year? How do you not remember Mahoney?
Well, wait. Oh, yeah, no, 2018. Yeah. I mean, they'll be in next year. They might slip them in
next year, but if they have somewhere sort of weird cutoff, that's kind of sick. Um, all right.
People recommending Veronica on Netflix. Maybe we could do that. Veronica. Not even familiar with it,
but apparently it's like another WG type deal. Okay. Uh, I was thrilled to see Roger Deacon's finally
wins for cinematography, especially I watched a rewatch Fargo last night to not give that man,
that man shot the assassination of Jesse James and the coward Robert Howard say the whole title. I
wouldn't remember it. And Fargo, which are two of the best shot movies of all time. Right. Uh,
and he brought it home for Blade Runner, which was a beautifully film movie, but yes, not my favorite.
No. Okay. So I'm a little torn Anthony Gujardo. So I'm a little torn because I'd like the fellas to
talk about Jeepers creepers three, but I don't want to put them through the misery. Last words of the
movie are so dot, dot, dot, come and get me you son of a bitch. We have that to look forward to.
So the creep doesn't die and predicted score two filthy uncut hogs down. Um, absolute garbage.
I'd love to hear his Joe's take on the creeper driving around in a now sentient trap truck in the
middle of the goddamn day for 90 percent of the movie. Okay. So the truck is now. Yeah. So the truck is
a lot of pristine, whatever. Yeah. Okay. Uh, I couldn't believe the part about the truck being sentient,
but then I read the Wikipedia synopsis. And I can practically hear Joe on the podcast furiously spewing
out. The truck was driving around by itself like herbie the goddamn love bug. Andrew Rich. Andrew,
I thank you for the for the line, sir. It's a great joke and better than what I could have thought of
as this gummy worm takes a really saddles into the old bones, uh, Ashley turned it off after 20
minutes. Ashley Davis. I mean, look, if I didn't have to do this right now, this movie would have been
off a while ago, but it is nicely shot. Yeah. I agree. It's shot very, um, you know, it's,
for me with film, especially with horror, it's always like, you know, if this guy would just do a
little bit of that guy and then a little bit of the, yeah, and buffet picked this, you'd have a
perfect movie. It's like, this thing, the plot of this is so fucking stupid. The sentient trunk is so
fucking stupid. What is it? Herbie? The love bug. Uh, but it's shot like this Stephen King movie. Yeah.
So it's like, and it looks awesome. So it's like, let this director do, you know, uh, uh, uh,
what was the shitty Stephen King thing we talked about? Let Victor Salva, director, that
we were saying? Yeah, give him a Stephen King thing to do. So I don't think we want to keep giving him
work is the point. He's, he's working. Yeah, that's true. All right. Not in the States. Not this. Okay,
so not this example, but you, you hear my point is like, it's like, let a guy find not Victor Salva.
Let a guy that has a this kind of vision direct the script by this guy that is this kind of
he has always one or the other. It's always like, yeah, the script sucks, but it was well shot.
Right. Oh man, it was a cool script, but the director fucked it up. It's like, just put some of
these guys together and they could crank out some amazing shit. Man, I understand. I hear you.
Ken Hanley says, guys, try to track down a copy of the last minute, which is the movie Stephen
Norton to made after blade, that is basically an allegory for how that movie destroyed his life
and career. It's as if the Cohen brothers made La La land. Sounds fantastic. It does sound
to me because I was curious what happened to Old Norrington. So I'm going to watch. He didn't do,
oh, that's right. He didn't do the second one because he was swept right out of Hollywood after making
a massive money maker that looked incredible. What's his name? Stephen Norrington. He's a British dude.
He doesn't even appear on the hours of supplements on the Blu -ray. So clearly something went wrong.
Is he still working in England? He is not working apparently as a director anyway.
So well, he did blade, then the League of Extraordinary Gentlemen. Okay. There it is. That was an awful
movie. I didn't mind it, but it's, you know, it's not great. The last minute is a 2001 British urban
Gothic film written and directed by Stephen Norrington. Bruce's you and Jax, you spits you,
spits on you and asks for your, and then asks for your autograph is the tagline or review on the box.
It's a, it shows a struggling man hitting bottom and finding light in unexpected places and trying
huge alternative as a solution to his problems while giving up the life he recently found.
So yeah, all right, that sounds good. I would like to see that.
Now are there any vampires? No, I don't think so. No, well then I don't see what this has to do with
the blade franchise. Drew Spindler has requested this as a commentary. He thought it was great. A lot of
great kills questionable CGI. I laughed quite a bit. The vehicle gets a lot of airtime.
And he tried to get us to do it. We're doing it. It's almost like he's got everything he learned about
filmmaking before he made it says Jason Busky. It is questionable. It looks kind of cool.
It is very questionable CGI. Yes. CGI has been terrible. Also the creepers main of white hair
literally looks like they cut it off a Santa Claus wig at Halloween adventure. I mean,
the lack of detail in the costuming and props and this is offensive. Matthew Little drove 40 miles
to see this movie at the theater during its one night release and still came very close to walking out.
Terrible is not the word for it. So most people don't care for the film. 40 miles.
Is he nuts? Look, he sounds insane. Sorry, man. No, I mean, man, you're a nice guy,
but 40 miles to see this fucking thing. So is that makeup or is that just?
No, that's just how she always looks. Even 20 years ago in the minus man.
No, she wasn't as wrinkly in the minus man, but her eyes are that like before they turned
into the white contact lenses. Her eyes are like weirdly blue. It looks otherworldly or something.
I wouldn't drive 40 minutes to see, you know, the third anchor man movie and that's a franchise I've
enjoyed quite a bit before. You know, you know, and they don't get credit for it because at some point
anchor man made that flip into like a frat boy movie, which the Big Lebowski kind of did too.
They're both obviously so much smarter and better than that, but the wrong element got a hole
to the movies basically. It's like when a band you love that's been indie becomes real big, right?
Anchorman in watching anything in modern comedy, I would say there is no more influential
dynamics than the Adam McKay will fail dynamic terms of what comedy is now.
They changed it. I'd say way more than aptile. Although aptile produced, I mean, what am I talking
about? But I mean, those guys in terms of alt comedy even, which is supposed to be like, oh,
we're so different than the mainstream, a lot of alt comedy is just anchor man.
And they also did the, in my opinion, Farrell and McKay did the last great
movement of irony in comedy. Yeah, they, they nobody in recent years did a better job than them
at depicting humor through the ignorance of some of the character. Yeah, they do very well in each
movie. And again, you're not, we talked about this last week, you're not laughing at hatred,
you know, or hating, you're laughing at a stupidity of a person. Right. They pushed that even further
with Taladega Knights, but that movie was huge with Hicks because they were like, finally,
somebody gets us. Right. And the other side was like, oh, look at these idiots, which is an almost
impossible tone. And they did it beautifully. And I'm shocked that you don't like the other guys.
I don't, I just don't get it. I actually went and rewatched it off your many others recommendation.
And I would elevate it a little bit. I saw it on a horrible date. I think I had a tainted memory,
but I don't put it anywhere near their best stuff, anywhere near their best stuff. And I,
Robert, Robert sweeps me away in that film. All right. He sweeps you away.
Look, Mark Walberg streaming. I'm a big, beautiful bird that needs to fly. It's really fun.
Yeah. All right. And because he sounds like the kid, I think they wrote it that way because it's
he sounds like boogie knights. Yeah, that's right. I'm a shiny star. Yeah. But when it's when it's
in a comedy, you're allowed to laugh at it. You're like, yeah, it sounds like an idiot.
To me, one of the most interesting, like, I always love this guy was going to play that part.
Like Tim Burton was like, almost not going to do Batman unless Bill Murray played Batman. Imagine
that keeps me up nights wondering what that might have been. But one of the craziest ones to
me for some reason is that DiCaprio, at the very last second, his agents took him off boogie knights and
put him into Titanic, which obviously worked out well for him. Right. But I got to tell you,
in no other challenge, would I ever say Walberg is a better actor than DiCaprio. It's simply not
true. But for that role, Walberg was the man for the job. No, he's the guy. He was perfect for that
part. He's the guy. That's why I like that they put that style of character into something where
you were allowed to laugh. Right. Because he wasn't a drama. My favorite commentary, or certainly one
of them, when I used to listen to director commentaries, was the boogie knights one Paul Thomas Anderson
as everyone over to his house, the cat. It sounds like this podcast. But he has the whole cast over
to his house. You have all these people who are starting out, but are now the biggest stars in Hollywood.
Everybody in that movie, except for Bertrand. And they get wasted and rip on each other and say
things they definitely shouldn't. And it's a fascinating commentary that's probably been pulled off
the latest releases, but it was very fun to listen to. It was like a party. And now he won't do
contests anymore. I have the cardboard box DVD release where it's orange one. Yeah. It's on there.
All right. Then I got to watch it. I always skip the commentaries. I rarely rarely listen to them.
When I thought I really want to be a filmmaker director, which was a big part of my childhood,
I used to watch them and try to learn stuff. But I love the behind the scenes. I think you can get
it from the behind the scenes. Yeah. That's much more entertaining. The the commentaries a lot of the
time are like, remember this thing. Remember how cold it was. Right. Oh, you're like, all right. Yeah,
you can tell 10 minutes in. It's going to be worth listening to. The Carpenter Russell commentaries on
both the thing and big trouble. Little China are dreams to listen to. Really? They're so funny and good.
Okay. And Soderberg always does a great comedy as well. Jesus commentary as well. Is this supposed to
be a vagina? I don't know. It looked like a vagina. Oh, it's his nose. But it did open like a vagina.
Wow. I mean, look at this. He looks ridiculous. If this was happening to you in real life, you'd say,
why is this guy in this shitty mask yelling at us? Oh, we got some nut.
I mean, he doesn't, you know, I wouldn't be like, this is a monster. Yeah, he's not that scary.
Well, uh -oh, tipping that truck. The wing effects are not great. But I get it. This is, you know,
they don't have the budget. I'm willing to look past things like that if it's a good movie, which this
is not. But. But again, well shot. That's a good shot right there. We say, I wonder why people can't.
This also could be, by the way, really quick. That's what you're going to go ahead. This also
could be the cinematographer 100%. It could be. I don't remember either the other Jeepers creepers
being this well shot. I would say the other are equal or better shot. I mean, I thought both of them
had some really killer. Oh, well, then it's that it's salvage. Yeah, unless they're use it. Well,
you know, yeah, anyway, go ahead. Where are you going to say? Did Coppola produce three? He probably
dropped out at this point. Right. He produced one and two. Francis Ford Coppola. He, and he knew about
the whole scandal. Right. But again, he had gone to jail and yeah, come out and went to therapy.
And, you know, so that's okay. Still, it's like, I don't mean it's okay. You know what I'm saying?
I feel like if you give him another chance, if you murder once, you know, I'll totally buy, you know,
it was crazy circumstances. You're never going to murder again. To me, I can't just assume that
you're willing to molest a child once and then never do it again. Well, I can't, I can't buy it.
I'll tell you what would help sell me on that, though, is the therapy therapy. I think it is
a major major major major mental deficiency that makes somebody do that. Right. And I think that
the only people that are even close to potentially being able to treat it are people that deal with
the mind, not the body. Right. So, um, so who knows? I don't know. I'm just saying, you know, I won't
I won't crucify the guy for producing copal. I mean, yeah, producing the movie. You know,
uh, have we really taken in the hair plugs on the on the sheriff?
Uh, I don't know if I didn't notice that they're plugs. I mean, I did notice that is a
die job like I've never seen because he's balding in the back. So I guess if he was going to do plugs,
he'd go full coverage. But it literally looks like the episode of Frazier where John Mahoney dies
his hair brown. Uh -huh. And he's like, he's like, Oh, watch out. I might pick up all these ladies
tonight. Right. And it doesn't look bad, but it looks ridiculous. You're right. We can tell your
hair is dyed brown. Yeah. Um, but uh, it looks like that to me. You know, we've even done a
crane shots in a while. That's true. I, I've, uh, I'm up to the third season. I'm enjoying it. Yeah.
It's, uh, I saw she's such a groovy lady, which I loved. Which episode is that she's such a groovy lady?
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. No, it doesn't end like that. It goes. It's got to end. Yeah. But we
brought right. Right. Right. And then they caught me back, by the way. Oh, now we got a shirtless
kid, Rhonda. It's not a kid. It's a grown man. That's a grown man. All right. All right. Uh,
they call it back later in that season. Yeah. I saw him. He's singing it in the kitchen. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. What show could you do that on anyone? I don't like it. And the audience laughs. I'm like,
they saw that seven weeks ago. Right. And they remembered it. Yeah. It's crazy. I'm trying to think
of a, of a recent crane shots, uh, you know, one that I've watched where somebody said something that
I really enjoyed. Um, I sort of, I had an introspeculation, and I feel like everybody was kind
of too respectful to bring it up. But I wondered if John Mahoney might have been a gay man. Uh,
he claims he's not. I read an interview. Oh, he did. Oh, they asked because there was, there was
tons of speculation that he was gay because he was so private about his private. But I read a very
later, not a very, but a later review and interview in his life. And he said that when he was a younger
guy, like early 30s, he had cancer for the first time. Okay. And he had a, he had to get a
colostomy bag. And he was like, so he's like, that was it. I just, you know, obviously I wasn't going
to date anymore. And he just kind of wrote it up. And then he was just like, yeah, then I just kind of
don't know. I got older and now he's like, I'm very happy. Just like my life. It's me and my dog.
And I go do theater. Like he seems like the dad a lot. Like he seems like he's just like, ah,
what are you going to do? You know, yeah, wait, wait, we got to talk it out. Just come on.
Or, you know, he's ganged and want to talk to that person about it. Or that too. He had a colostomy
bag his whole life. I don't know. That wasn't clear. Or it seems like a strange excuse. It sounded more
to me that he had it for a while when he was fighting when he was getting healthy. Yeah. But I don't
know, once you have one, I think maybe you just have one. I didn't show on the show. Well, it doesn't
show. They don't show. Yeah. But I understand if somebody would feel awkward, if you were single,
look, if I got a colostomy bag right now as a single guy, I'm not saying for anybody listening.
Right. If you're single with a colostomy bag, I'm not saying that this is how it should be. I'm
just saying for me personally, I could understand my own fears and insecurities running away with me.
But I would hope I would get over it. I was in scarities without a colostomy bag. Yeah, I was
going to say, I mean, aren't we all wearing a colostomy bag at the end of the day? I know I am. Now,
don't pat smells like he is. Hey, folks, folks, folks, these are shower bits. I don't know why it's
taken me so long to bring this up. Where the fuck is come? You're dog. And I say anywhere, Pat. He's
been gone for months. It's March. Well, the first few weeks, I was like, where is Conny's with my
parents and I let it go. But now it's been months. I ate him. It's been a tough run here. No, he
took him over once and Joe had the tail coming out from between a hamburger bun and was just finishing
it up. And I didn't put it together. My favorite, I'll tell you in a minute, where he is. He's fine.
My favorite three stages. Oh, you mean you didn't eat him? I didn't eat him. Okay. But actually,
I'll just tell you what, he saw my mom because I have to go back again to do this tour. And I was like,
well, I'm going to once again bring him back to LA for three weeks. Then I have to turn around and
bring him back. My mom's like, just leave him here and just pick him up for you. You're coming right
back. So he's good. He's healthy. He misses me when I saw him for some for about a week recently.
And when I was leaving, this is, I mean, this is heartbreakingly adorable. He was he was locked
around my leg and he was trying to go with me. It was very sweet. And I was like, buddy, I'll be back.
I love you. Yeah. I'm just trying to prevent you from having to fly multiple times on an airplane,
which dogs say in the world. I mean, you should be thankful for that. So I'm excited to get him back.
But my favorite three stages ever is Malice in the Palace, which is the one where they it opens with
them for some reason, running a restaurant in the middle of Saudi Arabia. No explanation in the
desert, in a tent. Yeah. It was the sex in the city too. You can't just shorts. So it opens.
Two Sultan guys come in and they're like, you know, we want, you know, some kind of Middle Eastern
dish, you know, right? And Papa Ghanouche. Yeah. I guarantee you for comedy word, they probably
want with Papa Ghanouche. Yeah. And, uh, Mo playing the mater deed. Yeah, Papa Ghanouche. Yeah.
Mo playing the mater deed goes, we ain't got none of that. All we got is rabbit and hot dog.
For some reason, all they're in the desert, all they have to serve is rabbit and hot dog. And
they do this bit. It's I'm at some point we should watch it together. All right. Don't
honor off this show because I still have a watched Eunice, the mama's family drama.
We got to do a commentary on that. All right. Uh, because this, this, this routine would just
set you off, man. It's, but it's so they do. I guarantee I've seen it. I've seen every three
stages. But there's a cat and a dog in the kitchen. Uh -huh. They keep getting loose while Larry's cooking
rabbit and hot dog for these guys. Uh, and Larry repeatedly chases the animal out of the kitchen,
picks it up while he's also holding a meat cleaver because he's cooking going like, why you?
So then the two Sultan guys think that they're being fed cat as rabbit and actual dog as hot dogs.
Okay. And uh, they get served the hot dogs and they get into this thing.
That's a layered plot. They're eating the, oh, building up to it, hold on. They're eating the, uh,
they serve the food. They're eating the rabbit, the hot dog, and uh, every time the Sultan bites the
hot dog, the dog actually barks. He thinks he thinks it's still alive. And then they go,
there's, we don't want to eat this food. Shem comes in. Shem goes, hey, not in wrong with this food.
And he sits down and he starts eating the food. And he takes a piece of, and nothing's barking or anything.
Suddenly it's fine. They're like, okay, we must be crazy. And he takes a piece of chicken and he cuts
into it and the cat suddenly goes, and he goes, as he's cutting it goes, oh, jumps up, hair everywhere.
Yeah, I'd love to watch that right now instead of this shit. I'm sorry. I know that was a very
detailed explanation. No, it's fine. But Jesus Christ, it's really, really fucking funny, man.
When I was a kid, I was scared of mo. My dad and I would watch like three movies every Friday night,
then we'd watch three stages afterwards. So I fell asleep. Uh, I was scared of mo, and I thought,
this is the ugliest man I've ever seen. And then Shem came in and I said, Shem is somehow uglier than
mo. Who's your favorite stooge? Shem. Shem book. I'm a Larry man. Shem was a mo's older brother.
Right. Yes. Clearly they were identical. And people say, oh, didn't it suck when the Shem
ones would come on? I love curly. Don't get me wrong. Uh, but there's something about Shem where he's
like, he's such like an every man and he's kind of like pathetic. And he's, he's the only things he
has it together, but he doesn't. Yeah. I am just really funny. The curly Joe ones were always a low
point, although in watching it now, I might find them way funnier. Well, really Joe is kind of doing
a Paul Lind almost. Yeah. And I think when he go, when he, when he gets slapped and he goes, stop it.
Not so hard. Yeah. It's like the, uh, it's like the line. Right. You know, it's probably. Yeah,
I find that very funny. Uh, the guy after that, though, Joe Besser or whatever. Oh, yeah, I don't
even count those. That's really where they're at the tailwind. What are they? They've been shaking
this pot for five minutes. All right. That's like on the honeymooners, like one of my favorite TV
shows of all time. Never seen it. Oh, dude, it's fucking hilarious. It's really funny show. It's the
hand of the creeper, by the way, in the pot. That the suspense that we're trying to draw out of
dumping that hand out of that pot. Hey, the hand would have rolled out the second they turned it
over. B, why the suspense? Stupid scene. Because it's got something to do with the fact that the hand
like possessed her. Uh -huh. The gram omelady or something. And then like I think so it's something
with like the town now discovering. Oh, she's like got this evil in her. I think this guy still
goes and gets the top of his hair dyed orange. Jesus.
Yeah, see, she's like now it's like the turn like she's evil. I think she's doing the creeper's
bidding. She looks evil. I'll say that. Who does she look like? She looks like a Jim Henson creature.
Oh, that's mean. But they've got her made up. I'm sure she puts herself together. How
on your buddy, that's what that lady looks like, man. Well, then I'm sorry. She's, she's
and in the she was in the in 80s Twilight Zone episode about like a synthetic dreams or something.
I can't remember what it was called. And she's stunning. All right. She's stunning. She's just
she just aged. She's got a linda Hamilton quality. Yeah, she's very leather. See, she's in the
in the way that Luke Perry is by the way. Yeah, joining hands. And it will put to the thing in you.
They've got her made like that's mascara and shit. Well, now the black under her. Yeah,
obviously she doesn't have black permanent circles under her. I'm just saying, I don't want to
heard to listen to this and feel safe. I'm sure she's listening intently. But no, that's what I was
going to say about Luke Perry is he looks. She looks this way and he looks. They look like two people
that have been in the bottle for a while. Yeah, right. You know, very leathery skin. That's a cool
effect. Yeah. I mean, it's just eyes turning wipe, but it looked real. I liked it.
Yeah, I mean, I kind of caught myself just in time. I think I I aging as anybody else,
strict, you know, rapidly. But I learned several years ago, stay out of the sun, put on the
fucking sunscreen and L .A. I have to with my skin. But I think the leatheriness, it can come from
drinking, but I think it's more of a sun exposure generally. But what do I know? Well, I don't
put on sunscreen, but I often stay out of the sun. Yeah. And you got to moisturize even as a man.
Yeah, I tried to moisturize that face. Little little alo sometimes. I have a nighttime care routine,
you know, do you? Sure. What is it? Slap some lotion on my face and go to bed.
But I have a variety of lotions. I mix and match. I have a nighttime care routine as well. You
know what it is, dragging off. I don't care. You don't care. That's good.
I thought that deserved more than you gave it. It was good. I love it was very funny. I've lost
the ability to laugh, but it was good. Pat, I am higher than hell right now. Don't take much
for me. No, I guess not. I feel fine, but, you know, it's getting higher. I love that they're
drinking from a bottle called bourbon whiskey. I'm going to go get some ice. Will you cover me? Sure.
Is I go get some more bourbon whiskey? Absolutely. Well, I guess what I'd like to say folks is
talk to you a bit about what I've been watching. This might be a good time to do that.
I watched old, what's it called on Netflix? It's age gap love. You know, sometimes you just
want to watch horse shit. This is great for that. It's a British show about couples with like a
50 year age spread. It is creepy. It is uncomfortable. If you were one of the early supporters of
like a hoarder or an intervention, it's a great reality show for that. Just watching these people
who look like older than your grandma and a guy who looks like he's 16, make out, you know, it's for
you. You're going to enjoy it. In a dish, I rewatched all of extras. And while it's no office,
it's just a fantastic program. It's wonderful. And the finale justly celebrated a lot of my
friends like this the only time I ever cried with the extras finale. It's a really well done show.
I'll say this. The second season is 100 % better than the first. And they nailed it. It's shaky
at first. I'll say that. It's shaky at first. Second season is nearly perfect. I recommend it. Yeah,
I remember when it first came on. I was I almost tapped out early because I was like, oh, it's just
another one of these shows where the guys awkward and whenever. Right. And then like
somewhere in like the third or fourth episode, I was like, wait a second. This is like going deeper
than that. And then it just kept getting darker and darker. And I was like, this is amazing.
Cry like a baby when I watched that finale. Yeah, me and my buddy Ian, who you know,
and saw the other night had loved the office, the British office so deeply that we could not wait.
I mean, we were shaking and anticipation. And the first few extras just were not there for me.
The Ben Stiller won the Kate Winslet or whatever. I was like, okay, it's a Hollywood thing.
But with that run, it's great shit. The back and forth run with Ben Stiller is one of the best
written joke setup things I've ever heard. Yeah. Where he goes, uh, would Ben Stiller as the director
and he gets mad at Ricky Gervais as the actor and he walks up to him, Ben Stiller goes, do you know who I
am? And he goes, and then Ricky Gervais goes, star skier Hutch, I can never remember. Yeah, that's a
great one. And then Ben Stiller goes, was that supposed to be funny? And then Ricky Gervais goes, I don't
know, mate, you were in it. You tell me that is a that that can't be leaner. I mean, that is like,
pow, pow, pow, pow, amazing, amazing writing. Well, merchant on that show destroys it as well.
I was a fan of Hello Ladies. I know a few were, but I liked it. I enjoyed it as well. I like
Hello Ladies quite a bit. I really, I really love merchant. And the the bits with him as his agent
and then that like houseboy that's his assistant. The guy from Barry from EastEnders. Yeah.
Have you seen EastEnders? No, but he really was. Yeah, no, I know. It's so funny about it. Yeah, it's
there's there's some stuff in there. I mean, the when he comes out and he's the effeminate
genie in Aladdin. Yeah, I was screaming. And I mean, look, it's got a lot of gay jokes, but some,
I mean, some funny ones. When he shoves that water bottle that's exploding into his mouth, it's
it's where it puffs his cheeks out. I mean, there's some massive laughs in it. One of my favorite
jokes ever is in the finale from the entire show. I mean, is in the finale, we're bunny the older
gay man that he knows. Yeah, yeah, he's reggae race is sitting in the park and then bunny comes out
of the bushes. Yeah, yeah, yeah, from like some kind of sex thing. And and he's talking to reggae
race and then George Michael comes out of the bushes, which is already it's awesome because it's
George Michael making fun of when he got caught in public. Right. He comes walking out of the bushes.
And he's like George Michael looks at buttings says something along the lines of like, you know,
sniffing around for low hanging fruit or something like that. And and then bunny goes cheeky bastard.
And then he leads into reggae race. He goes, I had him once in his car. He was swerving all over the
fucking road. Yeah, I mean, it's got some great characters, some great stuff. It's streaming on Netflix
if you missed it because it's not on HBO go where I thought I would find it. I'll tell you what
else is streaming. I'm saying that because I'm assuming you've seen the British office if you haven't
stopped listening to us and go watch. Yeah, you know what else is streaming on Netflix finally got around
to it. The IT crowd. Now it's real funny, right? Holy shit. Yeah. Now I started with season three
because here I'll be going to tell you why because I'm obsessed with Matt Berry and I wanted to see
when he comes into the mix and he doesn't come in until like two or three. Oh, I thought you
meant season three episode. No season three. Is Matt Berry in it from the beginning? He's in it maybe
if not by the end of the first season. He's definitely in it at the beginning. I'll go back and watch
season two and the funniest episode is the first one of the second season. He's not the boss and for
so I started with three because I wanted to see him as a boss. But I'll go back farther. Yeah, but he is
I mean, it is he almost deals the show. It's it's it's outstanding. Yeah. Did you see ever see the one
where he's got to wear? He's such a sexual harass or as a boss that he he wears he has to wear electric
sex pants. Yeah, watch the boss him. Yeah. That line where he goes where the pants keep malfunctioning
and he's he's looking at a car magazine and they're going off and he's going it's not sexy. It's just
that he slams the book down and he goes goddamn these electric sex pants and it gets a fucking
applause break. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. He is he is amazing man. He's very fun. Holy shit.
What's going on now? Look at that explosion. It's not actually happening. I will tell you I watched
the pilot of Derek and I was all the way out all the way out. Um,
everything about it made me sweaty uncomfortable. I believe I believe your review at the time. I
remember reading your online review said I'd rather would watch the pilot on my stove. That's that's
good joke. That's good. Yeah. Uh -huh. What happened? Why are you not into the folks jokes anymore?
Well, there was no folks. I well, I feel like it's it's unassumed. It's left it hanging.
It's assumed. Um, Derek is not one of my favorites but I will tell you this. There are some
hilarious parts and it's got one of the funniest outtakes. Regretary is always this amazing outtakes.
It's got arguably one of the funniest of all the outtakes ever from any of the shows. Okay.
So I'll show you that sometime and it's very funny. All right. You watched the whole thing.
I watched the whole first season and I watched some of the second season and I was like it's just
it was just a little two. It was just too heavy handed. Yeah. Like he does a really great job
in the office and extras in like slipping in the sentiment and it's not schmaltz. Right.
But like eventually I'm still a fan but eventually he crossed his over into like Rob and Williams.
It's the same thing Rob Williams did. Right. It was like beautiful and heartwarming and then it got
schmaltz. Yeah. Wow. I mean the CGI is incredible. It looks like Mario Kart. This is Mario Kart.
Now so the Mario Kart are sentient. Is that what you're telling me? Yes. That's cool.
I like that. It looked like a you know something they did on Microsoft paint but it looked cool.
It's ridiculous. I've never seen that shadow come in first like that. There's just a few
little interesting touches that make it better than most. Sure. But hey, a few little interesting touches
is what got this guy in trouble in the first place. Folks. Look at this team right here that we're
supposed to be rooting for. Oh my god. Is Danny dead? These two look like leaking weapon. Folks.
This is not a good movie folks. I'm going to be real honest with you. Well only 23
solid minutes to go. Oh boy. Look you guys wanted it. We are bringing it. Joe what's new with you?
Any interesting tales from the week? Well Pat let me go to my file here because I did I do
try to keep a file for the show. Okay. So I don't forget to talk about certain things.
I rewatched. This isn't really a movie corner. It's just a thing that we can talk about. I rewatched
the walk the line film. Okay. Recently on a flight. Yeah. I loved it. I don't really remember it.
I remember being bothered by Joaquin Phoenix, but only because I knew Johnny Cash so well. I didn't
I didn't see him in the role at all. Right. But what do you think? I loved it. I loved it the first
time. I think he and he and Reath's Witherspoon honestly make me believe they're like supposed to be
together. Right. And it's just very rewarding when it finally happens and they do the beautiful
epilogue where it says you know they they were married and toured together for 30 more years. June
passed in May of 2001. Johnny followed four months later. It was it was very very beautiful. It was
a nice story of redemption. And Johnny Cash was essentially stalking her throughout the film.
By today's standards you'd certainly say so. Yeah. You know, I was like he got that axe at party
city. You know what? You know what? You know what? Look at this axe. I know. I told you. You were right. Yeah. I
didn't see it up close in the sunlight. It looks like it's a balloon. I think you attached to a plant.
All right. Sorry. What I was going to say is you know that argument will always come up right when
you watch one of these old sort of romantic and the unpeople will go, my God. Can you believe if you
did that in this day and age? I've been one of those people before. Sure. There you go. What's
it ever? It's it's romance, but it looks like stalking and what I finally figured it out. Here's
the thing. By today's standards. Yes, he was stalking. But I also think by today's standards he would
have known if it was never going to happen a lot more quickly. Sure. I think Reese Witherspoon would
also be acting by today's standard. Yeah. And she would say, listen, buddy. But it's one of those
things but it's not. So stop. Right. Or okay, let's date casually for a while and maybe we'll
fall in love with them. They do. Right. Does that make sense? It does. It does. Okay. Pat.
I am. Yeah. It made sense. I'm just a little toasty. I'm sorry. That's all you had from your
week. Walk the line. Well, let me see what else I have here. I had a lot of video game playing.
Okay. You know, okay. A lot of video game playing. As my grandfather used to say, balls deep in
the new Metroid game. Okay. I don't mean that my grandfather would say balls deep. I mean, he would
say balls. He was new Metroid game. And it's harder to get old balls deep. You're wrong. They're
deep all the time. Well, if you're if you're talking about pleasureing a lady, you got to go deeper to
get to where the balls are on a deeper and deeper. Yeah. Yes. Ideally, if you're making love,
your balls are close to your penis. And then depending on the length of your penis, that's how balls
deep you can get. But if the balls are hanging down at knee level, my friend used to work at a
retirement home and he said the day he quit, he walked in and there was a men's room covered from
head to toe and shit. And an old man. And this is from the this is from the president.
The president of the. Oh, gosh, yeah. I thought that was like a wild political. No, no, I was trying to
think of, you know, manager. I don't know. I couldn't think of a word because I'm fucked up. Sorry.
Well, he walks in. There's shit all over. And then there's a guy who I may or may not have
been responsible for the shit sitting in the next stall with his balls up and over his legs.
So they weren't in the water. And my friend was like, I'm out. I'm done. I quit. This is a cool shot.
All right.
Now that's not a cool shot. I'm smelling a routine here, Pat.
I'm smelling a routine for your standup here. What's that? I think you do this bit. Well,
it wasn't me as my friend. No, no, no, no, this is just that that's just the tag. You come out,
you open with this. You go, you go, folks, I don't know if you've heard. I'm getting older.
Okay. Yeah. Wait, wait, continue waiting because there won't be one. Yeah. No, no, no, you come out.
You go, folks, I'm sure you can't tell, but I'm getting older than the left. Like that. Then you
get a laugh, right? Then I get my feelings get so hurt that I turn on them. Then you go, you know
what separates every age from the next ball distance. And then you do a whole bit about this. When I was
a kid, my balls in my cock was like roommates in college. You do a couple bits about college here.
You keep going far and far and you go, now I go to the toilet. My dick is in the penthouse. My balls
are in the swimming pool. Right? Wow. You're right. I think I'm going to get back in the standup
with this bit. You're really laying on. And then you tell your friend's story at the end there.
Right. I got my right ball in Chicago with Larry Appleton. My left balls back in me posts
with the Bartaka Moose family. Folks, I'm saying these balls are perfect strangers.
It's like they never met. See, you're getting it. I'm, I'm riffing. I'll get this into it. It's
good. This is a good bit. This could be your get her done or your dirty nursery rhymes. Right,
right. You know, or, uh, well, or your pig noise, Tim Allen. Sure. Yeah. My, uh, have you seen this?
What's your favorite sign filled bit of all time?
I, yeah, yeah. I like the, the meaner sign filled. I like when it's not like, you know, toothpaste or
whatever. I like when he gets a little meaner with it. Um, it's, it's too hard to separate from
the man and the show, his bits for me. Give me yours. Um, well, I've got a couple, but the one I'll
say right now, currently, my favorite one that I would like literally sit up, sit and think about
and start laughing. Right. As we goes, pizza hut. Now has the, and that was when it first came out.
He goes, the stuffed crust pizza, the entire crust, yeah, stuffed with cheese. Yeah. You're eating a
pizza. The whole goddamn thing is cheese. I like, what's pizza? It's next product. They're going to,
they're going to put a block of cheese right here and bake it in an oven. I'm going to eat your way
out just to get the five cents back. I mean, look, I've seen the man live. I've seen
all his specials. I'm a huge fan. I was, do you know Pete Corey Ellie? No, he's a very, very
funny comedian. Okay. And a good friend of mine. We were doing a show once and we, we were performing
in a show and, but we weren't the only two comics. There was some other people. Right. And we were
sitting in the back of the room and another comic was on stage and we were whispering discreetly,
like we weren't being disruptive. Yeah. But for some reason, we got on this thing about
Seinfeld's bit about the airplane pilot. Uh -huh. And, you know, we were a little tuned up. We were
drinking and stuff. And he goes, uh, Pete's going, the bit, the bit where, uh, you're on the plane,
the passengers like, listen to us. So we're going to take it up to about 30 ,000 feet and turn left
and he goes, yeah, and you go and, yeah, do whatever the hell you got to do. Just get us there. Yeah,
yeah. You know, he kept saying that to me, dude, and I was laughing so hard and he was laughing, like
well, what does that happen? Now we got a judge doom Roger Rabbit situation. That was like flat,
remember in Flash Square, one of the guys I gets poked out. I haven't seen it, but I remember Casino
and the dude's I gets poked out. Um, Flash Square is a lot of fun. You should watch it. All right. It's
ridiculous and it's bad, but it's fun. Um, anyway, he goes, uh, and he's telling me we're laughing
hysterically. And then he just goes, and we realize our friend on stage thinks we're like cracking
up that hard at his set. Yeah. And he's like, oh, he thinks we're laughing at this. Yeah. And we
left the room. I went, I went and saw Eddie Pepitone once and it's the hardest I've laughed in five,
six years, but I was going to see my old boss do a comedic monologue, uh, which we kind of all
felt obliged to do. So Pepitone, I, I am. First off, he goes up on stage. My, my boss and he
talks for like 45 minutes. And he had like a 15 minute set that he's supposed to do. Can you say
which boss? I'd rather not, but you can probably surmise. Right. Uh, he, he, it goes fine, but,
you know, like he's the kind of guy who's like glancing over at our table and can tell we're not laughing
and the room's not exactly lit up, you know, but the story goes on forever. Right. And then he goes
back and stands by the bar. When Pepitone comes out, I'm like, because he came over and was like, didn't hear
a lot of laughing. And I'm like, well, he wanted to hear your story. You know, you're telling a
story. It's a, you know, that kind of thing. He dirty bastard. He goes back to the bar. Pepitone comes
up and I'm not a big laughery. You know, so I'm just like, all right, whatever. And I know I love
Pepitone, but I and, and all my friends were there. We're scream like howling pound on the table laughing.
And at one point, I, me and Heather were like dying and I throw my head over to look at her.
And my eyes go a little too far and back at the bar is the boss staring directly at me like a
fucking serial killer as I'm throwing my head back laughing at somebody else. Didn't go great,
but what a heath. Not a nice man. The, uh, this, this is the funniest Pepitone joke I've ever heard.
All right. Ready? Yeah. He goes, uh, my grandmother died recently. I think you've said this on the
she was murdered by man. I owed money to. They needed a name.
Much as you wouldn't trust somebody not crying at the end of plain strands, I wouldn't trust
somebody sitting stone face at an out of Pepitone show. Who would love Pepitone strangely as my dad.
Maybe I can set him up with a tape or something. Holy shit, man. It's so funny.
Never done a special to my knowledge, Pepitone. No, he did in ruins. It's very good.
Oh, all right. Great. It might still be on Netflix, but it wasn't there for a while. God,
I'm going on that. Oh, wait, I did see that. That was great. Back when I used to have a weekly show,
he did the show when we swapped phone numbers. Yeah. And then I texted him. I was like,
hey, thanks for doing the show, dude. And, uh, you know, it's like the next day, whatever he's like,
I can't. I had fun, whatever it was. Good seeing you. I was like, good seeing you too.
I go, hey, dude, maybe now you can follow me back on Twitter, right? And he goes, uh, fuck. Oh,
yeah, dude. I'm not following you. Sorry. And he takes me. He goes, just followed you.
And I wrote back, listen, dude, long story, but I got to unfollow you real.
I'll explain. And I just sat there for a while. And I texted. He didn't respond. I go, dude,
I'm just joking. Yeah. And he wrote back. Ha, I was like, this cock sucker.
He's a funny fucking guy. He's, I mean, live to me, just like riffing is he is the funniest.
Man, this is a lot of slow mo, you know, you're the one that said this was shot as well as
the godfather, whatever the hell you said, but I didn't.
The hand keeps coming back. The mask is getting worse. Somehow in the dark, the mask looks worse.
Just a guy. It's a shitty villain. I've said it from the beginning. It's a shitty villain. Nobody
wants a dragon man. Yeah. That walks around dressed like a janitor. Wow, look at this.
Nobody's asking for it. It makes no sense. There's this ridiculous.
No, explain it. All the crows are falling out of this guy. That's kind of cool. See, they want me back.
But I'm saying explain what this thing fucking is. Yeah. What is it? I do not know.
It's a simple explanation with Freddie. Right. This here's a guy. He got burned because he got
burned. He was able to somehow come back in your dreams and murder your kids. It sounds crazy,
but it makes enough sense that you're like, okay, I'll go along with this. Why is he dressed like that?
Oh, obviously, that's what he's wearing when they burned him to death. Right. This says none of that.
It's like, he's just a remorseless killing machine. But you're like, why does this lizard have pants?
Where is he? What is this? I don't understand. These are connected in any way. Why doesn't he just run
with wingholes in it by the way? He's made fashion choices. Clearly, the sweater has wingholes.
Which you presume he cut to put the sweater. How did he get the sweater on over the wings?
He was at the gap going. Let me ask you something. Are the wingholes on this true to size?
It's a real shit fucking franchise, man. Well, look, this is obviously the worst of them.
Every a 23rd spring for 23 days, it gets to eat. Wait, so the second one came out 23 years ago?
Yeah, dude. I mean, 2007, right? No, they were definitely in the 2000s.
That's not correct. Well, then I saw the first jeeps creeps when I was in New York City,
and I would have been at least 22 years old. Yeah, who loves the jeepers creepers franchise?
Miles from Murphy Brown. Now, why is that? What's that guy's name again? Brandt Shaw. That's right.
Murphy Brown returning to television, by the way. We talked about that. Brandt Shaw, so I met
Grant because we did a scene together on Louis, and we ended up talking after when we had a break,
and he's like, you want to go to lunch? I'm like, yes, we went and got lunch together. Halfway through
lunch, I realized he's the guy from Murphy Brown. I didn't even realize it. Talked all about that,
and then he was like, what do you like, man? I was like, I love hard movies. He's like, and he's
got great taste, but he was like, I fucking, I'm telling you, go watch jeepers creepers, and I was like,
dude, I agree. I know. That's why I'm telling you because I think you guys are cut from similar
cloths. For me to get down with a horror, you know, I tend to like a lighter horror, a family horror,
or something with a great visual sense, you know, I did like Hellraiser, but that's the kind of horror
I tend to not want to spend two hours of my life in that world, that type of. Let's just be for
shape. Rub your face in the muck kind of world. For safety purposes, let's be very clear. You're
pad is saying horror, not horror. What do I supposed to say? Horror? No, I'm saying, I'm saying
just so we all know, you're not saying horror. You're saying horror. Yes. Yes. Correct. Oh boy. Sorry.
See, no, look, it's ending with two male and female child kids. I've never seen chemistry like that.
By the way, did you see these two characters once in the movie? I saw freckles earlier in the truck,
yeah. I don't know either of these people are. No. She could probably wipe the blood off her chin if
they're going to keep making out. Well, I mean, you know, it makes up for his freckles. Maybe she's
going to do it. Yeah, it's not make fun of kids. That's fine. I mean, I'm just saying they both
have stuff on their face. That's all. Come on, Joe. She's not actively bleeding. She's bruised from
their run -ins with the lizard. With the most interesting lizard in the world, the lizard
and pleaded khakis and moccasins.
Jepers, crappers. Where'd I get these sneakers? Up at Nordstrom. Here's my Dennis Miller monologue
joke about Jeepers Creepers. Ready? All right. Yeah, I saw Jeepers Creepers 3. It sucked. I don't know
tell you folks, but I'm not into monsters wearing pleaded fucking khakis. It's good. He's been,
people have been giving him a lot of shit on Twitter, I guess, because his jokes are so terrible.
He's like, and he's trying to act all above it all. He's like, yeah, I'll be going to the Oscars
tonight. No wait. Last minute I decided I'm going to sit in a fucking canoe and shoot my foot or
but like just somebody who had lost the ability to tell a joke. It was kind of sad.
What I just said was funnier than the actual joke. Jereer's bit where he goes
Javier, and I said, did you ever hear his bit where he goes,
Krispy Kreme coming out with a new drinkable form of their donut, because apparently they're
going to release some Krispy Kreme drink. Okay. And he goes, I can only assume this product is for
fat people have the coupe become too lazy to fucking chill. Okay. And he goes pour it in my mouth.
Why don't you just inject it in my gums with a fucking river read? Yeah, he's not my thing.
I think it's probably not my thing. And he's become much less my thing.
We have devolved through the end of the movie into a Dennis Miller debate. The movie
is over. Japers, papers, we missed it. Where'd you get those fucking papers, babe?
I'm not seeing Coppola's name in the credits anymore. I'm glad he severed ties. But folks,
this movie wasn't good. Even those that requested we do it, we're basically telling us you're not
going to enjoy it. I think we both agree. It's the worst of the franchise. Joe and I do disagree
about this franchise, but not about JC three. And not about our love for all of you. That's something we
always come together on. We love you guys. We don't do plugs on these. Thank you for supporting us.
We genuinely appreciate it. And Joe, you got anything to say last remarks? I got another Dennis Miller
bit. Ready? Yeah. You know, go on. Get through it. You know,
Salva actually approached Coppola to produce the third Japers creepers.
Coppola was like, yeah, Salva from the Godfather to a movie directed by a guy that
fucked the fucking wee blow. Holy shit. Good move. That that gummy might be taking hold.
That gummy might I can't even look Joe on the eye right now. You know, it's funny. No,
it was very fucked the fucking wee blow. And you landed wee blow. I kept thinking that it was going to
get away from you, but it didn't. I went. I was a boy scout through wee blows. Did you know this, Joe?
They are now letting girls into the boy scouts. Are they going to just change to the
scouts or something? I know. They're not because I was like, well, why wouldn't it be the girl
scouts in the whole room went like, so I just stopped talking. I didn't feel equipped to go down
this road. But I'm like, but it's not like there's only boy scouts. I agree. But let's get out of
this. We're going to cut everything from after you said, Joe, do you have anything else to say? No,
we shouldn't. We shouldn't. This is this is the stuff people like. Thank you folks for joining
us in supporting Victor Salfa. And we will see you next time. And we'll see you in hell.