Patty Walsh, Joe DeRosa here for the we'll see you in hell podcast.
Walsh, why don't you intro us this week?
All right.
Uh, what happens when two friends move across the country, but still talk a
couple of times a month about the movies they enjoy, we'll see you in hell.
Yeah.
We'll see what happens and we'll see you.
There you go.
Walsh, how's your day going so far?
It's like getting a, uh, a, uh, what are the, what are the, what are
the paddles at the, and the ER it's nine AM for me on a Sunday.
It's it's so gray outside.
It's nearly black and, uh, just got to get online and be funny.
It's tough.
It is.
Uh, it's not the easiest job all the time, but damn it.
We try our best.
Try.
I was under the covers with my cat.
The two of us, it never happens.
She cuddled in under the covers with me and I had her in sort of a spoon
position and my alarm went off and I was like, God damn you, Joe.
God damn you.
Well, we were supposed to do yesterday at a later time.
And then you said, I want to do Sunday instead.
So then I had to, I got to, I got a Halloween thing to get to.
So that's, it is Halloween and happy Halloween to all of you.
Uh, what are you doing tonight?
Joe, you got a costume.
I got a costume and I'm marching in the Halloween parade with some
friends in a group costume.
Okay.
Uh, and, uh, human centipede, human centipede.
And luckily I got the front.
Yeah, definitely.
We'll eat up, you know, it depends on how much you like your friends,
but I would say eat up.
I hate my friends and we're meeting at a, I got to go to my buddy's place
beforehand, my buddy Ari's place beforehand.
You know, Ari Gold, the agent from Entourage.
Yes.
Yeah.
Um, who strangely is dressing up as Jeremy Piven tonight.
By the way, probably my favorite standup working right now.
Not in no offense, but no, no, Jeremy Piven.
Woo.
Yeah.
Have you listened to his new podcast?
How you live with Jeremy Piven or?
I haven't.
Yeah, I haven't, but you know, these.
God damn celebrity podcasts.
Yeah.
It really pisses me off, man.
You know, it didn't.
And now it's starting to, because it's like they, they're the top 10, you know,
it's like people are listening to Dax Shepard and Kristen Bell listening to
Jason Bateman and Will Arnett.
It's all like, it's all like people who were on network television
15 plus years ago, very strange.
By the way, and continue to be on network television and any movies and everything.
It's like Seth Green is starting one.
Rogan.
Yeah.
Seth Rogan, excuse me.
I said Seth Green was makes sense to me.
Seth Green would make sense.
I'd be like, yeah, yeah, I get that.
Seth Rogan.
Released a book.
He's got a weed company, you know, it's and great, you know, I think the
man does Alzheimer's, uh, uh, benefits.
I, I hope he donates a lot to them.
I hate Alzheimer's and I hope I don't get it, but.
Hey, how would you know?
Oh, that's a good one.
Uh, yeah.
So what are, what are you being?
Uh, I don't want to say because there was a, there was an agreement.
There was an agreement amongst the group to not divulge the costume
because some of the people in the group are notable and didn't
want to be given away.
Okay.
Make sense.
Like, is it a controversial costume?
No, not at all.
It's just covering faces.
Okay.
You're going to be the girl from the Queens.
Wait, I can talk.
I'm being too elusive.
Sal's coming with us.
Sal requested that.
Can we wear a costume that makes me anonymous?
Uh -huh.
Oh, I see.
Cause that was the point.
And, uh, he was like, because then I can just like hang out and stuff.
This sounds terrible.
This sounds so snotty of him.
Should we cut this out?
Is this bad?
I'm saying he's a, he's a well -known person.
Yeah.
I don't think it's all night on Halloween.
I don't think it's snotty.
And he was like, if I walk in, he goes, it's fun to walk in the actual parade.
I just got to cover my face.
Otherwise it looks like the guy from the show was walking down the street.
So he said, what we do is, is we get a group costume so we
don't lose track of each other.
Uh -huh.
I went on the bonfire radio show with Jay Okerson, uh, and talked about this
and made fun of Sal endlessly for how dumb I thought the idea was.
And in the process of that gave away the group costume, which I got a lot of
shit for, because then they had to scour the internet to find a new group.
Oh, you dropped it.
I said what it was.
Well, what was the other one?
The first one was it's a philosopher Raptor.
Okay.
Thank God.
Did you build it?
No, it was like some goofy fucking, you know,
costume.
The point was it covered your head.
Okay.
Now we've got a different one.
Yeah.
And, uh, I mean, this doesn't come out till past Halloween, but for some
reason, I feel like I still shouldn't give it away.
You don't have to do it.
I don't know.
What if, what if while in costume, you all beat, uh, uh, unhoused person to
death and then the police will be like, well, how are we going to find these
people?
Then they listened to our podcast and like, oh, they were
dressed as a giant Komodo dragon.
You really doing this unhoused thing, huh?
You're going to, you're going to stick with it.
I switched last minute.
You know, I'm, I'm, I'm on it.
I'm, I'm doing what I'm supposed to be doing, you know?
Uh, I'm a couple of words I'm sticking with homeless is one of them.
Yeah.
And I'm sorry.
I'm not ready to give up prostitute.
I'm sorry.
I don't see anything wrong with the word.
What's wrong with the word?
That's a strange one because I remember when hooker was like, no, it's prostitute.
And it's like, whenever you're like rudely corrected by somebody, it stays
with you, like you feel shame and awkward and everything.
And then to have somebody be like, no, it's not prostitute.
It just keeps changing, you know?
And that maybe that's good.
It was a time where it was, where it was whore.
That was the actual word or if you're, uh, uh, Joey pants and the sopranos.
Yeah.
Yes.
Uh, she was a, who I text.
That word out sometimes that I phonetically spell it H H W H O dash
W E R E and I always hope that person gets it.
Sure.
Here's the thing.
I think, uh, I had a little bit of a TIF last night.
I was in a, I was in a pinch at a comedy show.
You were in a TIF and a pinch.
And well, well, it was TIF.
You're alive, right?
Yeah.
Snag and, uh,
it was a snafu.
So comedy shows sometimes in New York run late.
Yeah.
And when they do the city that never sleeps.
If they start late, it can fuck you up because sometimes you have to
get across town to do another show.
Right.
And you don't have a ton of time.
And, uh, this on crashing HBO's crash.
Yeah, there you go.
So this happens last night at the club I'm at show starts 15 minutes late.
I'm supposed to go second in the lineup.
A friend of mine is supposed to go first.
I'm panicked because I'm now I'm going to maybe miss my other show because
the, this thing started too late.
I, she comes in the room.
Uh, the host is on stage.
I run up to her.
I'm like, could you please switch with me?
She not only refuses, but then says, I don't want to.
I don't have anywhere else to be.
I just don't feel like it.
Wow.
So then I said, not in a funny way, like, no, no dead, very
callous, like dead serious.
You knew this person?
Oh, for 20 years.
And then I said to her, fuck you.
That's really fucked up and walked away.
A mutual friend who was trying to mediate this now called me today and
said, you were both wrong.
I said, please explain to me how I was wrong.
You shouldn't have said, fuck you to her.
And I go, oh, grant that you, she said a rude thing to me.
I had a rude retort back.
That's how a TIF works.
Right.
I didn't say, fuck you switch.
I didn't lead with fuck you.
She said to me, she didn't feel like helping me when I was in dire need of
help, right, because I was going to lose a hundred dollars because I was going to
miss the show because this show started late and it was out of my hands.
My back was against the wall.
When someone, a friend of 20 years says to you, I don't feel like helping you.
I don't think fuck you as an inappropriate response to that.
If you've got a friend, fuck you relationship.
Sure.
I don't, you know, a man, a woman is always different and blah, blah, blah.
But yes, we shouldn't be, shouldn't be, but it shouldn't be.
But I, but my point is this.
I think we're all getting a little carried away with the respectful, whatever,
you know, it's like getting into this weird territory now where it's like, well,
I didn't use any swear words with you, but it's like the, the subtext of what
you said was so much worse than fuck you.
Fuck you as a benign, whatever you said to me in so many words, I don't
care if you lose money you need.
Like, yeah, I think that sucks, but you know, maybe next time you
go, Hey, I'm going to lose a hundred dollars.
That's really fucked up.
Oh, they, she knew bad and give you the stuff, the spotlight.
She knew.
I mean, this is common practice.
Comics have to do this all the time because things happen.
Yeah.
And so anyway, there you have it.
There you have it.
When my friend said, this is either going to get me accolades with the
fans today or people are going to get upset.
Well, my friend said to me, you were wrong for that.
I said, not only was I not wrong, I'll say it again.
Yeah.
And do me a favor.
When you speak to her later, tell her I said, fuck you.
He said he wouldn't do that.
That's proud.
Yeah.
No mediator would, would relay that message.
No true mediator would pass that along.
You're a terrible mediator.
So Joe said, fuck you again.
Um, well, I'm sorry that happened.
Did you lose the Hondo?
No, I made it by the skin of my goddamn teeth.
Okay.
But I'll tell you, that's always a fun way to go on stage panicked watching
a clock in the back of the room and then wondering if you're going to be able
to get a cab in time and then hitting traffic, like literally running into
the other club, like I'm here.
I'm here.
Yeah.
You know, if I was writing the new Spider -Man, I would have him be a
stand -up comic and he's got to get across town in New York in like two
minutes, or he's going to lose, let's say a thousand, we raised the stakes.
That's a big studio.
Sure.
Then we just have him do his fucking web thing all over town.
You know, they did that with, um, in, I think it's the Andrew Garfield
one where he's a pizza guy and he, they, that they do that.
Okay.
Something similar where he's got to like get the pizza to the, you know,
and he's Spider -Man's the pizza, which I mean, I'm willing to believe the
guy can actually swing from buildings before I believe the pizza arrives
unscathed as it flies through the air.
Yeah.
I've never received a pizza unscathed when the guy drives five
minutes to my home, but I like that idea.
That's a funny, the stand -up comedy thing.
Uh, I watched a guy on, uh, I love now.
I like to go to bed angry as, as, as you well know, Joe, and I like watching
these compilations of mask freakouts, Karen's, you know, whatever it is, just
a 20 minute compilation of people losing their shit in stores.
I love watching that now.
One of my favorite things.
And sometimes they'll throw in a random video where it's not somebody
freaking out, it's just something weird that happens.
So as this guy is a postmate and he walks into this, uh, Chinese restaurant,
takes the food, walks outside, sits on the curb next to his bike, he sits
and eats from this food for you watch it for like two minutes, 30 seconds of
him just like eating it, reseals the white Styrofoam thing, puts it in the bag,
reties it, hops on his bike and goes, holy shit, unbelievable.
I mean, YouTube, I think the only reason I never really fully got into it is I
knew I'd get lost there and get addicted.
But, uh, man, those compilations are very, very, very addictive and fun to watch.
And I've never seen a double like it's, it's happened so many times and, and
you know, what's happened in the last two years there because they're all mask
related, man, it's fun to watch.
YouTube is, uh, YouTube is my, uh, it's my go -to.
I watch YouTube more than I watch anything.
I mean, especially now because there's like full TV shows on it.
And I don't even mean like, you know, produced Hollywood TV shows.
Those are on there too.
But I mean, like you follow channels, guys make Netflix documentary, like
right, uh, content and it's great.
And it's about any subject you could ever want to watch content on.
Guys have cooking shows that are like as good as anything you'd see on the food
network and the dishes are more interesting because they're, it's just
their own thing, video game shows.
Like I watched so much shit on YouTube.
Yeah.
I think the kids today who are coming up with only YouTube, like they don't even
know, we always talk about, oh, you guys don't know how bad you have.
We only had five channels or you had to go to blockbuster or whatever.
But now it's just, you can watch whatever you want in one second.
And I think that's why the movie it's in one of many reasons, the movie
businesses cratering yet again.
I mean, Heather saw the last duel because we heard it was leaving
theaters after two weeks.
Jesus.
Was it good?
I had had so many friends go, you know, what's fucking awesome is the last duel.
And we absolutely loved it.
We saw it on its last day in theaters for the most part.
This is a movie directed by Ridley Scott, one of the most commercially
successful directors ever starring three of the biggest stars.
Damon Affleck driver, Jodie Comer, who's on the up after killing Eve,
which was a great show and written by Affleck, Damon and Nicole Hall of
Centner, who did enough said in a lot of great movies.
It's two and a half hours, you know, it's fucking awesome.
It's a night movie.
I mean, I think the problem was the theater or the trailer leaned too much on rape.
And it is about that's what the whole movie was about.
That's the plot of the movie.
Yes.
But, and you know, maybe it would have been a little bit of a bait and switch
to, to sell it as a night movie and not mention the rape, but I don't know.
I can't believe nobody went to this thing.
It's great.
And it's got great reviews and the action is awesome.
And the direction is awesome.
Ridley Scott's like 86.
He's directing at the top of his game.
And he's got House of Gucci coming out in two weeks.
House of Gucci looks awesome.
It looks awesome at first.
I thought it was ridiculous.
And then I was like, no, you know, it's going to be great.
It looks kind of like, um, the same vibe as American hustle where it is a little
corny, but you have a great time anyway.
Yeah.
I'm excited for it.
Lady Gaga really blew me away in the trailer.
I didn't even realize it was her.
It's like, Holy shit.
I didn't watch the new trailer.
I only saw the first one and the Lido.
I mean, I don't know what he's doing, but, uh, we'll see.
It's so weird because you're not supposed to be able to do fat suits
and prosthetics anymore.
And we got Stellan Scarsgard in Dune wearing prosthetics.
We got Lido wearing prosthetics.
We got Linda Tripp, Sarah Paulson in the, uh, whatever that show is.
Monica Lewinsky.
Yeah.
Uh, uh, uh, impeachment.
Oh yeah.
Thought it was called, uh, say yes to the dress folks.
The, uh, do they show the cum in that show?
I I'm not going to, I don't have, I mean, it's what's his name.
It's what's his name.
So I bet they do that fucking Ryan Murphy.
Yeah.
They probably show the cum coming out of the dog.
I can't believe there wasn't like secret service in latex black suits.
Yeah.
Um, you know, but, uh, uh, yeah, that, uh, I think Halsey
Gooch looks pretty great.
Um, I want to see the last door.
I actually looked up the story of the last door and read about it online
because I didn't think I was like, you know, you think back to those times,
not that any of us were alive.
Right.
And in the trailer, I was like, this guy got in trouble for rape back then.
Like I thought it was like just men being complete animals.
Yeah.
And then I looked up the story and I was like, Oh my God, this is like,
this really happened.
Like, this is like, what a crazy, like, not like what an interesting.
It's a story.
I guess the best way I'd put it is a story that you never knew would have
existed.
You know, the assumption would be that it was just swept under some rug and that
was it, you know, in that time period.
Yeah.
Well, it was based on real events and they get into that.
There's this old woman in it who's like, you don't think I've never been raped.
You know, you keep it to yourself in a very chilling scene, but, um, it was
considered a crime at the time against the man.
So like for the, so if the woman, wait, it's Damon, Damon is married to, to,
uh, Comer and the accusation is that driver raped her, but that is a crime
against Matt Damon, not against Comer.
So that's it's, it's, it's all very much about, you know, it's, it's a
patriarchy movie in a way, but Ridley Scott is, is far too smart to make it
like most of the movies and TV shows now where it's just hammering you over the
head.
It's, um, it's super interesting because it winds up like the duel itself is,
and they tell you this in the very first scene, the duel is between driver and
Damon and whoever kills the other one.
That means that's who was telling the truth because God guides your sword.
So if Damon wins, it means driver raped his wife.
If driver wins, it means he didn't rape the wife and the wife sits there
watching, by the way, if it's proven that driver didn't rape Comer, then Comer
gets killed in front of everyone.
They dragged the wife out and kill her because she lied.
So it's really, really interesting.
But the movie's done in three parts.
The first being Damon's point of view.
It's very Rashomon style.
First being day or that episode of mama's family where she gets hit in the head
with a pot, right?
And yeah, a few points of things, but, uh, yeah, the first one is Damon's
point of view. The second one is driver's point of view.
And then the third one, it says, uh, the truth, according to lady, whatever.
And then lady vanishes and it just says the truth.
So, you know, that's what actually happened.
Okay.
But, um, it's fantastic.
Damon is playing some sort of like aggro meathead who's terrible at sex.
It's very funny.
Also, like the sex scenes between Damon and his wife are like, wow, this
man does not know how to fuck.
It didn't have porn at this time, mind you, but, um, driver is funny.
Affleck is hilarious.
Affleck doesn't even try to do like the British thing or anything.
He's basically like a bro with a ridiculous bowl haircut.
And it's very, for a movie this heavy, it's very, very funny.
I really recommend it.
And I just saw that the blue ray is coming.
So it had like a two week window in theaters, which is probably lost $150 million.
All right.
I, well, I feel like we're in the movie corner, so I'll do a movie.
Yeah, that was, there you go.
There was one also I'll stick with the theme of great directors.
Uh, I finally watched QT eight.
You've discussed it, the Quentin Tarantino.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Okay.
Doc, what a great doc, which just an awesome doc getting into the, uh,
as an artist and, uh, great interviews with Zoe Bell, Michael Madsen, Jamie
Fox, Jamie Fox really steals the show.
He's really funny in it.
Yeah.
There's a part where he makes fun of Spike Lee a little bit.
He's like, I love spike, but spikes like the old man and get off my grass.
He's very funny in it.
Um, but you know, that said, I showed a buddy, Jackie Brown the other day.
He had never seen it.
Obviously a great movie.
I mean, the amount of N words and Jackie Brown, it's a lot.
I mean, Django, of course, but it's like, man, you forget.
Good Lord.
Yeah.
The, uh, Damon tells a great story where he said, uh, in the movie where he
said DiCaprio came up to him and Sam Jackson and said, I'm having a very hard
time with saying the, the, the racial stuff to you guys, like it's, it's hard.
Sorry.
You said Damon said this?
I'm sorry, DiCaprio, okay.
Excuse me.
Uh, because we're friends.
And then like, I guess to motivate him, Jamie was like, fuck it, Leo.
We're not friends, dude, you know, do the scenes, man.
We got to do if we ain't friendly, you know, whatever.
Yeah.
And then he said the next day DiCaprio came in and then didn't look at him or
speak to him for the rest of the shoot.
And I guess that's why he was able to do, do it.
But, uh, but I mean, it's just an awesome, awesome documentary.
They do.
You mentioned this when you reviewed it.
They do conveniently kind of glaze over Weinstein.
They do, but which I don't really, well, look, it's not a movie
about Weinstein obviously, but it's bookended with Weinstein.
Like it opens with the Weinstein thing.
Yeah.
And then they come back to it later.
And then the end of the movie is that he's shooting, um, you know, hateful
eight or no, he's about to start shooting once upon a time in Hollywood
for the first time without Harvey Weinstein.
That is sort of the spine of the movie, but it is a little weird that
it's just kind of like Tarantino just said, I knew about this and I
should have done something.
And then that's kind of it.
Like they don't get into like, well, but why didn't you or why didn't you say
something and look, I'm not calling for anybody to, to, to rise and
be a vigilante or whatever.
I'm just, I'm just curious.
Like what, tell me about the position you were in.
Like I want to know.
Yeah.
They kind of dated Mira Sorvino too.
I don't know that timeline, but yeah, he did date Mira Sorvino.
Um, but Kevin Smith is kind of doing that too, with Weinstein now we're
like, he'll like, he'll like make like a, you know, a commentary against
which fine, obviously a commentary against Weinstein on Twitter, but
then it's kind of like, yeah, but dude, like you were part of that whole
crew, like you were right in the mix.
Like you didn't know about any of this or did you like, it's just kind of,
and again, I'm not pointing fingers at anybody.
I'm just saying like, it's kind of a weird, it's kind of weird.
Um, you know, in the sense that it's also weird when like the assistants
would be like, he would have me go buy him a dildo every Tuesday.
It's like, well, maybe, maybe you quit.
Yeah.
No, you had the door dashing sex toys to this guy.
You know, maybe.
Right.
Well, I think that the main, one of the main aspects of that job was, was
getting him the injections that he would inject directly into his dick because
even Viagra didn't work anymore.
So he injected like steroids into his cock.
I mean, Jesus Christ, look, here's the thing.
When my dick doesn't work, great.
Yeah.
I don't have a problem, but if I'm not in the mood, I'm not in the mood.
I don't understand these guys that are like, damn it.
I got to get into the mood.
Why your body is not in the mood.
It's like, it's like eating when you're not hungry.
Yeah.
It wouldn't take a pill to make you hungry.
It's like our power thing.
It's a power thing.
I mean, it makes it even sicker.
It's like, you know, the, the really only, and I'm not saying this is a good
argument, I'm saying like the only argument that people have really for
rape is, is, is, is I was carried away or in the moment or whatever.
If you're strategically planning to get your dick hard, so you can rape someone.
That's a whole nother world of evil.
It's all evil.
Yeah.
You know, I don't know what I'm talking about degrees of evil, but Jesus,
I know what you mean.
Remeditated murder is worse than spur of the moment murder.
Yeah.
It's, I'm sweating.
It's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, um, it's like, it's like the,
it's like serial killer shit.
It's like this guy's plotting out.
So my point is, is I would have liked in this documentary for them to maybe
get a little bit into, even if it was just them saying, Hey, you know,
he told me about it when he found out and he didn't know what to do because
there was no protocol or whatever, you know, like something on behalf of what
Tarantino dealt with, but they don't, they don't really touch on it.
Aside from that, it's a great, great, uh, documentary.
Um, I really enjoyed it and it sparked me into watching re -watching some
Tarantino films, which y 'all will get to later in this movie corner.
Uh, I saw sort of the original, uh, horror anthology.
It's not the first horror anthology, but, uh, it was from 1964 Masaki
Kobayashi, who was, uh, considered a, you know, almost a Kurosawa level
filmmaker, a master, he did a movie called Kwaidan that I owned in the
Criterion collection whenever Halloween rolls around Criterion goes, here's
some spooky Criterions and there aren't many, it's not a, they don't represent
a lot of horror, unfortunately, but, um, I always saw Kwaidan.
I was excited to watch it, popped it out last night, had no idea.
It was three hours when I put it in.
Didn't notice, which is unbelievable, but my phone was in the other room.
I didn't get up and get it.
I was blown away by this movie.
It's like, uh, a three hour piece of art.
It's four different stories.
It's more sort of unsettling, haunting images than actual scares, you know,
because it's kind of like they're Japanese folk tales where they have
a message, a moral, um, but they're usually about loss, ghosts, uh,
regret, et cetera.
I don't think I've ever seen a more beautiful movie.
It looks like it's, it's 90%, 95 % done on sets, uh, and the colors in this
thing, especially cause I rewatched the new Dune because we're talking about
Dune today, um, and my biggest gripe with that movie is that it's just gray.
It's just a two hour, 45 minute gray movie.
And this movie used every color in the box, like version.
I was shielding my eyes once in a while.
Like I, it's a, I don't know.
I always work the purchase to me.
Absolutely.
I mean, if, if you just sit down and you're like, all right, you know,
give me a horror anthology or whatever.
That's not this.
It's an art movie mixed with that.
Um, and, and an extreme art movie, like a slow art movie mixed with that.
So, uh, it's not going to be for everybody.
I was completely riveted by it.
I didn't turn it off.
Like I said, I was shocked to learn it was three hours.
Um, and just really cool, just cool as shit.
Loved it.
It's one of those, I always say on the show, you know, there you'll see a
movie where it's like any still you want as a poster on your wall.
That's how I felt about this movie.
Uh, strongly recommend it's the guy who did Herakiri, which I also loved.
And now I got to check out more of this guy's work because I'm into it.
All right.
Quite rewatched both of these films.
I saw in the theater the next two I'm going to do.
Uh, and I hadn't seen them since, so I rewatched them.
Yeah.
Uh, Django Unchained first time I'd seen it since I saw it in the theater.
Absolute masterpiece of a film.
That's great.
Um, I got to say too, you know, you mentioned the runtime on, um, this
movie you were talking about.
Same thing with Django Unchained.
You're sitting there.
I knew going in, you know, I'm like, this is a three hour romp, you know?
Right.
And I was like, I'll just turn it on for a little while.
Probably won't sit through the whole thing right now.
Just glued to the last second.
Couldn't stop watching it.
Yeah.
It's awesome.
Every performance is incredible.
The Jamie Foxx in particular, uh, it's just, it's an incredible, incredible
movie and it tackles, uh, the issue.
I wouldn't say it tackles the issue of slavery, but it's a slavery tale told
in a very graphic novel, comic book kind of way, uh, you know, ultra
violence, adventure, action, like, you know, aspects of modern life that would
not have existed back then, but are seamlessly sort of folded in, you know,
by the end of the movie, you know, the beginning of the movie, Jamie Foxx is
like, you know, dude, he's like, he's like afraid to speak and by the end of the
movie, he's in that like blue, uh, suit and he's making the horse like do that
weird dance and everything like, right.
He's like a superhero by the end of the movie.
Yeah.
Cheers.
When he came in, in that suit, when I saw it on like, I saw it on like
Christmas day or something.
Yeah.
And the part still, when the two pox starts playing and he's shooting
everybody, it gives me chills.
Just thinking about it.
It's so awesome.
Yeah.
Um, Sam Jackson in that movie too, one of the only times in his career where
he just played a true bitch, just a bitch.
Yeah.
He's awful in that movie.
I never noticed until this watch at the end of the movie with the big showdown,
Jackson throws his cane down and stands upright and you realize he's been
hustling DiCaprio this whole time.
He's not a feeble man.
He's just, he's getting what he he's like, it's just what an outstanding
performance, man, and he's really funny in it, man.
Yeah.
Like when he's, I think, what's his character's name?
I think I want to say it's Charles.
Uh -huh.
That sounds right.
But the thing where he like gives DiCaprio the tip, DiCaprio is like,
okay, okay.
And then he goes, he goes, Oh, well, thank you very much, Charles.
I appreciate your help on this.
And he's really fucking funny in it, man.
Um, and DiCaprio is like off the reservation in this fucking thing, man.
Like he is just like wild, like wild.
Um, so great movie, great flick.
Uh, I recommend a rewatch.
I might do it.
I've seen it a couple of times.
I love the movie.
Um, I finished squid game, which I'm not going to spoil, but you know,
there's a reason it's a, it's a global phenomenon.
It was like one day I had never heard of squid game.
The next day everyone in my life was talking about it.
And, um, you know, it's awesome.
It's a, it's the first thing in a long time that Netflix has dropped.
That makes it worth getting a subscription to their service.
They've really kind of fallen off and, um, it's very, very good.
It's a Korean show.
It's nine episodes.
It's, uh, I'm sure you've read the memes and everything, but the
guy had been pitching it for 10 years.
Nobody had any interest in it, but he stuck by it.
He knew it was something good.
And it was, it's, I mean, the appeal of the movie or the appeal of
the show is, uh, the challenges.
So in most of the shows, it's basically a hunger games type story where people
who are down in their luck, the guy we're following is a compulsive gambler.
And they are asked, do you want to go and compete in these squid
games for a chance at big money?
And then of course, when they get there, they realize that many of them will die.
Many of them will have to kill each other.
Uh, the challenges are extremely dangerous and extremely creative and
they get better and better as they go.
Uh, culminating an episode six, which everyone is very accurately saying one
of the best episodes of TV, certainly of the year, really intense show.
We'd watch, you know, we banged through it.
We watched three a night and we had to kind of stop ourselves from continuing.
Uh, it's great to have that feeling of something being really addictive again.
And I recommend checking it out.
It's really, really well done.
Great storytelling and great acting, particularly from the old guy, uh, who
you will know when you watch it, you'll love the old guy and, um, check it out.
It's a great show.
Great show.
Very, very well done.
Very well done.
Okay.
And scary, suspenseful.
I, uh, we'll close it out with a rewatch of once upon a time in Hollywood.
Again, hadn't seen it since I saw it in the theater, um, loved it in the theater.
And again, sat down, put it on.
I was like, I'll watch some of this.
Couldn't leave, could not pull myself away from the TV.
And I noticed so much cool shit that I didn't notice on the first watch.
The coolest of which is, you know, there's the parallel in the movie between
DiCaprio's character and Pitt's character.
And the idea that Pitt is the stunt man.
DiCaprio gets all the accolades, all the love, all the money, all the perks.
Pitt gets none of the money, none of the perks, none of the love, none of the
recognition, but is the guy that has to take all the hits and do all the real
deal stuff and blah, blah, blah.
I never noticed it the first time I watched it, but it, that, that juxtaposition
of characters is laid out so beautifully when they show DiCaprio shooting the
scene with the little girl in the TV show he's doing, and that's cross cut
with Pitt driving the hitchhiker girl back to the ranch that, that, you know,
the Manson ranch and Pitt, the ranch they're using is an old movie set.
And Pitt talks about that.
Like I used to do work up here.
And when he walks to the house to see, to, to see if Bruce Dern and see what's
going on, you know, she knows something's up.
He's walking literally through the set of a Western town.
Yeah.
So he literally becomes the real version of what DiCaprio was playing on TV.
He really is the savior and he it's fucking awesome, man.
And it's something you're just like, holy shit, dude.
And then it's Tantino.
It didn't even occur to me watching it.
That's a great point.
And it's shot.
And then when you realize that it's shot exactly like a Western, like it's
like the camera follows the profile of Pitt as he's walking through the town.
Right.
It's just fucking brilliant, man.
And it's so awesome when he beats the shit out of that kid.
It is being like such a shit.
And then the end, the whole end is so wild.
Like it's just an awesome movie.
It's one of his best.
I, he's talking now about maybe doing kill bill three.
He keeps saying this is going to be his last movie, but now he's
kind of going back on it.
Then he said he wants to do a Western comedy or something like that.
I don't know what he's going to do, but I'm excited to see it.
Of course.
Well, he is doing apparently for Netflix.
He's doing bounty law, the series and DiCaprio is going to start it.
And they're going to actually make the show like that.
He starts in the movie.
But yeah, he keeps kicking around a lot of ideas for this last movie.
He said, maybe kill bill three.
He said at one point he thought about remaking reservoir dogs.
Yeah.
Which I thought would be kind of interesting and cool.
You know, I'd imagine, you know, he seems like a guy that
doesn't succumb to pressure, but I would imagine a little bit of the pressures on.
It's like, dude, this is number 10.
Right.
You've hit a home run with every single movie you've made, except
maybe death proof, which is still a valiant effort.
Love death proof.
I liked aspects of it.
I hate the fact that it takes place in present day because it looks so grainy
in 1970s and then you see girls on their cell phones and it ruins.
I'm like, what are you doing, dude?
Why would you do that?
Okay.
It's weird to me that he did that.
I feel like that's beyond his, like that's something he would never allow.
You know, um, it just made no sense.
But anyway, that's the lowest rated of his films.
That's considered the worst of his films.
It's still, I think, fresh on Rotten Tomatoes.
So, you know, again, nobody ever talks about that Rodriguez
zombie movie anymore.
I maybe should watch that again.
I loved that when I saw it, I thought it was pretty cool.
Kind of a John Carpenter homage.
Yeah.
Wasn't Brolin in that Brolin play?
Like that was like the big Brolin comeback.
Doesn't he play like a creepy doctor or something where he's
like smoking all the time?
Yeah.
Anyway, let's get to our movie at hand.
Oh, let's do it real quick.
Shout outs to Matt McCarthy.
He sent me this in the mail, but all right.
He sent me this in the mail.
Uh, I haven't called him yet to thank him because I wanted to
talk about it first on the show.
I was hoping he'd hear this and then hear the thank you that way.
But now I'm like, yeah, got here a few days ago.
I should probably text him.
Um, anyway, he sent me this book.
Uh, Rex reads from Travolta to Keaton asterisks, Diane, not Buster.
From Travolta to Keaton.
They were stars at the same time.
I don't, it's not an A to Z thing either.
I know it's just him.
Like it's him, you know, little interviews or write ups on the
who's who's of a Hollywood at the time.
Like it's kind of like each chapter is a different actor.
And he like goes to the set where they're working and, you know, he, he's,
he's writing a sort of narrative of what's happening, but then also he's
working in, you know, like quotes and he's sort of interviewing the people too.
So it's not him shitting on people.
No, I'm very unfortunate that it's not a bad, it's, but you know, he's, he's
still caddy chapter six, Richard gear.
Okay.
First sentence, Richard gear period.
If the name doesn't exactly stop the doorman at Sardis in his tracks, just wait.
The doorman at Sardis is a lot to learn.
Wow.
Still, it's still Rex.
At what period could Richard gear not get a table at Sardis, even if he wasn't
famous, he was always a male model.
This book is from, uh, let's see.
1979.
Yeah.
So around 1979, I guess.
You know, speaking of, and I know I'm not, uh, at Richard gear's level, but
I've always been able to get a booth at Yoshinoya beef bowl, no matter what time
of day or night, you know, so we've all got our fame that we have to deal with.
Uh, we are talking to folks today about dune.
And for some reason, I'm glad my wife's out of town this weekend because I can't
stop saying dune like that character in, uh, dark crystal.
I keep going and I, I hate it.
I am annoying myself.
What character is that?
Oh, the, the, the, uh, Chamberlain.
Yeah.
When it goes, yes, for some reason, I don't know.
I hate it.
But I watched and, and this is coming from somebody who hates dune.
I never read the book, but, um, I saw the Lynch one when I was a kid.
I was so deeply disturbed by it that I never revisited it.
I saw the new one in IMAX and very high.
And then I realized that I needed to watch it again, sober so that I could
discuss it because I didn't really know what had happened in it.
And then, so I watched it again on HBO max.
And then I watched the Lynch one again.
So I've got a lot of dune to talk about.
I feel like through those viewings, I now finally kind of get the plot of dune.
Um, Joe, could you sort of walk us through the gist, the spice?
I'd love to, but I didn't watch it high.
Yeah.
And I don't know what the fuck is going on.
I had a hard time.
I thought it was sober.
Didn't help that much.
I think just seeing it a second time helps some things kind of settle in.
I thought, I mean, a second watch.
I mean, holy shit.
Yeah.
I'll say this much.
I thought the confusing aspects of the story were the fault of David Lynch
because I've seen the Lynch version numerous times and couldn't, couldn't to
this day tell you what the fuck is happening in it.
Uh -huh.
And he wrote it, which is nuts.
Like, yeah, it's just not his thing.
So then this one, when it starts, I'm like, okay, they're doing a much better job.
I get it.
There's spice on this planet.
The spice is used as a physical enhancer by some people and used as for
interstellar space travel by others.
Yeah.
Um, it's the most valuable commodity in the galaxy and the house of a tradies
led by, you know, led by a guy.
I wish just was in more stuff.
Oscar Isaac, um, has to go to the planet Arrakis dune.
That's also called dune to manage the spice manufacturing or the
mining, uh, on Arrakis quick pause there.
You know, what I'll never understand is in these books, when they go, you're,
you're trying to remember 5 million things and follow this very complicated
plot and they'll go Arrakis also known as dune or something, you're like, no,
just call it one thing you're in control.
Why are you making me remember two things or a guy's got a nickname
or in a book or something?
I'm like, I got to remember 800 characters and you're calling
him two different things.
Yeah, no, it's too much.
Uh, it's so, so yeah, so they have to go to Arrakis to mine the spice, not the
dune, they have to mine the spice and then, and I don't know what the fuck
is going on from there.
I would say the kids having dreams, by the way, is it Timothy or is it Timothée?
How the fuck do you say this kid's name?
I've heard Timothée Chalamet and I will never say Timothée.
I know that much.
It's like Imhotep.
I remember that.
Sorry.
I was not yet quick joke joke.
Yeah.
Uh, and I was just going to say a very funny moment on the, on the Willie, I
think it was the William Shatner roast.
Jessel neck was on it and Patrice goes, Anthony fucking, I refused to learn his
name and he goes, Gallifonekis was the last goofy white name.
I'm going to learn in this funky town.
That's funny.
Anyway, it's like that though.
Is there, it's like, I just, yes.
Timothy Timothée, I'm going with Timothy.
He's, I mean, he's a nothing, but then you watch the Lynch dune and it's like
Kyle McLaughlin was nothing in this too.
Um, I don't get Chalamet at all.
I, I particularly don't get grown women thinking he's hot.
Like he's shirtless throughout this movie and he looks like you go home and
your little brother's there, you know, like, like waking up at 1 p .m.
Humbling out, rubbing his eyes.
He looks like a child.
Yeah.
He looks like a little boy.
He's got the poutiest eyes I've ever seen.
Yeah.
Um, he's, he's got a, as, as Colin Joe's titled his book, Timothy's
got a very punchable face.
He doesn't see, maybe not Joe's punchable, but he's got a punchable face.
Um, but I mean, it's just, yeah.
So he's, I don't fucking know, man.
He's like the, the chosen one.
We had to go over a bit.
I mean, he's, he's sort of a Christ figure, you know, it's basically, is this
the plot of both dunes is kind of, is this guy, uh, the one it's also the
matrix and everything.
I mean, the matrix has a lot in common with dune really that I just thought of
right now, it's like, is this guy the one or isn't he?
And then in the end you find out he is.
But, um, he, in the movie, he's on this, this journey in the new movie.
He's on this journey with his mother who was played by an actress who is
not that much older than him.
I think it's like 38 and 24 or something.
Rebecca, she played Mary the hat in Dr.
Sleep, Rebecca Ferguson.
Yes.
Uh, and there's, there's some weirdness between them too.
The mom is kind of not in Lynch's dune that much, but in this, they have a
weird sort of chemistry and at one point with like 10 minutes to go in the movie,
they kind of check each other out while they're changing.
Did you notice that moment?
No, it's, it's in there.
I mean, in the theater, I heard lots of whispering after it.
And if I would have whispered myself, had I not been alone in stone, there's
10 minutes left in the movie and they both have to change into these suits.
So just cuts to you at an empty theater.
There's nothing, the movie's not even showing.
You're just, yeah, still talking to someone who's not there.
That there's, they're bringing in the theater for the next show.
Sorry.
When did dune let out dune?
There's no movie called dune playing here.
Yeah.
How are you talking about this is a chipotle.
So, uh, yeah, there's a scene at the end where the, they're changing into the
suits and they turn their backs to each other and Chalamet takes off his shirt
and his mom turns and looks at his back, his naked back while he's changing and
kind of holds it for a minute and then turns away, then Chalamet turns to look
while she's changing and then looks forward again.
And it's like, why would you ever include that moment unless you were trying to
bring up some sort of weird incest?
So maybe, maybe that, maybe that I never read the book.
Maybe there is an incest subplot.
Maybe it comes out later.
Maybe there is, you think you would have heard about it by now, but, but I don't
know the, um, but basically that's, that's what's going on.
And in addition, there's a character named Duncan Idaho played by Jason
Momoa, who's kind of the, uh, the bounty hunter or the Boba Fett of this world.
I guess you might say the name,
few movie names have pissed me off more than Duncan Idaho.
You're living in your own Duncan Idaho.
But, but let me just interject really quick because you bring up Momoa.
Yeah.
This is my first problem with the movie.
I was completely taken out of it by the cast.
Isaac, Brolin, Momoa.
It's like a Bautista.
I'm like, Jesus Christ, guys.
Did you, what did you shake the fucking comic book tree?
And these guys just all fell out and you put them in the, it's
like, I just can't see past there in so much shit.
You can't see past them anymore.
I know.
And it's really like, when you watch all these acts, because you've got everybody,
you got everybody from the, the way fee, uh, you know, frail chameleon on the,
all the way up to like beefy muscle Bautista, but all of them really leave no
impact and that I think is kind of the state of movie actors today.
There are good actors, Oscar Isaac, of course, has been good in things.
Brolin of course has been good in things, but they, they're just not exciting.
I don't know what to say.
Like any time any one of these guys came up on the screen, I felt nothing there.
They, everyone in all these types of movies, every science fiction movie now,
everyone is told, I guess, to speak in these monotone voices that almost seems
to be designed to put you to sleep.
The color palette of this movie is sand and dust.
It's so boring to look at, man.
It's brown, brown to gray is all you're looking at for three hours.
No colors, no.
The ships look cool.
Some of the like, you know, um, structures and things look really cool.
Yeah.
But God almighty, it is so bland.
And then you go and watch that Jodorowsky's documentary, which not to
name drops the other night, I get a text.
Uh -huh.
It just says Jodorowsky's dune.
And I go, who is this?
And she goes, it's Chelsea Peretti.
Jordan just told me there's a movie called Jodorowsky's dune.
And I keep saying Jodorowsky's dune.
It was one of the craziest texts.
I'm not making fun of her.
I'm just saying it was a crazy, I didn't know you even knew her.
We haven't talked in years.
It was out of the blue.
Just, it's, it's a funny sketch idea.
You could put that on, on your YouTube.
Anyway, you know, Pete, Pat, Pat, I'm connected to these people.
You know, I know, I know.
Um, anyway, the, uh, but no, but you go and watch that documentary and you're
just like, look at the colors and it's fascinating and it's so beautiful.
And this just looks like one of the mill, every fucking, you know, man in the high
castle, um, raised by wolves.
Um, uh, you know, I'm, I'm drawing blanks on sci -fi shows that are out right now,
but I mean, it looks like any sci -fi show you'd ever see cut from a color palette
standpoint.
Yeah.
Uh, the ships are kind of cool.
Um, well, the one term I keep seeing with regards to this movie and I, the
first time I heard it was from a network executive, uh, which was like it's
world building and I was like, what are you talking about?
Well, you know, like we really like to build a world, you know, with our shows
and world building, whatever.
So now I see that in every review, it must've gotten into writer Twitter or
something.
Everyone's talking about how great the world building is in it.
Um, and that is great.
That's the one aspect of it that that's great.
You definitely it's immersive, you know, uh, especially in IMAX, you feel like
you're sort of in the desert.
Uh, but I just don't even Lynch knew at least like when you're indoors, like
that the Baron is in this green room that looks almost like the Emerald
city or something.
It's like, you have to differentiate somewhat.
Um, by the way, who the hell was the Baron?
I still don't understand what his role is in all of this.
He's a fat guy that wants the spice.
That's it.
What's his authority?
I I've already read several articles talking about how fat phobic the new
dune movie is.
And when I rewatch it, there's one scene where he eats one scene.
That's what's fat phobic about.
Lynch has got creamed.
Um, Lynch was anti -gay and anti -aids is what they called on that one.
That's what they said.
I didn't think that of it, but that's what they said.
I think Lynch's they're saying that the new Baron is tent.
This is what I keep saying about the movie.
Yeah.
It's a better story wise movie than Lynch's dune.
Yes.
Lynch's dune is a thousand more times fun to watch.
It's a goofy, it's crazy.
The aliens are disturbing looking.
The Baron is like wild in that he's flying all over the room.
He's got puss coming out of his face.
Like the Baron is amazing.
And that stuff, I don't know if that was in the book, um, like Villeneuve was,
he's talked about how much he loves David Lynch, of course, but he was also
like, every time David went away from the book, I felt he was making a mistake.
So I'm sticking to the book.
So something tells me the scene where like a guy crushes a little bird or bug
and then drinks it.
And then the guy who's draining the puss from the Baron's thing and also
kind of hitting on him.
Then there's the scene that's one of the more disturbing in David Lynch's
oeuvre, which is saying something is the Baron's like flying around the room,
which has done way cooler, I think in Lynch's dune.
And then this like kind of twink young boy comes into the room to adjust some
flowers and stuff and the Baron like soars at him, flies at him, yanks this
plug out from his chest and then what appears to be violently fingers the wound
in his chest and like smears the blood on the kid's face.
Very, very dark.
Very, very weird.
I think that's in the, I think his penchant for young men is in the book.
Okay.
Yeah.
He's a leave.
He's alluded to be a pedophile in, in Lynch's.
He's not that at all in the new one.
No, he's just, he's just like a bad guy in the new one.
Right.
That's it.
He's just like, they even have the Baron and Lynch's dune, like looking at
Sting and in his briefs and being like, Oh yes, yes.
Now Sting, by the way, is the Bautista role in this one.
Right.
I believe that's very strange.
Yeah.
Strange types of casting for them.
Uh, I completely agree.
The Lynch dune is a little over two hours.
It tells apparently the whole book in a little over two hours.
Villanoves tells the first half of the book in almost three hours.
So obviously it's going to be a lot more clear, but, um, yeah, I mean,
I actually love Villanoves.
I just don't like this direction.
He's going in.
I don't like him making bigger and bigger movies.
Blade Runner 2049 and this one and so forth.
His best movie is prisoners and I love Sicario.
He's a guy who is kind of a master of those kind of awesome thrillers, but
every director now has their eyes on the prize.
They all want the biggest, biggest, most expensive movies.
I will say, um, he's saying the second one is going to be more of an action
packed base fun movie or whatever, but I will say this.
I, I, I, it's strange and I don't know if this is something I would be critical
about, let's say pre pandemic, but after all everybody has been through in the
loss and the closings and the, the, the, the stress and the poverty and all, you
know, after all of that being so amplified and, um, and, and upped over the last two
years because of COVID and everything else to watch something like this.
It's I found it almost offensive.
You're watching these sets.
You're watching these people walk out.
You're like, you know, then you watch the interviews and the actors are like,
this is unlike anything you've ever seen.
It's like, it just looks like a lot of fucking indulgence to me.
It doesn't look like a passion project.
It doesn't, it's not really unlike anything I've ever seen.
It looks like a Terminator Genesis or any of those movies that
look like the same throughout.
And I'll say this about Lynch's.
Lynch's is cast in a way where I see Lynch's passion for the actors.
There's a visual aspect to it where I see Lynch's passion for visuals on the
screen, there's a, there's his own storytelling approach to it, which I
know is coming from his own place of passion, whether you like it or not,
whatever.
And this now feels to me like the big studio came along and made the big
perfect movie and, and we, the casting was paint by numbers and, and it's
just really fucking boring and overdone.
And honestly, weirdly, I find it weirdly offensive.
And it's kind of like with the criticism.
It also, I realized clearly George Lucas pulled a lot of Star Wars from this.
Yeah, but God damn it.
Star Wars is just so much more fun.
Well, yeah, it's like, if, if you're going to put $200 million or whatever
into something, you'd think you'd want it to be fun.
Yeah.
I mean, that that's the movies that aren't fun.
You can make for $1 million, you know, like there's no reason for this to, to
put all this in service of everybody sitting there, like kind of bored for
even the fans of Dune are like, look, I admit it's slow, it's boring, even it's
And there's a, there's a place for that, I guess, but it's, yeah, right now, the,
the amount of money just being thrown at another, they're going to make the
sequel and because they didn't have faith in it from the jump, they're going
to have to rebuild the sets, re get the cast, everything else wild.
Yeah.
It's just kind of boring.
Um, it's not bad.
It's just boring.
I just don't care.
That's the best I could say about it.
Um, I agree on a second viewing.
I appreciated it more, uh, which is odd because the first one I saw in
IMAX, but it's a Lynch was movie too.
It's not a great movie at all to its great credit.
It, it has a pulse.
It's creative.
It feels alive moment to moment.
The new Dune does not the, I watched the documentary.
I got the new arrow, uh, Lynch Dune, which must not be selling well because
it's pretty cheap right now.
I almost bought it.
Is it worth grabbing?
It is.
I mean, I watched this half hour documentary on it and you know, it was great.
It was really kind of fascinating.
And they talk about how much, well, every, everyone at the time really hated it.
They also gave out a giant glossary of terms at the box office.
So when you go into Dune, they would give you this thing, which was
covered in like small print to tell you what everything means in the
universe.
And, um, this guy drew Mcweeney, who's a, uh, well -known movie critic.
Mcweeney.
That's what I just wanted to name McQueen.
He was, uh, he was with Scott Weinberg.
He did the eighties all over podcast, which I was obsessed with.
And it unfortunately ended too soon, but, um, he talked on that show.
I listened to their review of Dune from 84.
They go through, I think I told you, they go through each movie that came
out in each year of the eighties.
And he talks about how everyone who went up to the ticket booth, when they'd
hand them that glossary of terms, they'd go, uh, I don't think I want to see this.
And it just didn't make any money really, because they were like now, like, and
it came out at Christmas time, which is very bizarre too.
Um, Lynch, I, there's a great story in the, uh, in the book that comes with
the new Dune Blu -ray where Lynch is at a college talk or something.
And this guy stands up and he says, I just wanted to tell you like Dune,
your version of Dune is exactly how I saw it.
It is my favorite film of all time.
It's a film I returned to again and again.
And David Lynch goes, I hate Dune.
I wish I'd never made it.
And I think he's really, he's pissed that it took up three years of his life.
And he always like, that was his pre blue.
It was his elephant man between alpha man and blue velvet.
And you can tell he's just so pissed that like it took up those really fruitful
creative years of his life and he hates it and he never returned to big
budget movies again, he directed Dune because, uh, Lucas had offered
him return of the Jedi.
Jesus Christ.
Lucas offered David Lynch return of the Jedi and he didn't do it and,
and kind of regretted it.
And it's that moment where he's like, am I going to be an artist or a big filmmaker?
Lynch is one of the few people who chose artists.
Now everybody chooses big action film.
But, um, yeah, he, they, they, basically he got Dune because everyone knew he
turned down Jedi and he was like, for whatever reason, considered this big
hot science fiction director, Harlan Ellison, the very famous sci -fi writer.
Uh, absolutely loves Lynch's Dune says it's a perfect adaptation.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Huh.
All right.
Well, it's, it's better than the new one.
Although, you know, you're not going to tell some 18 year old kid today that
that's better than the new one because there that's what this is what they're
used to, like men who are 45 grimly staring at each other, saying three
words at a time in monotone voices against silver backgrounds that look
exactly the same in every scene.
And to me, it was a real drag and yet I get the accomplishment of it.
You know, I, you see the money on the screen, I guess, but to Joe's point,
I say, to what extent I didn't have any fun watching it.
Hog, I guess is down on this one.
My hog's down and my hog is, uh, is starting to plump on the Lynch movie.
I liked it a lot more this time.
I got about a half chub on, on the Lynch Dune, but I think there's great stuff.
And I love the Baron in it.
I mean, I love a great villain.
I mean, what's interesting is they took it as this big anti -gay thing because
it came out right after the AIDS epidemic, uh, and he's covered in boils
and pus and he's a homosexual pedophile, whatever, but, um, I certainly
didn't make that connection.
It was, I didn't realize how controversial it was at the time.
Um, yeah, but I also thought that the language in, in Lynch's worked better.
Yeah.
They spoke regally and you know, like there's moments in this new one
where they speak regally and then there's moments where like Timothy, you'll
be like, ma, I just woke up and you're like, that sounds way too contemporary.
Yeah.
You should always say mother.
That's it.
This is a big futuristic royalty bullshit thing.
You know, it's like mom.
It's yeah, they're doing the thing in the Lynch one where everybody talks
with a slight British accent, which is what they used to do in all science
fiction movies, all war movies.
I think it needs to go back to that.
It made sense.
Uh, Javier Bardem, we didn't even mention is in this movie.
Like nobody really pops.
I did think scars guard was good as the Baron, but I prefer the more over
the top one.
I gotta be honest.
All right, folks, next episode, Halloween kills.
Oh boy.
I can't wait to get into this one.
Halloween kills up next, uh, the patch wash Twitter and Instagram.
Why don't we even say that anymore?
Everyone knows where you guys know.
It's, um, Joey roses is opening this month.
Um, so just please follow us at Joey roses, heart eight on Instagram.
Uh, so you can get the updates, but it's it's we're, we're in the final weeks here.
So it's opening, uh, we'll see you next time and we'll see and how.