I'm here for Betrivers Online Casino and Sportsbook with poker icon Phil Helmuth.
And now thanks to the excitement of Betrivers, I'm also a slots icon.
That's great! And a same -game Parley icon.
Cool, cool. A Blackjack icon, a Moneyline icon.
A roulette. Take it from Phil Helmuth.
If you love games, Betrivers is the place to play in Betrivers.
Games on.
Must be 21 plus in present at West Virginia.
Void were prohibited. Terms in conditions apply.
Gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gambling.
This episode is brought to you by US Cellular.
With a variety of options, US Cellular prepaid makes finding the right wireless plan for
you easy.
That means you can get what you need at a price you can afford all while staying connected,
like two lines of unlimited data for just $60 a month and a free device like the Samsung
Galaxy A16 5G.
U .S. Cellular Prepaid, Terms Apply, See U .S. Cellular .com for details.
Oh, geez. Welcome to the show, everybody.
Let me just get up in my chair.
We're both sitting like dads tonight.
We both sat down like, I don't know why.
I don't feel very well.
I feel like shitty and kind of achy and not get coughed
through the whole movie.
Well, my sinuses have been bothering me.
Sorry to hear that.
Maybe I got a damn bug, you know?
Did I cough a lot?
What? It wasn't distracting. I just noticed you worked. Yes, coughing a lot, folks, right
up front, the question on everybody's lips. We're doing Star Wars colon, the last Jedi.
And there will be spoilers. And this is a movie where I know that people definitely don't
want spoilers. So don't listen to this until you've seen Star Wars, the last Jedi. Hopefully
Hopefully you guys got tickets and we'll see you this weekend if not just be patient, just be patient.
Or listen up till the time we start discussing the movie and we'll say,
Hey, we're going to start talking about the movie.
Yeah, you know, but a little discipline wouldn't kill you.
No, no.
And everybody, I really have been loving the Facebook formally.
I get on there at night. It's a good way to go to bed happy.
Everybody takes care of each other that it's discussed which episodes have spoilers, which don't.
I always ask for them, but I want even more of the transcriptions.
I love reading them. They're hilarious.
And somebody who cited his top five favorite moments the other day,
and I remembered one of the five, which was very troubling because it's just you and me talking.
But we've done a lot of hours of this material.
What were the top five moments?
Well, let's see if you remember any better than I do.
I'll bring them up. But yeah, because I'm pulling up right now,
Now, pulling up our Patreon list on Patreon,
because we got to do shout outs this week.
I know we're a little out of order.
We might have done them two weeks in a row or something,
but we're all ready to kind of back record.
We're going out of town, so there might be a little out of order.
Yeah, in fact, this is the last thing we record
before I leave, even though it's not the last episode by far.
Joe is joining the Navy, which I think is great.
And I support fully. I think we all know comedy wasn't quite working out. Right. Um, but I wish you the best and
You know, semper fly as they say. I don't know what that means
It's a it means you'd be so you know what I found it. It means blow it out your ass at me really. Yeah
Yeah, I can't believe that's not I was shocked not a great message for our own forces to be sending but
but the guy, I'm sure this isn't his name,
but it says Mick Mack.
And it's not his favorite, but he said,
here are some of the podcast moments,
I referenced daily that nobody gets,
which then makes me cackle with laughter.
This one I remember, he's my Rob Thomas,
of the Rob Thomas interview that you cited.
Yeah, I remember that.
Then, are you boys in the band?
Are you a good band?
No recollection of that.
No idea.
you. Uh, shut your dirty mouth, you pig person. I assume was said to me at at least one point.
Get me Michael learner. I vaguely recall, uh, I sang myself at one point, give me Michael
learn. No cups in my room, astounding, not a one. Oh, I think that might have been the girl
who knocked over the cup in my bedroom on my laptop. I think I don't know what else that would be.
But why would but then there was a cup in my room? Maybe I was saying I've never
had cups in my room the one time I had a cup in my room she knocked it over. Oh, okay.
It's kind of we're essentially like memento except we don't have amnesia. We're just
slowly decaying within our brains. This one says make it dangerous. Give me a hot broth
and I laugh but I have no idea what that means. That sounds like that sounds like something you
would say. That sounds like something I would say. I guess we were discussing soups. Yeah.
Uh, and then can you put it on a tapestry? Again, that sounds like something you would say. Yeah.
Now, my one, I definitely remembered in the comments here that I really made me laugh because I,
this was very recent. Me and my flower calendar are going to Atlantic City. Remember you were talking
about that flower calendar and they were like, don't, don't take the freebie and run. Oh, the, uh,
That was a very funny thing from like yeah, the children's shared yeah, yeah, see
I actually quality control listen to each episode before I post Joe's never listened to one of these so you know
I understand why you don't remember I'm couldn't tell you couldn't tell you what's this show about
I'm coughing again. Um, you're gonna be in a cough and folks
Let's get on with the show and in doing so get on with the
way right that was really good and I didn't even think about that you didn't know see I think
that's it's it's like anything when you don't think when you just go with it yeah as Jennifer
Aniston once did in a film yeah uh terrible terrible film I didn't see it in fact I lost I was on
Doug loves movies the other night I and I lost on Reese with it with it was we had to guess Reese
witherspoon movies. I got, we got way down the list, man. I wasn't like the bottom. Is she
in just go with it? I thought she was. That's what I lost on it. I had to use Jack the bear
real early because I was fucking blank in man. I was blanking on her movie. There's good. Yeah,
and I had to pull out that deep cut way early. Did you meet my buddy, Demi? Yes. Demi's a nice guy.
He's a nice guy. He's a brilliant joke writer and the best the best follow on Twitter in my
face. He's very good. Electro lemon is his name on Twitter and he used to be the best guy on
Vine. And he's on Gilmore or was he was one of the Gilmore guys who helped me hostage for four
hours that faithful night. Does he write on your show? He doesn't. I met him through Vine and I just
think he's a hilarious writer and he's like 22, which is very annoying. Oh, that's right. I remember
you introducing me to him at the Christmas party, the Virgil one year. Yeah, he's been
to a couple parties in my house and such. Yeah. Um, nice kid. Oh, yeah, that's right. He
wasn't your house. Yeah. Yeah. He's very funny. Um, folks, we're going to be discussing
the last Jedi and I think we're probably going to have a lot to say. So why be it around
the bush? And there will be spoilers. Let's get to Pat's movie corner. I mean, you want to
Run right in you're not worried that I might be sick and dying over here not in the slightest. No all right fair enough
Give it to me give me the corner holy shit what
It's a matter
What's the matter, Pat?
Oh, no, nothing.
Okay.
What happened?
It's got a briefly troubling email
that is not not troubling.
All right.
But maybe you had an amber alert on your phone.
No.
That had your name in it.
Pat Walsh is kidnapped a kid.
So we're still agreeing we're going to do a shape of water
in the future.
You plan on seeing that?
I do plan on seeing it.
All right.
I'll save that.
Frankly, I'm peeved.
You've seen it already.
Yeah.
Yeah, I gotta go on much to say about that movie
Here's what I saw folks. I saw I Tonya
Still watch every screener. He's still haven't got the screener as well. These are all Oscar screeners
I hear it's phenomenal some deserving some not I Tonya folks is one of my favorites of the year
That's the story of Tonya Harding
Margot Robbie Robbie is
Doesn't fall the cons gonna push that off the thing and it's gonna break kind stop
Margot Robbie is awesome as Tonya Harding, Sebastian, something as great as Jeff Galooly.
Sebastian Bach from Skid Row.
It's Sebastian Bach.
Okay.
Actually, it was Sebastian, the crab from the Little Mermaid.
I haven't seen it in a picture since L .M., Sebastian Bach shows up frequently in the trailer
park boys.
Really?
And it is delightful every time.
But I always love him.
He's very funny.
There's an episode where they're in Europe and like from off camera you hear what the fuck in the camera
Pads over at Sebastian Bach on a boat in the Lake Canal thing. Okay, it's he's very funny in it
Yeah, he was always funny on you know those like VH1
Clip shows. Yeah, it was as funny as the comedians. Yeah, in some cases funny or fun
Anyway, everybody's great in Itanya.
Weirdly, it is a good fellas rip off to some degree,
but a lot of movies post good fellas are,
but a lot of freeze frame with her voice over.
That's exactly right.
It's very influenced.
The soundtrack is wall -to -wall, 80s hits.
All right.
The only time it started to kind of bug me was,
I didn't realize you'll realize as soon
you start watching this movie,
that tiny hearting was constantly being savagely beaten by Jeff Galilee.
Oh, I didn't know that.
So I had seen her 30 by 30 for 30 and it touched on the darkness, but didn't go this deep.
So they show that in this?
Yeah, but it's so this is not a flat out comedy then.
It's the only way to describe it as a the very dark comedy, but it is it always goes for jokes.
and apparently to avoid lawsuits,
they went between Tonya Harding's retelling
and Galulie's retelling and they switch points of view.
I came away believing only Tonya Harding.
So it's almost like the deep throat movie.
That's right, yeah.
Inside deep throat.
Well, that was the documentary,
but then they made the movie about.
Oh, it's loveless.
Loveless, yeah.
Where it was too perspective.
Yeah.
What I found a little troubling and I would imagine people might have an issue with this as well is like gluelial
We'll smash tiny heartings face into a mirror. Let's say and this and but there's jokes around the mirrors
That's what I'm saying. That's what I'm saying is troubling
So I'll bash her head into the mirror and then like while her head is bashed in the mirror
She looks in the camera and then not narration her head, which is now being bashed in the mirror is like so then this started happening again
Well, so they're breaking the fourth wall even they're breaking the fourth they're doing like you know
But they save that to the last 20 minutes a good fellows when Leota comes off the stand and arguably the most exciting moment in movie history
It's not even 20 minutes. You're talking the last 90 seconds. Yeah, it's near the end
That's right to the him in the suburbs after that. Yeah
This this does it a lot. There's a lot of fourth wall breaking and there's a lot of
a documentary interview footage with recreated by these people and it's supposed to be real close.
Who plays Karrigan in it?
Karrigan has one line which is like why basically holding her knee.
This shit, my mom was super into figure skating and I was real into this for some reason
the story.
I know.
I remember a lot of shit about it.
Me too.
But uh, the two best performances in the movie are the fact guy who actually or the guy who thinks that he's like a masked criminal mastermind, the guy who orchestrated the hit on Carrigan, Sean, whatever, Eckhart, who is now dead.
Um, this, the guy, I don't know if this guy is just dumb and doing it or if he's the best at playing dumb, I've ever seen.
Okay, but he is like hilariously funny for the entire movie until he gets of course very sad
But the best performance in the movie and maybe of the year is Miss Allison Janney as Tonya Harding's mom
the
perhaps the worst mom
I've ever seen in a movie a horrible horrible mother all right, uh, and
Also, Jenny is real real funny in this movie and also terrible. She's also she's always very funny. I love her
She's one of the best acts as there is
All right, well check out the screener. I have it. I just haven't watched it yet
It's a good it's a good picture and it's a way funnier comedy than most movies that are trying to be straight -up comedy sure
Well, yeah, the I I saw
The trip to Spain the third installment in the trip series can't wait to watch it this weekend
love the other two. Walk me through it. I loved it. I won't say much. It's part for the course,
you know, it's a trip movie. They don't deviate that much. They do add a new layer of something,
which is nice. They add these sort of surreal dream sequences that Steve Cougan is having that help
break up the monotony of what you've already seen in the other two films. And also add a very funny,
but also a very sinister layer to it.
It's great. I liked it better than the trip to Italy.
I felt that they were rehashing less jokes.
Sure.
Trip to Italy, they were sort of doing the Austin Powers thing
where they were like returning to bits.
Right.
They didn't do that in this one.
I don't think they even do Michael Cain in this one.
Wow.
But it's loaded with impressions.
The centerpiece impression in this film
is a dueling Mick Jagger that they do throughout the movie.
And I was crying from it.
It was, it was, all right.
Cause, cause, cause, uh, Rob, um, what's his face?
Rob, uh, bride and, does like a more traditional Mick Jagger
and then Cougan's is all like 1980s, sure, satisfaction.
And he's clapping and everything.
It's, it's really fucking funny, man.
Mike Myers used to do a great Mick Jagger.
It's Cougan's is very Mick Jett.
It sounds like it was clapping, it sounds like.
Yeah, it's absurd.
It's really, really funny.
Why do you think that it was so shat on?
Like the first two trips got these amazing reviews
and then the third one was like, I saw like, D's.
I mean, because it's the same movie again.
There's no juice left in the tank.
I mean, it's three movies of the same movie,
but I like all of them and I think that this one,
in my opinion was more entertaining than the second one.
I think those two guys are just so delightful.
I didn't like in the second one
that Rob Briden cheated on his wife.
I didn't believe it.
And I thought it took that character to a place.
I didn't want that character to go to.
Yeah, I gotcha.
And this one is a little more in consistency
with the first film where Cougan is the guy
that's a little more hungry for fame and whatever
and Briden is back to being like a family man again.
Yeah, yeah, I like when Cougan plays like the Narcissistic
Yeah, there's well there's a really funny line where he talks about they talk about performing for like
The queen or something I can't some somebody you know somebody along those lines and
Like Cougan's kind of going on about what he would do and Rob Braden goes you would do Alan Partridge
That's what you'd do and he goes you'd walk out on that stage and you know what I'd love
If a sniper just took you out right as you said, aha, I was like, that's such that's such a thing comedians would say to each other
Then they act out him dying for a while. It's very funny. I enjoyed the film. I can't wait to watch it. It
You know all three of those movies come from like
Three -hour versions like six -half -hour parts
that they edit down to the best stuff and I would love to see the whole thing because I always want those to be longer
Well, the first one was aired as a TV show. I don't know if they aired the second to his TV shows or not
But I don't know anyway pet. I'm gonna I'm gonna do a few quick hits here because I saw some real turds
Film stars die in Liverpool
What this was a screener sent to me or not actually this might have been my buddies in the actors guild. It's a netbending
and Jamie Bell, who played Billy Elliot.
And here is the movie, and Ed Benning plays Gloria Graham, a very minor actress from the
30s, 40s, 50s.
She played the town skank, and it's a wonderful life, who's always like, George Bailey,
I want to come up and go down on it.
And that's how she's building the credits, the town skank, play by -
Anyway, I don't remember they're being a townscank,
but no, she is just not remembering.
Is Mary, Mary is a wife.
She's the main like, and Stuart's clearly like horny
for her, but she briefly threatens the two of them
getting together.
Anyway, the movie is this.
Gloria Graham is now washed up.
She's an at -bending who is still beautiful, of course.
But, you know, she's in her 50s and living in an apartment
and she runs into Jamie Bell,
the young handsome British guy,
and they fall in love.
And then for the entire movie, she slowly dies.
I don't know how many movies they have made
where somebody slowly dies.
They are only made to get somebody an Oscar nomination.
Right.
Who wants to watch this?
She died at one point.
Like the sex is getting kind of hot and heavy.
And you're like, okay.
And he pulls her shirt down.
And for the first time that I can recall,
you see a netbending's tit.
And I'm like, boy, I don't think I've ever seen a Nutbending's tit and as he moves his hand down it
We see there's a giant breast cancer scar on it. Oh my God. I'm like, you know what? Why am I watching this and that
Bending was good in it. It's a very boring movie. It's a character scar. It's not an atbending scar. Exactly. Yeah. Well, I would hope Jesus and then she you know
She becomes like assimilated into this guy's family. They judge him for having like a 35 year old year older
girl friend, but then bit by bit she becomes a part of the family. It's just like who gives a shit?
Who wanted a glam book and if you're gonna give me one of these young guy
Falls in love with an older woman thing and she's an angel. She's an old angel. I wanted to be like a boozy old Joan Crawford
That's exactly right throwing glasses at his head. You don't fucking respect me. Well, there's some of that. There's some of that
Yeah, that's all I want. There's a lot of like she's like I want to play Juliet in Romeo and Juliet
And he's like, but you're old and then she, you know, there is some drink throwing, but
it's not fun like the few that Betty Davis and Joan Crawford, she's not fun at all.
Okay.
Um, Marjorie Prime, I'll be real brief with.
And is this a Transformers film?
It's Optimus' granddaughter.
Marjorie.
Uh, Marjorie is this woman.
I believe they were pitching her for best actress.
She won't get nominated either.
She's this woman you've seen in a million things.
I don't know her name. John Hamm is in it. And Tim Robbins, who has gained 60 pounds and nearly lost his hair
And then so Tim Robbins is like a husky guy now big big guy and then Gina Davis who still looks like
Long kiss goodnight Gina Davis
And the movie is John Hamm is playing a robot
He's not, he's a, and this movie, I was finally was like,
am I just watching a play?
They sit in two rooms the entire time.
They never go out of them.
And it's this old woman, the opening scenes,
this old woman talking to John Hamm,
who was a robot version of her husband when he was in his prime.
Oh my God.
They talk for 25 minutes before there's even like a cutaway
to another scene.
And then, you know, it becomes kind of a, who's a robot type thing.
It played like a hallmark, hall of fame episode of Black Mirror.
Like it was trying to kind of say something, but it was done in this like, just drab, boring
lifeless, no energy to it.
Style.
And again, I'll give my input.
You want to make a movie like that?
Here's how you make it.
You want to make a who's who is the robot type of deal make it a farce a lot of doors opening and closing people are coming in. Yes, robot forgets his human skin. Yeah, that's to run the
Why are you looking at me so strange and they cut over and he's just got all the circuits visible in his face is gone. That's funny. Whoa, catch some his own reflection. Yeah, um, yeah, they're like that. Not great. Um, you got one Joe. You got another I have two more.
We'll go ahead. I finally cracked open this silent night deadly night. Parts three, four and five
Who you watched them all? I only got halfway through three was the third one I watched I watched them backwards
I started with five then well now five to me looks to be
Absolutely insane. I'd love to hear about five
Look, I'll start with five five was in my humble opinion a masterpiece
It is a one of the Bose bat shit movies. I've ever seen in my life
and not like the room where you're like,
this is so bad, it's good.
It is batshit where I'm like,
they were really, they really thought
they were onto something here
and the decisions are insane.
Mickey Rooney, who was a vocal,
yes, anti, the original silent.
Yeah, condemn the first film,
stars in the final film of the series.
The rare Hollywood actor
who takes an angry stand against something
and then immediately goes against it
when a check is dangled in his face.
You never see that out here.
Now, it's called Silent Night, Deadly Night 5,
The Toymaker, as you may have guessed,
Mickey Rooney is The Toymaker.
Take a wild guess what his name is in the movie.
Will I guess it?
No, okay, then let me just hear it.
Joe Petto.
So, Joe Petto, that's your starting point.
That's where we're starting in this show.
It's about these toys are getting into houses and the toys look innocent and then they
kill people in the house, mainly the kids, or at least they're aimed towards the kids.
And then it's a, well, who's doing this is this nice old toy maker doing it?
Yeah.
Whereas it is weird son or is it this other, like sort of drifter guy that for some reason
keeps buying toys.
Anyway, eventually you find out they make it look like it's Mickey Rooney.
It's not him.
Spoiler alert folks.
Yeah.
It is his weird son.
The reason the drifter has toys is because he's trying to track this guy and stop what he's
doing, and figure out how these devices work, I guess.
And in the final moments of the film, in the climactic sequence, the main character's
son is kidnapped, and they go to rescue him from the toy maker, and then when they
get there, they see Mickey Rooney's dead, and then it's revealed that it's his son doing
all the foul play. And then it's revealed that his son is a robot that he created. Okay.
So then you go full circle with the whole Pinocchio, Joe. His name Rob bot. No. Okay.
It's not. It's also not Pete. Ok, you know what I mean? It's not like they don't they don't
They had the taste to stop at Joe Petto.
And then they have to fight a robot
in the last like 10 minutes of the goddamn,
but it's fucking bad shit.
Now, the only thing I saw from it
appeared to be a nutcracker raping a woman.
Is that in there?
There's a scene where two people are fucking
and then these toys come in and attack the couple.
I don't remember a nutcracker raping
a woman. But I mean, I got to be honest with you, Pat. There's a couple of times I stepped
out of the room. I didn't feel like I needed to know the only scene I saw because somebody
saw about how it was just notorious scene was like a nut cracker removing his lack of genitals
and then he was like raping the woman. Well, no, no, well, here's what happens at the end.
The robot boy is naked and he's anatomically incorrect like a kendo. Right. And he wants
the woman whose son he kidnapped he wants her to be his mom but he's a robot so he doesn't know
what what that means. So he forces the woman down onto a work bench and he's like simulating
like fucking everybody can't fuckers is no dick and he's going he's going I'll be your son mommy
I love you mommy it's disturbing and then let me just stop you right there Joe yeah when I said
isn't there a scene where a nutcracker rapes a woman. He's not a nutcracker. You didn't think maybe
Pat means this scene. This is like the end of Jackie Brown. Wait a minute. You saw the bail bondsman
and you didn't think. Yeah. No, he's not a nutcracker. When you said nutcracker, a picture
of big wood. All right. Well, I was wrong. Uncle Sam looking thing. But anyway, let me just tell you
no dick region. Yeah. And the woman goes, your father made you and he goes, yes, he
could make anything. And then he looks down, camera tilts down to another close up of
the lack of penis tilts back up. And the guy goes, well, almost anything. Oh my God.
That's the last scene that well, no, that's before he says I I love you mommy as he like simulates like air humping her and then they kill them and
the smut it's just it's a real shit show. Yeah, I mean, and here's the thing. It's more goddamn offensive than the first movie that Mickey Rooney
You got lambastic, right?
So there you go.
All right, it sounds great, I'd love to see it.
Hostiles, Christian Bale, I told you I watched
20 minutes fell asleep, 30 fell asleep, 40 fell asleep.
Or actually, no, I talk about hostiles on a future episode
and we're gonna get them out of order.
But I finished hostiles, and when you hear me talk about it
on that future episode, I wound up being a little too harsh
when I watched it and stayed awake
for the entire running time. It is a boring Western, but eventually it becomes kind of interesting
and Christian Bale's good, isn't it? It's a Western and they're too rare. I was too hard on it,
but it is way too slow. I find that all Westerns are at least kind of interesting. Yeah, I like a
Western. You know, I watched the Florida Project. I've never heard of one of these goddamn movies.
What's the project?
What a project.
What a project is winning Willem Defoe a lot of awards and we'll probably get him an
Oscar nomination.
But it's the guy who made Tangerine, which I loved.
Never saw it.
I'm a whole movie shot on iPhone.
It looks incredible.
It's a very funny, interesting movie.
It's the same guy.
Florida Project is in a, basically, a Florida project, a building that has a lot of cheap
apartments.
Okay.
Willem Defoe is the manager and you focus on like three little kids and their bad parents.
like the woman's mom or the little girl's mom, little girl's incredible and her mom's like
turning tricks in the room with their daughter in the room and now does this turn into like a super
the super with Joe Pesci where William DeFoe has to live in his own building kind of thing.
A sentence by a judge to live in his own building is the plot of the suit.
But the Florida project is a, it was a beautiful to look at movie. William DeFoe deserves the
He accolades. He's getting. He's excellent in it as like the rare normal likable. He's the most normal guy in the movie.
I mean, you don't see that a lot. One of my favorite Dennis Miller jokes ever was he goes, watch auto focus.
Well, DeFo. Creepy. Well, DeFo looks like Christopher Walkin before you add water.
All right, let's see some funny joke. I hate Dennis Miller. It's hard to laugh at him.
You talk about Dennis Miller a lot. I don't like his politics, but I can't take away that the guy is a very funny joke writer.
Um, I watched an episode of News Radio the other day where Dennis Miller comes in and he's like a serial killer who's obsessed with Phil Hartman
Right. And he has like three lines and he's out and I'm when I listen to the commentary on it
They were like, yeah, we just all thought he was a real asshole
So we just kind of wrote him out of the show people do not like him. Yeah, let me cut his whole part. We hated him
Yeah, people do not like him. It's a shame because he makes me laugh. Yeah. I wrote a I wrote a good Dennis Miller style joke the other day
ready for this. I'm ready. Here it is. Do you, do you folks, people see Roy Moore riding a
horse and to vote? You know, I mean, call me crass people, but you think a guy that has such a
propensity for young chicks would have rode a fucking pony. It's a good, it's a good,
that's a good smell. I liked it. Yeah. Anyway, sorry. Go ahead. I liked it. Thank you. See the,
see the Florida product. It's great. It's great kid actors, and it's an interesting, I like when
When movies show me a slice of life, I don't see it shows how people you know on the fringes
of society there's an amazing scene where this old guy who's clearly a child molester
comes up and starts talking to the kids and Defoe comes out and like it's no spoiler it's
a very episodic movie there's these quick two -minute vignettes throughout it but he comes
out and he's like hey man are you okay and he's like yeah and he's like uh what are you
Homeless and he's like yeah, I'm just trying to get a soda and the whole thing's like real unsettling and creepy
And he's like well, let me get you a soda
He goes but you know soda doesn't really quench your thirst
You should be drinking water or whatever and he goes all the way back and get some water and he's taking care of him or whatever
And then they walk out and he's like well, we'll get you back in your feet. Don't worry about it
And then just start screaming. I mean because I never come the fuck back here again
You're trying to fuck these kids like it was insane, but I love the movies full of like cool little scenes and moments
It's very dark, and I like them.
Okay, well speaking of dark and cool scenes
and slices of life you never get to see.
I also watch Silent Night Deadly Night, part four.
Go on.
Initiation.
What a, oh initiating a new Santa or what?
That's the name of the movie.
That's the sub, right, whatever.
But who's getting initiated?
Well, I'm gonna tell you Pat, give me a second.
Taken long enough.
Silent Night Deadly Night, Pat, what do you think
I think when you hear that title, that franchise,
you think Christmas horror, correct?
Correct.
Silent Night Daily Night 4.
Maybe just to throw the fans of the franchise off base.
Center's around a Jewish woman.
Not a lick of Christmas in the movie, except for one scene where she goes to her boyfriend's
house, who is Catholic, and there's a Christmas tree, and they talk about Hanukkah and Christmas,
and the main character of the woman goes, she goes, you know, Hanukkah, Christmas, they're
the same thing.
It's just how different people celebrate a different time, or the same time of year.
and then the dad goes, that's bullshit.
Whoa.
Really gets really angry, really, really angry.
That's the only part that's Christmassy in the whole movie.
How do you, how do they do that?
It was very obvious.
There was a horror movie script called Initiation.
They got the rights to it
and they were like, let's just call it,
put Silent Night Deadly Man on it
and then people want to see it.
Anyway.
But like the thing that makes the horror world
to sew clogged up with thousands of pounds of movies.
The only thing that sets you apart is a Christmas setting.
Yeah, no.
No, it's shot in LA.
They say it's Christmas once or twice,
but they don't show any Christmas shit.
So here's the plot of the movie.
At the beginning of the movie,
a woman falls from a rooftop on fire.
Go on.
She hits the ground.
She's dead and her body burns up.
enter Clint Howard, Ron Howard's younger brother, who's also in part five. He's the connective
tissue of the Silent Night Daily Night universe apparently. Anyway, the shame at like Thanksgiving
when Clint and Ron have to trade stories of what their year looked like. Yeah, what they were
up to. Well, and this is right around what's Ronnie Howard doing in 1990? I mean, he's he's established
at this point. This is well -passed. This is back draft. This is parenthood, which had made like
a hundred million dollars. Yeah, Clint's like I was in a Silent Night Deadly Nightish. Yeah.
So here's the plot. The main character is a female reporter. And I'm only saying female because
they make gender a big, it's a weird sort of feminist piece. The film. And now you often refer to
women as weird feminist pieces.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, that's how it was brought up, right?
I don't know what to tell you.
But anyway, she's a reporter.
She wants to write a story on this woman
whose corpse was found burnt to a curse
because clearly, and this is established
within the first five minutes.
Clearly, this was a spontaneous combustion.
Oh, come on.
This is it.
And she goes to her paper that's all men.
And they're like, get out of here.
You little lady can't go,
go get me some caught that's literally a line of the movies like yeah just make us some coffee
and then she finds a group of women as she's researching the story behind your boss's back
who are very pro woman but then they turn out to be witches. Oh that was
all right I forgot to mute the TV that was the little thing okay we were
if for those of you that just might have heard that you know we have the little tag at the end
and that was a head come podcast.
And it's, we recorded past it,
so it just played through the TV.
All right, it doesn't matter.
Anyway, she goes and so then she joins up
with these women who are supposed to empower her,
but then they're just witches
and then they're trying to just make her evil.
And then they're trying to fuck her too.
So this lady's got nowhere to go, nowhere to go.
The witch has tried to fuck her.
Yeah, it's a very sexual like kind of lesbian snake, okay, witch affair, you know, it's
not an old haggie witch kind of thing, right?
It's more of a like a, you know, like a, like a sireny, you know, filth kind of peggy
bunty kind of vibe, you know what I mean?
Four room segment.
Yeah, exactly.
Okay.
So anyway, so I don't know, then she becomes a witch and then they tell her she's going
a burn on fire if she doesn't kill a young boy because all men are evil and then she doesn't
want to kill the young boy and then they, and she kills the main witch and then she burns
up any, I don't fucking remember, it was a fucking shit show. I mean, these, these movies
are bad shit. They're bad shit. They don't, they don't, they don't make any goddamn sense.
I mean, one and two made sense. At least in the construct of those movies. One and, one
makes sense. Two, the first 45 minutes of two is them just re -showing a truncated version
of one. Yeah. I may not have seen too. I think I only need these movies are creating
the third one, which I'm watching now and I'll wait to review it, which seems to be possibly
the best one quality wise at least, or at least from an acting standpoint, is even fucking
nuttier than the two I talked about tonight. I can't even believe that would be possible,
but I'd love to hear about it. Well, I'll tell you about it after I see it, but I'm starting
to love the franchise based on how batch it is. Yeah. Uh, it's it's nuts. It's nuts. Uh,
and it's got Clint Howard, which I've never seen him in anything except these two movies.
He is great as the asshole coach in parenthood. Oh, so he's in parent. So so Ronnie's tossed
them some bones. He run Howard had a little part in Apollo 13. He tosses them bones. Yes.
All right, because he's also in solo, the Han Solo movie really. Yeah, they're on Howard directed. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Okay. Yeah, probably gonna be terrible. He at least gives him a small part in each. All right.
And then the last picture I saw and what better way to bring it up than on this podcast was the hero with Mr. Sam Elliott, which was also for my consideration. He's also getting a lot of buzz about this film.
He to me it looks like if there was a
It looks like a hallmark channel movie the poster is absurd. That's exactly what it is. It's a hallmark channel movie
It's Sam Elliott
Being as good as he's been and everything else before I think this is maybe
One of his biggest roles is maybe why he's getting to talk and maybe they're worried about him dying or something but
You know, it's the most standard story
He plays a voiceover guy, so at the beginning you get the treat of him going like
Merlin Burb Accuses and they go could you do it one more time and he goes sure Merlin Burb Accuses, and they keep making him do it over and over
He's a voiceover guy then he goes over to Nick Offerman's house. They smoke like ten joints together and
Then he's like you should really go talk to your daughter
Who's Nick Offerman again?
swanson, but we're like a half hour in and it's like Sam Elliott smoking weed and thinking
about how he might want to talk to his daughter. Then he has a long lengthy love story folks.
And by the way, Sam Elliott is nearly 80 years old. A lengthy love story with Laura pre -pom from
And that's 70s show, who I believe is my age.
She comes over to offerments to buy weed.
Seize Elliott, Seize Sam Elliott sitting on the couch
and she's like, who's this?
Ching, Ching, Ching, Ching, you're the cash register girl.
Yeah, this is, that is absurd.
They have a full -on romance.
Hey, I like you on that sitcom.
Yeah, it's, I wouldn't say
It's a bad movie. It was just kind of generic and boring. And I of course I love Sam Elliott who doesn't
That sounds like a real dog shit movie. It's something I love Mickey Rooney, but I'll call dog shit when I see it. Yeah, it's it's
Dole, but fine. I
It's a bad time all these movies. I'm watching. I'm like, this is what I'm supposed to be considering
You know, I don't vote for any of that bullshit. I do vote. I take it kind of seriously. I try to see everything and I don't play their game
Yeah, I hear you, uh
That's all I got. All right. That's fine more way more than normally. That's fine. That was plenty
We got through a lot there my insomnia is a crap back
So I'm seeing a lot more movies. It's worked out great for me. I'm gonna go into a Joe scary stuff because I have something for it
And this is something that you listeners you fans of horror probably shocked to hear will be shocked to hear that I didn't already have
But I didn't already have it and now I have it. I finally subscribed to shudder
What was I thinking not doing this sooner?
This fucking streaming service is fantastic.
It's all horror movies and TV shows.
It's like $6 .99 a month or something.
And it might even be cheaper than that.
And that's it.
It's all horror all the time.
And then there's a feature on the streaming app
called Shutter TV where it's just like putting on
a channel that just plays movies all day.
It's awesome.
It's fucking awesome.
So, but what is the appeal? What sets it apart from a Netflix, which has a gigantic chorus
election as well? There is, this is all, this is a Netflix, well, I don't want to exaggerate,
but it is a ass load of content and it's all horror. It's no, there is no horror library
on any of the other services that comes anywhere close to this. Okay. So this is like if you
you had Hulu, but it was nothing but horror.
All right.
But like, why wouldn't, what is the difference
between going to the Netflix horror section?
Because this is more horror.
Okay.
This is like spinal tap, because this one goes to 11.
All right.
But do they have ever, like if you're like any horror movie,
they have it, or they just have a wider selection.
They have a very different selection.
Okay.
And they have a much more, in my opinion, niche selection.
and they break, there's a category, there's an alphabetical,
categorical section you can go through that is so many sub -categories of
horror films. And it's great because you're like, well, I'm in the mood for
exactly this 1970s devil movie. There's a section for it. You know what I mean?
There's you want a horror comedy. There's a section for it. The tire tells in the dark side catalog is on there
Which if you don't own in my opinion, that's worth the price of admission alone
Great Steve Cougan show. I never saw it called Dr. Terrible's House of Horrible. That's really really funny
And it's like a spoof of the old hammer horror series. It sounds great
Fear itself is on there, which was a short -lived anthology series. It's just great
It's a great service. And it's and it's run by I believe AMC
Okay, so you know, it's not you're not getting a bunch of bullshit. You know, look a lot of that shit on Netflix is like
Hey, a few guys got you know 25 grand together and it's on fucking net and it's terrible right there's not a lot of that on you
I think this is all like mostly stuff. You'd set your drink on right in one way or the other so
I recommend the service highly
All right, I will check it out.
Let me throw out a big spoiler warning and just say we're about to discuss Star Wars
the last Jedi.
If you haven't seen it, wait till you have.
Let's open it up.
Joe and I just saw it together.
Yes, Joe.
What did you think?
I liked it. Look, I always go through this weird depression period after I see a new
Star Wars movie. One of the main trilogy ones I mean. I like it when I'm watching it.
I enjoy it. Afterwards, I have a sadness because it feels like Christmas is done. It's like
It's like there's a lot of build up and that's over very quickly. So I always have to kind of
cross sex with you. Yes. Yes. There you go. There you go. Hey, we finished. We didn't even start.
That's a come in the pants joke. Right, right, ladies and gentlemen. The uh,
I liked it. Um, but it's it also takes, I need to process shit after I see with Star Wars because
Because everybody that loves Star Wars is going to have their fan theories and their ideas
in their head.
Well, why didn't it do this instead of that, or I thought they were going to do this?
So there's a lot of clutter that I have to kind of navigate my way through before I can
start to sit back and actually rank the movie in how much I liked it against the other movies.
That being said, it was great.
I mean, I have no complaints.
It is a very different Star Wars film, which is interesting, but also kind of strange.
Like Ryan Johnson, Ryan, Ryan, how are you the fuck you say his name?
Yeah, he kind of bent it to be like a Ryan Johnson movie and I liked brick, I hated
the brother's bloom, I thought Looper was kind of cool, but not the biggest fan.
I mean this felt like one of his moves especially for the first hour plus where I was essentially checked out
It's very slow. I think the first hour was really for
The you know the truest of Star Wars fans. It's a lot of exposition and it's a lot of getting to know Luke Skywalker again and
Learning why he left and you know and why he's hiding and all that stuff. So I enjoyed it as a fan
And when it kicks in, it really kicks in hard.
It was a lot of fun.
There were parts where I literally got teary from excitement.
There's a fantastic Yoda cameo, which I was, I mean, I was pat, you said next to me.
I was giddy.
I was like, every time I looked over at Joey at a giant smile on his face, it was unsettling.
My favorite part in the whole thing is, and it's just an action sequence really, but there's
There's a part in the final showdown where it looks like the resistance, which they
start calling the rebellion in this again, which is awesome.
There's a part where they're kind of getting the shit kicked out of them, and they think
all hope is lost.
And then Chewbacca sweeps in in the Millennium Falcon.
That part was fucking awesome.
And then he leads the tie fighters away from the resistance fighters so they can be safe
you know, have a safe cover, whatever you do.
You lead them into this cavern and it plays
the trench run music from the very first Star Wars movie.
The music is like,
boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
And I got really, that was awesome.
Like there were moments like that in the film
where I was so excited.
Yoda's return was, that was fucking fantastic.
And it appeared to be a puppet again.
Yes, it was definitely a puppet.
Yeah, Luke was awesome in it.
I thought Luke was wildly boring until that last hour.
And then I was like, this is so fucking cool.
Yeah, he's pretty great.
Luke, for the first hour, I was like, OK,
because I'm not the diehard star wars guy,
I really felt like, oh no, I'm watching a Mark Hamill movie.
That's how bored I was, like it just seemed like some generic Mark Helm, but at some point,
I made just a huge turn.
I know the point.
It was the scene where, what is it, Kylo Ren and Ray are squaring off in the chambers.
That room was awesome.
That Lord, of course, Andy Circus, because nobody else can play these fucking characters.
Yeah, that character was awesome, and from then on it was gold, but like that moment when they all fire at Luke
I love that they kept that insane performance of Adam Driver going like
And then when Luke does the brush off his shoulder. I had probably the biggest laugh I had in the movie all year
I love you really you really yeah, there's a scene where I love that several imperial walkers
Luke comes out into a battlefield and Adam driver says fire every gun we have at that man.
Yeah, they shoot and then the dust settles and Luke is still standing there clean as a whistle
And he just does the like dirt off the shoulder. It was awesome move. It's a pretty it's it's it's single
Pretty great. Yeah, and then the then one second later there was another awesome bit that made me laugh out loud
which was driver throws that henchman up against the wall.
Yeah, yeah, it's like, give me speed or shoot some more
or whatever.
And then the guy's like, I don't know if we can do that,
sorry, he throws him against the wall.
And then this British extra in the front goes,
right away, sir.
Left, left, hysterically.
It was two great jokes, right on top feet, sir.
Loved it.
There were, there were one too many jokes.
And I like those two quite a bit.
There are one too many jokes in the movie as with everything.
I don't know why everybody thinks that in order to make something light now, it means
it has to have jokes.
Well, how concerned were you because I was worried you were going to start shifting and twitching
and when this movie essentially opened with a call waiting gag, how close were you to losing
your shit?
I was not, I gave them the benefit of the doubt because it was Star Wars, but I was not
thrilled because Star Wars usually doesn't go for that shit.
but Rogue One was a very serious movie.
Yeah, well, I thought Force Awakens had too much comedy in it too.
And I like Force Awakens, but I felt like this was, I get it.
I understood what they were trying to do.
Empire is like that as well.
Empire is very playful and very cute, and then it gets very dark.
So I get that that's what they were sort of doing.
Do you like the little gerbals?
Yeah, I didn't mind that.
I thought they were adorable.
They did want too many cuts to them,
But almost every time they cut to him I liked it. I thought it was endearing and I liked that I liked that I always like because it happens with the Ewoks and Jedi
I like when Chewbacca
Has like some weird bond with like a cute animal, right?
Well, he's an animal. Yeah, it's it's not it's a good flick
There's a major cliffhanger at the end where it appears that Luke is dead
Uh -huh. I
I can't imagine that is going to be the case given the fact that Carrie Fisher in real
life has passed away.
And obviously she's not going to be in the next movie.
I can't imagine they're going to go into this next movie without any of the old characters.
So I feel like what it's going to turn out to be is that Luke is not dead.
He is just sort of transcended to a new level of the force or whatever.
I didn't even take away from it that he was dead.
I don't have a sci -fi mind, but you and Heather, my girlfriend saw it with us.
You both thought he was dead.
Well, I mean, he exerts himself into the force with the force and like a way that no
jet I ever has, and then he disappears, and his cloak floats away, and that's how, when
Yoda dies, that's what happens, but then Yoda's in this.
Exactly.
So I think like I think like Obi -Wan and Yoda came back as force ghosts
I think Luke literally was like and I think that's why there was all that talk at the beginning of like
That's not what the force is right the force is this other thing it doesn't belong to the Jedi
Right, I think that's kind of why it's called the last Jedi because it's the Jedi are gonna be something bigger than this now
That's what I think let me ask you this do you like?
I think the weak link to these new Star Wars movies is the characters
Do you like Finn?
Yeah, I like Finn. I like Ray a lot. Finn boars the shit out of me. The new
Asian girl in this I forget her name. I liked her a lot too Rose board me and board me sideways. I thought she was good
Uh, I like Ray quite a bit
And I like Oscar Isaac in it too. I think he's fine, but also boring. I gotta be honest like what would this movie lacked for me
was that just unquestionable star power of a Harrison Ford? Because Carrie Fisher appeared
sort of half asleep in this movie. Well, that's just how she sounds now.
It's weird. Did she get a reverse nose job where R was it just blown out from Coke?
Because she appeared to have like a big like already lying style Coke nose as opposed to her.
Well, I mean, I don't know if she ever style. I don't know. She didn't go right up to the end.
Yeah, I don't want to speak out of school, but I mean she her voice just said that's like that's a
Pacino Godfather thing. It's like that's one of the problems with Godfather three is you can't
it's not the same guy anymore right right. You know Godfather wanted to Pacino's like just never
never never stay it up against a family. And then the third one he's like, hey, pull me back
it. You're like, yeah, it's not the same human being anymore. Yeah, so that's that's that's one
That's tough with with the Carrie Fisher thing. I'm surprised. There's a scene where a very apparent that she's dead
Yeah, and then she's not dead
I'm surprised they didn't just run with that
But I felt like they felt it was very important to show her reunite with Luke one one last time
That was nice. I thought yeah, Laura the Laura and I love Laura darn Laura. Don't should have been cut out of the movie
I mean what what was that in there for?
Yeah, it was it was lame and like their their last moment of like like an emotional beat between them
I'm like
What are they even talking about? I was so bored by them. I I thought it looked it kept me guessing
There were some red herrings in the movie and I get it. That's that's Star Wars. I liked
I like that they made you think that Lard Dern was probably
a spy for the first order and then you realize she actually was doing everything she could
for the resistance.
I like that, Benicio, I like Benicio del Toro as care if I hated that.
And I love Benicio del Toro and I was so excited he was in this.
I hated his character.
I feel like my takeaway from this was that in the editing room, they picked a few of his
best moments and everything else was unusable because this this performance is so lazy as to be
Almost like he's like fuck you. I don't want to be here. I thought he's I thought he sucked it. I don't I don't agree
I thought he I thought he played like a weird like sort of con man kind of thing. I liked him. Well, I liked him
Here's the thing though. This is the thing that's that's not
Doesn't seem to be happening in these new films these new films are great. Yeah, you all know how much I love Star Wars
I'm happy to have them.
I'm gonna be probably starwarsed out
after the final film in this trilogy.
I'm happy Abrams is coming back.
I thought Ryan Johnson did a great job.
I thought JJ Abrams did a better job
of capturing the spirit of starwars.
I look forward to him doing something bigger
with the third film, which he said he is.
He said he wants to go way bigger than he did in the first one.
and he wants to go deeper into it and everything.
So I think it's gonna be pretty cool,
but I think after that movie I'm kinda done
because it just doesn't,
these movies are so clearly not just Star Wars,
it's everything, they're so clearly meddled with
by these fucking executives and these notes
and these rewrites and all this bullshit.
It's obvious, I mean it's just obvious.
It's like there's clearly do I like the pours? Yeah, they're cute. Yeah, it is there's no reason for those things to be in the movie
They're there were there were there were you know
10 moments that I thought were so egregious
like Luke squeezing the nipple of
Greenish milk into a mug and drinking it. I was like what am I watching here?
then
And when they're at the casino, which was a real miscalculation of a scene, and that
dwarf is putting coins in BB -8.
Yeah, and then BB -8 shoots the coins out later.
I'm like, even your dumbest kid is not laughing at this.
It's not comic relief.
So what is this?
Well, and that was one of the other things that I liked, there was one of the other things
that I liked more about the JJ Abrams approach, was there was a lot more CGI in this.
it was a lot more obvious like things were being green screened and I mean
when I watched The Force Awakens I was like that that whole thing felt
real to me. I never felt like one thing was computer at generated or anything.
You preferred Force Awakens to this. Yeah I mean look Han Solo will always and
forever be my favorite Star Wars character and he's not in this you know so
I, you know, and I was excited to see Luke come back, but it's a very excited to see Luke
come back, but it's a very different take on Luke.
It's not.
I thought they did better shit with Luke in this one in the last half than they did with
solo and force away, because Hansolo was never given that moment like that.
I might be making too much of this brush off the shoulder moment, but that whole scene,
I was like, that's one of my favorite scenes in all of Star Wars.
Yeah, it was great.
I love it.
The movie, look, the movie's great.
It's not, it's not a bad movie by any stretch.
It's a great movie, but it's, this is what I mean, I always have to sit back and kind of process
it.
Yeah.
Are you going to go again, bro?
Yeah, I'll probably go tomorrow and watch it again, because I, these tickets I paid for
because I bought them before I had movie pass, but I had movie pass, they're just going
over the fuck I feel like it.
Well, you can only see a movie one, you can buy a ticket to another movie.
If you do a movie past, you can only see a movie one time.
Well, I can see this at least one more time for free.
As far as I'm concerned, I felt exactly the same way about it as I did Rogue One, which
was an almost unwatchable first hour to me, a guy who's not crazily obsessed with Star Wars,
followed by an hour that was so awesome, it made the previous boring hour irrelevant.
I thought the, the ending of this was just pure gold for a straight hour, uh, same with
Rogue One. I think Phantom Menace was in more entertaining movie start to finish. Phantom
Menace or force awakened. Excuse me, folks. Geez. What a slip of the tongue. Force awakens.
Uh, um, but you know, I, I'd love to see one that's just this entered as, as entertaining as
this last hour all the way through. Maybe that's a prohibitively expensive movie to make.
I don't know. No, I don't think so. I feel like I feel like they had a lot. They had to
clean up in this and they had a lot, not clean up, but they had a lot to justify and execute
and, uh, and I feel like the third one will probably be the most fun and heroic of the three.
Uh, but I'm bummed out that it's not going to have Han Solo. It's not going to have Princess
just lay it and it might not have Luke fucking sky walker right so and I got to tell you
the people they have remaining are not enough to keep a movie afloat.
If I'm watching Finn, well, you know, driver and Ray, um, I like and they killed Snoke
too.
Snoke was awesome.
So it's really, they really clean the, uh, yeah, the power with this one.
So it's like, it's like, if I got to watch Dern and I, of course, I love
That's right. Oh, yeah, that's right. Yeah. Um, who was Lupita Neon? Oh, they killed
Fasma. They killed a Gwendolyn Christy. Is that the silver woman? Yeah. Yeah. Well, who
was Lupita Neon? Oh, she's, um, I saw her name in the credits. I was like, she wasn't
in them. She's, uh, yeah, she is. She's, she's, um, what's her face? Um, she's the lady
with the alien lady with the goggles in the first one, Maz or whatever her name is. Oh,
I mean, that's a name of my family.
So she's in this, but she's only in it for like a second.
And she, it looked nothing like, of course,
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I think that that was again, another red hair.
I think he's trying to misguide her in some way.
So I feel like in the third film,
there's still gonna be some cool reveals.
I feel like we still might get a nice little OB -1 cameo.
Yeah.
I feel like I just wish everyone was performing
at a driver level, you know?
Like, and I don't even always love that guy,
but like he's out to make a memorable character.
I mean, Finn, and it's not the actress fall.
That character has written, they give him nothing.
He's given nothing to play.
Well, it's a lot of characters.
There's too many characters, you know.
So it's, so I, you know, I mean maybe
that's why they killed a bunch of people,
but they killed all my favorite characters.
Actually, I love that actor in Attack the Block, John Boyega,
but.
Yeah, he's a great actor.
Man, in this, I just, every time he's on,
I'm like, give him something.
I thought they, I thought they took Poe Dameron,
and which is Oscar Isaac's character
to a necessary level in this film.
I felt like in the first, in Force Awakens,
he was just sort of the like fly boy, whatever pilot
that came in and was like slick and got the job done.
In this one, I liked that he was willing to commit
treason to save the resistance.
And I felt like they brought him to a necessary level.
Not that end to him either.
I feel like it's just a poor man's solo,
which is obviously probably how he was conceived.
but, you know, we'll see, we'll see what happens in the next one, but I liked it, and I certainly would put it above
Phantom Manus, absolutely. I would put it above
I put it above clones without hesitation. I think I would put it above clones. I mean, I don't know
You know, I like a lot of shit and clones because clones is the same thing that we're talking about. The first half of clones is a lot of corny
this doesn't have a lot of corny shit in it but like clones has like a lot of
corny boring shit in the first half and then like as soon as Obi -Wan gets to
the El Camino the rain planet it gets starts to get like awesome and it's
super fun and it's not this awesome not as awesome as the back half of this
move but I'll put it above for now put it above clones but I don't think I'd
I put it above Sith.
I don't think I'd put it, maybe Jedi, I don't know.
I don't know, that's a tough call.
I'll put it over Rogue One.
I'd want to see this again or I'd want to watch this
more frequently than Rogue One.
But you're right, it was paced very similarly to Rogue One.
I liked it, I liked it.
I hope I'm not putting up the vibe
that I didn't care for it.
I just, it's a lot to process.
Yeah.
Yeah, and I didn't give a shit about half of it and really loved the other half of it.
But folks, for those of you, and that's very few of you at this point who complain about
us riffing too much and not talking about movies, I got, I direct you to this one.
We talked about nothing but movies for what feels like four hours.
I hope you enjoyed it, and I hope you enjoyed the last Jedi.
We'll see you next time.
I am on.
Hold on.
I got it.
shout outs. I just said. Oh, I'm sorry. I'm on Twitter and Instagram at the Patrick
Walsh. Joe is on Instagram, but it links to Twitter at Joderosa Comedy. Yeah, and you
can still follow me on Twitter. I just told yeah. And uh, any plugs, Joe? Uh, not at the
moment. Just my penthouse column. You let me down every month in penthouse. Check that out.
I am also uh, in penthouse this month, fucking a Filipino woman. Um, if
Full -bushed Filipino woman. Yeah, and the the the the the the the the spread is called
Comejaltese of war
Holy cow
All right, it's it's called a cock -a -lips now. Oh
Shout -outs folks Derek Clark Anthony V. Manito aka part of the fly if Oprah shot David Belinger
Tyler Zach
Kurt Zeigler, Jenna Hunter McDonald, Zero Fox track clothing, John Wolt, Justin Bohogger,
Nate Roundtree, Adam Bembonic, Manny Rios, Demonio Rubio, Brendan Gash, Edmund Agabo,
Paul Pickery, Jake Ferote, I think, Chris Lindt, Tony Quinn, Rob Lines, Danny Rudd,
Jacob Barrett, Jordan C. Maxwell Ashcroft, Ryan Kohler, Joshua Christianson, Barbara Allen, Jonathan
Face, Rebecca Cohen, Smelly Bubbles, Chris Bowen, Mike Gibbons, Donnie Joyce, Michael Dawson,
Jennifer Smith, Luke Henderson, Hader Ismail, Nick Wather, Leah Vaughan, Connor Dent, Denahey,
Michael, just Michael, Stephen Calpa, Marcoupa, Kevin Swistowicz, Swistowicz, Swistowicz.
I think that is Thomas Koza, Anthony J. Guajardo, and he Johanison.
To be Kay, Sean Florent, Dolores Martinez, Will Foley, Megan Lybrand, Scott Blikkins -Durfer,
Alic Walker. Brett Wormer. Oh, no, sorry, Brett Wemmer. Tristan, Tristan Carlson,
Laura Sexton, Anthony Guajardo. Brett Klingner. Alex Lowe, Weston Thomas, that's the
one that we can never say, man. I don't know how to say that. H -V -I -D -H -Y -L -D. You
remember where he told us. Yeah. Sorry, buddy. You know, you know, we, you know, we're trying to do
over here. Yeah. Jared Blair, Josh Schmorridge, Richie Verdugo, Chris Hopper, Emily Griffith, Emily
Florence, Ron L. Jordan Parker, Dave Comerick, Abby Manuel, Kim DeAngelo, Jonathan Galatt, Michael
on Musau, Musau, Zoe Blaskevic, Edmund Dilland, Asley or Azul, asley, I think it is,
Kovinesland, Azul Kovinesland, or Azley Kovinesland, Dan McLeod, Lorenz Bunganiers, Alejandro
Salgado, Papa Spouche, Tegan McLeod, Matthew Little, Tracy Reddington, Sean Thomas,
Amanda Alzemora, Jason Weibel, Michael Curry, Drew Spindler, Andrew Kovale, Sam Mitchell,
Aaron Millinowski, Scott Nolan, Jackie Gertz, Greg Sarenson, Benjamin Tahia, Misty Zavar,
Brandon Nock E.
Dajne Wilford, Johnny Ferg, Matthias Paujo,
Superfan Giovanni, Michael Gold, Danielle Doer, Eric Lemora,
Michael Madrigal, go to Mr. Suit Records in Lancaster, Pennsylvania.
Stephen Reese, Walter Keegan, Kevin Marsson, Nick,
Erica Branding, Lawrence Anderson, Jared Smallridge, Zach Schoendorf, Will Potterf, Natalie
Craig, Nathan Baskett, Anthony, just Anthony, Kyle Kinslin, Brooke Adams, the man whose
name we cannot speak, Adi Babaduk, Scott Patton, Reed Ascetic, Brian Bolaria, I believe it
It is bar Bama M. O. Lee Marvel, Robert Pearson, boring Dan Clark, Michael A. A. O. Max
Unwraff, heightened Davidson, Brian England, and John Wyzengruber.
Guys, it is such an overwhelmingly long and supportive list.
We thank you so much.
Thank you very much, everybody.
I hope I'm doing your names just as better with each time we do this, uh, we're overwhelmed
by your generosity.
I mean that we mean that thank you for everything and Merry Christmas. Happy Hanukkah. Happy Kwanza. Happy New Year.
We hope to see you soon and we'll see you in hell.
That was a headgun podcast.