I'll see you in hell.
Folks, it's Will see you in hell.
Back again, this week we are talking about the devil's bath, the devil's bath, which weirdly,
I guess it's not even explicitly clear, but I believe was this time period's term for
depression, correct? I googled devil's bath meaning and all I got were article after article
dissecting the film. I couldn't find like what the phrase meant. I was really trying to
well, I mean in the movie when they're like, I think she's in the devil's bath. I believe it meant
she's like in the grips of depression. Well, we get to the moment. We'll get to what it's about,
but I mean, Christ, a heavy tale to say at least you smoking again?
Yeah, I've been smoking on and off. Today was a day. I just need to cigarette. I'll probably have
another. That's fine. I'm in that writer's room zone of diet where you're like, well, I ate a half
a chicken Caesar wrap and then a handful of pretzel bites. Right. I don't have any food in the house.
I'll eat a turkey sandwich at 9 .30. I drink some own broth. I call it. Sure.
I threw on and I thought Joe was going to roast me, but he was nice enough not to. But I threw on
this flat cap that I bought in Scotland and I brought it home and sent pictures to a few friends and
wore it out once or next. I never had the guts to wear it. Maybe. Oh, no, I wore it to
what's what's our bar? The roost one night. And people just don't like the hat. You know,
much like an Uncle Buck at Angers, people just the side of it. But I think it kind of works. I
kind of like it. It's got a peaky blinder vibe. I don't think it looks bad on you. Thanks.
My friend was like, yeah, well, they became very like cliche because bald guys wear them all
the time. And I'm like, well, then aren't I a nice surprise? I take it off. You're like, look at
the locks on this one. I agree. I agree. She much. It works. It's a good hat with a beard too.
And you have a beard. So yeah. And I got like Scottish Irish kind of vibes. I think it works.
But I definitely feel tougher with it as well. But they got to say the response wasn't great.
You know, and guys and it's, you know, you know, this more than anyone Joe has a comic
or people in comedy writers rooms are very similar. It is tough for a guy to bring any sort of
color, spice, even the slightest difference to his wardrobe and then go around his friends. It's
nearly impossible. You feel, you feel almost a stage fright feeling if you're wearing a slightly
flashy, let's say, maybe a chain around your neck or something. You know they're coming after it.
And that's why every guy looks the same. Every guy wears the same shit myself included. They're
scarred. Yeah, I do, I will say this though, I think living in LA, you have the best shot at getting
away with it unscathed. Oh yeah. I mean, you can do almost anything here and not be the stupidest
looking bastard at a party. That's for sure. Yeah. And most people, your friends might be afraid to
make fun of it because there's some new movement about the hat. How it's, you know, faces to make
fun of the hat or something. I don't know. Sure. Anti -Scott. Yeah. You know,
Scottish is still one of the ones anyone can feel free to make fun of, make fun of the accent.
Do whatever you want. There's something that it's just fine. It's really interesting. The Irish as
well. Yeah. Except it doesn't bother me. Yeah, you can still make a, you know, what do you, a drunk
joke about an Irish guy? No, he seems to care. Well, that's true too. But like, I really,
I actually really, really enjoyed the new Conan around the worlds on, on Max.
They were very, very funny and entertaining as they always are. And I think Conan is one,
like Jack Black, one of the most long term consistently entertaining and funny people of my lifetime.
And I dive treasure him. I watched, I've not watched the show. But I've watched a lot of the like 10 minute
segments they've released on YouTube. I enjoyed it very much. I was like, I know I've taken some shots
at Conan for always being on in the past. But I was watching and I was like, God damn it,
this guy's really fucking funny, man. Like he's really good in a scenario like that.
He's great. And you know, he's an older guy with maybe some blind spots. But like, if he goes to
Ireland on the show, it's, it's 30 seconds into the show. He's going, hey, the two, the two, the two, the two,
the two. And you know, it's not like he goes to Japan and he's doing that, you know. And I just
wonder why. I mean, I don't know. It's a hypothetical. I don't know why summer, okay. And some aren't.
I really don't. I guess more Irish people would need to be upset about this portrayal. But I guess
for the most part, Irish people are like, hey, I guess that is how I talk a little bit. You know,
when I do, I do fancy a pace now and again. You know, sure, that's most of my relatives.
I was telling Pat before we started that I haven't had much time to watch anything outside of
what we need to watch for the show. Yeah. Because of just having a work schedule now. And then also
the time difference with me and Pat and when we can record because he's three hours earlier means
we can only record after I get home from work. It's, you know, it's tough to squeeze in things.
But I've got what I call ass time. That's where I bring some hot ass over to the house and we
get down. And that's sort of not able to be played with that time. That's a good three to four hours
each week day. So what I'm getting to is is during the movie corner today, I'm going to, I'm going to
cover some new psycho stuff because I have had time for that. But one new psycho that I'll do outside
of the corner today because I think it'll prompt some interesting discussion. I was hearing about
this show Palm Royal or Royal, whatever. I haven't seen it. But I just was kind of looking it up.
And I'm seeing these still shots of the show. The first was of Carol Burnett. And I was like,
Jesus, Carol Burnett looks amazing in this thing. Like God, she's like 93. Like how does she have
zero wrinkles? I don't think she's had a ton of work done. That's weird. And I was like, wow,
good for her. She looks great. And then I started looking at other stills. And I was like, who stars
in this? And I was like, wait a minute, that's Kristen. Wait, wait a second. And then I started looking
at more stills like, why does everybody in this show have a smooth face? And I was like, Pat and I
were talking about this recently that this de -aging thing is just becoming now a touch -up thing. So I
Google Palm Royal de -aging. And sure enough, it is article after article, read it thread after
read it thread of people being like, the goddamn show is distracting. Why does everybody have the
smoothing thing on their face? Like it's the aging like wig and everybody. Everybody on the show.
Lauren Dern, if they're doing it to everybody, that must mean that's an apple thing that can't just
be like something they have the actresses decide if they want or not. It's clearly it's got nothing
to they're not playing younger people. If they're playing younger, they're playing younger by a few
years. It's not like they're playing people in their 20s. And of all of these discussion forums,
I found an article said the same thing. The show is distracting that everybody has this weird
sheen on their face to make them look younger when that's not a part of the plot. Like they're not
playing younger people. What is going on? What is happening? Nobody can figure it out. And it's like,
now I think what we were saying is probably happening is happening. They're just going to start now
using D aging as a method to make everybody look like a fucking perfect star on film now. Absolutely.
This I just read that apple has like .04 % of streaming viewership.
And their spending is just insane obviously. I mean everybody's talking about their shows. I feel
like right. Like it was the stiller one. Everybody that was the good one severance. I mean,
that's the one I signed on for the rest. You know, it's almost like they're it's almost like they're
broadcasting as an extension of their screensavers. They're just like things that are there. Now,
that Colin Farrell show. Did you read about the twist of that show? No.
So if you plan on watching this shut shut off for one minute, it's Colin Farrell in sugar.
And it's he's a detective. And he's like a LA night's detective or whatever solving cases. And
they do seven episodes of the show, cop show, whatever. And at the end of the seventh one,
Colin Farrell turns around and he's a blue alien.
They just they just didn't mention it for a hot seven kept it out.
So like suddenly you're sitting there watching it and you're like, oh, now I'm seven hours
into a sci -fi show. I hate sci -fi. I don't want to be watching this.
Yeah, that's a lot. Yeah, that's like the Adam Driver I read the script moment in
the Dead Don't Die. You're like, what have I been watching? What the fuck is going on here?
Yeah, there's a contract you sign kind of the longer, you know, that's why people have been so upset
with the endings of shows. They feel betrayed them or whatever. I get it. You have an emotional attachment.
We had a long discussion today, me and some of the writers about
true detective. Sure. And everybody had mixed takes. Some people actually liked seasons two and
three. Some people hated four. Some people thought four was okay. But everybody agreed on one thing.
And this applies to what you're saying. Season one was awesome until the last episode. Everybody
was like, right. And I forgot. Like it was fun talking about that again. Remembering how disappointed
everybody was in that final episode. Like what the fuck was this? What happened? And now, you know,
that's happened a few times. You know, the sopranos, of course, is a famous one.
sopranos, I don't know if I've told the story. I've always been worried about spoiling it for Joe.
And I'm not going to, but Joe's not, you know, either he's heard it or he doesn't give a fuck at this
point. But I was in this apartment complex that basically looked like the one where they go find
Brad Pitt and true romance. Like it almost looked like a ship. You know, there's like a circle window
in each unit, very cheap like $800 a month kind of thing. And I was watching the sopranos finale
with my pal Brian on my bed, because I had a studio apartment with only a bed. And we were watching it
riveted by the fucking thing. And then it ended and everyone in my apartment complex who had HBO
wound up running outside and were screaming at each other trying to piece together what had happened.
It was very exciting. I can't recall a moment like that in entertainment in since really 20 years.
No, that's awesome. People were calling their cable companies and what's going on, what's
happened? It was exhilarating. That was a huge one. I remember when that had, I actually watched
the finale when it was on because I was just like, this is a moment in time. I understand
enough about the show that I feel like I can get through this. And I did understand enough to watch
it. But that's a typically Joe thing that you've watched the prequel film, the finale, and been on
the podcast. Yeah, mildly, before I got a sense. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes, Seinfeld finale is the one before that I can think of time square viewing of the Seinfeld
finale, which is that's insanity. Yeah, that happened. We had, how many TV wheelings did you have for
news events growing up? I had only two that I recall. I was home because I was in call. Well,
yeah, I was home for 9, 11. I watched that at home. And I saw OJ, they wheeled in for the verdict
into class as like we were 13. I was like, all right, yeah, we'll do this.
I saw the OJ verdict. I was in freshman in college. And the student union building at the temple
Annbler campus. I walked, I was like getting out of class and I was cutting through the main
activities room or whatever to get back to my dorm. And I walked in and it was shoulder to shoulder.
Yeah. And I was like, what is going on in here? And then I looked up and there was a screen
that they were playing the OJ verdict on. I remember when not guilty was said everybody cheered.
Really? Yeah, everybody cheered. And I was like, oh shit. Yeah, they feel like in Missouri,
people were scared. Like maybe OJ was going to come to our town. I don't remember any cheering.
Wheel in moments, I don't remember any specific ones. I do remember seeing the challenger blow up,
but I was homesick or it was summer. I was home for whatever reason. Well, when that happened,
that was huge. Obviously. And then that's, oh, and then of course 9 -11, but I woke up to that on the
radio. My alarm went off and the morning radio guy and it must have been Dudley and Bob or whoever
because I was living in Austin and they were like, the second tower just got hit. I was like, what the
fuck is going on? What are they talking about? You know, like it was a weird one.
I guess there's really none of that anymore. And I think that's part of why I feel sort of a
general emptiness is that you can't really go into work or school on a Monday and say, hey,
did you see this last night? That doesn't really exist. Well, Trump assassination attempt, I would say.
Okay. Yeah, I guess news events for sure. Also welcome our new presidential candidate.
Kamala Harris. Yeah. After a full week of Biden saying, oh,
there's God is my witness. I'll never step down.
Nothing means anything anymore. Just say anything. Honestly, I think
it is so damaging. The most damaging part of the last whatever 5, 10 years is just how much everybody
knows now about what a disgusting facade this all is. Oh, yeah, it used to be a few people screaming
in a corner and you'd be like, hopefully he's just crazy. And the world isn't really like this and
you go about your day and you could be fine. But now everybody is that guy screaming because everybody
knows how bad it is. And it's just fully exposed. And there's no one coming. Yeah. And when you see
people try to be like, you know, say our Kamala Harris, come on, whatever, you know, that's not
getting me riled up gang. That's not getting me pumped about our win chances or the future of democracy.
No, no, it's a we're in a zone. And then it's funny that the, you know, the the Trump thing
humanized him for a moment with everybody. And everybody, you know, I was with a bunch of friends
watching it. And I believe all of them were, are, are from the roof of a building about 20 feet
across the way, right? Right. Right. All of them were, are registered Democrats. Yeah.
None of them are fans of Trump to varying degrees. But even in that moment, everybody was like,
this is terrible. This is not good. And we should live in a place where you can express your political
beliefs without threat of violence or whatever. Everybody agreed on that. And it humanized the man
for a second. And then when Biden stepped down, I was like, here's a chance for the new and
improved human Trump to be graceful. And he's right back in like sleepy Joe was the worst present
we've ever had. I guess, all right. I guess we're just keeping the foot on the gas here. We're just
okay. There you go. I need to do a quick. What's the one where we have a product that's got a horror
tinge to it? Scary stuff. Scary stuff. It's called room to dream. I had the physical book.
And then I got it on Audible because I was like, Oh, wait, David Lynch actually reads a big part of
this. Okay. But it's David Lynch and Carolyn McKenna. So it's essentially like a David Lynch
biography. Okay. And it's a woman kind of walking you through his life and then his movies, of course,
as with all biographies of this type, the film section is what you're there for. And it's the best stuff.
She does kind of the dry details biography. And then David Lynch hops on and just starts talking like a
madman telling a thousand stories about like working on Blue Velvet with no rhyme or reason, no
connection. At one moment, it'll be like the most moving story you've ever heard about him and an
old woman with cancer. And then five seconds later, he's talking about eating the world's greatest
apple fritter, you know, and how it, you know, he's just a nut. He's great. And it was a very novel
part of the pun. Great way to tell a guy's life story. I like that it was different than the
standard biography in that you got, here's the facts. And then here's Lynch. And what's also cool about
it is that they talk about how he's been in like five relationships that all were affairs. And in
each one, including Isabella Rosalini, they realize like, Oh, shit, he's in love with this woman
that's working for him. And it's like kind of a toxic pattern of his that they talk about.
And then Lynch will come on and be like, Yeah, I definitely didn't do too well by Peggy. I'll tell you
that. You know, and you can't be mad at him. It's not like some taudry tell all whatever you
and then they talk to Peggy. And she's like, you know, at the end of the day, I love David. I wish
him well. If he asked me to work on a film, I'd go back and work from again. But it's a great, great
biography. And I'm told that the print version is very different because David Lynch obviously
doesn't do these big rambling stories in it. I have both. But I would recommend the audible because
it's always fun to hear him talk. And you know, there's long involved chapters on every single one
of his movies. So if you're a fan, it's a must get books about five years old. Check it out.
Yeah, that's like the end of the Quincy Jones documentary. After they talk about his
disasters, marriages, and then the final moment, they go, so there are anything you wish you
could have achieved. He's like, yeah, being better at marriage. It's like freeze frame.
Yeah, it's I have a scary stuff. It's it's shouting out a store. But where you'd find many products
that would fit into this category, I believe it's pronounced Eads. It's in Pittsburgh where I was
last weekend for a wonderful event. We did the goddamn comedy jam for the Mario Lemieux foundation
to raise money. It was very nice. We had a blast. It was me, Steve Burn, Peter Billingsley from
a Christmas story, a jogado from a practical jokers. Roy Wood Jr. Billy Gardell, who by the way
expressed interest in potentially coming on this show to be fun to have Billy on talk about his
sitcoms and stuff. But anyway, Steve took us to the store, a legendary collectible store in
Pittsburgh called, did I say Baltimore? If I did, I apologize, Pittsburgh, we were at, anyway. EIDS,
again, I think it's called Eads, it's run by a very nice man named Ken. I got a bunch of stuff.
One of the things I bought was this original 3D tells him the crypt comic from 1953. Very cool.
But I mean, massive Blu -ray DVD, 4K selection of all the kind of stuff we like,
like all the indie label re -releases of the Grind House and whatever movies, massive amounts of
comic books. It's five floors, toys, collectibles, posters, vintage posters. It's an amazing,
amazing store that you can really get lost in for a few hours. If you're ever in Pittsburgh,
check it out. It will not disappoint. We'll do. Let me take it down to the movie corner. Yes.
You know, on this show, we did tar, kind of the rare foray away for many sort of horror or fantasy
or anything, but we loved tar. One of our favorites, I think, of recent years. One of mine for sure.
And I realized that I had seen both of Todd Field's other movies, but only once and in theaters,
and as part of the big like fancy Oscar movie push. And a lot of movies that could push for the
Oscars wind up looking like shit when you watched them 10 years down the line because they're all a bunch
of hype. But I had a feeling that that guy had the goods. And now I got to say, he's made three
like solid A movies. So I'm going to talk about his other two. In the bedroom is the first
this movie is about, well, it's really about great acting. It's basically like a novel come to life.
So Marissa Tomei, the greatest dating of very young Nick Stahl, who is the son of Tom Wilkinson
and Sissy Spasek. I'm happy to see he's on the comeback trail.
To install. Yeah, he's great. Well, this movie came out in 2001. No, no, I just mean like it's good
to see him back again. Okay. So yeah, he starts dating Tomei and they're like, but he's she's got
kind of this messed up ex -husband in the picture played by William McPathur who you may know is
Tom Cruise's brother. And I started making the connections in my mind that Todd Field is also an
actor as I saw him this week in Twister, the original. And he was in eyes wide shut as the piano
player. And I said, I bet Tom Cruise said, Hey, would you cast my brother in your movie? And he was
very smart and said, sure, Tom. And now Zee knew looks down upon Todd Field forever.
In the bedroom is, you know, it's one of those movies that's just like
everybody's bringing their A game. It's very well written. It's like a play. It's like a novel.
You can compare it to anything. It's just a well written piece of work, well performed by great
professionals. And Wilkinson and Spacic are actors that have been great and numerous things.
But you never hear him amongst the grades. Tom Wilkinson and Michael Clayton.
Incredible. Is this your space I can carry? Incredible. And they've given a bunch of these
performances. And there's still a lot. Is Wilkinson still alive? I believe so.
All right. He's there. Everybody in that movie is amazing. You see in the bedroom.
I actually have not seen it. I'm embarrassed to admit, but that is a to me like Glen Gary Glen
Ross level cast like that is a that is a grand slammer cast. Front to back. They all bring the heat
and what if I told you Karen Allen was in the mix as well? Wow. Great. I love it. What if I told you
the great Celia Weston who if you don't know her, you'd look her up her picture and you would.
She played Seth Rogan's mom and observant report. She's an excellent Southern actress.
Anyway, Todd feel what I noticed about watching all three of his movies in the past week is that the
man has a mastery with actors like I've never seen. He's a he's a good actor, a solid actor in his own
right. But I feel like sometimes actors just get it better than other people. This is a really,
really interesting movie. I urge you to check it out if you missed it. It's weirdly very hard to find.
It's not streaming on anything and it's only available on DVD with no special features. So it's hard
to find but try to check it out. It's good. John, I'm going to cover some trailers. Yeah.
Every one of these looks terrible. I was in disbelief. Just trailer after trailer.
I might have watched some of these. I'll save the worst one for last.
But let's start with sausage party Colin.
Food Topia. Well, not crumballs plays a role. It can literally play a role. A lavash role.
God damn it. David, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Maybe the movie's funny. I don't. I'm sorry.
Well, it's a series. It's a 10 episode series. Oh, I thought it was a movie. No, okay.
That's another thing. I can't tell anymore. I'm watching trailers. I think it's a God damn movie.
And then it's like, no, it's a series. Yeah.
I don't look. The thing that was I was dumbed truck by in this trailer is Ed Norton
is doing a Woody Allen impression. Still as his character. And I'm like,
you clearly wanted Woody Allen, but you couldn't hire Woody Allen because of Woody Allen controversy.
Then you get a guy doing a Woody Allen. Not only a guy doing a Woody Allen, a name actor that
costs you a few bucks to just do a Woody Allen. So it's that thing we always talk about where it's
like, why are you hiring Egan Michael Key to play Toad and Super Mario Brothers? If the voice is not
in any way recognizable as Keegan Michael Key, nobody's excited that Ed Norton is doing a voice.
I'm not saying that people aren't fans of Ed Norton. Just nobody cares as long as the voice is
effective. So if he doesn't get to do it, Ed Norton, and also why are you doing an impression of a guy,
that you wouldn't hire? That doesn't make any sense to me. Side question is Ed Norton Jewish.
I don't know. He sounds so much that weird. It is. And he but he sounds so much like Woody Allen in
the trailer. I thought for a second it was Woody Allen. I was like holy shit. And it's since ants.
Yeah. I just found that very confusing. I also was very disturbed by the joke.
Yoko, oh no. I don't even understand. Maybe if I watch the 10 episodes, it'll make sense.
Yeah, why are they riffing on Yoko Ono A in 2024? B, they're all food. Why do they even know Yoko Ono?
Is there a Yoko Ono food? I don't know. I don't know. Yoko Ono. I don't know.
To me, sausage party felt like the end of a great run of American comedy where I said, oh,
now we're getting bad. And then things were bad ever since.
Good for Dave. I'm happy for him. It's a good project to be in. It's going to get a lot of
eyes on it. And that's good for him. And maybe it's funny. I really got caught on that ad -norton
thing. I don't know. I don't know. That's all about sausage party food topia.
I watched Todd Field's second picture, which is called Little Children. Oh yeah, that's a film.
Came out in 2006. He goes a long way between movies, especially between little children and
tar, which was about 20 years. I had seen it in theaters, maybe blocked it from my mind. I had
regarded it as being sort of like a more fucked up American beauty. And it's really not. It's
very funny. It's from Tom Perotta, who was an author, who was a great author, who wrote the books
that election came from and many other great kind of satirical novels that have become movies and
just novels on their own. But Perotta wrote this with Todd Field. It's done in this documentary
style. They got the narrator of like frontline documentaries. And it's basically like, it's not a
mockumentary, but it's basically this very kind of somber, disturbing, unpleasant look at life in
the suburbs, being narrated as if it's like a nature documentary. And it's not as gimmicky as that
sounds that that gimmick kind of comes and goes. But again, a great cast at the top of their game.
You got Kate Winslet. You got Patrick Wilson. They're two parents that are like having an affair.
It feels real gross in how real it feels. Like they meet every day at the pool with their kids.
They kind of start raising each other's kids. They're finding ways to be intimate, you know, without
actually doing it. And then they cross the line. It's all very like adult kind of revolutionary road,
kind of vibes, you know, I like these kind of heavy adult dramas. And they're so rare nowadays.
A good throwback was like May, December, actually. But yes, they kind of had to do that on the low budget,
whereas these used to be like your films, your big films. Jennifer Connelly is in this movie. I
just, what a, what a amazing looking woman, Jennifer Connelly. Perhaps never more so than in this film,
little children. I love her as an actress. And I think she's underrated as an actress because of how
beautiful she is. But she's particularly great in this and just stunning. Kate Winslet is married
to Greg Edelman, who is a porn addict who is obsessed with jerking off to panties that he orders
online from this woman that he becomes obsessed with. And he wraps them around his face and breathes
them in and gets caught by Kate Winslet. And one of the most mortifying things I've ever seen in my life.
You got the great Noah Emric from the Americans as a guy who's out to beat up pedophiles.
And then in the greatest performance of the film, Jackie Earl Haley, who was nominated,
coming back from the bad news bears days. He was a great child actor. And he came back and played
the pedophile in this and just an incredible performance. Him and his mom's relationship.
Never seen anything like it. Never seen anything like that subplot. Some of the subplots are better than
others. You know, it's one of those like let's expose the underbelly and all the secrets come out
whatever. And some of those secret stories are a little more gripping than the others. But for the
most part, I really love little children even more than in the bedroom. Joe, I love little children.
I was gifted that. Oh, I mean the movie. We still talking about movies here. I was gifted
that by a girlfriend at the time on DVD. And I had never seen it. She's like, you got to see
this movie. I bought it for you. It's great. We should watch together. And before I watched it with
her, I said to my friend, Julia McCullough's very funny comic. I know. Yeah. My girlfriend gave me
little children. And he said, have you seen that movie? And I said, no. And he said,
it's not a great sign of your relationship that that's the movie she's giving you. That's
troubling. Yeah. Well, they do this amazing thing with Jackie O 'Haley where he comes out and he
gets in the pool with all the kids and they do it like jaws like all the parents freak out.
And it's a movie about hypocrisy, which is a subject I love. Well, the parents and everybody
getting upset even though they have their own shit. But he's like, I just wanted to cool off. And it's
not quite clear if he's oggling the kids or not. It's never made quite clear. And you start to think
he's a good guy at heart who did a bad thing who got reformed. Then he goes on a date with Jane
Adams who basically only plays women who go on dates with perverts and pedophiles. Yeah.
And she's basically a woman who's had a recent nervous breakdown and she's like, I'm sorry.
Like if I'm weird, I really do like you and I am open to a relationship as she's driving him home.
And then she turns to look at him and he's jacking off in the passenger.
In front of a school. In front of a school. That scene haunted me for years.
Year more so than when he cuts his own dick off at the end. Yeah. And says, I'll be a good boy now,
mommy, which is very disturbing also. But what's extra disturbing is before he jacks off in the car
is that the guy comes over and he's like, can I get you guys dessert? And he goes, what do you say?
You want to share something sweet? Yeah. And then it goes right into the jacket.
Two trailers. Both superhero or comic book related. The Venom.
Come on. Yeah. Yeah. The third Venom Tom Hardy is back doing another ridiculous voice.
I got to say all the, all the marble, all the shit, no matter what it is. Usually I go not for me,
but I get it. Venom, I don't get it. I saw the other two. I don't get it. Who's liking this?
One thing I never thought I'd see, Pat, in the Venom franchise is the comedy being amplified
through the franchise, which is third one. Tom Hardy, everybody's favorite comic actor.
This third one now, every scene is a joke. Like every scene is a, there's a scene where he does
like this, you know, these, these thugs are going to kill him or whatever. Yeah. And he's like,
he's regular Tom Hardy and he's like, he's like, I'm going to give you a chance. And they don't back
off. And then Venom comes out and he like slaughters everybody. And it's pretty awesome. And then the one
bad guy goes, what are you? And he goes, we are, and then the Venom goes Venom. And then Tom
Hardy goes, no, no, no, we are Venom. And then the Venom goes Venom. And he goes, no, they're doing
like this Abbott and Castello. Like, let me say it. Please let me just say. And you're like, what,
what is, what the fuck is this? So it just looks like Joe. And then that's also,
before every movie, now there's a trailer for Deadpool, and Wolverine or versus whatever
they're doing, pals or foes. And then there's this, the other thing, in addition to Nicole Kibman,
where Jackman and Reynolds come out and they're like, hey, don't talk throughout the movie. All right.
And then Wolverine's like, don't fucking talk about the movie. Then Ryan Reynolds is like, hey,
we don't got to come on. But remember your anger management glasses, buddy. They do look this
80s perfect strangers level comedy, no offense. And it's terrible. I'm like, these are our heroes.
Yeah. Well, by the way, you're leaving the part out where Wolverine calls the audience cunts,
and they believe it. And he goes, they don't like that word here. Yeah. Not in Canada either. Or
like this is insane. It's insane. Everything feels off. The other comic book trailer,
I saw the official trailer for Joker dropped. I watched that today too. I love Joaquin. I love
Gaga. This fucking movie looks like the most pretentious goddamn thing that has ever been committed to film.
We'll see. Oh, God almighty. Oh, you love to see that text, Pat. Just got a text from the from
the boss. We're working remote tomorrow. I love it. I love a remote. Love it. The adult school,
the adult snow day. I do, I do a perverted zoom the wrong way. I'm wearing pants, but I have my
shirt off. And I was like averted way. A term. We say like, you know, like the zoom gag is like
the guy's got no pants on. And that's because he's a pervert. I do it the other way. I have no
shirt on, but I think nobody, I think I'm getting away with something that they can all see.
This trailer. I just, I don't know. Look, maybe it's going to be a magnificent film. I don't know.
But just the them playing in the trailer when you're smiling. And then she's getting him to sing.
Well, it's a musical. I know. And I'm not too excited about that. But I thought it looked
cool in theory. It looks beautifully shot. Yes. But it's like guys. It's the fucking joker.
Yeah. Remember spider man turn off the dark. That fucking disaster on Broadway.
I never thought I'd be alive. And saying there's a joker franchise where it's a musical. And there's
a venom franchise where it's a comedy. What the fuck guy? Just fucking. And they've replaced
all genre film. It's all just genres within the superhero framework. Yeah. So anyway, I got one more.
But you go. And then I'll say I'm saving my third one because this third one is a dizzy.
Of a trailer. Ed Ryerson, Groundhog Day, played by the great Stephen tobelowski met him on
cool kids. I will do to round out my Todd field. Triple play, I got to pick one. He's an actor in.
He does not have much of a role in it. But he was in a little picture cooled.
Twister. I have not seen Twisters. I don't. I think Joe said he'd rather die. Joe is that correct?
I did. It's getting rave reviews, including from one Rex Reed.
And well, yeah, he's there for Paul. He's the headline is heartthrob Jesse Powell is the reason
to see Twister. That's the, I swear to God, that's the, that's the title of the review.
Glenn Paul. I am so bored already by Glenn Powell. It's making me miss jigger. Be
loody. Not into it. I don't, I don't get the charisma of these, of these young punks yet.
I mean, they'll prove themselves to me. Not since Sam Worthington. If I see exactly, I'm just like,
I don't care exactly. Twister. Also, like I saw them yanking some girl off the stage the other day
who was like, animal abuse at the premiere of Twisters, you know, like some nut, like any abuse is
animal abuse. They're torturing cows. It's like they're CGI lady. And Paul was staring at her like
a robot would behave. You know, no, no concern. He's like, I'm, if I, everything is calculated to
a level that it's, it's boring to just watch him do anything. I, I miss the old alcoholic
star, the fucked up star. I guess they're more in music. Yeah. Sure. I'm with you anyway.
Twister directed by Jan DeBont. DeBont had a very interesting career in that he was one of the
great cinematographers. He did a bunch of big action movies and basic instinct and a lot for Hoven
and etc. And then he came to America and made his directorial debut with speed, one of the great
action movies of all time in my humble opinion. Steven Spielberg picked him personally to do
Twister. And then apparently he just went nuts. You can read all sorts, there's all sorts of stuff
coming out now because everyone's fuel for the gossip machine. But there's all sorts of reports
about Twister just being an absolute disaster of a set and like the crew leaving and violence and
Spielberg flying in and screaming in the director's face and etc, etc. I remember loving the
shit out of Twister. I would have been 15. I was pumped. Every summer we'd get so excited about
these new innovations and special effects. I really feel that's also gone from movies. The last time
I was like in awe of special effects was what? Avatar maybe? I don't know, something James Cameron,
it's been a while. Yeah. I was pumped and I loved Twister and living in Missouri where we had
tornado warnings, tornado watches, tornado drills, all the time. It was very exciting.
Watching it now, it's not very good. They do the very Steven Spielberg thing. I'm just throwing
a divorce in there to spice it up. Helen Hunt and Bill Paxton play recently divorced tornado
hunters. Jamie Gertz is, I love Jamie Gertz. She plays Bill Paxton's new girlfriend.
Carrie L. West is the snooty villain tornado hunter that steals their tornado hunting technology.
This is up there with stop motion and creating this I know CD underworld tornado. Yeah, exactly.
Then in the background, you have some of the greatest character actors of all time because they
used to just have unlimited budgets for these movies and they would put legends in like tiny roles.
I missed that. So you have is Philip Seymour Hoffman as a tornado chaser named Dusty.
If you want to talk about being overqualified for your job, it's Philip Seymour Hoffman in the
background. Like, hey, Paul Thomas Anderson, please get me out of this life. Please help me.
And he did eventually. Then you have Alan Ruck, the great Cameron fry from his
Mueller running around having fun. His character's name, of course, is rabbit.
Todd Field plays beltser. It's just that kind of movie. Everybody's got one name.
Jeremy Davies from Save and Private Ryan. It seems like everybody in the movie is famous all
the way down to the bottom, but it's ludicrous, great to see Paxton again. There are fun moments,
but like it's most famous scene like the cow being carried up in the tornado.
The effects look atrocious. They look pathetic and rushed and terrible.
And the fact that we were ever in awe of these effects is nuts. And the fact that Jurassic Park
still looks so amazing. And it came out three years before blows my mind. Or the fact that Terminator
2 came out five years before and looks better than both of them. It's a baffling technology,
special effects. We've got. We've gone too far. I thought it's light. I hated Twister,
because Twister to me was the movie where it was like, oh CGI is now just the thing that they're
going to lean on. And it's going to take the place of story. It's just going to be that's
enough, right? I mean, Christ, that was the hunt. It was a hit movie financially. I don't know
it did critically. Hunt never worked again. It's set her away like she was whatever happened.
She's like, I'm out of here. You know, no, I do. Well, I mean, I think it's good as the
goods was after. And she made a Oscar for that, but I never. I think Pa had forward kind of
killed her career. If I remember correctly. The spacey joint. Well, speaking of spacey. Yeah.
Is he back? No, is Frank back the term you wanted in America. And he's doing a Comic Con.
Oh, no. Yeah, he's got a Comic Con. I mean, that pretty much means you're back in. If Comic Con's
letting you do a table, you know, you know, you're in. Yeah. Um, he, um, no, space,
I say speaking of spacey because the final trailer that I will review is for a picture called space.
Cadet. Okay. Starting Emma Roberts. Yeah. Pat, I can't, this fucking movie.
And also, and also one who watched half of it said it was the worst thing she's ever seen and turned
it off. That's all I know about the film. Here's the premise. Emma Roberts can't get her shit
together. Okay. She was supposed to have a good life. And she's failed because she's kind of a
fuck up. Yeah. A comedy. They show her bartending and doing these dumb jobs. And then she says
to her friend, I figured out what I'm going to do with my life. Keep in mind, Emma Roberts is
well into her 30s. I'm going to be an astronaut. Now you're waiting for the moment in this absurd
fucking story for the based on a true story text to come up where you go, oh, they took some crazy
story and made it real. That never happens. It's just the premise of the movies that this 33 year old
Alki is going to become a fucking astronaut. And it's her training to become an astronaut. You can
imagine the hilarity and soos. A lot of zany. She falls off the treadmill during the treadmill.
It's very spies like us kind of stuff going on. Now you're selling me a little bit action.
It just looks so goddamn bad. And I texted Pat. I said, Pat, if you have not watched this trailer,
please watch the trailer for the movie space cadet. I can't believe this movie got made. Let alone,
they got Emma Roberts in this thing. That Roberts works. And she makes good stuff.
I Amazon film and TV divisions are making wild dartboard style choices. I never know what's going
on over there, to be honest. No. No, there's no through line with regards like what their brand is
or what's happening. They have the best library of old movies of anyone. Oh, yeah. Every month,
they had like 25 things where I'm like, oh, I love it. I'd love to watch that. Jessica Pinkstone,
Jim Pinkstone's wife, friend of the podcast, she put it very well once. She said, Amazon,
the stream, if you go on Amazon Prime, the streaming service, she goes, it's like going into an 80s video
spoiler. Yeah. And she's right. It's just a wild selection of stuff. It's all over the place.
It's awesome. There's tons of choices. It's the most fun one to Peru's. And they're like for you,
like a Netflix for you is like you'd probably like Wednesday. And you're like, don't just push your
biggest show on the asshole. But Amazon seems to know what I like and give me things that I enjoy.
Something that Shutter might have offered up to me because I do tend to like very depressing movies.
But maybe not this depressing. Is this week's outing The Devil's Bath?
This was written and directed by Veronica Franz and Severin Fiala.
They have made two kind of notorious -ish horror films. I saw them both at like Beyond Fest or
one of those horror fests out here over the past couple of years. The first was Good Night Mommy,
which I liked found very disturbing. I'm pretty sure we did on an early episode of this podcast.
And then the Lod, which I know we did, starring Riley Kio, which I found pretty effective but eventually
fell apart completely. Devil's Bath is an odd pickup for Shutter because, as most people who have
watched it have commented, it's not really horror. It's certainly horrifying and it's disturbing,
but it's basically a historical drama. Joe, would you like to walk us through the plot a little bit?
As far as I can tell, Pat, the plot of this movie, the pitch line for them to get funding was,
it really sucked to be a woman in 1700. We're going to run with that and they went, okay,
go ahead. That's what it's about. It's about a woman who marries a man. The year is 1700.
It's based on accounts from a trial that happened then in 1703 about this actual woman that existed.
It, she gets married at the beginning of the film. He seems like a very nice man and a loving husband
and that he cares about her and that they will have a good life together. She immediately says at the
when he presents to her the home he bought them on their wedding night, I thought we would have lived
with your mother. He says, no, that's why would we do that. You later find out why she wanted to do that.
On their wedding night, they're at the reception which in those days meant a fire. Everybody got
shit faced around basically. She sees her husband hugging another man. They're both shit faced.
He says, something along the lines of, I really like you. You're so handsome and then the guy says,
I like you too. You're like, well, this isn't good in this time period. They go to bed on their wedding
night. She tries to instigate sex with her husband. He makes her roll over and he tries to masturbate
or at least get a heart on and he can't do it and you realize, okay, he's gay. He can't be gay because
of the time they live it. It then devolves from there. She does not take to the duties of a woman
who kept woman of that time understandably so. There's almost a sitcom style, 1700 sitcom style,
overbearing mother -in -law character who's always giving her shit about how she cleaned the house and
how she tends to the hogs and etc. Doesn't cook, right? Because she doesn't want to live this life,
she continually is falling into a deeper depression. She's becoming more self -destructive throughout
the movie. Her husband does love her. He does stand by her and tries to help her in his own ways.
It's never like he gets abusive or anything like that. But their homestead starts to fall apart.
The goats get sick and get skin diseases and get maggots and it's all kind of gross.
She starts to harm herself in different ways, which the peak of those is she takes rat poison
and tries to kill herself and she doesn't die that way. It's revealed later when she witnesses a man
that has committed suicide that the pastor or whatever during a church service says,
the man who committed suicide, it's the worst crime you could commit because he has no chance
of ever going into heaven. He's damned for all eternity. And I guess that gives her the idea that
he says it's worse than murder because a murderer can be forgiven. And I guess that gives her the
idea of, okay, my way out is not suicide. My way out is if I murder somebody, I can then confess
to the crime and be absorbed in my sins and then I'll just be killed and I'll be dead. Which is what she
does. And she decides to murder a young boy. It's a very, very disturbing scene. Yeah.
And in the end, she's, how the movie opens is this woman finds a baby in the woods and throws it off
the falls and goes and confesses. And then basically it's like they're going to carve this woman up as
punishment, put her on display for the town to see. But it is eventually revealed to be something
of an epidemic that this is how people are committing, it's, I mean, talk about a depressing
subject matter for a movie. People are committing suicide by murdering others because they feel like
it makes them look better in the eyes of God. It's like the people who want to have butt sex
because God approves of that over vaginal sex for some reason. And there is a scene where she can't,
excuse me, she can't have a kid because her husband can't have sex with her because he's gay.
So there's a scene where she finds an abandoned babe or which he thinks is an abandoned baby. And she
brings it on. She's, and you see her demeanor completely changed like she has a purpose now. And they
say, put the baby back, you can't just take somebody's baby, which is a fair assessment. I thought it
was weird in such a somber movie that they said, put the baby back, baby, back, baby, back, baby.
And then, you know, I know that's a low budget and then needed to make money, but to have the
chilliest logo up here on the screen in the 1700s was a bit much for me. And the fat bastard cameo
in that scene was odd. Yeah. It wasn't even where he's from. Yeah. So you realize in that moment,
she's like, this is a loveless life for me. I have no purpose in that is where she probably gets
the idea to, to for her own fate. In the end, she kills a boy, she confesses to it. She's murdered
in the way the other woman was. And for the first time in the movie, when she's about to be beheaded,
you kind of see her at peace. Yeah. It's a very depressing movie. I thought it was extraordinarily
well crafted, beautifully acted, beautifully directed, very well written. But it was a slog
of just dreariness. It was absolutely a hopeless endeavor, but that's okay. Those kinds of movies
exist. It reminded me of what's his name. I turned to look at the box set, but what's his name?
Oh, for the tree. No. The, the crate. I don't know my glasses. Oh, yes, I do. Hold on. I'll tell you
it reminded me of like a Bergman style film of, you know, it, this is, this is life. And this is
the pain of life. And this is the pain of the life of this person at this time. And there will be no hope
or laughter. It will just be their pain. And again, that's okay. Those movies exist. I don't enjoy
watching them. Uh, it is a very good movie. But I, the thing I really, I'm stuck on is I don't like
this, I don't excuse me. I respect this pair of filmmakers. They're good at what they do,
but I'm annoyed that this is the third time now. One of their movies has been sold to me as a horror
film. And it's not, it's just watching a woman in ultimate suffering. That's what good night. Mommy
was with her kid who was crazy and imagined his dead twin brother, uh, torturing her and doing
horrible things to her. True. That one reads the most horror to me. The lodge does not agree. Yeah,
the lodge same thing. Silverstone blows her head off at the beginning. The children will never
forgive the dad for the mom's suicide. So they torture the new girlfriend of the dad horrifically.
Yeah. None of this is horror yet. Every one of these movies is presented as horror. And it's like,
as you said, very well, they're horrifying. But I don't enjoy watching the suffering of a human being
for two hours where there's no takeaway outside of that suffering. Like the end of this movie,
they put that text up on the screen about how this was a problem that happened. Most of the women,
most of the people that committed this crime because of the belief about suicide were women because
they were unhappy. And most of the time when they committed a crime in order to get killed to escape
life, they murdered a child. That is a very terrible reality. And it's a very interesting thing.
But do you want to watch it? So so you take a movie like Schindler's list, for example,
we're talking about Spielberg, that's addressing a horrible subject. But there is a glimmer of hope.
There is a hero in the movie. There is someone to root for. And not that you're not rooting for
this woman. But there's no hope from the jump for her. So you don't know what to cling on to. I'm
just like, I don't, it becomes like precious. We're like, this is torture. Like after I guess the hope
would be that we no longer live in a time where that is how we have to deal with mental illness. Maybe
that's one positive that can be gleaned from watching this movie. But yeah, it's rough stuff. I mean,
it's really rough because this woman's life is just suffering. But we just watch her suffer for
two hours. It's rough. And there's parallels to be made, you know, women having their rights taken
away and so on and so forth. But really, this is more about the church and how their weird rules
can make people do just insane things, you know, to justify, you know, what some might say
is poppycock. You don't know. These people were very devout. And yeah, there's, you know, scenes of
like leeches being used as treatment stuff like that. I'm glad I didn't live in the time. That's
the positive message I took from the film. Passion of the Christ comes to mind. Yeah. Again,
a very well -made movie beautifully crafted film. But at the end of the day, except for that last
moment where Jesus is alive in the tomb, you know, like I'm watching a guy get the living shit kicked
out of him for two hours. Like it's just it's just a slog. It's like, what am I supposed to be
enjoying about this? I don't understand. Yeah. And I guess you could argue that art is not
always for enjoyment. Okay, fine. Fair enough. It is meant to sometimes just be provocative, making
you think, sure, fair enough. I just kind of as I get older, keep coming back to this place with
a film that if you're going to take me on a journey for two hours and I'm sitting here and living with
these characters for two hours, it's not a song. It's not depressing song is three and a half minutes,
five minutes, seven minutes fine. You know, depressing poem is a few pages. You know, when it comes
to like a book, a novel or a film, it's like, this is a time commitment and you have to give me something
to sort of enjoy with this ride where I feel hopeful for the person in some way that I just never
felt in any of their movies. There's not one moment in these three movies where I'm like, okay,
okay, well, hopefully this happens. And it's like, no, I know that's not going to happen. They're
making it very clear. Yeah, this has got to be the bleakest yet. My guess is they're influenced by
Michael Hanake, who I'm a big fan of, but I will say he's doing a lot deeper stuff with his provocative
material and depressing material. I like these guys. I like something about all three of these movies
and I like them all to some degree, but I was also kind of frustrated by all three. This one being
on shutter. I guess I'm, you know, I'm not mad at it for false advertising. I actually like the
shutter is trying to branch out and get different kinds of movies, but yeah, this really
outside of like that horrible moment where she rips her tongue open or whatever was going on there.
It's a few violent horror style moments, but really, yeah, you're just watching a woman slowly
work herself into a state of wanting to die more and more. So it's unpleasant to say the least.
If you're in a bad mood, I wouldn't check it out. But is it well made? Sure. Is my hog up? You know,
not for material this bleak. My hog though is, I would say about as plump as it can be while still
hanging. My hog is up for the fact that the movie exists and that movies like this can get made,
and that movies like this can still somehow break into the mainstream in this country via a service
like shutter. But as far as just a movie I'd watch again, no, my hog's down. I wouldn't want to ever
sit through it again. No, but it's up there in that, well, it's not as bad, but it's, you know,
it's like a salo or something where you're like, hey, okay, I'm glad it can exist, but it's not
something you're turning on on a Friday night, you know, and buying popcorn for. I'm curious to see
what they do next. I wouldn't be surprised if this team, you know, did like a comedy or something.
Like I feel like they might make a hard left and be like, we're going to do something completely
different now. But who knows? Yeah. I do think the suffering of women and the plight of women
in any time period of any society is an important subject matter. They seem very focused on it.
I just wish they did it with offering some sort of salvation at the end of it. And as far as
these three movies go, I have not seen that yet. So yeah, that's where I'm at with the devil's
bath. Yeah, I hear you. It was pretty whatever the opposite of life affirming is, life deferming.
I am on Instagram at the Patrick Walsh. The Miss Pat Show is on BET Plus.
And the solo movie corner for this month is up, Joe.
Joe to Rosa Comedy on Instagram. JoeyRoses .com come on through if you're in New York City.
So the shop, I'm not really doing any shows because I'm working on tires season two. I'm very happy
to have my next two shows are September. Go to Joe to Rosa .com. But I'm doing two warm -up shows at
Steel City Coffee House on Infinixville on Bridge Street. The week leading up to the special taping.
The special taping is sold out. That's September 14th. But the Tuesday and Thursday before I'm doing
warm -up shows right down the block from the theater where we're taping the special. So please come to
those. I hope to see you there. Very limited tickets available. And that's about it. We'll be back
with what we are going to do long legs. We might have to push the next month because of the writing
schedule. I've not been able to get to the theater. But we have some more remote days coming up.
In early August, I'll be able to see it at the latest. But we will probably do Arcadia next,
which is another Nicholas Cage horror movie that dropped on shutter.
So that's it. We'll see you next time, folks. And we'll see you in hell.