I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, and when the sound of your screams becomes
a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say, I'll see you in hell, you know I will, I'll see
you in hell, you know I will.
Folks, it's we'll see you in hell.
Time to talk about movies.
I'm Joe DeRosa.
And I'm Patrick Walsh.
How are you, Joe?
Pat, I'm here recording us on the, this is the inaugural episode of we'll see you in
hell on the new computer I had to purchase after my other computer was stolen from me.
So walk us through.
Testify, Joe.
Testify.
My house got robbed, fans already know.
Thank you to the fans, Emily wrote to me and said everybody wants to start a GoFundMe and
send you money.
I said absolutely not, but the gesture was very, very sweet.
So thank you all for your support, your interest, your kind words, your kind messages.
Thank you.
And I, you know, here we are, this is it.
This is the first time recording at my new desk, which he did not steal, that now has
a new computer.
You just bought that for daddy.
That was a little treat for you.
I needed a new desk and I said I can't wait to sit down and work on my computer at this
new desk.
And then the apartment got broken into that day, all computers stolen.
Yeah, it tends to be whenever you dare the world, the world takes that dare.
Yeah, just gives it to you.
Yeah.
I'm sorry to hear it, Joe.
Sorry to hear it.
Thank you.
Um, it's been one week since you left with me.
It's been, no, I was, I woke up today and I, I, I always know that I'm in a good place
when I'm laughing at how bad things have gotten.
I actually mean that because if you can laugh at it, you're in a Joker headspace,
you're good.
You might be a little insane, but you're, you're good.
It's a strange perspective to say you're in a Joker headspace.
You're good.
If you're sad, then you know that I just, uh, it's not my own life, you know, I'm
just sort of observing the world fall apart.
I'm not getting off on it.
I'm not, I'm not twisting my nipples to it.
I'm just acknowledging that the world has come to its natural end.
So like when Joe says he got robbed to me, I don't even know if that would phase
me at this point, because we're in the end times, it's just part of what would happen.
It's, uh, I don't know what the hell is going on at this point.
Uh, I've been waking up, uh, protesting.
I've been getting together with the, with the writers protesting the studios.
And, um, this is my last to the line.
Like, like Sally field, you got a kerchief over your head.
Oh yeah.
Except the difference is, um, the, the union listened to Sally field and, uh, they
enabled them to make some sort of changes in the workplace.
Now, um, quick question, just quick question.
Do you carry the lunchbox with the curved top with the thermos in it?
Okay.
All right.
That's all I need to know.
I also wear a very tight t -shirt and I nip it up for when I talked to the board,
you know, cigarette pack rolled up, rolled up in the, yeah, exactly.
I got exactly.
Um, no, it's just bad.
I mean, they, the writers guild basically said to the studios, i .e.
your Netflix, your Sony, your, your Amazon, whatever, Hey, we need a small
percentage because you guys are making a massive percentage, really just very
small gains, like if somebody watches an episode of stranger things 4 billion
times, the writer should probably be compensated for that.
And the studios have across the board said, no, we disagree.
They're w they're willing to bend on nothing.
And there's also an attitude of like, fuck you, we're fine.
We don't need you.
So now I don't know where we go.
They're also saying like, we, by the way, AI that's going to replace you and, um,
enjoy it.
You can't put any control on it because we're going to go ahead and start
doing business with AI now.
I snapped it.
It's all getting wild.
They're, they're done with, they're done with the human component of writing.
And, uh, we're doomed there.
There's just, there's no hope for art at this point.
I don't think.
Well, there, there, there's hope for art.
Uh, uh, the, the, uh, commodity of art is probably going away.
Yeah.
You got to circumvent.
I mean, it's just, we're, we're talking about monopolies like to, as Joe's been
saying since the first day on this podcast, there's no difference between a
Netflix and a Trump, but they're showing that very, very clearly now they're
because it's become very capitalist.
They're just like, fuck you.
I know you do the work.
I know we need you, but sorry, if you're going to bitch about it,
we'll find another way.
And the truth is I watched murder mystery too, this morning.
The truth is you almost don't have to try.
And they know that on the studio side.
Well, that's what I've been saying about the AI thing is they're going to,
from day one, I said, they're going to use this thing, this fucking thing.
It's already happening on Tik TOK with 24 hour Seinfeld.
Uh, and they're going to use this thing and they're going to do first drafts
with it, and then they'll pay one writer instead of 12 to beef that draft up and
make it sound normal or better.
And I was like, that first draft ain't going to be far off from what's getting
turned in anyway, because of, of the, the way they've reduced writing into, into
this paint by numbers, you know, sterile fucking ball, this, uh,
yeah, they want you to write exactly by numbers because the executives have only
learned how to do things by those numbers.
So you can't go out of those numbers.
And then all the networks act like they're, uh, they're for the artist and
they're, they're like, test the boundaries.
No, you're not.
No, no, you're not.
That might've been 10 years ago.
Now we are, we are talking about a product delivery system where every two
weeks they dump the latest Sandler and any two stars, you pair them up and you
shit them into our mouths and America goes literally because I only pay for
Netflix and have no other options.
I will open my mouth and swallow this turd that you are presenting me with.
And that is the current entertainment system.
I want everybody to remember this.
I want everybody to remember this when at the next big award show, they tell you
who you need to cancel and who you need to support and what you need to do to be
a better person and all these things.
I hope the fucking public finally wakes up that this export of Hollywood is
vicious.
It is soulless.
It does not give a fuck about the human condition or, or the human race.
And yet they are going to continue to try to tell you that they can lead by
example.
It's disgusting.
I knew this was going to happen with AI.
I, I, we were recording taste buds today.
I snapped at homeless pimp because he brought up, uh, he, he pulled up the AI
engine on the screen and I go pimp, get that fucking thing off the screen right now.
I was like, this is half the problem with everything.
Everybody just keeps feeding this thing like, oh, it's just fun.
Yeah.
And it's like, it's like, you know, it's
you ask Jeeves one too many times and suddenly Jeeves has your job.
You asked Jeeves too much and now Jeeves is saying, Hey, while you're down there,
why don't you suck me off bitch?
One of my favorite, whoa, whoa, whoa, Jeeves.
What what's going on?
And then Jeeves is forcing you.
It's my favorite.
My favorite Andy Kindler joke of all time is, uh, I've got terrible financial sense.
10 years ago, I was offered an opportunity to invest in Google and I dumped all my
money into ask Jeeves.
We all thought that was going to stick for a while, didn't we?
Uh, but anyway, um, it's a hard state of affairs.
Uh, Elon Musk is now so, so, so the worst part of all this has begun the, I kept
saying to my friends, actually to Pinkstone, Pinkstone and I have talked
to him at length about this and I kept saying to him, the biggest fear I have
is what this is going to do to the already shattered trust of the public AI
and what it's doing already and what it can create.
You know, this thing came out the other day where Biggie raps a Nas, the
Nas song, New York state of mind.
And it literally sounds like Biggie just did a cover of the song.
And it's cause AI learned Biggie's voice and just recreated it to not.
It's like, I saw something the other day where Ariana Grande was singing and then
she like started sucking somebody off and I was like, Holy shit, Ariana.
And then I fell for it.
I'm like, Oh, maybe, maybe on stage in front of millions, Ariana Grande
started sucking somebody off.
Stupid.
So it's, so I kept saying the biggest fear I have is what this is going to do to
the already shattered trust of the public.
They're, they're not, nobody's going to believe anything.
They see a read anymore.
We were already teetering on it.
Now it's like, people are definitely not.
And now everybody's going to run with that.
You think everybody's an armchair scientist and doctor and whatever else
you do, whatever you think that everybody's coaching from the
fucking living room now.
This, this is going to be a shit show.
So that's already started happening.
There's now articles coming out today and yesterday about that.
And I wasn't concerned about AI until the studios were like, yeah, we're
not giving you anything there.
I was like, Oh, they know more than we do.
And they know that that's the future we're fucked because that's why they're
not willing to negotiate on it.
So, so that's, that's happening, right?
Yep.
And now because you could reasonably make the argument of, well, that
didn't happen, it was fake.
It was AI, Elon Musk, who gained a few points with me by being one of the
billionaires that spoke out against AI and said, we need to pump the brakes
here and take a breath, uh, shattered all that goodwill by coming out now.
And he's already saying he didn't say and do things that he is confirmed as
saying and doing on video and saying it was AI, it was bullshit.
It wasn't me.
We're done.
We are done.
It's over.
Uh, yeah, I mean, it's, it's going to lead to a collapse of the judicial system.
I mean, it's, I, I'm not trying to be some sort of a basement nut job.
It's just simply looking at facts.
Like we're, we're, uh, we're in a bad place.
Because they can kind of control everything and you don't know what
you're looking at and if you're shown something that's to me always been the
one way to know that it's true.
And definitely that's the way for people older than me in this country.
So I just think we're fucked.
Yeah.
There's that band in, um, I guess they were an English band.
They recorded a bunch of music and it sort of sounded like Oasis.
Okay.
And then they used AI to turn it into an Oasis album and like this new Oasis
album where it sounds exactly like Liam Gallagher or whatever his name is.
And it's not him.
He's never touched it.
He's never, he has nothing to do with it.
What are the melodies?
Uh, I don't know.
I haven't heard it, but it's a thing.
And it's one of those things.
That to me is something you can never, you can never mimic a melody, a story,
et cetera, like they can come up with templates of things, but characters,
emotions, all that stuff.
It's happening.
It's not, no, that's not true at all.
Listen to this Biggie thing.
It's like he's, it's not like, Oh, that kind of sounds like a
computer that sounds like Biggie.
It sounds like notorious BIG learned the Nas song and then
did a great rendition of it.
It's got all the right emotion, all the right inflection.
They were already, I was already concerned.
We were warned about this in the Gemini man.
Listen, Will Smith, the, who would have thought, who would have thought
that demolition man, Gemini man, all the man movies were warning us and
see no man and see no man was there and see no man should have warned us that
we were going to be dominated by this actor for the next year of our lives.
Um, but here's the thing is, um, with, I was already worried when they were like,
you know, that article came out a few months back where they said James Earl
Jones has officially signed over his voice to Lucasfilm and Disney for them
to use for the rest of time, they use this new voice generator software.
He went into the studio for a few hours.
He said a bunch of stuff.
Now this thing can create James Earl Jones, saying anything as
Darth Vader or whatever, which is what they did on Obi -Wan.
Most of the,
it makes me want to die.
It makes me want to die.
I don't even care about Star Wars.
It just makes me want to die.
Most, most of the Darth Vader, um, dialogue on Obi -Wan was done with this.
My mic is moving.
It's, oh geez, listen to that.
Most of the Darth Vader voice on Obi -Wan was done with this software.
Very, very little.
And you can tell they made videos on YouTube where they're like, here's how
you know it's real James Earl Jones.
Um, but you couldn't tell when you were watching it at all.
Yeah.
Like the worst I thought was there were times where I was like, is that just a
guy impersonating James Earl Jones?
It's pretty good if it is, you know, so I was like, that's disheartening
that like that's possible and already AI has clipped, has clipped it.
Val Kilmer made a video where he was thanking these scientists at some
university or something, and he's like, they gave me my voice back through
painstaking, whatever they were able to mimic my voice and this program.
If I type into it, it'll say anything.
And it sort of sounds like me.
Like they gave me my voice back.
Yeah.
It was this groundbreaking years of work and now AI is just like, I got it.
I can already do it.
Like, it's like, this is fucking insane.
Yeah.
So I don't think that it's going to create machines that
destroy us like Terminator.
But I do think what it's going to do is
destroy us in more, more insidious ways.
They'll, they'll, they'll destroy us by replacing us in every aspect of our lives.
Well, that'll happen.
And I also think that AI will be the disease, like in planet of the apes,
like in planet of the apes, it's the airborne thing that kills off the human
race and then the left wars with the apes.
I think that that's what AI will do.
AI will create such dissension amongst people that this is going to, it'll light
all the fuses that we, where we kill each other.
It'll be, you know, that's what you see it at the self checkout.
You see it at the self checkout.
How quickly this breaks down.
Every time I go there, I have three items.
I realized too late that you can't check out alcohol for some reason, even though
there's somebody there to check your ID, you still can't do it for some reason.
So then you got to go somewhere else.
They don't have bags there.
They, they don't, uh, you scan it, you put it down.
It doesn't weigh right.
So it beeps at you.
They, they never get it right.
You know, but we're just, we've been acting like this was a
good thing now for 25 years.
It's putting your, your aunt out of a job.
I don't know about your aunt.
My grandma used to, my grandma worked for 50 years.
As a cashier at a grocery store.
It's a, you know, that's how she put my, she put three kids through school
being a cashier at a grocery store.
I'm going to, I'm going to pitch this.
I'll pitch this joke to, uh, we should start talking about movies.
I mean, we're, we're Jesus Christ, but I'll pitch this joke to
socio -political comedians.
I'll pitch it to Dennis Miller.
Somebody get me Dennis Miller.
Somebody get me, uh, is, uh, is, uh, who was the guy, uh, from the sixties?
Narrow it down a little here.
The political guy from the sixties.
No, it always bring the newspaper on stage.
Mort Saul, Lenny Bruce, Mort Saul.
Here's, here's the bit.
Yeah.
How, how about this artificial intelligence?
You know, folks, I always thought that needed to be preceded by
actual fucking intelligence.
That's good.
I think it, I think it works.
That'd be the cold, that'll be the cold open button on my HBO talk
show that cuts to the credits.
I mean, there's still the remnants of the last collapse of society hanging
over the Hollywood Hills as we just kick into another one.
That's, that's, that's the saddest part is we just keep papering up over it.
Like I was out there like striking and, and, and picketing.
And I'm like, they've already told us they don't care.
That's the thing you're out there.
Usually you're out there trying to make a difference.
They looked us in the eye and said, we don't give a fuck.
Yeah.
What do you, what do you do it out there?
Hey, so what are we doing?
Yeah.
Remember when they occupied wall street, boy, did that change things.
What are you doing?
Well, I mean, when I'm out there, you do, it's not like I feel empowers, but you
know, it's nice being out with writers and sharing the stories and et cetera.
But at the same time, it's like, they've already told us, you know, like we, we
are looking to them and saying, Hey guys, obviously you need what we have here.
Could you throw us a bone?
And their answer is no.
Then why do we keep stepping up to the table?
You know, I just don't understand, but I'm doing it.
Nightmare.
We've just, we've ruined everything.
I on a, on a plus note, I do like the shade Jenny Ortega is receiving.
Of course.
Yeah.
Uh, she's, she's going to be the next one.
I've had enough of, uh, you read those quotes about her on just talking to, I
mean, get the fuck out of here.
But that's, that's another symptom of this culture.
It is giving the power to the people who get the clicks and
not the people who put you there.
All right, folks.
Uh, start to the month here.
Hard disaster.
That was a hell of a bad time.
New psycho.
That was a hell of a new psycho.
I mean, look, that's where I'm at waking up.
I'm out there picking it.
We're picking it in all these studios.
It's a true new psycho.
Uh, we're not picking in shutter because I feel like they can barely
keep the lights on as it is.
Shutter's like, I mean, God bless shutter.
They're like, you made a, you made a movie for $10 in one room.
Yeah.
We'll take it.
I know.
Well, Joe Bob put them on the map there and every week he's like, well, we
would have loved to get you that movie, but unfortunately there's only a
$20 licensing fee that shutter will pony up there.
They're airing.
And by the way, not a slide against the films of, of Mexico, but they
were airing on Cinco de Mayo, like a law, like a lost there.
They're like almost like movies they're finding, like they're not even readily
available and Joe Bob has nothing to say about them because they're not good.
They're barely like movies.
So like this whole thing that I look forward to now in Joe Bob, they can't
even afford to rent good movies for him to watch.
So you just sit there with him trying to pretend like Savage Camp from
1988 is an American classic.
This is poor Joe Bob.
This is like, he's looking, you know, he's in his twilight years.
He's like, is this, this is it.
This is the last eight years.
I got to watch some cannibal hit movie from fucking Argentina says a
masterpiece for which board it's like, really, really Joe Bob, you thought
the which board was worthy of four stars.
Starring Tony contain another new psycho.
You told me the other day, they are remaking which board movie
that bombed the first time.
It is terrible.
Remaking which board, um, absolute madness.
They're also remaking.
What did that, what else did they just announce here?
Cause who's doing which board?
Somebody big.
You announced, uh, they, they just said it was also, they named it.
They sort of a sequel to something or something or other.
Well, there's a, a which board remake.
Oh, I'm sorry.
More join the cast of which from the dream warriors director.
Oh, from Chuck Russell.
I like Chuck Russell.
All right.
If they got Chuck Russell, I'll buy it.
He's probably a hundred years old.
What the hell are we talking about here?
I don't know.
I simply don't know.
Chuck Russell get a which board remake Greenland.
How is that even happening?
Here's what I do.
My aim Bialik is saying goodbye to call me cat.
Oh, well, what a sharing Joe.
She's sharing where the characters would have ended up.
You know what?
Fuck you.
We made a lot of people laugh during COVID in ways that at first seemed
impossible.
Bialik shared.
No you didn't, Mayim.
No you didn't.
Mayim?
Miriam?
Miriam, your show was one of the worst shows ever made.
Like I've watched a lot of terrible television.
This was one of the worst shows ever made and you should be ashamed of yourself.
And you didn't make anybody's life better during the pandemic.
If anything, you made it significantly worse, especially now that every time I
think of Jeopardy, I got to see you.
Who were you?
I don't, I don't hate her as a host of Jeopardy, but that show, call me
cat really sucked.
Call me a piece of shit.
Cause that's what I am.
Oh God.
Um, so she's okay.
So she's sharing that.
Yeah.
Okay.
Um, let's get to the movies.
Let's get to that movie corn.
I'd like to kick things off.
Speaking of shit with murder mystery too.
I mean, we're not trying anymore, gang.
We're, we're simply not trying.
This, this movie is a non -entity.
Usually they pad the cast with like all these like funny supporting players.
Honestly, I wouldn't have hated seeing a Keegan in the mix.
We don't have a single amusing performer in the entire film.
Here's the supporting cut comedy cast, Mark strong, a dramatic actor, Melanie
Lauren from inglorious bastards, Jodie Turner Smith.
I don't know who that is.
Okay.
Uh, okay.
I know she wasn't in regards to the movie.
She was given nothing to do.
The movie, um, it's a franchise that doesn't never takes off.
We never liked the franchise in the first place.
No one ever said we want more murder mysteries.
It's a, it's not knives out where there was a demand for more of this.
They're thrown into like a cheaper, easier sequel.
The action is pathetic.
Well, I don't know what to say.
The jokes are bad.
There you go.
I truly do have a great admiration for Adam Sandler.
Uh, but he is the stern of Netflix.
Yeah.
Like they just cut some deal with him where it's like, whatever
you need, Adam, we're here for you.
Yeah.
You know, he might not have left his house to shoot this movie.
And that's, that's how they do these things these days.
Well, serious XM just announced suddenly they're going to build
new studios in Miami and Oh, what a coincidence.
That's where Stern's been spending most of his time.
It's like, yeah, follow him now down to Miami.
He already, he already, don't get me started.
He's fucking greedy pigs.
These greedy fucking pigs.
Anyway, um, I watched, uh, I'm sorry though, the beginning, the
beginning of murder mystery.
I had to point this out.
It's clear.
The movie is 90 minutes, but not because you feel like they've made a good
decision, uh, and decided to make a comedy 90 minutes, there's a first
act of this movie with big stars in it that didn't work to such an
egregious extent that it's reduced to a clip show package and added to
the top of this movie, Joe.
Now you're, I almost urge you if you have Netflix to put this on so
you can see what I'm talking about.
They, they clearly had a first act of the movie that didn't work.
So they just chop up the events of that first act and present it to
you like a previously on, but it's not stuff from the first movie.
It's another case with Annie Momolo from the Fletch movie and like big
actors in it, but they just botched it.
So they go, ah, we'll throw this.
That's the level of laziness.
Now you're not even reshooting it.
They're going, ah, they'll get the gist.
Just throw it up there.
I mean, it's really pathetic.
Here we are probably cost $200 million.
Uh, it's like, it's just at a time when, when, when writing is so undervalued
to, to you look at this, it's like, well, yeah, yeah, there, there's no point
to even writing a script anymore.
They go, ah, we get the idea of that.
Just chop it into a few moments and throw it up there.
You know, like we've lost, we've lost Joe.
What did you watch?
Well, tonight I watched the movie Cyrus starring Judah, Jonah Hill,
John C.
Riley, Marissa Tomei.
Uh, this is a film about a young man played by Jonah Hill named Cyrus who
clearly wants to fuck his own mother played by Marissa Tomei.
They don't come right out and say it, but there is a scene where he goes into the
bathroom to use it while she's in a shower in the shower with a see -through
like shower door.
Yeah.
It's a weird scene.
It's odd.
Uh, it's the movie has a few laughs in it.
It's, it's disturbing though.
Like the way there's a scene where they go to the park and they, and Marissa
Tomei and Jonah Hill like wrestle.
It's weird.
It's just weird.
And it goes past a place of this is an overbearing mother or, or this is a kid
who's got a mom syndrome or whatever.
And at the end of the move, and then John C.
Riley falls and Marissa Tomei fall in love with each other.
And Jonah Hill tries to sabotage it.
And at the end of the movie, Jonah Hill has this big breakdown where he says, I
might be a seriously dysfunctional and fucked up person, and that's quite
evident, but it never goes far enough in either direction where you're like, this
is too weird to be a comedy and this is too comedic to be a drama.
Like, I just don't really get what the point of it is.
Uh, end of the movie, it says written and directed by the, by the duplass
bros.
I mean, these guys can piss in the wind against a Big Mac rapper and have it
walk and turned into a goddamn, uh, uh, feature film.
I don't understand it, but, but they had their period in the, in the, when I first
moved out to LA, like late 2000s, where, as I was telling Joe earlier, if a white
guy was taken a trip, they'd make that a movie, a $20 million movie.
Uh, there was a movie with Ed Helms called like Jack goes to his mom's
basement.
It was, it was somebody lives in some, some name, certain name.
John who lives at home.
That's what it was.
And it was Siegel and Ed Helms.
Jesus Christ.
Imagine in like the forties when you got to go in and you got 30 seconds to like
pitch David O.
Selznick on what the next script is going to be.
And you go in and you go, here's the next title, Dave, John who lives at home.
The duplass brothers.
Sound good.
You got it.
You got a big electric star.
I have Ed Helms, I go, Hey, here's $20 million.
The duplass brothers in that time period, pitching a movie literally would go
picture the poster.
Are you ready?
Five white people with beach chairs.
You're like, that was literally the billboard for their HBO show.
It was like, how sickeningly sickeningly white can you make something
fucking look right now?
Put a bunch of people on the beach with beach chairs and that's the poster.
And I'm supposed to go, Oh, let me race home to see this goddamn thing tonight.
See, here's the thing with the duplass is, and they're by the way, they're
doing what everyone else in this business is doing.
I'm not criticizing them.
I actually went when they first came out, their little thing.
I agree with you.
Cyrus is one of their best movies, but it doesn't move enough for, sorry.
It doesn't move the needle enough into the comedy or the thriller realm.
So you're left with nothing.
It's this whole mumble core movement that the, honestly, the duplass
brothers weren't even pioneers of.
They kind of absorbed it, but they let them make, as we've been saying,
seemingly a hundred movies and TV shows for HBO, big places, Netflix, whatever,
with interchangeable casts of bearded white 30 something males and long
suffering, attractive 30 something women.
They did this for 10, they did every possible combination of white people
you could do and they squeezed every possible scent you could out of it.
Then Hollywood changed and now we're about diversity and suddenly those
duplass brothers who have made a hundred million dollars off of the whitest
product imaginable.
Well, wouldn't you know now they're obsessed with diversity, Joe.
Isn't that crazy?
We don't even want to make any, any projects that aren't about diverse
voices anymore.
That's really their MO.
I've met with them and you're like, Oh, okay, fine.
You know, good on you.
If that's what you want to do, that's look good on you.
If that's what you would want to do, because you wanted to actually do it.
Fuck you.
If you're doing it because it's going to keep your ass employed, it's just gross
because it's keeping the lights on your projects, your white people projects
weren't going anymore.
So you switched it up and then act like you're ashamed of, Oh boy.
It's just, it drives, it all drives me nuts and there's no way out.
And the, and the duplass brothers don't deserve this either.
I'm just clearly in a ranting mood.
Oh, who gives a shit about either of them.
Good.
Yeah, it's just, you know, it is what it is.
The, the, the
I'll own all the duplass statements though.
All the duplass statements came from, I don't care.
The duplass now are documentary filmmakers and they do good
documentaries and good on them.
Um, I mean, you see what vice is churning out now.
These fucking charlatans now they got, they put up this, what really
happened to Bob Saget documentary.
They're interviewing internet sleuths, internet sleuth.
This is what vice has now sunk to.
First, they exploited homeless people and fat people and made fun of all of it
and acted like complete shits.
Then, uh, when they had the split of the three of them and, and all of a sudden
the guy that stayed behind wanted to look woke cause he was worried about what
Gavin McGuinness and whatever we're doing out there, uh, then all of a
sudden they became the woken, they became the investigative network that's
going down to like Bay or to, to Beirut or is it down across to Bay, wherever
the hell Beirut is, you know what I mean?
And they're in some fucking cocaine jungle, uh, talking about the issues
in hushed tones cause they don't want to get assassinated or whatever.
And now that that, that all the steam ran out of that fucking woke engine.
Now they're, they're doing exploitative like docu series thing.
It's like, what the fuck guys get your shit together.
We're in a place now.
I, so my buddy, Ian stayed with me for a week.
He comes home the other night from a meeting and I'm watching this new show
on HBO max cause I like Jesse Plemons.
Called love and death.
I don't know anything about it.
There really could not be a more generic, boring title than love and death.
It's awful, but one of the great Woody Allen Keaton dying Keaton movies.
Already a film by the way.
Uh, I noticed, I noticed there's a new movie on prime called
what's love got to do with it.
So that I don't care anymore.
So that I was like, Oh, they made another Tina Turner thing.
Nope.
They just called it that.
So where was I?
You watched love and death with Jesse love and death.
Ian comes in.
He goes, what's this?
I tell him he watches it.
He goes, wait a minute.
This is feeling familiar.
Did, when did this come out?
Have I seen this?
I go, no, it's brand new.
It's just came out today.
He's like, no, I know this story.
I know this story.
We start kind of sleuthing it together.
Come to find out this mini series.
Love and death is based on the exact same case as the Hulu mini
series, candy with Jessica Beale that came out one year ago.
So Ian goes, this is the exact same thing.
He has me bring up candy on Hulu.
They're using the same sets.
They're using the same sets or at the very least they're using the
same photos, so they recreated the sets in the same way.
Uh, one has, you know, what's her face, uh, Jessica Beale and Melanie Linsky.
One has, as I just told you, Plemons and Elizabeth Olsen,
but it's the same story.
So what we're getting now is streamers doing big budget, big star
takes on the same cases, then they'll also exploit the case as a documentary.
So you're getting remakes of documentaries of remakes that are
already existing on other channels.
I guess the thinking is the HBO Max brass is like, well, I hope our, our
people don't have Hulu so they don't know what candy is.
I don't get it.
What is your thinking there?
Or they think they loved candy.
They'll watch it again.
Maybe so.
Maybe so, but it's the exact same story with the exact same beats.
Baffling.
Um, while I have you here, I might as well talk about that one.
Since I've got you, but, uh, love and death is a very generic,
by the numbers thing.
It's Elizabeth Olsen wants to have an affair.
So naturally she picks Jesse Plemons.
Who's sort of at his most.
Not hot looking and Olsen is at her most hot looking.
It's wild.
Um, Plemons, not since Walter Mathau, who was still more Debonair looking.
But I mean, God, I want to be wild.
It's like Ernest Borgnein being like a sex symbol or something.
It's crazy.
Anyway, I've seen four of these episodes and you see Plemons fucking
at length in each of them, uh, missionary on top.
He's in like a wife beater, but then, so I'm watching all this and I'm like,
all right, so I get him, they got him in the white beat or whatever else.
And I, they understand that we don't necessarily want to
see Jesse Plemons naked.
Then they cut into the shower and there's Plemons naked.
It's just constant nudity.
It's like, guys, we miss nudity.
We didn't miss Jesse Plemons nudity, you know?
So the series is, um, you know, it's, it's, uh, as it's typical with these things,
it's explosive subject matter done in a very kind of, Ooh, aren't we daring
manner by David E.
Kelly, who does big little lies and those kinds of shows.
And it just winds up feeling like every other, one of these limited
series where like a woman has a secret and then she bakes a pie.
But you know, it's just like, who gives a shit, who gives a shit about any of it?
Yeah.
Uh, I w I'll say a positive.
I watched, uh, John Mulaney, baby J, uh, loved it.
Thought it was excellent.
Good to see John back out there doing his thing.
Uh, I loved how dark it was.
I loved how bitter it was.
And can I say, I saw him do that about a year and a half ago and it
was darker and bitter back then.
He actually cleaned it up a little bit.
Uh, a friend of mine pointed out something and he meant it as a criticism.
It made me like, like it even more, but he was like, I don't know, man, he seems
mad he got caught and that he can't do drugs anymore.
And I was like, yeah, that's exactly what he seems like.
And I, it makes me like it even more.
Yeah, that's, that's the full vibe.
He's giving off.
I don't think he's trying to give any vibe other than that.
He seems like a guy who desperately wants to use again.
Uh, it was great.
It, it had all the, it had all the Mulaney tropes that you want.
It was his personality through and through, but it was just a very
different subject matter and a very different tone, um,
and about an hour 20 and he didn't mind it.
No, I watched the whole thing straight through.
Can't tell you the last time I did that with a, with a comedy special.
I just sat there like, I guess, well, I did it with the rock one and then, but
this one, I just thought it was really, really great.
So, uh, baby J rock Johnson's standup.
I, you know, I watched the, the, the, the Chris rock things.
I want to, you know, it was, it was obviously, uh, there was a
lot of clamoring around it.
Uh, anyway, uh, John Mulaney, baby J Joe Bob says, check her out.
Love baby J big fan.
Um, I guess I'll throw out air, you know, because it really fits
with what we're talking about.
This is a movie being floated as a potential best picture nominee
directed by multiple Oscar nominee, Ben Affleck.
Um, this is a movie about Nike's.
It is about how Nike, a major corporation got Michael Jordan to be
the face of Air Jordan shoes.
So literally now we're celebrating brands as movies.
There's a discussion in this where Ben Affleck starts talking
about born in the USA, the Springsteen song.
He's like, it really got me thinking, you know, it's this big,
like rah rah anthem, but it's actually about more than that.
It's about Vietnam.
This movie is set in 1984.
When the song comes out, you got Affleck making these sort of like, Ooh, it's
just everything about it is dumb as fuck.
This movie is critically acclaimed.
It stars Matt Damon, Ben Affleck, Jason Bateman, Marlon Wayans, Chris
Messina, Chris Tucker, Viola Davis.
And a very fat Jay Moore, bald, fat Jay Moore.
Oh, Jay Moore, uh, shout out to Jay Moore.
He's, he's recently came out publicly.
They got sober.
That's good for him.
Good for him.
Good that he's working again.
How is he in it?
Bad.
He's not good.
Uh, that's a, I just think it sucks that Jay Moore got this part.
It's like, do we need to give this part to Jay Moore?
Um, I mean, he was a good actor.
I thought I was enjoying.
Oh, Chris Tucker in this movie.
I don't know what they're having him do.
He, he's now like a dad, but you can tell that they're trying to pull the
chain and get him to do the Friday thing a little bit, but he's also just
playing a normal guy in an office.
So it doesn't make any sense.
Everything about the movie to me was a disaster and the whole concept of it.
Let's talk about Nike and how they signed Michael Jordan, um, would not be
interesting to me as a documentary, but as a feature film, um, we have to aim
a little higher for what we're going to write fucking movies about for Christ's
sake, who gives a shit, isn't it?
I, I took it as, and maybe I'm wrong, but I just, I just assumed it was like,
you know, like the founder, like how that was about McDonald's a
much more interesting movie.
Okay.
You never, and you never see Michael Jordan here.
They, they have his, uh, his mom played by Viola Davis, but like the whole movie
is about people hustling and they act like it's all they, again, they act like
it's some big, more culturally relevant story than it was, and all it is is a
bunch of white people exploiting a black guy.
And then even though that's what the actual story was, that's what the movie
feels like too, you know, it feels like a bunch of white guys telling this
black family's story, um, about a brand of shoe.
And this is what we're celebrating as one of the best movies of the year.
Okay.
Fine.
All right.
Uh, well, I guess I'll close it out with, uh, an opposite film of
what we're talking about here.
Uh, it's an old picture.
Back when, back when it was a business, as they say, I watched the public
enemy starring James Cagney.
Yeah.
Uh, I watched it because they show a clip of it in J Edgar and J Edgar in the
J Edgar movie hates it because he doesn't like that Hollywood is glorifying
gangsters and that the kids all think gangsters are cool.
Uh, and I was like, I never saw that movie, but you know, it's a classic of
her, you know, I've heard of it, whatever.
It's in, it's in that whatever the hell that thing is, is where they say like,
this has been selected as a movie of cultural significance, words, whatever.
And yeah.
Anyway, James Cagney plays a street kid, turns into a gangster.
His brother is a good guy, an urchin.
They called them back then street urchin.
And it's kind of just like this moral tale of just like, you know, bad, but
when you live by the gun, you die by it.
That's kind of really all there is to it, but it's a cool movie.
Uh, Cagney's great plays a real bastard in it.
My favorite scene is he's sitting with his girlfriend and she hears on the
phone that he's getting tired of her.
Yeah.
And he's like interested in this other one.
He goes back and sits at the breakfast table with her.
They got these like, these like cinnamon buns out on the table.
And, uh, she starts kind of picking at him and he's like, what is it?
What is it with you?
And she goes, I don't know.
Maybe you're tired of me.
And he takes us and shoves it into her face and twists it.
It's like something like a little kid would do to his little brother.
Uh, I know it's inappropriate, but it's, it's, it's very funny.
Like, it's so crazy.
Um, this is not the one where he slams the grapefruit into the
woman's face, which is a different.
That's like maybe that's the top of which one ends with top of the world.
That's white heat.
I want to see that one next.
Anyway, classic gangster picture.
I honestly, I don't think I had ever seen James Cagney in anything.
I'd heard about James Cagney.
You know, every guy in the comedian, the fifties and sixties had a James
Cagney impression, but, uh, so I just kind of knew him from that.
Uh, and it was fun watching these old, one of these old gangster movies.
It made me want to kind of start going back.
I was like, oh, maybe this is a new genre to explore.
Like, uh, foreign and classic gangster movies, you know, my gangster
movie experience sort of starts with the Godfather and anything comes after that.
So anyway, all those early Warner Brothers ones are great.
Angels with dirty faces is probably the best one.
But, um, yeah, all those old Cagney ones are great.
Bogart, petrified forest, et cetera, et cetera.
All right.
What are we talking about this week, Joe?
Are we talking about speak?
No evil.
Speak no evil.
Now I watched this movie months ago at this point.
It feels like years.
I will say it fucking stayed with me.
I definitely remember what happens in it.
Um, and they are remaking it by the way, for Christ's sake, speak.
No evil is being remade starring a James McAvoy.
Oh, and I'm sure it'll be just as dark.
Oh, it's from bloom house Joe.
They got no fight left in me.
Oh, it's from bloom house.
Um, from the guy who made the woman in black, which is one of our very first ever.
Uh, I enjoy the woman in black.
Yeah.
Uh, so look, uh, the movie speak no evil is so it's about, it's about a Danish
couple who are on vacation, they have a daughter and they're on vacation and
they meet a Dutch couple who have a son who never speaks and they say that it's
because he was born with this condition where he doesn't have a tongue, but
they're a seemingly very happy family and whatever, and they all hit it off.
And the two families have fun and blah, blah, blah.
And as you do on vacation, when you pal around with some people, you just met
the Dutch people, the people that have the son that can't talk, say, Hey, you
should come visit us sometime in the Netherlands.
And they're like, okay, yeah, sure.
That sounds fun.
So they get invited and it's, you know, I, if I'm remembering correctly, there
is kind of a bit of an Oh shit moment of like, Oh, they actually invited us, you
know, uh, so, but they're like, okay, let's do it.
So they go and immediately, you know, they're having a pretty fun time, but
immediately, uh, there are some, uh, weird, passive, aggressive, sort of
confrontational moments that make the visiting couple feel uncomfortable.
I remember the main one being that the husband is like super into meat and the
wife of the visiting couple is vegetarian and he keeps kind of blowing that off.
And then her husband, yeah, he's very, yeah, he blows off the vegetarianism.
He's kind of like makes fun of it.
And yeah, we're right.
He's big, he like plays loud music while they're driving and he's super
drunk and they're like, Hey, come on.
He's coming into the bathroom when they're in the bathroom.
There's just a lot of stuff that's getting uncomfortable.
Yeah.
So it's, it's all, it's all very, very uncomfortable.
Uh, and, and it, it comes to an initial head when the drunk, the drunk husband
that they're, the family they're visiting sleeps in a bed next to their daughter.
Yeah.
And he, and I believe he passes out naked next to the daughter.
Correct.
So, uh, the wife gets very upset.
She's like, this is very understandably.
So yeah, absolutely.
She's like, this is insane.
We need to get the fuck out of here right now.
And they go to leave in it's seemingly the middle of the night or extremely
early in the morning before the other couple whose house it is awakes and.
They're there a way, you know, as the viewer, something terrible is going to
happen because that's how a horror movie works.
They, as a couple are aware that something is not right.
Uh, they are miles away from the house.
As the viewer, you feel relief, you go their home free.
And then all of a sudden the daughter goes, I forgot my fucking
binky or whatever it is or stuffed animal that she loves.
And what do they do?
They go back.
And this is where my problems with this movie began.
You got to be a fucking moron.
To dry and I think everyone watching this movie went, are you fucking kidding me?
They do their best.
They try to set it up at the beginning.
When they find him, he's literally walking through the city, looking for
this doll for his daughter.
So you get that.
It's very important, but it's still just too big a buy at this point in the story.
It's the, it's the flaw of the film.
It's, it's, it's such a mistake.
So they go back, they go back, the couple is pissed off.
Like, geez, like you're really rude.
You know, like we, we've been hospitable and this and that, and, and, and you
just leave like this and whatever.
They, they apologize.
They apologize, uh, for leaving.
Yeah.
What is, what is this?
Anyway, they decide they're going to stay another day.
Now you're really, come on guys.
What are we talking about here?
What are we talking about?
So now they decide they're going to stay another day and they
actually have a good day.
Uh, the wife, the two wives bond over whatever it is.
I don't really remember.
They're just at the house drinking wine and bonding.
The two men go off and they drink a bunch of beers and the, the, the one
guy shows the other guy how to do screaming therapy and he's like, let, you
go out to this cliff and just yell and, and they're, they're all having a great
time, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
And then after dinner, uh, the two kids want to do this like dance that they've
rehearsed, you know how that is when you're little and you do a little show
for the parents after dinner, the two kids want to do that and the dad who
they're visiting starts screaming at his son for his son making mistakes.
It's completely outrageous.
It's completely insane.
It's completely the fucking moment that even these idiots would go, we're
going now we're leaving, they stay another fucking night at this point.
You're like, whatever happens to you.
You deserve it at this point.
You're fucking idiots.
Yeah.
I mean, there's some satire here in terms of like, we're all, we all
don't know what normal is, so we're all trying to kind of play along.
But there is a point where you do wonder, wouldn't you care about
your family's safety at this point?
And this movie stretches that one too many times to be honest, to be, to be
clear, but it also really, really works.
I mean, for me, all the thriller aspects of it worked incredibly well,
except for the fact that I didn't buy, they'd go back, but once they're there,
I'm like, all right, well, I'm in this situation with them.
Uh, the big turning point in, you know, far and away, the most horrifying
moment of this is when he realizes that basically this couple, they, they, they
find a couple, they, they cut their child's tongue out and then they kill the parents
and they just keep the cycle going.
It's kind of the final grizzly reveal of this thing.
Right.
And then they kill the, they kill the current kid.
Yeah.
So they're going to kill Abel.
Uh, Oh, actually no Abel does get killed.
He, he gets, he's, he gets, they found his, and then, yeah.
And then the re they realize, Oh my God, they're going to steal my daughter.
They're going to cut her tongue out.
They're going to try to kill us.
Uh, the dad is, and they do.
I mean, that was for me, like if I'm looking back at like the last year is,
especially because some of that was pandemic and a lot of that was me watching
like three movies a night, not even, you know, even knowing what I watched half
the time, um, this one stuck with me.
Cause I probably, if I really looked, I probably watched it six months ago
at this point or something.
But, um, that scene where they realize what's going on and they grab this
couple's daughter away from them and cut her tongue in front of them.
Um, and then take her away.
And then the parents are driven down the road where they are stoned to death.
And the dad's like, why are you doing this to us?
And the guy goes, because you let us, which I guess the satire there is like
he, a man's got to stand up for his family more.
And in that case, maybe they're on our side.
Maybe they're saying, why would you go back there?
Why, you know, maybe that's part of it is we should be, we should be angry
at these people for going back to the house.
I don't know.
I thought, um, yeah, I think that's kind of works.
It's a very effect.
It's certainly a uncomfortable thriller.
You know, it felt kind of like Polanski, but with like, uh, a very
violent mean streak in the end.
I did like the movie.
And they also let them seemingly stone them too.
Cause I remember watching the end and I'm like, why would you just stand
there and get stoned like this?
I think that's the satire.
I think it's like, cause his whole thing about, oh, you're going to,
you're not going to eat me.
You're going to what it's like.
He's just a guy who's like, stand the fuck up for yourself.
And I wonder if that's not the director's point of view here also is
like, like we don't need a nation of people willing to just like roll over.
You know, people got to stand up for their families for what's right for,
you know, maybe that's what he's going for.
I don't know.
Certainly one of those movies where I feel like a very liberal person would
watch it and speak about how it's about the horrors of the world and all this
stuff, and a very conservative person would watch it and go, see, this is why
you got to fight because this is the point.
Like you raise a nation of weaklings.
That's what's going to happen.
And it is a challenging film in that sense.
I do think it leans towards the ladder.
I do think it's more about saying, stand the fuck up for yourself.
You let people do this to you.
They will, um, you know, and it is a biblical thing, you know, speak no evil
and the stoning and, and, and all that sort of stuff.
Yeah.
Um, but there's also kind of a, if you're not going to teach your children,
we'll do it.
Yeah.
Um, so it's all sorts of very uncomfortable themes.
And I think that's what makes the movie work and sort of interesting.
It works as a conversation piece.
Uh, it's definitely fucked up and unpleasant.
There comes a point at the end where it's got sort of that nihilistic.
All right.
Like where this is just miserable for miserable sake or misery, porn,
whatever you want to call it.
Well, that's my big, that's my big, but my big, but is I understand
that there's a point to this.
I understand there's a commentary to it.
I just don't want to watch it.
I'm just like, this is a bummer.
I'm sad now, like it's dark.
There was nothing redeeming about any person in this movie.
You hate the main couple because they're morons.
You hate the evil couple because they're evil.
You feel bad for the kids.
And that's so upsetting that you're like, God almighty, it's just disturbing.
Like in God, like they're murdering the kids.
And I just, I'm just like, I don't really understand it.
It is a, as you said, nihilistic, a very nihilistic foreign film.
It does make me appreciate foreign cinema because I mean, they don't
give a fuck overseas, man, they, they just make shit.
They're like, deal with it, man.
This is what it is.
This probably played in movie theaters over there.
You know?
So, so that aspect of it, I appreciate it.
Will the remake here be, be as vicious?
I don't know.
Absolutely not.
Yeah, absolutely not.
And it's funny, as I sit here and complain and say, I don't really
need to see a movie like this, it still pisses me off.
I appreciate that it exists and it pisses me off that they will make some version
of this in the States that is watered down and weak and stupid.
Uh, now maybe I'm wrong, but you know, um, they probably will.
Yeah.
We'll see.
You know, I mean, look, sometimes they go for it in this day.
I just watched, I gotta say before, before we wrap up this one, I think
this is an extremely well -made thriller.
I completely agree with Joe that it's very unpleasant in the home stretch
and leaves you with this feeling of emptiness, but obviously I think that's
your goal.
And I think of this kind of like miserable list horror movie of
which there are many, there are many on shutter actually.
Um, I think this is one of the more effective ones.
I really thought this was a really well done slow burn.
Uh, the problem is these slow burns, like a wicker man or a mid summer, they
usually build to like this big colorful crazy thing, and this is a slow burn
that builds to like the most horrible, unpleasant, unsettling thing.
So it's a very anticlimactic feeling, but I dug the movie.
I gotta say, not only did you interrupt my point, you talked for so long.
I can't remember what the hell I was going to say.
Well, I felt like we were done with the movie.
No, no, I was going to, I was just going to say, um, Oh, I remember
sometimes they stick to the thing over here.
Like I've been watching this 101 horror movie moment, whatever the
fuck it's called on shutter.
You know what I'm talking about?
Yeah.
And they, they, when they talk about Dr.
Sleep, Mike Flanagan talks about showing the movie to Stephen King
before anybody else sees it.
And he goes, Stephen King's only note was, well, that child killing
scene goes on a little too long, doesn't it?
And, uh, and Mike Flanagan is like, the scene was much longer.
Yeah.
And we edited it down and you're like, Jesus Christ, man.
Cause that's the scene they talk about.
That's the most disturbing scene in the movie.
So, and we talked about that when we reviewed Dr.
Sleep, we were like, we couldn't believe that, that, that scene got
into a fucking popcorn horror movie.
Uh, and, but that's horror.
Those are the scenes that should be in the movies.
That's why I can't be too mad at this movie.
It really worked for me.
Right.
Well, but, but, but here's the thing.
Dr.
Sleep has two characters.
I'm really rooting for.
Yes, true.
It's got a, a, a triumphant, you know, heroes moment when he
returns to the hotel and, and, and it's got actually a happy ending,
which I'm not saying a horror movie needs to have a happy ending.
I'm just saying with this, even as dark as like a movie, like smile ended
with where it ends, like sort of hopeless, um, you're still like,
you know, you're, you're rooting for her.
You wonder, she's making the right choices and she's at the mercy of this thing.
And again, maybe the commentary of this is the stupidity of choice and
how it can lead to your demise.
But it's, and that's fine.
It's just hard to find anything to latch onto in this other
than the dread of it all.
So, yeah, I'm glad it exists though.
Movies like this need to exist.
You know, it doesn't matter if I like it or not.
Yeah.
If you're looking for more dread in your life, this is one to check out.
Speak no evil.
Um, we are going to be back.
We are talking about, what are we talking about?
I'm going to, I'm going to watch the howling.
The howling.
I haven't seen it in a long time.
We're going to do the howling this week.
Well, is that, I mean, this week, Pat and I are going to record it.
It'll be the second episode that comes out.
We'll be the howling and then we're going to figure out what else we're
going to do the rest of the month.
Um, June, watch the beautiful new 4k of the howling.
I got the DVD.
I'm going to watch it tomorrow night and see if I'm not throwing
away the DVDs by the way.
I'm just, even if I'm replacing them, I'm still caping them because I'd
made this fucking mistake once with VHS.
I'm not doing it again.
Uh, anyway, I am going to check out the howling.
We are going to review the howling.
Uh, that'll be fun.
Um, we also, well in June, we know we'll be doing Indiana Jones, uh, possibly
the flash, I know I'll see the flash.
I don't know if Pat, if you will, but it's possible.
Um, uh, and you know, some other things are coming up.
We'll, we'll, we'll keep you, we'll keep you posted folks.
That's all I got.
I don't have any dates.
I don't have any live dates or anything coming up, but if you are around, uh,
Wednesday, the 10th, that's this week, we are doing the live taste buds stream.
The first ever live stream of taste buds by ticket, 10 bucks, be a part of the
big, big epic battle, the bigger than any battle we've ever done, uh, two Titan
things facing off against one another.
You can get your tickets at moment .co slash taste buds.
That's moment .co slash taste buds, 9 p .m.
Eastern time this Wednesday.
Oh, and go to Joey roses.
If you're in New York city, 11 30 AM, we open every day, seven days a week.
Thank you everybody.
I am the Patrick Walsh at Instagram and we'll be back next time.
We will see you.
Next time and we'll see you in hell.