I'm here for Bett Rivers online casino and sportsbook with poker icon Phil Helmuth.
And now thanks to the excitement of Bett Rivers, I'm also a slots icon.
That's great! And a same game, parlay icon. Cool, cool. A blackjack icon,
a money line icon, a roulette. Take it from Phil Helmuth. If you love games,
Bett Rivers is the place to play in Bett. Bett Rivers. Games on.
Must be 21 plus in present in West Virginia. Void were prohibited. Terms in conditions apply.
gambling problem called 1 -800 -Gamberland.
Firestone Complete Auto Care's epic savings advantage is the sign you need to stop putting
off your car's maintenance, and you can save up to $100 on tires and services while you're
Don't wait, call fires don't complete out of care for an appointment.
Hello everyone. Hello. Welcome to we'll see you in hell. It's me. The podcast is
now part of the Fangoria podcast network for more information about the
network including other programs. How to follow this show in five past
episodes. We'll visit. All right, you have a great calm. Now on with the show. I was
singing hello by Adele in the background. I thought you were singing. We just
a convert, not you and I, but I talked to somebody about hello and it was the Lionel Richie.
Well, yeah, they were saying like Adele now owns like hello, whereas he doesn't own it.
Not own it, but you know what I mean, like that was Lionel Richie's thing.
She's leasing a sizable part of the house, but she doesn't own it.
No, Richie owns it, baby.
I think she's got a lot more than Richie, the father of Nicole Richie.
I never noticed until right now that his, the root word of his name is Lion, and, and to
be honest, with all the pleasure of surgery, him and Smokey Robinson look like lions, yeah,
like majestic lionesses, there's a little lioness, a lioness, a lioness, a lioness, there's
a little lioness thing about them that makes them look lioness, lioness like, yeah, folks
love them both. Let's tell people what they're listening to before I tell my smokey Robinson story.
Well they know what we're listening to and we're in one ear. I'm in one ear patch in the other and
you know why because you play the movie if you want up the middle and that's just how this goes okay.
So you can listen to this with us or without us. Well, no, not without us. You have to listen to with
us. But you can listen to it with the movie or without the movie and if you didn't want to hear us
then you just watch the movie today we're doing the woman in black starring Daniel Radcliffe
which is the remake never seen the original but I would like to have you ever seen
the original uh I didn't know it was it's an old like hammer movie right yeah but the
remake is also by hammer I meant starring MC hammer he did that action movie with DMX called
too legit, too quick.
Yeah, so now's the time if you want to line it up,
pop your DVD in, find it on, we're on Amazon Prime today.
It might be on Netflix, I don't know,
but if you want to queue it up,
now's where you stop our podcast,
you can get your movie queued up.
And now that you're all cute up, we're going to do a count off.
We do it at one, two, three, four, three, four, play, but no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
I'm going to lean forward to hit play.
You count it off.
And then I'll hit play.
I'm not saying one, two, three, four.
I'm going to say one, two, three, four.
You give the first ever four count on here we go folks 1 2 3 play yeah we're
rolling woman in black we got some sort of CBS logo coming up is that CBS like
the TV station it is they they stuck their hand into a few films and they do
pretty well actually did they yeah really they do now I have to change the sad sound
output because I just realized it's not correct and that's why we can't hear
anything. So talk for a moment. Would you pet? Absolutely. I'm going to tell the Smokey Robinson
story. So if you get a chance to see Smokey Robinson before he passes away, which may be a while
because it looks like he's been embalmed or, you know, if frozen in time, something like that.
But we go to see Smokey Robinson at the Hollywood Bowl. He's got the same amazing voice,
song sound incredible. But between the songs, this son of a bitch had the funniest band
I've ever heard of my wife.
Funnier than most stand up, and I'm looking right at Jodaro,
so what I'm saying is funnier than most stand up.
But he gets up there, and he goes,
folks, this is off my new album, Fire and Ice.
It's only available at Cracker Bear.
And the audience laughs hysterically, and he goes,
oh no, no, I'm quite serious.
It's only available at Cracker Bear.
We looked it up.
This album was only available at Cracker Bear.
But he had a sense of humor. Wait, but you you think he was trying to be funny when he said that he was definitely trying to be fun
Okay, then he goes folks up we got we're gonna do one more now off my new album
The title again is fire and ice
Right and he looks out of the crowd the crowd of silent and he goes. Oh, thank you both
His his one liners were destroying the crowd. He was making fun of himself
He looked ridiculous. He sang like a damn angel. Where the hell did you smoke your Robinson?
I saw him at the Hollywood Bowl, which is how that story started. I wasn't listening because I fixed in the volume. Yeah, it's fine
It was great. He's one of the funniest men I've ever seen. You just went to see
Smokey Robinson headline the Hollywood Bowl. Yeah, you're a two ago
I also saw the Reverend Al Green at the Greek theater and he was amazing as well. Now does he still sing like let's get it on and like the sex tunes?
Let's stay together. Let's get it on with Marvin Gaye. Oh, that's right. He's saying some songs about you know
making love to your woman, not fucking her, you know what I mean?
That's a difference. But that's not what he was singing about back in the 70s.
No, no, he was singing about fucking. But what I recommend people is if you get a
chance, like a lot of times you'll see, or Ritha Franklin's coming to town,
and you're like, oh man, it'd be cool as you're Ritha Franklin, but you don't buy
that ticket. And they're gonna die very soon and you're gonna wish that you
going to Sam. So I go see Al Green and I go see Chuck Berry when I'm in St. Louis.
You go see all these people because then when they die you've seen a piece of American
history. And if you put it off too long, they're going to die. That's how I felt when
I saw Elton John. Absolutely. He probably did all the hits, right? It was wall -to -wall hits,
not including, can you feel the love tonight? Thank God. Oh, yeah. It was not a hit. It was
wall -to -wall every song you ever wanted to hear. That's right. He was tremendous. He was
was wearing a jet he was wearing the captain fantastic jacket. Nice. Nice. Which was awesome.
He opened with the bitches back. Sure. He's the bitch. I think he is, right? I think that's
what that means, right? Did he say Saturday? Saturday. Of course. Yeah. That's his most rocking
song. I think that might have been the encore. I love that like that's his toughest song and
he's like breaking beer bottles over people's heads and stuff. But then in the second verse
he's like admiring his sister's wardrobe and you're like, oh, I think this guy might be
lying about all the macho stuff. He's like, my sister looks good in her braces and boots
so it's like, come on out. He did is he did the most focus on the fights. He did one of the most
ballsy not ballsy like like cock rock moves I've ever seen in a rock show and I loved it. Yeah.
Uh, uh, the second song was Benny and the Jets, and all he did was this.
He just went, boom, and stood up and from the one chord, everybody started going crazy.
Sure.
And I was like, how awesome is that when you, how awesome is that when you can do that?
Yeah.
I'm going to do the one chord and he stood up and looked at everybody like, yeah, fuck you.
It was great.
like when I saw the Baja man they all go who same thing right five minutes because you know
let the dogs that is coming yeah and then when they let those dogs out Joe the sad part is dogs
I would I didn't even I wasn't sure if you were kidding or not because you've seen every god damn
concert that comes to town I wouldn't be that surprised if you want to see the bar I wouldn't go see
the Baja man right now when I saw John he sang Benny and the June's I don't get it in the June's
We've discussed it on this show.
It's a movie with Johnny Depp and Mary Stewart Masters.
Oh, Betty and June.
I thought you were doing a play on Jets.
No, like that there was some correlation between
June's and Jets.
And for a minute, I thought you said June Jets.
These are Jews.
It made me uncomfortable.
Sure.
That's not what you said, though.
You're watching the film with us, by the way.
Daniel, I mean, this is the most we've just completely
disregarded a film.
Thank you for reminding me, as if I was a listener,
that we're watching a film.
I mean, we haven't called one bit of attention to it.
We're in the scene now where Harry Potter is sitting
with, he's always just going to be Harry Potter.
Poor bastard.
He's sitting with the guy, cutting the cigar
and they're talking about something.
I actually very much like this film.
I've seen it before and you have two.
You just painted quite a picture that's
going to make people want to turn it.
I mean, Harry Potter saw going to this guy who's
cutting a cigar or something.
Hard enough to speculate on who this guy is.
Yeah, a ledger or something, you know.
A ledger's a book.
He's Heath Ledger.
But he's like a lawyer, it's his boss.
I know he's got a lot of books and things.
I don't know.
One of these English guys, it's probably a ledger.
I picture every guy in England having a room like this.
Oh, sure.
With paintings and cigars.
Five books.
Yeah.
Rugs, probably.
A desk.
Yeah.
Yeah. I always admired the English. It seems like a very nice life.
I did so. I went to this part of the other night and this guy was British, very handsome
gentleman. He starts talking and this entire room just stops milling about and talking
and just stares at him while he talks. The women, the hottest woman there made a b -line
forum the second she could. It's a very sexy thing and we don't have it. We sound boring.
I love the English accent and English accent on a woman and I find to be terribly sexy and on a man
Even sexier. I just find it pompous usually and boring, but this guy was I love it. I love the accent
Then you got your Australian accent, which is sort of a rough and tumble good day, mate
That's normal cousin. That's a shrimp bobby
Right. Yes, that's the quote. Yeah
Now, do you find that I have some sort of southern accent or a Missouri accent?
Because I get told it by some friends, but not that all.
If that, by that you mean do I think you sound like a dumbass?
Yeah, yeah, okay, like a real American dumbass.
Yeah, when you talk, I'm like, you sounds like a fucking podunk dumbass.
Every word is an eternity, just shut up.
Well, like Kid Rock, I'm an American badass.
No, I don't hear that with you, and I'm joking, of course, about the South.
I got quite an affinity for the South I'm from the Midwest and I'm also a fan of the Southern South will rise again
I'm a fan of the Southern accent as well on a not that I'm not a fan of it on a man
But I date women and I find it on a woman to be quite sexy. I'll take a Southern accent over British accent on a lady
That's why Holly Hunter was my favorite gal and movies for many years
Women alive
Holly's is a little too like like like auto shop for me. Yeah, it's a little too hard for me. I think she's the best. But I think she's a lovely woman.
She's in the suicide squad. No, no, she's in Superman Batman, which I'm excited to see. You just saw Hail Caesar.
I did. Last night I saw Hale Caesar and I liked it and what happens more and more with these
Coen Brothers movies is I'm sitting there. I'm enjoying the hell out of it. It ends. I go, oh,
that wasn't quite what I was looking for or quite what I wanted. I did it with Louis and Davis. I did
it with, what's the one prior to that? Burn after reading. Where I'm like, I enjoyed so much of it,
But a kind of a man simple man perfect example. That's now one of my favorites is a simple man. I loved it from the first time
I saw it, but I'm just sharp like that. Yeah, I just got it. Well, it's called a serious man, right serious man. Yeah, what's the the Woody Allen one is a serious man. No, simple man is the one directed by the fashion designer.
Okay, what's the Woody Allen not wrong serious man? Tom Ford Tom Ford directed a simple man
And a serious man is the co -embrothers movie. What's the Woody Allen label man? That is
If something man. Yeah, an inconse
Son of a bitch. I really like the rational man a rational that's right and the soul man is where see Thomas
Howl dresses like a block right now get I'll often get so man confused with the plot of every other one of those films. Yeah
Yeah, but yeah, I like all those movies.
Okay, good.
You were talking about Hail Caesar.
Hail Caesar, I thought was very funny in spots.
It's super weird.
There's a bunch of pieces in it
that don't seem to connect
and you don't really know if they do at the end.
And now today I woke up and they asked me
when I walked into work.
Did you like it?
I'm like, yeah, I really did.
Then you ask me now.
I'm like, yeah, it's actually all I thought
about all day. And I think it's a fucking amazing movie and that's why I think
they're working on a different level than anybody else. Now I'll tell you this
folks yesterday was a Super Bowl. Pat and I went to two Super Bowl parties
together. Yep. And then to a bar. Yeah. It was quite a day of intake. Yep. And
after all that, when I was so drunk, I decided to go get four tacos and a
case idea for Matruck, Pat went to see a movie.
So how drunk were you in that theater by yourself?
Not very, because I quit drinking long before you guys.
So at the, when we went to the second stop,
second party house, I left fairly early, went home.
I didn't drink anymore after that.
When I met up with you guys.
You left literally five minutes before we went to the bar.
And then you came and met us at the bar.
Yeah, but I met you like two hours later. That's amazing. Maybe an hour. I think it was at least two hours.
You probably didn't notice the time because you were so very drunk.
But when I got there, I was fine. I didn't drink anymore after that. And you guys were all pretty
amped up at that point. And I thought you left when I guess you just went and took a massive dump.
And I said, I'm going to go see Hale Caesar. And I did. And I wasn't that drunk at all.
and I followed the plot and I had a good time and I was in such a foul mood
that sometimes it's a better move to just go watch a movie by yourself I was in
horrendous shape yeah I woke up at where to press that's what Joe and I just had a
delicious home cook meal home cook by Joe to roast himself yeah contributing to the
will they are won't they vibe of this podcast that people comment on on Twitter
Joe made me a lovely dinner and we talked about how to press we
Describe the dinner because I feel like I will get some points for what I cooked. He made some perfectly season to spare
I guess a potato that at first seemed a little tough but grew on me to become my new favorite way to cook potatoes
And a piece of lamb is that correct?
Lamb with some delicious seasonings that Joe ordered on Amazon Prime
Amazon Prime who's also bringing you the movie we're watching tonight. That's right speaking of which
pay us no money we are watching a movie yeah man the people that complain
that we don't talk about it but the movie enough are really gonna be unhappy
those people have kind of stopped because they know what they're getting
now here you got Daniel Radcliffe in a creepy room in an old haunted house where
we assume he's gonna meet the woman in black he's wearing a Henley shirt which
I don't even know they made back then even weirder it's a Don Henley Henley shirt
right so it's got a Don Henley end of the innocence tour poster on it right and
that album came out in 1991 that's what Don Henley should do now make Don
Henley Henley is yeah the Henley's by Don Henley well I love Glenn
Fraze Fraze he makes those are delicious season Curlies those are delicious
favorite part of this nation is delicious season Curlies right when the drive
through the funniest sketch in the history of music. I don't know what I'll play it for you
after this. Tenacious D album. Thankfully, they only made one. It's perfect from start to finish.
The songs are incredible. No, they made three albums. Not album album. Yes they have. No,
none have come out after this self -titled Tenacious D. Yes, they have. You mean the soundtrack to
pick up Destiny? And then they made another album called the about like the phoenix rising from the
ashes. And that was like their follow -up album. They absolutely did. It was like a big
true. It's 100 % true. I'll bet you please bet me a large amount of money. Well, the Phoenix rising
is that's the tenacious deal. So there must be one before that. No tribute to the best song ever.
No, that's the first one. Okay. Then came the soundtrack to the movie and then they did a follow -up
to the first album which was officially their second album. Oh, I gotta find this. I didn't know
that even happened. We're in the Phoenix song. They apologize for the pick of destiny. Okay.
say like we you thought we were down and out but here we're back all right it's not as good
as the first time but it's enjoyable let me look it up so yeah now I got to hear it anyway
season currently says from that uh yeah he goes through the drive -through and he's like you know he keeps
ordering things it's so it's so funny and you would you would love it so much he just jack black so
he's ordering food and he'll order like a lot of food and then feel really guilty about it immediately
like, uh, do a large soda or everything. He's like, uh, can I get half diet, half regular
in this? Then just everything he says is great. And then he goes, uh, can I get a, uh,
bacon cheeseburger, please? And he goes, excuse me, a junior bacon cheese, junior bacon
cheese, sure, bacon, there's no funnier way to say junior bacon cheeseburger than junior
Bacon Chi and then it's one point he says season Curly's I'm assuming. Yeah, he goes
some curly fries please. Seasoned Curlies. You're gonna have to give it a
listen. I love it. I think it influenced a lot of the way I speak because I
listened to it every day when I was a kid. I've heard a lot of that kid first out but
I've never heard that sketch. Yeah. Big fan. You know, my kid on workaholics. How does
he not Adam divine? How does he not pay Jack Black 10 % of his salary? I think
Adam Devine's very funny, but like he's doing Jack Black.
How does anybody not pay anybody what they owe them?
It's true, but he's a little too much on that.
I agree.
No, I'm not disagreeing with you, but the, here's the thing.
My favorite tenacious D sketch is the one where Cage is standing outside.
This is a video sketch where he's standing outside with a poster board that says below jobs
$5.
Take that salad.
And then Jack Black pulls and pulls over and with sunglasses on and he goes, hey man, you know, I'm looking to party. Yeah, KG gets in the car, blows Jack Black, not realizing it's Jack Black because he has sunglasses on.
Jack Black comes, they literally take a bottle of lubricant and just squirt it into the air to simulate Jack Black gizzing.
Jack Black takes off the sunglasses. KG goes, oh man, it's you Jack. And then he goes, you don't have five fucking bucks.
or is Jack the one that blows him? I think Jack blows KG. They played that when I saw them in concert.
They played that. That's an amazing sketch. I saw if you want to talk about a great classic early 2000s concert.
It was Weezer headlining.
Tenacious D below them. And Jimmy eat world as the opener.
One of the best shows I've ever seen I mean you lost me a Jimmy world. I love Jimmy world. Especially the big songs
The middle is their big pop. How's that one go? It just takes some time
Which okay, I can see how you get sick of that beautiful song
But the rest of that album many other other songs you would enjoy I have a feeling
I dare you they're great. You don't know what I would or wouldn't enjoy it. You don't fucking know me. Well, thank Christ
You fucking asshole. Thank Christ. You don't know shit about me. Joe's drinking again gang
So he's home from the factory gang. You're drinking too. I'm having a gluten free beer. That's good
Yeah, and I have a glass of white wine. All right. That's all you know, I like I'm swinging out of a flask
Which I'm not above. No, I'm sure you'd be swinging out of the flask by the end of the swinging out of the flask is what I just said folks
Hey, that sounds like a good name for an album.
Swinging out of the flat.
Like a Brian Setser orchestra with BSL album.
Swinging out of the flask.
Yeah, well, let me talk about Hell's Season for a moment.
I want to see it again.
I think no Colin Brothers movie you can figure out, make your mind up on until you see it
a second time.
That's when a serious man became one of my favorites of theirs because I got way more into it the
second time.
Clooney, I'm tired of him working with the Collins.
I think they can do better. I like when they give
Really funny character parts to people who are not necessarily that kind of actor right George Clooney. I'm sick of it
I've seen it. I know he's kind of funny enough. Doesn't mean I want to see him in every fucking comedy, right?
Same with fucking Brad Pitt by the way
That said we'll say Brad Pitt steals the show and burn after reading no question
And Clooney too Clooney and fucking Richard Jenkins who is amazing and everything and Clooney's off the in my opinion off the charts
in Brennan after reading. I got a problem with my larynx. No, he's great. Yeah, I'm a little tired of it as I'm tired of
DeCaprio and Scorsese, you know, you want to see people work with different kinds of people.
Jonah Hills in one scene, kind of funny. Nothing else. Christopher Lambert was in a scene. The Highlander himself.
Chris Lambert is in this film. He's in it. Scarge. He's often quite fun. Ray finds his great and the who steals the movie is
Is Channing Tatum for one he does a musical gay like sailor dancing number that was amazing, right and
Sings pretty well and he's really funny in it, right and then the other new guy who's playing like the cowboy and the trailers
Is off the charts funny, and I think it's gonna be a big star. How's my boy JB?
Josh bros
By boring to be honest with you. That's I hate to hear that. Brolin was fan. Brolin was perfect for no country for old men
he can't do any bigger characters than that. I like Josh Brode. I found him to be the only
redeeming and immensely enjoyable part of that that shitty PT and shit movie. Inheritbice,
absolutely agree. Yeah. The way he's sucking that fucking positive short. I didn't even get to
the martin short part because I couldn't get to the goddamn movie. Yeah. It was not not fun. Yeah,
What are you gonna do? You know, these are I liked I also at the theater on the aisle this week with Dorosa and Walsh
I
Saw a little movie called dirty grandpa folks. I
Mean now you're he
Grand Paul you've been waiting to tell me about this. Yeah, now for those of you listening at home that don't know Pat Walsh on a personal level
Know this
He's the type of guy that will text you
several times in a week asking you almost desperately please go see dirty grandpa
with me and I'm like I don't know I don't want to see this movie yeah and he's
not saying like it'll be funny because it's I will go ironically and I don't do
that we'll get like drunk before and it'll be a who he really wants to go and see if
it's any good and then of course you would say something beautiful about me as a
human that I'm optimistic about I text you the day after I said how was dirty
grandpie you said disturbingly bad yeah it was off the charts bad folks and but I am glad I saw
it I worked with our buddies Jake Weisman Mattinga Brutson Brian DeGwire I saw it was Brian DePalma
okay myself you split that was worth it he kept saying he wanted more split screen and lesbian
action on it yeah yeah yeah okay kept asking why there weren't more chase scenes yeah
well there certainly couldn't have been more cocaine and uh... dirty grandpa
was there a lot of cocaine stuff
but cocaine ecstasy xanax everything
now the movie's going out again
we're still here with you
uh...
the dirty grandpa
robert deniro just completely goes for he never looks embarrassed which is
embarrassing
and what i think happened is there's no way he knew any other references in this
movie
deniro's like
Oh, you know, this reminds me of like Queen Latifah taking a shit or not.
So we're great.
It's stuff like that.
And I just imagine rather than you know, we're just like look at a frame of the whistle line again.
And they tell him and he goes, if Queen Latifah taking a shit on a,
I don't think he thinks about anything he's saying for a moment in the movie.
It sounds like he's just dryly reading a script, the first glance.
First time he's seen these words.
Oh, that's upsetting.
Efron is
Beyond bland and boring and should not be a movie star. Although of course he's a good -looking guy
I've had enough you're not a comedy actor's neck
I'm getting upset. Well you said it for neighbors to no, but I didn't despise neighbors
I hated neighbors one. I would say it was the worst of theirs for sure
I hated that movie it was really haphazardly written and I didn't careful and I'm not shitting on Seth Rogan in those guys
I like a lot of the stuff they do, but I hate it. Yeah, of course.
But yeah, it was really bad, but maybe because I was there with comedians and people who like to like study comedy, we talked about it for a good 45 minutes afterwards, and about how depressed we all felt by it, and how sort of lazy and sad and desperate it was, and like Danero, there's a gay black guy that rolls with them, and Danero calls this guy like every name in the book,
He says insanely hateful
things against gay people to his face that aren't funny and there's no like bounce to them
It's not like when bad Santis says something and it's funny because they wrote it funny
He's just says these awful racist things into this guy's eyes
The audience is so silent
Well, what like give me and then the gay black guy never says anything in response
So you just sit there and watch the hurt on this poor
K black man's face as he registers the hate being spewed by the hero
What's one of the things he says and he doesn't respond?
I wouldn't repeat them, but it's the whole movie is like I bet you want to gargle this guy's cock
Conn't like all this kind of shit and you're like okay
None of this is really funny, but I know the black guys gonna get back at the mirror, but he doesn't he never gets back
He never says a word in retaliation
They it's like when David spades telling Chris Farley you're a big fat piece of shit
It's funny because Chris really tries to come back at him right like or makes a joke back
Or that he says well, you're an asshole and they go back and forth. This was an old man hurling
racial epitats and
sexist things at
People and then you sort of watching the hurt absorb on their face terrible in a comedy
I don't like the sound of this we were so blown away by it and it was interesting and I'm glad I saw it because
was you couldn't believe what they do in this movie was like it was like watching
birth of a nation was a study in yeah exactly and you know at one point
De Niro beats up a gang which is an actual gang of seven black guys he beats the
shit out of all them except two in the back are just standing there watching I heard
you complaining about this yesterday you're really mad maybe I wasn't clear he
beats the shit out of seven guys and there's two just standing there like not
fighting. No, what are you guys doing?
I made that clear yesterday. You were really
going to hear what I said. I know.
I'm just saying, for the audience is
sake, you were really hung up on the
logistics of how this fight would have
went to. My overall point here, and I
realize that makes no sense if you haven't
seen it. And don't see it. But there were
so many things in it where you were
like, how could everyone have been just
asleep that day? How did no one say,
wait a minute guys, this doesn't make any sense?
Or hey, this jokes terrible. Let's come up with a new one. You work in television. You have to ask that question. Yeah, no
I mean, we've all worked in television. It's not we've all but you and I you we all in this room two people on this couch
You know, we you know how it happens. It's you know, everybody said something and this has got to change and this has got to change
Then people tap out and people say fuck this and yeah eventually gets to the finished product and it's terrible. Yeah
You know, so yeah, the director was this guy Dan Mazer who was Sasha Baron Collins riding partner and help do all those movies with him like these are people who knew comedy.
Wasn't working.
That's a shame, man.
That's really a shame.
I hate to hear it.
It happens.
Yeah, it's a shame.
I regret writing and directing dirty grandpa.
I just read it. I read an interview with T .J. Miller, who we've known for quite from
before, when back when I, we could say we know him when W. B. W. Baby. But way back
when I read an interview with him about Deadpool, which I'm sure if I want to see or
not, I've decided I am excited to see it. I because my problem with all the Marvel
movies that they take themselves too seriously and this doesn't. If the joke sucks then I won't like it
but maybe it's gonna be funny. I don't think the Marvel movies take themselves too seriously.
I think they get a bit masturbatory to be honest with you. They get very like pleased with
their humor and everything. Yeah and they're two hours and 45 minutes. Well that's stupid but
so I'm not I'm not against Deadpool. I love Ryan Reynolds. I want to support. Boy that guy's
been in need of a good vehicle for 15 fucking years. He's so talented. He
might either as a bad agent or the other people above him get the office
first. Right. Well in any case, I'm not again seeing the film. I just don't know
if I'm excited about it. But I read an interview with TJ Miller where he talked
about the jokes that were too much for the movie that had gotten cut. Uh -huh. And he
was only allowed to give an example of one or two. Apparently the studio said
don't talk about these. They were cut for a reason. Right. But one of them that
That was apparently too much was when he's like telling him what he looks like, how bad
his face looks.
Yeah.
He goes, it looks like your neck took a shit and then grew ears.
Something like that.
Or somebody showed us too much for the amount of blood.
Somebody took a shit on your shoulders and then it grew, then it grew ear.
Yeah, that's what I was confused about.
He got billboards up all around town.
I don't know if they have these where you live, folks, but out here in La La World.
Yeah, probably.
They got dead pool billboards everywhere.
that literally say, wait till they get a load of me.
Like the sexual innuendo was almost not even innuendo.
A load of jizz, you're sorry.
Somebody, I don't know who did it on Twitter,
but somebody doctored one of the Deadpool billboards
into like Photoshop and said,
they're really going too far with this Deadpool marketing
and the thing they put on it, it was Deadpool laying there
and it just said, I shoot bullets and come Deadpool.
Well, what was the like I don't understand he's saying wait till they get a load of me
But is he coming in the photo or what no, it's just he's saying load. It's very beevus and butt -head
He okay, all right, but my point is I don't know Deadpool's style of humor
I know on the trailer the this girl beats a shitter to somebody and he goes who I'd hate to be the guy who tries to rape her on
prom night. I was like that's not a funny joke. Is that in the commercial? In the trailer.
I guess I assume it was a red band trailer, but yeah, don't try to have four sex with her on
prom night. Like that pool. Which does he say? He says four sex. I can't believe a comic book movie is
rated are. I don't think a comic book movie has been rated are since the original Punisher film
I'm starring Dov Lunger.
Longy, baby.
Was dark man a comic book?
No, it's a comic book style movie, but it's not.
It's a superhero movie, but I don't believe
that was ever a comic book.
That's Sam Raim's.
It is best.
Big fans.
The plan is his best, but yes, go on.
But I'm not saying that's his best film.
I'm just saying that's him top of his game.
He does a really great job with that movie.
Speaking of, your boy Liam Neeson, your girlfriend,
is Mick Dorman, hell of a flick.
And your boy, it's on Netflix.
Your boy, what's his face?
The play Larry Drake Larry Drake. Yeah has only ever I think I've seen almost every Larry Drake will be only ever plays a
Retarded man or a villainous scumbag. There's no I mean talking about a type casting
We got to run a movie where we can cast him as a retarded villain a scumbag
Mentally handicapped folks
By the way
I'd go see that movie and you know Larry Drake will do it
name the guy from Rome. I don't know. I'm calling Daniel Radcliffe Harry Potter. Yeah. By the way,
let's get back to the film we're watching. Okay. This is perhaps a molestation attempt brewing.
We're watching the woman in black folks starring Daniel Radcliffe. This is the remake of the hammer classic
the woman in black. I remember when I tried to rent this movie. I misspoke at the counter at Black
Western. I said, do you have the black woman for rent? They didn't know what I was talking about.
Yeah, looking for a black woman told me to get out of the store
I was being racially provocative sure
You were singing brown sugar by the round stones odd that this guy's got paintings of small boys on his wall
Shouldn't agree
Unless it's his son actually looks a bit like my dad whoever this actor. He's a great actor. I can't think of who he is
though. He's from Rome. He's on the show Rome and then he was in every movie ever made for like 10
years. I never watched Rome because that was my breaking point. That was my brief breaking point
with HBO, because they had at that point released too many TV shows. Yeah, it was mortified to hear
that you had left. They had released too many TV shows that opened with a credit sequence that was
clearly done an after -effects and some sort of kind of like middle -eastern -y passion of
the Christ kind of music and by the time they got to Roma I was like I can't do this anymore.
It just feels like the opening to Carnival and you know that was really weird when Carnival
now started with Joe's very tasteful recreation of the theme to Rome.
Well, I was actually I think doing the Carnival theme.
Yeah.
I think there was the theme to how to make it in America.
A show about making jeans.
I like that they just did a close up cut away of the painting over the boy.
Now they're doing a second close.
Yeah, and that's not supposed to be funny although it is kind of odd. Yeah, the master of the house here who was also in Rome
As you pointed out. There's a bit of an Alan Rickman vibe. He does. I still find myself getting quite sad that Alan Rickman is dead
I just think about him and I get sad he was one of the best. I
Feel like I could do an Alan Rickman impression if I really tried. Well, I used to do on vine
Recurring sketch called pool party at Alan Rickman's house. All right. Do it
where he would be, uh, all right, let me think.
Friendly reminder that there is to be no intercourse in the jacuzzi.
Thank you.
There you go.
That's great.
That's really good.
Intercourse.
Hold your asses.
That's really good.
Hey, Alan, you can do it really well.
really bad. Alan, do you have any more checks mix? Are you sure you wouldn't prefer the
muddy buddies? Which is the best kind of checks mix? That's very funny. Is muddy buddies
with the chocolate? Yeah, puppy chow's another name for it. Muddy buddies to me sounds like
a pair of underwear covered in shirts. That's exactly my point. It makes me think of shit.
Yeah, like you ask, hey, honey, can you go clean up Brian? I think he's got a case of the muddy
Yeah, I got to get out of this party. I have had a muddy buddy.
You ever show yourself, John?
More times than I'd like to remember. Oh, wow.
Never like I can't control my bowels and I've now shit myself. I wish I had a diaper on but laying in bed
probably sick, right, flu, whatever, and I push a fart out and I get to I get two way too confident
And then you got to miss and then you just got to lay there in it for hours.
Yeah, she's the worst part. I wish you had called me because you didn't have to deal.
I, uh, I did not, I was getting off the highway once coming home from Vegas.
And if you miss this one turn off, the next one's like an hour and 20 minutes.
And sure enough about 10 minutes into that.
John, I was like, Oh, no.
But I wasn't about to turn back because you just want to get home from Vegas as quickly as possible.
So my guy can make it an hour
Not not true. So I'm like, okay, this is a problem and I
Parked my car outside of this bathroom. There was a huge line
Because it's like the one stop. There's two gas engines across the street from each other
And I pushed my way through every one to the front of the line and I just yelled in this woman's face
I'm really sorry. It's an emergency. I'm really sorry and everyone in the line got it
Nobody gave me any shit. No pun intended and the guy comes out and I jump in there
And as I'm walking in the guy looks me in the eye and go sorry, man
I go what I open there and this is how much of a germ freak I am. It looked like he had been throwing shit
Around the bathroom and I was so disgusted that I almost vomited
But I also was about to go to the bathroom and I looked at it and I was like even in my state
I cannot do this and I sprinted taking a chance a big chance to the gas station across the street
I got there a little like a paddle wheel attached to a key. I threw it open
It was a maculet and I thanked Christ that I had made it and you made it and I made it
She didn't shoot your pants, but even if I had I would have felt good about not going in the style
I thought I was gonna end with you shitting your pants. No, it's the closest stuff come
I've never actually crossed the threshold. Uh, I was in uh, oh there's more stories
Where the hell was I?
Church. Denmark. Denmark
mark or Norway. I did a tour over there a little while back and we were on the road. Yeah,
we were on the road and I had an attack because I had eaten at a McDonald's over there which
not that it was not clean or not good or whatever. The weird thing about McDonald's over there is
they try to make it taste like you made it at your house. Yeah. Which is fucking gross. It makes it
worse for some reason? Right. If I went to your house and you came over here and I was like
and you didn't know what a big Mac was and I was like, hey man, I'm gonna put these two patties
on a roll. Yeah. A thousand. I would dress you be like, this is disgusting. Yeah. Get it out of my face.
So anyway, I ate this stuff and I was like, oh my god, I'm gonna I just was an emergency and I went
in every stall. There were now the nice thing about it over there was the doors for the stalls and the
rest up. Floor to ceiling. You're fully in a closet. Wow. Which is beautiful. You never
get that in the rest room and a public place. But everyone I went into, the first one was
no way. And then each consecutive one was worse than the last one. Yeah. It's a real problem.
And I, well, women don't understand. I don't think how bad guys restaurants get. I shit, I shit
standing up. I had to stand up and shit facing the door. And two things happen when you do that.
Number one, you feel like your eyes are going to shoot out of your head. Right. The pressure,
the pushing and the pressure is insane. The second thing, it's three things. The second thing you
think of is, if somebody manages to get this door open, I'm going to be knocked out. Right. Right.
The third thing is, if somebody gets in here and I'm not knocked out, I'm already in prime like
rape condition. Uh -huh. Ashes out, I'm standing up with it perked, perked up in the air,
because odds are somebody's going to open a restroom door and just go straight into rape mode.
Your only defense is that you could shit on the guy, but then if he's got a really bad fetish,
you're in trouble. I think the odds for this are about at powerball levels.
Well, let me tell you, when you're in that five minute span of experiencing it, those odds don't
seen that crazy. Okay. Okay. It's very especially if you're in another country where you don't
really know the language. It's a little frightening. Right. But I got through it. I shitting. And
then I was like, Oh, I think this is how they shit in Asia. They should standing up. Right? Uh -huh.
I believe. Well, why not? Well, they squat, I think. I think some of those bathrooms, it's very
you're standing like a hover over it. Yeah. And I was doing. I was kind of squatting.
Okay. Couldn't sit on it. I mean, it is in a maculate country. I mean, you could
eat off the streets yet the bathroom stalls are like yeah the most beautiful
people I've ever seen I didn't make no sense you realize you still haven't
told us what country this is oh I've had a few guesses I think it was Denmark I
can't fucking remember Joe stores are great because his attention to detail what
do I give a shit you know I'm ready to check out of this whole thing anymore I
don't care
uh Finland who gives a shit that's how Joe's that's the scene for his debut
novel. I think I was in Finland, Denmark. I don't know who gives a shit. It actually
is a good person. It is a great set. It's very Bukowski. Yeah. Yeah. Very honest. This
guy writes from the heart. Okay. You know, we're all gonna die. What's it matter? Boy,
that's the truth, isn't it? Ain't it though. I was thinking today you double my age. I'm
pretty much dead. So like if I once I live what I've already lived, I'll be close to
that. That's crazy. Well, I'm 38 and I figure if I can get at least another 30 years out of
this thing, I'd be pretty happy. But, you know, I'd like to get more than that. I'd like to get
another 50 -60. I'm 35. I think I'm going to hit probably a 75 -80. Why do you want to get a history of
heart problems in my family? You know, now a history of mind problems in my mom's side. It's just to
cut a recipe for disaster. Well, you're giving yourself a pretty liberal age for a guy that's
for a lunatic with a heart problem. Not a lunatic. But you will be. Yeah, no, definitely.
You're not going to be remembered to take those blood thinners. What are you going to do? I don't
know. You don't know. I think I have a lot less stress in my life than the man in my family who
have preceded me because they were all men who I admire a great deal. But they were really scrounging
for that next paycheck every single week. Maybe they wouldn't put food on the family's table. Maybe
Maybe they wouldn't hard work in men.
My dad was doing a lot of drywall construction.
I've had a much more charmed life.
You know what I'm saying?
Sure.
That puts a lot less miles on a man.
Well, I've only a pussy.
I'm not.
But theoretically, but you also work in television, would I?
Which I would say could be the most stressful of all industries.
Fair enough.
It could be mentally taxing, sure.
But right now, my life's not that stressful.
I truly hope you don't die of some kind
a heart mental condition. Thank you. It would break my heart to see you out on the streets,
talking to yourself in a bathrobe. Yeah. Let's say we're maybe three, four years away from that
happen. Good. That's good. If you're watching the movie with us folks Daniel Radcliffe is now going
through a box of letters. He's inside the woman in black. We have not had a woman in black sighting
yet. No, which is odd because I feel as if we've been watching this film for four hours. Where am I
How long has it been on?
Do you see Crimson Peak?
We talked about it now.
I like Crimson Peak, but the beginning of Crimson Peak,
the woman, the creepy old woman is telling her daughter.
She's like, I'm going to die now.
But beware of Crimson Peak.
Beware of Crimson Peak.
There's like 10 times throughout the movie
this ghost of this old woman comes to her
and is like, always beware for Crimson Peak is at hand.
And then she made it.
And what is Crimson Peak?
She marries this guy.
The first place he takes her is this blood red mountain.
And she's like, yeah, all right, it looks pretty cool to me.
Let's stay here.
It's a red mountain.
It's like a red mountain.
I go, you tell me to look out for Crimmy Peas.
Here we are.
I'm looking out for Crimmy Peas.
So what is the thing to be where?
Now let me guess what the movie is about.
All right.
It was a beautiful looking movie.
Yeah, kind of stupid.
I didn't watch it.
It's worth watching.
I didn't care to see it because it didn't look at all
It's scary to me. It looked like a graphic novel and I thought this will probably look pretty, but I don't care. You're right, but it looked real pretty. Okay, so first thing first I was right about that.
Let me guess what the plot is. Okay.
The brother and sister have to kill the wife of the brother as some sort of sacrifice to the haunted house and the brother and sister might may or may not be sexually involved.
You're not that far off and we'll tell me that no, you're not that far off
I mean to save any more than that would be kind of spoiling it. I'm saying spoil it. I don't care
What are listeners mine? It's all right, Joe. That's all I really remember. They're happening. I mean they try to kill her
And they're bad and their brother and sister who might be sexually into each other. Okay. I don't believe the tell you remember
Did you notice now the road to the island where Daniel Radcliffe is staying is buried? Yeah under water
submerged. What did you think of Shutter Island? I like Shutter Island I thought I was
interesting. I'm always a little disappointed when in the end it just turns out to be like it's
yeah I was all in his head and he's crazy even though even though it all came together very clever
yeah is it cleverfully or cleverly cleverly cleverly you know when you're like oh that person
was his nurse and this was that and that was cool but I liked it you know for
Scorsese you know first time out into the world of horror and suspense it
was impressive I gotta say I really fucking loved it and when I watch it again
recently I really fucking loved it really I think a lot of times with a movie like
that you know and I bet Shyamalan could benefit from this as well is you're so
built up for the twist or the thing at the end or like what your expectations are
the movie that if you watch a movie a second time a lot of times you know where it's going and you
can really respect it a lot more because it all the time. Who else is in Crimson Peak? I don't
remember. No, Diac. I'm in my favorite movie. I like it over and over and over. Who else is in
Shutter Island? Excuse me. It is DiCaprio. It is uh who's the old guy in it? Cromwell? James Cromwell?
That might be wrong. Is tutorial in it? No. Is Jackie Earl Haley any? Yes, Jack Earl Haley is. He is. And he's letters wife Michelle Williams. Yes, that's right.
She was a real intense scene when she drowns her fucking kids.
But she's like the nurse in the end, right? Yeah. She's not a bad guy at the end. I think that's bad. Yeah. I want to say fair enough.
I tell you the more I have to take in the more stress as we talked about mental stress the less I remember about movies
I like specific plot details. I would have been able to write a lot for every move I've ever seen in my life
And now I just let stuff out. I don't need to remember this specific plot of Shutter Island. Sure
I loved it and I'll move on. I at one point in my life was able to tell you the real name of every contemporary rapper
Yeah, I was such a rap fan and and where they were from right
easily. You could have hit me with anybody I could have told you their name. Yeah.
Barely remember now at this point. Can you still do your states and caps which I
used to be a master of and that would probably fail. Never knew my states and
caps. Never cared to. Yeah. Didn't see the point. I was sort of known as and again
folks. I hate to brag. I was kind of known as the states and caps guy in like
third grade. I knew him all maybe. I knew about secret states that they never
or told the world about what their capitals were.
Couldn't care less.
Don't see the point in knowing the states and caps.
Yeah.
Couldn't point out most states on a map.
I know where the big ones are.
Your key states, your California's, your New York's,
your Florida's, your Texas's.
Yeah, here's what you wanna hear this joke
that I just in my mind wrote for Woody Allen.
Sure, maybe I can get it on his new Netflix series,
whatever the hell it is, Amazon.
Amazon, we're giving him more.
Is he gonna be in it?
Yeah, with Miley Cyrus. He's in it. Yeah, but I hope hopefully not fucking Miley Cyrus. Miley Cyrus is in it. Yeah, it's those two
It's the two of them. Yeah, that's great. And he's writing and directing it. Yeah. Oh, that's awesome
I love and Elaine May is in it who is a comedy genius. I love Elaine May so much. Oh, that's great. I love it
Anyway, here's the joke. I just wrote for what I am I guess you could say I live in two states
New York and confusion
Oh God, it's a horrible joke.
You two states in New York and anxiety.
Is that better?
No.
In a state of anxiety.
You see it coming for a mile away.
You got to mask it a little better.
Fuck you.
I just came up with it.
You got to mask it a little better.
You put that in his joke tonight and it kills tonight.
This is how you got to do that one.
You got to go.
It's probably playing clarinet somewhere.
You got to go a little bit back about me,
my background is born in the state of New York. Eventually I took a
president's state of turmoil. That's how you do that joke. Okay, that's how
you do that. That's how he would do it. We go out there and we see what the
public decide. We'll let the guy who lives above you who almost spatted my hair
tonight. Well folks, here it is. The first ever we'll see you in
elk contest. Send your votes to Twitter. Who had the better version of the
What do you know Joe? I don't think I'm gonna win this one, but that's fine.
Um, I was, I, the guy didn't spit at me. The guy who lives above Joe's spad olugie that just missed my
Kind of upsets me that the upstairs neighbor is hawking Snotty Lugies off of the balcony. He missed me. He wasn't aiming for me. I know
That's an important thing to know. There's only six of us that live here. It's like, you know, yeah
It wasn't a great way to to come see an old friend, but well
He also doesn't live there. He's just visiting. Okay, so it's waiting to spit on me when I leave. Yeah
you can probably hear every word we're saying as you can hear there's not there's not a problem
with noise transfer in the department folks I've moved into a one bedroom and I mean you just hear
everything yeah everywhere and it's been a good exercise for my nerves because I'm not going crazy
even though I wake up every morning at 7 a .m. and having had a decent night sleep in two months and by
the way I'm not saying like oh 7 a .m. boohoohoo I'm saying my job I work at night mostly so you know
my eight hours ends at like 10 a .m. usually. And I'm not getting that I'm not
getting anywhere near near close to that. I feel like I have a kid. Maybe that's
what this experience is about. Maybe I should just go have a baby now because
I'll be used to waking up. I said this on the last podcast. Maybe the two of us
need to have babies with other people when I kill myself. Could you imagine anything
worse? I mean, I mean, I mean, I can't do it. I couldn't do it.
It doesn't appeal to me.
Yeah, woman I work with, I was like, how was your weekend?
She goes, uh, my son just shat in my bed.
Kids like 10 years old, took a shit in her bed.
He's shit in her bed.
Yeah, I mean, I don't know if I can deal with all that.
Really?
There's only one guy that's shitting in my bed, and that's me, baby.
And that's umwa.
And sadly, my girlfriend as well.
We both have pretty severe issues with it.
well she's not a guy so that doesn't count right she's a gal uh have you seen any movies
lately that you enjoyed Joe well I believe we said we're gonna talk about this I watch
Good Night Mommy yeah and I thought was a blast and you hated it and I'm surprised by
that look it was very well acted yeah it was very well shot it was very well written
Okay, that all sounds good to me.
The reveal at the end of how it all kind of came together was well executed.
This is a rave review.
Well, look, my problem was I signed on, you know, I don't care.
I'm going to say the spoiler.
So if you don't want to hear this, cover your ears.
I signed on for a movie about two kids thinking the woman in their house was not their mother.
It was a lunatic imposter.
Within three minutes of the movie beginning, it becomes painfully obvious that one of the brothers does not exist.
That this is not going to be what the movie is about.
It was not obvious to me, but I'm still.
Within five minutes, I'm not exaggerating. Within five minutes, I was like, oh, so that other brothers dead.
I don't like to ruin movies for myself. I let them wash over me.
So anyway, I didn't try to. It just popped in my head because it was so obvious.
right she's never talking to the sun she doesn't know who has two kids she doesn't
make the other kid food I mean it's like it's like that's like the first three
scenes you're like all right so anyway so that that was too obvious and I thought okay
well I'll give it the benefit out maybe that's what they want me to think and then
it's like no not really that's just kind of what it is and then it becomes very
obvious soon after that like that this is their mother clearly and she's experienced
some kind of traumatic event and that's why she's acting so strangely. And then it starts to
become even more clear like, oh the mother's not acting that strangely. The kid is fucked up.
There's something with this kid. I really love that journey of a moment. And then it turns very
cool. And then it turns into a torture movie. Yeah. And it's just this depraved thing where you're
like, okay, so this kid's a psycho and I just feel horrible for this woman now. It's like terrible.
I don't think I'm like I don't watch this. I was excited about this scary thriller where it was like
This fucking crazy lady lives in our house. We don't know who she is
well
Every movie doesn't have to put you at ease Joe. I don't know. I don't like stuff like that. I should go watch that
Log in front of a fireplace for a couple hours calm yourself. Yeah, hostile is the only movie that involves like torture and stuff that I like
I love to hostile and hostile to starring beauty Phillips who I made out with once
I didn't care for hostile to, but I like hostile one quite a bit.
And the main reason I love hostile one is because there's vengeance at the end.
Like the kid gets, the kid gets his, gives them their come -upence and you're rooting for him and
it's exciting and you want him to win in the end. Whereas with good night mommy, it's like,
it's just like, oh no, so nobody wins.
That was a nihilistic movie.
It's just, it's just like typical of a lot of like the overseas horror movies,
Where it's like it's gonna be this one thing for a little while and then it's gonna turn out to not be that
And it's just gonna be somebody to privately torturing somebody for it for the best version of that's audition
I fucking love dodged. I hate it to me. That's one of the best horror movies ever met. I hate it
It's not a horror movie. I actually screamed when I saw audition. I hate it. Look at it. Put pins in his eyeballs. Oh, okay, great
So this is like just like an awful
Part of horror too
Like that's a poor to horror you don't enjoy that's fun that to me isn't hard to me horror has to involve
You can't just show me something disturbing and go that's horror
Because that's not entertaining to me
Do you know what I mean like like yeah, oh look I'd always much rather like a six -sense type movie than a
Fucking Texas chance on master that's kind of more my thing, but here's the thing. I love Texas. I got to play my heart for all of them
I love Texas chainsaw massacre but Texas chainsaw massacre has suspense. I'm not against slash your movies
I thought I didn't had a ton of suspense. Oh, it was just it was like okay
So she's gonna be crazy and obviously from like three quarters of whatever it is and then it's just like she's just gonna do
Horrible things to them now and we just sit here and watch that you're like
But that's why some people some people go to
I don't know I didn't care for it. I didn't care for it. That's fine folks if you're gonna see one of the movies in that genre
Auditions a good one to say and so it's hostile, frankly, I thought I was the best was more of an action movie really
Which I thought was awesome about it. I love hostile. I think it's I think it's a masterpiece. I think it's it
I really loved it to elaborate on what else makes hostile such a great film that these other movies in my opinion don't have
There's an amazing social commentary to it about yeah, and a great sense of humor the buying and selling of people and a lot of nudity
Uh, the justification people make in how it's in what ways it's okay to pay for people to give you services, right?
It was it was it's tremendous. It's a great movie. It's got a lot of depth to it and uh,
and I don't think those other movies do. Now on the flip side of that for Eli Roth is I watch this weekend
the grain inferno. I want to see that. I haven't seen it yet. I
despised it
And, I mean, here's basically my big problem with it.
The whole movie is about like how people, exactly exactly what we were talking about
on the last episode of this podcast, how people will like get on a cause and be all about
it, but never do anything more than just like update their Facebook status.
You know, it's like what you're doing actually less than nothing by saying on your Facebook,
look, you know, power to Paris or whatever.
That's what the movie was supposed to be about.
Starting from that point, he puts these people
really through the ringer.
So clearly the movie should be like
they're gonna go on some really expensive senior trip.
You can keep the same beginning where they're very
insensitive about these issues, but they're all like
pretend and new, they're drum circles.
So it seems like they're interested in this shit.
Okay.
You have them going like a expensive vacation
and the plane crashes in this cannibalistic society
that's like these tribes that they claim to want to help,
but they've never done anything about it.
All right, I wanted it so far.
That to me would be a very interesting movie.
What actually happens is they are activists
and they set up trips to like stand with guns to their head
and try to stop the destruction of rainforests.
So they go, they're plane crashes,
and it's like, but these aren't fake activists.
They went to the Amazon and stood in front of guns, right, to like stop this place from being torn down. So when they're punished by
All these cannibals who are literally eating them while they're alive eating their brains and arms and legs and everything for hours
You know
Then it would mean something sure like it just really was like these are people who are trying to actually do something good
And now they're going to get eaten where the whole point and in interviews that I've read with him since because I was so frustrated by the movie
He's like this movie is a straight -on critique of doing nothing is him or whatever you call it fakedivism fake -dism or something
Hacked his bism something like that. Okay. He said it's got to be a direct critique of that
But it's just not because these aren't people
Updated there like if they were like I hate
Let's say okay. Here's the short twilight zone version of it
a little girl writes on her Facebook, everyone please support the Amazon rainforest, send
your money, I love them when I, then she goes in a trip, lands in the Amazon and they
eat her, she didn't do it, okay, she's getting punished for not caring, but you can't have
this woman do a lot of activist work, right, and start to like really get into charity and
like thinking about people other than yourselves, and then have them punished by those people
because actually the message is not only a bad message but the message is like don't
ever try to help people right including these poor third world countries and stuff because
they're all going to eat you leave them to die if that's the message of the movie then what
what the hell is that and it made all this disgusting cannibal shit which is part of the genre of course
but it made you just feel terrible for these people and actually the worst person in the movie a guy
who master bates seconds after this girl and the cage with them is killed and
eaten and they go why are you masturbating and he goes you all should do the
same thing because it'll keep your mind clear. He's sitting in jacking up like
he's clearly the worst of these characters. That's disgusting and he is never
killed. The good people in the movie are all killed one by one. It's like what are
you saying here? It sounds like the plot to the last Rambo movie, except I love
that one. I like the last random. Yeah. And that had a fucking message too. Where those activists
are going up and they said we want to make a change and he wards them. You're not changing
shit up there. Don't go up there and then they do. And then he has to go in and save them.
And they get slaughtered. Yeah. I guess they didn't bother me there because it was just such a dumb
movie otherwise. Rambo. But like to me, Salona saying like it's not worth helping these people.
Which isn't great either right doesn't bother me because Rambo is like a nihilist dude, right this movie was just like
I don't know it just made all the disgusting shit no like there's there's several cases in the movie of female
General mutilation that you just sit and watch they show it to you. Yeah, I mean not you know close up
Now all am I watching these people punished who are trying to help
Yeah, I was listening to the Eli Roth podcast. He does a podcast. I'm sorry. I was listening to the Brady Stinnellas podcast with Quentin Tarantino, and they talked about this movie on it and Brady Stinnellas said that the death of the fat guy was very disturbing. It was. What was it? Tell me about it.
Well, he's the first one yet said, but he didn't what happens he's a big
fact. I he's been really nice the whole movie too. They sort of make him
drink this stuff. Then they lay him down and this woman like looks like she's
kind of giving him the sign of the cross and she jams her thumb into his
forehead, pulls out some brain, starts eating it. He's still alive and like
children are ripping off his legs and arms. He's still alive. She saw his tongue
off he's still alive and they don't cut away from it just goes on and on and on and he
had been like a nice dude that's it that's it and they all eat him you know okay it's gross how
does he manage to get her thumb through his far head that was not explained unless it was this they
they're always rubbing like creams on them they're like loosen them up loose that's really yeah I just
wish I hadn't watched it was really gross and my favorite movie in recent years
however is Wild Tales which I told Joe to watch, rented it, fucking loved it, you
know my girlfriend kept running around my house going, these are some wild tales,
these tales are getting wilder by the minute and they were. It was six wild
tales, tales of revenge, Argentinian movie, it is the fucking shit, if you have a
problem with foreign movies it won't bother you there's not a lot of subtitles and it's just six
amazing stories I fucking loved it you should check it out all right I don't think it's streaming
free anywhere but you can probably run it for three bucks on it and you told me that this was a
sort of a pulp fictiony kind of thing yeah the stories don't intertwine in that way but it was just as
like the stories were just as cool and surprising and everything all right twisting and turning anybody
Nobody we know in this picture or is it all just it's all overseas people overseas people. Okay. Who are people to judge? I'm not saying that I'm not saying that that don't you put those words in my mouth. Don't you do that to me. Don't you put those fingers in my mouth by the way. I haven't said anything for the last hour. It's really annoying when I'm trying to speak on a podcast. Don't you put that thumb through my heart and soldier entire fingers and hand it in my mouth. If you're watching the movie with us. Daniel right click click. Cliff.
That is not being haunted by the woman in black.
The mattress on the bed is coming up with some sort of ghostly period scenario.
And there's a figure now rising out of the puddle on the bed, which is gross.
And who is that figure?
Is it a young boy?
I believe it is.
It's a child that was left in mud.
It looked like that.
You ever seen that peanut butter, baby?
No, I did not.
What does a vine?
I think it's like they've covered like a two -year -old baby from head to toe in peanut butter and the baby
I look at the camera and I'm like, eh, it's horrifying. It's one of the most popular vines which tells you how
who covered the baby in peanut butter? The parents I would assume. That's not like abusive in some way.
It probably is, but people are laughing too hard to care.
Is that that's disturbing? Yeah. All right. I mean, can he breathe and stuff?
Yeah, he can breathe. He can breathe. I assume they didn't like jamming his nose.
Now after our potter looks a bit like McCullough Colcombe's does. Who Radcliffe? Yeah, a little bit.
They got a bit of he's got a bit of a Colken vibe. Modern day Colks.
Now I'll tell you this, we just watched Radcliffe experience sites of terror one after the next.
he looks like he's about to fall asleep yeah he's now going back out to the main land or whatever
from this island where the haunted house is you think the director would have been like Daniel let's
try one where you look like you've ever been scared in your entire life I mean I don't know why
he goes back to the house after this he doesn't look that scared but what's happening now there's people
being burned. There's a fire and he's going into save what I think he
believes is a child inside because in the house he saw a thing on the wall that
said you could have saved him. So I think he thinks that was a sign and now he's
going to go in here and try to save somebody from this burning building. And he
just ran right in. You know what I liked. Which is what I would do. That's why I
liked it. I'd be a hero like that. You know what I mean? Yeah. You see that in
me, right? I thought, I mean, you know, I'd put you at a 50 -50. You know, I just I feel
like a real hero, you know, I feel like I really have it in me. The woman in black is
there in the fireman being. What are you singing? A real hero. Well, we just
watched a child commit suicide. It's also very loud. It is kind of loud, but this is
the first part that's been loud because a child committed suicide so I guess
they cranked the music up a bit for this. Lot of smoke. Let me tell you if you
were in that amount of smoke, do you know how quickly you'd have smoke inhalation?
Yeah. In that amount of smoke. Joe, do you feel it's true the old expression where
there's smoke, there's fire? You know, I always believed in that one. Yeah. But I
always equated it to STD's as my dad taught me. What does that mean? Like if you see a
bubble. There's probably going to be more bubbles in your future. No, he literally would say if you see
smoke coming out of a lady's pants, she's probably burning. Yeah. Uh, no, he never said that.
I, yeah. Well, you know, what else would there be if there was smoke, a fog machine?
Yeah, but I mean, I guess the expression means if you suspect something, it's probably true.
Yeah. Okay. I suspect it. Well, I don't agree with it because I suspected that we were almost
done with this movie. And I think we're about 50 minutes in. Yeah. Uh, I am struggling right now
because I stopped paying attention to the film. I don't know what's happening. He's
plus. No, I've seen it before. Just go same by the same. Yeah. Even though I've seen this before,
I'm lost. I can't remember why he took this job. I don't understand why he will leave this house.
They said, how would you like to work in a creepy house with ghosts that are trying to kill you?
I mean do our book work. Why are the why are the ghosts showing up everywhere?
I don't remember that either. I think somebody killed ourselves in the house, right?
Where is he now? He's in this guy's house. Yeah. This guy's bringing him a whiskey.
Rackup looks like he could use a ham sandwich before he gets that whiskey.
Yeah, Radcliffe does look quite a macy. He has a very Fiona Apple vibe to him right now.
I couldn't sing one Fion Apple song if you had a gun to my head right now I couldn't
remember.
You ready when you cast your spell, right?
I'm going to get weird out on the horn.
You've never heard of Fiona apples on if you know Apple is I know her song gorgeous. I couldn't
an amazing songwriter. I couldn't recall. That's a by the way gorgeous is a distant sea. I couldn't
recall any of them from memory is what I'm saying. Yeah. What if you had to do a weird out spoof what would
you do? What song would you do? Well I already wrote it and it was a big hit in the sixth grade.
A little song called Losing My Pet Pigeon, which was a spoof of losing my religion.
No, I got it.
You didn't need to explain.
People loved it.
Mine was also in our EM song.
Really?
Yeah, it was a spoof of stand.
Was it shiny, crappy, poop hole?
No.
That's off the top of my head.
No, it was a takeoff on...
I get zero from Joe.
It was a takeoff.
Because I want to tell you about mine and you're just telling me more shiny crappy poo poo well
I was starting to understand and you're just coming in with your own ideas. Okay, which is selfish. Your song was called what?
Queen. Oh, no
Queen in the place where you pee. Oh, God
Queen from the place where you pee
Man, it stinks. Oh
Joe, you gotta stop singing that
just look around and see everybody sick queen from the place where you pay how how
do you have sex ever I just made that up on the spot I thought that was funny oh I
thought that was something you wrote when you were a child I believe that just now I
made it up I'm hard to believe you just wrote that as an adult I made it up all right you wouldn't
listen to that song. I just did. And the answer is no. Again, knowing what I know now,
I wouldn't. Why not? I don't have to answer my questions to you. I don't have to answer
your questions. And often it's funerals. I'll sing this. I'll sing. Would you believe
they put a man in the tomb, man in the tomb? All right. Oh, that's good. And it's clean.
You didn't have to work blue and I was saying it just like bill calls, but you select your people on remember Bill
It said you guys don't have to work blue. You got to be like me
You got to be an upstanding
Society where is his pants button all well what he said and then what he did and it's terrible. It's a very disappointing story
Oh, sorry Joe if my truth bothers you. It's just I'm still not over losing the
childhood hero. It's still heartbreaking to me
Hey, sorry America, if my truth's too much.
Hey, I didn't know I was doing a podcast with Jamie Kielstein.
I don't know who that is.
He's a truth teller, man.
Oh, well, then yeah, I guess I am Jamie Trillstein.
Kielstein.
Okay, I guess I am Jamie Kielstein.
Girls, look out for that woman in black.
Now, how would losing my pet pigeon go?
I don't remember the lyrics.
Well, the chorus.
That's me in the corner, that's me with the bird seed.
I don't know, right?
That's pretty good.
What the hell could you do with it?
I don't even know.
Uh, no, right there.
I think you just answered that.
Losing my pet pigeon.
Did you love where it all has a boy?
Of course.
There we tell the story to you about getting where it all is.
The autograph when I was very young, young boy.
No.
I was at six flags over mid -America in St. Louis.
It was my first concert, and it was to see Weird Al, and I was shaking.
I was so excited.
Sure.
Tired day.
I was so excited.
I was about 11 years old.
My mom took me.
And then we're waiting in line for the Buccaneer, which is the big pirate ship that goes back and forth.
Yeah.
And my mom goes, oh my gosh, Pat, I think that's Weird Al.
And he was in line like one row behind me.
to wear like when our rows crossed we were going to be like right next to each
other holy shit what the hell's he waiting in lines for I don't know he was
probably just a nice guy weird out can't cut off kids in line at a amusement park
you know good point so he's got this beautiful blonde and his arm possibly a
prostitute like hiding her face from the sun hiding it in his armpit you think
it was a hooker maybe it just seemed too good to be true for weird out but he's a
rich man, I guess. Right. Um, and I had told my mom this joke earlier, we were waiting
in line. I go, Mom, how much does a pirate pay for corn? She was how much I go a buck
in here. Oh, boy. Yeah. Well, we're in line for the buck in here. That's very good. So
she goes, Pat, you should tell weird out your joke. And I go, no, no. And then as we pass
each other, my mom goes, can my son tell you a joke real quick? And I'm like, Mom, he
He goes, yeah, sure.
So I tell him my joke, Buccaneer.
Guy gives me a big, hardy laugh.
Signs a piece of paper that I still have to this day.
Could have been nicer.
And that was that.
And if I wanted to.
And if I wanted to lie, like everyone else here.
Exactly.
Like in the movie Fear.
Now see what other people tell this story and lie.
Like everyone does with their like origin story.
Then they would be like, and Weird Al told me like,
he got to keep writing jokes, kid.
and now I'm Dave Chappelle.
No, that never happened.
Of course it didn't happen,
but everyone who tells their comedy story tells it like that.
And I don't believe you.
Well, everybody's a lion piece of shit.
Yeah.
Now I want to get in touch with Weirdo and pitch -queeth.
He works clean though.
Is it too old of a song to reference at this point?
It absolutely is.
Also, it should probably rhyme,
so you know what's being parodyed.
Does it have to rhyme?
Standard.
I don't weave.
I don't think they all rhyme.
I will say that doesn't rhyme with bad. That's what's close enough. I think America's ready for a song about Queens. I
Love Queen Fumer. I always have I
Think it's very funny. I like period jokes quite a bit. Yeah, I just like that kind of thing smelly balls
I just like this sort of stuff. Okay shit jokes. I'm not above them. You're kind of like a
the, uh, sort of a high -brow, like a George Wallace type, like a, uh, who's the guy?
Not George Wallace, the comedian who's one of the funniest men in the world.
And this has already fallen apart.
I meant George Wallace, the quote humorist who used to be on 60 minutes all the time.
Yeah, I'm a very New Yorker type.
Yeah.
But I like this kind of stuff.
Let's see, like this scene, the movie, Daniel Radcliffe is, is, uh, submerging mud and
I'm pretending it's poop and it's making me laugh.
Okay.
it's just making me happy it helps you out that's fine yeah pretend he's
swimming through poop it makes the movie funny it makes it horrific to me my
favorite part in Austin Powers when he drinks the poop and goes it's a bit
nutty oh see that's my least favorite part of Austin power that's your least
favorite yeah that's not for me that kind of joke I love that joke I love that
joke it's coffee tastes like shit it is shit Austin yeah that's not for me I
I find it very funny.
Now I really, this is a moment where I wish we were paying attention.
What is this guy doing here?
He's got Danny Radcliffe tied to a rope.
Right.
He's pulling him out of it.
Very unlimited story move.
Yeah.
He's trying to pull, he's got the rope tied to his car.
He's trying to back the car up to pull Radcliffe out of this mud hole.
Right.
He's having no luck which I don't get.
I mean, how hard could it be?
I guess it's I guess the suction is you know, oh no, they're trying to pull that thing out
I'm sorry the rope was not tied direct that the rope was tied to this
To this thing they're pulling out of the mud. I tried to solve the mystery
I assume with the dead shoulder and look at this. They're pulling a goddamn car out of the mud
So you're giving like a a true play -by -play of the scene. Well, I mean, you know
It's the least I can do for the people that really want to know what's going on in the woman in black.
Not only a car, but a goddamn carriage is coming out.
Well, it's just a carriage. I thought it was a car, and I missed.
What if there was a horse on the front being dragged out too?
Covered in poop. A poop. He's got a little boy's body there from the carriage.
The horse looks on the camera and goes, get me out of here.
And I ate horse and around
Right, and then they never mentioned again it goes right back to being a horror movie right here
Right, right yeah
I'm screaming myself horse over here and I thought the horse they shot had a bad day
I can't think of a famous horse that died
Oh, I was gonna say old Yeller don't look a gift me in the mouth. That one doesn't make sense
Now he's calling the body of a young boy covered in mud who is dead. Yeah
Oh, now we couldn't show us a little
Little Medreff Potter
I don't know the way they dress back then this guy just got pulled out of a mud pit
He had to get cleaned up. He's now putting on a full white silk button down shirt
Yeah, he's putting essentially another suit on right right. He's got a vest on a tie. This is this is this is cash
Yeah, you know, I'll tell you you give me a bathrobe and a towel for around my head any day of the week when I get caught in the rain
Well nowadays, I mean
People are wearing you know pair of boxer shorts to a to a casino to a fine casino. That's right, you know
You find a nice casino like the commerce here in LA. Yeah
that serves a money Christo Sandwich.
There's no sense of dressing up for things anymore.
And California's even worse out at the most.
My friend John Harwitz, dear friend of mine,
once took me to the Commerce Casino here in LA
and wore a suit.
No, no.
Because he felt that it was better to dial out.
Unless it was a swimsuit, he made a mistake.
I wore a suit because he felt like it was good
to dial it up for the dealers
and maybe get some free stuff.
And then he ordered a money Christo Sandwich
and spilled the white powder sugar all down the front of the suit.
I mean it was just a picture of trash in action. It was really nice.
The Monte Cristo, if I'm not mistaken, is a ham sandwich on French toast?
Ham turkey cheese on French toast with powdered sugar on top.
It's a delicious sandwich. I don't blame for it.
The commerce casino is very disgusting. It's the one I'm thinking of.
It just looks like an elk's lodge, like a wreck haul kind of.
Yeah, it's a kind of like a big room with all the games in it. Yeah, that's what I've been to.
And thank God I hate it because I would have been out there every couple of nights.
But there was an old Chinese man next to me.
Leaning completely into my space and gnawing.
Like gnawing as if he had no teeth on this giant turkey leg.
Oh, at the commerce casino. He's balancing a plate like almost on my arm. Big pieces of chicken falling out of his mouth.
I love a giant turkey leg.
He was eating it almost in my mouth.
Do you ever get the giant?
Is this supposed to be real or a toy?
No, it's real. The rabbit thing he just found up.
Oh, it's just a toy.
This is like that he's luring out the woman in black.
back. Okay. I thought that was supposed to be an actual animal. I was like,
no, no, it's supposed to be that he's whining up. You don't have ILM, but let's get
something. Let's let's let's at least get Spielberg on the job. I mean, that was supposed to
believe a monkey's playing the Morakas, so be it. That's, uh, I see some Morakas there in
a front row with my plan with. Don't get mad at me. Don't get mad at me, you. That's
Pat's famous skeptical guido is named that character
That's the name of that character. I don't know why we got to go in on it house. I mean
Didn't see that cool to me. I don't know
I'm supposed more of a scared. I was gonna join in but you just don't want to see me let me get a word in it
Would you shine? What can I let you shine? Oh, I don't want to anymore. All right good. I just saw that we have about 10 or 12 minutes
Let's in this film and the relief that washed over me. It was like it was like we're gazing
Joe we are supposed to be putting on a product that people love to listen to listen people you can't even get through
The people seem to like it no matter how much we complain. Yeah, no matter how slow that the conversation gets
I thought that I was the was a good time. I almost said a lot of fun that I downgraded it to a good time
I had a good time wasn't a lot of fun. I had a good time, but I'm a little hot. My apartment's very hot right now sure is
I paid too little attention to the movie this week
I've no idea what the hell's happening even though I own this film. Yeah, I don't know what's happening right now
It's okay. We each had one drink which has now left me in that weird
Kind of sweaty. I had one drink zone, you know
I had a gluten -free beer and it was
Disgusting what's disgusting about it?
Well, it's missing like some key ingredient of beer and you you really tasted it tasted like
spoiled water it was disgusting
It was like Bud Light with like a hint of an expired cranberry in it, and I hated it.
I hated expired cranberry.
Yeah, at least favorite cranberry.
Take them off the shelves when they get expired folks.
I'm in there buying cranberries five, six nights a week, and I like them fresh.
Your friend who I met yesterday who was very lovely has a son who's 11 who writes a blog.
Yeah, the kids are damn genius.
And I read the blog today.
And he's the Buddhist by the way.
Yeah, I read the blog that it's 11 year old kid. It's like a kid that's not published. Yeah, he's like a doogie house or time, but at one point, he made a joke in one of the entries where he's like, he's like, let's say you're eating a Fiji apple parentheses because all other apples taste like.
And they shit on all the other apples. I came over the analogy. He's roast an apple. And then he puts an asterix under the piece. You get through the whole piece and then under it. The very bottom is an asterisk. And it says, promise I won't be an apple racist ever again.
It's nice. I mean, I was like, this kid's 11. Yeah, he's great. I mean, he's got two funny parents. It's probably a big part of it.
One of the one of the entries was called, I don't care if God exists or not. Yeah.
And the first sentence of the blog entry was, in quotes, and I don't care if you exist, comma, said, says God,
petulently. Yeah. The 11 -year -old wrote this. Yeah. He's a very impressive young man. I've
wasted everything. I've wasted it all. That's scary man. Check out the kid's blog. It's called
Some Idiots blog is the name of it. Yeah, it's on Squarespace. He's a very smart, very funny kid. Yeah.
What, Pat? What? Spitted out, Pat. I thought of when you were talking about him making fun of
apples. Is this a funny sketch? It would be like a 10 year old boy. And it's the comedy central
roast of like Brussels sprouts. Okay. Would that be, you think it'd be a pretty funny sketch?
Like five kids get up and rip on wide Brussels sprouts. If you could get the kids to take on the
demeanor of adult. Yeah, no, of course, then it would be very fun. And like, maybe by the end,
it's like some kid who's like real crude about it. Yeah. You know, yeah, shove these up your
mother's twat, you know, like a five year old boy. Well, you got to have the kid that's doing like
Nick DiPolo like all hunched over like like you know what I mean like close to
the mic let me tell you some folks but one of the Brussels sprouts yeah this
thing would be amazing I think yeah if you definitely need a Lisa Lampanelli
some heavy set young girl she's very thin these days I don't like it I do often
find a bit of sadness when somebody I know as being heavy set loses weight yeah
I know Lisa as a friend so I was happy for her that it was good for her to do that
But I never I don't know I don't know in any way on a personal level Seth Rogan or Jonah Hill
I will say this I did not like Jonah Hill thinning out. I was happy to see him get fat again
Yeah, I agree and I'm not crazy about thinning out Seth Rogan. I like these guys husky
All right
Not in a mean way because I want to see them fail. It's just weird
I hear you, I hear you, I hear you.
Newman slimmed down, Wayne Knight.
Newman's in kind of a Hell Caesar, actually.
But he kind of puffed out again, right?
Yeah, he's fat again.
Is he Newman fat again?
The audience, there was such a huge laugh of delight
when Newman came on the screen.
I love Newman.
He doesn't even say anything, but he was good in it.
He has a couple lines.
Now is he Newman heavy again?
Or is he just heavier than thin?
He looks like a guy who lost a ton of weight
and then put a ton of weight back on.
But it's not as bad as he was in early Newman days. All right. Well, that's good
That's more like buttoned up paris lacks Newman by the end. Okay. That's fine. I can look at that
Yeah, I'm happy
Healthy I just you know, I hear you just get used to it
I hear you we need fat people on this planet now of course for earlier John candy and lost a ton of weight
I don't know if they would have been that's funny
I'll tell you what's his name. Goodman is shaving him off, man. Yeah, I mean he goes
up and down and I like goodman no matter what he's in. I love him. I just saw the trailer
for 10 Cloverfield Lane. It looks amazing. I love Cloverfield. I've not seen the trailer
for 10 Cloverfield. It's apparently not related. It's not a sequel. That makes no sense.
Why would you do that? I don't know, Pat. Am I J .J. fucking Abrams? No, you're not.
not. I bet that the, I just thought of, I just thought of the nictipolo joke for the
Brussels sprouts roast. Okay, go for it. Let me tell you the Comedy Central roast
of Brussels sprouts. Yeah. Roasted Brussels sprouts. Oh, that's funny. I got you. Yeah, you're
goddamn right. That's fine. I got you. All right, carry on. Let me tell you something, folks.
If I wanted to eat green disgusting balls, I go suck Kermit the frog's cock
That's a perfect Brussels sprouts roast Joe. Could we find parents to let their kids do these jokes?
I think probably so in this sick fucking town
Yeah, they offer him a like Simba in the line. Yeah
Take parents paying you
Okay, now it's gonna be he's gonna be
Under our supervision for like a month and a half you won't be able to see him take him
Please take him have some money. Yeah, please treat yourself because you're all
Yeah, it's a disgusting town. We live in we live out here in Hollywood. Holly weird. I call it. Hey, that's yeah
I call it hazy wood because everybody's in a fog
That's me that up just now
Look at Radcliffe's adorable son in this movie
not for me. I think that kids adore what kids not for me. And this is the
part now where Radcliffe dies. I think the kid dies too. It's not a very
happy ending. Now the train and the woman in black comes and yeah horror movies
don't have to end happily. Well, I like that it's not a happy ending. Most horror
movies end with too much hope in my opinion these days. American ones. American
shot. I'm good night mommy for ending without help. I listen. I don't like I
I didn't mind that good night mommy ended.
It does end with hope.
It ends with the three ghosts.
Like we're finally together.
Wow.
I don't mind that it ended.
Oh boy.
Well, Radcliffe and his son just got run over by a train.
And now you're going to see the dead children.
That's pretty cool.
In the train.
That's a cool movie.
It's a cool movie.
I'm glad we watched it so carefully.
And then the woman in black.
And everybody's dead.
Yeah, whatever that guy's looking at on the train track can't be pretty. He's looking at the remnants of Radcliffe and the kid
They're not gonna show it because it's a PG -13 film
You know that website the people we got real into in college
That was like pictures of horrific things the now are probably on NBC at night of the week. Oh, he lived
Like a you know like somebody got hit by a truck. I do but hold on Radcliffe lived. I forgot that that happened
Maybe he does now or no, they're dead. They're in heaven
Yeah, that's right because they see the wife or whatever. I think yeah, they're dead
This is very similar to the end of the last Harry Potter movie isn't there a whole thing on like a train thing and
Trans were always backward into Harry Potter. Have you seen all you don't know if he's alive or not?
Have I seen what all the potters? Of course I have they're fucking incredible. You take me for I'm excited for magnificent beasts. I
Am I'm not I can really give or take that guy
Well, I think it'll be a fun flick.
Yeah.
Apparently, it's a prequel.
And your boy Gandalf is, or a dumbledore, excuse me,
is really campaigning to come back.
Has anyone ever done this as a character?
James Gandalf, feigning?
No.
Hey, we got to get to the twit that was.
Right?
I like that.
We got to get the ring back to Bilbo.
I think it's very good.
You should not pass so did you hear me with the fuck you not pass you dumb fuck you could tell you ugly sister
She can I pass needed
Here's my character. I want to do William H. Macy Gray. I don't know how to do it though
We got to get we got to get these characters up and right. I don't have there's not enough famous William H. Macy or Macy Gray things to do that
Care all I know is I try and I barely remember that song
Yeah, you could you could do something out of that. And that's our film folks, it just ended
with them in heaven, finally reunited as a family, because the mom had died early on, but then
the woman in black's watching them. And so what does that mean? Maybe they're not in heaven?
I got a habit over here. I got a habit over here. I got a habit. It's coming out. My god damn
ears. And now AJ won't do his homework. Come out loud. Where's the ZD? Huh? I like it. You
can't say Carmella though. You got to say Samwise. Samwise. Gangie. Which Samwise Gangie,
Gangey sounds like Angie which sounds like an Italian name. Samwise Gangey sounds like it could be like a villain
They bring in for season four of this prank. Oh wait, isn't one of the guys named Sam? No, no
Who's the guy with the white hair? Hey, Tony. I want you to take
Take I want you to meet my cousin. This is a Samwise Gangey's
Hey, I don't Samwise ever see you Sam. What should you be? What you want?
I know your father. I know your father. Sam Dumb Ganges. Okay. I'm breaking your bulls.
I'm breaking your bulls. I'm breaking your bulls. Sam, why is Sam Dumb? You get it.
You know what, Joker? I wish you wouldn't have been earlier. You know what, Joker?
I wish you wouldn't have been earlier. What?
When we were talking about bad dirty grandpa. Yeah. We should have said.
I don't know why did an arrow keep making these movies. Maybe he should change his name to Bobby.
No, Danero.
Oh, that's pretty good.
I know I wish I would have said that.
CR in Hines is that dude's name.
He's a great actor.
Well, folks, you've been listening to We'll See You In Hell.
The podcast brought to you by the Fangoria Podcast Network
produced by Thomas DeFaio, an executive produced by Ken
Hanley, a Fangoria Entertainment,
for press opportunities, advertising inquiries,
and information about We'll See You In Hell.
Contact cannetfangoria .com, follow Pat Walsh on Twitter
at the Patrick Walsh, y 'all. Follow me at Joe DeRosa Comedy on Twitter. And if you are in the,
what's my next? I can't even remember. Oh yeah, Torn in March. If you're around that south,
a bunch of places. I'll be in Wilmington, North Carolina. I'll be in Hattiesburg, Mrs. Cippy. I'll
be in Greenville, South Carolina. I will be in Minneapolis, Minnesota, so come on out in March.
That's all I got. I will be eating at the Glendale Soup Plantation this coming
Thursday. I'll probably start with the salad bar and ease into perhaps Sunday.
Sometimes I like to put the soft serve in my coffee there. Thanks everybody. We
hope you had a good time and I'll see you at Soup Plantation.