Summer is here, and Bed MDM Casino is coming in hot with Casino thrills.
Play your favorite games like Blackjack and Roulette with a live dealer.
Or check out our exclusive slots like MGM Grand Millions and The Wizard of Oz, only available
at Bed MDM Casino.
Spin on spectacular slot favorites like Cashy Woption, 88 fortunes, Mystery of the Lamp, Raken
Bacon, Cash Machine, Flintstones, and Squid Game from anywhere.
Enjoy the thrills of Bet MGM Casino right from the palm of your hand!
Download the Bet MGM Casino app today and get a piece of the action!
Bet MGM in game sense reminds you to play responsibly and offer resources to help you make appropriate
choices.
Bet MGM .com for T's and C's, 21 Plus to Wager, Michigan, New Jersey, Pennsylvania and West Virginia
only.
Games may vary by market.
All promotions are subject to qualification and eligibility requirements.
Rewards issued as normal throwable site credit slash bonus best unless otherwise provided
in applicable terms.
Rewards subject to expiry.
Gambling problem, call 1 -800 -Gamber.
Firestone Complete Auto Care's epic savings advantage is the sign you need to stop putting off your car's maintenance.
And you can save up to $100 on tires and services while you're at it.
Don't wait, call Firestone Complete Auto Care for an appointment.
Hello, everyone. Welcome to the Thanksgiving edition. I'll see you in hell. The podcast brought to you by the Fangoria podcast network for more information about the network, including other programs how to follow this show and other shows and find past episodes of any show.
of course including we'll see you in hell please visit vangoria .com and here we
are I am on one side of your head and my man Pat Walsh hey yeah on the other we're
still getting a few complaints about why the audio is split we just do it so if
you want to watch these movies with us you can send that right up the middle and
it'll feel like you're sitting in between me and Pat on the couch in a nice
Sandwich. Every young lady and gentleman's dream. Yeah. Our podcast today finds us in Los Angeles about
11 .30 in the morning
T minus about 12 hours from T gives thanks giving day. Yeah, we have whiskey in our coffee.
I've got a bear's to admit that to anybody. No, I put a splash in there.
We're doing the prophecy today, not really a Thanksgiving theme movie.
We did thinner last.
We should probably mention this in thinner today, but whatever.
We know oddly enough, until I was doing the introduction with you for thinner, I didn't
put together that I could be making a Thanksgiving show.
I just used my sweet, sweet improv head, and I said thinner even though you get fatter
on Thanksgiving.
But it's not like we planned it.
It's very true.
That was right off the cuff. So let's not beat ourselves up too much. I'm not beating it. I'm not beating anything
Obviously, I currently I can't tie it to Thanksgiving in any way. I'm just thinking there's a religious element
Okay, pretty good. There's not very religious stuff to do with Thanksgiving is there also at stars Christopher walkin
And you'll be walking to the bathroom after you eat that big meal. Yeah, perfect
Chris starts Christopher walking who looks like he hasn't eaten ever
Looks like he's never eaten salad food in his life. Yeah
Q it up now get to your Netflix find the the prophecy we're going for the first one now not any of the sequels the original
Prophecy cue that up as we talk here for the next minute or so and
Then we'll get going
Pat what are you most thankful for this year? Oh, you and this podcast Joe
it gives me a place to go you know otherwise it just be wandering the streets
masturbating into bushes you know life was bleak for me until we got this
podcast gone if there was any for two hours a week I'm off the streets just
if there was was any thread of sincerity in that it would have meant something
did it mean the sarcasm and I'm thankful for you I am thankful that was a hurtful
I am thankful for you. I am this podcast. I am too, but you know, what am I going to do like?
Well, I didn't say do that. You know, I'm thankful for a lot of things to be honest. Yeah
That big dicky urge that big old dawn. Yeah
You know, I got I got good things going. Yeah. Yeah. You're gainfully employed as they say rich others would say
You know, got a beautiful house, beautiful lady, the world's my oyster, and I'll take a
baker's dozen. What? I agree. Look, I'm thankful too, you know, all's going well.
I seem to have had a roof over my head for telling what I consider to be almost
standard jokes for the last 12 years. You and America. Yeah, I mean, we're doing
all right. You know, a lot of people out there who don't have it so lucky. That's
something important to remember. They're yeah. Yeah. And there's other people out
there that look lucky that are unhappy. And those are the unluckiest folks of all.
Right. Right. You know what I mean? Let's start the movie. Now you're hitting way too close to
Proficy you should be paused on the first frame so we can count off together and hit play
one two three play here it comes at all Miramax logo at old Miramax opening
logo I rented this movie as a kid when it first came out yeah based solely on
the scene in the trailer where Christopher walkin goes I kill you I kill you
black woman. I was thinking we'd be
dueling impressions during this, but now I
realize I'm going to win the
impression. We both did very well last
episode doing impressions of Sam
almost at Sam Waters and Sam Rockwell.
No, I do have a Sam Rockwell. Oh, Sam LA, Sam
Elliott. Yeah, that was fun. But we were
doing I you want to hear my Sam Rockwell
Yeah, I've heard it and you've done it on the podcast, but do I have? Yeah, that's not very good
It's all right. This is a by the way I went to film school. They're using an orange filter on this
A light orange filter
Well, it's wrong with that
Nothing Joe. I'm just I'm pretending that I'm telling people something they don't know. Oh, okay
The screen is pure orange. Oh, I forgot Eric Stoltz was in the Stoltz the original Marty McFly
I forgot he was in this! Yeah, I saw this too. My dad rented it probably thinking it was a religious movie and then discovering it was a horror movie.
And as I did with every movie, I saw, when I was a kid, I had to sneak it after he went to bed, which was like 3 a .m.
So I would set my alarm for 3, take a movie downstairs, and watch it with my ear press at the television.
And that's why I watched this, looking for nudity, and I pretty vividly remember they're not being any nudity.
No, but you do have your Virginia Madsen in here and never been attracted to her
I I realize she is an interactive woman, but not my for my money. Nobody nobody hotter. Okay back back in her prime
I mean she's still beautiful woman, but I'm talking if you're talking prime if you're talking prime Virgid's
Adam Goldberg is in this awesome
Is that the guy from saving private Ryan? Yeah, there's a confused. He's in this. Apparently. It's gotta be
He's got really one one trick and he's been playing it for 30 years like Rappaport
Where's he been? I'm always happy to see him Michael Rappapot
He's around he's on the Jim Gaffigan show, which I think is a pretty funny little sitcom a man to plumbers in this
I didn't come here. He go mortish and isn't this he go mortes
Jesus who does he play the devil or does stolt's play the devil?
Well stolt's just had glowing orange eyes, so they were black
They were black eyes, but not from the orange filter, not from being abused like his eyes literally were black
I actually am wondering if after I made that joke this might just be the movie or maybe your TV needs to reset its colors
Because everything looks orange unless that was a choice maybe that'll be coming out on Halloween
No, because the menu screen for the Apple TV looks fine. That's true, Joe. Sorry. I think that we're in some sort of a flashback sequence here
Of course, once again, we've got the subtitles on having filed a fucking lick of it yet. No, and why do we put these subtitles on?
It's good to look down or sometimes you get a funny sub -tot like when somebody
Y 'all's fucking it says fuck with an exclamation point. It's always kind of funny. That's kind of funny
Casey Jones, but I'm glancing down now. I'm seeing sons apostles. I'm seeing worthy priests these words
I wouldn't be able to read this fast if I wasn't doing a podcast. There's too many words
This is the guy that played Casey Jones and TMNT. He was yeah, Casey Jones. He still shows up and things. He's a solid little actor.
Elias Coteis, this is man.
That sounds like a demon's name. Yeah, or the name of an angel Elias Coteis. That's an insane name. What is that? Is that Greek?
What is that Greek? I tell him. It's all Greek to me, Joe. Hey. What does that expression mean?
It's all Greek to me. Yeah. It means like, you know, like it's like you're speaking a language.
I don't understand it. Yeah, I don't know why they picked on the Greeks for that. No, I feel like you could do with any language that you don't speak. It's all Japanese to me. Yeah, it's all Spanish to me. That makes more sense doesn't have the same ring to it. The Greeks probably the most similar to English.
this movie I'm looking up the movie online right now it's gonna only a 43 % on
run tomatoes I think I honestly think standards were a little higher than because
movies that came out were good and no movies that come out now are good so
Vigo Mortensen does play the devil okay Gabriel Stoltz is just a demon well no
Okay, Stoltz is Simon who's clearly an angel because he had black eyes right Adam Goldberg's character is named Jerry
Assuming he's not a supernatural being in this film. Who do you play in this new horror movie about the devil?
Jerry I'm playing Jerry. He's a car salesman with quite an evil streak. Yeah, well, hey, they all have one
All right. You ever tried to buy a used car? Folks, the people are demons as with a
lady friend recently and we drove by, we drove by a meditation center and she said,
have you ever gone to that meditation center? And I said, it's a center that you can go to to get
centered. And she said, I knew you were going to say that. And the disgust dripping off of her
Santa. I knew you were going to say that. I mean, she was just disgusted by the joke. And
you thought, why don't I tell more people the joke? I thought you would like it because it's a dumb
joke. I don't mean that as an insult. I just mean like, I feel like you're kind of joke. No,
it's all right. I thought your joke was gonna be does it look like I've been
to a meditation center? Because you were probably seconds ago screaming in a
car or something. Yeah, she's gonna say as I scream in a car. Yeah. Here's some
other stuff under the director's belt. Kotea says the same haircut as my aunt.
Yeah, that is true. This by the way this movie is almost a complete copy of the
Constantine story. Yeah, from Wow, if you're watching this go ahead pause rewind back. That was the worst actor in film history
They got to just came in why he goes hey, you're not supposed to be out here, and then Koteus holds up a cigarette and he goes
Sorry, no, no badge badge. You go sorry
I didn't I'm terrible perform we can't rewind is the people running the podcast you can't reward
Well, that's something I've learned from working on a TV show as you're like, okay, the character
has one line and they'll go like, uh, miss, where's my salad?
And you're like, well, we don't need to audition people for that part, obviously.
Anyone can do it.
And you get an actor in and they'll be like, miss, like they don't know how to say the words.
It's like they've never been a human being before.
Well, it's there, there are no small parks, just small actors.
That's true.
now Simon now what we have so far here is Elliott Kazan what's this fucking guy's
name? Elliott Kazan directed on the waterfront which is Elias Koteas. Elias is
Schlesinger who is playing the main cop in this right Elias Koteas he was a
pre -ordinary sensation yeah Elliott right before her tragic that he is he was a
priest now he's a cop and this angel played by Eric Stoltz named Simon has come
to them come to him now I get to feeling that Simon is a bad angel yeah and not a
good angel and walking is sort of a bad guy too sort of I mean he plays the angel
Gabriel but if I remember correctly he's sort of like an anti hero in this okay
because the premise is that God started to care more about the humans than the
angel so the angel started to go fuck the humans have you seen the other
prophecies I tried watching two wards okay couldn't get through it walk and
stuck in there though for good three four of them yeah he it really seems like
he'll be in almost any movie and he's such a great actor I think he's just a guy
that works if he likes the idea he'll do it yeah other credits under our
director's belt Gregory Wyde and he wrote back draft. Yeah, he did. He was also the engine
lieutenant in that movie. Okay. Highlander, he wrote. He wrote another movie called Weekend
War. Not tonight. Another movie called Space Rangers. That was a TV series. I'm not aware
of that either, but CBS. All right. Wrote an episode of Tales from the Crypt. I'd love to
hear that. Also created and wrote Rescue 77, which I'm assuming is some sort of
like fire person show, right? I don't know, Joe. I just want you to be here and present
with me. I just like giving the people little facts. Yes, it was a show about firefighters
on the WB. Well, he was a firefighter. How did you know that? Because I did my research prior to
the film. Seconds product to the film. I was in the bathroom. I see a drop in a
douche. More like a trace. Sounded more like an Ocho to me. Now another angel
is just landed who looks evil. Yeah subtitles are saying.
Omnist music continues. Yeah. That's how long the ominous music subtitles have been
up there. Horror movie there's probably going to be ominous music throughout. I
your thoughts on the Stoltz man. I have always enjoyed Stoltz. He reminds me a little
bit of your friend Jim who's coming in today. Yeah they have a similar coin. Jim doesn't
have long flowing red hair nor would he be able to do a fly battle like this. Stoltz
have you seen the footage of Stoltz's marty McFly? Yeah I liked it. Yeah I mean it wasn't
in Michael J, but what is, you know, I wonder if he feels about like that being like, especially
because back in the future, winds up in the news every two weeks because they went to
some date in the movie and it's like, oh no, it's that date that's happened 10 times in
my life.
Right.
They went to a lot of dates, folks.
It's not that exciting.
They're time travelers.
Right.
And it's fake.
It's a fake movie.
Anyway, uh, Stoltz, like anytime it comes up, there'll be news articles, magazine articles,
Every documentary goes into how Stoltz was bad in the role like he probably doesn't like that
Probably hurts his feelings folks. I mean, I'm hard pressed to believe he was bad in the role
He just didn't have the charisma like when I watched it. You're like, no, that wouldn't work
I mean the the guy who's the guy that wrote it with
Bob Gale. Yeah, but like you you shoot this thing you shoot for like three weeks
They fire you and then it goes on to become a three movie international phenomenon. It's got to sting a little bit
Well Bob Gale this last time came out and was like because people were showing you say like well, you should release the Stoltz cut
We don't like to see it. Yeah Bob Gale came out this year and was like I've seen the Stoltz cut
There's a reason it's never been released. It's like jeez you'd have a little
It's so shit
I think he went as far as to say
Had it been released it wouldn't we wouldn't be sitting here talking about the movie today. I mean that seems unnecessarily harsh
Well, I'm saying like this doesn't deserve this. I
Like stolt's
You know pulp fiction singles
He's a good bit part guy and I like him in a pretty underrated in the movie called mr. Jealousy
I've heard good things about mr. Jealousy. I love him in pulp fiction. He could be my favorite character in the entire movie
Yeah, he's just perfect in that drug dealer part.
Yeah.
Who did he, what was the other one you just said?
Oh, singles, he's like the mime.
He has a very small part.
Oh, that's right.
And he's like a real dick.
He's great in that part.
He's funny in that.
He's a great character act.
Where's he bid?
But maybe not a lead.
Maybe not a lead.
You see, he's still see Stoltz.
I think he directs TV now if I'm not mistaken.
I think he did like a bunch of CSI type shows,
but that could be wrong. Not a bad gig. No, that's big money. Not a bad gig. Your
boy Fred Savage went into television directing for a while. He did. It's so
smart. He's like I you actors waste days and days standing around doing
nothing. And he was like hey instead of whining about craft service maybe I'll
learn how to direct. And he's got a second career. Yeah smart. Very smart. That he
shows that beautiful face in the almost called it the Terminator. It's not called the Terminator.
Whatever that lawyer show is, it's very funny. Very funny. The Grindr. Yeah, like the Grindr
quite a bit and I think Fred steals a show and he's a great looking man to this day.
Older than me, looks significantly higher. Love seeing the Mrs. Charlie Day in that move in that show,
too. Mary Elizabeth Ellis. I think we've talked about the Grindr. I think we talked about it so
long ago that you had seen an advance of it on a plane. Yes. And I expressed my, I
almost called love for Mrs. Charlie Day. Yeah. Find her to be just a blast of sunshine.
Okay. Take it easy. All right. It's not love. It's, you know, I don't know where I'm never
married. I'm in this music continuing. Yeah. You jumped off of that quick. Was it that weird? I was
just being funny. It wasn't weird at all. I used to hang out with her. She's great. She's delightful.
They're all good people.
Seems like a girl you could sidle up to in a bar,
just throw them back for a while with.
Probably.
You know, seems like fun.
I don't know now.
People get married and have kids,
and then they don't throw drinks back in bars anymore.
Yeah, I call that turning on the pussy switch.
I think most people turn on that switch,
or else their lives quickly become a shambles.
Not JoJo.
Well, you're not married to kids.
How can you the Virginia Madison first appearance in the film? How can you not find this woman attractive?
What's the matter with you? She certainly is pretty. She's not my type. That's all I can say. Oh
Either is this girl talk about a girl that looks like you could throw them back
Mads Mads looks like you can I mean you don't my dream -drinking
Situation would be Virginia Mads in Michael Mads in I'm right in the middle. Are they bro and sis? Yeah, oh, okay. I did
which actually came out today. The Gilmore Guys podcast and it was a pulp
fiction or a Tarantino themed episode and I dressed up like anyone would do
who has no wardrobe. I dressed up like Michael Madison reservoir. It's just a
black. You have to dress up as a character. It was a live show at UCB and they're
like we're all dressing up as Tarantino characters so my buddy Demi was
Django, everybody was the Asian schoolgirl from Kill Bill.
Why would you not go in the Stolts costume?
I had a black robe that's not gonna work.
Go buy a blue bathrobe.
Three minutes.
And then I thought maybe I'll be Tarantino.
He also had a bathrobe, but it was like a checkerboard robe.
I had looked good.
I had a cup from a fast food place.
I had a knife.
I had a pocket full of ears that I cut out from magazines. It was a cute little costume. All right fair enough
People enjoyed it fair enough and I did my maths and impression which was sounds exactly like Christopher walkin to tie it back to this moon. Go ahead
Are you gonna walk all day little doggie?
Are all you gonna bite? I'm getting douche chills. That's such a bad impression. Are you gonna walk all day little doggie?
Here here's medicine, right?
Are you gonna bite I'll do it. I've never done it before, but I'll do it better ready
You gonna bark all day
Little doggy, so it's it's your voice. There's no difference look at my face though
Were you looking at my face were you giving me that? I mean you were doing a Christopher walk in yeah, pretty much but everyone
here's my favorite impression to do from Resardarx ready yeah he says dad he's
coming down he's fucking pissed Chris Penn I just watched that is so funny in
that moment he's tremendous don't you point that gun at my dad he's tremendous
yeah he's really funny he's tremendous when he's driving the car he's going
Larry he's a wet back he's a waiter he's a friend of mine he's just I mean he's so
fucking funny in that movie that's a that's a it's a kind of a well not even
and suddenly the dialogue in the movie is pretty racist.
But it's, you know, in tune with the characters.
Yeah.
That scene in particular is like five minutes of just
kind of rough racism from those guys
driving around in the car.
Look, that's me, everybody.
That scene is nowhere, in my opinion, near
the level of the scene in the office
when he wrestles Michael Madsen.
Yeah.
Gets into the amount of black seeming
that's been pumped up his ass hole.
Yeah.
That that that that's that gets a little more comfortable for me. It's wild and for it to be your first movie like before like now
I feel like everybody knows Tarantino's a pretty good guy. I guess
People don't know that back then. It's like who wrote this thing. Yeah, but I think that was still a time when like especially in those gangster movies
You could have racist characters and it was like for some reason. Oh, yeah, good fellows. They're all really racist
They're not all racist good fellows only peshy
But, well, I mean, no, Leo to two,
Leo to drops an end bomb, you're right.
I forgot about that.
The heroes of the movie.
But Pesh, he's the one where it makes me
I'm really uncomfortable when he's giving like that,
like speech about, like, you got it.
The lady says that she finds Sammy Davis Jr.
attractive and he's going like, that's what I'm talking about.
You got to watch what you say.
And we'll just might take it the wrong way.
It's very upset.
I don't want to lean over here and find out I'm kissing.
That King Cole.
Yeah.
And then Leo does laughing and he's like no and Pesh, he's like am I right?
And he's like no you're right. You're right. Yeah. No you're right. Like he doesn't really he doesn't tell him like hey, Joe
Well, it seems like Joe. He's not playing it. Kenny Bania. Yeah
Kenny Bania. Yeah, Kenny Bania's in this wow
This is a star -studded affair
It's like what you do one of those previews where it puts everybody's name up and it's like Bania because no one knows his name
I introduced my mom to curb your enthusiasm earlier much earlier this year. She wasn't very familiar with it. She fell in love with it
But I showed her I started out with showing her the Seinfeld reunion episodes. Yeah
In the table read episode it when it cuts to him and he goes it's gold Jerry gold my mom lit up. Yeah, sure that I just thought to myself my god. That's how
Transcendent is that the word?
That's the the reach of Seinfeld. Oh, yeah
I was like my almost 70 year old mother just lit up at the at a character from Seinfeld
that I would consider almost inside baseball. Yeah, it's almost like an all comedy joke.
It is real. You know, and like gallery, yeah, yeah. And then that that show also it works
on its own. It's super funny. If you don't have any interest in the entertainment industry.
But also the whole gist of it is how Banya is a time slot hit because he's going up after
Jerry and he's getting his laughs. Yeah, because he's like I killed and he goes up there and rides the wave
Then he goes he's like a shark who eats laughs and George goes, I don't see how a shark could eat laughs
Jerry's like it's not the point
But anyway
What they're commenting on was that any show that aired after Seinfeld they'd be like check out this new comedy smash
The only reason anyone to watch this garbage shows
I didn't even pick up that that was a commentary
It is and when you go back and rewatch them now, you're like, man, this show really hates the entertainment industry
It's it holds up tremendously. Yeah, I just watched the pony episode or the I had the pony
I mean, it's his tirade at the table is so funny when he's trying to explain
How out of line this woman is. Yeah, and just the line who leaves a country full of ponies to come to a pony list country
It's crazy. Yeah
It's also like almost everything that happens now in certainly alt comedy, but kind of comedy in general
If you really want to point to things almost every TV show every standup everything you're like
That's that's Seinfeld sure you know are like they'll take a nugget from Seinfeld and take it in their own direction
But like the influence goes beyond pretty much anything else
Certainly in my generation like anytime anybody's doing a bid or talking in a voice or what you're like you are doing Seinfeld
I think all of my favorite shows comedy -wise that have existed after Seinfeld are all undoubtedly and probably would be admittedly heavily influenced by Seinfeld, 1000%.
You know, I love it's always sunny, clearly big Seinfeld influence on that.
Yeah, of course, curb, obviously.
You know, I'm trying to think what other shows I really love, even Peep Show, which I'm a really...
I just got I started getting into peep show hardcore. I can't stop. They're really funny. They're great. They're influenced by Seinfeld for sure. A rest of development.
Pretty much everything. Yeah. How great is peep show, man. Peep show is really really funny. Those guys are
Really good. Yeah, I watched it obsessively. Yeah, and then I was like, what else to these guys done?
It's like a couple comedy specials and that's about it. No, they had a very popular sketch show called the Mitchell and Webb look
Okay, I thought that was like one -off. No, they had a they had a they had a
Radio thing called the Mitchell and Webb sound
Uh -huh. That was a comedy radio thing and then it became the Mitchell and Webb look
Because they turned it into a TV show and then there was also another thing. They've done a couple movies together
They're they've done a lot together. They've really gotten the that's walking by the way. It looks like a young, but a young old Pacino. Yeah, it looks kind of like a beautiful woman when he came in the door here. He does look good. This is, this is walk in sexy age.
this is like a beautiful gaysha how much coke do you think this guy has done over the years
walking I mean he could also be a guy who's never done coke he does have that thing you never
know with these people he's either never done it or done it a billion times how much do you think
Pachino's done over the years. There's no way Pachino hasn't she knows doing coke now
The day and his wife's like, oh, we gotta put the turkey in the oven
And he's like, no, I'll be right out, baby. I'll be right out. I just got to finish washing my hands
Every fucking year, I got to put this turkey in an oven
Can I just have a good fucking time? You know, you're supposed to cook
You're the woman
I don't know why you have to paint him as a sexist.
He's a sexist, let's be honest.
How was he a sexist?
I assume with these people.
We're just assumed Christopher Walkins of Coke at it.
Now we give him the benefit of the doubt.
I'll put my money on Pichito.
But you know, Danny Collins carries,
I told you this last week, I'm gonna watch it this week.
I believe that in real life he carries
a cross filled with cocaine around his neck.
I saw him once in New York, I almost walked into him
because I came around a corner as he was coming down the other side.
I literally almost walked into him for two reasons.
We were just in our each other's paths.
But he also was so focused on the ground, right?
Like he was walking and talking and he just wasn't looking forward.
He was looking down as he was talking.
Yeah.
Anyway.
Well, Pacino in New York, he's probably getting stopped 800 times a block.
But here's the thing, I bet you never get stopped in New York.
New York's got a big stop people talent.
But here's the thing, I remember this, the cab went the wrong direction that I was in,
and this wrong turn that he made cost me like, it just fucked the whole trip. It was like
this deadlock traffic to the point where I had to get out and walk because it would be
literally three times faster, and I was so mad because it was like a hundred degrees in New York.
It was so hot out and I was so pissed that this guy made the wrong turn and now I had to walk
ten blocks in this heat and arrived to your thing's sweaty. I walk around the corner, almost
run directly into Pacino, who's wearing not just long pants and a, like, dress shirt,
but down dress shirt. A wool sport coat. Yeah, that sounds right. And a bandana tied around his head.
That's not even more right. And I was just like, does this guy even look at what the fuck, like it was
crazy to yeah I think I mean well obviously he's a little nutty it's disgusting yeah whatever
scene we're in now there's food all over the floor by the way every oh we're we're in Jerry's
house Goldberg can do better man here comes Jerry I got a little walking story I used to work at
Conan O 'Brien in New York when he was on at 12 30 on NBC and I was the desk page so I would have
have to kind of bring up the guests from the street,
make sure they were comfortable,
get them what they needed.
So walkin' comes up and the musical guest was Wilco.
And Wilco was like, hey, man, is there any chance
we can say, hey, Christopher Walkin'?
Sometimes like even the actors would be,
you know, like I wanna meet so and so.
Right.
I was like, yeah, I said, I think real quick
and I'm like, but we gotta do in these situations
to just gauge really quick if he's into it or not
Because you know, I can't be responsible if and they're like, yeah, no, we got it
We got right so it's walking in his wife and he comes out of his dressing room in a complete tuxedo
Right in his wife Georgian walking is a huge casting director cast sopranos and all kinds of shit
She's trying to tie his bow tie in the hallway and the wilko guys come up and he goes, hey, yeah, excuse my impression
You guys the band right and they go, yeah, he goes I didn't get a chance to hear you are you a good band?
You know, yeah, we like to think we're pretty good. He goes, that's important. Confidence is very important.
And like it was a dream for everyone involved.
So then she was like, Chris, we got to go and he's like, where are we going again? He's in a tuxedo.
She goes, Chris, I told you, we're going to this whatever charity thing. And he goes, see fellas, when you get married, you got to do what your wife tells you to do. You don't get a say.
You don't get a say she she puts a bow tie on me now. I got to go to win event. I got no say
And they're like yeah, we know we're married or whatever and then he goes
Let me ask you one question before I head out fellas
Which one of you here is the drummer
The drummer raises hand and he goes now. I have often heard it said
That the drummer in a band gets the girls
And they just stare at him and he goes, I'm asking you, is this true?
They go, uh, the drummer laughs and he's like, that's not really been my experience, Christopher
and they all kind of laugh and he keeps, doesn't smile, the band is laughing and he stares
at the drummer with his hand out pointing at him and he goes, no, it is true.
I've always heard that the drummer gets the girls and he goes, that's probably true of a
a lot of bands he's like maybe Ringo got a lot of girls but you know it hasn't been my case
and he goes no it is I've always heard people say in bands I got I got friends in bands
that the drummer's the one who gets the girls and he finally the drummer was like yeah you
know I guess it's true I the drummers do get the girls and he goes see that's what I'm saying
and then he's like it's nice meeting you fellas shakes their hands gets in an elevator with his wife
I was like that was the greatest thing I've ever seen and all that scene was missing was Kevin Spacey going and just like that
It was gone. Yeah, yeah for it like the end of usual suspect, right and that's a perfect story
He was so weird, but like very delightful. He could kind of hang in conversation
They tell you when I was on Carson daily and Jeff Goldblum was the guest no, and I wanted to meet Jeff Goldblum so bad because the fly is one of my favorite horror movies ever and
and I just love Jeff Goldblum, but it was my first TV spot I ever did and I had
nowhere near the galt to ask if I could meet this guy. Right. And I was standing
in the hallway plus I mean you're already flustered because you're getting to
meet Carson Daling. Yeah. Yeah. I was all wound up about that. And I was very
scared. First TV. I was beyond nervous. Right. Anyway, I'm in the hallway pacing
and my manager goes, don't look now, here comes your hero.
I look up.
Goldbloom is walking toward me with his entourage.
Yeah, he passes me.
I don't meet him.
This is all I hear as he passes me.
Ah, ah, it's a, it's a Western, but it's, it's a tolerable Western.
That's all I heard.
And I was like, that was better than meeting Jeff Goldbloom.
What's he talking about?
I guess he was in, he was in Silverado.
I guess he could have been talking about movie. He wasn't in I think he was just talking he was obviously talking about a movie of some
Yeah, it was the end of the world
Yeah, do you see him on Conan when he like oh sure and letterman will bring his wife out
He'll be like my my beautiful wife. Yeah, she can do a handstand. Yeah, honey honey
Come out here until they're like do like a handstand. Yeah
Yeah.
That's great.
It's really weird.
I've seen him many times at like any time I've gone to a health food store like four times
in my life.
He's been in there with a new like very hot 21 year old yoga girl.
So I guess he's single now, but no, he's married now.
Oh, he just had a kid.
Well, I hope I didn't blow something up there for him.
No, this was in the past.
This was music.
Uh, I did hear that years ago before he settled down, he was quite, uh, oh, sure.
Quite the man about town. God bless him. Did he hook up with like Nicole Richie?
I think so. I think the tabloids. He's like, you know, at least 55, I think still looks great. He plays jazz up at that rock well up on Vermont, which I know I want to go, but I just want to go to meet Jeff
Goldblum. And I know he probably doesn't appreciate that like he, you know, he probably just want to go play music. He's an amazing piano player. I assume he's got great banter.
I mean I never need to go see anyone play jazz as long as I live
Must have been miles Davis sitting the face of an entire genre of beautiful American music. I mean look
I respect that it's the notes that you don't play that are important. Oh, God
Here we go. Here we go
We go speaking of Carson daily when my parents came to New York
And my sister I got them all tickets to Conan in like front row. I was working there
was very easy. I was like, can you get in the front row? So they're going in and they're like,
who are the guests going to be? And I was like, I don't know. And the night before the guests
had been, I think it was Bruce Willis and the band was you two or something like that. It was like
a huge night of Conan's life. Actually, I think it was Springsteen looking back. So my parents are like,
who are the guests going to be? This is so exciting. We're going to be so close. Here were the guests,
Carson Daly who came down one flight of stairs to be a guest on the show. He's a great guy. He's a very nice guy. He's a great guy.
Carson Daly, a professional surfer was the second guest and the third the band was D12.
Well, that's cool.
M &M not for your parents.
Was M &M there?
No, M &M was not there.
D12 parentheses not featuring M &M.
It was sans M &M.
Yeah, oh boy. Wow, all right. Not that my parents would have been like, ooh, M &M.
I'm actually jealous that your parents got to see proof before he died. And I never got to see proof.
I'm a big D12 fan. I'm not, and I know I love rap, but I don't know anything about proof to be honest with you.
He's the guy that got killed that was in D12. He was like M &M. Oh, right, right, right, right, okay.
But I would have very much liked to have seen him before he passed. Yeah, absolutely R .P. He was a great rapper.
I just realized in this moment, as usual, the half -fast fashion in which we're watching this movie, Eric Stoltz is a good guy.
I think he's a good demon, let's say. He's an angel. No, he's an angel. They're all angels. There's no demons in this except the devil. Yeah.
Yeah, but I just realized she's a good guy and I think he teams up with Virginia Madsen.
Okay.
Because she's the skeptic at first when she meets him.
Why did that?
How did this girl get this role?
What is going on with the pants?
It's a child in 1990.
And she's got like, I've never seen a child in like full mom jeans, like belted under the
where the tits would be.
Okay. He's gotta put like, he puts like his soul in her or something.
Okay. Does she start talking like him?
Uh, I'll just, I don't, I don't remember.
No, I just forget he's gotta, or he takes her soul.
Uh -oh.
Is he gonna kiss this girl?
Well, that's weird.
He's not kissing her.
He's just like sucking her soul out.
But wouldn't that be a weird scene to shoot?
Yeah, it would be weird.
I would say gang.
How about you we we baby shoot this as a reverse any other way than me passionately kissing a young girl. Yeah
That was weird
Set now now she's puking like it feels a little molestie
Speaking of molestie as we always have to do in these upsets
I just saw spotlight the new film with Michael Keaton and Mark Ruffalo about the investigation into the Boston Catholic Church sex scandal
How's my boy Keaton in it Keaton has never been anything but amazing how's my boy Roof Roof was great and everybody's raving about him
But he he was better in Foxcatcher, and I don't know why people kind of slept on that performance
He's tremendous amazing when I wasn't a huge fan of that film
But I thought all three of them did a really nice job in that movie. I agree, and I was a fan. I like creepy shit like that
like creepy human fox catcher was another black mass for me it was tremendous
performances it was well done but I just kind of found it a little a little
uneventful or something I completely get what you're saying and I they do have
a similar tone they both have that icy blue like filter over them the whole time
exactly that just makes you feel fucking hopeless yeah exactly
um so all right I gotta go see that I was excited to see there was a new
Keaton movie out. They're going to send spotlight as a screener. It'll probably be up for best picture. It's a great great movie. Now who plays do any do any people that we know play priests or they don't it's not like that really. There's a couple. There's a side priest here and there that they talk to but it's really mostly about the journalism aspect. I love the one with. I love the one with. What's it called? What was that one. It was called like
our fathers or something, but it was, it was the made for HBO one about that scandal.
But you had, you had Brian Denny. He is a priest. Yeah. That was a good flick. Yeah.
Christopher Plummer as the, the bishop that always created me moved, all everything around
and hit everything. Yes. You had, uh, uh, uh, uh, what's the lady from the exorcist, uh,
Allen Burston, as the mom whose kids went through it. I think Ted Danson's in it.
Dancing is in it. Yeah, that's a great movie fucking great flick man. Yeah, it's I mean really if you're gonna tackle that subject the movie better be pretty good
Otherwise, it's gonna feel pretty exploitative and gross. Yeah
It was really good and then I also saw Brooklyn which I think will be another awards contender and that is my favorite movie currently of the year which Brooklyn
Brooklyn is a very simple movie Nick Hornby wrote the script guy wrote high fidelity. It's
50s Irish Catholic girl moves to New York from Ireland falls in love with this
Italian dude and then she's got to go back to Ireland and she's kind of
trapped between the two places I know that I'm not selling this well but it's
so far it sounds like the most boring movie I've ever heard and maybe you
wouldn't be into it I don't know I really fucking loved it I think the star is
Sure see Ronin the girl who played Hannah. Okay, which is an awesome action movie. Yeah, I like that girl
And she's great. There's nobody else really in it. I'm not selling it well
There's a comedy as I started to tell you the plot. I was like I'm spoiling something
So I'm not gonna say this is a comedy or drama
It's a drama a couple funny moments. It's like a romance to be honest
Which is not not generally my bag, but it's really good
But you left out a big plot point like she's actually a cat demon or something like that
She you know, she's a cat demon from the first thing, but there's more to it than that, okay
Very good and I thought the the tagline should have said a young
Irish immigrant cat demon, but they left it out. I guess they didn't want to right or at least because you know
Or does it do wealthy Oscars at least young Irish in immigrant parentheses cat demon and
And parentheses do it like that. You don't see enough parentheses in tag lines. No, you don't get out. No, you don't. I think our podcast description has a parentheses or two.
There's one you and I kind of wrote the podcast description in a rush and we wrote it together. There's one wording in it that I hate and I want to change it if we can but I think it's too late. What is it?
I don't know I'd have to look at him.
I get really weird about you know what the tagline
where the shit know the tagline for that green inferno
oh Eli Roth movie should have been now tell me welcome
to the pain forest that's what it should have been yeah that would
not have it would have been even less of a hit with the tagline
welcome to the pain either that or nobody saving you in this
rain forest. Uh -huh. How about this? Some rain forest shouldn't be saved. There you go. That's
what I was trying to do. Okay. That's much better. That's much better. What tag would you give
black mass? Black what tagline? Yeah. Yeah. I don't have something off. And I was fascinated by what
walking was doing. Yeah, walking right now is in a grave and he's growling and saying
he loves this corpse he's standing. He said he's a beautiful, mysterious monkey and now he's
sniffing the corpse. Yeah, that was probably an improv line if I had to guess. Hey, yeah, I want
to do something here about a monkey if I could. Oh, this is the guy, they're in the grave of the guy,
I, uh, Stoltz already took this guy's soul, okay.
You can take a soul, I guess.
Well, by the way, I love that the angels are sent down dressed as reservoir
dogs. Well, that's because this came out like right around that time.
You know, that's why plumbers and that's why Stoltz is in it.
Miramax is like, let's get anything to do with Pulp Fix.
He looks exactly like Tervolta and Pulp Fix from the back.
He's got the same hair.
This was a good time for these for these art house licks man. They're a lot of really cool these came out at this time my favorite
That I so infrequently hear anybody talk about was things to do in Denver when you're dead
Which I was liked it. I really like that movie. It's a good. It was clearly an attempt at making a
Tarantino -esque thing, but I love Andy Garcia. Yeah, he never disappoints me. I
Love treat Williams. I love that he plays a guy that each shit in the movie
literally yeah and walking is in that movie yes he is walking is also in
Pulp Fiction which people walking is in that movie and he he accuses he
accuses Andy Garcia's character of being gay because he does like like charity
stuff and Andy Garcia says I'm sorry how does that make me homosexual and he and
Christopher Watkins line is it's always what happens one day you save in the
rain for us next day, you chuck and cock. He's Irish in it. No, it's just my
shitty walkin' impression. Oh my God, that was just a straight -up walkin'. I
wasn't trying that hard. I just remember he says chuck and cock. I had an accent
or something. That was crazy, John. Sorry. Maybe he was chuckin' cock.
He's obsessed with monkeys. Well, he calls humans talking monkeys. Oh, okay. That's
problem is like he's trying to kill off the human race because he's like there he's he's saying
he only talks about monkeys when I'm looking at these lines of dialogue yeah walking with saying
the angels were second to God right and they did all God's work and everything and then the humans
took took took a God's place okay you know yeah and walking is like fuck this I was the main angel I was
Gabriel I impregnated Mary for Christ six, you know, but I guess it doesn't mean he boned Mary. No, it's it was a macular conception, but
Yeah, well, I'm sorry. He didn't impregnate me. He was the angel that came to Mary and said you're you're with child. Okay. He gave her the bad news. Okay.
You're prego and you're out of wedlock. Yeah. Good luck not getting stoned in this town.
You do the the Hunger Games shit. You fuck with that. No. I have now seen three. The fourth one just came out and I'm like I was so bored.
So amazingly bored by the other three. And now I'm going to go see the fourth because I have to finish this.
Well, apparently I couldn't care less how it ends. I don't remember the other ones. The ending you won't believe your eyes or so. It's one of those things.
my eyes. The only reason I liked the last one is because it seemed more
Hoffman's last time. How was how was he in it? He's great. And Julian Moore is
solid in it. But it's just like, man, it's boring. All that young adult shit is so
boring to me. Except Harry Potter. Oh, wait, I know what just happened. Sorry, I just
realized something happening in the movie. Stoltz wasn't taking that girl's
soul. He was hiding the soul of that general in her. Gotcha. So so so Gabriel can't find it. So that's a very important soul for some reason.
And look at this Goldberg plays his right hand man. He also was doing a walk in impression with walking, which is balls.
I don't say this with any disrespect. I'm a tremendous fan of the actor, but I saw
Pacino and Bobby Kenna Valley in Glingreg, Leross in New York. And Bobby Kenna Valley
was playing Roma, and he was almost doing a Pacino as Roma impression to Pacino. Sure
it was. It was very strange. What was this? Because I saw it with Alan Alder. I was the
Second it was the revival after that revival. Oh, okay. I saw twice. I saw it once with Pete Holmes
Yeah, and then I saw and then my friend bought me tickets for Christmas and I was like I already saw this
But I'll gladly see it again was Pacino playing Shelley the machine. Let me yeah, yeah, everybody was great and he was great
He was fucking great John. John see McGinley played
I don't think I'd want to see anyone other than lemon play that part even more than Pacino is Roma
Lemon to me is as good as you're going to get and all of it in okay job
But you're not touching what lemon did it was hard for me to see anybody in any of the other roles outside of that movie
Because I was introduced to it but through from the movie and then that movie to me is the most perfect cast
It's a hundred percent flawless casting to me. Yeah
Which is hard to say about movies so
You know, it's hard for me to see anybody in any role, but like it was good because it was it was a very different approach
They really played up the comedy in it, right?
Which was interesting like the McGinley scene with where it's boss and yeah
Air now, yes, that scene is was like hysterically funny, right and they're rendition of the play
Yeah, whereas in the movie, you're just like you just feel so fucking bad for Alan all day
You're like this guy's gone out hustle. Oh Alan Arkham. Excuse me
Can you do an Alan Arkham impression? I've never tried it, but I will
what are you talking about wait it's not what I told you to do I'll read the
next line is Alan all the I guess I could have done what I can do it right now
it just says chanting in parentheses I like how anytime a thing in a different
language happens they just write chanting yeah put the fucking words up I just
realized my Alan Arkin is the same as my Christopher Lloyd so it's probably not a
get impressed.
Marty!
Great Scott!
Yeah.
Did you see when they appeared on Kimmel?
No.
Oh, it was so great, man.
Yeah.
We'll find it online over time.
It is online.
But they did a thing on Kimmel where it was the day from back to the future, too.
I remember.
And the time machine comes into the studio during the monologue.
And Marty and fucking dock it out.
Yeah, that's cool.
It was great.
It lit me up.
I've never seen and I have a couple friends who have written or are writing for Kimmel
I've never seen Jimmy Kimmel. It's pretty good. I don't watch late now like I used to when Conan went off
I was like I can't do it anymore. I don't really like watching any late night
But I mean, I think Kimmel does a nice job. Yeah
He did it. He did it a hundred percent Star Wars episode the other night. Okay, and he had Carrie fish
Sure, he had Harry Ford
Do you already have your Star Wars tickets?
Of course I do, seeing it first screening on the East Coast opening night.
I'm really hoping, and it is a strong possibility that there's going to be advanced Oscar screenings
and we might get in a little earlier.
I don't think there is, because I just read a thing about the premiere, and they said people
are having trouble getting into the premiere, right, like it's like so closed off to just
people that were like involved with the movie, like nobody can bring family. There's people
like, you know, Andy Dick is like, uh, I'm Andy Dick, like at the gate. Yeah. That
might work sometimes, Andy, but it, uh, it, uh, it, uh, what's it called? Um, it, it broke
the, uh, shattered the presale box office record. It's made $50 million in presales already.
sure it was. I can't wait. I bet my friend Keith Robinson $500. It would outgrose the Avengers
too. It will. It absolutely will. And he swore to me there was no way in hell it was going to happen.
There's actually a 100 % chance of life. Yes, the easiest 500. I bet him too. He's regretting it now.
He's been calling me and being like, God damn it. I mean, I was, I'm a fucking idiot.
The other night I went and saw Uncabaret, which is like a storytelling show.
my boss did it and Eddie Pepitone who makes me like screen laugh. I think it's like one of the
funniest people in life. He did our show the other night and he told a joke that's so funny. I
keep saying it out loud to myself. What was it? Maybe I heard it. He goes, my grandmother,
sadly just died. She was murdered by two men I owed money to. They needed a name.
he didn't do that like he is the funniest man alive to me I mean you know he's up there
I just I'm like helpless laughing when he does his shit when he's screaming about anything
but he had he did this bit I'll come back around because Andy Dick did the show too which
is my point but uh Pepitone did this thing where it's a little one be funny people in Los
Angeles but he was talking about how he uses ways here maybe like this app I fire up ways
the other day, I'm stuck on the 405, I've been sitting there for three hours in traffic,
not moving. I get on ways, help me out ways, I say. And ways says buy a gun and shoot your way
up to the getting museum. Like the audience was like breaking glasses. They were laughing. And then
time and did a beautiful song with no jokes about his sister being a multiple skits
of front.
Right.
And because some of the show is serious and it was like people in the audience were like
kind of crying.
Sure.
I was not.
But whatever.
So Peppa Tongue gets up and he goes, I didn't know was this kind of that elegant night because
I guess I could make up a song about my brother.
Here we go.
A one and a two.
He goes he's addicted to porn
He eats terrible foods and weighs
400 pounds
Heavy foods and jacking off is all he does
He's 56 years old. I was like
Like tears were splashing out of my eyes. I was laughing so hard
So funny just a funny looking dude
Oh my god. I love it. I hope you hear this, Eddie Peppetown. Why don't I ever tell them?
Why don't I walk up and say you were hilarious? Oh, I should have one of the greatest. I swear I'm not saying this to compliment myself in any way
But we're talking about Eddie Peppetown, and it was literally one of the greatest moments of her had his comedian. I finally met him in person
Last year at the Montreal comedy festival. I never met him and I saw him in the lobby at this party
and I walked up to him. I was like, Eddie, I just want to say hi, we've never actually met and I go, I'm Joe DeRosa and he goes,
oh, hey man, yeah, I dig you, dude, I dig you stuff.
And I was like, thank you, man, that's a huge fucking compliment.
I was very nice.
I was like, I think you're just the fucking greatest. You're so funny, man.
Yeah. And then he did our show and we had a great time.
He's done the show I write for twice in two different roles because he's just like,
He I don't know why he does get more like little supporting parts as like scuzzballs because he kills it
He played a underground subway suit salesman in an episode that I wrote where he was like selling suits on the ground
He was like he had this bill where he talked about the different colors of the suits and he was like this one's a must -eed
It's a beautiful must -eed. It's really really funny. I think the whole scene was cut
Andy Dick gets up. Oh, yeah. He's like, I only got a couple minutes to talk. Oh, gross.
These are peeled off faces on the guy that played Casey Jones. What's his name? Ezra Miller
better than Ezra Miller. Okay. He opened a box full of faces. Yeah. And seems oddly unfazed
by it. Yeah. So Andy Dick gets up and he's sober. But he's like, I said, he lived in a
facility and it was kind of sad and he seemed a little shaky. He's living in a facility.
What he said. Like, what kind? Like a rehab. I don't know. I didn't ask him because he was giving
a performance. But then he said he was talking how he dated a girl for a year and he kept reaching
between her legs to jack her dick off and then realizing she didn't have a dick because he was trying
to go straight for a year. And we were like, okay, boy. Then he goes, I went, I just
got back from Ben Stiller's 50th birthday party. He's like, I, you know, I turned down
the Will Ferrell role in Zoolander. We were all like, okay. So then the host goes, why
did you turn that down? He goes, because I thought I didn't want to live in Ben's shadow
anymore. He's like, now I would literally eat shit out of Ben Stiller's asshole to get
one line in a movie. If this, we're all like, this is getting a little dark. And he
goes, I also turned down, ah, fuck, it was some huge role in a movie that he probably wouldn't
have been as good in, but, you know, he's just talking about all these big roles he turned
out because he thought he was too good for them. And now he can't get any roles. And then
he said he got blacklisted by Howard Stern and somebody was like why did you get blacklisted by Stern?
He goes ah
I called him on the air. I called him a hook -nosed money -grubbing Jew.
The audience was silent. There was like a couple audible gas. And he goes, I know
you don't call people hook -nosed money -grubbing Jews. Isn't he Jewish though? I think.
I also find it hard to believe that Stern would ban him for that. I feel like Stern is like a well the Andy dick is clear
The type of person who thinks everyone hates them. You could tell even from five minutes. He's like he hates me. He won't talk to me
My friend was telling me he did it did the show a few weeks back with Andy dick and he goes it was Rosanne was on the bill as well
I'm on the show and Andy that's great. I wish you didn't I missed that she doesn't talk like that anymore
I wish he still talk like that. I love Rosanne. I love her good
No, he antidicks like boy. This is a big 90s like for people in the 90s
Like remember the 90s Rosanne when you and me were on top and Rosanne was like we
At the crowd laugh for like 25 minutes. He's we Andy
I do love antidick on news radio. I love him and everything I've ever seen and his get show was hilarious on him
I'm upset that he's that he's falling on such hard times. I know he seemed okay. He's just self -destructive guy
But for sure, you know, but he also did the show I work for and he was sober, but he was like three hours late
And we're like come on man. Yeah, we had Lindsay Lohan on the show same deal
It's like you can't just show up three four hours late this like and then act like you're a victim patty
What do you audition the dirt over here? I mean you're like Perez Hilton right now. Yeah, this is like you're us weekly
rant last week about Matt Damon's divorce rumors swirling. Good lord feeding a kid
of mint now. There's a lot of action with children's models in this film. I'm not loving.
Also on the bill, Julius Sweeney played its pat, the character that ruined my childhood.
Why? My name is Pat. So I was like, that things are going okay for me in school. I've also
had a hard time despite the beer tip telling if you're a man or a woman. Well it's why I grew the
beard. It doesn't help. Yeah but they all stop calling me at Brenda Walsh which they were calling
me at this time and then switched to call me. It's Pat is he a bluer? Is Brenda Walsh from 90210? Yeah and
I would be like I've never seen it so I don't know what you're making fun of it like because it's a
girl's name. That is rough stuff. Brenda Walsh that's a tough one. And it's not just that they're
calling you Brenda Walsh because it's a girl. It's almost like they were calling you
like a saucy bitch. Yeah, exactly. Which that that hurts. Well, I'm sure a comedian
Brendan Walsh had to deal with that in school as well. I haven't talked to him about it.
That's a great point. I never asked Brendan that. I like Brendan. He's a good guy. I love
Brendan. One of the funniest guys I know. Yeah. Can't tell if when he's speaking to me
if it's real or serious ever. Please more pranks than I've ever met. Yeah. I'm not a real
prank guy. I'm also sarcastic all the time, but whenever anyone talks to me with sarcasm,
I just believe it. Just in a knowing quality of mine. He started tweeting me one day with
a profile he made for a guy we both know who wasn't on Twitter. And he made a profile of
this guy and tweets people as this guy. And he's a comedian or he's just a friend of yours.
He's a comedian that I know him through comedy. Okay, we're friendly. I don't know him very well, but
So but but I'm in I'm playing the city where this guy lives Brendan starts tweeting at me
Meet me at the mall
Okay, meet me at the mall I go to the fucking mall
I'm texting the guy like where the hell are you? I'm here
He's like no, no, no that I didn't tweet you. That was Brendan was tweeting you
pretending to be me. Now you're up at the mall. I mean I didn't care. I was
going to go to the mall either way. Buy a pair of slacks and you go home. But he
would also send messages as this guy to people on Twitter and he'd be like, Hey
man, I had a really weird dream about you last night still shaking up. Please call me
as soon as she can. Just odd messages. This is going to have black eyes when her head
raises. There's no way there's no way she's not going to have black eyes when she
looks up. She's looking at the ground. He was going to punch her in the fence.
No, that's I already made that joke earlier. But if you want to steal my stuff, I didn't
hear you.
Come on. Why do you have her looked out of the ground?
They're blackish. No, but she was speaking so creepily while staring at the ground for
three minutes. Then she looks up in her eyes, aren't black? I think they're blackish.
Their ABCs break out, hit families that come blackish. She should have looked up with black
guys and went like that. All right. So she's got this soul in her. I guess the soul that
stolt's put in her is him is is obstructing them now how to defeat this threat of angels.
It's a weird plot, man. Terry. It's a little hairy, but that madson. Good Lord. They this independent
And then at movie boom and the 90s, like there were as many independent movies, all of them good, pretty much all of them good as there were blockbusters because of like kind of because of Tarantino.
Yeah, it's a shame because all the all the indie companies now got bought up by the majors and they still they'll do like their signature films with those smaller companies, but it's still a major.
I saw a talk after spotlight a
Movie and the cast is Michael Keaton Mark Ruffalo Rachel McCatams, Lee F. Schreiber
John Slattery it goes on and on and on and they said three different times the funding completely fell apart
with that cast in place
And they couldn't get the movie made whose dick do you got to suck these days ridiculous Michael Keaton coming off a best actor win
Can't get the movie met
He didn't win best actor for Birdman. No, he didn't win the Oscar. Yeah, he didn't win. I'm almost
positive. He didn't. He absolutely didn't because there was that clip of him putting his speech back in his
pocket that was going around the Internet. So who won? I used to know that I used to know every Oscar winner
from 1929 to whenever I was like 16 and then my memory started going. It's nothing to brag about. No, I
honestly I'm ashamed saying it. I'm glad I don't remember winners. He won the
Golden Globe or something. He won something. I saw him give a speech. Well he might
have yeah sure he might have won the Matthew McConaughey for fucking Dallas
Buyers Club. Yeah I have a tremendous performance man. All right. Lito that won
best supporting actor. That was just last year Dallas virus club? No. Well, I
googled Oscar winner 2014, the picture of Ellen, he won in 2015. I think we
didn't have the 2015 yet. Did we? Oh wait, yeah, you're right. I guess I feel
like I watched Dallas virus club a long time ago. You're right. I'm thinking the
2015s are taking place sometime before Christmas. It is confusing. They're doing
the year after. Neil Patrick Harris hosted last year. That was the worst that's ever been.
Uh, best picture of Birdman. Uh, you sub me, you sub Birdman, right? Yeah, together. Um, hold on.
I'm trying to find it. There we go. Winners and nominees.
I also really think I'm right here. This is exciting.
You're 100 % wrong. I mean, I bet you money on it.
Eddie Redmayne for oh shit yeah I lost my pool because of Eddie Redmayne undeserved
Redmayne no that kid I mean he came in swinging movie was born well everyone's
fucking everybody in them I go to see a Stephen Hawking movie and like it's all
about infidelity it's very weird oh they did get into that stuff I never saw the movie
the whole movie is about everyone cheating on everybody including Hawking oh yeah so
So he cheated before he was like in the wheelchair and everything?
I think both.
No, he cheated when he was completely incapacitated.
Yeah, like a few years ago.
Red means following up with that movie where he plays the first transgender man.
I mean, he's the Danish girl.
Yeah, that kid's not fucking around, man.
He's going after the Oscars.
He gave one of the most ludicrous performances I've ever seen in the movie Jupiter ascending.
What did he play?
where Channing Tatum plays a half dog, half astronaut.
I mean, I don't know why you saw the fucking movie.
Because I still go, well, the Matrix was good.
But then speed racer and everything else comes out.
I mean, they've never matched it.
Never even come within the ballpark.
Jupiter sending is a real, it's a new low.
It's worse than like Cloud Atlas or any of that stuff.
So who was, who was Eddie in the movie?
He was the villain.
It was me lacunis enchanting Tatum also. They're fucking and you're like well, he's a dog though
So you are fucking a dog just so you know
I'm gonna just say this I don't say it to be mean
It probably is mean I don't ever need to see me lacunis in anything ever again. I
Could I have no opinion either way I can give her take she can't change her voice. Yeah, and she will always sound like
a girl that smokes pot from the 70s. Yeah, like she, it's like it's it's it's
distracting to me. The only time I ever thought she was pretty good was in black
swan but anybody could have played that part for sure. I loved her in a I loved
her in say saving Sarah Fisher for getting Sarah Marshall. Oh yeah forget it
sure she was she was she's romantic comedy. Yeah she was great in that sure but you
know I don't want to see her in Jupiter ascending. No I when they cast
is the witch in fucking the odds. I was like, Jesus Christ. What is happening here? That movie made my dick very song.
They had her as the main witch and they had fucking Rachel Wease as like the secondary witch. Yeah.
The fuck is going on here?
I kept saying, hey, which witch is which? You know?
yeah I said uh oh wait here's which here's wait this is the walking line which is which
well this is the scene where walking says the thing this is this is where he says I think it's
hold on I think this is uh maybe it's not I kill first born babies there he is here it comes
the audience isn't hearing you right now because they're still laughing at which which is which
This is the these moments of the problem on the podcast if you're not watching the movie because you're just all they're hearing is me just going wait a second here right we're almost there we're almost there.
Jerry just got shot walking as lipstick on now he does have lipstick on doesn't he yeah just in that shot he does why oh here it is here it is.
There you go. What a great line. Yeah, I'm about. I kill firstborns. What a mom is watch. I turn cities into salt.
That's very great. That's a great line.
And the only thing you can count on for all existence is never understanding why.
Great dialogue. Yeah. Would you say it sings?
I would. Somebody, Joe was telling me earlier that somebody once told him the dialogue in a certain movie sings.
I'm asking you, this is the question of the week listeners. Could you remain friends with the person who saw a movie and you said, how was it?
I tell you man, the dialogue sings. I would end the friendship. It made me want to see the movie. It's a fantastic move.
I bought it on blank face still have it watched it's called sweet smell success. Yeah, one of these days
1955 -ish, which is uncle
Five -ish Finkels in it. No, I said 1955 -ish. Oh, I've never seen five -ish Finkel before the age of seventy six. No, I don't think his mother had
Sweet smell success is like a very very very dark movie about like a gossip columnist and
Uh, and his like protégé and he kind of destroys him essentially, it's just it's about losing your morals losing your soul, et cetera.
Did you ever see a face in the crowd?
Love it.
I think that's directed by Eliay Kazam.
It is.
That is a rough one, man.
Yeah.
That is a rough one.
Make sure you realize that uh, Andy Griffith is a fucking tremendous actor.
Yeah.
Yeah, no idea. I thought he was like good, you know, I was like, hey, he's a good actor. Yeah, I only ever saw him in Matlock and the sitcom
You watch him in that movie. You're like Jesus Christ. Yeah, he's a fucking tour de force
Yeah, he was great. He never really got a lot of roles either
Can a guy be a tour de force or can you just have a tour de force?
A performance can be a tour de force. I don't think a man can be I'm gonna say this guy's a powerhouse
That's right. I knew it. Sorry. I'm dumb like that
I'm a little dumb. How much longer is this movie at, by the way?
That ominous music is continuing. It's just keep saying it.
We're here with a little Apple TV remote.
You're going to wind up turning this off. Hardest to find remote in all time.
No, because I'll just hit the center button.
And it paused. And it paused and paused real quick.
We got, with that 109, this is 130 set of half an hour.
Not there half an hour.
Well, there's credits.
Folks, I hope you're listening at home, and I'll find this to be like an endurance test as Joe clearly does.
I'm getting nervous because I got to pick my friends up at the airport. That's all. It's fine. They'll be fine.
I'm sure they're excited to see me. Have you asked them?
My friend Jim coming in loves you tremendously. He can't wait to see it.
He was very excited to hear your coming to Thanksgiving. Yeah.
Yeah, hopefully you don't disappoint everybody this year by not drinking again.
I mean, I shouldn't even understand.
You know, our whole thing, Joe, is when you don't drink, I never say a word to you.
I'm like, oh, good choice.
When I don't drink, you scream at me.
I don't ever scream.
While drunk.
That's not true.
Yeah, I'll take a video next time.
I don't.
And play it for you the next morning.
Listen, we talk this out.
You fucking pussy.
Well, that's a drinker fucking shot.
That's joke screaming first of all.
I'm not abusing volume.
A joke scream is loud as a scream scream scream.
I don't think you could name a time
where I told you I wasn't drinking.
You take breaks.
I take breaks.
My point is it's a holiday.
Let's celebrate.
I'm going to be drinking.
Good.
I believe you me.
I'm actually kind of feeling like getting wine boozy tomorrow.
You know what?
I'm not against it.
Yeah.
Okay, he's caressing this girl now that shot from the back his hand was dipping too low, folks
We were in a restaurant once it was actually the two of us
It was you and myself and Jamie Lee and our good friend Karen co -garrif that we were that yeah, we were at
Elkhampadra. Yeah, somewhere. No, no the other time we were at Mallow
We were at Mallow eating Mexican food and do you remember there was the dad with his daughter? Yes
rubbing her back and I kept through the whole meal saying, guys, this is inappropriate.
He's inappropriately massaging this girl. Everybody kept saying, Joe, no, you're being ridiculous.
It's his daughter. And I finally got a room to look. And the second everybody looked, they were like,
oh, no, that's weird. I had looked and I was like, Joe, you're fucking
to scut. You're being ridiculous. And I looked over and I was like, no, these two have a relationship.
It's not father -daughter at all. What I'm saying. Maybe she had that
Webster disease and she was actually 37 a little touch of the Simon Birch. Yeah, you know, some people just look young and don't have the disease. Ralph
Moch is a good example me as another good example. Yeah, Machio, a little known movie trivia. He was 52 when he made the karate kid and my cousin Vinnie, he was in his late 80s.
But why not a Rocky Balboa style?
Daniel is the karate kid, you know, I understand the macho is not as big a star as Stallone and maybe couldn't know who moving.
You hear me, you hear me objecting?
Why wouldn't any everyone would go see that you hear me objecting and we just said he still looks fucking great
I would kill to see that Machio comes in. Machio's trying to you'd have to get a big star to play the new karate kid because
Machio's not gonna open your movie, but you get somebody big in there as the kid somebody not Jaden Smith
I respect the next karate kid more than that remake because at least your next karate kid was still canon
and I agree, Joe, that new karate kid,
A, it was two hours and 20 minutes.
And B, the karate kid, Jane Smith,
and I'm not projecting what I know,
Jane Smith's personality to be,
his character was an asshole.
Really?
Why would you make the karate kid an asshole?
Why was he an asshole?
He's just like cocky and like a dick to everybody,
and then through the movie,
he becomes less of a cocky dick
and learns from Jackie Chan.
But like Machio was a sweet kid that got picked on that got picked on and needed to learn how to defend himself and
This thing starts and like jid's miss like hey you fucking assholes
He's a prick
Hey karate kids in the house. That's the exact line is hey you fucking assholes the karate kids that he actually kicks through the scene
Screen during the title sequence. Yeah, and that's how the movie starts
He said, how does this thing get a PG rating if that's the first line?
Yeah, yeah. I heard he actually says at one point it's called sweeping the leg you cunt
Exactly. I heard that was a line from the movie. I just bought credit kid one and two on blu -ray
Little box set and I looked at the Amazon reviews and this guy was like
The Amazon views are always hilarious. The sky was like five stars. If I could give it more, I would
He's like the picture on this movie is the stuff dreams are made of oh boy
I never I had only seen it on VHS. It was like having a new world opened up to me. Oh boy. Just on and on and on
I'm excited to see the picture
I know I never liked to I always liked one and three I like to two is considered the Empire of the Karate Kid series
Phil your mouth with your mother's feces. He's the devil. What do you expect him to say? He's devil.
Oh, this part's cool. The devil's got like little like creepy minions around him. Yeah. Okay.
I never liked part two. I didn't like that they went to Japan. I think it's a great idea for a
secret. Or do they go to China? I wish I knew, but I don't. I think it's Japan.
Okinawa was Japan, right? Yeah. Yeah, I didn't like it was too like serious. We didn't have the fun of the fur. I missed the Cobra Kai.
I love that the guy comes back in the third one for revenge.
Did I ever tell you the show I pitched with Robert Kelly and I pitched a show to Ralph Machia?
I think you did tell me about that. Yeah. Can I tell you about it on the podcast? No.
Now, years ago, Robert Killian, I had a meeting with Ralph Machia, we pitched him a show
where we played two agents that got fired from William Morris and had to start their
own agency.
And the only way they could think to make money was by finding actors that weren't working
and exploit them by making them do terrible gigs.
That's a good idea.
And we said, we want you, Ralph Machia, to be like the third guy in this, because the premise
the show is you have so little going on you're just you just hang around the office all the time
with us and end up working with us did you phrase it tactfully or were you like we phrase it
tactfully but but he also was very adamantly like look I like the idea but you can't make it sound
like I failed he was like I walked away to have a family he was like so that's my one thing I was
like okay that's fair but the premise was that Williams vodka who played Johnny right
But it was having a big super bowl party at his mansion and he wants to hire Ralph Machio
to host the super bowl party.
So we tell him like you got to go do this, this is good money man.
And Ralph Machio is like I'm not doing it.
You don't understand that guy really is a fucking asshole like there's no way and we're like
it'll be fine and we can take him to the party Williams Vodka is really nice for like you got
this buddy.
And then we leave.
And as soon as we leave, they turn on him like karate kids style,
being the shit out of him, because like I paid 25 grand to get you here
just like kick the shit out of you.
What more do you want?
Yeah, that's fun.
Machio ends up in the end of the episode.
He really liked this part, faced down in traction and said
and we're going to shoot it like the end of the outsiders when you die,
right, except you're calling us cock suckers.
Uh -huh.
And it's not sad, it's funny.
He was like, I love that idea.
Yeah, he's like as far as fighting Billy's vodka called him Billy's vodka
Goes people been trying to get us to fight again on screen for 30 years. There's a reason we haven't done it
And I was like okay, I guess maybe they have tried to reboot it with them or something
He just didn't like he didn't like retreading that but he loved the outsider's idea. Did you feel like macho really walked away to have a family?
Yeah, yeah, I did he he's like lives in Long Island. He had
He you know, he was still doing stuff when he stopped like yeah
was in my cousin Vinnie and you know right there's there's like a very clear end to him doing
movies yeah it's not like he did a bunch of bad ones and faded away it's like it just stops
suddenly yeah so I believed him but now what's weird is like macho let's say first karate kid he probably
made let's say max $250 ,000 then each additional one he might get a mill or
something like how is that money hanging in now 30 years later? Well,
dude, you're forgetting that he was like a huge box office draw for like five
years. I guess he had that run where he did like crossroads. Yeah. All right. He did
Yeah, he made his money. He does TV stuff. He works when he wants to work like he made that clear and I'm sure he's I'm sure he's sitting pretty
He also might have got to deal with the karate kid where they're like look man
This is gonna pay shit up front
But if it's a hit you'll make it on the back end
And he might have made a lot of fucking money on the back end
They didn't know better about those deals back then. Yeah, that's why that was a better time to work
Yeah, it's why Lucas is so fucking rich
You know, yeah
How did that guy have that foresight? How did he have the fucking foresight to be like, I'd just give me the merchandising money on this movie.
It's just to have a complete belief in yourself. It's so crazy that he knew that he knew to do that.
He's a walk in his mouth sitting in a diner with blood all over his shirt and with a mental patient and a mental patient in a hospital gown played by a man of plum.
Amanda Plummer
Related to Christopher Plummer daughter. I believe so I leave some and his Michael and Virginia Madsen bro and sis. Yep, okay. Oh, we got the whole thing connected here
I love Christopher Plummer
He's a great actor the insider is
A fantastic movie
What am I gonna do beat him to death with this notebook? Yeah, I like that part a lot
Plummer fucking kills on the insider. He kills it
He's also in Danny Collins, he plays his manager, he must be friends with Tremendous, Tremendous, it's the only time I've ever seen him play a character like this, he's like a prickly,
like old bastard kind of, you know, like he's got a lot of line, like he keeps having to go to Jersey to deal with Pacino, right, and he keeps going.
for two reasons number one I'm your best friend number two do this so I can
get the fuck out of New Jersey like I've never seen them play that kind of
guy yeah did you see beginners now I heard it was very good it's so good I own it
I'll own it to you if you want it's actually on Netflix and I was supposed to
audition for that what part do you and McGregor role I doubt it was the McGregor
roll the dog yeah no I don't I don't know I didn't I wasn't able to do the
audition though because I had a commitment I couldn't make it but it's
weird because I can't think of any role that you would ever could have
played. Maybe it was cut. It's a numbers game where you go in and
fucking you know yeah I also auditioned to play the role that Zach
Galfanakis got on board to death. So you're like did I really ever shot at
I auditioned for another thing once that David Cross got of course you hired David Cross. Yeah. Why would you even bring me in here speaking of speaking of David Cross. I just saw a preview for the new chipmunk movie. Is he in it?
I'm sure he is it was just a little teaser. I have not seen any of the chip on movies
But it was I'm gonna chip monks the second one was called the squeak hole. Yep, which is a good title
Let's be honest
The third one they dropped the ball so hard it is called Alvin in the chip monks. Yep
Road chip. Yeah, and I looked at it for like two minutes until I was like, oh like road trip
It's terrible title took me 10 minutes to think to remember that they're chipmunks and not squirrels, and I was like, wait, why is it chip?
Yeah, well, it is called all the name.
And then I was like, wait, is chip in our chip and Dale in this? No, that's the rescue rangers. Yeah, I couldn't, I couldn't wrap my fucking head around it, man.
It's kind of amazing that out of the chipmunks for whatever reason makes $500 million. I guess kids always love that sped up record player sound.
but the Chippendale people aren't like, hey, let's reboot Chippendale. Or maybe they are.
Maybe right now and something.
It's making a reboot.
Yeah.
Your favorite co -host, Pat.
Joe.
Just got an audition to read for Launchpad McQuack in the DuckTales reboot.
Movie?
No, TV show.
Oh, wow. That's big.
That would be some juicy cash.
That's big it my hands on that animated or are you wearing like a bill and everything's animated except me
And I actually get you ducks. I play a human no launch pads. They're friend
He's like the dumb guy that flies. Oh, yeah, the big like got you guys. Yeah
One of the notes in the in the you know, they give you notes. I'm like this is how we want the character to be uh -huh said
we're not looking for put on cartoony voices here make it real wow get back to
the real launch pad McQuack I don't know every time I audition for a cartoon it
says that yeah it always says like don't put it don't put a voice on like just
they want it to just be your voice okay which means I'm not getting it because does
this sound like the voice will launch pad McQuack to any of you not from what I
Remember hmm now now like Jeff Garland has a launch pad the quack voice
Pete
McQuack boy. Yeah
That's my Jeff Garland is launch pad impression if you didn't figure it out by the way. Yeah
You don't like to how
These did Christopher walk into say it's your night to how or you'll like to how you all like to how you all like to how terrible stunt
them. What does that mean? I missed the first part of the line. I love walking
is putting a certain effect on to his voice. Not post like he's doing it on
purpose. Where he's making it real growly and it's great. I've never heard him
growl like this. It works really well for him. It's very good.
That rag rat, he just called Virginia Medson. Well earlier, he was telling people to watch their profanity, you know, it's calling people rag bitches. Well, because the guy said God damn it. Oh, he said you're gonna have to watch that profanity. He's an angel. God is a soldier of God, Pat.
You understand? Yeah.
I do. Do they? I'm sure they explained it and we missed it because we're fucking
yapping for the sake of the listeners. Yeah. Did they explain why God never comes
down to help out the way devil does? I don't think so. He keeps going on with this
monkey thing. I'm gonna say this monkey business. Maybe the sequel is God's revenge or
or something. But God's a God's a good guy. Yeah, I know Joe. This is exactly the
plot to constantly. Joe just told me God's a good guy. Well, thanks God's revenge
doesn't make sense. There would be no revenge with God. Well, maybe the sequel is God
turning the other cheek for 90 minutes. The other butt cheek. Oh, then it's a the
sequel is a lot zainier than this one uh the yeah this is the plot of
Constantine but Constantine was a comic book long before a film so I wonder if
the prop is he was ever accused of taking stuff from the Constantine comics
probably how is Constantine the movie yeah fucking awesome I have it on my DVR
it's fucking a reason child of Booth yeah it's great all right I'll watch it it's
great and it's I mean that's like that's like machino and an arrow and heat it's that pairing
finally La Booth and Reeves my heat pairing would be Justin Long and La Booth together it's something
wow uh met Long the other night it's hard not to have a man crush on that guy I've met Long's
a nice guy very nice guy eerily nice uh what was I just going to say oh Constantine it's the turn
it's the it's the Reeves turn when Reeves became cool okay now there's that
turn with Reeves it was like Kiano's like you love Bill and Ted and all that
stuff and then he did all those movies where but it was like what is with this guy
yeah and then he turned and got cool again yeah that's like right in there like
he plays like a badass you saw John Wick right I didn't I want to see it it's
fucking awesome I want to see that new one where knock knock I like knock knock a
I didn't see it you saw it already I did watch it on demand was it out already
No, it's one of those you could buy it for five bucks on iTunes the day it came out in theaters and it was good
It was Eli Roth. I mean, it's a it's not perfect. It's that's
Reves actually has a couple scenes where he's doing like Nicholas Cage and the wicker man
Like he's just embracing the fact that he's not a strong actor and
It's funny, but it's very ballsy because he risks becoming a joke, but John Wicks got him now
I the guy from Big Bang Theory does the best Nicholas Cage in version I've ever seen which one the kid that plays the the kid that looks kind of like Ben Stiller on the Big Bang Theory.
He also does an amazing Ben Stiller impression about Johnny Galecki.
No, Simon Helbert.
Oh, that was good make a good effect. Was that the little girl?
I viewed out this fucking soul fine. Oh, that is not a good special fun. That's not bad.
This thing is gonna kill walking
Anyway, he doesn't amazing Nicholas Cage impression and he did it on Conan and he talked about the end of the wicker man when Nicholas Cage stands up and goes
You bitches
Okay, it was very funny
I met I had a meeting with Simon Hellberg who is very quiet
Must just be like one of those people who turns it on I always see him at one of my local bars
Not always I've seen him a few times at one of my local bars, which one you're resting?
I don't want to give up his spot not Joe but the guy go. I give him a little more credit than to think he'd be at Joe's
Where you always Joe's?
Jays, I mean jays bar. I hate that bar. Why do you hate it?
I've said a million times ahead and you're always like over at jays. It's fine. It's there's nothing splattered
about it it's not divy it's just a bar and you go in and you fucking wish
you were somewhere else you have a nice time it's a good bar to get a drink
with a lady I find while I would take lady to good luck good luck is fun but
it's a little it can be a little depressing because it's dark in there and it's
very dark in there. It also doesn't open until like it's not open at like happy hour. Well,
I like to take a lady out at about 2 a .m. Do you? Yeah. Because then you know you got a better
chance of sticking your prick in. I'm like, let me just get you home. I put my cape around. I like
to wear capes on days. I'll sure. Of course. A long flowing cape. Now when you are having sex with
the girl. Do you do you refer to your member as your prick or your hog. My sweaty hog is
usually right. You're ready to take this sweaty hog is usually what I'll say. Right. Take
it all the way bitch. I'm kidding. I'm just I'm totally joking. I just thought of a Freddie
Kruegery way to say it. Yeah. So I said it. I like sweaty hog. Subtile just said lead the light on
Thomas so whoever did the subtitles for the prophecy. Let's focus on your job. Should have said leave. All right. I'll also say, uh, take my come hose. Oh, God. I'll say that. Uh -huh. I'll say when I'm, when I'm about to, when I'm about to have an orgasm, I'll go, pull the rip cord baby, pull the rip cord.
There's a friend of mine who has this killer story. She's a beautiful young lady married now. I won't reveal her name obviously, but she was having sex and she told me the story she was like, I don't know what to tell you.
I had sex with this big fat guy.
Um, I just liked him. We went out. We had a good time. I liked him. I went home and she was on top having sex and when he comes, he puts his hands out like jazz hands and does this like waggles his hand, both hands out like jazz hands and shakes him around and he goes, I'm gonna explode.
I was so blown away. She was like, I've never been less turned on in my entire life. But I love that story. You hear, you just hear the creaking sounds of a giant
He's going to be like so sorry about all that so eggs yeah, I'll show myself how I had sex with a girl once years ago and while we're
We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We'll do it again. We
These people are going to have to take a shower.
The subtitle during the credits, by the way,
is upbeat music, parentheses.
This is upbeat.
This is the show and this was the prophecy. Thanks for listening to We'll see you in
hell presentation of the Fengoria podcast network produced by Thomas DeFao, executive
produced by Ken Hanley of Fengoria Entertainment for press opportunities, advertising inquiries,
information about, we'll see you in hell contact, Ken. He's a Ken at
Fangoria .com. If you're in the New York area, I'm headlighting Gotham
Comedy Club December 18th and 19th, five shows over the course of two
nights. Please come out to see that and happy Thanksgiving. Follow me on Twitter,
Joe DeRosa Comedy, Patty. You want to plug? I am at the Patrick Walsh Twitter
by Instagram, etc. And you know, that's all I got. I want you to have a good Thanksgiving.
I'm doing fine. I don't need you to come out and see my shit.
Happy Thanksgiving to you. Keep tweeting us. Give us five stars. Give us those great reviews and iTunes. We really appreciate it.
Thanks folks. Take care.