I'll see you in hell, I'll see you in hell, and when the sound of your screams becomes
a thing of my dreams, you know I'll say, I'll see you in hell, you know I will, I'll see
you in hell, you know I will.
Folks, we'll see you in hell, back with another episode to talk about the blockbuster picture
Mission Impossible.
My name is Joe DeRosa.
And my name is Patrick Walsh, and Joe's incorrect there, we're actually talking about Dead Reckoning.
That's why I said Mission Impossible.
Mission Impossible came out in 1996, Joe.
So you refer to it as the colon title.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just so people don't get confused.
Yes, Mission Impossible.
Or I'll go, hey, you seen DR yet?
And let's throw in the part one, because there's a part two coming of this riveting story.
I don't like this.
I don't like this whole part two thing.
And I'll tell you this, well they did it with this Spider -Man animated thing, too, you watch
a two and a half hour movie, and they're like, to be continued, I just, you know, Back to
the Future did it, other movies have done it.
It's just played out, it's annoying, you're forcing me to spend another $25.
What if I didn't like part one?
And I'll say this when we get to Mission Impossible, nothing about Dead Reckoning indicates this
needs to be a five hour feature film, nothing.
It started, look, sequels are sequels, right?
Or cliffhangers or whatever.
I can't argue with that, sequels are sequels, yes.
Yes, but this specific approach to splitting, where they let you know we're splitting a
example, it was Harry Potter, and it made sense, because the final book was coming out,
and they said, look, the final book is so big, and these films have been so successful,
we want to close it out right, we're going to do a two part theatrical version of the book.
The only thing I could think of before that was Kill Bill, right, where it was like, look,
this is a movie cut in half.
And now, and then Twilight did it, and then The Hunger Games, I think, did it.
The Hunger Games, yeah.
And now it's just, but again, those are all books, and then this is like, when a franchise
does it like this, it's like, you're just jacking me off here, like, what are we doing?
Make a concise part seven and a concise part eight, and we're done.
Yeah, I mean, we'll get there, but like, there's nothing about this that indicates we need
another 180 minutes to tell this story, but we'll get there, we'll get there.
We'll get there, you're slowing it down, you want to get into a little of the touching,
the feeling, the petting.
The squeezing, plus then we get twice the money from our podcast, because we'll get
to discuss parts one and two of Dead Reckoning.
It doesn't, well, I get you in theory.
It trickles down.
But if it wasn't Dead Reckoning part two, it would be, you know, Veggie Tales, whatever
the fuck they're doing there.
You know, there's a Lord of the Rings Veggie Tales.
It doesn't surprise me.
I mean, I grew up around churches, going to friends churches that seemed more fun than
mine, and Veggie Tales were always a big part of it.
I just can't believe they did, it's called Lord of the Beans, and I can't believe they
did a full, like that seems like a big scope.
Why not Gourd of the Beans?
Pat, I didn't write the goddamn thing.
I don't know.
Why Gourd?
Wait, what's a Gourd?
A Gourd is like a pumpkin, or, you know, it's something you'd find along with your other
veggies.
I don't know the, I'm unfamiliar with the word.
I'm embarrassed of my limited veggie vocabulary.
Should be.
How do they decide what, like these were all Christian, correct?
Veggie Tales?
So the Lord of the Rings is also Christian?
No.
You're thinking of the Lion, the Witch, and the Wardrobe series, the Chronicles of Narnia.
I didn't know Veggie Tales was Christian until you just said that, until you made the church
joke, and I was like, oh, that's a Christian thing, I didn't know that.
I thought they were just low -budget, kids things.
And they are low -budget.
You're right.
What was that?
I'm looking it up now.
Oh, it says, why is Veggie Tales no longer religious?
NBC required the shows be removed of scripture passages and references to God in order to
reach as broad an audience as possible.
So there you go.
It was about God, and then it stopped being about God.
Well, I'm just surprised of the Lord of the Rings parody, or whatever you want to call
it, because Veggie Tales is just so low -budget.
I'm like, why would they take on something this big?
Yeah.
When your thing, I mean, it looks like flash animation or something.
Anyway.
Veggie Tales.
There's also a Bible Man 50 Shades of Grey adaptation.
Now, I don't know who Bible Man is.
Bible Man is the religious superhero who uses the powers of God played by many people, but
originated, the character originated by Willie Ames from Charles and the Shark.
Sure.
Bible Man became quite a kitschy cult thing.
You know, there were action figures that they sold at like rock and rolly kind of stores
and things.
I had a Bible Man action figure.
It was definitely when I was in college, like a sort of kitschy thing you'd get high and
watch and laugh at.
But people, there's a big following to it, a legitimate following.
People loved Bible Man.
Do you think you getting high and laughing at Bible Man is what has caused the Lord to
smite your existence?
He was already smiting it.
That was my first time saying fuck you to the big man.
Yeah.
I'm not going to take it anymore.
And I will.
I do take it.
He's God.
He makes you take it.
You don't really have a choice.
It's a good question.
I can't argue it.
Now, you're up quite early this morning.
It's 830.
My mushroom coffee has brewed and I see it from the corner of my eye, but I haven't had
a chance to get to it.
I want it.
You can get it.
Why is it mushroom?
What do you mean mushroom coffee?
Well, I tried it out.
It's not mushrooms like it's going to make me trip, but it's these new trendy mushrooms
that give you focus and energy.
You heard about they're putting mushrooms in coffee, haven't you?
Nope.
That's why I asked.
Lion's mane.
You know, they got all these names and it's all, I'm sure it's bullshit, but the coffee
tastes good.
I got a new coffee maker.
My sister had given me and my ex -wife a $250 gift certificate for a couple's cooking class
Christmas before we separated.
And I said, called them up and said, Hey, what can I get that is not this couple's cooking
class?
I'll take anything.
Just please don't make me go to this alone.
And they said, well, we have some, some great kitchen items and I got this coffee maker
that is the best one I've ever had.
I fucking love it.
It all worked out for the best.
I think, and I mean this, I think the cooking class, I'm not making fun.
I really do think this is a good, a good idea.
The cooking class certificate is a good thing that you could write into something.
Like the guy's got the certificate.
It's like the last thing from the marriage.
He's got it like in a frame or it's, it's, it's some significant thing in his life.
Uh, and you learn about the marriage through that.
Well, if they still made romantic comedies, I would go to this class alone and there would
be one other kind of clumsy person there alone and we'd get partnered up and then we'd wind
up fucking on the, on the dough or something, you know?
I was thinking more of a, like a wonder boys.
It's like the tattered bookmark in the novel you're writing.
And then somebody at the end of the movie is like, what, what is that?
And then you learn like, he was, he was kind once, you know, like that, that kind of thing.
Sure.
Okay.
Fair enough.
I got that on the brain.
I watched a movie.
I'm going to do it in the movie corner called a little white lie last night starring Michael
Shannon.
Okay.
You're right to make that face.
I never heard of this fucking thing.
I'll get to it.
Yeah.
A good movie.
I'll talk about it in the corner.
I don't want to get to, I don't want to say too.
I don't know.
I get a lot to say about it.
But I talk about it while I pour my mushroom coffee.
I'll hear you.
All right.
Then we'll start the corner.
My first movie is called a little white lie starring Michael Shannon, Kate Hudson, Don
Johnson, Emmett Walsh, much like Patty Walsh.
Is it Emmett Walsh or Emmett Walsh?
I'm going to look that up real quick.
Bear with me people because that's going to bother me.
Yeah.
It's Emmett.
Emmett Walsh in this thing.
By the way, this came out in twenty twenty two and it was great to see Emmett Walsh is
still acting and stuff like that's wild.
Who else is in this?
Zach.
Righteous gemstones once in a while.
That's great.
Zach Graf shows up in this.
Jimmy Simpson.
It's a great cast.
It's a really great cast.
What attracted me to this movie, it was on Hulu and it was clearly a sort of romantic
comedy, indie comedy kind of thing.
And I was so intrigued by Michael Shannon being in a comedy.
I was like, I have to watch this.
I don't understand.
Like, I've never seen him do anything where he's not either the like racist sexist boss
or he's the neighbor of a family that beat one another.
He's only in these horridly sad films.
So I wanted to watch it.
I'm unfamiliar with the writer, director.
He's done a couple other things, but whatever.
2022, as I said, it's not the greatest movie, but I would say it's a delightful little
film.
It's again, much like when I talked about paint a few episodes ago, it felt like a
throwback.
Like we used to see these kind of movies a lot, these independent things.
They'd often star Parker Posey or somebody like that.
And they'd be playing at the one cinema on the outskirts of town, but they'd still get
out there.
And we all kind of enjoyed them and enjoyed that somebody put their story on screen and
got it made.
Now that all of these types of, in heavy quotes, indie films have been sort of absorbed and
corporatized by the studios, now they get bashed and people are like, this fucking
thing, 36 % sucks.
But I still appreciate the aspect that somebody wrote this and got it made.
And it's not an easy thing to do.
It's about Kate Hudson is a teacher at a college and so is Don Johnson and so is M .M.
at Walsh.
The college throws this literary festival once a year.
It's a little rinky dink festival and I believe takes place in Akron, Ohio.
And the dean of the school is like, we're not going to do this festival anymore.
Like, we're done.
Like, it's just, it doesn't do any, nobody cares.
It loses money.
We can't get any notable writers to come to it.
And Kate Hudson says, well, I have somebody that's going to save our festival.
And it's an author of a book called Goat Time, which I don't understand why the book is called
that, but that's what it's called.
And this is, he's a catcher in the rye.
What's the guy?
Catcher in the rye.
I'm blanking on the author's name.
J .D. Salinger.
Salinger.
Yeah.
It's about, you know, he's a J .D. Salinger type where he, you know, he wrote this one book.
It was a massive hit and he disappeared from the spotlight completely.
So Kate Hudson says, I found him and he's going to come and he's going to speak at our school,
at our festival, and that's going to make people care.
And sure enough, it does.
The twist is, Michael Shannon plays this guy.
He gets the letter and the immediate twist is he's not the guy.
He just has the same name.
But he's a down and out handyman with nothing going on who's an alcoholic.
And he's like, his friend convinces him to go and pretend he's the guy because nobody knows what the guy looks like.
And nobody knows.
Go just do this.
Like, it'll be a great way for you to make some fast cash, basically.
So Michael Shannon agrees.
I'm going to spoil this movie.
I think you're safe.
He goes.
He is pulling off this hustle.
And he also does have this weirdly inexplicable ability to kind of write and be sort of poetic with his words.
As the movie goes on, you realize he is the guy.
He has just suppressed it because of a traumatic experience.
Then Zach Braff shows up and claims to be the actual author.
You don't really know who's who.
But it all ends up with essentially Michael Shannon being the actual author.
There's still a tiny bit of doubt that he might not actually be.
They just want him to be.
And he just wants to be.
But it's about the redemption of this guy.
It's a very sweet movie.
It never gets heavy.
It never gets too dark.
You know, it's it's kind of like it reminds me of like, remember that that movie?
This was that movie with Christina Ricci, The Something of Sex.
The opposite, the opposite of sex.
It's like one of those kinds of movies used to get those movies a lot, you know, and it star like David Schwimmer or something.
And you'd be like, this is an enjoyable little film like, you know, it's not going to change my life.
But I liked it.
And I like when you see those things pop up here and there and when they have the same vibe as like 90s, 1997.
And this certainly did.
I'm not going to tell you, you need to go out and see it.
But if you do catch it, you're not going to be mad at it.
Let's put it that way.
OK.
Michael Shannon, by the way, does nothing funny in the entire movie.
I was going to say.
Yeah.
But Don Johnson is very funny.
I'm halfway through George and Tammy with Michael Shannon, the story of George Jones and Tammy Wynette, which is fine.
It's hard in a post -Walk Hard world to do a music biopic and not have it just, you know, seem like a joke.
But it's entertaining.
Heavy stuff, George and Tammy or no?
No, I mean, to me, that's all fun and games.
It's just a guy who likes to drink too much, trying to stay married.
You know, that's the story of every country couple.
But it's good.
I mean, they're both good in it.
It's pretty by the numbers.
I watched one of the most boring titles of the year, Master Gardener, directed by Paul Schrader.
We've got Constant Gardener already out there, which is a more boring title because that's a guy who just can't stop gardening.
But this one is about a master.
All of Paul Schrader's movies these days are about guys who are obsessed with something.
They're all essentially the same movie.
I thought the card counter really sucked with Oscar Isaac's.
I really enjoyed he's even trying with the titles anymore.
No, no.
The card counter, the Master Gardener, a grumpy accountant, the new Paul Schrader movie, the estranged zookeeper starring Mark Ruffalo.
They're all of a piece.
I did really like First Reformed with Ethan Hawke.
I mean, these are beyond depressing movies.
These are basically movies that suggest there is no hope to living.
And Paul Schrader has really embraced that theme in his old age, which, you know, sometimes you're in the mood for this shit.
Sometimes you're not.
This one just ain't really no good.
Joel Edgerton is not my favorite actor.
He looks a lot like Conan O 'Brien in this, which was hard to look past.
I'm going to read you the quick paragraph description.
Narvel Roth.
Let me just stop there.
The character's name is Narvel Roth is a meticulous horticulturalist who is devoted to tending the grounds of a beautiful estate and pandering to his employer, the wealthy dowager, Mrs.
Haverhill.
When she demands that he take on her wayward and troubled great niece, it unlocks dark secrets from a buried violent past.
So that is the card counter.
It was a card counter.
And then halfway through, you see him like beating the shit out of people in Iraq.
And it's like, oh, OK, this is the same kind of vibe.
It's a guy with great secrets.
He's fucking Sigourney Weaver.
I always love seeing Sigourney.
She's not great in this.
It's that kind of like, oh, you know, you don't forget who runs the show here, young man kind of parts.
But she has Joel Edgerton take care of her attractive, seemingly 18 year old niece.
She and Edgerton have a flirtation.
Edgerton takes off his shirt at one point and is covered in Nazi tattoos.
That's his back story.
He's a recovering white power guy.
And the niece is half black to add more complications to things.
These two have a relationship that it seems like Paul Schrader thinks is totally cool and legit in 2023.
I kept thinking that the point of the movie was going to be how inappropriate this age difference was, but that didn't really come up.
Sigourney Weaver, you know, has her criticisms of it.
But basically, it's this very strange love story.
There's there's weird violence that pops up.
I'm not quite sure what the point of the damn thing was.
And I wish Paul Schrader would kind of veer out of this box he's in because it's not really that interesting to me anymore.
And I love him when he's on his game.
But it's been a while. It's been a while.
All right.
Not a great film.
I watched.
And this was a rewatch.
Yeah.
Because I was like.
This movie can't be as bad as I remembered it being.
Always a mistake to say that.
It can be.
It's Pacino.
It's McConaughey.
It's two for the money.
Oh, wow.
I don't think I even saw two for the money.
Pretty sure I did not.
It's a gambling movie.
All right.
Here's why I turned it on.
Here's why I was like only give us a second chance.
You know when you're on like I think this was also on Hulu.
But you know when you scroll over the movie it'll play like a scene from the movie.
Yeah.
Auto play it or whatever.
I was scrolling around and I landed on two for the money.
And it's this scene of Pacino.
And he runs a betting company.
And he's talking to McConaughey and he's it's classic awesome Pacino.
He's in a suit.
He's smoking a cigarette.
You know he's like and he's like he's like let me tell you why people give us their money.
Come Monday.
They're desperate.
They got to get out of that hole they built for themselves all weekend.
That's where we come in.
I'm like I'm into this.
All right.
This is like a Glen Gary Glen Ross kind of thing like I'm going to rewatch.
Yeah.
So the story is Matthew McConaughey is a small town Midwestern kid.
Big surprise.
He has he was a star football player.
He was supposed to go pro but an injury ends his career early.
He has an inexplicable ability to pick winners for betting.
He gets a job doing the nine seven six or eight and one eight hundred numbers whatever it was at the time where you call him and you give him you know you put bets with him and he gives you your picks or whatever.
And there's a lot of like legal loopholes they have to jump through so it's so it's no actually I think he's in Vegas so it's legal.
He gets a call from Pacino Pacino's in New York Pacino runs a company.
Because it's illegal to bet in New York the way the company works is you they just advise you and if they want to keep getting the advice they pay you but they don't actually bet for you.
You just have to give them a percentage of your winnings.
And you know it's the classic thing McConaughey goes to New York he's never said a curse word in his life literally that's one of the plot points.
He it's it's devil's advocate he's very close with his mother he's a good guy.
Pacino lures him to New York and the allure of New York is you know in the fast lane and all that stuff starts to change him into a monster he swore he would never become.
But she knows is a recovering gambling addict.
He's married to Renee Russo.
Renee Russo is a recovering drug addict their whole thing is desperately trying to just stay clean while also finding great success in this business they do this gambling business or whatever.
It's not a good movie it's just not good Jeremy Piven is in it.
I'm not saying it's not good because he's in it I'm just saying he's in it it was like it was like supposed to be.
It was supposed to be this big flick it was like McConaughey was up the ladder was coming up the ladder Pacino was you know still in the grace period of like post heat that realm.
Piven was about to do entourage like this was supposed to be like we're going to launch a lot of stuff out of this flick.
I actually think there was probably a good movie there.
I think it was recut and studio noted and ruined.
There's a McConaughey voiceover through the first act of the movie that just goes away and the voiceover serves zero purpose and I feel like that was a studio note of we need this.
Yeah.
I also don't think Renee Russo Al Pacino and Al Pacino at this time would have signed on to this thing.
If it was if it read the way it came off on screen McConaughey I do because McConaughey was in that zone where he was kind of.
I mean you know we all forget it wasn't till true detective and Dallas Buyers Club we had written McConaughey off.
We were like this guy's this guy is a joke.
He does like you know failure to launch.
Colin Farrell did the same thing at some point.
We all we all felt the same about Colin Farrell and then he was like no I'm just going to make great one million dollar movies for a while until you all like me again.
It's a good strategy if you have the talent to back it up.
Yeah there's there's not much to say to this movie's credit outside of there are some great Pacino scenes.
It's a really funny scene where he's at a gambler's anonymous meeting and he does this awesome Pacino speech.
Yeah where he's like he's like if I may my first time at this meeting but let me tell you what's going on with all of you.
You're a bunch of losers you know and they're like they're shocked and he's like I am too.
That's what we like from gambling lose it.
He does this great speech and then somebody goes wait a minute aren't you that asshole that pushes people to bet with his hotline.
And Pacino when he's he gets mad at them because he's like you got to tell an ex alcoholic bartender to get out of the A .A. meeting and he's like fuck you.
You guys are jerks.
So then he starts handing his card out to everybody and going call me when you relapse.
It's a really funny scene.
There's some scenes in it like that where you're like this is kind of fun.
You don't quite understand though what's going on like Pacino is undermining and playing McConaughey throughout the movie and in fact betraying him throughout the movie.
And in the end McConaughey saves Pacino's life out of love.
And that's why I say I feel like there was a bigger better movie here and things are just cut out of it.
We're like I don't understand why he would save him after he screwed him over.
There must be stuff that's not here where he was way more of a father figure.
They had way more of a debt to one another blah blah blah.
So two for the money.
None for the show.
I say it does.
I mean a gambling movie with Pacino.
I do even with your negative review I probably will seek this out now and watch it.
I like gambling movies.
I watched I rented a freak scene.
The story of Dinosaur Jr.
And I had been excited to see this as I absolutely love the band Dinosaur Jr.
And the music that they make I think even down to their latest album they're still making great great records after you know 30 plus years in this business.
And I didn't know much about them.
I know Lou Barlow went on to form Sabato and so forth but I was like great an opportunity to learn about this band that I love so much.
Unfortunately and I'm sure the director realized this immediately.
Dinosaur Jr. are not interesting people at all.
They can play and sing music really well.
Sometimes those people aren't charismatic and compelling.
Jay Mascis comes off like you know he'd rather not be there.
He'd rather not be interviewing him.
He'd rather not have gotten out of bed in the morning but not in kind of this grumpy funny way you get sometimes in a documentary.
He just seems like shut that thing off kind of vibes.
And the story is not that interesting.
I mean it's got less drama than your average sort of rags to riches band saga.
So it's kind of this unpleasant feeling of loving the band but having a shit documentary.
It's happened before you know.
Sometimes a band you hate will have the best documentary simply because they had the craziest times you know.
I don't give a shit about Motley Crue.
I'd much rather watch a behind the scenes of Motley Crue than Dinosaur Jr.
Even though the music is better.
So you know if you're a completist, if you're a huge fan, give it a watch.
I mean it's obviously got good music in it.
But if you're looking for some sort of definitive portrait of a great band, this is not that.
I don't know.
I don't really think it's the documentarian's fault.
Although it's certainly not a good or well put together documentary.
I just think he had a band that was pretty uncooperative and did not want to really talk to him.
And you're left with a pretty dull movie unfortunately.
Yeah that's kind of like the Pixies doc, Loud Quiet Loud, which is an enjoyable documentary.
And they're amicable throughout.
They're happy to be doing it.
But it plays a lot more just like a behind the scenes bonus feature on a DVD.
You're like there's no real drama here.
We all kind of know the story of the breakup and how contentious it was.
But they don't really delve into that.
It's just them kind of being pleasant on the road doing these reunion shows.
And you're like okay, like cool.
Yeah the only thing I like in that movie that's sort of like just heartbreaking is that the drummer was called by Dave Grohl.
And asked to drum for the Foo Fighters.
But he missed the voicemail and didn't find out about it until years later.
That's the one aspect of the Pixies documentary I found amazing.
It probably cost him $30 million not getting that message.
But oh well.
Speaking of Motley Crue.
Oh go ahead, sorry.
No please, please.
No and you just had said the music is bad, which it is.
There's a great Mike Patton quote where they're interviewing him about the new Phantomus album he had put out at the time.
Which Phantomus is very abrasive, very experimental, very challenging art metal.
The guy goes, what do you have to say to the people that say this is a hard record to listen to?
It's a very hard record to listen to.
Mike Patton goes, it's not a hard record to listen to.
You want a hard record to listen to?
Go listen to the new Motley Crue album.
Yeah.
What did Mike Patton do that was like sex music?
It was a side project that popped up.
He did an album with Dan the Automator called Lovage that was like...
There's a sex element to it, but it's sort of like satin bathrobe 70s vibes.
Like a Playboy mansion -y kind of thing.
It popped up on my fuck mix and I was like, who's this?
And I was like, alright.
And the woman that sings on that throughout, I'm not familiar with her, I only ever heard her on that record.
She's very good too.
Yeah, that's a good record.
Alright, my last one is a documentary also called California Typewriter.
This is the latest thing I've seen that convinced me I need to buy more old shit that nobody uses anymore.
I want to get a typewriter now.
I got an old one from Galecki as a gift and it looks fantastic on my desk even though I'd never use it.
Apparently Christopher Nolan uses the typewriter on set.
Tom Hanks is a big proponent.
He's featured throughout this thing.
Tom Hanks said...
By the way, I meant to ask you this and I'm sorry to cut you off.
Music documentary, and I assume you're like me and used to watch these VH1 100 best bands of hard rock or whatever.
I used to watch these countdowns all the time.
Who would you guess has the most screen time in the Dinosaur Jr. documentary?
If you can imagine, who's a guy who regardless of genre or year, he's got to give his two cents regarding that band and he's in every music documentary?
I'll give you three guesses.
Now me and my friends used to joke that it was always Vernon Reed of Living Color because they needed a black hard rock guy and there's only one.
Is this a music guy or you're saying he's not a music guy?
He's a music guy.
Oh, he is a music guy.
He has to give us two cents.
Always in a music doc.
You'll know it when you hear it.
Well, I mean, Dave Grohl is a good guess.
He's in everything.
Grohl is a very good guess.
Absolutely.
And I love Grohl because he's always passionate about whatever he's talking about.
And this guy too, he's always well informed.
He's just a little annoying.
I know you're a fan.
Henry Rollins.
That's fair.
Is he in every music?
I didn't know.
I didn't realize that he was somebody that always popped up like that.
He certainly was when I was in like high school in the 90s, especially in that VH1 best artist of hard rock.
He appeared constantly to a crazy degree.
But Dinosaur Jr. is not even really his world, but he's in there a lot.
He likes he's got a wide, large palette when it comes to music.
He likes a lot of stuff.
I'm kind of you're sort of surprised like, oh, really?
He also I believe I've met him once or twice.
I believe that he is autistic because he's like he's so just like.
It's very it's very intense is the wrong word, but it's just he's so thorough.
And like he starts talking and it kind of just goes.
And then like when you watch him on stage, you could watch him two nights in a row and it's a completely different show.
He's got this ability to just take what's in his head and spew it out to the audience.
And when I met him, I was like, I think I think he might be autistic.
And that's not a disparaging comment.
And I just think that so I think that might be why he.
Is able to sort of regurgitate this sort of encyclopedic knowledge of every band that has ever lived.
Yeah. Or it could just be that he is stone sober.
And maybe that's what happens after 40 years of sobriety.
You're just a Wikipedia page at that point.
American typewriter Tom Hanks is a huge typewriter enthusiast.
This movie also made me appreciate John Mayer a bit more.
John Mayer, I was just kind of like, yeah, I mean, I never liked his music.
But as a guy, he seems kind of annoying.
But stole a tweet from there you go.
He Tom Hanks said he has 250 working typewriters.
He said that if you know him and you say, I want a typewriter, you will have one from him.
Courtesy of him on your desk the next day.
And he said that he even if he comes to your house and then sees it up on a shelf, he is like, get that thing down here.
Come on, what are you doing?
Like, so Tom Hanks is very much.
And this is what made me want to get a typewriter.
Tom Hanks was like, I type something every day.
No matter what it is, maybe it's a thank you note, maybe it's an idea, maybe it's part of a script, whatever.
He was but I type something every day.
And he get he got really into the visceral aspect of it and the tangible aspect of it.
And so did John Mayer.
John Mayer made a great point and was very insightful.
He goes, I bought a typewriter and he goes what I was working on the lyrics and ideas for I think it was his third album.
And he said, I had a thing.
I was living in New York and he said I would I would type three pages per day.
Either right before I went out at night or right after I got home at night.
And he said that was the rule.
Three pages.
And he said stream of consciousness.
That was it.
And that's how he said I started to get the ideas for the lyrics for my third album because I wanted to get to a deeper place and all that sort of thing.
But he said he goes, I have hard drive after hard drive after hard drive.
I have never once gone back and checked any of it.
But everything I've typed, I've accessed and referenced.
And he's like, look, because it's here.
Here it is right here.
And Tom Hanks was saying that, too.
He's like, you know, you go into a museum and you see a typewritten note from the Duke of whatever.
And he's like, he wrote that.
That's it.
You know, and I was like, that's actually a really cool point.
The name of the movie comes from a shop called California Typewriter that is apparently the last shop in the United States that is still repairing typewriters.
Yeah, I doubt it's that's how it's sort of poet posed as presented in the movie.
I can't be the last, but it's got to be one of the last.
And, you know, it's a struggling shop, obviously.
So I enjoy.
I mean, I have this this really cool old one that I'm sure does work.
I just never thought I would.
But maybe maybe I'll be inspired by it.
Take it off the shelf and just try it out today.
All right.
You know, I'm going to buy do I want it to buy.
I want it to actually go into a store and buy one because I want to support them.
Any shop that might have these for sale.
But, you know, it starts to get a little tough because there is there is a place in Manhattan.
But I looked them up on Google Maps and it was like by appointment only.
And I'm like, you're just asking to pay seven hundred dollars more.
Yeah. Then the typewriter is actually worth.
Yeah.
And what this sounds like is how I buy a new notebook or a new pen or something,
thinking it'll inspire me to write and then it just winds up collecting dust.
That's the part that I am.
That gives me pause with your purchase of a typewriter.
Also, that I can't fit another book into my apartment.
Yeah. Yeah.
Let alone a typewriter.
So still, I'll do it.
I'll do it. I'll probably have a typewriter by the end of the weekend.
I know for a fact you will have a typewriter by the end of the weekend and probably buy a new car to go pick up the typewriter.
I listened to Ron Shelton's audio book about the making of Bull Durham
and I really enjoy on Audible somebody walking you through their experience making a movie.
I think I talked last time I listened to As You Wish about the Princess Bride, which was a blast.
And this Ron Shelton one is more a one person's point of view look at making a movie from the original concept to the editing room, to the fights with the studio, to blah, blah, blah.
So I listened to it.
I loved it.
And then I rewatched Bull Durham, which I hadn't seen in 20 years.
And I've never loved Bull Durham.
It is considered like one of the all time great sports movies.
It is considered one of the all time great romances.
And it just does nothing for me.
And I don't know why.
I think the reason is you mentioned Tom Hanks, Joe.
There's something about a Tom Hanks and a Meg Ryan where I'm rooting for them.
I love them.
They're adorable.
I want them to succeed and be happy in life.
There's something about this combination of Tim Robbins, Susan Sarandon and Kevin Costner that I don't care about.
And I like all three actors just fine.
But there's something about the combo of them I don't care about.
And I don't know why it is.
I absolutely love Thelma and Louise.
I think it's a masterpiece.
Came out around the same time.
It's not a Susan Sarandon problem.
I love Costner in most things.
It's not a him issue.
Tim Robbins, you know, I find him to be one of the most difficult guys to cast correctly.
Like I like him in Mystic River, even though I don't really believe him in the part.
I love him in Shawshank, even though I think a million other guys could have played that part.
He's just a weird dude.
I actually like him in Nothing to Lose when he tries a big broad comedy.
I thought he kind of worked in that.
But for whatever reason, these three together doesn't get my dick hard.
I don't know what else to tell you.
The premise of the movie is Kevin Costner is a minor league catcher.
He's on the way out.
Tim Robbins is on the way up.
Susan Sarandon is the stunning woman who decides every baseball season she's going to fuck one guy to glory.
She's going to fuck him so good that he becomes an amazing baseball player and gets all the way to the major leagues.
Tim Robbins and Kevin Costner.
It is a wild premise.
Like it wouldn't be made today.
It just wouldn't happen.
But she's like the good luck puss.
She goes from town to town fucking the hot young rookie.
But this time she learns that her heart really belongs with the washed up guy Kevin Costner.
So even in terms of Ron Shelton movies, I don't think that this is as good a movie as White Men Can't Jump.
I don't think this is as good a movie as Tin Cup, which is super underrated and I love also with Don Johnson and Rene Russo.
That's all I can say.
When he does his little speech, like when Susan Sarandon asks Kevin Costner, what do you believe in?
This is one of the most famous scenes in movie history.
And Costner goes, I believe in long, slow, wet kisses that last for three days.
I believe in the cock.
I believe in the pussy.
It's the most wince inducing monologue.
It is so unbelievable.
Nobody speaks like this.
If a woman asked a man, what do you believe in, Pat?
And I gave a minute, 30 second monologue about the things I believe in.
And it included the cock and the pussy.
This woman would throw me out of her house rightfully.
So it's overwritten.
It's kind of annoying.
I can't say I dislike Bull Durham.
I just think even though I just listened to a 10 hour book about this thing, it still couldn't make me love this movie.
I don't know what it is.
Joe, your thoughts?
I saw it when I was young.
And it's got Robert Wool.
My mom loved it.
Moms loved it, yeah.
I can tell you, I think I know why you guys like us don't like it.
I think I can speak to exactly why you don't like it.
It dropped at the same time as Major League.
I love Major League.
Major League's awesome.
But Major League is a fun, awesome baseball comedy.
And Bull Durham is trying to be sexy and smart.
And who gives a shit?
Also, look, I like Kevin Costner just fine.
The guy does not ooze charisma.
He just doesn't.
He's also not a guy who should be giving 90 second speeches.
No.
Costner is good.
The guy who should grunt.
Costner is good in a sort of a clinical role where you want to root for him.
He's, you know, the Untouchables.
JFK.
Field of Dreams.
That's the kind of thing he's good in where it's like, I've got a mission.
I'm on it.
Are you with me?
And you're like, well, of course I'm with you.
You seem like a nice guy.
Sarandon is sexy, but she's sexy in her own way.
And that role is not the way she's sexy.
Sarandon is sexy in like in The Witches of Eastwick.
Like I'm a teacher who's going to let it loose.
And oh boy, does she have a wild side.
Sarandon is sexy in like the Sarah Jessica Parker way and like Family Stone.
Where it's like, well, you're tied a little too tight, but boy, I bet you got another side to you.
Like that's how Sarandon is like sexy and fun.
You know, Melanie Griffith is more the bulldorum at that time.
I, in my opinion.
I can see that.
Yeah.
And then Tim Robbins just, who gives a shit?
Who gives a shit?
Well, they talk about how much the studio didn't want him because he was coming off of Howard the Duck.
And Shelton's like, can you believe it?
I'm like, yeah, I believe it.
He's coming off Howard the Duck.
They didn't want to cast him in this thing.
This guy's gotten, this guy got good stock and good faith off of the player.
Yeah.
And Shawshank, which Shawshank is a very good movie, obviously.
I could give a rat's ass though.
It's like Shawshank to me is a good movie.
It's a good movie, but it's a good movie the way like Forrest Gump is a good movie.
It's like, it's like guys.
Yeah, it's kind of hard to fuck this up, given the circumstances.
You know, like I think Shawshank is excellent.
I don't think anybody could have played Freeman's part better.
I think that I agree with and I'm not, I'm not exaggerating.
I think a hundred actors at that time could have played Andy Dufresne as good as or better than Tim Robbins.
He's not bad in the movie at all.
I just don't think he's the guy for that part.
That's what I'm getting at.
A hundred actors could have played Dufresne or the other parts outside of Freeman, right?
And it could have been directed by any one of a dozen directors of that time.
If I told you right now, you know, Shawshank Redemption actually was Spielberg.
You'd be like, oh, OK, I see it.
Yeah, like there's a million guys Ron Howard or.
Yeah.
So so my point is, is like I'm going to even take Shawshank off the good off the good, good, good, goodwill, good faith points, whatever the fucking term is.
So my point is, is Tim Robbins has been coasting on the player for Jesus Christ, man.
I can't name.
I don't think I can name aside from the movies we just named.
I can't even name any other Tim Robbins movies.
Yeah, it'd be tough. It'd be tough.
What else is he in?
The ones I said, you know, Mr. River, Howard the Duck.
Nothing to lose.
Austin Powers, too, for four minutes as the president.
Sure.
Like tape heads with John Cusack back in the day.
Bob Roberts.
You know, he directed movies for a while.
Cradle Will Rock.
Bob Roberts.
That fucking run of like he's a guy.
Yeah, he's the president.
But he's not whatever.
All right.
Another one of these fucking things.
Joe, let's reckon with Dead Reckoning, if we may.
Yeah, because you got to go soon.
You got therapy, right?
I got a therapy.
Mission Impossible.
Dead Reckoning, part one of two.
You know what you're getting here.
It's Tommy C as Ethan Hunt.
It's his ragtag team.
Bing Rames seated as always.
Simon Pegg out, you know, making quips, coming in hot with gadgets and things.
Yeah, Jesus.
Now, I just rewatched all of the Mission Impossibles.
I've been going through them on the solo movie corner, and I'll update the list on this month's.
But what I noticed in watching the first six movies is that even the worst of them,
which I think most people, myself included, would say is probably Mission Impossible 2,
is an above average action movie.
It's a really great, consistent franchise.
And I'm just saying it, this is the only one that I would say hangs down around part two.
It's got some great moments, but it's on the lesser end of the spectrum.
And I think the issue is the running time, which is about two hours and 40 minutes.
All these other Mission Impossible movies have hovered around two hours,
but they're getting longer with each one.
And they just don't need to be.
In this one, they spend 45 minutes describing what the threat is.
In every one of these movies, Ethan Hunt is looking for a box, a jewel, a gem,
whatever, something, a remote control.
You know the bare minimum about it.
You know that if it falls into the wrong hands, the world will end.
And Ethan Hunt has to get it.
That's all you know, and that's all you need to know.
This one devotes 45 minutes to telling you what the threat is.
Surprise, it's AI, which is going to be, I guess, the hot new threat for the next five years at the movies.
But they spend so much time talking about it, how it works, what it does.
It basically sounds like Wi -Fi, but they describe it like it's some amazing new technological breakthrough.
Well, it is. They just don't do anything interesting with it.
They don't do anything cool with it, yeah.
The action, as always, is great.
But for some reason, in part seven, they decide to really lay into the technical jargon and explanation.
I don't get it.
I had a good time, but for the first time in this franchise, my patience was tested a little bit.
That's what I would say.
I'll say the one thing they did very right was establishing a premise of this AI weapon is very dangerous.
Why? Not because of what it can do, necessarily, in the immediate sense.
But the reason is it will have the ability to create a completely untrustworthy reality
where none of us know what is real and what is fake and what we can trust and what is not trustworthy and blah, blah, blah.
Which is the thing I always feared the most, and I've said about AI.
It's not about what it's going to do.
It's about what it's going to do, what it's going to make us do to each other in that circumstance.
So when that was established and laid out as the premise, I was excited.
I was like, oh, wow, this is great.
That's the good part.
Here's the bad part.
For the first time ever, Mission Impossible, as you said, is trying to make a statement.
You're not good at making statements.
This is the fourth movie now in a row where they have to go full rogue.
Guys, write a new fucking premise.
Jesus Christ Almighty, it's too much.
Every movie for the last four movies has been he has to do the mission, but he has to do it on his own terms,
and therefore his own agency is out to get him, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
This is the fourth movie in a row where Simon Pegg is in multiple situations where he is screaming under duress
and has to figure something out and can barely keep it together.
It's old.
I don't give a shit anymore.
This is the fourth movie in a row, as you said, where they just have Ving Rhames sit and talk about things that are boring
and we don't care.
Yeah, his team is just and I love Simon Pegg.
His team just doesn't pop enough.
You know, like there's a there's a routineness to these movies setting in that.
I'm not loving anymore.
I got to be real with you.
This is the fourth movie in a row where they have to go to a big ball in the middle of it to deal with something.
This is the fourth movie in a row where they hammer yet again another woman that Ethan feels strongly about who's in danger.
And by the way, they're at the point like to they're all calling this.
They're calling this out in the movie.
They're they're calling all of these tropes out, which is another lazy thing because they're just going, you know, we're going to do it.
So blah, blah, blah.
Yeah.
The biggest gripe, though, I have with the movie and I saw the movie with Pete Holmes and Matt McCarthy, our friends, because they were in New York.
Yes, we saw the biggest gripe and we were all in disbelief.
This entire movie hinges on if some there's a device, it's a key.
If the wrong person gets the key, they are able to operate the AI thing, which, by the way, the AI thing is not just some vague program on a server somewhere.
It's a living, breathing structure that can that people can inhabit like literally like the computer in Superman three.
It's fucking ridiculous.
So especially in a day and age where we we already live in this world.
Like, why are you making up something dumb?
So anyway, yes, I agree.
So the whole movie hinges on if somebody gets this key, they control the most dangerous thing that's ever existed.
And throughout the movie, whoever has the key puts the key.
I'm not exaggerating in their front pocket.
To the point where Tom Cruise and the Mission Impossible Force has to employ the help of a pick pocket played by Holly at well.
It's ridiculous.
So much of this movie hinges on dumb luck.
And that's not what these movies ever were.
These movies were always they are put in an impossible situation, hence the title, and they're so good they pull it off.
This movie has moment after moment after moment where it's like, well, luckily, he flew through the window right at the moment the guy was going to shoot her and he knocks the guy out of the way by accident.
It's like these are like Star Wars gags.
That's not what this is.
This is the first Mission Impossible to do like gags.
Like at the end, you know, Tom Cruise comes flying into this train with his parachute at the exact moment he needs to to stop the bad guy.
And it's exactly what Joe's saying.
You're just like, OK, but this is not Mission Impossible.
This isn't a team deciphering the most clever and amazing way that they can possibly get out of danger.
This is Tom Cruise accidentally happening to crash through a window at the right time, which is not really what we come to these movies for.
I don't think.
And also in the modern age, in this modern age of give them everything like and then that'll get them to the theater.
The big stunt that Tom Cruise does, which is an exciting stunt, but the big stunt he does.
They literally have shown it to us already on the Internet a million times behind the scene and how we did it.
Yeah, everything.
These stunts used to open the movie or be in the middle of the movie.
Now it's the big climactic scene.
You're not excited about it because you've you've seen it already.
And it's shot, by the way.
It's shot, by the way, like a reality TV show like like they use like a drone camera that starts on a close up of him and then pulls out to reveal like there he goes on the motorcycle.
It's really him.
And there's no mystery to any of it.
It's not exciting.
And then they ruin it because it's that he needs to land on a train and they go so far out of their way to establish how impossible it's going to be for him to land on this train by jumping off a cliff on a fucking motorcycle and parachuting down to the train.
And then the way he lands on the train is he flies through the window of the train in this just accidentally happens to fly through the exact window in the exact car where a guy's about to shoot Haley and he knocks the guy out of the way.
And it's done for a gag.
It's done for a laugh.
And if you saw it, I'm actually, you know, big crowded audience.
It got that laugh, but it was it was not one of those laughs that just keeps going.
You know, it was like a quick, unsatisfying chuckle.
You could tell that nobody liked it.
It just, it was a bummer in a lot of ways.
And then they got Cruz like they I had heard that they had to remove a de aging sequence with Tom Cruise that was done because between that and the train stuff, it was too similar to Indiana Jones.
It's like apparently there was some overlap.
Well, what you feel it's like the amount of time they're punching each other on top of a train.
It's like, why is this the hot location for a fist fight this summer?
I've seen it.
Also to that entire ending climactic sequence where they're climbing up through the train.
I was like, this is Uncharted 2.
This is the beginning of the video game.
And then I was like, maybe I'm being too much of a dick.
And the the guy that directed the video game of Uncharted 2 came out and was like, you stole my idea.
This I did already in Uncharted 2.
And you just took and they did.
There's there's a lot of stuff in this where you're like, I've seen it.
I don't care anymore.
The motives of the characters are not justified.
There's no understanding as to why this woman at the end betrays the main bad guy and then pledges her allegiance suddenly to Tom Cruise.
There's no.
It just sucks.
It's just not a good movie.
It's bloated.
It's too fucking long.
I'm I'm I'm over the goddamn face shit, guys.
I mean, the mask thing is supposed to be, hey, we're in a pinch.
We'll do the masks there.
They do this through four movies now.
It's like it's their go to fix for everything.
And then more than four.
I mean, they've been doing that since the jump.
But yeah, there's the big handoff in this one where the head of the Mission Impossible Force is meeting with the woman to get to obtain this key.
And it's Haley Atwell in a mask.
And you're like, Tom Cruise did the mask gag to you at the beginning of the movie.
This is the most important meeting you will ever have ever in your life and for the history of humanity.
And you pat her down, but you don't do a mask check.
They'd always forget that mask.
Yeah.
It's just a lazily written movie.
It's not good.
My hog is way down.
I'm sorry on Mission Impossible.
Dead reckoning.
I don't care about part two.
I'm not excited about part two hogs way down.
I got to say my hog is up.
This is the least I know.
I've talked a lot of shit.
It's my least favorite of the franchise.
But a less good Mission Impossible is still a good action movie in my opinion.
I still had fun.
There is a long sequence where they get a mini car.
That part, which is also Indiana Jones.
Yeah, it's weird.
I got on my honeymoon.
I got one of those smart cars and try to drive it like uphill.
And so I kind of related to it.
But also I found that stuff very funny, very well choreographed, very well shot.
There are highlights and stuff.
But like what Joe's saying, when they get to the edge of that cliff, you're like, I've now seen this scene 500 times.
It's like the Nicole Kidman AMC deal.
You're like, I got it, guys.
And when you're building to that as the climax, that don't make no sense.
Like show us a taste of something in the trailer.
But we've seen this from every angle at this point.
So that kind of sucked.
It felt a little anticlimactic because far and away the most exciting action sequence we've already seen literally more times than we could ever count.
But I liked Mission Impossible.
I liked the new one.
I just think that the franchise is starting to show its age a little bit.
Joe, wrap us up, if you would.
Yeah, I'm going to double down on my hog down because I forgot to mention the scene where Tom Cruise does a fucking magic trick with a key.
And I'll just let you see that for yourself.
Clearly, because he just wanted to do it.
Hogs down, folks, I'll close this out here with a plug for my big tour coming up.
I'm all over the place.
Jersey, Toronto, Denver, Salt Lake City and much, much more.
Please go to joderosa .com for tickets and show dates and venue information.
And please go grab that salsa windfall album.
August.
Well, it came out on August 4th or comes out.
I don't know when this is going to post.
But the point is, is releases August 4th.
You can purchase it if you like.
But, you know, in fact, I knew I do know when this is going to come out.
It's available.
Presale.
Currently on Bandcamp for 899 discounted.
Well, if you want to get that album before Friday, Friday is when the album drops digitally and you can stream.
It's up to you.
I leave it up to you.
But, you know, maybe you buy it anyway.
Folks, I appreciate all of you.
We appreciate all of you.
Hope to see out there on tour.
And we have a huge announcement coming very soon about the pod.
We'll keep you posted.
We'll see you next time.
We'll see you in hell.