I'm seeing the way you go, I'm seeing the way you go
When the sound of your screams becomes a thing on the dream
You know I say baby, baby, I'm seeing the way you go
I'm seeing the way you go, I'm seeing the way you go
Hey! Welcome to the hug!
You know I said we don't need a practice run on sitting down but I found that really difficult
A series of traps to get to the chair
I have yours notes, you have mine
I got mine now baby
So can I do this?
I just need to be closer to the table but I don't want to
Is that all right?
Am I overthinking it?
Hello everyone!
Welcome! Thank you! Chicago!
How are we?
What's going on? Who's actually from Chicago?
Welcome! Welcome!
How many psychopaths?
Blue in for this!
We thank you very much for that, that's awesome!
Yes, thank you so much!
Thank you, I hope the hat's going around to pay for our flights as well
I've been here since Friday, I had a real Chicago time
I saw it all, I've been here once before when I was like 16, me and my friend Ryan Murphy
saw the breeders at the metro
And it was awesome, and I had a demo of my band at the time, the PTA
You're familiar with them
And afterwards I was like Kim, Kim Deal
Here's my CD
And she was like put her hand over her heart and she was like, you're giving this to me?
Which was like an insanely nice response
You know? Sweet woman
Former pixie
And thank you! And then what happened?
Did you ever hear from her?
Well obviously she signed us to a six record deal, you know
And then you went by Frank Black from there on air
Yes, yes, exactly
No, I didn't hear from her believe it or not
I was only in Chicago one other time
But I made a real Chicago go of it, what I did was I enrolled in a local high school
And then I played Hookie with a man I'd befriend it named Cameron
Sure
And we went to a ball game
Principal chased us all day
It was a wild time that day
Now he was also chasing some children that he planned to fuck, correct?
Yes
How you doing, folks?
He was in the Deadwood movie
Did anybody see that? I was like
Why is he in this?
Everyone knows he's a child molester
He's in it because you're allowed to fuck kids back then
Oh and the old West, that's right
That's right, it was a different time
Yeah, lawless
That was a your daddy's West
Yes, that's correct
I tell you, if you meet that guy, you hope he has Deadwood
Folks
All right
I needed a big win there, I felt like I was losing
I got it back
Yeah, me and Joe Aydette, what was it?
Cafe Italian
It was around the corner
It was a great restaurant
It was called Lucky Club
Lucky Club, anybody been there
Is it Club Lucky or Lucky?
It was awesome
That was great
Four men get murdered in the restaurant
That was like, that was such an awesome like, straight out of 1970
Chicago joints
That was such a good place
Yeah, we had a real fitness meal before the show, some sausage
We learned from Bert Young's performance
Which we talked about on the show
Where he had a four pound chimichanga before entertaining us
The last big, that's right, that's good
Is everybody else seen the last big?
Has it made it to Chicago yet?
I'm sure it's true
You know where I was surprised
We were watching the Tony Awards next door
I was surprised to not see it mentioned there
But the Tony, they had the bar next door
There's no one in there
And they have the TV blaring the Tony Awards
And we were sitting there
Hosted by James Corden, did I forget to mention?
Does any, raise your hand
And there's no repercussions to it
If you like James Corden
Then how is he this successful?
I don't know
No one likes him
And the people you think like, oh my mom probably likes him
And she's like, oh
So who is it?
Who is it?
What does he know?
Yes
Really
And Marine was in a lot of musicals
They didn't give him a god damn late night show
The show, wait, what about Hamilton?
He got the guy from Hamilton
Oh, to get in the car and sing on the show
Oh, I see
Okay, he seems like a tough guy to get
Lin Manuel Moran
Every time I turn on the TV, he's tap dancing into my heart
Not interesting
No, it's terrible
It's a terrible show
The Tony's open with a joke song by James Corden on a couch
How you want any show to open
And we're admitted into this thing
The massive audience hasn't laughed
Yeah, everyone's just like
Is this going somewhere James or
And they're there to see James
And speaking of Chicago
I turned to Washington
I go, could you imagine David Mammoth watching this right now
I'm just being like, god damn it
He's doing his play
He's doing his new play in Afghanistan right now
Would you say the flip side?
The flip side, he was like, no that's theater
That's fucking theater
Is there anything worse than a musical or a play
And I used to love them when I was in New York
I would go all the time
And everything they did to see the musical
And we're watching a clip from it
I mean it was embarrassing
And every time I've been to a musical or a play
You're like, thank Christ
This is over
And you remember there's a 20 minute intermish
And then another hour and a half
Is there anything worse than a play or a musical?
Is that what you just said?
What are you talking about?
I mean please you're wonderful
I love them for a long time and I can't do it anymore
It's something about the feet on the stage
And it's just fake
I saw kinky boots and Los Angeles
I saw kinky boots
I tell you these kinky boots were out the door before the intermission
I tried
You just said it too fast
Give it a little penance
I didn't say it too fast
What do you think the worst
Because they turn these awful movies into awful musicals a lot of the time
Not the tootsies great
But what do you think the worst music
What's the worst movie you could ever turn into a musical?
What's the what do you
Lie a liar?
Spider -Man
I saw that actually in New York
But that hasn't been done
No
By the way
This is the fucking problem
With entertainment
And Hollywood and all this big level shit
Remember that play?
Spider -Man was called turn off the dark
And everybody was like what the fuck does that mean?
I saw
An interview
With the lady that directed it or wrote it or something
And she goes that yeah
The title comes from
I had a friend and she said
When her little boy would want to go to bed
He would want a light kept on
And he would say mommy
Turn off the dark
And I just thought that was so great
That how's that as a kick in the balls
Every fucking struggling right or out there
Oh a fucking moron three year old
Said something stupid
And it becomes the title of a Broadway show
That's how this business works
You fucking scum bags
Well also why didn't she then write a show about her stupid kid
Instead of going oh that's a good title for spider -man
I got a new play it's called any kid
Turn off the dark
No I saw that play it started
And it was like you know like a big like guitar solo
And then he's like I'm spinning away
But I was like all right
I don't think I made it past the intermission on that one either
It was embarrassing
You know what I like little shop of horse
Yeah
And it's like 90 minutes
That's a good one
Did you go see legally blonde the musical?
I didn't
The worst movie I guess would have to be
I mean the exorcist
I'd see that
Jam that crossing
You're pushing hell
Holy cow
I'd go see that
Your mother fucks gox and hell
That kind of rhymed
So here's what I did
I wrote down the restaurants I went to and shot that
Hold on I still want to talk about the worst movie to turn it
I want to do this quick because my hand is shaking
Your hand is shaking
I watched that too
Yes that's true
I'm gonna go with summer rental
I think that'd make a bad musical
I mean Schindler's list
Fair enough Sophie's choice
He's making a list
Check it in twice
Alright
There we go
I had another verse but I'm done
That's the bit
That's the full bit
Since we have Chicago locals
Let's see if you know these places that I have eaten at
Since I've been here
First off Joe said don't do the deep dish
You'll be on the toilet all week
I did it
I went to Pizano's
I've been on the toilet all week
Pizano's was fun
But then I order a pizza and the guy's like you know it'll be 45 minutes
I'm sitting at the bar
But you're a pizza place
You don't have the system down any?
You don't imagine that somebody might order a pizza
And get it ready
Well it's a different thing man
Pippins
Awful bar
And I'm like oh perfect it's a dive
Great I go up and I don't know how much the drinks are here
I hope I'm not telling tales out of school
I go hey I'd like a t -dos and soda please
Alright $12
The place the floor was half piss
But this is why
I'm like you're a dive what
This is what drives me
Did I drink it? Yeah and I had another one but
This is what drives me not about you
He fucking idiot text me
He text me on Thursday
Kind of a hostile start to a story
But alright
And if we're going to talk about texting I got one for you at a minute
Alright alright go
I'm out here because I was doing stand -up shows
So I was touring around the area
He gets here on Thursday he texts me
I just got to Chicago
Why? Because he's a psycho
That goes on vacations by himself
He'll just go to a fucking city alone
Which is psychotic
I like to explore the city
So he texts me on Thursday
Hey where do I go in Chicago
I go I go lessen if you need a bar
Go to North Bar where we're doing the shows
Jim will hook you up with free drinks
We're doing shows there
Hour later
What the fuck I'm at Pippins
It's $12 a goddamn drink
I go why don't you just fucking go where I told you to go
Because Pippins was one foot
For my hotel
And this place is 40 minutes
I mean you gotta understand that
Fair enough
Also so Joe
As we're leaving
I go hey uh
Can we do five o 'clock instead of 430 for dinner
Three hours prior to the show
And Joe with his typical condescension
He goes yeah
But let's do five sharp though
I go you know what
Because of that I'm gonna be there well before five
I was I had a few travel issues
But I was there at 450 and as I'm walking up to the restaurant
I get a text from Joe to Rosa
That says gonna be about 10 late
And folks he was 17 late
17 late
That's the kind of guy that goes um here
And then you go outside to find him
And he's 10 blocks away
Because you can't park in your neighborhood
In my defense
There's nowhere to park in his neighborhood
You do the LA thing
Yeah I'm here but that means 20 minutes
But I'm like waking up
No people do that but in your neighborhood
I'm always like I'm here
But then I always think by the time he comes to the door
I'll be at the door
And then I realize
When I have a sprowing estate
There's a flight of stairs
I thought maybe you can calm your fucking dog down
So it's not barking in my face
I'm over there three times a week
And every time the dog is like
Like come on you don't know my scent
I wear CK1
Strong enough for a man but made for a woman
I went to uh uh uh where did I go
Uh egg experience
Oh clearly a chain
My favorite restaurant in Chicago
And you know why
Because like when you wake up and you really hung over
I had friends here from Missouri and I hung out with them
And I woke up really hung over
And you go here's how they start
Before you order anything
Picture of water on the table
They pour you a glass and put the picture on the table
Glass of coffee and then a picture of coffee on the table
So I never even need to see this person again
A dream
The food wasn't amazing
But I liked what they were doing at egg experience
You know I got like the diet plate
Uh I had like four pounds of mozzarella cheese on it
But you know I had a good time
What else did I do?
Any other pun restaurants that you would do?
No I didn't eat that much
I went to uh uh Rigley Field last night
Have you guys heard of Rigley Field?
It was fun
I had a good time that neighborhood is really cool
Afterwards like it's fun to go out over there
I like it. You mean the chewing gum stadium
Correct? Yes
Uh okay that's
That's really good buddy
Is it rigley?
Are you saying guaranteed rape?
Sir
What are you saying?
I thought that's what he said
R -A -T -T
Why take a chance when you're a financial institution?
With a name like that
Hey lady come on into guaranteed rate
What did you just say to me?
No I said rate
You ever been to uh hub above a stadium?
Hub above a stadium is one of my favorites
It's not - it's not rigley
I was a little blue when I was there but you know
That's it
Uh uh no it was great I went in
I came - so the stalk - uh the uh scalper situation
I used to scalp tickets to make my rent
So I usually know what to do
But this guy was so bad at it
I guess it was his first minute on the job
But I come off the subway
He goes uh hey I got a ticket right behind home plate
I said yeah that'd be great
How much is it? 120
I go how about
He goes all right
I wish I'd said five
But uh yeah I was - I mean I went in and sat down
And I was - I knew my friends were at the game
And I was like I guess I'll find you guys after
But just so you know here's where I am
He goes look to your right
It's like four people down
It's not a funny story but it's cool
It's a big stadium
You should have done the pee -wee urban silence
Do the pee -wee - I love that story
Yeah
Uh I uh uh
I've been touring around Michigan for the last three days
I had a lot of fun last night
We were in uh miskegon
Woo
Yeah
There's the one guy that lives there
Interesting town
Okay so a couple stories
So I've been touring around with a very funny comic named Aaron
Puttin' him who helped us put this show together tonight
So give it up for Aaron
And give it up for -
Give it up for Emily Florence
Please
And give it up for Liz back there helping us out
So anyway um
Aaron's a very funny comic and he put this run of shows together
Uh and they've been a lot of fun
Uh but the two standout stories were the first one we were in -
Or the second night we were in um
Uh ham tramk
How do you say it?
Ham tramk
Detroit
It sounds like you're right
Yeah definitely sounds like the name of a city
Ham tramk, ham tramk I think it's called
Uh anyway we - we -
Aaron opens up the show
He gets on stage he goes
Yeah man he goes um from Lansing
Lansing's a shithole
And then he goes this place is a fucking shithole too
Zero laughter
Well sure
Then goes into his set I see you after his set
I go what's wrong he goes I didn't have a good set
They didn't like me for some reason I didn't get it
I go thinking anything maybe you tell them they lived in a shithole
30 seconds ending your fucking routine
He goes oh I did
I go yeah you did
Told them they lived in a shithole right off the bat
And then the second oh good
And then we were in miskegon
Michigan which was an interesting town
We walk in I'm playing a banquet hall
Connected to a bowling alley
I go
They gotta start somewhere Joe
Yeah
Oh you've been doing it for 15 years
Back when I'll connect to a bowling alley
I go how many tickets do we sell
I go about 30 don't worry about it we're gonna a lot of walk -ups
I go great I walk into the bowling alley
Two lanes are open
In the bowling alley
The thing is pitch fucking black for 11 lanes
Like who the fuck is walking up to this place right now
Not a lot of foot track and foot track
Maybe all the bowlers were on strike
Me
Folks
I got jokes to spare
I got jokes bumper to bumper
Anybody ever bumper bowl
Okay I thought they might be a stretch but all right
Stay in your lane is good
Yeah
But stay in your lane sir
So we're in this gigantic ballroom
It's about a 10th full
People are sitting at circular banquet tables
I'm like this is what the fuck
I'm sitting in the corner like this
I'm just sitting in the corner like this
Aaron comes up to me and goes what's wrong dude
I go what's wrong
What do you
So in order to feel better
I go and sit down in the couch
And decide to watch Henry Portrait of a serial killer
In my down time
To prepare for the late show tonight
If you're a stand -up comic
And you also have to do a podcast
Where you're reviewing Henry Portrait of a serial killer
Just a tip
Do not watch it right before you go on stage
It is not a pick me up film
Especially if you're playing to four bowlers
Then a circular banquet table
And you're already feeling a little love
But in Aaron's defense
And I can always admit what I'm wrong
Best show of the fucking tour
No bullshit
It was the best show that it was an amazing, amazing crowd
They were awesome
They're not here, you don't have to say them
No, it was great
I will be going back
When I was leaving going
When can we book another show here at the banquet hall
Holy yeah
I'm serious, it was that good
Can I ask you this?
Yeah, is it going to be another pun?
No, okay
I was going to ask if they make you pay for the shoe rental
Or if they comp it
I got nothing
Do you need it to be
Do you do the show in the bowling show?
You know what? They said they said sorry buddy
You got to pay for your own shoes even they were a performer
And I said you got a lot of balls in this place
That's good
You got any more? I'm on pins and needles
Folks
Between shows I'll show you my mom's form
My mom's the only woman in Missouri history
It's ever bowl a 300 game
And she's pretty
But I'll show you after the show
What her form is, it's criminally insane
Really?
I couldn't do it now because it took me five minutes to sit down
I don't want to have to do it again
I don't like people watching me
Which is why it's good that I've chosen to do a live podcast
But I did carry okay at
Brando's the other night
You want to talk about somebody walking the room
This was the most supportive room
Everybody that gets up
Of course people suck
Everybody's cheering them on
And dancing like they get up and dance
They do a rap song
It was so fun and everybody's cheering
And loving each other
And it was just a good group
And then this guy gets up
He was about 60 years old
He had been the entire night
He had been completely silent just pounding drinks
He walks up, takes the mic
And he starts singing
Louie, Louie, Louie, Louie
Oh wow
Did the Louie theme song
No, that's an actual song though
Is it? Yeah, that was a song that Louie
It certainly got a connotation
No it is
No, that's a real song
That's a real song
And Louie said if you let me eat your coffee in front of you
I could make you a theme song
Oh
I mean
You cannot sing that song
The entire place walked out
It was just like all right, we're done
It's not a good song
It's not his song
But the entire place didn't walk out
Granted the bar had just closed
And it was Louie singing it
You left that part out
Speaking of singing
Yeah
Let's get on with the show
25 minutes in
And at the same time on
With the
Jo the reason in my life
Jo's the inspiration
I want to have you near me
I want to have you near me say
Yeah
That's Chicago
Chicago
I hate Chicago
The band I hate
I love the town
This is one of the best cities in America
I'm not just saying honestly
I'm from St. Louis and there's this big rivalry
But then you come here and you're like
This is so much better than St. Louis
In every way
Are you guys celebrating Pride Month by the way?
Yes
Happy Pride Month
So I got the other day
He goes, hey, when straight pride month
I said he already got it
It's called football season
Folks
For some reason I have the word
Chicago just written in my notes
Good, circle that
We might use that later, Jo
Make Chicago references
Right, right, right
Before you take us over
Well, I wasn't going to really
But we got a thing we got to do here
In the spirit of the city
That we're going to do at the top of each pot
It's hard to say I'm sorry Chicago
Yeah
Jolder now
It's hard for me to say I'm sorry
It's not they're not a great band
I prefer solos atera
And also the balls of naming your band
The city you're in
Like try harder
There was a time where they were awesome
They were like a jazz fusion 25 or 6 to 4
Which Green Day ripped off for that song
The Dana
It's exact same core, exact same thing for that
What a brain stew or whatever
Green Day also ripped off sister golden here
They ripped off many
For shattered for their song shattered
Or scattered, excuse me, scattered
Shattered's a great song
Shattered's not a song, it's scattered
And shattered is a rolling stone song
If you want to split hair
It was also the theme to Louis
Did you know that?
Louis
But the first show I saw
Was Weirdel Yankovic at Six Flags
I got his autograph
I told you this right
On the podcast
Anyway, my mom goes go tell him a joke
He was in line with us on the Buccaneer ride
Which is pirate ride
And I'm like he doesn't care
And he was there with what appeared to be a prostitute
No judgment
But my mom's like go talk to him, go talk to him
So I go up and I said hi I was like 10
And I go my mom wanted me to tell you a joke
Obviously couldn't have been nice
Or we all know he's the nicest but he was like what's the joke
And I go well I just told it to my mom
How much does a pirate charge for an ear of corn or for corn
And he's like I don't know and I go a Buccaneer
And I mean he had the hardest most genuine laugh
Obviously it was fake
But I just I mean what a hero
What a great man
You know like almost anyone in that situation would be like
I don't want to talk to this fucking kid
He was very nice
But the second show I saw was the beach boys in Chicago
With Chicago headlining somehow
And
Well because you're talking about like shit Arab
You're talking about Stamos beach boys
He wasn't in the crew
You're talking about like Kukumongo fucking
Whatever the fuck it was called
Kukumongo
By the way why haven't I done that
I'll do it on the next show
Jokumongo
Jokujo
You're blowing all of them
You're done three now
Save one for the next show
But Chicago gets up
Everyone there is there for Chicago
So obviously they arranged it right St. Louis
Again I really love Chicago
From the first song
Every song had a
Seven to ten minute flute solo
Heavy flute
And like people in the Chicago shirts
Are just packing up their bags
And leaving
It was embarrassing
It's a rock band
Is this the satara or is this post satara
Oh my god
I mean that's you're at like saved by the bell
The college years at that point
So it comes up and he's like
Yeah
Screech trying to make his voice crack
I
Bell things like coked out of his mind
Mr. Belding by the way Dennis Haskins
I used to go to dimples
Which is this karaoke bar in Burbank
After I'd finish a taping
Of the critically acclaimed sitcom
Two broke girls
And by the way the man next to me last night
He goes that's my favorite show
And he goes you know why two reasons
Points to two his two boobs
Anyway
So I go you all go over to dimples
And Dennis Haskins Mr. Belding
Would be there his face glowing red
Like you could feel he coming off of them
With like coax a sweaty coke smear across his lips
And he'd be like hey and put his arms around two girls
And like grab a handful of these
Oh come on i'm not kidding
And the one of the waitresses was like
Dennis and like walked away
And I said how often does this happen
And she goes he's in here every night
He showed up to my birthday party one year
He did I had a birth I had a joint birthday party
With tone bell and our friend Vince Avril
It was the three of us at a birthday party
And tone bell at the time was on a sitcom
With Mark Paul Gossard
Is that Zach Gosselor
Whatever his name is Stone Gossard
Stone Gossard of Pearl Jam
Had a sitcom
No but Mark from you know Zach was on the sitcom
And tone was like Mark might show up to the party tonight
And I was like look that'd be a good time out
Yeah that was his big thing
You know who was there
Yeah I'll tell you who was there
Nicholas Shea was there
Oh 98 degrees from Stardom baby
Yeah yeah yeah
But I'm like can't have an eye open all night
Like is Zach more?
It's gonna show up to this fucking mark
And Zach never showed up
But who did Belding walked in
Walked in, scanned the room, walked right out
Yeah it was probably like no tail in here
Got the high hat from Belding
I was flashing a little, a little skin out of him
He wasn't into it
I think the reason that Mr. Belding hung out every night at this karaoke bar
Because it was directly across the street from NBC
And I think he thought somebody would come in and be like Dennis
We gotta get another show going baby
Can you, which is real dark
Stop kicking the man, isn't he down enough?
Jesus Christ
I don't think he's a listener
Played a fucking principal on a sitcom that aired at 9 .30am
I tell you they should have called the man Mr. Belding
I'll kick him again
All right, let's love our bald fan
In Toaster Chicago we agreed to, this is kind of a surprise
I didn't tell you about this
But I agreed
How many times do I tell you I don't do shots
It's okay but now I'll be forced at gunpoint with everyone watching
That's why we're doing this
We were told that there was a...
Yes, it's Mallorca
Yeah
We've never had it?
I don't know what it is
All right, everybody's like it's disgusting
I'm like well then we'll do it on the show
So what, how is it disgusting?
Just taste bad or it's super alcohol
There we go, ready?
Oh no buildup
How does it compare to like Yagermeister?
I've heard it is somebody described it to me as picture Yagermeister
Without any of the sweet
That's how I was just...
All right, I was like oh Christ
Picture an early grave
Why are my hands shaking so bad?
I don't know
Cheers guys, Mallorca to Chicago
That's not bad
No, it kicks back
Woo
That's got a tail on it as they say
No, it's deceptive because you're like oh okay I've done worse
And then you have them
It tastes like one of those drinks they put like flowers in which are all the rage now
Yeah, that felt like in the movie when a gangster goes like this
And it goes
Yeah, exactly
Exactly, I didn't like that
You probably could have mimed it by the way
Yeah, why don't you take us down
To a little place
Say it the way you say it
These people drove minutes to be here
No, some of these people flew, I mean we have people from LA here
Thank you so much everybody for coming
Yeah, thank you guys, we can't express that enough
Let me take you down, if I, if I may
To a little place
We'll get there fast and then we'll take it slow
Down to Cucamanco
Way down in Pat's movie corner
Joe start us off, what have you seen?
I'm gonna do different stuff on this show
Just a little preview for the late show
Some of you are staying for both
Some different people are just coming to the late show
In order to maybe tempt the people into staying that aren't staying
Or planning on staying
Late show, my whole movie corner is dedicated to the remaining episodes of the new season of the Twilight Zone
And I've got a lot to say
I've watched a couple more
I can't believe my eyes
True story, and I know Jordan Peel
He's a very nice guy, and I believe in him, and I'm a fan of his
And you used to be friends
Until he saw the fuck out
I was walking my dog the other day, and Hollywood and I saw him on the street
And he goes, hey man, and I go, hey
Love your stuff
And I was like, there's no way he's heard the podcast
There's no way, there's not
But that's on the late show, if that's tempting to anybody
But wouldn't that be a fucking nightmare?
You go in to pitch your movie to Jordan Peel
And he's interested, you get your whole pitch out
And then he puts his hands behind his head and he's like
So I, it wasn't your podcast
And that's the risk we take all the time
It's so stupid that we do this while trying to succeed at the entertainment industry
But that's how you know we're telling the truth
We don't sit here and say we love shit that's got all
I watched an interview with Orson Wells
And the reporter goes, it's called the Paris interview
Apparently, it's very famous interview
And they give me a wait
Oh, you're the end?
Yeah, you're talking
That's what he was at his best
He's talking Transformers movie
Have you guys seen the outtakes of him doing the wine commercial?
Of course, yeah
All -time classic
But the Paris reporter goes, you know, do you think artists should be critics
And Orson Wells goes, absolutely not
I think if you need to get your kick, you need to get them elsewhere
And I was like, he might have a point
I mean, it's so dumb
So dumb
Anyway, I am going to start with a classic film that I've never seen
And I watched it and got damn it, I loved it
It's a Vincent Price film called Cry of the Banshee
It is
Have you actually seen Cry of the Banshee?
All right, never seen it
Two of us
Vincent Price, it's okay, so we talked before in the podcast about the conqueror worm
Which is the one where he plays the magistrate, witch hunter, whatever
This one, Vincent Price also plays a magistrate, witch hunter
But it is like conqueror worm times a thousand
He is such a fucking cock sucker in this movie
He just kills people that he just maybe he saw a pointy hat in their house
He's just killing witches left and fucking right in this thing
No remorse, his family hates him, everybody hates him
And then the witches that live in the forest put a curse on his house
And a wolf man kills his entire family, including the good people in the family
That have criticized the father to not do this anymore
Which doesn't really make sense
But it's a really really really fun old school Vincent Price harvolic
And how do you kill a witch?
Has it just gone to the head or is there a trick?
Well, the thing is is they're not real witches
He's just killing women that are perceived as witches like they didn't sell them
And then it turns out there are real witches that put the curse of the Banshee on his house
And a Banshee never shows up, I don't know why it's called that
It's more of a wolf boy
But cry of the wolf boy, it doesn't have a good ring to it
But yeah, this wolf beast comes and kills his entire family mercilessly
And it's awesome, it's awesome, it's classic horror
It's priced at like 1968
And I always love any movie where they're passing off Vincent Price
There's like a ladies man
Hello
Yeah, yeah
Come here often
Yeah
No, that's one of my favorite things
But it's a classic, I can't, you know, I've kind of been on a little bit of a kick lately in my own life and on the podcast
So I'm going to meet these classic horror movies that didn't really get a lot of recognition
And I would say check this one out cry of the Banshee is really amazing, it's worth seeing it out
And you go watch it for free on Amazon Prime
So give it a look
All right, I will
Folks, I watched a picture called Wine Country on Netflix
You mean the Rachel drag vehicle?
I got to tell you, I didn't know they were spelling it W -H -I -N -E
Look, the movie was horrible
And I love everybody in it
They're all hilarious
And no one had anything funny to do or say, has anyone seen it?
Okay, I couldn't believe it, I just couldn't believe it
And it's, you know, it's Anna Gasdair and Rachel Dhratch and Amy Poler and Tina Fey
And they just, it just goes, Paula Pell is one of the funniest people in the world
Who?
She was a writer for us and now he's becoming an actress now
Okay, she was always the sweetest woman at a place where no one is nice
But she, it was like, I guess improv
But that stuff didn't also feel funny to me
And they just...
They followed me out because I saw the billboard for it in Hollywood
And I was really happy for Rachel Dhratch
I was like, oh, she's getting a shot again
Because I always felt like she got cast aside or something
That's a bummer that it's not funny, man
Because she's so much fucking funnier than a lot of the people that get a lot of shine
Out of that scenario, you know?
She absolutely is
Tina Fey, I think probably read the script and was like, maybe I'll do two scenes
Like she's barely in it and she's funny in it, I guess
Jason Schwartzman is in it and he plays this guy who comes with the house
So you get an Airbnb and he's the chef who comes with the house
Like just things that never even happen
Everything about it, I was like trying to figure out why they'd even think that we buy it
Well, of course, not laughing
But Schwartzman is not funny in it, I love Jason Schwartzman
It's also a cast of, in 2019, 14 white people
Like every lead in this movie is a white person
But they're all women though, right?
Isn't that the...
Does that my Rudolph?
Okay, yes
No, no, I know
Listen, who yelled but they're still white, I agree with you
No, no, no, no, no, it's okay
It's okay
I was just blown away by it, it was so out of touch
I'm saying like that, but that's like kind of like people
That they never mind, I'm gonna get myself in trouble
I'm gonna shut the fuck up
It's just, it's the kind of movie where like they're all just like hanging out doing nothing
And then because it's been on for an hour and a half
They have a fight that feels like every comedy does this now
Where it's like they have a fight that you don't believe because these people are the best of friends
Then it's like you never listen to me
They all have one issue with each other person
That they resolve in 30 seconds
And then they all roll down a hill together and it's over
I just, I don't know
It's just, it's like such a great opportunity to have all these hilarious women together in a movie
I just, I couldn't believe it, personally, I'm sorry
Okay
Alright, yeah
Sorry
Yeah, no
Well, I mean, look
You know how relatable a movie called Wine Country is about a bunch of people that can afford a personal chef in it
Sure
And also don't want the personal chef
They're like he's gonna be here all weekend
I want to talk, I'm gonna do something out of the ordinary here for my second movie
I'm gonna talk about a movie that I haven't seen but I've only seen the trailer for
Okay
And because it's not out yet
And I can't even wrap my fucking head around
Ladies hear me out
The kitchen
Has anybody seen the trailer for this?
No
The kitchen
A movie that takes place in 1970s Hell's Kitchen where the Westies were
The most ruthless, awful, decapitating gangsters that ever fucking lived
The Westies, 1970s
And this movie is about how
Melissa McCarthy
Tiffany Haddish
And the lady from a bridesmaid's tale, Elizabeth Moss
A bridesmaid's tale
Handsmaid's tale
Sorry, that shots hit me
That shots hit me in the head
It's creeping in for me too
Actually
This is not a comedy this movie
How the three of them bring the Irish mob to their knees
Come the fuck on
Well, isn't it a true story?
No
All right
It's fucking outrageous
And then you've got these guys that literally cut tongues out of people's mouths
Going dissladiate no smarter than me
And then it shows like Melissa McCarthy
Like we're gonna show these boys what's really going on around here
What the fuck is happening?
Can you make it remotely believable?
Is the implication Joe that three women can't fight back?
No, it's that three anybody's can't take down the fucking Westies
In the 1970s
It's not like they're feuding gangsters
They're literally like, you know what?
I'm tired of cooking eggs for my husband
I'm gonna take on these gangsters now
And you're supposed to be like, oh, okay
It's fucking absurd
I'm sorry, it's absurd
Is it a comedy?
No
No, they're doing like a resurgence
I mean, it's like you have a five -year window
Who's funny with the most McCarthy in Tiffany Adish
They're hilarious
And this is what they're doing
Because they want that Oscar
And they completely abandoned the skills that got them there
And then nobody is funny
Nobody's ever funny anymore
No, well yeah
And then also, let me talk about Elizabeth Moss for a fucking second
And she's dating Tom Cruise, by the way
If I, you know, Handmaid's Tale in Dona Press Us
She's a Scientologist
Yeah, exactly
Who's dating Tom Cruise
If I see one more fucking bus station or bus stop poster in LA
With a picture of Elizabeth Moss
It says, set yourself free
As she fucking lives in the top room of the tower
At the fucking Scientology center
Honey, you're in the sea orgas
She sucks
And I've said it from day one
She looks like she smells
And I'm right
She looks like she looks like the girl that smells at your grade school
Whoo
Get a drill
Alright
Thank you
It was good, alright, great
Well, after my cry of the banshee thing went over
Like I was fingering a dog up here
Sorry for recommending a movie
I thought horror movie fans might enjoy
But, I mean, part of the show when we talk about movies
isn't always gonna be funny
No, I have audience you do feel the panic set in
I clearly didn't
Yeah, I just kept talking
Yeah, yeah
I mean, when we're on our couch watching your dog tongue itself
The stakes are a little lower
But I enjoyed hearing about the film
I don't know, I'm just kidding
Oh no, you did that trail, okay
I thought to myself, what is...
I watched six fucking episodes of Southern Charm the other day
I haven't watched a reality show in like decades
I'm like, it's a waste of my time
And finally, I stumbled into Southern Charm and I am booked
It's on Bravo, whatever, it's just about awful people boning each other
But I'm watching the sixth episode of it in a row
And I said, Pat, what is like a classic movie you've never seen
And I realized I had never watched Barry Lyndon, which I own
Stanley Kubrick's Barry Lyndon
And I always wrote it off as being boring
The only thing anyone ever says about it is like
They shot it with candles as the lighting
I'm like, yeah, okay, but it's three hours and 40 minutes
That's whatever
The movie is awesome as is all Stanley Kubrick movies
It's hilarious, Ryan O 'Neill is an awful boring terrible actor
Who never, I don't know how he became a star, but it works
Because he's playing in idiots who just keeps stumbling up
He keeps stumbling into success after success after success
And as somebody who works in the entertainment industry
I related to it very much
That's all you see is these idiots who are just like rising through the ranks
Did you know they originally offered that role to Ed O 'Neill?
I didn't know that
I saw the married with children fountain while I was here also by the way
I saw the fountain see, oh yeah, that's great, it takes place in Chicago
Oh shit
I sent you a picture of a fountain and you didn't even ask why?
I didn't even, I was like
I sent you a picture of the fountain and he's like, when are you getting to Chicago?
I'm like, I'm here and that's the married with children
I swear to God, I was like, this guy's coming unglued from going on a vacation by himself
He sent to me pictures that like my Nana would send me
It gives me a nice fountain, I didn't know what the fuck it was
I got, I spent 10 minutes getting the exact angle from the opening credits of married with children
To delight my friend Joe who literally said not one word about the picture
The picture was ignored completely
I'm sorry, I didn't know what it was, I didn't know what it was
I'm over it, clearly
But I mean, Barry Lyndon, if you're put off by the length or whatever
It is as beautiful as everyone says it is
And it's funny and just super entertaining, like somehow not much occurs in it
But for three hours you're just riveted by it, I thought it was a great move
Great
You know what, I was going to do for the third one for me, I was going to do the documentary, the 90s
It was great, it was a great documentary, it's a lot of fun
They talk about Nirvana
They did, yeah
Every 90s documentary you're watching it and then it's like, but then everything changed
Yeah, gown get down, it's like, yeah, you've done this a billion times
And they take the same exact copy and put it into the Seinfeld portion too
But then everything changed, gown, gown, gown, gown, gown, gown, gown, gown, gown, gown, gown
Look, for my final one, I'm going to do, because we're in Chicago
I'm going to do my favorite, one of my favorite married with children episodes
Okay
It's, we already did the Kinnison one, but it is awesome
Look, if you haven't seen the married with children Sam Kinnison episode, it's called it's a Bundiful Life
Sam Kinnison is out, out, out, out, Bundi wishes he was dead
He gets electrocuted, Sam Kinnison is his guardian angel
And then all he does is show him how much better the world is without him
Like with him being dead, the world is a better place
Which is a great premise
And then Sam convinces out a live at the end
And Al goes, I want to live and then Sam Kinnison gets his wings, right?
That's the plot
And the last shot is Sam Kinnison spinning in a circle thrilled that he's got his wings
Because now he can go haunt his ex -wife
And this is a network sitcoms that ends with Sam Kinnison spinning in a circle
Screaming up at the sky, I'm coming honey, you pig, you whore
That's how the episode ends
It was a different time
Anyway, my favorite episode of married children is an episode, I can't remember what it's called, but Al and Jefferson have to put together a workbench
And talk about the beauty of simplicity
The entire episode is them trying to assemble the workbench on the couch
And Peggy and Marcy watching them and making fun of how they're not going to be able to do it
And dude, they go for every fucking loony tunes gang in this thing
At one point he's holding the power strip
It's got too many plugs in it
Peggy's like, you got too many plugs in that Al, he's like, I know what I'm doing
Plugs in a 10th plug
Blue electricity all over him
Do we see his skeleton?
You don't see his skeleton
It's just blue electricity with the Frankenstein
Yeah, yeah, yeah, noises
My favorite joke in the whole episode is for some reason they think they need a blowtorch to put together this workbench
And Jefferson is looking into the nozzle of the blowtorch
And he goes, this blowtorch doesn't look clogged to me
You're like, what a great setup for a joke
And then it cuts away and you just hear...
Uh -huh
At one point Al says, I need to go think about how to work on this
Bad to the bone kicks in, he puts a newspaper under his arm, walks to the bathroom
It's every gag you could ever want in a married with children episode
I love it, I love it
I know for a fact that now Fox would say, where are the stakes?
Where are the stakes?
And I go, well, it's super funny for a half hour
Oh, we're not interested in that
Where are the stakes?
Now, did you work?
I did, it was a different type of game
All right, good
Yes, I saw her
I'm sorry
I love the way you see her
I saw her movie called, at the heart of gold
Which is a documentary on HBO
A network that has committed itself 100 %
To producing movies and documentaries about child molestation
That's all they do
I watched the Michael Jackson thing
I didn't know what at the heart of gold was
I'm like, oh, cool, a documentary
It's all about the gymnastics guy
And I, I mean, as I'll say, when we talk about Henry on the next show
Like, God, I wish I hadn't watched this movie
I have been in such a funk since I saw this thing
What it really boils down to is this clip
And somehow, I mean, I knew a little bit about the news story
But it is, I mean, if you want to watch it
If you wanted to watch the Michael Jackson thing, watch it
They're well made and it's an important story
But Jesus Christ, it was rough
At the end, they read a letter from him
Before he's going to get sentenced
So maybe this was a big news story, but I missed it
But the judge reads this letter from him
He reads highlights from it
And this guy who has now been confirmed guilty of molesting hundreds of young women that were in his care
He says, hellhath no fury
I guess hellhath no fury like a woman's scorned
And the judge reads it, it's the exact same reaction in the courtroom
Which is full of the victims
Jesus Christ
And she reads it and the judge is awesome
You can watch the clip, but she's like, the reason I wanted to read that section
Is because I wanted you to know that I asked you, did you have a letter
So I could take it into consideration for your sentencing
I have read it and taken into consideration
And now I will give you a much more severe sentence
Oh, good
Put a jail for like 600 years
That's great
And then the other highlight of it, which I had somehow missed, is this dad
Who's probably like 6, 6, 350 pounds
And he goes, I have just one question for the judge
And she goes, yes
And he goes, could I have but five minutes in a room with this son of a bitch
And the judge goes, no, and he goes, could I have one minute
And she goes, no, and he goes, I asked and jumps the man
They tackle him and pull him off
But then, I mean, it was, I was cheering
I mean, it's, but they pull him off
And he says to the four cops who pull him off
What if it was your daughter? What if it was your daughter?
And all four cops are like, I completely agree
Like they, they hated having to keep him from this guy
But, I mean, I don't know why we are fascinated by these stories of evil
I guess, but, I mean, I watched it, I watched the whole thing
But, God, it was rough
And it's available on HBO
So any of the folks, cry of the banshee is a Vincent Price movie
You may want to check that out
Yes
Let's get on to some 24 -hour news cycle
What do you say here?
Let's do it
Somebody remind me on the next show to tell my Nordstrom story
I got a Nordstrom story
Let's go
Our movie tonight is Candyman
Yes
Now what, are we doing a scary stuff?
We're doing a, I got a scary stuff to do
I thought we'd do news cycle first
Well, we can do scary stuff
But you're announcing the movie, which is traditionally the last part of the show
Sometimes we announce it at the beginning
We just forgot tonight
We are doing Candyman
We're doing two Chicago horror movies tonight
Can you hand me this bag under your chair here?
I have to get out of here
Sorry?
No, no, no, don't
Oh boy
I can get it
Oh my god
Thank you
Nobody's happy about how that went down, but...
Jesus
Thank you
I'm worried if I get up, I'll get in the cord, you know
Where do you have to get one of those plastic claws that the old people use to reach things
Look, obviously, it would have come in handy
What are we opening?
I'm giving away something to an audience member tonight okay for scary stuff
I actually went to the store today and bought two things one for each show to give away. I don't know how to determine what
How we'll give it away
There's only one
But well actually I know well the last show wasn't an issue because nobody wanted the gifts we brought
Yeah, honestly, this is a good one
Who I was like who wants this and then five minutes of crickets who has a PlayStation 4 stand up
Good okay great. I'm doing this because I know how much you love it when I talk about video games my favorite part
I haven't my hand uncharted the Nathan Drake collection. This is a wonderful this guy sat down doesn't want it
They this these games are awesome
Yes, these this is an awesome collection of the first three uncharted games remastered HD for the ps4
If you don't know anything about uncharted, it's basically they were like we want to make an Indiana Jones game
And they're like you're not allowed and they're like okay, well his name is Nathan Drake in this one that
That's basically what it is
They're everyone plays like a movie they're they're just fucking brilliant brilliant games
So I have the trilogy here for one lucky. I mean this guy is in the lead so far
He's advancing on us. I would give him the game
Does anybody standing not want this?
Well fuck you then
All right, so there's three people standing
There's three people standing haven't I asked one trivia question about the pod. I got one ready if you want yeah
Paddle ask a trivia question. Never gets it right gets the game. How about that all right in the the story I've told in the on the show many times
Pat Walsh is fagging
What what play was I cast as fagging in?
No, you can't yell it if if he sat down he's displeased. Yeah, you can't yell it
No, no, no hold on hold on you can't by the way if I was a son of a bitch like Trebek
I would say it's actually called Oliver, but yes, Oliver twist you can't yell the only the people standing can say the answer
Okay, ready. Yeah, I have another one what color
Was the fleece
sweater
Pullover that Pat war before he gave it to his dad as a gift
Shut up. Don't yell it if you're not standing. Oh, you are standing. Oh, where where oh, I'm sorry. Would you say?
Yeah, he got it
You brought out I'm sorry. I didn't know you were standing. I thought it was that guy again
There were hints of oatmeal in it by the way if we're being real. Did you want the game?
By the way, I called my that's what you like to hear after a gift is given
There's a giveaway on the next one for an Xbox game. The man gets an uncharted game. He'll take it
He says me too. I brought a game called who farted
Where you have to remain as a memory game and you see who I called my dad right before the show and
Wish him a happy father's day and for the second year in a row. It was not father's day
And he goes I don't think by the end of the call. I had convinced him it was father's day
But it was not. Is that terrible?
I mean, I don't know. Why are we hearing about father's day for a month before father's day? Does anyone give a shit?
I guess people who like their dad, but who are you sign -failed? I mean once a day
My dad also asked he said he gave you a joke at the wedding to use in your act
I was wondering if you were using it in his act. I was like what's the joke?
I believe the joke was who's got two thumbs and loves blow jobs
Now that wasn't a joke. I don't really hope not. What was the joke?
I don't remember what the joke was the the joke was he goes well, you know, you go into Walmart and
Like you could be in there at two in the morning and
You're standing there looking at what you want to buy and there's always
Some fucker my dad has never really used the f word in my presence, but working blue
I guess to appease to Joe I bring it out of people he goes, but some fucker always wants to look at the same exact thing
you're looking at and
I go okay, and he's like well, that's it and
I said I can pretty much guarantee Joe is using that joke in his act
Which is why he's playing the bowling app?
I
Think I remember you're a funny man. All right. I think I remember
Yeah, the the the only thing worse is the learning disabled kid pad on the back. I don't fucking need that
The now I actually think I remember your dad pitching me that joke. Yeah, and saying that's a great bit
Like because I did because what was I gonna say like you needs a punchline, you know go go work on it
Why don't you and five of the grooms been get together and go workshop that come back to me was you know
There was only he goes I was telling it to a buddy of mine at a restaurant the other night
So he's still like telling this joke to people and he goes these two Hispanic gals behind me turn around and told me they agree that always happens at Walmart
I'm like, let's unpack a lot of stuff in this. Why do I need their race?
What I guess he was trying to say he reaches, you know everyone with the with the humor
Yeah, it's very bizarre. It's a broad -reaching humor. Yeah, anyway
Okay for the new psycho. Let's do some candy man related stories. Oh, yeah, Tony Todd
back
Oh, he's back for can he's well, he's in it. He thought he had they haven't said yet what the he's probably playing the old guy
He was like you better watch out for the candy man, and then they're like all right get him out of here. Nobody cares about Tony
They said he's he's back in the movie. I
Think he's gonna be playing candy man. I mean that would be great. That's kind of what it sounds like he's 78
He still looks like he's 34
Yes, you know, it's like he he looks great. I hope he gets I hope he that's what he's doing
But he is back and that's huge news because everybody said, you know, what you know
Is it gonna be Tony Todd or is it I had a feeling when it was Jordan peel behind it
It was probably gonna be Tony Todd that he was gonna bring back
My my issue because I sent you all this article about the movie is that it is supposed to be about toxic fandom
What does that what does that have to do with candy man? Well, I
Might have some insight into this. I was watching a Tony Todd interview today and he said
He said all he knew about the movie and he said all I know is is the movie centers around an artist who's very obsessive
So I think it's gonna be that this young artist is very obsessed with the history of candy man who was also an artist
Okay, then somehow summons candy man because of that right. I would guess, right? That sounds all right. I'll watch that
I'll watch it
I mean look I know the first one was about the legend of candy man. I'll give it that I mean I don't want to see a fourth movie
Where it's him chasing a bond around for two hours again. I mean they've done that three times
It's got to be a little bit different here
It's got to be a little bit and the movie has been criticized
by some
Black film initiatives is saying like you know to have a movie that centers around
A black male lead. Why does he have to be obsessed with a white woman, you know
So I think that they're trying and the shutter doc. They also felt like why is why would he be killing poor people that lived in his community like
Doesn't make any sense right so I think it sounds like they're trying to maybe get away from some of that stuff that has been in the other
What's but not that the other ones are bad and I'm not criticizing them
Do you want to talk about the movie?
Should we we're gonna get to candy man? I think so I think we're
Hey, why is the movie completely unavailable?
Like you can't so I ordered the the blue ray of it. I got they have a great screen factory of it
But it's nowhere online is it so that they can remove it from online so they can
Release it to coincide with it or what you think they'd want people to get into it because everyone's talking about it
It makes no sense to me personally unless the studio thinks they'll buy the DVD that might mix well it might just be a rights issue
Yes
Yeah, so there you go that answers that question we figured it out
It might just be the most obvious reason
Well, it's like everyone who comes into my house is like uh -uh like why you got all these DVDs
Like you're gonna give those away right give all these blu -ray as well. You don't need that anymore, right?
And it's like no a it looks beautiful and
Be I have like a collection of things that can loan to people like like a human and see they're like
Well, you can just get everything online except one of the biggest horror movies in the last 30 years like it's insane to me
You can't find tons of shit online and I have found that frequently
The main reason for that collection is so you can loan it to people
I've noticed that with you you'll invite the neighborhood board children into the house and you'll say guys have added pick a movie house
Here's I think Joe's been in my house twice. Oh stop it. It's true. Stop whining. It was always open
Thor's always open
I ain't interested. No, I'm kidding. The uh, no, I love your house. It's a great house
And you do have a big display does your wife like the display of all the movies like she's not
We haven't discussed
Oh, of course and I got a big vinyl collection, you know, I mean, I don't know if that's how she would have designed the house
But and she let you just she let you put that whole deal dough to display out for and I thought that was very it's
Three -dilded small medium and large
Screwed to the wall in case we want to
Experience but that large one takes up a lot of space the large one is essentially a room deal
I mean, it's a it's a conversation piece, okay?
Candyman, I mean I would imagine everybody has seen this movie at this point
But if you haven't seen it it is a movie about an urban legend of the candy man
Who is a
Monster or specter that will appear if you say his name five times into the mirror and kill you
So that's the basic plot of the movie
I was very disappointed because I thought this movie was going to be a biopic about Sammy Davis Jr
Featuring his hit song the candy man, right and I thought it was the story about Jim Butterfinger the air to the Butterfinger
Dynasty
Yeah, the guy that opened that wrestling camp and then killed the one guy. Yeah, yeah
So open on Virginia Madison who's a
College student that specializes in urban legends because you know
That's a common major at every school that you got a minor dinner
I a minor in urban legends final cut the sequel to urban legends
Will we just watch that the sequel to urban legends starting the right of divine I could remember my guidance counselor saying to me
Why do you want to get into engineering urban legends?
Yeah, it's a ripe job market. Yeah
Anyway, she starts
researching the candy man legend
Starts finding out that some murders have occurred in the neighborhood that matched the candy man's MO being killed with a hook
And then she finds out that she has somehow inadvertently summoned the candy man
And now he needs to shed innocent blood to keep fear about so his legend will continue
That's the basic plot right of the film in the meantime. It's a Dracula style thing. He kind of falls in love
With Virginia Madsen once he wants her to be the candy queen the candy girl as
Bobby Brown used to say but the yes, the
backstory is that he was a slave who was in love with a white woman
They had a baby and that is why they cut off his hand and killed him and a good artist
That's why they cut off his hand and you learn he was supposed to sketch her and wound up doing the nasty, but then years later
When he meets this woman, she's the spitting image of his his paramour. It's a very cool story
It's very well done. It uses Chicago well is the Cabrini green project in Chicago or is it a made -up plan?
Not anymore. So what was it? It was like a
Housing project, okay, all right
Why did why did it go down because candy man killed everybody?
Okay, all right
So one thing right up the bat just from a casting standpoint that I like that they did in this movie is they didn't do the thing like
Like when he sees Virginia Madison
He's like, oh, you're like my long -lost love
But I like that they actually cast two different actors
For the Virginia Madsen and not mad with a mole. Yeah, exactly. I that always annoys me when it's yeah
It's like her with a with braided hair or something and you're like, oh, that's the 1700s or whatever
You know, it's Virginia Madsen related to Michael Madsen. Yeah, it's a sister. Is that right? Yeah, all right. Yeah
Do you like the film overall? I like it very much. I liked it very much
I have not seen the sequels. I mean I saw when I was very little when I was a huge pussy and
The the images of it have stuck with me for my whole life like when I wash it again
I remembered everything about it when he opens the the
Cloak and he's got the ribcage with bees all over it. I mean just fucking horrifying
But yeah, it's a it's a good movie. It's got a great kind of tone and vibe to it
The bees with the ribcage thing is kind of creepy look one of my one of the only
Grypes I've ever had with candy man is he's too good -looking
Okay, it's it's a monster who's not scary looking. He's gorgeous. You're trying to be scary
But you're kind of tugging it on your couch. Yeah, I mean it's like
You know
Denzel slides into my bedroom. I'm not gonna be that freaked out no matter how many bees are coming out of his mouth. No
I'm gonna I'm gonna throw the covers off and say come on in. Yeah, sting me, baby. Sting me
No, I just I yeah, I like would you have sex with Denzel one?
I
Don't say I wouldn't
I don't know. I would maybe I may be now. I don't know I would have
Just for the story imagine if like I came up here tonight and I was that was my lead off. I'd have sex with Wesley Snipes for the story
I mean, you know, I'd have sex with Raj from what's happening for the story
He was talking pure attraction here
So and here's the thing if you've seen the movie you know that the big twist at the end of the movie is
Virginia Madsen's character dies and then she comes back at the very end as the candy woman or you know the new urban legend
They don't name her but she dies in a fire
So when she comes back at the very end of the movie it's Virginia Madsen, but her head is all burned
And that's what bothers me about the Tony Todd look is he dies getting stung to death by bees
And he doesn't have any of the swollen stuff on his face yet for some reason his ribcage is open
Which that doesn't even happen when he's getting killed that like they don't do anything to his ribcage
They cut his hand off the government honey and then he gets stung to death by bees
So I don't are some aspect like the the framing of her
Doesn't really hold water when you really look at it
But I mean the murder the murder frame like okay to me like and then be heading a dog or whatever
It's like why do they believe that this woman did all this stuff, you know, but I
Think it's sort of supposed to have that dream logic that is that is a style of horror movie that I love
I don't like to have to be thinking when I'm scared so I had a good time with it
I don't like to think in general really to be honest with you don't like to think well, I think no
I think logically that the movie makes pretty good sense the one thing I never get about these movies
That that that feature a monster who is somebody who was wronged who comes back is
They're want to hurt people in in a later life as much as they were hurt
I never got that like they did that in lights out where like this little girl was like tortured and treated awfully and instead of her coming back as a benevolent
Spirit as was what you would think would happen you think you'd die and God would be like oh shit kid
You know real fucking shit run down there, you know what I mean instead they come back as like these demons
Yeah, he's a pig
But instead they come back as these demons
I never quite understood that like I feel like if so if the if the world wronged you you would come back and be like
I want to help which is why the the film scholars make a great point
Why is he killing other people that that that live in you know in poor circumstances and stuff why why would he do that?
They also criticize him falling in love with a white woman
I get it because that's who he was in love with when he was alive and he's killed by like a hundred races white
Dude, but then doesn't come back and want to kill race as white dude
There is an issue with that unless they thought at the time that white audience wouldn't embrace it or something
Yeah, I went through it and to see if like well
Maybe he only kills white people he doesn't he kills a black lady. Yeah point does
Which I don't get and I think he kills those some of the gangsters. Yeah, so that doesn't really makes much
sense to me
But still you know again, you can't get to you can't get to nitty -gritty about this stuff
It's still a pretty cool fucking flick. Have you seen the sequels? Yeah, I saw part two. I never saw a day of the dead
I didn't either are you guys
Candyman fans candy fans. All right, it's a good picture
But like did any of you like say oh great. I'll watch it before the pod and realize you can't
Yeah, that's trouble. Yeah, it's troubling. Yeah, the only option was $10 on like Microsoft
But you had to like purchase a robot to get access or something it was like it was too involved for me
There's it's available on voodoo
Okay, which
Voodoo
VUD which I didn't get cuz I'm like I'm not getting another fucking app. Yeah, it's like how many apps you already got to be and to be plus
I got to be I got yeah, I got them all I don't you be are not to be Jesus Christ
Oh my god
Have you seen the second film I've only seen one the second one goes real bad shit. Yeah
It gets way off the rails and I've never watched the third one
Apparently a third when he's running around Marty grow like throwing beads at women to see their tits and stuff like that
It's it's it's I'm kidding guys. That's not what happens. Jesus Christ
Now the second one's erected by Bill Condon who did like Shakespeare in love and shit
Which I found very interesting, but I want to talk for a minute because I want to pull up what else the candy man guy has to oh no wait no
I actually know that he's immortal beloved with Gary Oldman
The director of the rich candy man candy man one was directed by the same guy directed a mortal beloved
Okay, the Beethoven picture. Yes with the big dog and Charles. Yeah, the dog that writes music
Yeah, it's sad when he loses hearing at the end. That's very sad. Yeah, yeah, you ate my sheet music. Bait's hovel
It's not not my piano. Bait's oh, no, Bait's oh, let's do P. I want to do groten as candy man. I
mean
I
Mean what's blood for if not for shedding? Come on
There'll be the stuff of nightmares. I don't do a good groten
Will we will review the the new candy man as well for sure
Let's not make any promises. We could die tonight. Who knows?
We definitely could candy man could kill us
Especially if we're doing these again on the second show we will die. Yeah, I got to listen
How many you were staying for the second show by the way?
Fantastic, yeah, well sounds like some of you are just fucking losers
That are what are you gonna go jerk off somewhere?
Well, that sounds like a great evening. They give them to give them a bad example stay for the second show
Another fuck you can jerk off here. It's very dark
We were talking about B. We herman and that incident earlier actually we were yeah
I'm trying to
Yeah, I
pictured him the jizz hitting the seat him going did I do that? That's oracle
Wow, I didn't like that didn't pee we go no
No, yeah, sorry to have my nerd shit straightened out everybody
Is this something you'd like to share with the rest of us amazing Larry?
There's many great quotes, but I did I do that you know what pee we did do was got any cheese?
No, that's oracle to Joe. Yeah, that's oracle
Did oracle rip back can we herman? I guess so no no little no, but John Mulaney ripped off oracle
John Mulaney is doing a little John Mulaney is oracle. How should I say this read old with homeless people?
That's true the same voice. That's true. I love John. I'm joking. John. I love you
I'm not that sounds like her
Joliel why to as you as you know was a huge asshole to me during a game of beer pong once and I don't like him, but
I don't fucking like him out my
Candyman dice. We were on the plane to Ireland and with with my wife and
She was watching the 510 to Paris or whatever that movie the Clint Eastwood movie 1012 to Yuma no
515 to Paris 9 to 5 starring Dalley Parton
25 or 6 to 4 and they had
They had
The actual actors are the actual people who stopped this
Terrorist attack playing them in the movie so she turns to me halfway through was like god these people are terrible actors
And like yeah, of course, they're not actors. It was a movie lost tons of money is a huge mistake
But she elbows me at one point like look who's playing the teacher in this scene. I look over
Joliel white so Lenny how did Joliel white get an audition for this Clint Eastwood movie?
Is he an oracle fan? I had so many questions. I wouldn't be that surprised if Eastwood was like I like that oracle
What circle up to I honestly I wouldn't be that would you I wouldn't be that surprised. Yeah
There's always those crazy
You know, yeah, you'll see like Olivia's final movie and it's like you know some fucking exploitation horror film
Or you know, it's there's always some way I'm gonna play the Sean Penroll and Mystic River
Is that my daughter's car in there?
right I
Never saw Mystic River you never saw Mystic River now. I thought it was a sequel to Mystic pizza and I was
Very upset when it was and I walked out of the theater. I used to Sean Pen was it in the first one
The trailer was always is that my daughter's
Carried there. That was the end of every trailer of Mystic River. I remember loving it
I don't know if it holds up, but it was a very good intense movie also about trouble would do dice
Probably available on HBO. Can I do dice Mystic River? Sure. Yeah, it's had my fucking daughter's car in there. Dad, who
Thank you a good dice impression is still a good thing. That's true. Oh
All right folks folks that's it for us correct. That's it. Yeah, we should call it
We got another show starting in 40 minutes 10 o 'clock. We will be back
We'll see you next time and we'll see you in hell good night everybody
You